Alex
Beverages
Dad
If you
Just stop
Just like
Take a motorcycle ride
From the east coast of the
Intercontinental
Across the
I use the wrong word
Directions to the Sheraton
I feel like you were tired of it based on you having to do all the heavy lifting I didn't even respond to you
With the same thing
I've been getting a lot of criticism has been levied that you do know a lot about Alex
Just change the introduction of we'd sit around and drink novelty beverage and talk about Alex Jones
Speakers
At this point they're much more recovery
I don't know I think that maybe
2 years ago whenever we started this whole thing up about
Mentally unwell
Perhaps much bigger tolerance for listening to Alex Jones
Right
And he wasn't near almost relation
Wasn't nearly as awful
Present I mean boring
Still listen to his 20s
16 chip
But something has changed
It's not as satisfying to me anyways
Head further as we've got a long I have come to
To the point where we talked about this
Here and there
The bigger revelation
That we learned
From watching him and studying him is that like he is at
Larger
Ecosystem
I'm busy
Really are bigger message
Is it almost everybody who is a
Speaking role
On the right
Is a clone person
They're trying to defraud
That is the game
Symptom of a bigger thing through like the Project Camelot isn't right wing
There's
Yeah there's that end up even more
Talk about other
Very clear hucksters
Alex Jones
Anything like that but I feel like working
I don't I don't I don't feel like it's a holding pattern or anything like that but I feel like we're on the cusp of
Evolving
Sing new
Not not abandoning what we have been
But
I think I can speak for both of us
Episodes about the present
We have
Outgrow
That is
Alex Jones
Maybe intellectual
Leave Alexandra.
Just cuz I still
The easiest person to
Illustrate a lot of these
It's about
To treat this like a job
The continued moving forward one of the things that I need to do
Have some sort of intellectual exercise to it
33 some kind of break
Like challenging
Compelling
It's not true that we talked about
Singer want to go to The Hague
Is that still has this job somewhat turned into a live
Little bit of like a knowledge of like a knowledge fight Starbucks
Really I'm going in and I'm making coffee
Listen to anything
That is
You can do it
This introduction I guess in my way
Really a conversation
What we need to do really have off their meetings or anything
But I do feel the need
And put some listener
Anybody has any idea
What you think
We should become
Sakura
View millennial
You're always talking
Sing about
Filmont you're always talking about all this
You know the older generation of podcasts
They would go to work
Oil in their Cold podcast
8 hours a day
And they would f****** deal with it
God damn Millennials you're ruining the podcast industry
I really could hear Adam Carolla saying that
Yeah
Shut up
We're going to keep going
The showing
Does that happen
Fascism
Exactly
Greg showed up
Thank you
I'm a policy wonk
Refrigerator
They scare me
Michael
Sassy Sister film
Like
That much
You know
Be involved with almost
Incapacitate me
But I realize now.
Probably when I was
5 years old
And this is a weird story about
My dumb family
Thrilled thrilled to hear that
I was playing like a little like a wiffle ball
With my grandfather and I
5 years old
And then we had a based system
That was built around the tree
But and he decided that third base was the
That a giant bee hive
He specifically knew about this in advance this is not an unheard-of thing he was like
I don't even worry about it
I'm running around the base
Like
Like three of them steadily right on the top of my head
However
I learned that at one point in time either knew how to make a poultice
I had heard of a poultice
Or just put some s*** into a Boiling Pot and then put it on my head
Okay
She has exhibited
Zero Down Home Country wisdom
And thank God she was there
Is never happened after
I feel like if I knew how to make poultices
Goodnight
Opportunity
I doubt if
You did and I had pulled
Over that s***
If you like Jack Sprat and his wife
Another weird
World all right
We all know this guy we met him a little bit
From today's episode
It does get weary raising money
Yeah yeah
That is rough
Really
That is the most
Ridiculous thing that you could say write a Z
Rich dumbass f******
Right absolutely most of yours is it like that
Get money
Is getting some money
The Christianity has back.
Anyway
Wearying
And I can't tell you what that job is because this job
By asking you for money but I wish I wish I hadn't said that.
First
Venture into the world of Jim Bakker at
Jim Bakker Show
We went over and episode where a fellow Alex Jones
Steve Quayle
Sort of a concrete bridge
Alex Jones Show
Different gas
Africa Bridge
Benji
Nope
That be great
Mister myxlplyx
Or if I came out like rainbows
He did like a count
Point-counterpoint
Fantasmic
Love it
Amanda
Good parody
It is still kept going
I don't still just yelling at each other
Restart announcement of this guess who
Tammy Sue Bakker
Very special gas and her husband
Now please go to my parents and the host of it
Jim Bakker Show Jim and Lori Bakker
What
They're not answer is their kid
Also
Also co-hosted putting it incredibly strong
She's very silently just at the table
But
So do you know Paula White Cain or Jonathan
Container
I will start really unhappy about this whole
She's she's being out to the kid is being Mauser for the show that
Is there
She's usually
So if I understand correctly
As an adult did not divorce
Name from her parents name forever and ever in perpetuity
She was brought back in like a like return to the dynasty of evil Pedley
Hello.
Weatherby
On the
Food
Got to get that food
Here's where the food every time she open
Only one time show at these here are my parents
So I blow your goddamn
Doesn't talk much
Extensively about him
Is one of the main
Members of the band
Burning
Yeah
You know
Yes
He's not the original keyboard player
But he was the keyboard player
Cleveland Jonathan Cain
Okay play it live
Sit down at the piano and play I don't stop
Arnel Pineda
Because it's like
Saint most of their
I mean
Difference between
He's like a famous guy
Nothing like terms is like recognizability for anything like that most people don't know his name but couldn't pick him out of a lineup
Super rich
And people who know who he is
So you probably to get a lot of stuff at the State Fair
To divorce from $40
That is
Is that they will send $40 to judge
Just about any 40 bucks for
Four tickets to see Journey at this point.
Here's where the food or whatever you got
How do you know Paula White
Kane
Something about there on the
Same playing
She talked to him the whole time
I think
Imagine he probably was tired of the Rockstar life or something like that maybe
Some problem
She's a very strong woman
Like that
Maybe she
Corrected
Lifestyle issues
Call Pat
Like is he he's gone evangelico
That guy
And from what I can tell you still injured
But not for me
This was
This is from 27
Disappearance
Free time
David
Figured out he said he was never going to never going to get married and then we married
3 time
What is at 3 wedding ceremonies a Love Wedding
Oh so you just got married
My prediction is that it's actually Also Paula white-cain
Third husband
3 * 3 * 2
I did not expect
I do not know anything about Paula White
It's not bad
Google contacts
Musica pick up as we go
Cheshire Cat grin
Grateful that you could come by I know your schedules extremely
Almost midnight
So here you are here you're catching
Going somewhere else but you have unbelievable
Energy
Is so good is he gets
Boundless Energy
Surrendered
We try to eat right and exercise and take care of our
Our stuff also
It's really the wife
Could I not come here
Which one of the greatest generals
Play God is everywhere
I've always the countless lies
You take the cats for so many of us in sometime
People forget
Really
This significance in
And who you are spiritually
There.
You paved the path paved the path
The moment she said that I was like in for a you guys are going to f****** do your dance on
Because he paved a really lucrative business out of
Course
Replacement windows
Words for this m*********** right here
Televangelist
Also adherent of the Prosperity Gospel
The idea of
You know you pave the path is the
You made it possible for people like me
Scam millions of dollars from people
Now let's not lie
Evangelicalism has been scamming Millions upon Millions upon Millions
The people almost killed
Trout Creek
That's just that's just like
The revivalist tense of the early 90
F******
It was
Sane
Christian results
But these guys are so f****** good
Singing you got to worry about
Weeping
We got a really
Thought home for me
Go
It's very weird
Suspicious
But pastor of the temperature
Which called Without Walls International Church
Bankruptcy
Remove a major lender Atherton court papers isn't
The temperature
The Foreclosure judgment
The california-based Evangelical Christian Credit Union
29 billion dollars
Hey calls Without Walls filing for chapter 11 bankruptcy protection on March 5th
Litigation tactics
To prevent foreclosure on the web
Columbus Drive
Polk
The time
She was preaching the Prosperity Gospel
Imani church
Mysteriously
When she's living there
Amazing lifestyle
All the prosperity
Self
It's the congregants fault Union to lend her money
Well I mean
But she was let down
By the parishioners
That's why the church would be able to be
She still is doing quite well
Absolutely after that ended up running
Church would she still drunk
Now called
Center in Apopka
Orlando
Which band
Like
Proceeding still
Is it still litigated
Are they still fighting it out
Itchy it if I don't know about that
Like Kaiser so say like what's going on here
More than like
All right we got the sort of traditional backstory of huckster preachers
Wrecking everything
Blake money
Or any of these abusive capitalist Fox just like it says in the Bible
Absolutely so she has that in her in her background
And that only makes it may
Make crystal clear sense
Why is this
Yes sir try to make it up at least
We left you know a lot of people are present love
We were at the Kennedy Center for the
Freedom and I love it because
Grip for a while and
And you just said let me tell you something
As long as I am president
Football games
You can pray
Whoever thought of making Prairie illegal
I am
At private
You praying
It's due any any of any number of God
Just
Just this one just whatever prayer you are saying to Jim Bakker and Paula White's God illegal
Illegal
Well
Paula White
Maybe Trump
Spiritual
Center
She's the one who game
Shiki
She gave the benediction
She gave a really pretty hands on him
Like that
But that's part of it man
This is all like this is
Endemic
The system that we have
Operating right now
The right wing special
Things like this
This version of the right-wing
Is all the holding
Pecan
Everyone's running Khan
And so they work together on these cons
How can I Elevate you while you elevate me falsely
It all it's it's all interconnected Khan people helping each other
Didn't we used to have a system where was every con man from
Yeah
Blockbuster and they are running
Realize that they could Ocean's 11 the world
They started a religion or politics
Whatever
Octopus
Crazy
Problem is that I mean this literally
Paula White
Okay
Like
She was excommunicated from a church
And shall be put to death
As soon as possible ability because he's made many statement
Deny the Nicene Creed
Okay which if you don't know is one of the foundations of Christian dogma
The Apostles Creed
Our foundation that pretty much every branch of Christianity
I understand that and I are
Respect
Your
But
So everything is permitted
Egos
We believe in one God the Father Almighty the maker of heaven and Earth and things visible and invisible
Jesus Christ the son of God the begotten
Father and
Got the Father the only begotten
What is the essence
The father
God of God light of light true God of true God
Begotten not made
I have the same nature of the father and by whom
And this is the Armenian version but
The same as the other version
Which
Essence of the nice team
Comes down
Come to the idea
That Jesus Christ was
The only son of God
He was of the same material
Incredibly important for every branch of Christianity
Pretty much every branch of Christianity that probably a couple exam
Apples that are in the fridge
Jesus without ever like
Hey what Jesus did
Let's not talk about that
Without a plywood Jesus
He was
Multiple times
Paula White
Has made the state
Quote Jesus is not the only begotten son of God
He is the first
Fruit
And things like that
It's sort of like a Urology well gears
Are are we going to the genetic line
No
It comes back on
First fruits is an idea that people for the Prosperity Gospel leave Angelica world
Really abused
They have this especially Paula White she doesn't all the time
First fruits belong to
The God so she can courage is people who watch her shows
To give their fur
Month salary of the year
To the church
Because you give a sacrifice of the first fruit
I'm at Usher's with more plentiful Harvest
For the rest of the year because you know God going to provide for you if you provide
For the church
So even the phrasing that you was using
These times What you talkin about
Jesus wasn't the only son of God he was the first fruit
That was God offering the
First fruit and sacrificed in order to have a more plentiful Harvest later
Which would imply that there are more Sons
God which is 8 Direct
Camper to the Nicene Creed
And
Is part of the heresy
Council of Nicea together to correct
Do all of this stuff like
Play outside Christianity
Even with like even within the Prosperity Gospel which is
It's one thing to lust after money so much
You make it this over about like
You know gives me all this money
You show up on Jim Baker's f****** show
Absolute
So tired
Super important about this about how like
Offensive the Trump would have her give the
To give the prayer
Like Christian folk are like
If he had a Buddhist or Hindu person or a Muslim prayer
That is not a pensive what is offense is someone who believes in a piratical version of Christianity
Presenting themselves as Christians
Yeah it is it away they'd like
To the the faith of the church
No problem
Good good prayer
Pictures of bit of a problem bit of a problem for her
Go bankrupt the churches
Now
Is Trump's favorite preacher
And I don't know why they would see a lot of themselves
Game recognize game the little bit like that
Next clip she talks about how she's been friends with Trump for a really long time I like that
You might not know this
Trump logo
Prayer
I've known our present for 16 years on
Sure we'll get into that that in 2011
Yes sure
The how much
Present love
2011 by this time I've had a
Extended relations
I'm thinking about running
Prescient
He said would you
Bring some men and women of God
Really pray I need to hear from you
Because I really want to hear
What about friends
Hours
Talking about God
Talking about what
Where are nationwide spray
Back in 2011
So the next day called me if he says
What do you think God saying
I don't believe it
Good luck keep praying do we have to make a decision within 24 hours.
Sexiest things with the networking
Difference between Intel screw continued
I have to prayer group
And what he was asking
Was I really
Do what God has
So we should talk a little bit about 2011
Really play around is running for president 2011
Running for presidency was like in Norco
Basement reflection
Decided not
Pursue the office
The presidency
This decision does not come easily or without regret especially when my
Potential
Validated by ranking at the top of the Republican contenders in pools across the country
Night night sweetie
By being front-runner published
Monday by Politico and George Washing
University showed 71% of those surveyed becoming president
Simpler times
Friends
The situation from Jersey Shore
Got it from somebody was there behind-the-scenes information
Trump complained that the woman he was supposed to hand his coat to onstage wasn't hot enough
He demanded the joke supplying is not as rich as he says he were off-limits
Roasters were told to refer to him only as mr. Trump
Hair jokes were also apparently off-limits until 11
Mr. Tire on his way into the punchline the net worth used in the joke became a negotiation
Use a complete
S*******
Alright
Doesn't sound like a man of God this lady I gave my coat to isn't hot enough
But he was talking
Spiritual terms
Bemidji wasn't
Praying that my damn that's possible
Iherb
Interesting Theory
That's possible.
Henry white coat when I walk up there I want a woman
Wearing
God damned if it isn't
Chat what's the show
That's what I was
That's what I was reaching for
Also funny
Snoop Dogg was one of the
Alex Jones screams about Snoop Dogg video
Sugandha Trump's head in the bank like comes out
That is all
Charismatic
I kind of want to
President Obama
Donald Trump at The Correspondents Dinner
That's what motivated him to try and run for president
I don't know if I necessarily believe that 100% but
It's a it's a it's a lot of people seem to believe
Also
I don't know
I just need everybody to pray
Back in 2011 and then we know what he was doing in 2011 this is all bulshit
And let's talk about what he would have done it
In 2011
First of all he was never going to run because he knew Barack Obama was going to f****** win against anybody
He didn't want to be humiliated by losing that election
The reason he had
No I don't think any
No cheating.
Constructed they had probably wasn't nearly as good as
People as well as
Trump
Unboxing
Friends quote
You have people in this country for twenty years they've done a great job they've done wonderfully
They've gone to school they've got good marks their productive
Separate them from the now we're supposed to kick them out of the country I don't believe in that
Now
He's been another six years watching
Crazy broad play Forever
Complete fabric
I mean I bet no way any of this is true
According to every report we've heard from his
Outgoing
It's like he hasn't
That's a element
But then also like
Most of the fundamentals of this are the embellishment of tala evangelist
Yeah I don't think I don't think this is true at all I think it's like
I have my horse
I have my guy
That is my guy
And I'm going to do everything I can to go to the greatest Baxter where were intimately involved and he's been on the right side of things
Because if I have to rest
The fact that I have chosen
To take this card man and believe all these positive things about him
When the evidence is
All to The Conch
In 2011 he didn't even believe in the principal's I'm thrilled you than acting now in terms of what you do with that
With immigrants
What you got to rely on
Is the rules of
The code
She's got the comment coach as long as she's
Helping him out he's going to
Corroboree whatever dumb s*** she says
We prayed for 7 hours probably just didn't
You realize you was in a prayer for a few hours
Televangelist
They're all liars Liars
Crazy
Sao Paulo goes on to talk a little bit
Norbit
Pablo wants
The middle of a story the rest of the story isn't really all that important
Kind of just more about praying
Coming in the middle of the story but
It's really important
She says at the end
Which is one indication that everyone should be like
And then within minutes
He calls in any says
Shrimp
Pray
It's a weaker winner
Where's Melania
Some others were around 7
Family and I just turned
And I'm just giving
Lyman estate wedding
Prophetic declarations and frame
No
Cut hair to put out
I don't know if she explained
She's dead and then they cut it
That she had done it in the first place
Not what you prophesied was like
I believe the Trump
Is going to make everybody clap
But in that broadcast you can't clap
You can't let her say that
I don't know if she ever gives any
DivX on the prophecy
I know that she does talk about one thing I don't know
Here
She talks about how like when she
She came to God
But you was
Are we 80
18 year-old or so
I think I think
Don't Stop Believin
Reisterstown
Also has writing credit on Faithfully it's pretty exciting
But I don't have a different videos put out but
Talking about how
Real rough backstory
Oh yeah she did some drugs
Arsenal Bournemouth
The journey
And she's talking about like
I was living wild we had like
Paraphernalia on the table we would be up late
We'll be up late with our drug paraphernalia
But even though
Even though we were doing drugs dude
Still turn on Christian
Easy
Enjoy that as long as you're doing drugs I said when you're not doing drugs
Sync up music
To this guy
A real name
We called him the Rev
He was a televangelist in Central Missouri
He was very like you did a lot of hand gestures
Stuff like that
And watch him
What is whatever it is she's doing
She had a prosthetic vision
God gave her
Yeah but that was that
She was going to be on all cotton
I'm and that whenever she would speak
People would be saved in miracles happen but if she closed her mouth
All the evils of the world
What happened
Play Just Like A
Certifit
Allegorical explanation for why she doesn't shut up
Alright
Listen
This lady is mouthy
She is goddess
Where is heart attack without
Misogynist
Mystic language
I'm not on board with any of that right
These episodes
Please go for it even feels sad for me trying to edit this stuff together like
Point where I can stop it
Because
Ever stop talking
She just takes little breath
And then goes to New thought
It is just a rambling like it's clearly she's on some
She's probably on adderal
But she's got a long
She's traveling a lot she's got some uppers her husband is MacGyver
Journeys
She knows a guy like
Pressured
Each element students at
So I believe that I have thoroughly called myself out if
The minimal and unfortunate
Like misogyny that I expressed by saying like
This broad earlier
This is set up for the next clip
So I apologize for that if anyone's offended
Some of the ladies especially men to need this book
Really feeling the same with women today
They needed
Obedience
Yes sir yes sir
That's what I've been saying yes sir
If you
God uses me because I say yes all the time
Yeah yeah
Oh my God this hurts busy
This hurts every part of the
The way they speak
I hate it
Like if
If God was
Is real
He brought up
Jim
Look I understand what you're saying
Interested in
As a whole
Red flags whenever condiment
To me like a maybe you just want people to be malleable
Following her every Clan women should really listen to this
Implement
Women really should read
Your book
Because
That's what women don't and some men too but women don't understand obedience I don't know why
The women today
Do you have any lingerie
Tammy Sue
Yeah I mean there's there's something that
You can't get away from that's really there that you're expressing
I'm feeling I'm feeling like telling women what to do
Search the book that she wrote is about Esther
Oh no that's
Blank slate
When she gets to it but
It's important
The cheese like really idolizing
Raise up
Hamsters
Yeah
We'll get to that in a little bit
Paula White wants to tell you
A little bit about what kind of man
Donald Trump is
Good man
And she knows it be
Because of a couple
Really innocuous details about
And 1 best ways that I can describe him as if
He said I'm going to be there at 12
He will be there at
Well I can tell you the story just like Mark Berg net will have Wednesday eat Mark Burnett came in and
And and he says he's pitching it out he's got
Survivor he's pitching the show called
He says to him in a picture didn't
Shakes
He says deal
Brunettes
Dentist office not many
Munson
After that he's told me
Story they call it a big
Can a won the big agency
There's two basically William Morrison
Navigation States
A sister's Asian
This is absolutely
Punctual
Great
Because
I know a lot of contract
But he's not honored
He didn't shake his head
There's a lot of contractors
I know you haven't paid
I think that those are more important though
The handshake of a contract
Didn't physically shake his hand it doesn't count
I understand English
He doesn't know as long as you write it in English
Follow up on your right will translate it back to Marion and then we'll figure it out
From there but for Christ
Play I should have thought about that
Find
Punctuality
This is how I would describe him
He's on time
Cool
Awesome
Fear Talent
There's no there's no equivocating is a sincere talent to make
A guy being on time one time
Story into a like
And this is what
Kind of a great
Right
We should meet at 12
Will meet you at
Can you imagine a man who
Can do something like
I guess I can
Punctuality
That means you're in a tough time coming up with good after
Low scale
Good character traits
No
So yes
He was not warm
He did not particularly enjoy
You kept talking about not wanting to rent to black people
Really really wanted us to shut up when we were praying after our our six
You kept talking about jeans
Jingle I really mention how is everyone blood
Really German
But you know what that's not bad because now he's blaming the Germans for not taking advantage of another Holocaust
Those were in those were in Italy
All over the place
Sort of Hitler
Anyway
Authoritarian leader loves train
Trains are big part of fascism
Seems I wiped
We know one thing
With that has got a lot of Prada
But he likes to push
So the buckets on the last episode
Bucket
Today but probably a 10-minute responsible commercial
For a water bottle that you stop
I know what you're saying
What are we going to do we have all of this food
Let me tell you something
If you send in
$700 we will give you one
Buckets of clothes
Now we will give you a second buckets of clothes
Watertight close
Very weird
Dehydrated clothes
So we got a water bottle commercial on this show
They do a very long commercial for this water bottle
If this is what I would describe the probably the most irresponsible part of it goes
Is anybody else does what they do
I think there's a chance they'll get sick
Into the rainbow
They said
Do not drink the water
After we drank the water from our water boots
And we ate our lunch there
Everything and we drank our water
I think you're kind of being a jackass
Everything that they
Say show me
Dates
Add Japan
They're they're great
The island
An Army's this is the number one bottle
That
View
Why the hell did
You drop that thought about Japan and then why did that guy say I'd hope so
Is that a story about Vermont
Drinking a clean water
I'm guessing if I had to guess I don't know this but I'm just guessing it has to do with Fukushima
That's what I would get I'm guessing that they believe that all water is unclean and radiator
Or something like that
Barback
Even if it's just like a random aside like
I like to imagine it now as more of like whenever
You buy a movie ticket and somebody like enjoy your show and you're like
That doesn't make
Can you sense that
To me it sounds like you just trying to voice I'd hope so whatever
Got weird
I don't know don't do that
Hey you know what I
Specifically hope the Japanese are using
If everybody else
I am ambivalent about but the Jeep
Baker coupons
Amazon water
Normal pollutants of water that you have
You know people who have Brita filters and s*** like that probably very competent on that level
Don't trust it
To take poison
How does your water
Here's
We have
One-story
From a group of known liars and huckster
Interesting
Financial interest
I don't know like
Naked and Afraid
Going to leave your house to find out. Your water can destroy you
Dangerous watch Discovery Channel for a while you'll never drink water again that's just gross
Unless you're in Japan in which case you better drink that water
Drink water
It's like the reverse of that Matthew song
Do drink howold already there's no blood in the water
This
Commercial Interruption Paula wasn't there for
To Paula White
If I was on the show
Have they started doing that water commercial
And the guy
Was there a
It's like there's a lot of smoke on this water
You know what I'm talking about Jonathan Cain
That's deep purple
Smoke on the Water
Every
Throw it in space
Any any any references possible
Lights
If I drink this water
Me and my stomach
Men
I don't need no instructions to know how to drink water
Foreigner
Nevermind
It was not a big hit no instruction
No fuc
Whatever
Alright alright now my classic rock
Brought water filters
Start
What you going to do
I need to ask you
How can the president
Wristband
The hatred in the pressure
Everything he says they turned it around
I can't believe you say this
Especially if you are Christian right now you have a responsibility that Jesus Christ
Against flesh and blood but against principalities against powers
She says principalities about
25 *
Against Darkness against Witness
So you know the enemy and the principalities are going crazy cuz princess
How is Monica
Whole Nations by controlling a person and principalities cannot control this man because he's around
He is a Christian
Beloved prayer and like John said he is fierce
He has an inner strength
Man could withstand in the natural
Responsibility
About to pray for those who are in positions of authority desire god-given responsibility
You got to play the wheel. Could be done for him and through him
This is
The law to give a little bit of most of the show
Taking those little brats and like keeping going
Randomizer
That's
Quadrants
That is all the stores prayer Place Alex prayer with Alex Jones
Madeline Hunter was that Alex
Brian brings relief
Code words it supposedly mean something
Quadrants of the enemy
You know the quadrants.
You've got the elderly you've got one of the four quadrants again
Ugly ones that are important for selling movies
Sheetz marketing
She is so talking and you know the quadrants of the enemy or the markets they we don't tap into that goes
I think that's kind of the subtext of all of this
I think that's
You giving up
She's not even bothering to
To be better at hiding that
She's talking about
TV
Like everything's supposed to be interesting
Thinking about hitting a targeted audience of people who are
Cable and also believe in
Christianity thinks of our enemy
Non-white males
Look look out amongst yourselves in this audience you old
We know the demographic where again they look at you old white people
Choose any demographic you're against guess what
You know how Alex Jones
People put on victimhood as a sort of a suit of armor
Trump is worth
Withstanding a level
No-Man
Set it on fire
Why they don't remember
And that's because they don't work
Scores
She herself had a Lynch Obama apogee on her home and then she's like
Or whether they want to admit it or not
Support them are
Largely of that
And it does them no favors
To admit that
No one ever
Actually been killed
Lego
Not yet
The quadrants that we are
I'll tell you that to kill the president except for the one that killed that one guy who was against slavery
That was the quadrant that we were super fun
Those
You know what it's not
Attack
It's people of God
Jim Bakker
Yes
Pastor Troy
President-trump
It was in
I was
I was going to Warfare physical event being physically
Beatdown I mean I thought I was going to die
That
From one of the Watchers
But
Watching
We're going to destroy you
And they got ahold of one of them
And told him so you tell your dad
He'll never reach again his never
And I had to decide
By the way
I know he's trying to be vague cuz
The story isn't true but you just told that Tammy
Cuz he said your dad
Call Bernardo
One of the many kids that are not his legitimate
Who are like
Hey for real
I'm here
Could you please
He'll never preach again
Never
And I had to decide
And
You know what I've come too far thank you
To turn back
If you don't
America
We're in deep trouble
And this this is
Another chance
I think it's over if we don't
Open right now
Global
Stupid
Ideas
Do you think about
Jim Bakker being threatened
To me what that sounds more like
While he was doing
He had himself a thought occurred
I'd like okay
Well I'm doing
For all the crimes that I could
And I can either like get a job
As like a guy
Have a job
Or I can just keep on doing them crime
But doing better
That's what I'm here
I don't like working at Macy's
I don't I don't want to end up
Some
You know some celebrity celebrity who ends up working at Starbucks
The Walmart greeter
F*** that time for me and God the ride for the money
Right right
But one of the
TW announce
Awesome
W.w. answer
Starbucks now
Really
He would sooner
Start a TV
I mean what is the very least you would sooner go back to jail for the same crimes that he is already committed
Right but you don't have to go to jail
As Long As Trump is in office he is a free man
You will get it
Paula White
About
Easter
Is more important
I don't know if she
Likes a stir as much
Has she hates another character in that story
What job she gets into in this next
And let me tell you something
That side is easy to be replaced
Who is married
Because she did not spell purpose
Cheating and it seems silly
It doesn't matter
She could not be obedient
What was asked of the king because sometimes
Agenda
Until what it was it doesn't matter if you would understand instructions
Young girl actor whose name
Myrtle tree Myrtle trees come from the bottom
What is RAM
It's interesting entire story
Like that but I would like to talk about that
Oh yeah
Who was a character
If I recall correctly
Does appropriately punished or in the
She said no was he was the queen
Aquarius
Persia
Look the issue is
The translation the scholars who study at the understanding of the story is that
Can't get drunk
And he called people
To bring her to dance
Crown
And the understanding
Is that
In front of them
Incredibly inappropriate
Request for
Even if
Use back then
Ain't that culture especially
So she said no
Astro gaming
Once again a great story about dude
This is a bad story about
Look
Ladies ladies
Tell you what I'm telling you about that's why your man walks out
Is that when the king tells you
You do whatever it is
Just like when my husband asked me
Tells me to do because Kim
Did whatever was as women
Do whatever you're told
People people who
Again I just need this
Incredibly clear if the time
In the contacts
Regis Lee inappropriate request for a king
Movie making of a queen
The idea that you
She said no
Like we know why you wanted
They're to Come dance naked
Jamaican friends jealous or something
Any of those motivation
There is no higher purpose to that come
For me and my drunk friend got us
No
He didn't
Did the king
King's Garden
Done
Well she didn't even know
Zoroastrian
But that's not important the important part is that God of a different Faith who made
The douche it the way that he said he's
What was my point I don't know no
I think that I think the idea
Especially in the modern world
Is that
Which he's advocating
4 is
You say yes to this obviously
Inappropriate
Fusing humiliating request from the King
Because then you'll be able to
Stay around
And maybe have some
Influence later
Which makes
Mesick Trump request for her
I'm not saying my mind isn't in the gutter or anything like that
The idea of
She knows yet that she's not saying
You keep your mouth shut
And then you'll have the ear of the king that sort of thing
That mentality if that's the last thing that you
She's getting from vashti
Esther story
Ipiccy
Look Beyond even the heresies that she's guilty of
I think you have a really warped
Dirty
Diversion of Chris
Dangerous
You can run up on him like a b****
The king the other thing to make this point crystal clear
It's all about this idea of obedience
That friend is not a accident on the show
The show
Is so much about
Like
Quizzical obedience obedience
You don't even understand that sort of thing
He's very important to be
People with a sort of
They want to put it
I remember
I remember it all the time
I will get you the payoff of
Man
Pause what's really scary
Jim is about to I think make
Audience brilliant
We were not mentioned Miss Earth
We were just sitting here
We were sent here to take over
We have
Yeah it is
He's not
Hits from the bong
God has raised
Before we get into the rest of this
There's a
Excitement discomfort
Because he knows that
She has the ear of the president and also the
The cheese
One of the big
Megachurch televangelist preachers
Like slumming it here hanging out with Paula White Cain
To her right now
This is like
What I would describe it as like you know on a podcast like
When Jimmy Pardo Paul Reiser
Or something like that we got this guy to come into the show this is very exciting
Jim is really excited to Paula's there
He's he's trying to preach a little bit in order to impress her he's out of the game though
So you standing up now and yelling at the audience
To the walls
In the Bible game
Used during broker
Into that Brokenness
So I said there's a discomfort
I think what was going on
I would guess
Teams videos working
Refused to punctuate his yelling with Applause
Absolutely
How do you even know where the apply side begins or ends
The View have in common
They're all fumbling with their boners and not being able to
Hit the right point exactly
I'm a big fan of the weird growth Scooby-Doo villain ask
Is ghost
Who's bad
LOL I kind of love it because it is one of those things
But like
Everyday you get to see Jim Baker try and pull his skills out you know like this show it's kind of like
I don't know
Former pro ball player going down
Park-like trying to play Pickleball
Well they do a good job or whatever but maybe some guys going to be like
Yes Rocky 5
Metaphor
Good on you
I appreciate it
This reveal will not surprise anybody
Keep talkin about OB
And somebody needs obey God right now because you need to give a lot more than $45
You need to get thousands of dollars in obedience
For the word of God
I pray right now for revelation
Hey man open your eyes according to Ephesians 1:17
The eyes of your understanding might being like that you may know
What is the hope of the riches of the glory of your inheritance
Wow
Putting on a show
How impressive is that
Razor
But that's the payoff of the OBD
You talk about your like
View is obey
Earlier introduced
The concept of $45
Because is the 45th president
Give your give your Easter sale gift to God or whatever
They always do like symbolic meanings
Bible verse that's like
Do you know something like that
Specific example Paula White has been like
Give me $818 in a year on a monthly basis
Black because that adds up to the scripture
It's all magic I don't give a s*** I don't think I don't think that asking people to support you
Creative Endeavors or whatever like that is a negative thing
I think at the waves at this
Sort of
Economy has come up
Supporting artists
Create stuff
All the people who support or show I think
Great
But if I were to come up and try and manipulative trick people into donating to us
It would be as evil and ugly is this on the level
Using to do it like this manipulative
There is a reason to do it like this cuz it works better
Exactly
If you would look if we had a GoFundMe
And I was like
We're going to put out a better show
Like people would not be as driven to that as it as opposed to if we all the sudden we was like if your soul
Anna has cancer
Dan is dying $50,000
Which is this turned out in Ephesians
Thousand-dollar verse
Right
We would get more money then then that strings
Is there a lotion and stuff like that you're able to get them
You override the part of your brain that works
On a rational
You overwhelmed with this
Emotional response
Much as I did the last time
Listen
Jim Bakker where he like
The swelling music
Vinny Appice
Great but like listening to Paula
I kind of understood
Like how you could
Tricked into
Almost a hypnotic state by the way she's
Oh no absolute the quick measure like they're the measure of her speech
Never ends a sentence
It always leads into something else
There's always a reference
Mister something
I like it's all
Ostensibly
Some sort of biblical truth when she's
You just making s*** up
She's trying to run a Non-Stop
See how it works
Take ethics
Morality out of it
I respect it
In the same way that I respect
Alex's
Former gift
Broadcaster I respect this in terms of like I know what you're doing you're trying
How to get people to
To give you money
With the with the
Michelle around the Eminem of Christianity
I want money you trick people in with bright colors
Subpar chocolate
Another like
AT-AT
So similar to if
You've been like
If you been doing stand-up
Persolog
At a certain point
Don't you stop
You stopped seeing
Jokes and you start
People
You start seeing
The sleight of hand
Wright's just the rhythm
This is just
You pause for butt and then
And that that's all you need to do
She is got that
Patter down so good
You can even now even in my
State of mind that I am in now
I can still
Feel that that
That preacher Revival and then all the sudden there's all there
340 year olds going how you save a bit about this
I don't know if I've ever told you
And I pretended to be overwhelmed by the
Lego Baptist Mega
When I was
Like formative years
My parents left
Churches
You are talented workout
So weak
Just another right fields we went to a bunch of places
Define
We ended up at this Baptist
And it was the sort of place where it let me know it wasn't like snakes
Talking Tom
Is there anything like that right boring but
Soft version of that are like adults would be putting their hands up and Fry
Absolutely people like on their knees
Like during the
Some stuff like that overwhelmed by the Spirit fall down an aisle with
Not aggressively not like right where the preacher is touching them
Sort of image in my head of like what it meant
We feel God's presence
And like it really bothered me that I never felt it
Until I went to Camp one year
And it was through the church
We weren't going to this
VSCO
Decision
That I was going to
To force it
One of the songs I don't know what it was but everytime was
Our God is an awesome God He reigns our habitats about from please
What
Yeah Johnson
The great retreat
Whatever the song
Decided I'm doing it
And I like I acted like I was overwhelmed by
But
I ate dawned on me that like as I got down there I didn't feel anything
I thought that doing the
The ACT would force the feeling
Come in and be like all right
You did it
Somehow that would
Introduce the worst feeling I've ever had in my life
Which was
I cannot stand up now
Winesburg Ohio what the f***
I had acted like I was overwhelmed by the spirit led me to come to
I'm surrounded by my peers in the youth
Who are all like oh my God damn
An experience
I didn't want to stand up
For a week
So I had to
I had to sort of play it out and see what I did
Crying
A little bit
Like I put my head down on a chair
That's the retina
People came over and
Like padded
Thank you
I didn't want
It was
So disappointing on so many levels
Well that doesn't work first of all time
Second like
Why did I do that like that I had it like I thought that I could
Could get around got on it
Technicality
And then just like
Well
Yeah I know I bet like
But that
Battery that comes up in my head when
I listen
People Like Us
Yeah
She's trying to get people to like
Overwhelm their limbic system
In order to
To get on her side and
I've been there see this is why I don't want
I will never now anytime I'm at Pike
Repeat the innocent people are
Desperate I think
Maybe not all of them but I'd say the vast majority of them
Or like me
When I was 14
Who really wanted to feel that thing that they saw other people feel and we're willing to play along
In order to
Maybe try and have that experience
Right now whether or not they're the same as me and when they had it they realized
This is all artificial
What am I doing or whether they're like going to tell myself I had a profound experience
Extra
Human Experience
Something
Super spiritual
We want to feel
They want to feel something that's not the normal
Day-to-day Xperia
Really abusive
You tell people that you know how to do it
And you got to give him money
Need to do it
Like it's such a natural impulse the people have
Anythink
From history
Everyone always
You don't want to feel like
Visceral wild animals
But I'm just a biological a
Do you want yet
Profound
Connection
To something bigger
And a lot of people understand
But there is a way
Make money
Off of that
Supposed whole
Finn the Human
Psychic
And I think that's
Maybe one of the most evil
That is ever happy
Pepe borate like they know they can manipulate it and they do
Yeah
It's so it's so f***** up
Alcoholic
What what else is that
Tumi
If you can
Experienced that feeling by
Meditation
If you can experience that feeling by going
Wisconsin
If you can feel it
I have no problem with the The NeverEnding
PS4
Human transcendence
In a
I have a problem with
The
Commodification
Manipulation
You know I don't even have a problem with that
I think I have a problem with you guys today that it is
If we include like going to the gym
Sometimes being able to be transcended
But
I got the same
Is the gym doesn't Market itself as a sump
For your soul
Really really f***** up kid
This is a f*****-up for mcritchie
Like this is all f*** this whole f****** thing
I don't know I don't know
I guess my problem is whenever people try and tell you
Because look if you're going for a f****** spiritual experience
Human history has shown us that
You can find one
I am fine with you trying all of
My problem comes when you deal with these
Who said that
The only way
You can have one of
The other ones who have aren't real don't have one
Not only are you
Not having a
A spiritual experience
Your work
You're the worst
You're worse off
For not even
Well that's part and parcel of the Prosperity Gospel
You give this
Seed of the money
How many grows into more money coming back for you and there's a built-in trapdoor
Doesn't work and if you didn't
Want it hard enough
You didn't love God enough you didn't follow
I didn't obey enough
Any preacher
Can just
Any preacher like these people
Around that that that sort of thing
There's it there's a built-in
Excuse to blame the person who's the victim of the
I have no words
For how much I hate
It's
I guess the best word for it is pray
They love
Turning people into prey
Because they are
AR
Editor
President
So in this next
Jordan
As early as you
Really.
Hiding the fact
She's talking about like
Demographic stuff the quadrant
TV terms
Stuff like that
She might as well be asking what our Sunday ratings next clip was
Pretty you like
Business
This is weird
We're from the same tribe system really well
Listen I know how to do
I would like to buy a TV
Are trying to be popular we are being purposefully this run
And deliverance is coming
You be the carrier of it
Then destruction will come to you and your father
Enlargement instructions
For real why haven't you picked up my goddamn show yet
We are bringing God's
See you at 4 p.m. 3 p.m. central
1 p.m.
Grinch meme for the money that
Comes back when you play
Plant those seeds
Very directly about the idea of like
Are you going to get on board
She started that f******
Sentence by saying we can do this in our sleep
We know what to do
Manipulate
Pulling her dick out on errands being like
I know what to do I don't give a s*** about you guys
You're so stupid
It was still stupid look at you
You dumb sheep
I can manipulate you with my eyes blindsighted
It's crazy
Another level
Which
Only only
Titan virus
It's not that hard to convey
Is really hard to
And then have them believe you anyway
Some people just like the thrill of the hunt
She's like someone at their hunting boar with a knife
Yeah yeah she's like open her she's she's
It's playing on New Game Plus
Barely able to do a straight Swan Dive without a splash
Backflips
Terms and all that s*** yes
She's nailing it
She's the Rodney Dangerfield in back to
School
So it is excellent
Mantis
Made me so f******
This made me feel so weird
So there's a relic
Showing up on the show Relic
They don't call it that but that's how Jim is acting
So f***** up but then at the end of this clip we get something
That is very familiar to our podcast
And I would say I
This is a platform
But the platform
I'm against abortion
The platform is also an album
The
He wants to
The Johnson Amendment
I felt like
Evanston open I can't describe this moment
Grayson in this for probably two of the
I think fully understand
Yes sir
Brown
And then he reached over
Play
What a major moment
I want to get
I want
You got to get back.
$45 to help us stay on the air
We need support
Jim Bakker
After almost coming in his pants about a pen
That's outrageous
That
Next level
Rootin for climate change
I have now given up entirely on Humanity
There is no point to any of this
Those people were all going Apes
Kit for a pen
He turned
Pain
Being signed for f******
Can whatever into an ad pivot
Why do we wire really
But do we even meet us
This pan is what happened
Good
Stop and died
If Obama Henry a f****** pain
This is a f****** b****
He's like this the pain that I'm used to
Define NACA
That's cool
The Relic
Shroud of Turin
Now I'm Anthony big I would not fixed up man I could not go to worship that pain
Dream now
Adjust
Going to one of these
He shows
And just losing my s***
I want to go. Weaker at the World Cup like the Borg
Ripping their variada. Everything apart
It would not work
Oh my God I would have one of these episodes that I watched it like people get paid to come a train
Disrupt his show
So he's aware
You got security 18 year olds
Probably just
Alright Google.
Cuz you working
So yeah man
Let's go home
Beer
So you talk about the Johnson Amendment that's worth
Executive order
Loosening
And the Johnson Amendment doesn't know I have to do with churches at barter their 501
Status
They can't advocates for or opposition
Public office
That's the major part that they really hate
Right through
It's almost like that part
Is trying to keep them
Procreate
If your entire religion is built around the concept of a theocracy
That's one part of it but it was put for a 1950
Before
If you think about what was going on
In 1950
You had a lot of
WWII
Are a lot of
Christian
Organization
Happy quotes
2 equal rights
I can't think of any of it with three
They said we're not in
Into
Yep that's it
You have you had like sort of agitating
Groups
Hiding under the auspices of
Of Christianity
And I think
I think a large portion
Lynch
Things that the Johnson Amendment
Is capable of
What is assertive
Split up
That
And I don't
Think that
To the place for political messages
But if you think it is
I think we have any fundamental disagreement about what faith is
What are country
The case for a long time
Pretty hard how does the heart sad
That was
Really
Yeah
Because really seem so stoked about it and then
Immediately after the ad pivot
All of the all of the pre-show screening
Showed up in my head of them being like
Okay we want you out here do you have any
Gibberellic
I've got I've actually got this pain that Trump gave me in the like
Phuc yea
We are going to turn that into a set-piece lie about it being a stripper
Stand up for this
You want $45
Time is now
We need you to really incompetent
$45
If you thought that $45 wasn't worth it let me show you a pic
Great pain
We have another
Moment
This one more unsettling the first
You're the greatest woman preacher in the world
I don't want embarrass you but it matters you are and what you're sitting here
Yes sir yes sir
Broke
What you going to do
Are you going to curl up
Come on
Because you made a mistake
Trite
Because
Are you listening to me
Florence
Also wait what about
About about about
You should ask her about don't do that
What is this
Price
Games
Yeah
Enjoy your cross
The only people that make me want to take the things from them that they are afraid of me taking away from them
And you are
Facilitating the continuation of the
The circle
No I don't want to take your cross away
You will now I want to take away your making me want to take
Hear you now touched
He's actually talking about and why this has nothing to do with religion
The reason that you want to take his cross away and I think even though you don't care about Christianity and neither do I
Is because
He's not
Church
Like
The reason to anyone
Would want to be like hey you need to shut down
Because
The message of God or anything like that myself
Open to ideas of spirituality
Right but I have no no love lost between me and Christian Church
But at the same time I'm super thrilled I think they should exist
I same as all Muslim churches Buddhist temples
All of it across-the-board Jewish synagogues
I could name them all
Shinto hot
I don't know I just do the Point Community baseball team
That's the same s*** to me but
It isn't for a lot of pee
The reason the gym is so much like people want to tear down our crosses and want to shut us down
Is because he's keenly aware that he's calling
Keno's
Accusation
Things that come at him or legal
They are like
You are committing
Unethical business practice
Here
Crazy what you're doing
Has nothing to do with
God
It has to do with you
Using got the message
Spell your b******* buckets
To be like
We are under attack because we love God so much
Because I'm at frames the argument for anybody who
This very measured reasonable
Complained
You are I would have
Has about him
And that's not respect
You say I want to tear down
Now it becomes
You are the embodiment
Exactly what he is lying about existence
It doesn't matter
Of course not. I do it so I might have
Will f****** take your goddamn cross away you piece of s*** lying
Go fuc yourself
I want to sit on it
Grandparents
I think Jim Baker's whole operation
This whole show would just be really funny
If there was just transparency about it
I think that the real crime is the
The sleight-of-hand stuff about like what were using the money for
Stuff about
BB abusive
Marketing tactic
And s*** like that the rest of it
Is just like
Look
There are 20
Problems
In the world
Someone going to a dump
If there was just a
Opening of those
Those
Release documents
I think
He could that he could
Escape
Exist
It would be an amazing
Adult film adult Adult Swim show
Like if we didn't have so many
F******
A televangelist shows on at 2 and at 2 a.m. in the morning or whatever it is
Adult Swim would have won
It would be you
Are the exact same thing like this is a parody of itself
Staind
Jim Bakker is a person who
Was it hard time
Time for fraud
Because of this
Exact same behavior
The few things and now came back
Story
It's like if someone did something bad went to prison for it got out realize all right now I know the LIE
It doesn't
It look I went to prison for selling I went to prison for sale
Selling heroin
But
In prison
I got my pharmacology
The great and now I sell opioids
2dr completely different thing there's no difference whatsoever
It's more I went to prison
Because
Someone snitched on me for selling heroin
I'm Solo or whatever it is
It's cuz it's it's not like he got clean
Eagle
What are you doing is still the same fraud
It's not like
Just because you didn't create a hotel this time
30 / book
And she like that do they got him on the first time
That doesn't mean that there's any less
Like this
Is marketing
And that's why it is
Adult Swim
In terms of
It's almost
It's almost Beyond The Pale
What you think is like
This is vicious
Is not this is
This is
To mate like
That camp
B-real that's a lie that she tells him her know that he tells her
Bunch of pictures of her
I don't know
What the f***
Televangelism
Show that was on air that reached Mara Lago
He would watch her
You loved her
Melt
Now flood
This is the first time I've really believed that God was right whenever he got rid of
He nailed it
You just let the wrong family like one time
And that was when he killed everybody in that but Noah live like there was probably a guy allowed bees on
Pollination
Got to make drone
We would
God could not
Rather be fine with that
If there's one thing I know about the Bible it says that God can't make drone other me and Paul are on the same page
Heritage
Depart
Music to make drones is not directly a heresy again
The most foundational
Doctrine
Christianity
So I want better footing than her
It's crazy
It's legitimately crazy
Rebukes the Nicene Creed
YouTube you straight up to
I will.
Denying then
Team Creed
If you donate 8100
18000 $1000000
Whatever it is
I'll believe in
Anything for as much
I will believe in anything for money also in case you're curious the Apostles Creed
Is the
Declaration
And the reality of
All right also a really good song by
Navigate to you know how
You are just a little bit
Let's talk about how she does prophecy
Cilic
She does. She likes to do proper
Here's the thing that she had
Did I think
Is Ludacris
It's 2018
You know we don't do prophecies
When you put yourself
Position of ibuprofen
Shaky foundations
I think most Mainline churches
You at home
It's at least narcissistic most churches are like
Look we got a lot going on with our bulshit as it is
Concrete
Man
I didn't mean anything and you could just throw whatever you want
A little a little iffy
You don't you don't give out like I'm going to prophesy this because it's not going to come true and look
I'm sure Christians Christians believe
A lot of what they believe and that's fine
But even Christians alike
Do don't
Don't put our names prophecy
We're not going to you know it we know we're not telling the real truth
It's not the point
The point isn't that were telling the truth
The point is that we're like feeling it you know
Look okay on the sun and yeah so somebody prophesied that we did
Felt like we didn't
Well here's one of the things that's really interesting is that like
In terms of
This time is white Paula White
Her prophecy that she talks about with her
Child
Joe she would prefer.
Refer to
Jesus
If there's anything that we've heard so far it's that you would prefer to be her husband
I'd make sure that everybody knows that
Her choices are absolutely
I don't even like the color mrs. King
Sup Niger
That she has of her first like old-time proper
Kathy is just as vague idea of like I'm going to be listened to and if I stopped
I will be hurt
Because that's just a good origin
Story
Begrudge that that's
Avenger but I'm fine
Adjust counterfactual
Real things that did happen
What year is one that you gives
About what
Which to me is a shity prophecy because
Great alternate Earth
What are we doing like this is a Multiverse Marvel
Comic Twin Towers wood
F***
I was made
Religious liberty
For oppression
In five years
But only understood
Everybody's like delightful counterfactual prediction that is like hat
Here's a consequent I imagined for it to scare you about
Why we need to support Trump because
He is in his avoiding
The church is becoming an underground Church
F*** all the majority religion that runs his inside
Country five years
I think they
The reality is that if
On a national level
Conservative
Republicans
Not done
Traditionally all that well in the last
30 years or so
Last 50 years
Particularly
They've not won a ton of Alexa
Especially ones that didn't involve George W bush
He's bad or Nixon
Which is why they learned how to cheat better
Speaking of George W bush
Yeah what
He's Express
Is actually probably an accurate prop
But has nothing to do with
Church Going Underground
Eventually
If people
Keep
You know making liberal progress
Archon is not going to be allowed
At a certain point people are going to get sick of this
The words going to get out on us and do our livelihoods are going to be
Completely bought
If people
To the point
Where
Fear-mongering bulshit
Doesn't really make sense
Even to them
Weird
We are so
We need to make sure it was on the side of the coke billionaires in the like
Is because if people's lives aren't
They're not going to go in like we get back to the
Now I can't
Remember
Right if you have all of those
Bill
Then you are not afraid of
Somebody from another country is coming to take my job
Do you know why I'm not afraid of that
Because I have my needs met and I'm comfortable in what I'm doing
Rite Aid of Emigrant
Then I'm really not going to be picked
Picked up by the
The comment
Because I don't have that I don't have that
Play on
I don't have that imaginary people are offering to fill for me
Of course all of these things are jumping in with that because
Cuz they need
Base level of misery
Otherwise they're not going to be 6
But I also don't
Thank
FedEx
Most really
I understand
It's very easy and the numbers are real
Interval especially Evangelical
But I also think that most of
Evangelico Cristiano
The sway of really talk
Sticker version of
I don't think Christianity as a whole is bad at
Very smart Christians
Exist
Very scholarly Christian to
Write essays about how Paula White is a heretic
Things right that what we've done is the world we're like
Anti-intellectualism his
Metastasize to
Include
Do you have these con men who are like rebuking
The very idea of knowing
Yeah probably doesn't like I don't want to get briefed about stuff I don't give a s*** by impulses or
Are perfect
Distrust
I like Politics as a
Things like
Take politics out of
Show me dirty game diplomacy
Or international relations
No needs to study that I know better
Because of my great jeans
If someone like Paula White
I'm probably have much more influence
Jim Bakker
Seminary
She's not she hasn't
What
So she has
Accreditation
Christianity
She comes in
With a heretic aversion
Of a misunderstanding of what
About
Are you have just like
You know what you
Super charismatic
Confunden like
Let's let this become Domino
But there are
Tons of her
Around
Idiotic world
If that's what bums
Because I think a lot of people who are
Beaten this is me going back to my
Route but like
This is something that I care about a lot
I know a lot of really
Good Christian
June people are my parents are
Devout
Christian
Folk are also they are
The people that you are also very liberal there
Progressive is s*** right there
Very understand
Like the ideas of
Being
Adaptable
Metaphorical on Tumblr
Have to be beholding
3 dumb ideas about
Like
I watched a video where they were talking about like
Paula White was on another show they were talking about
Why the Prosperity Gospel is the
The truth
I miss because when Adam
Was sent out of the Garden of Eden
It was about
The sweat of his brow
He would work
It would mean nothing
You'd have all this work it would never come to
The middle it would never
It would never be made right
Jesus
Had the crown of thorn
On his head
And humiliated him
The bled from the Broward it was the parallel
The
Poverty
Was thrown on Adam
And so there was a metaphor of economic
Redemption that I'm bringing to you
Jesus
Makes the least sense of
Anything
Ever heard
My tire locks
Just because the idea of the brow the word brow
Farming is hard and then the other one is like
Getting murdered as
The literalness
Scriptures
And I think a lot of Christian
Get a really bad shape
And I know that I have now abandon
I desire to defend Republican
No I I I I still think I still think I hold out hope and I believe that there are a lot of grapes
You're you're talking to me
Is f******
Nuts
All of the s*** that she is
They would totally say
Listen to this episode
If everybody in my family listen to this episode
I swear to God they wouldn't even hear the ad paper
Like it would just like
Like some part of their brains which is
Now what you saying
Is good truth
Prayer is good
Believe that I don't like
I get it
You're just missing the additive apart you realize that
Your
Ripped
Because you're focusing on
Lucy the skeleton of what's supporting that meat on the animal part of it is just like
My family is
They're wonderful beautiful
I'm not going to
I'm not going to paint my family is something awful like
They will give you a
No need to whatever your face is for like an old person is
Sure but
If if
You can't
Go back on it to them
It's almost like
Committed you know like right in their life
Well we've already put all of our chips
Why would we stop now
A pic because birthday
It's money protecting Bad Bunny artist
Because I hate cuz I worked here 10 years and also
I-4 so many of these people even if my parents
Even if my mom and dad
Who been with this church
Even if they know
It's b*******
If they leave it
Now they don't have any
That stuff now what
You got nothing
Let all of that but I'm really not about
Yeah it's a Prosperity Gospel but I don't really worry about
Rivermark
I'm just
I'm just doing that for the for the Godlike
Of course
I get it
Itsjustjord
F******
You're ruining it
DePaul are people like a gym
Much deeper
Things that they want
They have
Issues
They care about
That are not
About being religiously
Like that
The reason
Jim almost
Jesus on himself with that tent
Stripping of the John's
What's an amendment
Is because when he cares about
Is using
The church
But he has
In a political way
Because
Open up
So many more vistas of fundraiser
There's so many more things
Able to
To do in a tax-free environment
If you able to not have the
IRS
Breathing
Like those sorts of things with
So
Thank God for
The crimes that I committed
For legal now
Dialect
Trump there's so many benefits
Ludacris
Mi jobs
Had a
Something
Happened to whatever
Andy
Corporate
Suck pads
What are you do
Discreet
My last day working my old office
Came in a cup of coffee shop
It's one of the only people I
Actually like
Interacting with I worked at a roller I had to
Collect overdue amount
From people who
You'd always be
Super busy
It always come into the office
About once a month or so with a check
Checkbook and be like yeah
A cup
Really
Cool and fun
Very exciting to see trash
No cuz he wasn't it
Around my last day working
My second
Is that coffee shop
I still have it I thought it was really
I thought it was really sweet
Sweet very nice
Aw
Where is iff
Like Donald Trump
Signed bill with it
And I know it doesn't mean anything
What is a Sentimental artifact of my time or whatever
I respect that more than
Jim Bakker being like
I've waited my whole life for this then
That's very different
That is very good talk
Nicholas gets a historical revision
A reminder by American
What's the purpose of America
What was the purpose for us
Forefathers came over
Which they did not last night
Lighthouse
Murdered all of the people
What's up blood everyone restaurant
The sacrament
Nevada side I don't
This will be a Christian weigh station on the way to other places
Ivan I think that what we have there
More importantly whether or not that
Blatant
Historical revisionism
Them or not
There is
Absolutely
Declaration
Yep we want this to be and we believe that
It was supposed to be
I need to know.
Because of these
Demon flow
Who are you and I
I mean
Because
Here's what you're doing
I mean
Your
Taking everything that Humanity has ever done
Going like
No that doesn't
And that really doesn't support by our
So I'm going to make my own up
Human history
Supports what I want to do
So let's just make that the real
Okay
What God makes perfect
What if I just convinced enough
People that realities
To do
Good at it
Private conversation I feel like I keep having this conversation more and more
Recently than I think I ever had
At before which
She's just like
What we've always
Talked about witches like
A conversation doesn't happen until there's an agreement of
Terms and agreement of definition
Classic what is
When you say table
Are we talkin about table
And we are no longer doing that
You can't happen with
There is a conversation to be had with somebody who believes
That the founding fathers wanted a Christian
Percy what is your you believe that guy
What are you saying about well here's a good concrete example
If you look at
The reality of
Korea
Bob made
Has to be one of the most
Hilarious
They are rubbing their asses at our faces
And I think it's a
But we get back to this idea of
The beginning of a conversation
Is the definition of
Terms
And you have
Denuclearization
Is being a term
That has been agreed on
In this
Statements
Trump
Denuclearization
Is a one-sided
Saying where he gives up all of his nukes
And submit
Where is for
Jim the term denuclearization
Is a
The Unova takamori
Unilateral thing where is South Korea gives up their weapons
The entire Peninsula big
The weaponized
Is the United States
Scales back
Involvement
And stuff like that
Come to an agreement
We believe in
But if it means accent
Then you don't have any
It's not real
Converse
The conversation
Keep having its
The reason why bad
Actors like
Alex Jones
Commentators on
Such a big problem
They don't have a consent
And that is because
Can't have the conversation
On like
Level plane
Because weight doesn't make any sense because when you nail things down people can't
Getaround
You can't be like
What what do you believe
Leaving
Make it hard Declaration of what you believe
Well and this is how this is how everybody
Absolutely and it's something that we all
I think it's one of the big things
As far as growing it's like
Getting over this
Is when you are talking to some
When you're having an argument
And they start
To pin you down
You start
To feel it though
Like there's a certain point where you start to feel like
I might
I might be wrong
And instead of
What like this
Humanity like 95% of us
Instead of saying like
Oh no that
Okay tell me more about that
You're like
Well
Bright
And Dismount fast exact
No I wasn't staying.
And believing the same s*** that you
For a brief stint
You have that chance U
You have that moment of like
Maybe I could be wrong
And I could say I'm wrong
And then I could
Two things that I do and
Robbie the first thing is
Universal
Assassin
Then the second thing is
Either
Did this conversation
Yeah
If you're wrong about something you're wrong about
Worst thing in the world
Fun things that
I have experience with this
With our old
Eventually
You're right
I said was dumb because it was based on information that I didn't really have
And you have that
Like your reason
Growth
Excited to do this talk about
Boring for Alec
Can you sell this stuff
For me it's really exciting because I
Like
Not being wrong
And when I'm wrong
That's just a super exciting opportunity to be wrong later
You know
Luggage
Great I like
Learning ship
And so often like what these
You could
Tell them
You couldn't get any you you could rhetorically have an
Where they're like
But maybe your butt and you just keep him down just like
Stay in the pocket
This is what we're talking about
This is
You are staying right here with me until you and I agree that this is
Talking about we are not
Talking but this is why philosophers don't go on Infowars
This is why people who are actual
Really good at like God
Conversation
Not in that sense don't go on these shows
Because
Stupid
Think that's also one of the problem
Is that why do these philosophers today
I'm sorry about it
At regard
No I know I understood the impliedly
You're making butter
The same time
Just on its face
No
Why won't it like it is a problem that smarter people don't go on these shows
Yes no that's not what I'm talking about and yes it is a problem
Do you know
This will never get better
If these worlds
What it is is this
Is is a
Infected tooth
Jim Bakker
Alex Jones is another insect
It's not going to get better in
Until you put
Medication
Root canal
Root canal is probably
Smart people showing up and embarrassing them on their own shadow or something like that
B ukulele
Right but I think that
Where
One of the Big Dipper
Connect happen
And also as we've seen
Like dr.
So people go on and they do a root canal and the behavior of eating candy all night happens again and that you have
Have another
It is
DeWitt the way that you
You put it is what trade
Triggered it for me
When you said
Well it's that people who are good at this
This kind of thing don't go on there
And that's the way people viewed
You're not
You're not right
You're just
Better at arguing
It's really good at arguing
Right but not really but that's the way that people get out of being in that conversation with
I've had this happen to me plenty
Tons of them but they're just
Right
But if I never have it
But if their argument
Is losing
They will say it is not because
Has their argument
Or is because their argument
Doesn't make any
The states because
You're just better at arguing
Oh
Who is Dominic
Whether or not you
He is making
So many people British
Fears about sending their kids to play
Steve Angelica
This is like
You're going to think
Did they have knowledge that
Is there just tricking you with better argh
Because we don't know how to
God says don't argue or sneaky highfalutin City learning Toledo
Bedford
It is about a
Quality of argument
Being
As opposed to
Affect
The end of the day
I really don't
Ticket matters
Because all these things that we're
Pic-a-lilli cancer
What about these
Issues
We've brought up here
Sexualism
Picture of argumentation
Agreement
These are two things
Things that are really important having a
Matter with you
Because there's one thing that this is about
You
$45
FedEx.
Close to 40
Do they even for a
Single f******
Second
About that
Doesn't matter
Threat
Spiritually and naturally
It's their spiritual assassin
But you know what I did John and I grabbed each other the other night
We put our speed and oil
We started taking communion like this prophetic
We took the mountain.
Who does the song
Because you said it would be for the preservation of our life
Reservations
Children's wheel
You need to get thousands of dollars and obedience
For the word of the Lord that is coming because it's going to preserve you and your family
How I pray
I didn't pray tell God will you just keep
Crazy
No
Just
Describe your trying to make the metaphorical literal
She just described
Her and her husband
Who controls Oliver refuses to allow her to
South of course she is
Subservient to him in every apostle
They were told by God
To sew somebody
Into place
Known for their children
You are selling your misspelling the word
Pwn20wnd
Couch
Throwing Steve
This is just the basics
No this is
The basis of
Prosperity Gospel
We talked about this over and over again
What I hear
Where is
I'm going to lie
That have communion
That
They took a bath together and drink
Is wonderful
But the idea of her selling this
Either whatever what she's talking about is I made
And now I'm trying
Reply
You need to do the same thing but with
Jamaican investment in me
No course
I bet I do bet they have like a safe
Dewey's
Detox
Never exist without a grain
Paranoia somewhere
Was a metaphor that was also a very real story
About discussion that they had
Bio-Oil on there
Something I mean like
For real that does sound like her dramatizing a
Like we took a foot bath
It's not like
It's not like God told us to
Giveaway
Recognizable amount of our Fortune
Not that
I don't believe that for a hot second
But she wants to fight it is in order to make it
Like you have to go
Give more is that
Like again
For all of our intent
And our pretenses of
So trying to have a real conversation
In about what these people are up to
It always boils down to
Do this.
Yeah always boils down over and over $45
10%
Of everything
Because I have this magic
And I primed with our God
King
Who is the
Amanda
Sort of behavior
Down the road
A growth
Really feel like
America was founded on lyca
Man there was something about
I remember when America was
Started
They were like
Songs off of empire real
Oh yeah
You know everyone knows Reelin in the Years
S*** like that but
Uncle King
Kings
Battle simulator album
But
Cancel
We seen
A good King Richard
Right raise up
Your Glass
Mark Wahlberg
Classic
Three Kings
Steely Dan's version
Kings was really all about the
Fall of Richard Nixon
JFK
So is the movie Three Kings
Wow
Absolutely
I got to go
I want to talk more about Steve
787 Raptors up band midnight Cruiser off at
Turning into a middle-aged man in front of
I like that now my new thing is going to be like musically
Last time I feel like
20 year old girls
Cornered by a man talking about Steely Dan which is not an uncommon feeling
I already said midnight Cruiser
I can't think of a third song
It's great and Hulu good time
Let me get it
The parallels are very clear in
Work is more important than
I need the actual content
Betrayed
These are two things are very relevant to our show even
Alex Jones
If you like our showed want to hear more of us
Talking Ed nauseam about out
Then go and find that stuff over at knowledge fight.com
You can follow us on Twitter
Support the show Japan
Leave a review
Any of that
Shityoucanbuy do it
You can put us on message boards
Lot of fun
And
It is your turn
No lettering
What time there was a cornucopia
Do you have
Narrowed it down
To a few key players
I will
Please
I'm certain
Of who
I need to
Given the honors at the end of this episode
Television
Member of
Journey
A lot of a very credible musician
Some of them have
I don't know
Probably speaking
I have no idea what their life is like but from the
Do you know so I decided to
Play sucks
Eden come up on this episode
Involved
Neal Schon
Journey
Deal Sean go f*** yourself
Holding
Alex