Alex
Beverages
We had
Pretty much exhausted this bit beyond
This version of the B last episode well you know way too much about Alex
I also know way too much about Alex degrees of where our lives
You know a little bit
I found it very juicy business
I know a little bit more about Alex Jones knows a little bit
We both made up our minds
2 layers
You so much to Christopher
Christopher Robin
He's our new sponsor very excited about hanging out
I was at 7
Christopher Robin
Although
I wasn't allowed to play Christopher Robin
Father with the best of them
Let's get into
Play me where you at
To start things off with an out-of-context drop
Singer Flora
In the video
Finger Soros
Best additive of hours
F************* people only for the first few minutes
Harold buddy our good friend
Living his best life Rodger Stone get
Without being named in an indictment
Of 12 Russians to hack
Soros
The entities the DNC leak
Guccifer
To point out
Rodger Stone was forced to go and embarrass himself on television
You talking about
My favorite part
You released
Messages
Completely a one-to-one match with what is later in the day I am say there's probably
You were saying that Rodger was thrown I think it was a little bit but I've realized it wouldn't
Through him the most
Is the Chris Cuomo
Cuz big catchphrases
Before I could
To take the power out
What Chris Cuomo said
I know I know they can indict a ham sandwich
And I think Rogers
F*** are you son-of-a-b**** before
The first thing we should say
I know you're going to try and cut me out
And then they're going to be like I don't know what to do
You know what he's like
Rodger good
Interview with Rodger Stone
Version
Because he's always
Against Alex Jones
He's up in that world or just yell at people
Racially charged
He called Don Lemon a mediocre negro
At least
Remember the specifics
He could be slippery in a way that he's baiting you make
Trying to make you angry
We can't really play that game it doesn't ruin
Playing
Whatever it is
Winamax or something like that
Alright
Rodger Stone
Is no competition whatsoever
Rockin Jump
This is level I'm out of practice with children
Troy
In the morning in the evening and nobody
Live from one sentence
Myself and everybody be like
Yeah I don't know that's the smarter thing to do
I like I like realizing the baby his muscles
Proceed more than we realized
Well
This is interesting
Because
When we started the show is beginning
We largely focused on going back
The beginning of
I want to do all that much of us looking is looking at 26
Because if you came
Fairly pointless once we realized
The transition for Alex
Trump seems like it wasn't all that important
I realized
You look at that indict
I thought maybe it would be interesting to go to
The exact date after Rodger
Definitely is in contact with Russian hacker
Okay see what happened on Infowars see if there's anything
Something that is very interesting to me
Is it there is a YouTube channel that I largely get most of my episode
It's from the guy
Why the channel on YouTube
Clearly in
With Alex Jones
Permission to post by the hour up to
There's a chunk of
Alex's first our second videos
You have any commercial free
Empire show after
Everyday I don't think it's one guy I don't understand
How I never thought to ask like
If he is just reposting it Alex Jones videos
All of the Special Report
Aeropostale
Like the War Room
Mike Adams for the Sunday Show Now who cares
How's my episodes
Search for August
16th 26
Nothing
What are the only episodes
Epson does not have on his
You can find August 15th
You can find August 7th
It interesting that this episode is not that one specific
Explanation
Entirely possible baby was sick
Maybe you know I don't know we had an episode go missing
Possibly you know there is a benign
Malaysian that I would accept
Although it looks very sketchy
Now that's
Is that because
August
Rodger Stone was in contact with
Alright by the time Alex is on here
But on the 16th
August 16th
Context clues
Going around
You're like
Grin is delightful
Yeah probably
Dan has got something big coming up
But first let's deal with some small stuff
As we know it
Mostly yellow
Beers
Scared
Bad stuff
Rashad on Saturday
Shocker
Ewan Mitchell
They're own words
Rid of white people
They're selling this to the ninety-plus percent of the planet
This is a reverse colonialism Conquering the West
Populations are being used as cannon fodder
2008 Copenhagen
Double
One point below.
Is on the third world
So
It doesn't mean anything cuz easytouch remember the details of this
Years later
Who did on the third world
That's not that's not at all
He's using numbers where they don't belong
Copenhagen
Internist Alex it was released during the Copenhagen climate Summit 2019
The biggest
Betty
It wasn't just like a text message
You up you alright alright it was
To illustrate a basically a public-private Arrangement worked out
Subvert the Kyoto Protocol
There was between the United States
United Kingdom
But the issue the people had with it was
It made a distinction between power levels of countries
Which was stigmatizing to countries that were vulnerable countries
What
People are going to get that and the fact that you don't
I was really trying to focus on the
You said power levels
Power level 9000
It's over.
Anime
This is why I don't get it
Dragon Ball Z
Now Goku
He is
A listener do Love Your Dragon Ball Z talk so maybe we should keep going
The planet
Freezer
A problem
So the second problem was that it
I took power away from the UN proper and allowed other end
Implementation
Concerns of climate change rules
And then we get back to the numbers that Alex is talking about it it's not packed
It made an imbalance between rich and poor countries in terms of admission
Standard
Or rich countries they could admit two points
67 tons
Per capita
As opposed to poor countries with 1.7
.44
So that is about double
Or so
Talk to the choir fervor during the climate change
Conference in NY to
Summer
Craigslist in a way that makes sense
If I understand correctly
The rich countries are allowed
Far more leeway with their admission
And despite the fact that the poor countries
Probably relies further upon those emission
Not be poor
Write in order to break out of
Principles
Just a little bit
Building up
Yeah and you'd hope they just by virtue of newer Technologies we have they would have a lower admission rate
Whether or not there was a cap there or anything like that you could do it as like well rich people get to drive in a car
Can poor people get to drive the car
You could
Correct referencing this as like
Something that's
Do you know
Being done
Clandestinely
Brett
Is there tax exempt
True
It's really made me
Tax exempt
Idea
Hours of private corporations
World population
How do I dice actually in the documents as well
That means the enforcers
Alright
Really bad plan
We're going to get here in a little bit.
Are there is
Like what
Sphere of illegals coming in
You know how the government even under Obama
Deported
Almost like a million people
They were really planning like in short order
Deport people
Give them back
T-Mobile Arena
If it's a really adhere to British
There's no doubt
When he says the old
Right right
Keystone
I'm so whatever I don't care
I still think this is more interesting to present-day quite frankly
Already we're a couple Clips in and I'm already like
I'm bored interested said something about that
Climate change
That you confirmed is true
The best-case scenario for Alex
Present
Just lies
Well here comes another lie
Fun with a decline of
Define partition
Gallows humor but this is going to be an incredible
Research Institute study
Democratic election fraud on a massive scale
From
Bernie Sanders
And a Republican
Donald Trump
About 5
The big news
I actually disagree does much bigger news but this is his big nose
So he's big news if there's this
Attitude
Study
What are you
What's that noise
I was just saying
Spoiler alert
Don't even get both right you don't even want a review
Paper claiming to show election interference
It asserted that Hillary Clinton did better in states where there was no paper trail to vote
Follow back
But even just a cursory glance over their data shows that they didn't complete job with data
Bay County
Where there were multiple ways of provoked
Yeah machines with paper trail where there were multiple
Other machines with no paper trail they just counted the entire State as one with no papers
Okay I got you completely just incomplete
Percent paper trail but not 100%
Yeah is this ever
Because data is
Corrupt
It's not because it's not indicative of
Reality
Pruitt
Students axle
Tilburg University in the dialects and Rudolfo Cortes Barragan of
Stanford University
Call the bird report
Published
And pushed on social media
Even the authors admit
In the paper that no time to pee review any of their Phi
So what this is something
Classic in Fort Worth
Go for it but I mean
There there's a conversation to be had possibly about the unfairness of the
Democratic National Convention
Clinton endorsing
Not like this
And brings home like how little Alec really cares
About the things you talk about
You could bring in something real but instead you go for it you much flash year
The fast-food version that isn't
Actually beef
Or whatever
Millions of listeners
Have you ever trusted
I'm not sure
Untrustworthy names
I know that there's one
It's too white
The name Rudolfo is
It makes me think of like
A reindeer from the North Pole going on vacation
Cancun
I like trying to fit in he's got a mustache fake mustache in prison
Player to it is what you're trying to lay low during the summer months
Down there having some surveys
My nose blue nose reindeer
How do you say rich
I just know French
Are you awake
Soros
Emails
And stuff like that
Earlier
Females
Mirror Dave
Before that apologies for interrupting and screwing up the
But there is something I think is interesting about his
Is Nonpoint
Then he makes
Steal the election
A burning
And then and then he says that they aren't
Was trying to steal it
But one of them one and one of them lost
Which is
Really interesting to me in a reflection of how
Politics actually works
Like the Republican moderate
Whatever it is
Have
0 control
Like it's all lunatics
On the right wing
Where is the Democrat
Republican
Like Republicans from the nineties in control of
Actual Progressive
So of course they have a larger block of life
What's hey guys we can't be having these crazy ideas out there of like
People drive getting better
Stay the course
All all the time
So it's set up in such a way as
They will always defeat the crazy
And the Republican party set up in such a way
They will never defy
Interesting
He doesn't even really on
Yep
Interesting
Explain
Career
Anybody else would put up with
Each of those countries from Sweden to France
Online to arrest anyone criticizing Islam
Mayors also announced an initiative to arrest you and the family
Pictures of blanket George Soros
Arrest rate of you
I'm scared with the London mayor is in Chicago
Pecan wand
Nonsense
Neither you
Nor your family
North people even broadly related
Foreshadowing of Alex becoming good friends
Being curtailed
In England
UK is
Somehow
Question Islam
What I mean like
We have to
F****** pump the brakes
It isn't something Alex never does on his show
Because he lives in this dumb idealistic bubble
Places to
The same
Yet he is a national
He seems to think
Our constitution applies to every country
And so like when there's hate speech laws in the UK that we don't have deer
Exactly why we didn't have his first amendment
You want Universal Global laws like that
Very crazy because
I don't
I don't know enough like I haven't done
Copious amounts of research into free-speech laws
From everything I understand.
Confining
Super repressive
But they do have a lot more allowances for
Something that's interesting
Especially recently
Because they have just recently
Curtail
Free Speech laws in a way that has not been done
For a long time, where activists
Worried about that
Counterpoint to that
You know
Do we have two lakhs free-speech laws versus
Are we
It is any free
Free speech like going to eventually lead to
The suppression of speech
That should be
I don't know
Has received Global Alliance of nationalist as though
Hey hey hey
Nationalists
To take out the globalist
Choose definitely
Definitely rely on archaic Jewish stereotypes
Is this group that we don't like wow becoming a global
To be against
In
This group we're demonizing with eighties about Excelsior mystery
Everything makes sense
Concern is much more
And I don't know I don't know I don't
I don't believe
Cuz it comes up in stand up a lot
Limit any speech and it limits all
Necessarily believe in
Because we have
Similar versions of that like
You can get in trouble for yelling fire in a crowded building like you can get in trouble for
Threatening someone with violin
Like they're already limits on Free Speech
You can't extort people
Like that sort of
You're given the option to get make
Wet
You can't do that to her
The idea that any limit on speech
Is a limited speed
I think
Contradicted by
The fact that we do have
Just basic
Limitations on
What is just
The only argument is the slippery slope
Either comes true or doesn't and it's not an actual argument
That you can really make it something you know like
Slippery slope
A logical fallacy
If you make an argument based on
Like, that's all you're doing
Earlier when I told Alex that a dumb plan you came up with
Listen to this
It's crazy
Notre Dame
1st of August
Means to me
This is how it was
This subject
Education program to create total
Sure it
And create a Utopia
Now this is Mexico
This is America
Sushi places
Nicaragua El Salvador
For all of those countries
Understand why those every country
Also has like a historical event where you're like
Forever
These programs have been in place as of last year
What you mean is like okay so kids in
As of life
Which means they're in 4th grade
Azelastine
Fifth grade
Bigoted
Homicidal
If people with white skin
I finish your thought you're going to give him 30 more years
The job on his stupid
Welfare
Real quick all white fears
The real reason that
Security
You f****** knows that most of his audiences are very scared
Gene Wilder very clear laws about being able to
Any welfare programs
If you are an immigrant who comes
Legally or illegally
No, legally there's no way you can
Didn't place since last year
And as we all know
Democrats have complete control of the Senate that the house and
I'm right in 26 Republican
Baby crazy
But you know
Like those Republicans
Alex Pettyfer
That would be interesting
We can't speculate about someone's
Secret voting habits
But
He's
I want to get out
I want to get out but I can't quit
Money is skimmed
Organized
So what do I hold on
The NFL ever in organized crime rookie combine
They have to take the the test
No no no no no
We have kids being indoctrinated in schools as of a year ago
Elite in order to come
Year
Zayn
They are being
Some of it
World
And then bus
Seems like a lower
Across the border and then bust like
Nebraska
Like okay makes absolutely no sense
11 year old in
I dismiss it out of hand like that absolutely not I reject the premise today
But then when you talk about a fraud
To vote Democrat and the other one is to skim money off the top
Skimming money off the top there's better scam this seems like
It'll be way too many cooks in the kitchen
Someone would talk
So ineffective this Camp is no good
Secondarily
Alex is already claiming that they're just voting in dead people's names
They don't need this elaborate
Stupid planet makes
No sense
None of this even with the motivation
Ending ZZ villains
Are old
Ten Grand to get a dead person
Kaze
People are voting but it's actually illegal immigrants
Never wrestled
Is like the second
Third stages of the plans that he's a numerator
Because the other thing barely neither do the globalist
The other problem is
VSCO
It's got it
Exist
With
All of the other
Like
16 East Oak
You got have that part in there too
You both have to have all of his
Being
Altruistic
Will they have millions of people work at the globalist
Millions of people working
If you don't need that
Everybody's got a lot of games a lot of pies
But look we have that many people
You can come up with these harebrained
Perhaps
You know what
Sometimes companies fuk up
Sometimes companies
The dog on this rack money leaving money you know like whatever
Got diplomatic immunity cuz apparently that is something that the megabanks can have
Are you lovey ideas like this
International
Cabal that existed for hundreds of years that comes down from like
The black nobility in Venice and stuff like that they also come up with like
International House of Pancakes
Should have figured out the whole
Instead of now being like
Haha we tricked you like no one was trick
We all thought this was
Stupid
Same level of like business
Activity that he's
Does fixing into the minds of globalism
He's been around for
Thousand
They don't make me
Everybody makes mistakes
Fair enough
Globalist have run so many plans over the thousands of years
Over and over again fresh
Yeah sometimes you open up that crazy
Pattern
Let's embarrass ourselves for real
More pancakes
Guys
We got to do something crazy
We get it you have waffles
We can't call ourselves the International House of Crepes nobody's going to buy that s*** we hate French people in America
My dear friend
Go to IHOP for lunch everyday
Be hungover as s***
It was always
The only reason
Logs of mozzarella
Anyway
IHOP
Physically
Flagrant
Misrepresenting
Some comments that he had made
Alex makes the mistake of
It becomes very clear with him
Memes
Alex
He looks like a
Ding-dong
On his own show
So embarrassing
So disgusting
I love it
It's so great
Alright
I do I don't like
How he never have to live
Play Disco.
Any right-thinking person who listen to this
Absolutely trying to
And maybe a very nice unifying statement
Into something
That is evil
Message is inherently anti-white
Absolutely
Diversity
Is
That's what
Supremacist
Here is what Alex Jones
Process
Hillary's VP
Whites must become a minority to atone
Does real quick
Take a second
To take that in as the headline that he's reporting
White must become a minority
In order to make up for rape
That makes sense
This is the ultimate racism
Experience
We must make white cement
Who's going to leave this
And organize all the different racial groups
Is it going to put your
Different racial groups
Part of the KKK it's particularly funny
Consider racial incarceration rate for Alex stupid artist
Let's put
This is incredible
Is 11 Sunday morning and that was a challenge to pay and so I've made my
We're we're not segregated in fact we were
When we started there one of them
A few white families in that church it's now a very well integrated church but it was important
Especially I think the burden is on those of us who were in a majority
Put ourselves in situations where were in the morning minority
Okay so there are
Eminem
Percent of that identifying as a
The planet is Angela
Okay
Apologize
Everything else
Great
Craig
Identify Zengo
But
So we've got
Not only is Rachel dolezal
Outlier
She's she's just even crazier for doing it the wrong way
Because what she should be doing
Accidentally or incorrectly
That is 3%
What
What is
3%
What's the 3%
Fitzgerald's right Utah
I don't have the numbers in front of me but I
I can't imagine
I feel
Feel like my
My Spidey Sense tells me
Well I don't know cuz
Transit
I'm trying to find demographic information I should look that up earlier but
It's just it's just it man it feels like that's what he say
Just 500 million Chinese people saying
That's all he's talked about he's just talkin about
Very well publicized 500 million Chinese people
Who's David there
I mean
DD
I mean even without us being able to say exactly what
He's talking about
The idea of like now you're not white is the whitest thing ever
Exclusivity which is what we talked about all the time
The notion of whiteness has
Is based on exclusion not on include
I don't know
You know I don't
I wish I had those numbers
Play song
You talkin about
Whitney would like who does that like swarthy Italian
The Greek
I don't know man you know what the issue is it
Electric no matter what the answer is it
No matter what
If you talk about the Irish
You know what go f*** yourself Alex
Sure we've been the whitest for a long time
There's no sun
We were grown
It's disgusting that that sort of his take on like how am I going to respond after this
Before I play
Because what you're saying isn't really good message
Which is
Say
You telling a personal anecdote about the idea
Has one of the more segregated places
You have denominations
Churches that are primarily black slime
I'm in dub there's between doesn't usually meet
And his idea of going into places that are not where you are the minority
Is something that is very helpful
For everyone
No big deal
Here's what I want to say
I was rambling around a little bit
If you hear what Tim Kaine said
And you are against
What you were against integration
One more round or I only want it on my terms
I only wanted they come to me and come to my
Barbecue or whatever
Like you to put yourself into
Situation
Where you get to experience other people's culture
Respectful empowering
All and enlightening
I've never had the experience
That black people have
Just about every day
Create
How cultures actually works learn about something instead of having a character
Uno
How many times have you seen like a young white, go into
And be like I don't know how to act right now
Like I do
That was much more examples
Generally nude
How many more times I saw them go in and it'd be no big deal
I don't like not because people pandered or anything but because
When you go in
Situations where you are
You realize
But it's not as big a deal as you think
It's not a big
I wonder who's going to think I'm the other
If you thinking that
I cherish so much that I had growing up
Tubi
In so many different communities
Because like I said talk about this book my dad is a religious studies
Professor and so he had friends
Like
Spend time at the synagogue
Break bread with all these family
And go to their houses for
Whatever
The holidays
Various States
And it it's not a rewarding thing because sometimes
You know they wasn't about that
Is about regret
I really don't look much food
Picky eater
IHOP very frequently
I don't have credit
And that's what I was growing up
I only was around
It wasn't until I moved away that it was like
Oh I'm interested in like experiencing other cultures in meeting other
And I feel like if my family if so many family
Just
Like Dave themselves be opportune
Go to places where there
All the sudden a lot of those conservative viewpoint
Disappeared
Granola
So much more in common than they have
Auto,
Infinitely
Three fighting back against that and arguing nothing erase pimp
You made a point of stopping the Clipper li2se like
Hyzaar
Presenting it as like
The headliner
He saying putting yourself in situations
Where
You aren't
Tata
It helps
Together we have all
Much more empathy we have much more understanding is opposed
Staying or stupid
And listening to world
WorldNetDaily
Jerome corsi and all these
These whites
Supremacist
Tinkerbell
Every
Single child who was
On the Vanguard of school integration
In the text
You will
Never
Experience
If you're awake
Person how could you
Abreva
Sitter judge
Somebody who's been through
Unless
You spend a lot of time being in the minority
Situation
You'll never comprehend
And if you judge them for their
You're fuking idiot you are that's all you can
But I understand
Absolutely
Which is the fact
The other
Caucasian situation
I'm sure there's a Neo-Nazi.
I would go the other way I think there's a black nationalist
Group called The
Consideration
Laughlin weather
What has what has the SS
But the yeah it's more difficult for me to talk about that
Experience I don't have
It's impossible
Right there
My limited version
Of being in situations where I was
F****** Elementary School in Hawaii
Lakeway couple years in elementary school we lived
And me and my brother were two of four white kids in the entire school so like
I mean the mainland
Came back in 94
I came back and Rico your so far from America
Even even better
Making it
I only know the material
For a white person to ever understand
Black anime
Real-time
Completely lying about Tim Kaine
Comments
The only reason to lie about that
Stoke White
Beer and racial division
And the idea that he's
Arguing
Is Ludacris
And very responsible
Hey
You know what whenever I hear somebody call for a
My first thought you wanted
That's obvious
What are you asking me to
Somebody else's Walk of Life
You know what
Sounds like you would not be in the minority you know it still exists cookout
I think that that idea of white identity
He's kind of built around
It's built around exclusion not ink
The idea of empathy
Directly counters
Which is why
As my campaign statement
Stop Yes on white Jetta
Alright
Move forward
Monster
For social justice
I feel like that's a good trade control welfare
This guy is a Muslim I jerk off to measuring
He says he wants
Almost
Is on
That's astonishing
I mean that's
Really
Free races
No
Because we just put terrorists
In charge of the police
We need white terrorism charge of the police this is
Fundamentally like
Construction
Flagrantly racist trip
Really races
Rebuttal is always Muslim
It's okay. Brownstone
F*** I only brought that up so you can make that rebuttal to trade agreement
It's crazy I mean this is
It's all just a bond
Ideas like
Trying to do a better job.
Systemic
Racial in
Religiously-based
Exist online if you want to pretend
Entertain his argument
Replace
Muslim with black and you clearly see how racist it is
All of these black people are becoming police chief
It's clearly A Reign of Terror
Like what are you
F****** talking about you
Experience
Do well actually we've experienced
Pretty much word for word
I mean you let black people become president and then they're everywhere
This is something
No
Understanding
I knew a bit about
You know the white nationalist uprising
What happened
Yeah but I know nearly as I never watched videos
You know about Oklahoma City
What about the roots
Ruby Ridge and Waco
Similar things
And I couldn't watch this documentary
Inasmuch
Hey what I got from it is
Watching White
Just l
From the early days talk
They use the same language that Alex does now
Like
It's a parallel
It's bizarre to watch
Can you go back and watch these guys
Who had like the the
That compound in northern Idaho
Are you going to listen to those
Supremacist
That gives their sermon
There's so much talk about sauce
There's so much talk about the ethnic identity
There's so much talk about
This replacement fear
All In
Every ever
Everything is the same
That makes me think that nothing
For two years
Very pretty
Who was the
I think I'm a little bit
Mystikal argument
Soupremacy showing up
In full strength every 30 years
Leggett maybe it may just be correlation but his
His main point was like
Alright so we got a s*** ton of white supremacy
Bright
What was 30 years before this
What was 30 years before that
Regular Nazi movement years before that was free
Crash when everybody was
Totally against Jews
That was coming around
The Civil War
It's like somebody arguing that there the full moon changes things
No it's not
Something along those lines that was the classic quote it's a remix yeah
I'm so
The one thing just like R Kelly
And is threatening
The one thing that is not
The original version
Alex Jones
Make bad
Here's one of his prediction
We talked to ARB
We talked to our
Pipeline
To the Secret Service
They added some very important information
Dealing with Hillary staging a false flag against yourself
Assassination
That lines up with our other information
Hillary's going to false flag herself
School
Seems like a dangerous
Free time
I'm dumb
Very very.
The Accidental headlight of like
Can a woman with permanent brain damage become president
I don't think so
You heard that earlier when you son with a tumor eats the rest of her melon
Deepen me like
She's about to die
Realize that clearly I didn't leave in
Most of the time he's talking about
I would say good third of this show is just him being like
So
We know that from necklet
Braxton prediction is bad
Yes multiple sources
One who has
The information
Interesting
Steppin Out
Zach
Is not on the run yet
Credible source
Cuz they're probably made up
These sources are real
See if you can figure out what sources
He's driving
This information from
This is the 21st century
Wavelengths being sent out over the cellphone to causar
That's one of us or allegory of what's actually going on
Population
Garth Brooks
May 2nd
Worth it song
Allegory
Going up into space while you bio-weapon the whole Earth
You can put You Only Live Twice
Biological pathogen
Runs its course
Like in 12 Monkeys
Designs
Extreme
They're telling you the plan
Like in Andromeda
You know how many more movies would you like this
Choose another sign
Action movie
You could play this game with any
Movie site
Sure
Do you know what Osmosis Jones
There's like a rocket
Stop it
A remake
I mean this this is just the sort of stuff that the
Embarrassing
I mean I don't know like
If you had a point
You wouldn't
Constantly reference movies
Because Hollywood is
That's why he watches every move
Free movies
So stupid
Ever actually so
You've done a lot of great
Thank you catalog
All of Alex Jones
Not all of them have you considered
Also catalog
All of his movies
And kind of developing a unified field theory of what Alex Jones prefers in a movie
Cuz I feel like he's a huge science fiction book
Right but I really like
What is Berrien Center
You said something a little bit later than
He's all over the place
No I think it was a fan of David Lynch
David Lynch
Agreed
I don't think he's actually Olympia
No
He didn't get the o.j.
What's it like
No it was a
Whatever
Alright
We've been talking for about an hour now about
Some of these Petty narratives that he brings up and the reason that you can't ignore them are the things like temp
Alright
This is so f****** rape
It's crazy
It's crazy to want to listen to that like
Ignore that
Clip was when I was like
Oh no
I was right to go back to this episode
Is he starts with Alex rambling about George Soros
Something happen
There's no future under this new world order
Everybody
87 year old crazy Nazi Collaborators
President
Who wants to run the world
Business
Okay
So
He got a text
In the middle of a show
From somebody
We all know
Gustafer Dubai
Rodger cell
I got a text from Rodger
Let's go ahead
Cam
Wait Rochester
So Rodger Stone
Wait
Wait wait
You might need a while
Hold on
If you are
Correctly
This is the day after
Yep
The day after August 16th 2016 after he had absolutely been in contact
3 / 2.0 he writes an article
Narrative
Dewar's
To put it out
I guess we had a byline on the hill to I'm not entirely sure I was only able to find the article on Infowars
It's just about Hillary
Would be evidence that he's
Jit primarily comes from that Stanford article right
Paper on a review paper
Talks about how
Bunch of
Voting machines
A primary narrative that Trump is going to
Toulouse by hacking or something like that
Which is sort of the
Backdoor way of
Right
Exactly
Creating
Because it's important to do that
When you're doing that
That's really smart though
Fairy
Fun
Every time they said when they go low we go high
You look back at that in your life
Oh going Louis the other problem too
Who is that like
The reality of conversation
And all the information
Is this
They go low
They're going to lower than you
Like that
Trump insulting like that their Gold Star Family
That's pretty f****** low
But behind that was how much lower they were going
At the same time
Exactly or flipping a red cape
I mean look there's no way to slice them
This is very clear to me what's going on this is Rodger Stone creating
Essentially strawman
He's doing this because he's in contact with
Russian intelligence agency
I don't believe for a goddamn second at the emails and private messages that have been released
Are the only messages of course that's not even a possibility in my mind
There's no chance of that
And the fact he's not named in that indictment
He's jamming to him
Oh no he's felt it would be different
They're saving some of that because they have more information
If they had named him
In the indictment
Then you would know
He was not part of the thing
The fact that they kept it out of the
Suggest that they are going to
The text has more information that's yet to be connected
It's probably further communicate
Further
Information
That
The probe the Mueller probe has that we don't have
Do me when I see that unlike Rogers f***
And I want to look at I still think he's
When
Saw that and I was like let's look back
Visnic
In 2016
And I saw that
Alex's Maine
Archive
YouTube channel doesn't have this episode up
Listen to it
And Alex gets
Text Jean are to publish this article
About how Hillary is going to
Steal the electors election fraud possible
Like that sort of thing
Tumi
That to me is f****** clearly indicative of something
Game god dammit
The balls on this guy
To have a conversation about rigging the election and then the next
Jay
Write an article about how their rigging the election
Look at his article should have been should have just been like
Can you rigging election
Years man now it gets so much worse
Put your mic down
And there's going to be more hacks a little bird told me there were other hacks
And prepare
I'm afraid all the emails but they released
Election
And no amount of false flag
Soros
You can run on for a long time
You just admitted that you have advance notice of things that are to come and the content of those things
You know what you know what that proves
Alex thinks Hillary is going to win
Yep like
That's the only way
That you become the weakest of Link
Because
Like you could just throw this in court never was like
This whole thing happened
He said
On air
Yeah
And the only way
The only way it would not be investigated
Is if Hillary won
Oh yeah I mean is soaked
Brazenness ND
Aspect of him being like
A little birdie could Rogers.
Before the podesta emails before Rodgers
Is still to come Rodger absolutely have things that are about
And Alex is reported this stuff from
Another outlet from the GR
Like this is very clear like I don't
I don't know any other way to slice
But I think he's stupid
I think he doesn't realize
This is why
We
Talk about Alex is because
He is
The weakest link
If he has no no no no
No one
Who do the details of this stuff
Would come on Aaron laugh about how
I've been told there's more stuff coming and I know what's in it
Yeah earlier on the show be like I don't care if it's the Russians
Or something like that unless you were
Like
I think at this point quite frankly
Alex B
This Behavior indicates
Vicki's on the Audi
Most outermost level of the circle
Using him as a
A way to disseminate information to be sold out
There's no way that
Rodger
Only text
No other people
Pretty hard today, along with Alex
Lot of conservative media was given this information as well as
This is a bad idea
Let's talk about the restraint
To be like oh s***
And only end up
Text Jill
Is because the hill was like
Will clearly this isn't truth coming from Rodger Stone and the people that Rodger texted at
Breitbart Fox News or whatever
Are like
Oh s***
You're committed all the crimes
We can't talk about that
Otherwise you've got a paper trail
Phuc yea throw it on the air baby
I'll reveal that I know
Is that last clip works just like the laughing about knowing what's coming into
Talked about
Talking to Russian intelligence
Am I I get that I understand he's a liar
Yeah I understand that
What makes him so
Plausible deniability of that
Is what you
Yes
But I can tell at this point like I can't Elsa
Sincerity from Lion in him I believe Malcolm Gladwell level
Of of Alex Jones
Turn off and Wendy's
Bean
And to be I hear this and I got a I got like my heart was fluttering
Why did you say that
And why is this episode not on your channel anymore because you said that
That's a really big deal.
PID
That's a huge deal
In terms of the indictments
8 terms of his testimony that he gave to the house
Judicial committee
But that's a really f****** serious issue
God dammit
Are we can become material Witnesses is
No cuz I do we have an email address I have a faith healer at
Fbi.gov I have a I have a certain amount of faith that if we
I kind of don't I don't think there's any way that a series investigator would be like well obviously we have to listen to
1 million hours of envy
Little importance
We absolutely wouldn't
Yeah whatever
He says later in this episode
Really check out this next
Got time today
Cool
If you go to Russia and are arrested
Probably on your side
Well hold on it if you get arrested
If you get killed your journey
You're just a political
-1
I mean even when you were looking at 2015 he kept being like Putin
Hearing like
Pro-russian
It is not like it anyway
No I mean so much as it is Pro
No it's pro-russia inasmuch as you saying
George Soros should be arrested by government Russia's government
They're better
Do you like Russia
Yet turkey for sure
Horrible
We're open tonight
Kicked out of
General
Square
You have
Nationalist uprisings
Freight Quote
Crazy
It's crazy that he would be technically speaking or or prep
By Word of Mouth against
The cultural revolution that Mal put for it
I need at the same time
What could be described
Exact same f****** thing
That
Bad
Not important
Good call
I don't know
And that is
Jordan Fisher
Blew my f****** mind
Like it could literally be evidence in a federal trial
Very very very
Is even more mind-blowing in Subway Langley has been a joke
For a long time
Travis Langley
Went outside
Firefighting after college is a good man
As far as I know I haven't spoken to in like it
Business Clips is so f***** up
Apologies for convicted of sexual assault two years ago under the shirt
He's one of those fun guys
He was one of those guys that could drink as much as me and college because of that ended up
Together a lot because everybody else
Years ago of Edna
But my dear friend I'm sorry
Is profoundly f*****
I don't believe
Half of it
Put on the part that you do believe is true
No I want it all to be true just because of this Funworld that it creates a Nighthawk
Punching Bill Clinton the face before she was so ill
And just
Not Justa Cutlery plate furniture
Are trash
He wants to assist
That's just
Evernote
Does not give tips
Complained
That's amazing
Post-mortem book on Hillary campaign
Even even that book which is
Insanely critical of her campaign in the way that it was run
Even that book never says
Tip 15%
Lego
You would have no
You went to dinner with
Image of Alex Jones
Therapy to a waiter
Hey what's going on with your buddy
Do you know what I did when we believe
This hurt me because I genuinely believe wait staff should be a protected class
Like if you're an a****** to your weights app that is borderline a hate crime
Targeted abuse
I would
I guarantee you 95% of any weights at 5 ever met would be like
I would prefer you give me $0
But no speech
Talking to this is the perfect example of the like
Being able to suss out live from
Like
I know about something that's
Knowledge
The LIE is
I'm going to really really play up how empathic I am
I'm
I care about people like is a lie because he flushed it out into
An elaborate scenario where at
But you need to really know that that makes me not want to come in here
If Alex if Alex gives details
His lies are likes and then I was born from the
The perfect one
It's game representing
Now we get back to
And Alex
Really
Unfortunate
Make this
Episode this August
Episode
The next level weird
He called it
Arley
That's a Freudian slip
No Charlie
No it's not no it's our Ali
No General is the American people
Missing
No
That means that he thinks he's a part of
Let me ask
That means that he thinks that this is something we are doing
Someone named Rodger Stone
Lights
That's what we're doing with the help of course
On August 6th probably learning
You still around
On August 16th the information though I had not
Actually been
Correct most of it
Most of it a couple days earlier
Emails
October
So there is there is a
There's a beginning of it but not
In the middle of it at this point in the only reason
But it literally the next time I'll know
Rodger Stone was in touch with this date
I bet I bet if we go to
To the 17th decimal
Incriminating
But maybe not as incriminating
Hourly
Harley
Really really
Incriminating
Well it means to me what it means
And I take this from also this next clip
Listen to this next quote and then I'll explain what I mean
By what I think about him saying
Pizzagate Joe Biggs
You still around
Yeah
Erik Prince operation
The carbon tax is being exposed
Decline
Climategate stuff that is a Russian
But this is not the Russians us intelligence
Risking their lives
Because Hillary
It's finally turned
So here's what's going on Alex Alex Smith
Like Erik prince in Blackwater
You have people like Steve pieczenik and Rogers that are lying to him and confirm
Details
Amongst
Themselves
Yeah yeah the Russian
A bunch of stuff before and they're still trying stuff
This one is
Pacific one
Actually until Patriots risk their lives
Because Hillary has gone too far
And this is what happened
Which we now know
They have spent
Hours
Upon hours upon hours upon hours of deers
Actually disproving that Hillary has committed any crime in the specific way that Alex
It's insane to me
How
Think again I hate to keep saying the right thing
In person because that becomes so much like a
What do you think
Infected brain worms
Sure
I've been trying to train myself and that's a reasonable so much
Cuz he used to be like a trigger for me please
Almost my Tourette's something is reasonable
But like this to me is like
If you look at this
The only assassin
You can really come away from and I would welcome anybody to go Lizabeth whole 3 Hour episode you're not going to get more
Contact
You can listen to
For a bit
I would not recommend anybody listen to this entire 3M wrap
Do the same s*** we talked about it
But like if you listen to
I don't think
You can come away from
Gloating
About what he knows it's coming
And then he says things like this
Which indicates people like
Rodger Stone
Right maybe Eric princess
Text Alex
Sense come out inside
Derek Prince was a big source of information
You have
People who
Can guy you have
Yeah
Come out
That is a lot of berries
Information about the
Specific computers
Emails Gru agents
Using witches that matches up perfectly with what describes provided the information
This time it wasn't
Which is what
Rodger
Steve pieczenik
I think
Is Alex
Acting is a patsy
All of this nonsense
He's got really hot
But Alex is so boring is
I think he realized it's some point
Because of the white nationalist
Movement
That are still being a bold and Denise
He's pushing through the legislation that he would like to be
Kick noises
That things like this on Earth
Evidence
That's why he should was boring in 28
He knows people are less
Like know the people were listening
Yeah I don't mean it like you didn't think anyone was let me just not like
Hades doesn't matter it's all good
And you know what it's not all good
It's not all good
A nail in the coffin
Ever
Convincing
Ever like
Making Alex
Front the fact that he has been lied to and taken advantage
What takes away so much of his masculinity
Power
Because if he took that episode Down
Which Wich
Can confirm
If he if he was specifically not cool with this
Episode
That suggests
For now
That is intense
It's like
B he found out
That he was f******
Or later in the day
You just drifted outside
Dangerous and you're going to hurt my sources
I have no idea whether this
Never went up or it was taken down
From
Years
Everything
Which is smoke but not fire breath
It looks like it's smoked
Like
To me there's always been a romantic idea of like
If we could just
Get to it
And just like
York
Whether or not we agree on policies or anything like that
All we can genuinely prove to you
Is it the people you've surrounded with
R-Truth
F*** you over
Get rid of any possibility ever of redemption
Number one
Many times where you can point to
Concrete example
Of him being
Actually
That he was
By the people that you supposedly Trust
Like so many times we pointed out that by the people eat trout
But this is a confirmation about Mars
Disc
He was trying to get on my show and Saints
Some dumb s***
When he's been on
It's not like it's an anomaly for him to be on or say something weird
The media picked up on the Mars base thing that he said
Also like
Delightful
You have that
Working
Robert David Steele
Robert
Right now
He's become
Woven into the DNA
2 years
To the point where
Kinkos downtown
Annex trick
But it's not
Actually that
Not true there's a way that Alex can Dodge
If Rodger Stone goes to prison
I think Alex
I think I think it's I think it's possible
But even if these guys go to prison
Right here
This episode
Is the closest I have ever come to being like
Alex
Is going to
Prism
Like because
This is
Had Advance knowledge
Admit to
Perjured him
Interviews
So he's still like on the right side of the law
If he comes
Queen what you can't do
But it involves selling out Rodger
No longer are we going to romanticize the idea of ever convincing him that he's f***** over
Here's what we do
We email his lawyer
Alright
And his lawyer is like
Email Beth
Alright and
We send that email we have these
Eclipse they here
All We Do
It is
Get an email back
That is just them salivating at the billable hour
Yeah
All that's going on
If this information is part of Buehler's probe
This is so many billable hours like
The lawyers if they heard this Brie they would
I I really think that this sort of these these indications are the song
Cuz he
Business
Protective
The kids
He like Evie doesn't want to go to
Like I know I know that he believes in
Prison mentality
It's a program
Alex goes to prison then
Cuz he was offering
Becomes the new Mark Richards for us when we go visit him
Here's the new Alex Jones interview by knowledge
I don't know I don't button
Just
It's nonsense
The only way out is
Bad
But
I don't I
Still don't see
Like
I think at the end
What's the date
White
Supremacist
F***
Hey Ya
Hate him so much
Rhetoric
And it's the worst
And all these people were talking about like
Should he be allowed on Facebook
I don't think it's a valid conversation to have
You get off
I don't think I don't know
It's not clear to
I hate
But I don't
Like even all of this
I think that he's
Smart about
A lot of
Cultural issues he's cancerous about
I would say he's not smart
No like he's got he's got to be an infant
No I think he knows what
The racial
Stop.
Yeah I think
In charge of
Secret information in all this
Counter-coup narrative in all this
I think he's
He's the bar
I think you can see it played out on air
I'm at think it would be disingenuous
He's committed
Cuz what we're talkin about is treason
Like we're talkin about
AR
Sedition against America I mean you say that but it's like
Stealing an election is that so bad
Dukes of Hazzard
Rey's speeder you're in a Patton Oswalt Bush and Cheney
But
That's not
This is
Is
Prime
And you can't hide
Wonderful people in the intelligence agency
Very clearly forensic leben study
I still don't think
I've heard him in the past talked about like people are investigating him
How do you take that with a grain of salt I always
Things from like
Investigating
Social media presence
Stuff like that
That was always been the point
Is that was going on a year-and-a-half ago
And now it's his own are talking about Advance knowledge
Publix
I'm stuff like that
I'm in the f******
Hopper
Yeah
Here's my prediction
Either
Howard's Meats
The flip
She's going to get real dark
He might
I never thought this until it wasn't this
Disagree
I think that he might get indicted
I really don't think anybody is listening
Are you
I don't think so
I don't think Siri
Take this seriously
I think that if
You have the reason that we take it seriously is because we are not serious
We are decidedly unserious people
I think that if you are
Investigation
And you're focusing on Rodger Stone
And you realize
Rodger Stone
You probably wanted
Easiest forensic things to do is like find out what he said on that show on various days
This stuff is very well-known
Investigators
I think it has
Then
Here's here's why I feel like
And this is not to say that
Is morphe
Here's why I feel like my assessment of this particular situation
Regarding what the FBI regards as serious is more valid
I listen to weigh less Alex
Turn up
99.99% of the population
We all feel like
Alex Jones can be disregard
Never a bad idea to suggest that people invest
Navigating things
Can disregard details that would
That's generally the real
She goes back to that like when you were looking at your peripheral vision is
Focus on one
You Don't See
The very obvious thing on the side
And so is at the same time
Infowars
So in the next clip Alex talks about
WDC leaks
How do you says that they say
Play like all of
They're a bunch of hacks
So they're like
Have you ever heard about Infowars
Facebook
Within days of calm
Daily Caller
The diary
It's open-and-shut
Call Mike Mitchell
Apothecary recipes
Fellowship in the same
We got going on
I watch nobody's Netflix documentaries about various admire them for not trying to sell something during them
The crime
Try to sell something in this
May 11th
That interrupts best
Oh yeah
How about a lot of things
4 furlong
Timer
Some
Impressions
After the clips you play there
There is some left
And also
With this
A hundred percent
Proof
It is a
Claim
Based on evidence that has been
Right and
And based on everything they are
Information and
Criminal justice system
Investigative body
Have put out
It is very clear
That
Malik
Guccifer 2.0
Empathy
4 Russian hackers to you
Disseminate information
Yeah from the DNC
And from Soros
Now why this can absolutely
Confirmed as
Is because
For all of Mueller's and die
These are the one bowler
I've been criticized
Like there's bill but I didn't know if he's ever going anyway
Dick but someone is
Zelda
Agree
Here's why this one I feel like can
Can absolutely be
Confirmed
True regard
Is that
This is the first indicted
Feel like that molars brought
That will mean nothing
Because none of the 12 people that he is indicted
Will ever be extradited
Godzilla
Some companies
Some numbers
Which ones
Some Russian companies that were involved
It's just like
Guys
We are presenting incontrovertible evidence
Simply Be
Close
Nothing can be done about it
Course not what kind of world
Trump
Who f****** loves
Ever be like we're recording us right now
Giving him a hand
Innate
What world would you be like okay well
We got we got to do this
Give me 12 guys from your military so I can
Prosecute them in the United States
Come on
Bottom line
Absolutely
That were involved in the
Easy hack
Cannot be disputed much more embarrassing than Alex
Beginning
Proof
Salute
I mean yeah
Yeah
Like this is a guy who's being trick
I don't
There is a version that he is a person who Woods
Call Jonesboro
I think he is
Completely Hook Line & Sinker
On this stupid narrative
August
16th 2016
Who knows what he knows later
But at this point
He's being f****** lied to Undead
Thrilled about it and that's why he's
So
Outward
With things that are
And evidence
Okay so here's how
Alright both of us
Moved
Respond to it
We
First off I loved it
Yeah how much their there's a great hot sauce shop
2 to 4 years unlocked
Are LSAT
Pasta Bar
Go to
Go to town
We spend years as public defender
Then we parlay that
Into a private practice
10 relatives of yours at partners
Good morning
15 years from now
We run for attorney general
We have the authority to
Take the information that we have gathered
Over this past two years
Alex Jones
Accessories
Don't think
I know
I know how bad a propaganda
I still think
Who are
My view
Yeah
I don't know everything I only have the information that I have
Actively involved
Treason aspect is actively involved in the propaganda
I think the propaganda is not a crime but
I don't think you would necessarily have a crime
Hang him on for that
I think
In terms of his involvement in all this
I think that
He's probably a guy who which is both wise
Is
Used for this specific purpose
Like people tell him way too much
Or or at least
At least for a week
Guys who spend all of our time talking about
But in reality
They tell him
Way more than is necessary in order to get out in front of the narrative
And make
Crazy
Possible
The Rogers
Who were manipulating
Cuz it's very cool
That that so cute
It is from everything I can tell her I might
Everything I can tell
You have Steven Rodger coordinating Lee manipulating him on this side
Like I don't think the three of them are involved
Nichols is another site
Exactly is not part of the cabal
2 he's being manipulated in a similar anti-hillary way
Never
I think he's just a
Crazy old dude
But
I know I lost my train of thought entirely
The burden of proof of someone actually
Doing
We're talk
Yeah we talked about
We are
He should be hung by the neck until dead I believe the burden of evidence
Pretty high
When I look at Alex
Am I look at stuff like this
Like what's crazy to me
Legitimate
Is that looking at this episode
The day after Rodger Stone 104
Wasn't
With Russian intelligence
Do you have Alex thing
Damning stuff
That he knows
And he's been told
Stuff
Do hickeys on the outside
I still think that there's an innocent
Which is hard for me to wrestle with as someone who
Studies Hitman
I think he should be
Yeah I don't know how to deal with it
Misdemeanor
Such a hard thing to wrestle with that I have
I found something
Alex
You
Hargray
David Vance
Notice of weeks that are going to come out
Which is a huge part of what you deny is part of your information
I still think the only reason he's lying about it now is cuz he's realized he was lied to back then
She is finally aware
That he is an accessory
Yes yeah
Accessory to treason which kind of pill is treason
Cover up is crazy
And cover-up is what
DC going on right now
I think so too
Snowboarding
Because it's just
You just go back to being weird
Kind of think if
He bailed on Trump
The Fox News people would follow
Yeah I think you'd be the bellwether
I think if he got approval
I'm being like
Trump live
The whole time like if Trump is impeached
If you somehow was like proof-of-concept
Yeah
Jump on board
I don't know
That I don't know
I don't know but I know
Dunno
I know people commit treason
That's not that's not any argument
It doesn't invalidate anything that I thought before
Yeah it adds a little bit
Figuring out the picture
Previous
Concept of what happen
Very intact
Just with more like
Yeah
It's just evidence that Alex Alex has information
Is not saying
Yeah parts
Something's going to have to happen
If you are Mueller
Whether or not you are aware that you're going to be attacked by a foreign power
And report it or not
Is a question of like
Can you actually prosecute
Sure you know like
Rodger Stone
Ratcliff
If you're Rogers
You're aware that
As we know now
Russia committed an act of
Warwick Ontario B
At the same time one of the one of the realities we have to admit is that the only way that we could possibly
Know this
Is if we hacked into their systems in the same way that they did to our
You know like that it's not possible to know that in any other way
So if you want to say you know they committed an act of war against us
Moral like we should I do about this
Is the same
What
The defense
Awareness
Knowledge requires the same thing as the spearfishing in hack
Right
Some of that can just be done by monitoring
Suspicious people
So it has been rightly pointed out that we absolutely helped install Boris Yeltsin
So it's
I know but that's not it they didn't declare war on us then like
It's not
I'm just saying that this is something that should be that we should be aware of before
People started saying that this is an active
An act of War
Ameristaff is espionage
Go to war with Russia
It's stupid
What you're saying
Quid pro quo south of like we f*** with you
Also this is okay I don't agree with that because I don't think anybody
Stop doing that
That's a different
Respond
I think the only thing that you can do
Did the Jews
Mother is putting out
These indictments
Impossible to ever enact yet of course the evidence out
This is what happened
To make a document
15 years old
Yeah dude all of that out there
Prosecute as many Bad actors
Here is you can
Yeah I hope to mitigate the damage
Magic
You hoped
Be able to
Difficult to understand
This is the process that happened
Investigative
Patterns
The ways
Was known
Revealed that
Yeah you start to under
Understand
Look out for online
Right
Careful about what you
Trust
Because
It's very easy
To manipulate your opinion right
Algorithms and s*** like that
Because that
Is a huge part of the story Criminal
Then you take the criminal piece of it and you hopefully
Put
Comes probably
But like you get
You get people like Rodger Stone
To go to prison
You get manafort in prison
Hopefully some of these other people I mean
Blind to go to
Some of these other folks maybe they
Flip and become
State's evidence
State Property
Maybe they
No make some
Deals for themselves
We try and wash this
National nightmare out of our hair
And then move on and
Can do but
May I don't think
It's possible
No as we as we
As we all know needs to happen
Even even if the Democrats run.
F****** table
Penguin
Every election
They're still going to
Actually impeached
Need to be
Like I understand that we all want him
He needs to be stopped
Yeah
Perhaps
More importantly the Republican Party
Stop which
Would be
Better served in our interest
If he was if Trump was just neutral
With an entirely Democratic Congress
As president
We just want to make sure that
All of the dumb s*** but which is probably based on diminished
Intellectual capacity
Much better Optics
If he stays as president
Display
Who yells all the time
Maybe that's a better thing for the Democrats have been impeached
But I always forgive Andrew Jackson was never allowed to in
Implement
Like he's allowed to stay all that b*******
But none of it actually
Like better circumstance
Because
Ultimately we kind of want Trump
As the
President
In order to make sure that we continue winning election
I don't care
Ugly self-serving
Opportunistic idea
I think the only good thing about having a president
Maybe
Teaching
Yeah like you know like as long as
He stays in office
Flounder rig
Combative
Child
Like there is an opportunity for people watching it to learn
Because here's what I would say
Yeah
What European countries are older
In terms of their existence
No I'm just
A lot of a lot of them don't necessarily have the same
Boundaries
Because of
Various world wars
How much further
Childish
Country
Maybe is going through growing
Right now
And there's there's one opportunity in front of us
We
Lean into the
Combative childishness
I'm at the night
Or the other opportunities
One of these
Kierkegaard
Did come with your development
Yeah and we realize like
How is a mistake
And everything comes into sharp Focus.
Reaction out that was childish
Beat beat
We need to take everything a bunch more
Seriously
We need to get back on the straight and narrow
And maybe we can move forward from
Like America hasn't survived a white supremacist senile president
Before like we've got a lot under our belt
The same as now
But that's
World hasn't necessarily survived
White nationalist
White supremacist
Denial president
Exactly
Yeah
The world is LA
Like it's unfortunate but currently
The interesting thing is watching the world kind of realize
We Trust America
The order
International order
After World War II
I mean I mean after World War
The EU has had a lot of situations
Of breaking apart
Like this is a regular thing
Like you're a f****** nuts
Jay Paterno
You know it's not the same as when
That's even maybe pejorative
International partners
No I kind of think we're good
We've we've created a situation in terms of the international
Order where's the United States
Power yet so much
Superpower
In terms of
Like
Not control
But
This
We're going to work
Be on the right side
Yeah just in general Hemet
Yeah German
Indicate we're not going to do that anymore
Terrifying because like the world can't do without
But if we become bad actor
Worldstar
Well I mean it's kind of built around the concept that has been
I inflate problems for the last
40 years of life
America's military
Is such
That
As as
Far out is anybody wants
To go if you go too far
America does have old
You know so many guns are
Russians building up their military building up to their military
Increase by tenfold
That still puts them at
1/1000 of the Dumbo
For so long
Even even the people who want to act as Invaders
It's not a World War it's America
Blowing your ass f******
You know
Roll a dice
Understand
I think that Refuge
Bleeding a lot of those places
Yeah
Well I mean they understand it all too much
Now
Is another piece
Puzzle
In terms of
Yeah
Directions
Will do I don't know I didn't work
We're spending way too far
I think we're butting or heads up
Does that like both of us
Stocking fatalistic and we think we do
Tiny bit of light
Dead to rights
New
S*** that he claims he doesn't know and I'm still saying that like
Still being tricked
You don't like it so maybe I'm Dreaming I'd optimist
Isn't born out of America not surviving Trump
Or the white nationalist
Like what
Which is why creates more refugees would only create more nationalist
Separatism
Which is why in the
Memo
That came from the open Society
They were talking about this Refuge
Glocks being
The New Normal because of some sort of like
Desire
4 hey let's fuk up white people brown people
Do you look at the realities of the world and if
Keep going the way they are
There's going to be
Swatches of land uninhabitable
If you want to go
Have to be displaced
Better f****** let them in
You think just think about how people have reacted
Puerto Rican
Oh are you a citizen
America
Government
Elvis
Absolutely
You're like Wonder Woman millionaire
You're not mainland
You were saying
Anyway I know but that was that was a joke
I want to leave you with
A fun
Jake this episode
I would say largely evidence that Alex Jones
The party
Has been
But
Now I have always been a Critic of Alex Jones
Childhood literacy
Star Wars Trilogy in one paperback by dad
I think I actually read that
When I was 7 years old
William
And
My mom's doing
Do you understand that
But
Did you understand
He was just looking at book
Is not
History
Well I mean the parts of history that he's involved with don't go well
No as lot of philosophy
And if you're somebody who's into that
I'm not into you
Also
8 years old
Now obviously that makes me both an interesting person
And
Think I should be murdered
Like
That's what you say to me if you're an eight-year-old who this just furthers my argument that I've been making
Entire goddamn time understand
You studied in for capstan
I wonder if you understood the Star Wars trilogy
Probably not
Yeah he plays The Imperial March all the time on his show
9 years old I read a bunch of
Tintin that my dad
Ridiculous
I grew up in my
I like the stories but
Holyshit
Holy Ship
In the house
Does a child isn't like wandering around going like
Fork with the world like
Crazy
I'd forgotten about it
College
And I was like
Oh no
This is
Also the child
Is no concrete
It's
The problem that we run into
Is the limits of our
Well
Investigative abilities
Insofar as
We have
I think the most circumstantial evidence
That you could ever meet
To convince somebody of
Committing
Tracy
But we don't have that like
By Whitney
Like we don't have that
Prince you know what I'm saying
Well yeah but if you could
Actually get him I mean I suppose if you testified
See you again
Cell
We moved to us
Become lawyers
Pasta Bar
Four years as public defenders that care about that
Yeah
His ex-wife
Is now trying to sleep
Unplugged
What
But if we get
As material with
You know what
Make Alex answers
You can just use bring things up
Alex new stuff
Yeah
A timeline
John Saxon
I love this because
This to me
This is the reason why
He knows people are like
Let me know if you committed
Dude
So what time with just
Screaming
Saying the same things he did
Back before that are less
You could go into the
Much deeper now.
Condo on
Now we're going to
Going to save you
Or whatever
Zenith
Because that's what is
Okay
What's not okay
Is recognized
Dude
You
You don't know it
You do know it
But you might not be aware of it
Your time is
You know what
I feel like this is
I I feel like you're wrong
Based on like the Megyn Kelly interview situation
Where Alex
New note he said some s***
Where he should have been dead to rights
And then whatever it actually came out
There was f****** nuts
Node like eat the same thing though because he under
They're not going to play the clip
There was going to try and make him feel bad by playing good
About that
Give a shilling
He's just going to say like I want to apologize to them for what the media has said about
I want to make it right I want look to everyone lies about Megyn Kelly show
Here's what you do
Now
Beyond
Here's what happens when you do that
Alex will storm out
He won't sign the release
Fair enough
You sign the release beforehand
The f****** video
The way that he was acting about the way that he was afraid
Genuine
It suggests to me that he signed it before
Like he would have been afraid if if he had
Final Cut Alex does not have any fear
But you didn't have any
You're right of approval or whatever it is
Right
He's an inch
She pretends
How these shows are made and stuff like that
But he doesn't really understand it so he
He knows
4 hours
He probably was
On a hot mic
Right
Stupid s*** could be used against
But like
Keno's
Probably like off camera
He seemed
The jinx
Well I probably said something really was f***** up and
They could use that against me is like
That's what he's afraid of on some level not realizing this is
F****** stackery niece
Sunday night show yeah all they want to do is make him look bad about Sandy Hook
But not too bad
Look like he was wrong
That is something that is indicative of a larger issues but not like him
Apps
Solutely
It ruined the entire pie
The whole show was about him
It was not about him
The pre-show
News about him squirming
It works for both
Anyway
In concert with each other like
All kind of know what it is they're going for
They're all combat
Have You Seen Her daytime talk show
Juicy
It was brutal
I don't know I don't know
How it is we're supposed to
In a way that doesn't
Involve like actually putting
Propaganda
In jail
Is propaganda
Never experienced any consequences for their actions
Then it's never going to stop
Because propaganda is only going to get more
Yeah
Information Warfare
4 in
Infowars
Still think
Beheading of
Responsibility
Like because
It's not a crime to lie
Accepting the situation
You're lying about
The building burning
Or something like that
Look dude
Book propaganda should be illegal
Then going to open up a can of worms look like what
Is propaganda
Definition between
No
It's not
It's Logistics
Where where
You draw the line
That's not the same as a slippery
Slippery slope of you like I say this is illegal now this
What you're saying is that
If we are going to start making laws
About property
Then it matters
Who is in
Control
How those laws
Like with
Trump and illegal immigration
Or what well you know
What makes a conversation
Who's going to be president
And over again
Deported more than you know if it's like
Regardless of who's in Powerade
Does matter about how they exercise
That power products
So I so I don't know they say it's a slippery slope argument
The way that
Who the f*** knows if an autocrat is going to become president
That's not
That is 8
CERN
That's not
There are there is a difference between
Voicing of a concern of what
What could be possible in the future
Different
That's like that's like I do this and then right
Before you know it acts
Well it but at the same time we are dear wifey
That means that in the future
The other person can do this because it's
That's not a slippery slope that's just recognizing the future
Also the creation of ice
And the way that we all assumed that Obama was fine
Obama was against from the jump and then he allowed
And then truck is in power and all the sudden that hog-wild that Obama allowed
Weiner
No could get
Worse
Cuz like I think
Just as a person who was out
About
Living the life
I knew that
Ice was
Yeah even another
I would go to open mic
I hear from people
There were
Trap
Yeah
Yeah we're just trying to get
Immigrants
Legal or illegal
Separated
Right
What's going on
Not who gives a s*** about that
Like we got an
No I'm saying is that in Chicago the urban
Enforcement is at 101 West
Is Parkway Chicago Illinois
If
Feel like protest
Feel free to show up at awesome
And laugh
So there's been
Some murders
By the police
Ear Inn
Chicago
Yeah I mean they're always are but these ones are
The Chicago Police Department is a white supremacist organization that is
Willing to murder
We have
Where people are tortured
Police Department
F******
Abolish
And replaced with a I don't know
Community policing or something
But yeah we're
We're overwhelmed by white supremacists
Terrorist
Good time is knowledge
Absolutely
Episode
You could leave a reply
Please share this episode
Because I think the evidence
Uncovered
I think a lot of people needs
What is very clearly
He has knowledge
This is
Probably
Not incontrovertible but God damn close to
It's proof that Alex was aware of trees
Way more very specific way
Absolutely
Your turn. I just don't want
I don't like doing
So are you something right now I'm thrilled to make you
The thing that
Bothers me the most
Early
At least for today
Is that the u.s. ambassador to England
Absolutely lobbied the government to try and get Tommy
F****** Robinson
Released from prison
If I have anybody who should go f*** themselves
70% of the state department
Oh okay
To someone else
I understand
Alright
Well I mean obviously
Play the most
Important
That needs to go
LG styler and profiler in
That will almost certainly
Wind up getting
Go fuc yourself Rodger Stone
Alex