Alex
I love your work
Dan
Summarizing knows what a bit that has run its courses
I would tell them we'll be pulling around a bunch
Tourette
Here we are in the world I don't know how to start this episode
McDonald's
Just a minute ago and
Make me feel like I was running late getting home from
From the appointment to do this show
I was feeling a week from now.
McDonald's
And I feel worse
Destroyed I don't know
I don't know how to get to Baltimore
Moving in the right direction
Kingsley moving and rolling if you got it you got it we got it
Your belly that's why I haven't even
Yeah today
I'm always for the good
I hope I can provide my fingers are crossed
But that will be ready in
Results of it
McDonald's
Something I'm less
Concerned about being great as one of our new donors
Pump it up a little bit we appreciate it thank you so much
Technocrat
Tell her you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Jar Jar Binks
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Support the share button we haven't heard level clip in a long time and a lot of
It's been awhile we had some crap man that is hot
Surgeon
Just feel exactly what was of you know
Almost
Clear evidence of
Notice
Clear notice
Your stone knows a lot more than you
Being forthright about
Especially since immediately after that we got the single greatest
Example of a president being like
About it worry about it
Willow Wood
Grammar police countdown on this morning
Classic
I don't know
Committed a bunch
The world is not responding
Woodside pads
Unfortunately it's not Project Camelot
Carrie
Kerry Cassidy just recently London I believe Oregon England
Happy f*****-up awake and aware conference
Rich
No one needs
To know this was just a conference at weirdos
Not be lying about being in the secret space program
Here's the fun part
Project Camelot was
Clearly a racist alien
Guess what
He showed up
She confronted him about his racism on Aries like yeah but you know what you know what reality is sometimes races
Perfect
Perfect nothing matters nothing
I listen to a bit of god dammit
Stillborn
So I just decided
I found something very interesting in the world of Jim Bakker
Taking a little trip
Down to Pleasant Valley or whatever they're lucky closes
And we we start the show
Something very big
Welcome to the Jim Bakker Show Kung Fu from the village of Morningside Ozark Mountains
Today where's the daughter
Broadcast
Dr. Irving
Easter
I'm your compost Ricky Baker and now most of the Jim Bakker Show in my parents
Baker
Are you coming down or not being there
The Brothers Brewery
Hard to say with these Evangelical Christians could put him at 85
Absolutely
I don't want to start any kind of sibling rivalry or anything like that before
Charisma I would say
I just like how is Jim Baker's responses
Well they don't really have a relationship very
It would be to have to be so transactional like
Everything that they do
For Jim has to be like a
It's going to cost you one year's worth of food
The catch
Very very wild stuff
Irvin Baxter I know that if you are an actual doctor you should not be
Anywhere near this show
I got some thoughts about him being a doctor
Are they are all
No
I don't know how much I want to giveaway
Just right off the top but I will say that Irvin Baxter has no formal education
A real doctor
From an article about him in the Dallas Observer
He's largely self-taught he finished high school but never attended college or seminary
Galloping and preaching his particular version of the end times
In which this massive war will kill a third of humanity
And Jesus Christ will return to whiskeys followers heavenward after vanquishing the Antichrist
So did he get a
Did he get a PhD in
Ivy's write a few books
I think he's easy like a
What's a doctor of theology like to go down to get the
Real srilanka is plans for the end times you know like being a doctor of the all
Ecology is like a you have to go to school
Did you could just get it for my car
Diploma
Let's face it
If you believe in this s*** you but your every meal is it
I didn't do enough that I can do a background check on this guy or anything
Abuse in there
Guessing it's not fair to have a pattern of behavior
I'm not sure that's what it is
A very important pattern
Spoilertv
But also there's other things
That are are like
Guys racist
Controls about sunset
I'm so like I said he is a x guy
Let's not let's just jump in
The two of them should hit it off famously
We are in
Is that right
Dr. Baxter
Hayward
Maybe the end time of the end time is coming
The end time has arrived
We are in the middle of it
Let's thank God
To get to the
Right we are there
You know and
You don't get
Right
Little different plant but
No
Open the word
Even when you
Bass
You teach on the Bible
You know what's
Bear bear
Sarahah
Famous catch
Rejection of premise
Is vacate these are both to post
Trib Rapture guys clearly from what they're saying
Then they would have to that admit that they should have been raptured
And are now
Orders mid-trib Rapture and we haven't gotten to the halfway point believe that
There's mid trap
This is from that article in the Dallas Observer
This is me editorializing before I get to the quote
Seems like this guy's a little nut
19 times in 30 days
He quit his job as an internal auditor to become an evangelist
He studied and prayed all day and preached at night delivering a sermon almost daily for 8 years
He said he was able to identify three Modern Age
Represented by biblical Beast
In the Book of Daniel
England was the lion
United States
The eagle and Russia the bear
But the 4th
Quote I woke up 1 Monday morning and God said go buy a newspaper
Mr. Baxter
He's Evangelical travels found him in a small town in Louisiana and a paper wasn't easy to find
The headline
The mystery
On the front page it said Germany sells leopard tanks to the Netherlands
Germany was the
If you get
This from
Just making it up
I mean just like call the Bible the Book of Daniel specifically pointing out
Lions
Bears
Eagles
And then leopard
Especially especially since
I'm going to go by just
The geography
Add how biology
In the Book of Daniel they would not have had any idea what a leopard
Probably not
Also
Interesting that Germany is not widely associated with leopards
It is just one headlight
Then the writer of The Book of Daniel would have had to know that one day
What's a urban Baxter would be proselytizing in a small town in Louisiana
Equator
Germany and leopards
Who prophesied that and put it into the canonical Bible
Possible
When you know you know that you know that you know
Clearly
He is
And
Is
Brett now Daniel
About leopards
Sure
Mustard
You know you know you know
You know you know when you know
Jimmy's Egg
Your prediction
Antoine because
Irvin Baxter fancies himself a bit of a profit
I don't think he specifically using that
To describe Irvin Baxter
That is
Now that is a in evengelical
Like bulwark
Believe this b******* always comes down to if you start to confront them with
It's like reality I've had my mom and my dad both say you know
When you're you know when you know I understand but he's also talking about Baxter's prediction
Bridging it over to his prediction
Yeah I'm just saying that it's not specific
And it's not like he always
But don't talk about Baxter
So let's
From an article in the religion
Irvin Baxter took a deep breath and surveyed the more than 2,500 faithful
Then
Some current events
Voice to dire
The world's population
Quote two billion people will die but Mr Baxter
Who's fiery oration Sunday at Garland
Connected Homeland Security measure the real ID Act
With Satan plant
Enslave Humanity
Quote we have either just entered or we are just before the beginning of the seven-year period that will end it Armageddon
He said
This article came out
We have either just entered
It is or were the middle
But it could be over
That article came out at 12
Prediction
And is
Anytime you know you know
Explain that away by saying quote
I mean if we find out the Rapture is going to happen
Days would you like us to send you a letter
Good Goodwin
That's pretty smooth
Of course
Because forgot only does snail
Because these guys are always con men
Don't stop calling
It should be pointed out that the contact information card through that people to fill out we're also subscription cards to use magazine
Skype good
I think it's one of those like we get you up for free and then you got a recurring sale
It's weird that it's a $30 a month
Subscription for
4 Page magazine
So he's just
Traveling itinerant
Preacher I don't think anymore
But back in these days he's just randomly going around
Who gets out of town before you realized
What's happened
You still in monorail
Little bit further in the past
And talk about what he
I'd say about the Iraq War
Alright
Article in the Washington Post
Call Sarah lifelong student of Old and New Testament prophecies said casualties will be tremendous
Not only of combatants in Iraq put people in neighboring countries hit by retaliatory missiles of mass
Destruction
An American to fall victim to terrorist
Disarm the portable nuclear weapon
In other and other countries will take the opportunity
Pursue their own interest
China trying to retake Taiwan or India
An all-out assault on Kashmir
Leading to World War 3
He said the results back to Baxter
Conclude could be nuclear Holocaust that takes the lies of two billion people the 1/3 of mankind
Revelation
Constantly trying to work that 1/3
Also
That is not technically a third
Scores from 2003 so far
I also in his March April
2013 and Time Magazine Baxter reported the quote Iran's nuclear program is complete
Citing a quote Source in the revolution
Guards
Intelligence unit
I don't think or talk to him
Hold on
How did you get ahold of this song
I need to know that
I need I need information about that clay
I unfortunately
I was traveling around
Preaching the Lord's word
As the Bible tells me to do in Perrine one more
And God said to me
Fly to tehran's see what happens
So I did and I bought a newspaper
First off
Lotta Love
I met a member of the royal Revolution
I explained
And he was like dude
You have no idea how great the end times is going to be
We're going to start
Perfect
Two possible option
Most likely
Exciting without sliding
Some sort of Republican
And they're making it up and he
Poorly reporting app
Predictions
Regan picknsave that was just a cursory glance
We can see that
You're like it's always
A third of humanity
But it's the context in
Change
About almost everything
Do the same material
3 years if you're going to be an itinerant preacher
So
You might be thinking that he's calling this is going to be the end of the world
Be wrong
Reveal
Kind of tip their hand here a little bit
Got that on the other end of this clip because I make it clear what they're interested in
Watchmore
What is enchantment
Well
I have people
What are you do I see why I'm the founder president I'm Ministries
The backup freeze
And I said no stop
Call Dad
And the beginning of
The kingdom of God
The present government
Are coming down
The Bible says in Daniel
79 I beheld of a Thrones work
And the extra days that's it
4 long
Good politics is bad politics and Squirtle get rid of them all and Jesus
Surprised
Blerg
But like the it is it is important to
To point this out because like the 1000 year reign of Christ on Earth
They're fine with starting that without Christ showing up
Isn't he going all of us though
So if you want a thousand year reign of Christ you have to have the people
With whom Christ is inside kill the rest
And that's how the end
No no no I got would never allow that they have a little bit of a crusade actually go a little bit more
Murdertown guy in the in the Book of Revelations
And the old test
And everywhere that's not Jesus saying please don't murder me
Jesus
I never really thought about it too much
What the end times as a like
Considered until I heard him phrase it that way
Maybe that's the part that I don't consider
By default
Religious
Messaging
Call obvious
Iskcon people Express
These sorts of ideas
Like I said I think
I can't put it better than to say
They're fine starting without God
Define starting without actual Jesus appearing they don't need that part
Bill McDonald make filmmaker
She would ruin it
I think
Thank you to have trouble selling those buckets
I don't think Jesus would be thrilled at the buckets
I think you'd be really offended by The Carter 4
Disorder
Ministry
Yeah
So you know what I'm sorry for sorry
The one the one thing that I really hear now that I I
I haven't for awhile is like
The cuz most people when they're doing the end times Ministry don't do the the second part the Thousand-Year reign
Christ
And I think that's mainly because now we know how long time is
And that's not that long
You don't get a while like back then no it is a while but back then 1,000 years is all of the time that there
Aware of sure sure
3 billion years old 7 years is not that long even if you want to go with us though the Earth being only six
Thousand years old
A thousand years is still not that long what can happen after the Thousand Years
I don't know
Yeah. It only fine with us 6th of the length of time that the
You're putting your finger on that something
It's interesting is the human aspect of these
Supposedly divinely
Inspired ideas
History
Help
But
Impressive
We don't worry about those things
We spell
Battleship
It's so
Jesus
Read another commercial for those water bottles
Do not
Drink the water no
Is the life
The sales going on
Give me the second part of this commercial it's really fascinating that their sales pitch
Is basically
You find yourself going to be helpful
It's great
Find anywhere else
Breaks down at the airport for a couple bucks
Do you need this $80 bottle of water bottle with a filter
In high altitude
What's the problem at all cuz you know he used it on Riverwalk
Mister Fantastic
Scooped up
We're having
Three of these for just my birthday
Free shipping
I mean
You're still a 205 dollar value
For $78
And that's my
My birthday special
But I don't get any of that
That is
All goes
Keep this ministry on the air
But this
Is the king of all bombs
You can take water out of a mud puddle
And filter
And drink it
You drink water out of the Mist
Zippy when it
Villanova
You did out of this bottle
He's obsessed with this river water
Loved
Special but don't worry
Go fuc yourself
Call
To sell those everyday manufacturer price
$5
The Cure
F******
Gulliver
Almost makes me want to buy one
Just like
The blatancy of that scam
Is so
It's hard to imagine me not being like
Listen
You got me on this
I love it
Good call I love obscenely overpriced dumbshit
You can't beat that kind of savings
205 bucks 47
What you going to do I don't know
So what are the things you should know is
Much like all of these
Sort of area into the end times
Doomsday
Pro-israel
He's really into Israel
And of course
Is very celebratory of trump
Change
Empathy
It's all they talk about it here and then I just have a weird thought
Father Kurt to me while I was looking
Episode
We will discuss on the other end of this
On December 6th
I'm sure you know what I'm referring
Donald Trump decided
He was going to recognize Jerusalem
As the Capo
Business
Is going to be there
Oh so quiet
Doesn't run around the world
He's going to Israel
Literally be there on the 70th anniversary
And be there when they open up the embassy
Is that it
Just a thought that I have two thoughts
Jim Bakker sister haven't stopped talking to
Crazy I have no idea
Transact
Everything is transactional
To me like when you have somebody who has had such
The career of like
Manipulation and lies based crime
Bed like a stealer like
I'm going to go I'm going to go to the hangout at Morningview
I'm going to still associate with him at some point say that such a don't exist in a
Meijer on one level
Is it a promise of a lot of buckets of food when the end could be the knowledge
She was there when snipers were shooting
Down there for a nice maybe cracking the champagne bottle
She was actually there when
Murders
Where I continue
Looking for a pallet
It's a nurse
That was the best I could do
The exact nature of the israeli-palestinian conflict
It's something that people smarter than us
Can do a much better job better job than Irvin Baxter
At the dedication of the first temple
God said I will put my name
In Jerusalem
Alaska reasons been more Warriors than any other city on earth
Because
You want your name there
Guess where I want my
And the final war Armageddon
The biggest shoe that I have there is I don't
Like the idea
Like
Petulant
Siblings
Is God and the devil like I really don't I don't I'm not a fan of that
You have a ball in your brother wants it
I don't
Creator of universe
I'm not into it I find it also to be
A profound
Failing
Our intellectual
People like this
With a straight face
You know like
Jesus wanted to put his name here
For thousands of years of war
People dying all over the place
3 Stoopid
You couldn't you can correct me if I'm wrong
Here but what I do appreciate about that
That is very different from
Is that the Greeks had
There was also black especially when you read The Iliad
And the like
There's a lot of Shame for the gods that he has
Where is like
These f****** a****** gods
The Greek mythological
These guys are the exact
Fitbit create
Really really human Gods another like look at how great these guys are
Pissy as little brothers I prefer the Greek version
Re2
Cuz there was a lot more return it into a swamp people back that
Lido
Songs about the Lido Shuffle was about to
Different name sound very close
So I like it whatever your
Knowledge of certain songs and knowledge of Greek theology lineup
No perfect way they only thing I can say
The only thing I can say is that the sign of
This is great
Call Corona
That's really good
I got to find that look up
Coronavirus
Anyway
Speaking a good stuff
Earlier
Irvin Baxter
Is a
Presenting something very stupid
If it's indicative
Kind of knowledge
He's very calm
You know Jim
Twice a year
Christmas
Keep said I won't do this but I do it every time
I'm standing
And like I know the Lord's going to come
Okay
Preserving my spa
Anyways
Is it
If not
Eating you
What the Bible says
This week you don't want to miss
Today but if you want to hear
To pay the bill
My guess knows where Jesus is coming back and he's taking it out for
Festival seating blanket down maybe have a brunch
Little little little picnic
Absolutely
Then
Pivot on your own
And hate guys in order for us to continue scaring about the end of the world
Continue this feedback cycle weed eater
How many very similar to Alex Jones
Experian
Thousands of years of the end times are happening
Now
Christians going to accept
Before they're like
Maybe the end times
It seems infinite
It does kind of seem infinite right
The years that I've been an adult
The weather of
Funeral like II we've gone through this
Over and over
The end times going to happen
Right right thousands of years has said we are living through the end
But some of that might just have to
To do is like a
A lot of these
These Prophets
And speculators
Con man
Being unwilling or unable to
To wrestle with metaphor
Historical context
We're written
Lego bring together books that were written
Hundreds of years apart
History of
The socio-political climate was different
This is what you know there's
Lumos
Well one day
God told him to turn his
TV on
To National
Right and he saw a
And as we all know
Hawks are represent
Chirp
That Hawk
Coming
Ferrari
That's what's going on
We are either in the beginning or
Do you know if you know you know
That last clip was a pretty harsh
Add pivots
But nothing could have
Like prepared me for
Jim Bakker
Accidentally saying something that I think is profound
On-air about his money
Stop
Just shortly after
I have to pay the bill
Fiorinal
TV station
Don't they just give you that time
Some cost me $17,000 for 1 hour
TV for about 50
Seitan everyday
America
I would never be
Listen
Please come true
Like people said I'd never be back on air is like yeah but you're you're paying for brokered
Program
You're peeing to be on of course anybody can be on AirPlay pay for it
Like I'm on all these
But also
I don't think Alex Jones is nearly
Guilty
Time slots are probably broke
Programming on radio station
Windsor
You know like that's all that really likes
Again
The right-wing
Talk radio
This is what like freedomworks
Americans for Prosperity and the Heritage Foundation
Booster careers
I'd like a Rush Limbaugh
And that Glenn Beck in particular Mark Levin
All these people they would do
Embedded commercials
Open stuff like that for the Heritage Foundation
It always talk about how positive there
Their information that was coming out was
And it was because they were buying all there at
They were both stirring them they were buying their books in bulk
To make it look like they were bestsellers
This is
The scams that goes on
This is the next
Level of the media scam
Keyscan behind
The scam
Like Jim Bakker is on are scamming Granny's
You tell them water bottles
Is it like that they'll never know
They're selling unless they go to the
River selling these food
Gates and stuff like that
Super level scam
I meant the business
Behind it
I wish I think Jim Bakker
He probably does have to
You know Pony up and buy every
Still he's making money off
You can't afford $17,000 for an hour unless you are make
Lot of money
I have to pay for all this and I break you
Nope not a f****** turn outage
I'm beat. The other side of it is
The people like the rush
Who
You know whatever their career is now.
15 years ago
They were only in the position they were in because of those
Benefactor
Just like that
There's not very there isn't that on the left
We don't have that evil about it
No but everyone wants to pretend that that's what Soros is doing
Eva wants to pretend that that's what's happening but it's not I know you are but what am I
I8
It will never it will never end
The
The Brilliance of the the right wing
To do the most
Evil ship
And then simultaneous
Easley accuse their enemies of doing eggs
Exactly what they're due
As a way to preempt you
From criticizing them for doing what they're doing
See Rodger
Stone in August
It's
Really
It is awful and that
That's why we lose that's why we lose
Like
Strongco Highway
I'm not even positive how you do it
Necessarily
Really
It's works
They might be
Socialism
Maybe I don't know
The do certain things are certainly beyond our capabilities as broadcasters we don't f****** know
What the answer is we just no problem
There it is look at it
That's the other name of this show. Look at look at them
They're all con men and looking
Look at it
Stare into the abyss
There were similarities
Make this episode of
Very relevant
Do the Alex Jones
That we know
And the topics that we cover for play structure that to Jim Bakker
Expressing I don't think that
Maybe not
The biggest
Parallel I think there's some overlap and nothing I can prove
He's probably dishes
For some of those Channel
War room
But be that as it may
To me is
Like
As a businessman Alex
That's not a terrible idea
We don't know that
I know that you will soon
Like this is like
You might as well have Alex Jones
On the Jim Bakker
The Jerusalem Embassy
Pastor 1995 IR Congress
Which is a half
Move the embassy
Buttery
They put an algae
Security the president can sign a waiver
So guess what 44 time
The presence of sign waivers online
And then
Afraid of the enemies of their afraid of offending
The un's destined to be
A Wonderful World
Actually we're going to go straight directly against
Do you win
V
Because that's serious
The One World Government
I'll just
Is outside
Charter
That just I mean that's just not yelling Alex
And that's why we need
Strong
Nationalist movement
That aligns itself with other name
In order to make sure everybody's nationalist
In a global unified front
Yeah that makes sense
Could it also be
Now I'm going to positive
Could also be that the reason
That the waivers have been signed 44 times
They were aware of the
Mass murder
And
Instability of the region that we
With results
From
That's an interesting Theory
I'm just saying
Possible possible
I'm just saying that it might be that our government has known is real would be willing to murder any and everybody
I want to focus more on Irvin Baxter
He believes in a satanic One World Government
Even further parallels of Alex here in a little bit revelation
I want to talk about something very specific
This guy
It's been making money
That's kind of what he does
That's one of the ways you Stokes up here
So what do you think
Married to you here what do you think about that
The signing of an arab-israeli peace treaty will be the most important prophetic fulfillment
The crucifixion
Jesus
According to the Bible the signing of this treaty will begin
The last 7 years before the final battle of Armageddon
In the middle of the seven-year. The Great Tribulation begin
That's something he wrote
Okay
Now
Little lessons
Sincere when you realize that he wrote that
In 1990
D2
Still got time to be right then
He's not he's talking about the tallest Noah Court
7 years is a lot longer in God
The date of God is a thousand years exactly
The tree will be signed in 1993 is it coincidental that 1993 is 7 years from the year 2000
Yes
As always
Is it part of a con
The article that you wrote goes on to say
We want to send out 1 million magazines in America this month as the treaty is signed
People will not respond
Is that what they do not know this special emergency edition of end time
We'll explain the arab-israeli treaty and its role in Prophecy
The cost of printing and mailing a million magazines
Is $400,000
We're opening a emergency fund savings
All who would like to help awaken America May contribute to this emergency fund
After four issues event time we will have 10,000 subscription
If 10000 people give $40 a piece we could all wake in America
I'm sure all of the
The money in that for
Awakening America
Looking to go to that
Secure
I guarantee that all of the money that
Yeah
Just going to go right back out to the
It's very easy to see through game
Like I said
Much more similar
Alex
It starts in this next clip and it made me
Stutter
We often refer to International Community
New World Order
World community
Hurting this whole world
Then you can control
Every person on Earth
And he intends to control every person on Earth
You know what he wants to do
He wants you
To worship
Him
Instead of you and me worshipping God
He wants us to worship
And he's got a plan to her the whole human race
It's true this one world government
They call it globalism
Oh boy
How fun is that
You know I have
Okay
So
Satan wants everybody to worship
At bright
He wants the balls at
Has it has any ever put forth a good reason why that bad
You mean as God or Jesus before the reason
Yeah or or even Irvin Baxter
If Satan wants everybody in the planet to worship Him
Because he's old scratch
He's a liar but I feel like if everybody agreed
Solo piano
So how is it different if the One World Government Old Scratch
It's still two supernatural beings with
Infinite power
Can do whatever it is they want and we're just
Why would you want to be part of that.
I think if you want it
Look at it from a humanistic standpoint and take the lot of the
Window-dressing away
I think the argument that they would make would have something to do with like God has your best interest in heart
Read the Bible
He does I think he kind of doesn't like
It's case-by-case
The argument that they would make his Vic God respect
Man and
Old Scratch
Just wants to trick
I mean but if he gets what he wants
Why would he continue to trick
Because
Jim Bakker went to prison for fraud
Wait what
What that argument is four or the equivalent of the
The devil getting his way
In some ways because it's the logical fruition of the
Xcamy was pulling
Okay
Keep doing it after he'd already played it outright I would argue him going to prison is not a failure necessarily
A money to meet the day he got out of prison
True no arguments for yourself
Hey Auntie idea that he can't keep
Keep doing it again
Like you can't just like that
I was wrong
Wicked
Stupid pet to me is the devil getting his way
I'm probably wrong about the really not following
Really don't know what to draw
It would be
I don't know why does Alex keep lying now.
Trump's president
More games
Metro
So maybe it's that maybe the devil gets in charge of everything and 90s
And then he would protect Jesus was trying to
Destroy things from behind the scenes
You know it would be something like that
Did the games
We played with lies Never End never end
No that's depressing
Real f*****-up
If you're like
Globalism and globalist
People who are
In alignment with him without
Pulling the whole enzymes
Right
So some of that but not nearly as overt as this
But yeah
Definitely listen
Infowars but I wouldn't
Surprise
Or at least is like in that community
Like that that weird
If you ran into white make
Perfect sense
Infowars a Json so the people that you know
No info ideas made Popular by something Irvin Baxter
Yearly is in
And that's not good
Text Cliff also because a lot of these ideas are based on
Protocols of the Elders of Zion
Course
We get to hear another similarity
With Alex Jones
Am I
017 Republican
All the sudden he starts speaking against
Wait a minute
Good
Speak against globalism
And then he spoke again
The establishment
I need it for 50 years
The same power control both
Republican and Democratic Party
There's a private club in America + 50
What are the Republicans on power or the Democrats
I wonder why
Isis does.
Under
A politician
I can't imagine what would happen
Somebody who's willing to update or perhaps the corrupt
I think every three weeks we have a politician running on upending the establishment
I think this is a good story
For a person
The towels because
Bury the lede of like I heard him saying really f***** up stuff and I was like
He's going to be repressive
I heard
Donald's
Olmec
I've never heard of her
Say that before
You don't want to be the guy going on Jim Bakker Show
He was against the establishment
That you can grab them by the p**** I was
Absolutely
I read about him raping his wife
So
Like
I don't know
You know you have
You have this guest
Jim Bakker
Gershow super into
Real inaccurate end time prophecies
And it turns out he also believes the same
Alex Jones about
Superfund
Hey
Also this is super fun
I don't think
I think that he was a good example of Evan Baxter talkingshit
The Bible actually tells us
September's a great harvest coming
Because we've got these two witnesses you know
Satan has his two ages
Antichrist and false prophet
They're alive somewhere today
Do you know who I am Christ
But these two are on the York right now
Because
He will send his
Two witnesses
They called them
The two witnesses are the two Prophets
Alexana prophesy for 1260 days
And these two
Bistro
Preacher
Powerful
They're going to be at the option to turn off
Sometimes the water will be turned in
Are pass-through turn off water
You know what
What you going to do that's what happened to Flint Michigan
God for a little bit too long Waters oil now
So we got the false prophet and
Impersonate Christ
Right arm in the Falls prophet bolsters
Turn off rain
I don't know I don't like this like superhero match I don't like it this is the worst Avengers movie
Good side
What is the other guy do
The other guys
How deep is Run DMC
All right we got this is this is over
This is a run the jewels you got your Killer Mike you got your lp1
Not the best rapper
The other guys
Spits Hot Fire
Subway ghost
Now we now you're going to disagree with me about LP.
Well that's what a lot of people
Like in these circles believe
Antichrist
Evil
B Pope
He's telling us
Should survive and we shouldn't destroy
He is saying that it's okay
Be a human being and accept other people
And there's only one
Call Abbott
Salt as opposed to the other Pope who was a Nazi
What that was a great talk
The pope who covered up sexual abuse that wasn't the false prophet that was a great Pope
The thing that I love about this
Is that so
It's so Evan backs
Hairstyle to be like
He's very careful not to make these specific predict
Send about Doomsday's
Which is able to very easily
Come up with a couple
Years B you would never be dumb enough to be like I know who the Antichrist messenger is
Is the false prophet
Honest
Listen to
You don't get any cash out of that it's not fun
Set sexy when you're wrong all the time
I love
This level of psycho
Like serial killers
Is there such a bummer
They're fascinating but they're bomber like this level of psychopathy
And sleep so well probably another day in the factory School
People out of money I am good
He probably has left
Concern of like
People hurting him
And more like the IRS
Beer is kind of like know when I'm in trouble
They always think they're going to outsmart whoever's coming after that
So
The only
I had that reinforced
Out of prison
And jumping back into this game is like
All they did to me was put me away for a few years but now I just hang out in a cell with Lyndon larouche
I can do this again the parameters of what's not acceptable I know my limits now
All over again I came in with a
Marijuana and I came out with a bachelor's in
Cocaine or whatever
All this is
Is to say that this is just
Banging the same gone over and over
Goddamn car
Just trying to
This game granny
Out of money
Poor people who've been caught up in the fear cycle
More importantly
Do what there is
Espousing has real-world consequences
And it's awesome
Easy to
To say they don't really care about the consequences just want the money
But sometimes
They accidentally
Depakote
Kind of want to hurt the people that they end up here
So they're like a they're like
First
Bright close second
Remind me
I don't even know but
Ariel
And then
With the next
Video
Is the first
Armageddon
We probably vote
Started
And I'll just
Hit the Hat just a little bit
And that is
And I believe it was November 29th of 2012
The general assembly of the UN
As
A non-member state
Recognized
Join
The world Court
I must have become
The international criminal court
They have the right to file charges against Israel
Put the leaders of Israel on
So this was the first step
Please protect your DVD
That's another aspect of the understand
Are you need to know because
The king is coming back
You know all hell's going to break loose
So
He is super afraid of the idea of Palestinians haven't right
That's a terrible the right of
Recourse
You start giving people rides
We've seen this
Time and time again throughout his
You start giving people rice
Eminem
That is true
The only the only the end time for one thing
But I don't need
It's not even
I think we're probably talking about like white supremacy
It's more than that it's
Cuz it's not just about what
Minority-majority
System of Oppression South Africa
People and then being really pissed when 90% of the population
They aren't we human beings
No
No interest in the status quo being equitable
Wrong can have
Recourse other than
Protesting in getting shot outside a wall
So
Cool we let them have their protest
I didn't do s***
Do whatever they want
Do what thou wilt
Take me to rule the world
Aleister Aleister Crowley was Aldi version Satan a 3L bottle of Coke
Satan
Play One More clip
Another parallel cuz the other day when we were doing an Alex Jones episode
I'm have that guy stand Deo on
Fundamentalist
Caldera in Yellowstone was going to blow
But then also saying a bunch of
Flagrantly races
Stop
Because that's all I know.
Jim Bakker
A new headline about Yellowstone
Is the Yellowstone volcano eruption
Reddit can you read that the world's major black
Million
Eruption could kill scores
The people actually million
Rocky kanaka
Disrepair travel even threatened
Peace
The world
Unprepared for the next major volcanic glass
Scientist say
So terrible
This next
Could very well happen
In your life
Goodreads
Brand new story
Today
How many people
Do not stay quiet for a long time
People killing people doing all kinds of crazy
You're going to want a bucket food
They're the ones who are going
Be prepared
And they're going to be Soul winners
At the time
It is short
We're sending these
And where
You sent a gift
$60
We're sending you
You have
The Americas god-given
Destiny
Most people think
America doesn't have much
Really I haven't seen this one yet
Be like Israel
Comedy is at the end
I haven't
60 bucks I'll send you four of them
Got to do it
You know I don't like that money mode
Right around the corner
Atwood
You knew it's b******* because if I understand the volcano under Yellowstone correctly
That is an extinction-level event
If it if it erupts
It's going to kill the planet
Baby Alive
LiteBlue
Like that's going to f*** everything up
Estimates say that I don't know
The definite thing or sort of a
Worse than
Next
2 worst case scenario
I think I think regardless it's like a climate change in your phone
You know
Like and all the stuff that he's talking about climate change is already doing as we speak like people are
Absolutely
Displacement
Leading to increased nationalism which ones have leading to Wars
Caesars
And respect the outcomes when it's presented
You as a science fiction movie premise
Like Yellowstone blowing up
Spirit really happening in the world around you
Whatever
Sing the thing that I
Notice
Most as far as a parallel
Baker and
When you go down to the lowest levels
The blue stuff
It's.
And what bums
Doubt about that
Christian
Are like
Well we would never be taken in by that
You mean like out
We would never adjust Dominican Republic we would never be taken in by
You just go up 11 with the same f****** scam and they're just better at it
Go down all the way to the bottom and then you can extrapolate do this whole thing is a f******
These guys that were looking at all the time or the desperate con
Exist
Either tricks
Very easily
On higher level
Absolutely
That's the contention that I hold very strongly
To me what's fascinating is that there
Think I would be
Wave
Better off with myself if I was taken in by like a really good,
You know like the best
Con man
There's no shame in that
You know you got taken in by the best
Going to get you still good
Would be better if I could call it would be better that it be a good one
You got me
When you're taken and Christians are are pissed off about what and that's why they can't get back
Is because they keep they get to look down on people
Taken in by the
Cuz it makes them feel better about being taken in by a better comment
At least I got a better one
Stupid for the comfort of the con
To hear the bark
The conman isn't just offering you a way to get rid of money they're offering you a presentation
So for like
Jim Bakker
Minions
Maybe not his supporters
People who
His minions are his children they get fake food out of it
Time to get the comfort of checking that off the list
Right in reality there's probably no need for those buckets ever if they're gross
And you don't want them
The fact that you have them in your home get rid of some sort of in
Insecurities that
Created in
MSN way that Alex Jones
Because the world is so scary
And so can
Fusing
He is able to
Contextualize the world
Adolescent
The people are really like it gives you a comfort if you
You think that all the world is this one group of people who are messy
Things up
Trying to get us all to fight with each other or whatever because I want a One World Government
Strapped whole thing
That's much easier than being like now man there's Rogue agents all over the place people are selfish
People often miscommunicate thing sometimes
Things happen by accident
You know that there is
That's hard to deal with because
Chaos of it
Leaves you with
Anon
Really verbal anxiety because I never going to be able to know all of it so if you
Berryville
Blah blah blah
Your house offers
And that's that's the part of me that I think
Open up part of me that's a part of this that I find the most
Gross
Is it
Anxieties in order to relieve them
The hegelian dialect if you will problem reaction
Solution on are on a psychological level they are offering that to their listeners
And the solution is always money
Always the queen to get might give us money
It will either give you a thing or we'll fight the globalist for you
And that will solve your problems and you can go out your life
Bright
You are taking
Arrows but still be afraid of not white.
Because they're usually up something Soros is paying
To be mad at you
Bruno's I am
The
Fears that they have of the mm
Like the
The devil
Like all of those things
Light
It is interesting to me
Cuz
The real
Reality is so much of this s*** is
Actually just psycho
Does not have the ability to feel emotions
For other human being
He is a
True psycho
Hey what's up
His daughter
Like so many of you know they do that they do the surveys and all that
Like what is the highest
Is possibility of finding a psychopath
Go to work
What is the highest place where you can find psychopath
Go to d.c.
Like all of these places of power we're stuck
Psychopath Kongregate
In order
To f*** you over
Getaround
Squeeze just a human being
That is a psychopath
As opposed to an actual malicious devil taking over and imbuing them with a psychopathy
Kernel of Truth
Extrapolated
People like Alex in order to
Create this vision of
A team of psychopath
Like this idea that yes, power is Blake recycle
Congregate
Except which
I mean it does make some sense if
If you don't
Really understand housing
Like if there are a ton of psychopath they get together and psychopath together
But generally they
Kimberly work together all that well
Generators going
You don't usually see serial killers working as a tea
The Army that's very very rare
Examples of
You have the hillside stranglers
There's way more loan for that is generally people of that mental
Frame
Don't work well with others
So they can be type A and
Focused
Driven enough
To the top of the business world
Like crushing other people to get up
Stuff like that idea of all banded together
To fleece
The rest of the world challenge
Say is what they're doing
Is just
Psychology work
Is I would really prefer that if it came down to
There would be two Psychopaths
Who
Who are fighting against two Psychopaths
And some of them
Could turn off the ray
Exactly
Bible songs question who will stop the rain
Who won of God's messenger
You're welcome in a purely punitive way for no reason
For not respecting God enough
Yeah if there's a
REI
Really really that's one of the things that I really
Wish
Is that
People could
Get past that
Primitive
Reactionary
Idea of
The way to solve things
Punishment
Like
Even if got a God's messenger
Their plan
Is to f****** punish people who don't like
Is built into that the hard right
Evangelico b******* is like
Of course poor people shouldn't have money
They need to be punished for being poor
To get over the poorness
Makes perfect sense
That's the same f****** idea
Oh oh course these people aren't acting the way God wants
So we kill them
We don't kill them but where we celebrate that they got killed
We don't want to have the agency of it they were thrilled
The result
CB Express
That's gross
Engross
Regarding Palestinians
I think that's what I said
It's not that's what I meant
Alright
How much they hated it whenever people had right it's almost like they had a financial incentive
So anyway
Eclipse
I don't want to come up person I don't care cuz I
To obvious
There is only one
Ricky Baker
No I'm going to go with Jim Bakker sister what are you doing lady
Oh okay I forgot you was in this yeah
She was in Israel has unknown sister
Alexandra Thurston color