Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
What up
What's your favorite
My favorite drink is probably cranberry splash Sierra Mist
The seasonal
Variety that's only available during the winter months
It's delicious
Just crisp enough
Enough cranberry flavor to get you
You threw those ponies Chicago Winters
That is
Infuriated
Furious
Oh no
For some reason
Your favorite drink
See I'm a simple man with self
We Are Who We Are
Comedians in Chicago
Very popular open mics in shows
Chicago can take ownership of Jameson and Ginger
Take ownership
Cinderella
I know only what you tell me
That seems fair
Like to give a shout out to a New Daughter
Appreciate it though so very much so Jeff
And tell her you're brilliant
Bank of
So you can do so by going to our website
I am going
Victor homepage
But
Check your shoes
Show me to handle as
Is an engineer
Now that the transition
2002 r2009 investigation
Last we left off
We found
Alex Jones
Going through a Cavalcade of stories about asserting their sovereign
There were a number of states
Tried to push through Houston
Concurrent resolution
Allowed
The number of those bills and saw that they died in committee or never got voted on
Just worried
Working at whatever just left alone
So we don't need to go over a lot of that if you're interested in that please go back to our last 2009
Episode where we cover it
I only bring it up because it's very rare
Where we pick back up
February 12th through 16th is we're going to cover here
Alex is in what I can only describe as a
Terrible holding
He cannot get off this story
Really this story is the biggest f****** deal in the world
Right cuz he's hoping it's
Secession 2.0
Exactly during the course of this time. They were going to go over has one of the house
Represents about how
This is
So even there's a little bit of a miscommunication
Him and that
House representative
Starting to believe
That investigation
All cards on the
Table to find out what Alex was at the beginning
Of the publicized nation of the Tea Party
And I'm secondary to figure out when
He starts talking about George.
He's looking into in 2009
And I believe that this story
We discussed Isaiah August is one of Alex's
2009 episode
Might be a
Shoot Steel
Okay might be very very big piece
Of his transition
Turn towards the Tea Party
Reserving judgment
I think we're going to talk about the story again
But we want on this episode because
All of it
So I'm sitting here listening to these episodes
Something out of this
He's just it's like he's in syndication
10th Amendment
He's like great Seinfeld on at 9 every night
Fine
It's it's
Along those lines
I can't
We had to do a show
The 12th is mostly that many is Mark Dice on to talk about the Illuminati in
Enchanting
I don't even want
Illuminati
Because I
Not interesting at this
He will become enter
A little bit later
Down the road
Five star
Early on whatever books
Not trying to trick people
Wearing flip-flops
It is current
State
Evolve
What state
Let me consult my notes here to talk about
Stuff we're not going
So he does
Is Big everyone stopped traffic
Because I got a big thing coming up
That's a fun time. I wish you could bring that back
Is that is no fun now screaming like everybody
Tell the person in the car next to you
I agree with whatever the president does cuz he's too worried about self-driving cars hitting advanced
Narrative trying to build up his this idea that
FEMA is going to find places to dig up Mass Graves cuz they're going to turn on America and all the
Search
Find places this is all about
Who's the guy who wrote
Something on a Blog I'm not sure exactly the website
Whatever
Just a guy with a Blog
Conservative journalist
I don't I don't know
I'm not sure
He is a guy who interviewed a whistleblower
Audio is
Come out
Quality is terrible and it's
Just like I can
Going to tell you what he says
No because
Like 12
Rex's already contributor
FEMA organization
And that they got us some like local
Local organization
Noxzema
FEMA called them and wanted to know where power plants are where police stations are
Where you could make a mass grave that sort of thing
Aggressive way to start
I'm not sure I 100% believe this guy's story
All this stuff
Sounds like
Exactly what the
Emergency Management agency might be into
You consider the possibility
Outbreak
Disasters natural disasters
There's all sorts of benign explanations
To know where power plants are
Wanting to know where resources are where is hospitals
Where where are your like triage centers that
On the off-chance
Fix bad breath
So we don't run into situation
Seems like we had
In Las Vegas
Other
Mismanaged
Situation
It could just be somebody who's actually a white terrorist
Because that seems like something they would want to know is
Prank call
I don't know
My point is this
Is this whistleblower does not blow my mind
It's not worth stopping Alex spends a lot of the show talk about that
Is important
Forgetting.
Superman
The man
Who made a lot of money off golden South Africa
The only reason
I even
Only reason I want to include this clip
Because Bob makes very weird offers Alex
Extended clip
Instant my survival Instinct
There's nowhere to nowhere
Operation
Because
Interested the nightmare could all in
It's so horrible
It's my 50th year in this
Believe me like believe you I've been there
And incidentally if you want to hide your kids
I'll hide them
So it's not even that
Very weird Bob
You want me to send me a kid's Alex
Couldn't get up kids
Alex you want to hide you
I will make sure they are never found it
Maybe that's just
I know it's probably in their world a nice offer
Yeah it's one of the nicest things
I love you so much I would hide your kids
Make your kids the most
Appearance
Used to this sort of Alex
In present day
Because of the times where Steve pieczenik is come on and Alex's had to get therapy from him or Jon rappoport
Times have to talk Alex back to life
Half an hour
Just complaining to Bob
Just like
Shipyard
Lip lift
There is a slight difference in why they left a y Alex needs to leave America
NY Bob actually left a mare
Bob left America
Well no.
Fake running away from 2009
You. That was in his past
Pre apartheid South Africa
I thought you was I thought you was originally the states
And then
No he was in those African countries
Then he moved to United States and Canada
Where he lives but I don't think you went back to spell pepper
I don't I think of his life
M27
Oh yeah because it would be burned alive
A tablespoon
Not wanted
Either way dead or alive
Realizes
S*** there's a reason I have bobcat
Chapman on
I think you're right but we've got together to
Enough people
Publix
But also is you say Lauren Foresman
And we got to make the money
Forecast for.com
Kiss you
You better I would think that was intentional like Alex's better joke
What is a joke
In the middle
Toto Toilets
Excuse me sir I would like the soundtrack
From Beverly Hills Cop
Please
There's a middle of that conversation
What the f***
Complaining to you for half an hour time is valuable obviously
You need to sell gold so are we get
I assume it is I don't know
Tokyo
Think they get back from break
And Alex
Start
And I know they talk about how great
The Ozark
Number so great
Are they
Everytime bobcat
Fantastic
Absolutely fantastic
What the thing about it is Bob I mean if I can get in here
It's Not Over
It's a great
Why is Ted Gunn
It's fantastic
No cuz he won't know how
Does any goes into a long thing about
Fire-sale prices on gold
Because I care about you
Still don't understand this
This whole gold business
We've been doing this show
Anderson has been Hawking
For the entire show
Understand how deep
F****** s*** works
At a lower cost
What it is now
And then he sells you gold at the cost that it is
Because then it's going to get more
So how does this f****** business
Haha
If you get getting this from
Is this what is this is this flotsam
I don't understand
Do you want to know the truth or the stand
I bought this gold when it was $50
Yeah always 85
I'm going to sell it to you for 75
Even more profit margin exactly
How is that not already like
Wait so you're telling me a business is telling me something so I can make more money than that business
Capitalism
Emirates in reality
He might have the Specter price
75 dollars an ounce
But there's all kinds of like brokerage
These hidden cost
Those sorts of things that bump it up
Some people who've done business with you end up with
$95 an hour to post
Do the 85 but it's worth
How to get all the hidden behind the stand
No matter what the price is your paying more for it
And then also the people who work for
You actually
Individually
From all the reviews that I've read they also do like
A lot of like well if you want to if you want to sell it back or probably only going to be able to get 65
Score
Old people's gold hostage
Tow lot of these
And precious metal operations that are very
Reputable Opera
And the people who helped get you in the door
Stirrup mouth
Salesman
Is there like a real gold business
I assume so I don't know what it is
Let me know I think they're like reputable collect
I don't know
I would assume that most of the if you want to make a profit off precious metals most of those people probably ski
But if you're already rich
Here's one
Collectible coins
I think there's probably a lot of reputable in that world
I cannot get past the idea of gold bars to this is what
Really frustrated over those mostly coin bullion and all this
I want to have a stamp
You look into gold bars
Right
Call Bob
We got Bob Chapman
Friday
May 13th
Alex's kids
I'm at score Saturday
No show
On Saturday
Alex being petty as Hell by Barack Obama
Target his first clip I just like
What are you doing
What are you
Doing
This is a in response
The bailout bill
Has been discussed and then Obama went on vacation
Over the weekend
Show
On hold
For the Obamas weekend off after pushing Congress for weeks
438 holiday getaway
Obama arrived at the home in Chicago on Friday and treating his wife to a Valentine's dinner downtown last
That's sweet
The couple was spotted leaving upscale
Specializes in southern cuisine
For the First Lady
Tuesday weekend
In the windy city Amazon expected to sign the bill until
Why did you say doggy bag with seriously why is there a drug
Furthermore
Irene
I understand
The desire to be
You're the first lady you don't need left
I like to imagine they gave it to
Really like
Already got everything he needed out of it to be like Kathy 100 bucks we went to a nice red
Restaurant
Freebird
Finish for me
Specializes in
Is it Southern to f****** dog with
Down home country food no
You don't
Especially
So weird
Here's the other here's the reason I think we don't hear about
That
Like we don't hear about Trump's vacations
Except from
People who are like
This is his 7000000 weekend consecutively playing golf at one of his properties
They are paying for
He is committing a violation of the emoluments
Emoluments clause
On a regular paper
Restaurant
Whenever he takes a vacation
Because that
You won't do anything
Sing f****** to he's going to do some stupid
Do you know Trump just announced that he was going to sell Florida to Russia so
Thank God we got a couple of days off
I think I
Tweet and we'll all just
Pretend
The president Ray Ray
To go
Get a Putin look-alike
Just like looking go at this
Benign
Example of a presidential
They went to an upscale restaurant
Obama also it's Presidents Day weekend anytime a president
Should be able to like go home this weekend
Literally
One person even allowed to stay it's Presidents Day it's classy
This is just forever
Super crazy
You get weird about on
Episode
So
Weird to live in that way it's so weird to live be back in 2009 where
President
Took his wife out
For a very sweet
Valentine's Day
140 thousand dollars through a fake lawyer to
Pornstar that
Cuz he didn't want the story to get out
Stop
Almost during his wife
When everybody's we're just we're just living in a world where it's like
Sure
This is just how we live now
Back then it was so amazing all he wore a brown suit
Hot dog
So also
Plane
At least according to Alex is very serious
So a 9-11 truther
Was in a plane to crash
These things have
Yes
Alex
Would have you know
If it was no coincidence
Obama remarks on plane crash stimulants you can pull up the video that's on YouTube
Real quick
To he's talking about this situation with
These are dark bomber
Statements
Here's the tax present Obama this for the washer
Tupac
What terrible tragedy took place outside of Buffalo last night
The families and friends who lost loved ones
And as always our Thanks goes out the brave First Responders who arrived immediately
Legos on tragic events
Other fragility of our life the value of the end of every single day
One person has stood
That will
This is Jim babbling
No perfect
One person who stood that well
Was Beverly a card
Who was on that flight to do I met
With just days ago
Is she Beverly lost her husband on 9/11
Tireless advocate
Forever changed
On September 11th day
Of course she knows Hillary Clinton is a high-powered Democrat she was
She dead now
Shell there is that report
Right there very very suspicious
Someone who lost
Husband
Call 911
Yep
I win someone who I just met with the president with someone who just died in the plane crash in
She was a 9-11 truther and it is billions 212
I want to go I want to go to Pat's
Trips it's billions
Conceivably true but it mean if you just
Takeout
A bunch of variables
Bodies life
Like you and me doing this episode of the podcast
Extrapolate out like
Someone who lived in Hawaii versus someone who
Podcast with someone who was born in a cult
And neither of them died on 9/11
Unlikely thing
But it does happen like that.
Because there are certain
Aspect
That are like
But don't mean it that doesn't mean it's official
Also I imagine
Who fly places
Physically sooner or later one of them was going to go down
This one just happened to be somewhere in the proximity that
Was close to the president met with Obama
Days before
Which doesn't
A 9-11 truther was allowed to me
Who was the president
But
She's not as much of a 911
Truther is Alex
And Morrison
For the family
Yeah
I think that's probably more
And I think that you probably more of an investigation
As a member of his kind of 911
Organization
Maybe an actor
Yeah I don't know enough to say but that's what we got
But who cares
Alex
Cannot make Obama
He wants
Trying so hard
And it talked
Pikliz trying to like do all these different things
But if you just listen to the words you like
Oh yeah that's a bit
Sentence he's a good writer he's got speechwriters he's
Yeah he's doing a good job.
Taking time out of a press conference at the start to
Spell comment on something really sad that happened in pay respect
I don't know
Most of the rest of the show
Is just a lot of that
Lot of lot of talk about that
Alex
Good to reinforce
Alex Jones
Opinions
Or not
Consistent with what you would believe in
Pro-gun control group
They're there to neutralize and control gun owners
Control group
So he's
He's pretty anti-nra
What's going to end up happening
He's going to say that the NRA
At some point it became more lunatic
They got wild
Controller that was
That's that's
That's just because he's super in with Larry Pratt and gunownersofamerica
As we pointed out on our route
Sacha Baron Cohen
And I knew.
By being
Wonderful
Absolutely
The show
Tristan it
But you know what
It's therefore
In front of my position
Like
I don't like it
What why do you
I guess I get the outlandish things like
We're going to arm children
I don't wear outlandish because
What they're saying now seems like it
It should have been enough
You know what is what they say
Getting one entrance for schools
So why do you need to go further
Well yeah window is gone so far that you have to
Isn't it you might as well have to be
I always ridiculous a better way to do this as a parody is
Like put it out as a serious show and never say that it's a
Something like that
Just like
Is they would probably promote it
Oh yeah if it was put out as a serious he never realized it was
Because they didn't realize it was a prank while it was happening
Yeah that would be
Great
Is he dead
I don't know
We do a pure we do the exact same show
But with Ted Koppel
You're right
It would crush in the
It wouldn't
They wouldn't
Be ashamed
They wouldn't say they were tricked they would promote it
That idea
The conservative Wrightwood tucking love it
Most likely
But just like those just like those politicians we're like
Yeah let's on your arm kids if we put it out as a serious show conservative be like
Why haven't we already armed
Possible
Oliver North could do a commercial for that right now even after
The
Joke played by Sacha Baron Cohen and most of the conservative right if not all would be like
That's actually a good idea
I know it was a prank show with the tummy does not good ideas
We're going to cover on the 15th
Who cares we gotta move along
He's really just talkin about that state sovereignty
Most of what he's doing in this time
And I need to get out of this like
Stretch of a couple days
So
Through and I look forward to
Further episodes that
Don't
Have as much
To do with this goddamn
But I think I'm going to hear a lot more about it
Yes
When we get to the 16th here
February 16th 2009
Alex pivot
It's the narrative a little bit
To start the show
Not talking about the states
The are declaring their
Their sovereignty
How many days it take him to get there a while but at least
Appreciate it's a difference
You know
But at the same time
Kind of scary
No no
Extension
Long pause here
They are actually selling out
International organizations
Reports that out what he's getting at is that
Doing these at
How's compare resolutions
We know from living in the
Which is
The future 2009
A lot of those didn't pass
So they are failures in defending the Republic
In what way
Could have state declaring
Sovereignty
Be considered defending the Republic
Wow it's big
Find me any explanation
Besan Alex's
Alright he believes that the federal government doesn't really exist because it's
Been taken over by the global
Right
Any point in history if he's not happy with who's in charge of the federal government
Exist to what he wants
Yes at this point 2009
Is very specifically secession
But
It's the suspension where state to start their sovereignty dissolve the federal government
I'm in Bring It Back Together
He's weird paper version of a federal government
Necessarily involve some level of
Global involvement it would still involve some some level of
You know supremacy clause has
In terms of the piano
Murders illegal everywhere
America
On paper
So like that
Is his idea is
Who's awesome thing where
Are you break up the union then bring it back together and its original better form or whatever
It's the same problem that a lot of these
These idealists
That have idealistic utopian vision
That are really regressive
They're really point back to a bygone time they don't realize that in order to get
To the starting point of their Utopia you have to
To create hell
And also
The odds of you getting
Through that hell to reach your ideal place
Is almost 9
And along the way the people who are going to
To be hurt or the people
You don't have any
No it makes perfect sense
That's right
We have
What would you say
2030 decades
Complete and utter chaos
As the world Burns
Right
But that
Fix it
Sure
I don't I don't like
I understand
This is what he thinks is going to help everything and get rid of these
Demon globalist
Littering charge of everything
I look at it from
Just a little mystical
Ghost
Dia of
Like we talked about this before I don't understand why you
You think you don't understand this
Don't forget to go
I forgot know we talked about this it is like
You can make this sort of rhetorical argument about I want
To dissolve the federal government in order to
To have us all come back together under a better federal government
What you're really advocating for is
You don't want
Like
You don't want the
You want a different
You want a thing where
You know
Say they want
It's not
It's not that simple but
You know that is a part of
You know it it is a part of it
We don't want everyone
For people that sort of thing is
Dumb federal regulations that are ruining the free market
End up with is a bunch
States that are going to be able to agree on anything
Investigation are you end up creating
Two different countries
That you couldn't possibly create because we
Contiguous states that would be on the same
So what you'd end up with is probably
Four different countries
With two different ideologies
Yes and all you would do is
Complete power imbalance in the world you created
Zester is foreign policy state
Hilarious
Randomest
Even forget about where we are in the present
The worst
Worst possible
Policy level
Going to happen next
Italics
I know that he's not that stupid
I don't think he is that's why I think there's a
Right you have to act like he doesn't have those thoughts and realize that you had asked us going to become
Stand-alone
Country theocracy
Where we can
Kickoff
You know what he doesn't realize this is most likely what's going to happen
You can go back to gay bashing
I don't know these damn wheelchair ramps that I have to build it in for no reason
Don't have any minorities working for me
I don't have to feel bad ever again ever again for being myself for being
Why do people not like the
That's the real issue
I just want to be white
And I
Never want to see anybody else
Well
Are we move along and we get to
Too familiar to us
It's been a little while
Through taking a road
And there's going to be long
But I think it's necessary
Because let's have a
Positive
Moment with Alex before
Horrible s*** on this episode
The way
Out of kind
Freebirds
Breadtube
X
Macabre on the song is done
Merle Haggard
That's fair
It's so hard
Atlanta
Cheap hotels
Cleveland pool
Merle Haggard
Live
After
Out of
So we're back live
Love it
Personalized love that song like mxon World Haggard sounds like if they made a muppet of
Skaggs
Dreads
I would love the way you lie
Like that hole that's good stuff
When you go to karaoke
Do you could not
Go through the night without
At least three people singing God damn if you don't call me by my name
While they were saying you did anybody
And by the way they have weaponized dogs we'll talk about that after the end of this song
Vietnam flashback level
Visceral reactions whenever
Since I left Missouri
Alcoholic
No I couldn't do that
Karaoke bars on The Fringe of town
Hillbillies
Can't do call and response I'm not talking about
I'm not talking down on the good folks
The Roadhouse karaoke bars
What a great country Folk
LA tonight stricken
Sloe Gin
Spurs
Scuba Steve
I beated to do that
Because first of all I love the song
Because I
Alex doing his
DJ
A couple times
But give us a story like
They're going to kill the internet
I also we need that
Because we are about to get into like
Alex being a mom
Absolute monster
How to patent
Soy
He takes calls
Hermosa
Sure
Is telling him to
He woke up
Thanks to some
Infowars and Luke rudowski
Dvideos
Conspiracy type
Videos
Then
Something to this guy
No one should
Ever
Say to some
Like
Termite down
You're going to scream but the
But
On the other end explained
More in-depth what I mean
Real quick just because I was a little muddy that I try and tell
The closest people to me
I'm crazy
Talking about
About what
What's going on and stuff like that
Occult
I lost a girlfriend over this question
Trust them
If you
Yeah it's like the Matrix when they tell you try to wake somebody up
All the evidence
And everything and
Do the double stick
Yeah a lot of times I don't have no respect you sir they don't respect you
The next
Devil
Credibly irresponsible
As a thing to say
Is like
You know he's saying that
My family says I'm in a call
And then
He goes to the leader of said called who says
At least I'm not
I'm still check it out
The most out of life
But at least he is still saying like
Not like ice
Too late yourself from them
Use your craziness on Strangers
Like maybe they'll listen to you
There's a way to say that without saying your family and friends don't respect you
On the other
If
I had a family member
Who started telling me about
I would respect
I think it's possible to respect them and not respect
That part of
I think there's a
There's still
Familial love
They probably exist
What Alex is doing
Trying to shut that down
Trying to make it like your family's actually
Well if you don't if you
What you don't realize
We don't realize they already don't like you
You know who does
Infowars
This is a family
And then you got a new family
Old family what is it what it what do they want
What do they want
Healthcare
That's what the guy is talking about
Do you know I just told them I don't trust
The government
You're mad at
Because that's what Alex has to present as like that's what I'm responding
If anybody
Remember sound of my voice
A liking it hurt you in anyway
You know you became so into it it ruin the relationship
Stop listening
If anybody ever came to me with like hey I like your show too much
People think I'm crazy I would say
I appreciate that I'm glad you like the show but
It's not worth it you have a life
Repair your relationship
Try and get her back tell her that you're sorry
Tell her that you know what
Even though she is an infowarrior yuca
Concealed lover it's about what's inside
You know they used to say what did that one Republican
Wife
And how did they make it work a Democrat and a Republican
Imagine if we had a policy walk ended info Warrior relations
Ridiculous if it does exist out there
Cyril
You be very clear which side was the bride and which was the guru you know
You just look at the clothing
How many Hillary for Clinton Clinton for prison shirts
We would still play The Highwaymen
Doesn't matter what side you're on everybody loves the Highway by
So that was really terrible I heard that nosey
Alex
You need to know what your
You can't
You said it twice to him
They don't respect
That's f***** up
But if you want to be like really generous
That's at least
Stoves
Lake
Not intense
How to drive a wedge
Between his listeners and their family
It's so irresponsible
Reliable the like you shouldn't be you should be on it
What is borderline you're listening to call into a radio show
Activate your really really depressed
You're talking to this radio host and the radio says is all the sudden like
Well you know what
Maybe p
People don't like you
Who has been apart of
Stefan molyneux
Colt
You know he doesn't like to call it back but
Cult leaders rarely do
Abusive people out of your life and then defining of those who don't agree with my philosophy
Exactly you see that sort of thing coming out here now it's and it doesn't happen all the time
But there was enough instant
Pictures of things like that but you like
Alex
Stop it
Stop
Look at that.
Let's get that out of our mouths
Willis
Food
In school lunch program
The children crash
Didn't last long
Listen to the entire Eastbound & Down
Baby episode
It's f****** full
I didn't include the last one but he does also sing along with that
The unknown stuntman
Ridiculous
At the end there
He's getting into what's going to take out the next couple of clips
And that is
His idea that they're putting
Coke and Candy into the school food programs
To get your kids
All jittery and hopped up on the standard that they get them on pills
Which
Flies counter to most of Michelle Obama's initiative
2 / 4
What's healthier than
Coke
Who you going to trust
A little too much English.
So that is like alright Alex if you want to start down that path
You're getting into what
Call
Slightly dangerous territory
Because
You're not a joke
Doctor
But you know I understand there's a lot of conspiracies out there
This is where you wanted it
Spend a little bit of time on your show
Heaven
Let's see where he's at
What happened
Sugar
Is there not playing sports few hours a day
Girl your class
Meet you at the movies
You're walking home
That is your power
Does your soul that's your mind
Your glands giving you the real drugs
So he's starting off his self his first Salvo that is that
Mystique
Normal human stresses with people who have chemical imbalances in
You know cycle
Logical
I don't want to call it problems or anything
Do people who have
Siri
Okay
He is a syphilis
Alright
Because as We Know
Brightly
Is how you go to the dark side
Is JoJo f****** get past that in the liver Beyond
That is exactly what it said Lord would say
I have opened
Jordans
SLK
I would say is it all he is like you just goes on today like
I don't know if you want to be like
That's a good.
Go to be with your young kids are trying to give to Bob Chapman
Obviously,
Although I think he does believe in
I think this part he does believe
Like the
They give you is like
Ritalin is evil like all of these
And all that stuff I think he believes that
He's not conning people on the
I'm willing to believe most of it
He's a
He's working with con people don't let General stubblebine
He's genuinely again
Any kind of
Prescription
Right
Well I mean
Know his Christian Scientist
He probably wouldn't say this about like it
He threw out his back
Copious
They
Concern
Like psychiatric Medical
Because
I think rightfully
They've recognized
Is that a lot of
The people who
Salt Lake fall for their con
Happened to be people who have psychological condition
A good way
To keep people in your tent
Keep them on Medicaid because when they're on medicated they're more likely to have
Parents more likely to isolate themselves from their family like he advocated that other
There's all sorts of ways that you can get them to be more in your camp
And I don't think that is a coincidence
It is 8
Front of the brain active process where he's like
I need my audience
Do not get healthier because if they get healthier that leave me
Or is it
It's just something that he subconsciously
They understand
And so he's made that
Apart of his
Worldview possibility
It's just
A really easy way for him
Come up with a white scale thing that use blame the club
Now there's another aspect to it where you just consequences better really give a s***
Well he's not Hawking
So he's not right now he's not replacing
Okay cuz the end of in the presence of course he's going to say don't take
Medication B
Because Superman
In the future
I don't I don't think I
I don't associate
This level of it with the present
I'm hesitant
To put it up on our board as a
Major
Put me in the past
Present
So it would serve as a giant
Different
Can being alright with pharmacology
Like that in the present
Crazy it would be strange
I think that he would never go as far as he ends up going
On this episode and oppressor
Strap it in Jordan
Because you're only alive
Put your foot down on the pedal brakes
Research
Titrate the dose
You need to bring it down.
Watching too much TV video games
Getting healthy
Exercising
Volunteer at local soup kitchen
You are star starving
Is your soul
And then you won't be depressed because by helping others
You are fulfill
So
We need to
Prop up
The capitalist
System
Their bike
Creating
A lower class
And people with diarrhea
Help
And feel better better better because you have gone
Can you ding dong
Also
Fully get off their meds
Okay
Like they we hippy-dippy wishy-washy stuff about eat better exercise look at the stars
I don't hate that
Of Alex Jones
You know if if a doctor was telling you
Don't stop taking
You have to lessen the dose
If you're in the care of a doctor and they're saying that
Cool
Alex Jones saying that
Very different thing
You know anything about who's listening
You don't know anything about
The caller that he's talking to
He doesn't know anything about the caller who he just told their family doesn't respect them
You know anything about these people
He's not like
He's not flippantly saying that he's saying the doctors
You got to do is it I'm not saying this but we've got to do is you got to take less and look and if you go in and tell
You want to take less and less
Nuggets
Cuz they're going to get all that computer to do that
Jump and then when you say Alex Jones
They're going to be like mobile
Paranoia about the people who are the only people in the position
Only people who are in a position
Understand
Exactly what they're going
Through it all psychiatrists
Start good cuz Lord knows I
Not a lot in the past
Real Ding Dongs real takes a while
There's a lot of people who were just like get out of here
You can find somebody and I know that not everybody
I feel f****** terrible
Receive everybody
You can find some but Reagan
Somebody who will treat you
I didn't go through find the medication
That works for you
The Listener
Thank you about your side effects
The listen to that stuff
To be able to find what you need
Live
Lit cuz that's
The goal it's not
Create
Zombie horde
Alex
Creating this fear of doctors
In people in medication
F*** you up and all this stuff is
Sync all meds are healthy
I don't necessarily
Think that I think
There's a lot of over-prescription we talked about that and
So essential
Alex knows nothing about what
Take the pharmacology out of it
Take that inexperience out of it
I mostly
Interested I've already said
You said again
He has no idea what these people are going
He has no idea
He's being so irresponsible
This is dangerous
This could get people killed
I don't know it would be very
Capricious of us if he has a large enough
Four of them follow this advice
Stands to reason that at least some of them have died because
Right or have killed
He said Vista
Without
Extensive research
Getting lucky enough to find some local news story
We can't say with any certainty
We can't necessarily say that actually do cause damage
It's so much potential.
Some of his listeners f****** showing up a pizza
You know like there's this is this is not
Like
This is something that has absolute
F***** up
Somebody's life
I mean because of his irresponsible if you take
Alex
People
Outside of the care of a doctor going off medication
What is a very large
Cause of
Very large causes
Destructive Behavior
Pacific Pride
All we can say with absolute certainty
Alex
Advocating something
That you had no business
Waiting for
You have no idea who he's giving this advice to
And what they might
If they get this badass
This is Joel.
Scary to me
Are you this
I understand
Conspiracies about the medical
World go for it
Companies that make drugs are
Prices is pushed upon people
Bye
To make those drops
Run with that help
What do look Julie the enemy of my enemy is my friend
You hate
Doctors in all that
Let's go for the source
They can't because they are the right-wing is propped up by a lot of
Pharmacology
But you can't trust the doctors
Prescribed it you can absolutely trust the kind and benevolent corporations that make
Absolutely he wasn't in prison I'm sure Alex would have Martins
Crowley on right now
Yeah
There's no
Get worse before it gets better
Alex
Even further
Yeah I just want to thank you for
Two weeks I didn't hear you say one comment in passing to one of your guests
It was that
Holes in the brain actually
Actual home
Well what do you think it is when brain cells die
What do you think it is when toxins go in
Sharks dying
Is not going to go
Can't prescribe drugs
Giving you the garage
Yes
Okay a little bit about the New World Order with him
Yes yes and that's how I knew that basically I do not listen to these people anymore
Call psychologist
Their power trip over
Can you bring up the Wall Street Journal
Associated Press writers
You can bring on the wall
He will then probably try to have you committed
Because that that that is a threat how dare you say I'm wrong
It doesn't exist
And find out
So
There's no words for how irresponsible that is
You know
Should be illegal
How many other f****** Peddlers
This b******* are there
This is a Tale As Old As Time
Paltrow does this
Bulshit like all of these people I will have their alternative metal
Can go right the f*** off
Like that
Every
What you need is ginkgo biloba it's natural it's all of that b*******
Broadcast
Really really giant
Especially when he's talking
To somebody
Who like clearly
So I mean if
He's talking to his therapist
If it's a psychologist prescribe
So you saying stuff about the New World Order and stuff like that
In the psychiatrist respond poorly then yeah you should see a new psychiatrist
Stats
What do you want because
Mental Health Services are at your direction
You know that
Don't like what's going on or you feel bullied by your doctor
You should talk to them about that if they respond poorly they're a bad doctor
There are other doctors
It's not a good cause for Alex to be like glass
On the truth
Like that's everything all all it does
Is feed into the paranoia
Whatever negative impulses other listeners have other listeners who have fun
Treated
Conditions that they might need help with the ear this order thinking alike thank God I don't need to go all these doctors are just going
In a f****** manipulate me and if I tell them what I really feel they're going to put me in a box how could you trust
Any doctor
If part of your part of your
You say something like
There's the New World Order he's going
Illegal
Unless
Unless you were in imminent danger of army or going to other one
You're danger to yourself and others
Even then
Actually committing somebody without
A family member present
A committed without their like
Involvement you need more than one.
I believe
I shouldn't say that cuz I don't really know but I
Military Tribunal
I think this is a story I read about Brittany's
Baby I'm not the expert
No
I'm saying it would Alex's saying
Is
Like we
Dangerous
From him
And I'm not just talking
When Milo came onto promoted
We've heard dangerous and there's definitely other things that he says that
Incredibly dangerous
Very dangerous
The the world
This specifically
And I don't know I feel like we haven't encountered something
Flavor
In our in our time doing the show
I feel bad if we have an responding this aggressively to it
Because I feel like
I feel like this is almost a new low
I don't know
I'm trying to think about I know
I know he's
Old people in the I know will I know we've heard
In the past
Don't trust
I don't know if we've heard him say actually get off your get off your meds and don't
You're just just take it smaller doses over time and never tell anybody
Cuz they'll have you
We out
So then he goes on he has another caller
Who calls
You get back to the topic of
Psychologist
Again
Who he's talking about
Amanda
I've been on
Sertraline
Or well quite a few years and I finally want to come off of it at Justino
Doctors day and they did say exactly what you described
Like why you want to listen your dosage and then you can take the pills in half
And how do I do it
You got to wean yourself off you got up
You know take a half pill for 2 weeks it takes about 4 weeks both ways you know to go on a bill or guapa
Colleges
Medical
Doctors took it up the step higher
This is what the experts yourself
Such a coward
Cowardly after spouting a sort of face to be like
Terrible
Unbelievably awful
And so
Bummer
That's such a bummer
There's no Lo there's no bottom
That there's nobody
It's just it's just so
It's the person
Likes to think of how
I would
Probably be
Dead
If I took his advice
Like I would I would almost certainly
Yeah
Like to see how it's changed
Change my life and it took a lot of I went to a bunch of different
I tried a bunch of different
And if I had
Done that or if I had just
Ben likes
Because I'm God
Perfect creature
Set stats so f******
Disheartening
All the
All the f****** people who are
Not help
Because
Of assholes like this
Because of people who distrust
Justice League
Fetishization
If you don't
It's almost like what he really rather say is
I wish you would never heard of.
That way you
Proud and
And confident
A confident in your f****** stupid Behavior
Right
Because
Regardless of what you think about
At at heart
Part of our our beliefs
Has to be built around
If you spend your entire life
Learning about the
If you do this if you
Continue to learn about
If you keep doing this as a doctor
You should be trustworthy
Dude hope that's the whole point
That's a whole point having doctors in the first
Popham sucker whatever I don't I don't give a s***
Are our commitment to actually getting better as a society
But it looked a doctors used to bleed people but we still believe them at
At the time because they were
F****** trying
To move the
Society
You know why is that
But maybe took longer than it needed
It took too long for assholes
Realize that you needed to wash your hands when going from an autopsy
Because
People don't wash their hands
Yeah I don't know I don't know what else to say about it that I haven't already said I think
Thing things I've heard from him
Note that the tough list
Real
So bababababa
Eclipse
Where we just
Skip sort of the rest of
What I want to talk about
Episode
No
Taking the clip of the unknown stuntman
We get a caller who calls in
Because you know
Beautiful Warriors out there
They don't know how to recognize each other in public
Whose kids got an idea
Colorado go ahead
Alex I salute you and everything you stand for
I want you to know that I'm one of the legions out here that has your back
Pre-registration
Thank you
Originally I was going to talk about
Spirituality in general
Specifically fear but I had an idea that I thought was a
Important
People are wondering how they
You can talk about with spirituality
They're going to recognize
The fellow awakened Patriots
Both now and in the coming weeks
Are likely to get
Little crazy
I realize we need a sign or
Symbol
Call Aram
So here it is
Picture in your mind the peace
Flip it upside down
What do you see
Okay
Alright a victory sign
I see a human with their arms raised in Victory
That's why it's a life sign
Okay well I didn't know that
The tragic irony of this call
Lowest of lows
Planet Fitness
I've got the idea and all ideas
Upside down pizza
Alex is like
I already have a bunch of those t-shirts
Hello
Most likely
Gleams like he ozmosis
The idea from
Like this guy is
Probably well aware of the whites
I don't think so
Scholars reaction
I thought it look good
And Alex
F****** love to use attitude
Obvious
Go back to the drawing board
Give me a couple of lightning bolts or something
Goddamnit how about
How about 8
Black star on a redback
Been adopted
The next half hour of the show
Integrative
Describe the Star of David
Oh that's a tupana crew
Longer than the other
And the other bisecting the other but
Literally in a little bit
Little bit later in the show Alex has an interview with a guy named
Alright
Big fat heads
Where are you at
Because it's just
It's kind of rambling and halfway through the interview I realize that he's be moderator for Prison Planet
Message boards
What is like that but they kind of are burying the lead on that a little bit yeah
He's a new character I think we'll hear from
Listening to him
Is one of the reasons that I believe that this
States
Asserting their sovereignty
I'm a much bigger deal much bigger narratives as we go
And they only mention this in passing a little bit that's why I didn't
Can get a clip of it
But
The reason
The GT coyote is on the
Michelle
Is because
He was an aide to someone in the
Colorado legislature
Wayback
In the 90s
That they were doing the same thing to try and assert their sovereignty
And then
You know what happened
Columbine
False flag
Columbine in order to get Federal control back in
This is
Is this isn't new new stuff
I've heard him say that before I didn't know it was so the federal government could supersede
Sovereignty plans that Colorado
He said that for the past absolutely
He gets into like Ruby Ridge
Gets into Waco
Are those were attempt
Have the federal government usurp movement
Corrine order to
A certain States asserting sovereignty
At this folds into a belief
That Oklahoma was asserting their sovereignty
And then wouldn't you know it the feds blew up the Murrah building
So it's this idea
Alex is trying to implant the sea
That all of these states that are asserting their sovereignty
Get ready
There's about
To be false Flags in
So that is why
He's been spending a week in half
Okay Southeast A-OK
It's because he thinks of these
Concurrent house resolutions are going to mean a damn thing because it was hoping to work for
Expect will be
False flag terrorism attack
And just because he needs to really cancel widenet he's basically saying half the country is are these
Sooner or later
Sooner or later one of them going to have a match
Grab something
Cuz we're America flag I got another two weeks worth of material
And then I got a Year's worth of
Going back and using this as a waypoint
Coyote interview
Yeah it's really not great
F****** moderator Prison Planet
The interview
I don't feel like that
Worthwhile
Quite frankly I have no idea she actually was in the Colorado legislature to anybody
Content
I mean
I hereby call it out at some point
I don't give a s*** it's just to me it's more like alright
Your work Buddy
Gives a s***
He does spend about
Super pissed off
Because someone post
Did a video critical
So we're going to get
It's looking to Alex that get into the house
I had to print out here in my stack I was just got mine started a bunch
What's the name of the Christian God
That's a little vague around
Spider goats
Well
Ellenton ice
This isn't about me I'm doing this because
Is entirely
This is an example
Distractions
When we have serious issues in front of us
The spiritual nature of the New World Order
Mark Dice
Love talking about end times
Never always a good looking
Donna guy
This video
Is a guy
Posting on MySpace
Well I only know that because
The audio is
So bad it sounds like this guy's recording
He also says
Myspace will only let me record for 10 minutes so I'm going to make this brief
I want to be like
Just being put all my cards
On the table this guy in this place video
Alex talked about the spiritual nature of the New World Order
Detox
Really talk about snakes
It's like that
Company doesn't talk
Like his criticism of Alex is invalid and Alex's response to it is also invalid
Because he's only doing this
He doesn't have to deal with valid criticism
Does this sort of thing to create like this
Strawman of people the people who are attacking me spiritual Indiana
Behind it
Oh that's not
A religious
Show
All the time and talk about God
Flash Forward to now and yes you do
But
But I get I get his respond
But at the same time
I think back then there probably were some people who were pointing but hey
Every time Bob Chapman comes on your show you seem to bring Ted Anderson and you guys are doing the real clear Vaudeville sales
Trying to pimp
I imagine there's plenty of people who have valid criticism
About the content of his show will never want to talk about that
Guy who sang
He's stupid for saying spider on that later
He's talked about her
No I mean the YouTube video whenever he's
Not the one about the spider goats
He's right but I'm sure that even that is like so
Some dumb dumb talking about
Is wrong about spiders
Look like look
Even even the dumbest of the dumb
Able to be
You can makeup you can be right that Alex is wrong and still make a bad argument and therefore be wrong
In the bigger
Pictures
I'd like to know how
Spider goats
Oh s***
Alex band
Non-stop battle
The purist
Very racist or the goat
Typewriter ghost
Spider-Girl leadership actually Fighters that have attributes of God
It's not like it's not like the spider still
Infusion
There
Eat spiders.
Because the goats
Spiders hatem
All they got is each other
Climb up Mountain
Crags
Eat garbage
That's all I know goats do I have no idea
The grease I ran into a pack of goats
Rio type
I get that hashtag not all goats
But yes I'll go
All goats rule of eating garbage
Yeah but they have to they have to wrap it in
Kakuna at the drink the blood of the
That's the Spider Guy
A really long self
Defense about this guy
Goodnight fair play Alex
You know whatever you're just not
You're not dealing with real cream
But then
He's going out to break
Listen to this
We're going to have to deconstruct this 45-second clip
Maybe
10 minutes
This
He's one of the most
Convoluted
Self-contradicting narcissistic
I've ever heard in my life
Alex
You can't figure out where to land
Okay
Start this over
Talking about before this is about how
Should be on the same page
We all should be fighting the
Specifically
All of these
Disparate communities that are all Patriot in nature and Christian
Should all be on that we should all be unified as opposed to
Two bickering with each
They just sit around
When meanwhile
So
Real
He's getting played on
The reason that he pause there was because
He realized
Oh that's all I do
Focused on one group
How do I how do I
Cookies
The reality is that
Finished
You can't do it it's crazy
I love it
Blah blah blah
Meanwhile
Can I just feel sorry for him because
Outbreak
Focus on an exaggerated one group
Does everybody
Jealous
50% of all these right-wing website
I just
Criticizing each other and upsetting overall this
And they're trying to exaggerate the problem and blow it out of proportion cuz I do it better than you
And that's why I have the biggest website that's why I have the most followers
That's why you're just jealous cuz I have created a bigger better enemy than you
You created King Kong motherfuker I created God
Villa
Like to me is
That's the kind of Alex Jones I relished
Cuz you're a lunatic
Clear
The narcissism is coming through the like sort of laughable elements of your character
Group
So disappointing
Update
Like he is
Still the same person who tells people who he has no idea about the they got to get off their meds
Gone
He wasn't that kind of an a******
He could just be a large
Yeah and blowhards are kind of fun
Especially when they sing Highwaymen
Yeah but unfortunately
You know like
To talk about
Like the
Prince between modern-day and passed out Jones
Really matter he's a s*** head all the time
Still there
Who cares
Knock knock who cares about like his rhetoric
It's like who cares
About creating a positive version
Yeah
If we got the chance
Like if we got if we got to do over on Alex
Like I say that there is a God
An X happen
Right before enzymes happen
We get raptured
Taken up God's like hey
You guys got any way to fix her shirt
Ouija
Explain how to make Alex
Go back in time and that he would put it back for the
Eddie Bravo
Supposed to be all-knowing
Woodstock IL
I love the Project Camelot episodes
Thank you
That's
It's not. You don't have the money
Lego
So that brings us together this Patrick
To move forward cuz I have not had a great time
Listening to
Like five episodes
I was stuck
For a long time like
Can finish this
Episode
So boring
I imagine he expected there to be a mass shooting or something like that already
Alright
I described it as a holding pattern
That's why I think he's
I think he
Is a man without a third-act
So he's just doing the second acts over and over and over and over again having a boring State rap song
To talk about their states identical bill
If they're trying to push through in the
The house resolution
The sky and saying rain
And then
When it finally does happen
He's going to be like
Isaac so I think that's what we're seeing
I don't remember history
As some people do
But I don't
Know if there's a
Large-scale attacks coming up
So he might be stuck in this holding pattern for quite a while
But on the plus side we are now only 11 days away
In 2009 from the
Big break out of it
So
Closer to that and that might distract him
They might
Somehow dovetail into each other
Which is what I'm more suspicious
Okay
10 days of this show
What I'm thinking is
There isn't progress with a
The Narrative these house resolution
Committee
Intuit
Energy
He has for this
Gets folded into the Tea Party
He starts bringing
All of that too
Yeah that might be
I don't know I hate to predicting cuz I'm almost
We'll see
Where are you can go to our Facebook group
Go to iTunes
You can do the other stuff
If you ever listen to podcast you know how they tell you to
Just do that stuff before us
Everybody everybody
It closed signs off
With the same b******* podcast
I don't know I'll take this one so it is
So ghost
To do today
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color