Alexandra Thurston color
Seems like Lagunitas
Strong rotation
I'm running out to go to the liquor store I pretty much picked out just about every novelty beer and drink that I
I can find their wheel well
It's for sure you definitely fear that direction
You're in first
You're going to mess with
Coriander
Rascal
That's a great opening
Explain show
It's evolved into everywhere
You know
Talk about you for a while
Episode
And he had a very good
Request request
I'm very mad at him for giving me this request
Go down
It's not his fault I appreciate it on the other level cuz I got to learn the number 3
That are a lot of fun
Anchored introduced
Doesn't folks that I wouldn't
Otherwise
But then I'm putting together a book
To keep track of everything much more
Completely much more like
To-do list
Yeah sort of thing trying to organize my life and my bills
Right and so I wanted to take a second to recognize
The time-travel episode but there are others
Better,
Because I haven't been done
Because I keep forgetting
And that's
My bad
Alright I'm working on it we will make everything right apologize for all the stuff that you
You haven't been doing
There's another element
Time travel episode that I've been putting off a little bit
Not for not wanting
Explain it
No need to beat around the bush about why
Absolute listener gym
Who came and visited we had to
He requested I believe you requested his birthday
The episode that I found for his birthday
Was when Benjamin Netanyahu came to
The United States
Oh that's right
And it's
Complicated because Alex
Interstate Batteries
Pro-israel but
Pro sovereignty difficult
To sort of get into
But I realize why I've been putting that off
Is because when we were in 2009
And we are looking at him
Be very pro-palestinian
And fairly auntie
The state of Israel
I don't think
Jumping forward to that point
When he's going to say pro-israel thing
He's necessarily all that
Interesting for our
Pass through this
I'd like to get to that episode where Netanyahu
Comes to America eventually
Well
Not necessarily organically but I think
But it does all of us much more
In terms of
Understanding
And learning
Pivot
Towards being pro-israel
Result eventually
So I think I am
It's difficult for me
Need to get myself to do that episode
Because
I want to watch him change
As opposed to
See him
Post change and then go back and watch
Flick from a structure of our show standpoint
It feels weird
Yeah this is my way of saying an apology
The gym
If he has another suggest
You should feel free to
Tell me
Talking about his real name
Wright's just from a narrative storytelling structure I think
Byblos
Are 2009
If you have one that you think I've forgotten about which is entirely
Maybe it's maybe four if you haven't donated on that level and you want to try and trick me
Very welcome
Please send me an email and I will start putting together my to do list
To get everything in order will be
Rock and roll in
As they said
Back in the old
It sure is that what that is that what they said in the old
So Jordan today
We have a time travel episode that is not an Alex Jones space time travel episode
Is an inch
Since we're actually got in touch
One of The Inspirations
I'll bring Jim Bakker in
Search about how I
He was right in line with the
Pecan man stuff
I look at him
And he had
The Jim Bakker Show
Distance from
7 through 10
Noh8
I'm not sure
Few days in 2015
Oh that's my birthday
3 days
You know what
Jim Bakker
If you just record that all and then put that out
Chunks
I just assumed that you would take that
White guy why would you know that
Glories on Grace Street with their gas
And they probably record something to the tune of like 4 hours
Of them
Talkingshit
And then he cuts it up and he doesn't
Stepney releases it throughout the week
As if it was multiple
Like 1 hour segments
It maximizes
For 3 hours and
You know it's called time-consuming and maximizing effort while minimizing profit
Production crew
Here is an out of
Text dropped from Today Show
Netflix
Is a fulfillment of Prophecy
Chrissy from me
Me too
There was
There is no and it went
There's no
It's going to be the devil
I did not see it coming as his own profit
Is a fulfillment
His brother
How come you wasn't on the ground floor then
What time is bedtime
That's why
Dead or alive
Steel horse
I got a ride
So
We're going to get into this
Wait to steal horses a train
Yeah there's a motorcycle
It could be
You're right
I always allow motorcycles aren't made of steel I know that's
I always
What is gold bullion
It's a soup
It's like a rich people that like they put gold flakes on top of your job
Treated as one episode
It doesn't really matter where the brakes are from the days already
Intro 3
Listen to it
What's the Christmas special
Good night music
Slides in with that flourish
Junior High Musical soundtrack
Sickeningly clothes
Spinners bad
How old
No
Have some restraint act like you've been there before great out it's never the same introducer is
The guy who's leaving the bank
What do they cost
Do they have it do they have weekend I can't speak today but I do know that
The table is a little crowded
That's not entirely true
Defacto co-host
She's not Lori
Yokai named Zach
He's around a lot
Was he in a different
I don't know if you should have done that
10:25 Morningview
It's a perfect place to hide
No one with you, everyone's arms employees have guns
Haven't
Masturbated
Or should I say picerne
Hahaha
That's right
Right now
In the middle of a large
Not funny
And it's amazing
The scientists are looking for God
Nope
Approved
So this show is going to have a lot to do with CERN
That's good I like
A lot of the research that I did have nothing
You knowing a bit about it
I know enough to know number one
Not looking for God
I like
The Large Hadron Collider
Technological research
They've done
Organizations
Like it's not like
Yeah you're nodding
Really dismissively at mix
Up until this point
We weren't able to generate we weren't able to fire protons and the like with enough
Measure the effects that measure the particles
That could be created
Built up
You know like
What is it creates a black hole
As if that was a thing
Play 88
It's really fast
I would look into it
There's also another one not necessarily the same
Thing is that the kleider but
It's also being built
Why can't I remember any of this
The Higgs boson
I wish
With kind of an
Is a really fascinating thing 2013
But the fact is that wasn't confirmed
That the Higgs boson was what we thought it was in the standard model
It's a very fascinating
He's going to come in at a certain
Prove it that would disprove the standard model
Or another way that way
Perfectly prove it
Came in the middle and end
Make a recording of these guys
I'm not going to talk about crazy nonsense
The question becomes
When do we get into strength
How far away
That's not the question the question is
Those f****** scientists up to
Very very important
Book
Of the immortal
Wasn't drinking right there
Also also sounds like a Jedi mind trick album title
The top tap that they are at
They want to make contact with the Immortals work kind of warning
Contact with him it's not going to be pretty
What wow
Today
News
As well
We had amazing stories
Amazing news Jimmy
There we go
I mean what more could you ask for
Their scientists are looking for the Immortals
Name of the book
But what they're actually doing you see is that they're trying
Create
Some sort of the connection where they can
Communicate with
Open up a portal
Another dimension
That's what he say
Well first off
Based on his voice alone
Banana
How does a human being make those sounds out of his
Listen to his voice again
It is
Disgusting
Eighth grade
Any
It's gross
As annoying except that allow it
Your voice has spectacular and I could listen to it for
A little bit Petty about
I know what character is
Rustic but you know it does come from the jowls
Probably
Probably hasn't
No matter what you say about his voice or anything like that
Can't argue that he has a
The grass on the science
Listen to that
Sometimes
Is that right
These programs are playing on television this thing will be revving up
To the most power
The face of the Earth
Are we going to accelerate
Hundreds of Millions
The proton
Inside of the tubes that you can see their behind us
To just beneath the speed of light
Then they're going to compress them down to a human hair
And they're going to call Mini of 600 million particles
This is never happened on Earth before unless maybe it was windy
First time
Around
What's
Protons down to a human hairs with
How many protons
Does he think
Oh man
Probably like 16
6 equals
Okay here's Witt
This is crazy
So is that the go is that like the
EU standard of measurement cuz you know we use
It's imperial measurement
Is down-home European slang for a quarter
The size of a quark
So is he talking about that
I'm not sure I don't think he knows but if
Alright
I'm not I'm not going to
Trust somebody
Who eat like uses that as like a like a measurement that they're going to compress
Protons that have been collided down to hundreds of millions of protein
Sure
With
That's like almost 2,000 Angelique 109
You still treating this one at a time
Hundreds of millions attire
I don't know man
The dishes
Scholars
Jim Bakker about it
Jim
Is coming at it from a real
He don't really know that
North
Here is the picture
Who is
Is God alive
Find the God particle
Very different thing
He thinks it's literal
You guys called
The God particle
Jim Baker thinks it's
Literally like particles of God
What is God
Who is God
Questions that scientists are all that
Not really but not really they're bad
The audience of solid
Explain the importance of
Well the idea is
We don't know why gravity
There's always matter
Is gravity a
Particle is it a characteristic is there something that
Endows
Things with
Matter with grab
With all of it that we don't actually know why it happened and every time we look into it it only gets more obtuse
And every time you do more experiments they almost
Seem to contradict
Each other half the
And then you got the standard model with
Predicts what we think we're going to find
For the most part
Makes perfect sense
Right up until you get to things like
Dark matter
And Phaeton and things that we just
Can't measure
We have no idea how to measure
So what they're really looking for is some sort of confirmation
Of the standard model
Or
Some
Other model or something
The standard model being wrong and
All are we start getting into crazy
That's
That's what I hear are they making
Probably bigger show
Gravity
And if we can create gravity
What
Now you're starting to sound like a paranoid
She fears
I was just never
Best thing
Never great
Although I think it's probably very consistent that you would
Embody that would be afraid of
I think that's probably
They're afraid of
There's one aspect
Concerned
Not stop talking
Lottery
Sheba
Discombobulated the world
And what Tom just said I want to reiterate that point
Okay well I was right
Pooja
Mini X in religion
Why would they have a God put the got back on the
Screen mando
There's the god
Outside the doors
Why would he be there
Square ice
It is called
Perez
Placement
Take the rails
All those idiots
No way coming back over and over again serve like
It was a gift from the government of India the state of Indiana
Because they were
Associate
Start working on
I want to write
Writing
Postdoc student quote
Is teaming with life
Chivas teams play for University
We shaking things up
Making itself
Never up never static
Contemplate the deeper questions
Literally
The long Shadow over our work
A bit like the Shadows on Plato's Cave
Chiba remind me that when we still don't know the
Answer to one of biggest the biggest question
Presented by the unit
I am at Everytime We collide
We must take
Cosmic balance
So I'm going to stay
Real quick
Nerd
Look what it's like whatever you hear somebody who's intelligent talk
Right listen to those words
And then compare them with what I stumbled over a couple of them
This is the this is B false
Further explained
The Tower of the Dallas physics
Toshiba symbolizes all
At the same time she reminds us that
Manifold forms in the world are not fundamental but a loser
Never change
I need you to stop using words like manifold
An illusory
If we've got Jim Bakker listening's knowledge not understand
Creation and destruction
Is not only manifested
In the turn of the Seas
Birth and death of all living
Creatures but also
In the very essence
Inorganic
So there's a lot of very nice
Poetic Waynesville
You couldn't work in it
The idea of
Everything
You don't have to do religiously
You can just do it poetically
Good guys
Know who Shiba is
Write these guys are like
This
Is out here
Any like you
Do not know anything about
Keep saying
That's something
So crisp
Austin peace during the
51 diet
Surprisingly
What I could glean
I would guess it was a heart attack
I don't
Don't take any
Enjoyment
He is nuts
And he jumps in here
Explain
That
Prove God
And just to put it really simple
Einstein discovered in Winter discovery
The smaller they get
Gimmick
The best
The Observer
Effects reality
It looks like
Like I said
Now
It's actually both
Until somebody looks
When you look at it actually determine what state
Which is really odd
Given
That wouldn't make
Why would your mind
Have any effect over reality
Always proving our worldview
No
Mindset whether they realize it or not
R&R soul
Our essence
Actually affects physical reality
In a way so we really don't
Nope
Not how that works at all
Improving is that
Light effects
Lights
Not that the human mind
It's not that when we observe it we force the way from
To collapse we have to shine light on it which then
It's not like our eyes are doing
No it's alright
Play I don't know a whole lot about quantum physics
Let's not area of study that I am
I'm not even really
Conversant in it necessarily
Watch some YouTube videos
Einstein wasn't
No no there's a little bit after
You know
What are you
Idis is one of those things that like I think
You know uncertain
Rules
Really bring up this
Form of science
It's most
Easily abused
Right by people who haven't
Especially since the people who do know about it also agree
Nobody really knows that much about
Going to be like
People don't guitar
It without studying it don't really
These guys have
If you are talking to a quantum physics
You're eventually going to get
To the point where they say
We can measure
And I can tell you that this is true
But the stuff that we can't measure
Is so great
That I can't tell you that
The f****** you a****** we're not looking
We're not trying to open a portal
But
So far a lot of this is just
Still
A little bit of laying the groundwork
Is going to spin off the rails
Pretty hard
I believe
But it starts misrepresenting experiment has already made me angry at the
How far off the rails is gone off the rails Safari off the rails
I have one piece of evidence
There it is
Damping
Did Jim Bakker doesn't have
And that is guest still.
Hold on
That I look
Gintama coulibaly
Disqualifying
Ever read the Bible
Or has ever studied read the Bible
Studies of Christianity
I think it's
You don't know this
Information
I think it's one of those times when I wish I got them
This is one of those times where I feel so miserable that I couldn't
Talk about
Information is spinning around in my head but now I'm trying to improve it and pull it from all kinds of different directions
I'm going to sound like an idiot I should have texted you
Brush remember movie
You're doing good
Everything goes off the rails
Starting
Hey Miss Mexico
Verify a parallel reality
Remember correctly
Bible days when they were building a tower
Call babbel or B baby
Tower
Is that right
If my mind
Correctly
They
They look
For more of a
A doorway to heaven
You're not going to build
A Stairway or a tower
And walk up
I'm going to have
You can't
I don't think they were trying to build just a tower that would get out and say hi.
Good morning
What time is it at what time zone does God live
Upper Crust
Subscribed
Fair play to you
I suppose
You can climb high enough
I would call I'm glad he does know that
That's good
That suggests a basic understanding of science
Is in sharp contrast
With his co-host
Who comes in with this
Another crazy thing is this
Possibly
Gotten to heaven
What they have
If God wouldn't have destroyed them
With an emphatic answer
I expected him to say no unfortunately
Yes
Yes they what up
Genesis chapter 11
But it's built ourselves
We may make a name for ourselves
To see the city and the tower the people were building
First of all I love the idea of like God coming down just to see it by
Well actually the real problem was
You hanging a toes
Off the edge of Heaven for a while and they almost brushed up on the
He's like no I got to stop this s*** there f****** with my fishing
Strongly disagree I think what happened is it one of God's buddies came over as I can
She becomes over his name
Shower
Grocery store come on
Are you ready for this
If I was one people speaking the same language they begun to do this
Then
Nothing
They plan to do
Will be impossible
The very thing
The god of the universe
He said
That nothing they do with the Impala
Case of the very thing
So
That's going to be a really don't understand
So even biblical literalism
I like
They weren't actually building
The Tower 2
Guys
You can't do
Well
Upstairs
Tower of Babel
Does not exist
The Bible
Also it's not a real thing
Etiology
Which is like a little story people have different languages
Teach children against the idea of hubris against God that sort of thing
Similar to this other myth
It's like a it's like a big one in the public consciousness
Led Zeppelin reference at one time
It's that guy
Dyer maker
Went up like really close
Yeah there you go
Cigarettes
Flying Too Close to the sun more literal analogues throughout his
Different cultures
The Sumerian myth about Ember cars it's a Mexican tale about the
Construction of the Pyramid of Cholula
There's a bunch of different
Conversions throughout Africa and even some in Tibet
Who tried to figure out exactly like is it possible that there was a
The Tower of Babel that this
It's like something that
Actually comes down from history
And there was a ziggurat
Dedicated
Tamar Duke
In Babylon called
Historical context
Story The Bible
Was referring to
What are the chief problem being that the Tower of Babel was said to be billed under Nimrod which would have been around 2,000 BC
Is almost certainly from around 12
Is it possible to tell for sure
Destroyed and 689 b.c.
I was just ride along with
Either way
It was built
About 300 ft tall
But for comparison that's less than half the height of these
Chicago Board of
Building
The 44th tallest building in Chicago crazy about that building
It's about to be taken down by God
It got a little too close
Everyone they're speaking the same language real close
Nothing is impossible for these people who speak the same language
Tear down that wall mr. God there's also
Even the story that they're missing and not
Dealing with meta is the idea that God is affirming that if people work together there
Their boundless potential
Furthermore it is suggesting that God is afraid of
People or is it invested in them not working together
In some ways
No
Yeah it so I mean
Keep coming back to this
I'm trying to
Compare CERN to the Tower of Babel
Whatever
It's only because that one theme of the story The hubristic
God
Is what they're trying to
Create a
So now
Yes
There's more
WhatsApp
For now
Tom Horn
And Chris Putnam
That sounds like a class
It is one of the great Tales of History
For the great love stories
Not since he's old and Tristan
Star-crossed lovers
I only know about that is old
Tristan because of like
I worked at a movie theater when that movie came out
And all I remember was all of the marketing materials
So petty about Romeo and Juliet
I remember to the Daily
Even the movie
That was part of the marketing
Not alike
20 years ago probably be working at that movie theater
Maybe a little less
Genuinely do not know why I know any
Tristan
Other than I was in a dumpster
Became a reference
So
Little bit of the story of the beginning of
Conspiracy
Your eyes and I'll fill in the blanks
Cuz best I can
Is there some kids today
John Cusack
Perhaps
Also I should say Tom Horn
Wrote Love in the Time of Cholera
Thursday Supernatural
What's going on
You all have been on Amazing trip
Y'all
Meet with
The Indian leaders
You have got to meet with leaders
Around the world Supernatural
I was
Writing down
When you were
Going to meet
Adductor Moe's I believe his
Was that correct
What was the
Medical doctor or
Is the Navajo Nation
Third generation Medicine Man and oral his
Historian
Cancel
You know the whole
Down from
The world
Is this called Lucifer
Good morning
Technology inside the large
Just called the Lucifer
So well that that makes everything clear Dan
A big
Conspiracy
Propagate
By Tom Horn
Just because you guys are the ones who were popularized
You could say that there were other players involved too but their major figures
The Vatican having a Lucifer telescope
But a lot of
Conspiracy around it was that
The
The vacuum is in touch with alien
And they're using Lucifer telescope in order to
Track Nibiru
Or Planet X okay back around in 2012 at the end of the Mayan calendar
Of course
So if you leave that piece off of it and that's why I believe Tom Warren is like
The technology
Birthing chair
So anytime somebody is like
Let's throw in something that some assholes
People do need to get better at naming
Why you would name it Lucifer but if you need me poop
Give no idea why
What it was
Place
There are multiple
Zerva Tori's multiple
Unrelated
Empathy
On my G
Include the Gregorian telescope
Yandy Thomas
Astrophysics facility
Where's said telescope
His house is the Alice
Thomas
This is commonly referred to as the
Complex
Also on Mount Graham but I'm connected to that is the Mount Graham International Observatory which contains the large
Binocular telescope
Part of a technology mgio
Is an infrared spec
Spectroscopy module known as
Binocular telescope near-infrared spectrasonic utility with
Cameron intrical field unit for extra-galactic research
Initially the acronym for this was Lucifer but since Chris
Those kept been weird about it they changed it
Because
You take out some of the let him if there's no way that's going to make a word couple of the word acronym you end up with
Lucifer if you were some sort of
Ugnaught Vatican connected
Astrologist
Yep in the same way that that Blue Horse Outside the Denver Airport that giant blue horse
Valdosta
Lucifer the artist
Lifan
His dad only
Indian shop when he was a kid
So we decorated with some neon eyes
Isn't omage to his father
All this s*** anyway
Assuming that the pope has sanctioned
Telescope
Called Lucifer in the middle
Mount Graham
Yeah where is it
Seems like a lot of people are communicating with aliens
Seems like we're the only ones who aren't the only ones we have
We really should get one just like a small one
Lakewood
Put it on a mount
Damn sure
There's a Danville in almost every
There's a little time
Hill in Danville
Good
Knowledge fight Memorial
Mount Dan telescope
We're going to get to the Native American
Himself a little bit later
He's going to bring that back up and Native American Medicine Man if we're all about
Endomorph full wave before I get in
Into the more the stuff here about this
Telescope
Most of his ideas
About
B b
Connection with UFOs
Is based on the guy named guy
Console.log know who
Is he was a past president of the iau commission on planets and moons
Have an affiliation with Nevada
So he had an interview with me
A little bit
After
Tom Horn
Started putting out a bunch of in
Information about
Interviews with this consolmagno guy
With this statement
About a year ago and author who am I will not name or link
You conducted an extensive interview with me by email
I thought he was a legitimate journalist
However seeing the ways in which is Twisted misquoted invent
Falsehoods from
Some things I said I've come to speculate either a knave or fool
There are no Vatican
Secrets about UFOs
Neither I nor anyone I know his any evidence of extraterrestrials exist
We do not believe that Jesus is a hybrid or any of the other bizarre claims this author makes
He is either seriously deluded or deliberate conman
Let me rephrase this as strongly as I can
I do not know of
Any credible evidence at all that there is ever been contact of any for between
Extraterrestrial aliens in
. I cannot imagine a circumstance where such contact could be
Kept secret for very long
And I say this not only as an active astronomer for 40 years
But also is someone who knows a lot of people in the city community
Who would
Love to have such evidence
And as someone who's been an officer of the American
Strama Astronomical Society and the international astronomical Union
If there's something like this going on
We'd all be talking about it
There isn't
They would pretty much be talking about it now.
Stop it might be the only thing anyone would ever talk
People to be like
What would we talk about aliens again f*** off
Yes sir he is a completely misrepresent
Interview
Which I bring up parsley because
Mostly because
It is the sort of behavior that these be
People to take
Entirely out of context
Make stuff up
You can roll the bones and no one will know.
Hope they never find out hope no one looks at
Also there aren't a lot of good opportunities to use the word knave properly
That's a
Fun word to toss around and that is the
Most accurate where that guy could have used it's almost like he chooses his words
And decides to use them when they are
Also it's fun because when they talk about going
Mount Graham
I believe there'll be some of this in the episode as we go along but they broke
Or like it was some sort of a like
Ballsy investigative
Project Veritas infiltration
Triumph
Presented as like
A dramatic
Active sort of thing
You can take a tour like it's open to the public
Like it's not
If you called and you presented yourself as a journalist
You could probably interview any
Anybody there
You can go to work buddy we're not close
Oh okay but
Create this sort of miso surround
What day did like going
To my gram was dangerous for that
The Native Americans
All of it is horseshit
Play all of it is just
Classic
They are selling you on a
Otherwise like
We've all been on
Just tell it as
It's an investigation in
We figured it all out because of
Himself in the face and take a pic
Picture while he's on vacation
Oh yeah
Right on your trip but the trip wasn't it
Good story
How good of a story is they let us in and were very gracious and talk to us
You got to have punch up on every
Reality is kind
I told you that we're going to get to the Native Americans
Sooner than I expect
Still just
Let It Go all of the ship
They said so far as not being that far off the
Because
This is going to get further off the rail
A hundred percent
It goes off the rails in multiple directions Tower of Babel is about them
Being capable of getting all the way up to God
Write the character of God
Alternate portal
So far so good
What are we doing here
What are we doing
I the best I can tell you is that goes along
It's not like the train goes off the rails
It's like little cars break off of the train and go off the rails directions
And your sword is still tracking those trains as
Some of them explode
Sure here is where we get into the sooner the beginnings of what you want to talk about about Native Americans
We think walk a week we solve the mystery writer what's going on
You talk about after he got it too
And then
Who wants the radio
And he says the reason that the Apache
Join the environment
It's because
Graham is one of the four holiest mountains
In the world
American Inn
And it is
Because
It is a portal
It is a doorway
It is a gateway
Location on Earth
The beginning
Of this reality
We went through
Amboy the conspiracy light went off and our head about now why
I would like more information on this vetting process
How do you
This is a portal that
Many people have many ant
Entered in and out of over
Humanism
The only response
I looked into it and I'm very sad to report the top horn has not been on Project Camelot
Doctors that belongs on f****** truck I was just thinking about what happens when you combine
Who believe in God with people who are willing to lie about science and then
Throw God in there
Like beneath the surface a little bit carry is probably a little religious
Elaine's a little religion
Generally speaking
Not always
But
Usually
Responsible
And so they don't
6 Acres like
We're trying to provide
Apache are the protectors
There's a certain bit of like old-school like 19
Forties adventurism
Observatory
Armetta's Pizza
There's the whole thing
Go backwards
But the same religious nevermind
This is a 1940s Boys in French
The reason I can't respond to that clip really
Is because I don't know his writing process
And I can't get that information pretty sure he threw a rock through the portal that information
But I can bet other things he says
And I can use that is
Context clues about whether or not I should trust him
This next clip
And you lived in Arizona by the way
You know why they called The Phoenix metropolitan area
The Sun
It's because
And he said
Across the Earth
Very so
Headline
On that day
Giant killed by flood
How big were the Giants
Huge huge were they the New York Giants
Nephilim
Giants Nephilim
The Native Americans also believed in the Nephilim the Nephilim
Just
Believe in the Nephilim
And of course
This as we all should have now
Because of the very
Well-known concert
Everyone within a certain
Community knows
The Valley of the Sun
Bright
Cuz Giants got flood
Giant
So they pray the god of the sun
Mysteriously didn't kill them in the
McCabe's
Seems like a trap during a flood
Furthermore
Is this
Did this guy think that
Believe that that did happen
In line for Carmen
It's like you never really ate you know
Like a good poker player
You're not really sure if they're bluffing or not right
Good con man or people who could doing it for long enough you
You don't know if they really believe it or if it's just a bluff
Within his Twisted world
Bright
Because of a literal events that happened
Raw
The Jehovah
Bravo's
Why did they get the flood
If they're okay cuz they just think of it serious
It's all one God many names
He is busy is the god of the sun and
I'm telling you something
Ain't no son like the Son of God you know I'm saying unfortunately I'm in Arizona Central
Azcentral.com
It's critical for cities to be properly marked
Create a sense of place for residents and alluring vacation destination for tourist
Roosters coded Phoenix
Boosters touted Phoenix as being the quote Denver of the Southwest and the 1890s
Unimaginative
In the 1920s they try quote wear summer
I swear summer Winters
Spot of America the Beaufort.
In 1935 the Valley of the Sun slogan was coined by a local advertising agency for the
Commerce
The group felt the slogan had a quote directory to repeal the cannot help but attract entry
According to
1835 Arizona Republic article
Cooked up by the Phoenix Metro area
In the 1930s
Because it sounded better than the accurate name the Salt River Valley
The reason for the name is at the Metropolitan Area will be one of the sunniest places in the country receiving an average of
295 days of sunlight a year
As opposed to the national average of 205
This does not come from Native American comes from 1930s Arizona tourism board
I am a big fan
Looking into it
At all
Congratulations on your study of anytime that kind
How to claim comes out
On our show and then you just
Immediately point to
This was Market
This is an addict also speaks
Is that also years later
Now probably
So you just got to tell Tom Horn something he wants to hear
And he will be true
So
Like I'm saying
Their claims you convey
And there's claims that you
The fact that prove or disprove that
The Giants were flooded
Boosie I can't
But I don't care
Because I can prove that he doesn't know that I was a tourist slogan right from the
Agency came up with
Not something that is
Really indicative of
Navajo Legends
Parallel thinking
ABS parallel to the Navajo came up with it first
And then
Hundreds of years later
That marketing guy he just got influenced by the sun god I recommend everybody to read
As many articles as I have today
About why is Phoenix called the Valley of the Sun
All of them will point you in the exact same direction
Has nothing to do this son God flooded him
Ideas
And that's what
That's why it's called the Valley of the Sun
Emmett clip before this where Tom was talking hot bulshit
You said you talked
Navajo
Perhaps
The Medicine Man by dr. Mays
He was Apache
No he's very fast and loose about these
Freshly.com
Who's we
What is that only come up on Jim Bakker Show by the way
Specific racism
Maybe it's not even race
Ignorance
Yeah
Wilfred
Seems very consistent
And actually I actually
You know why it's because the Tom Horn
Steve Quayle are good
There's contemporary
And know each other and do each other's radio shows all the time
About Anasazi
People
Yeah absolutely
More from this Navajo gentle
Talk to
I'll tell you what
I have a very simple explanation for this
Fishes going down the storyline
There's a lot of evidence
Princeton
Everything behind all the tools everything was still inside the case
And he says
Well I should not tell you
And then he starts saying if you would have asked my great-grandfather
Here's the story
And he describes a portal in the four corners area
Comes through over there
Years before Jesus Christ walked on the Earth
Portal of spiral vortex
Support
Giant halo around
Teaching the Anasazi
Historian
He starts
He starts teaching the
Dark magic
An underground place
Holy places
New Testament
Would call if they start using
And they're getting contact with these things and they bring them
Giants in the NFL
So
That's a lot
I can actually explain that in one sentence
I should probably save before you go off on
The reason that this Navajo guys grandfather would say this
About the people who he's referring to is Anasazi
Because if we recall what we talked about on that Steve Quayle at
Anasazi
Means literally a Navajo language
I have some sort of cultural tradition about demonizing on
Jimmy's dress
Sort of an Artful
Fold
Etiology of not like these
Right call them ancestral enemy
No not
Just that
It's because when that portal open
A demon reptilian beings came through
They were susceptible to the black magic
And that's why even though we probably should all just get along and
Live out our common
Purposes
I'm good no they are the author there the other and we don't trust them
What you doing it's being f******
Credibly
Stupid cultural context into it at all
If I heard like
I do
What I don't
Is
Why is everyone listening
And nodding
You mean the people at morning 2
It's weird
Doesn't this fly in the face of all of their beliefs
Like
If that's true
No no no
They're not as though this was a thing that cuz he emphasizes that this is what the
Navajo
Historian says to have brakes
He's also insisting that portals are real other real so he's now suggesting that a thousand years before
Jesus Christ
Navajo sorcerer Navajo
Who has the capability to open portals
Bring giant Sandra
Killian guys with halos
Everybody's Christian is just like
Wow I can't believe that happened is
They believe that Giants are in the Bible
Extra demonic beings or whatever.
I'm not sure he spells without fully
Sarasota blase
There's a service like
Whatever
Or whatever
Tom
He does bring this up a couple time
Angel just means messenger
I wouldn't have to be a race
Of being
Be all sorts of different messenger
Job not a typo
So
Christopher Lloyd
Let me tell you something
Is a remake
The best podcast ever
Messengers in the Outfield but not nearly as well
Good movies a year right
Baseball season
Guys
How do we move forward from
What's a good Angels in the Outfield B Gone it's
It's hard it's hard
He thinks that all that
Fits into his
Diversion of what
Christianity
And like what
The Bible
Sounds like
Distance learning history like that's the way that they
Is there like
Human history that
100% real that I do
No
What's going on here
Visit
You you pointed this out early
Worried that none of these people have ever actually read the
Nouveau
Translations of
The bible message version
The Bible and stuff like that that's one of those
Maybe after even both
Or X
When we were in the church
The translation that
And stuff like that so it loses a lot of the
Of the King James version
Or even the NIV version
You guys aren't
Adventure
Put sunglasses on
And even those versions
Like the classical version
Even have their problem
Classical Languages it all going
You know you start to have to
Look at is that
Like for instance
Usually ever right
Vowels
What's up like that
Between words
You know you suck it all out
Construction that you can make of
It's imprecise sometime
And that's Greek a language
We fucken understand almost fully
So when you take
These biblical texts that are from like koine Greek and you have
That level of detached
Turn from it
Like the other thing
Like so in college I translated The Iliad
And what am I
Translate Audelia
In my head
Like it's something that I think about
Very regularly
There are multiple words
In The Iliad
That don't exist anywhere else
Ever
Like there's one that is the only one I can remember is Polly Floyd
This word the only exist
One time
In The Iliad and never again in Greek
In no other Greek writing
It means many
Free flowing
The word that used to
To describe
Almost the sound of the water laughing up against the boat
And stuff like that description of a river
He's always struck
In my mind because
When you have these
Ancient languages and there are examples
These words that only exist
The one yeah there's a
Preciseness
Translation
And then on top of that if you've ever looked in
Scrolls
You would know that most of that is
Fragments
Yeah
Somewhat early people considered to be
Part part of a far larger series
Anyways I'm sorry for interrupting
Whatever it originally was it
What it was
Girls you know in
They found all those Scrolls at qumran
Tried to put them together as best
Scholarly texts
About the Dead Sea Scrolls you're going to have caveat
Little Liar books
In the Bible verse
Constructed and have been overtime right
So give it to me
When you have
That much you understand that much
You kind of have to accept salability in the
And then beyond
You have to
Really
Avoid
Cool translation
Because they're going to lead you into like a stupid world
Where you're like reading this God says hey bro what's up
But it's that sort of parallel
Like a God says what's going on
Yep you're going to lose pretty much everything
Spirit I guess
Maybe the intent of the text
Well in my world this very clear
The message version of the Bible
Jim Bakker episode we did was about to Paula White Cain
Find one we're talking about what
They ever read the Bible
Version that's almost like a
Harry Potter to be red
By people who like novels
It starts poochie
Moreland
In like my world just in a
Pure present
Reading
Rainier Maria rilke
A book of his poetry
In German
And then reading the translation
In in German and English
Very very close languages
Actually get like
There's such a mess of differ
Between those two
And we all understand
Like people who speak
Speak German have study German their entire lives and and
Translators are trying their hardest
To get the same kind of
Feeling flavor of that
And put it into English and you simply
Cannot know so that it's just something
Let alone something where you only have 10 words
That he used and you have to try and
Extrapolate
An entire language
Consider like
Idioms
Ways you can date
Like a lot of the times you
You can solve this. Cuz that idiom
Was not
That makes it incredibly difficult like wordplay exist
Languages wordplay exist in German that can't be translated to English
Modern languages you lose
A bit of Rex a bit of a player
It's like trying to
Exactly Translate
So let's get back into this
This point we are here what I would describe as a rookie
From Chris Putnam who's playing second fiddle
Throughout most of it
He comes
He comes in strong
5 with a
A very stupid thing
Good
220 30 years ago would you think there be a reality program on television about hunting for ghosts
Competing with each other
Okay
I think that's indicative
Star of the age that I mean
That belief in these things aren't crazy
Are becoming
Manifest
What
What are the times that is a bunch
Ghost hunting
Shows where they never find anyting
Most of them aren't about ghost hunting there's like
There's the one show that's like
It's really more about the fact that
These are a bunch
College students
Doing this
Aren't they cool and young and fun and they
Ghostbusters
There's that one or two frat guy was yelling at ghost to hit him and stuff like that
It's really more about that then there's fear on MTV that was really just about
Defective cameras on the person's face and everyone cries all the time
And stuff like that or like a prison places that are haunted
And they be left there
Have you only Video Only video it's like a team of 45 people
On the show
Is from
Surveillance cameras set up around the place
Pointing at their face at all through the night spend the night at his place
And throughout it they could challenges we're generally to be like two pizzas
HomeBase
Scott MTV was great they've a home-based b
Emma's lights and stuff like that
They stay in their initially and then they get these missions
To be like two of them half
Virgo
To like
The aaf
J wing of the prison
Someone hung themselves in that cell so one of the people will have to stay in that cell for like
30 minutes and try and contact that spirit
Specific and then the other person will have to go away and do something else
So they all end up getting left alone everybody
That was like the real world vs Road Rules challenge
I was trying to tell you got to go into the cell where somebody hung themselves but you go
Got to do like 30 pull-ups in
You got to drink a bunch of yellow about women
I would like that combination celebrity version
That one was awesome everybody wants to watch celebrities be afraid
As I recall
As I recall the only person who wasn't
Gary Busey have no fear
I celebrate you spirit
Gary Busey was in Point Break Dan he's never been afraid of anything
Thanks Drew
So I don't hurt my point about this
This more than I do
That happened because people realized
Turn this
Genre
Into a different
I like a reality show
The same way that like
Yeah there's a lot of different
Dating shows generally it's not about the dating
It's about the twist that you put on
Next was grateful next was all fake
There's at least shows like
Shipmates
Waiting on a boat
Xvideos2 chip
Motherfuker mates was so good
If we get more Project Camelot talk from Tom
Nation you were just showing
Joel Richardson
It's another Thursday.
Hear what we have is this is literally query Kerry Cassidy talks about
How very like all of these wars throughout history have been at the Iraq War
Vietnam they weren't about actual
Geopolitical struggles they were about closing Stargate Stargate talks like doorway portal
Exact same thing these people are saying their pitching the same narrative
Different audience
Confess
Because
At no point do any of these people realize that so many of these are like
Regional fears
You know like
These guys have a reptilian with a Halo
Over there you can spider leadership
Over here or whatever the f***
All of this s*** is just
Regional
Sears
That you can clearly take back to
This culture got f***** up by spiders for a while like that was kind of a
That was the situation everybody had their own like we get f***** on the problem
Komodo dragons be hardened
Some
Cultures.
Psychic
Japanese dragons in European dragon
Little Things
Intrinsic like in terms of lizards being sort of
Is evil
Yeah he's very very strong
Distrust of something that doesn't have legs
Like snake rolling around also also they can kill you
Also like not Elizabeth
Don't kill you also
Stilbite
Aeropostale
Can constrict you
And generally speaking like lizards aren't
So like
There's no reason to really like them
Over history
Lizards
In reptiles are
The greatest
Possible Lake
You're bad
Bugs
Mean also
What's a bird ever done for you
Firewood to burn ever done for you
But not much else
I would love mystery based off of Still Believe
Things that you like
F****** loudest
Do you think a lot of myths are based on last
Dude what do you know about orbs
So I know every time somebody asked me that question
The answer is not what I'm going to say do you know about phenomenon
Paranormal
Pictures of there being orbs
I know about the
The song by the Yeah Yeah Yeahs named
Not that
You don't know
Which
So orbs go to haunted places
Forbes
You take pictures
I just don't
The pictures back
Check-in there's orbs in
In the picture
Open always
Failure of the camera or more often
It's
It's the flash reflecting on a p
Pizza Villa
Interested
Chris Putnam
Not a big fan of the
Reasonable explanation
Four orbs
Bucking orbs
What's going on
Sedona is famous
Pittsburgh being
A portal Arrow
In fact there's actually one area called the Bradshaw Ranch famous
Already struck out a couple times on Arizona I would just stop talking about Arizona
Skinwalker Ranch Punk
Bradshaw Ranch
Week
Then after a famous stuntman brats I was a lot of the old western
What happened
Mysteriously the government ball all that land and fenced It Off
But now you can't even answer it
It's famous in the UFO community
It's famous in the ghost hunting
Now
Sing something on identified in
Sky so you don't have much
Problem bleeding
As we're probably
Cameron
They are particles and things like that
Just kind of
Some sort of anomaly with a camera reflection inside the professional photographer
Are we set up to camera
From different
And we actually did get orbs
Anselmo
With two cameras at same time
Sorry it's not the Spartacus
What doesn't actually prove me
No
Because if they're shooting in the same direction and there's something
It might reflect
Or refract
White from their Flash
A shooting from two angles it would do the exact same thing on both camera
Also
So-so
Before this before he took professional photographer out
So it's not like I'm assuming that they're using Flash
So-so
Resorts
So he knew so here's
B Mike
With us
He knew about orbs
As a thing
And he always thought
That they were
Something wrong with
Which means that he knew
Bet there were a lot of picture
Orbs
Is presenting it is like I thought it was bulshit before con men
If I understand correctly
The way
He set out to be
2 cameras
So there were hundreds of cameras no one had ever thought to do that before cameras in the past
That have found these orbs and he's like
But if I use
2 cameras
Well then I know there's two cameras
Light is both a particle and a wave
Right
Illustrate like this
Guys
Is very gullible
Just not gullible
He just wants to put
Are gullible people
When are they going to sell
Cuz they have to be around the corner in a little bit because there's so much here
I cut out
Okay mostly because it's
I'll just that water bottle man
Yeah he's pushing that water bottle hard
It's all these packages the water bottle and Tom's book
Eventually we all get to see
We were selling yearbook staff because
To me honestly like
That is in the realm of
Respectable unplugging the book
That doesn't seem like gross salesmanship to me
Who have a book
Yeah give a little plug to the book
With water bottles
Little weird
But because we've
Ants all over the water bottle for the last two Jim Bakker episode
There's so much
Let's not
Jump into that
I will say we learned that the water bottle he's been burying the lede
It's not just for drinking river water
Is your water I did not know that I've always needed my water alkaline
APA brings the ph up
Sure
Be careful
People think acid bad bass good or something like that too much
Trying to bring up
Drinking alkalized water is that alone is dangerous
Turn the frogs gay
Long time
Long styling
Giggling co-host
Now
The story
She also says wow
Wow
So she comes in with a story
And this this is
It's kind of fun
Cuz it gives us a little bit of flavor of what Lori
Like as a husband I'm not going to like that
At the end of the story
I actually
And that area
Mountain near Safford Arizona
At time
Actually
Terraria
For a Time
Cartelera
I have fat
Second home
Sedona
And
Buckhannon
I'm like
Blowing my mind thinking that these are
I have had
So many
Credible
Variances with the Lord what the hell
Ferret
If I told you
The TV off and go
Supernatural so I
No
Supernatural really sitting here
I don't know how to explain
As real as you're here right here honey I'm touching you
Supernatural Angel surrounding us all around us
Where in
The final
Stay
The last days
Where I really
What the hell man
Your wife
Just told a story about seeing demons and angels
And then you launch off on your new phone that you wanted
It's the verbal equivalent of being like
I'm not interested in your story Lori
There's angels all around us right now
Alright we're in the final stage of the end times everybody probably ignore that
Bulls
The problem that I have is that like
Her story isn't out of line with the stuff they talk about it's not like that story isn't anyway like
She say that
Angel
These demons are all around us right now they're more real than you and me
This is something that everybody has literally said
In this f****** show
Baker's just like
Heard it before Lori Werner
Marry you
There is a there's a
Maybe this is a little bit one-sided
He's a f****** psychopath
Course he doesn't care if
Man
Wait till we get to the end
Disconnect
In his brain
Diesel
Psychopath
Is not accurate Maybe
Comes in
Uno's
A couple things
I don't think
Describe
Has been contained under the surface of the Earth again we're talking about the Earth
Understand
And they are under the surface of the Earth waiting for the day of
There is an extra biblical book and some Orthodox version
Book of Enoch
Stop route
It's only in
Orthodox
So the first thing is Hollow Earth
Clearly talking about Hollow Earth
And then also
The Book of Enoch
To those two
Two things
I don't think that's great
What's not great about it
Well one Hollow Earth is
It's fun to think about but if you believe it you're you're out there you're not as serious
You're not a Serial B
You're not a serious thinker 6 United States
Huge Hollow Earth guy
Reaper when was that
46 years ago
What is it that much different from what
Dumb
That's what I'm hearing from this
If you are listening to this
And you're like
I want to buy this guy's water bottle
Your f******
Dumb
B
Or or your
Suggestible
There's other ways to get there other than dumb
Circumstances maybe you live in a small town
No Way Out
Sort of accept
That sort of thing I don't know why
Sincerely.
Judgemental
Yeah I agree
I'm just cuz you're a victim doesn't mean you're dumped no but I also don't want to I don't want to hear doesn't mean you're not.
Humans are the people who are
Caught up in the hustle
What we're talkin about
Hustler's
I understand that that's the worst better for them
Truitt's
God dammit that's dumb
Because end
This is again something that we talked about
I want to be taken in if I were to be taken in by a comment
Top-level Kahneman
These guys are taking in the dumb but also taking advantage of other people circumstances
But they don't have any
Control over
Because of those
Because it's possible
He is a good con man
And for them
Trigger things in other people that it doesn't Trigger or not
True
You know
I don't want this to be some sort of weird
Everything is relative kind of argument
Some things are fairly relative
A good con man
To you is not
The same thing as a good man con man
Does someone in
I don't know
Auxvasse Missouri
You know like Tiny Town Missouri
Place to go there whenever
Right there was a lot of portals
So much
Selma sport Alexa
Bad to be
Text super into the book
I'll get to it a little bit after
When it's going to happen
He said that's going to happen Generations
The Flash
What is a generation will the generation based on Psalms 90:10 is 70 years
So you would say if I could go
70 generations of 70 years which is 4900 years
Statistics
Groups are working on the Holocene impact
Because they think a meteor hit the earth and that's what caused
Vista 4849
The 2829 hundred b.c.
49ers 2015 2016 2017
I thought you were setting up
So
Alright
Whatever I don't think the Hollis
Impact group is a reputable group of science
So if we say
2800 BC was when the flood happen
When did we
We
Stipulate that in the Arkham
Just say whatever
This doesn't
This is tough
To work out with the Book of Enoch
Because
Enoch was Noah's great grandfather
According to the Bible
To use the 70 generator
If 2800 BCU is BCE was on the flood happen
Three generation
Four generations back
I will be around
Enoch would have been around
But the problem is
Book of Enoch sold as parts were written in
300b
And then the most recent parts of them are dated to about 1
So when the flood half
No
I don't think that anyone makes the argument that
Enoch
Wrote the book of
There was in the Enochs now
But it's in the Enoch
Skiing tradition
You don't
Right you don't name the book you right after
That would be very idealistic
A book called
Jordan why not
Because I wouldn't I would wait
Somebody else wrote it
Call Jordan
Come on these sorts of ideas of modesty or modern
Want to write books about
And that's fine
Text thank you but I don't think I can get
I think it's fine for the
If you not had written The Book of Enoch
Centerview
Severe
Severe problem
That timeline when you would have been alive
Is impossible for when the book was written
The other problem is but he's only
A couple books
In the Bible only a couple times
There's maybe like three or four references to
Enoch one being that he
Was along with
He's one of two people who ever didn't die
But God brought him up to heaven
Elijah
People who have never died are Elijah and Enoch
Let's
There's a reference to
But
East
Hey
Hey Jordan
There's no reference to him in
Parts of the Noah story the story of
The fly the Deluge there's no eyes
Grandpa at least one
What is great-grandfather predicted the flood it would seem incredibly relevant those stories of
Noah and the flood were written before the Book of Enoch
So that's why those aren't
In that book
Well they were also written before the
Told about the flood
Plug message been around
This piece of the mythology
If you would have been present
If so many other places
If it were
Some part that wasn't
Pseudepigrapha
Watch later
Book is
Interesting I liked it I think there's a lot of really interesting contest
My favorite part was when Hermione's
Cast the spell in Enoch
Tournament
Into a frog
Something something
There's some that is the best name to a sequel
Something dumplings name for the
I'm liking that
Yada yada yada
Snayper whatever
Yourself and I'm trying
There's a there's a reason that it's not
Included in the canner
For me to say at someone who really doesn't give
In the Bible
There's plenty of Reason Just based on like biblical scholarship look at the times that it was written
Factory was written over the course of like
200 years
Difference
Between the
Like the oldest Parts on the newest parts
Affected comes
From
Traditions that are outside
Of what
I get it
In the fact that he is bringing the same as like a like
Strong primary source
Means to me that
He doesn't care
About like
Actual biblical scholarship
He cares about like oh this is fun
This this sort of
Weaves into my already existing beliefs
That's the way that they treat everything
They trying to create that website
God dammit
You're helping somehow you're frustrated with running I'm not frustrated by it it's just
Are there
Has less obvious
Texting whatever
That's what I do
Jesus
I just
I hate I hate
So much
How do you assholes
Spend all of their time
Demonizing
Scientist
Who are running CERN
Trying to figure out
Universe
The moment they're like
As far as
Giants and portals
You guys confirm what you already know using science
So now whenever somebody disagrees with you
Guess what you have
Giant Schnauzer
Double blind
Forbes
Talk about them
Actually know a guy who worked
Concern
We are bored
What was that game
Ha
Does a Genesis
Where's the guy made of
Oh no I actually know what gif
I used to run a comedy show this guy used to come out to it
Every week
Show up late
Dance party after
And then
Mid late 50s year old guy
Kept to himself
Heat shield for like the last 20 minutes
To the show and then dance
Like crazy
Love it and so I was very confused by
I couldn't figure out what
And soda
Around that time
Mike Timlin
Very funny comedians Mike Timlin
He became one of our
I grabbed them
Your first job
Is to find out what that
Cuz I want to ask him
And I f****** cat
I can't emotionally do it
Just need to know why he's here cuz I
He's not threatening he wasn't James again grabbing on people right you must a problem but he confuse the s*** out of
So first known abuse of an intern
No very first one has ever been
So the end of the night
I talked to him
He works
FTI Hadron Collider
Swiss
He's on vacation
He's doing
He's here first season in Chicago
He's a long vacation
And Jackie loves yoga
So he's late because he goes
Yoga class
But likes to dance
And also likes
The show
Wishes he could come on time
But
Yoga classes more important
Save-A-Lot going on with that guy
You are the best internet ever you got all of the information that you've ever wanted
We never really
Quick bite
The headliner
Is that show or a couple weeks later
Amazing storyteller
Amazing
And afterwards
And this guy who worked at CERN
Ended up at the bar next to each other
I became
FastFrame
A bit guy who ended up doing the blackout Diaries
Captain touch
Super nice guy
So
The only story I have that relates to that is
There is a
Karaoke bar
Attiki
Key themes karaoke
Too many teeth ER
Navigate to Lincoln
There is this guy who
Comes dressed
Scrubs
He comes directly from
Alright alright
But he's
He stings
Every third song
He goes
Hard this dude
His entire life
Is wearing scrubs
Singing this song
And I've always wanted to ask
Whether or not he asked
At a hospital
Never
I never had the
An intern I would know everything about the
Who's the best
Oh God
Michelle
Holy
S*** not going to do it
By the way
You know you know
Convincing
Office out
Talk about stuff not related
Strictly speaking
Do the episode no jump back in
I text
And I told you
For the show
Of information
Indicates to me
Did Jim Bakker
Have not in any way
Wrestled with
What the Bible is
What is cultural historical context is
They know that's from the past
Corn is on here and
Hocking Hills
Translation of the Pacific
Do you know what that is
So
What it is is it
You mocked me for making that you use
Did you notice
The earliest
Greek translation
Like
Depends
Or the auditorium the first five books of the Old Testament
It was something that was worked on
14 years added in a bunch of like
Prophet book
What are called Deuteronomy
Deuteronomy ProBook
Opso
He's
You selling
Translation in
To English
Of the septic
Pronounce that terribly
It's weird there's too many vowels and places you don't expect it
They see something here
That is
Deeply
Deeply flawed
So he wrote fancy
No
I believe we actually accurate
From the Greek
Okay
I'm going to say it's not a great
Translation
Define
But
In this clip Jim Bakker says something and
In response to
I'm talking
About
And then
Something weird
So this would be
The disciples
Whatever
Read from
Listen for Lori's house again
And it we're just
Kickin It Out
We like
2 weeks and we can open the house
I mean two weeks
I mean it's not going to be open
Fire Marshal
To go in
Already married
I got to get some water faucet
Sit down to is well we about to
Finished at all
Weird
So weird
You have an entire episode where they discuss the reality of portals and
Reptiles with Halo
Other life
What's the fire marshal gives us the permit
I just $1,000
Turnover you yelling I think it'll still come up in the audio but like he was like
He's talking about that step 2 again so this is what the disciples read and then Laurie is like
Isn't that a listen
That's it that's what I was hoping to see you just tell him to shut the f****** because his old ass mind is still like
Oh I've got on the thought that I need to sell
Are you
Crazy
So
Do the activity side I will get
This being credit
This is this is where we're talking about the Bible that Jesus would have
So Jim and Tommy both suggesting that the Septuagint is
Because I have some sort of
Different scripture fear scripture
And if they're saying that it's the one that
The biggest problem is
Most of it's not all of Jesus's disciples were illiterate
Professor of theology at the University of London Catherine Hessler estimation
Literacy rate at the
The time and area
When the apostles were alive would have been approximately
Percent
Entirely made up of what you call the culturally
The priests and academics
Of the day
The disciples were definitely not
Specifically
Purposefully not
You had Andrew Peter James and John who are all fishing
One-hundred-percent not know how to read
Fisher of men
12 metaphors used disciples were f****** fishermen because in Galilee that have
Very vibrant fishing economy
Crazy
There was some indications that Judas was previously a thief
Which doesn't require education
Matthew was a tax collector but that position was actually wouldn't
The proper historical context is less than 1 who audits
Spreadsheets are does accounting
Is Boursin who literally takes coins for people and delivers them to someone else
More of a courier or even just someone who sits at a booth when people come and bring them money
As he's described to be in Matthew 9
Simoniz
Described as a zealot which likely means that he was a political agitator against the Roman governor
Which is more of a rabble-rouser
Kind of think America
Political activists
Most
So who know how to read
It was more just like a
The rest of them were likely fisherman
But it's on specific for a bunch of the dudes
Analogies
At the assumption
Statesboro is the Bible describes
Thomas and
Bartholomew
Being caught off guard fishing
At some point like I said
Galilee was a major fishing
Import
The economy
And
The idea that like
One of the most
Famous scriptures
Famous sayings of Jesus
You Fishers of Men
Doesn't really make sense unless you're talking to a bunch of fish guys
And that is the that is a profession
Confirm most of his
They would not have known how to read they knew that's all you need
Jim Bakker
Reselling
Port is selling this
Septuagint
Being what the apostles would have read
F****** horseshit
They don't know
Know how to read
Did you know how to write
And a lot of people might be single how did they write the Books literacy
They did well
Logical conclusion
Didn't accept
Any of the synoptic Gospels
But Paul was almost certainly I believe I believe
Paul was Walmart was literally
Paul definitely
You didn't write even along the lines of
Everything
In the Bible wasn't written by the person that they sing
Almost
Across-the-board
Most people believed to be either a a rabbi or
AAA
Misrepresent wherever right is most likely able to
It's possible there's actually
Two there's two main
Corporate
Historical
I don't I haven't looked into
A long time
Conversations
Professor Zoom
Most
Biblical Scholars
Believe
Is that there are
Inflation's
This was
Crucified
Is not the same Jesus
Who said all the sayings
That are really popular
The Jesus who said all the sayings was a rabbi around that time
Would absolutely literal
Because
Crucified
Around that time
Was
A criminal
And throughout time those two
Persona
Have been Blended
I don't know if that's totally true
Just something that
Some of it was passed onto
By professor
Could be wrong
That's just what indications are because homeless people record around then
And all of
What's that in the Bible
Is them
Yeah it's not there isn't a ton
Matches up
So you have to sort of make
If you're reading the Dead Sea
These girls got to fill in gaps
And Scholars know how to do that
Much better than
Tim Horton's book about a guy
Several hundred years after he
He's already dead
You just started
Well I mean
So now important more importantly I think
I made the biggest
The fact that
None of these dudes
Are being like the apostles couldn't
Feel like that's just
The truth of
You would never you would never accept that
So many modern Christians today would
Never
Ever except that the apostles weren't anything other than
The exemplary human beings of the day
Because we believe that literacy is the Norwegian
Just a bunch of
Everybody knows all those of the Epistles were written by all the Apostle make sense
No
Call the Whole Thing Off
Like a
Actual
Ridership
Open stuff like that is all
Juggling balls
Well you were
I on that wrist
You know like
Assume that literacy is so common now they must have always been
And it's not
Not now every
This up to again
You selling it as if it's like
A pure version of scripture
All it isn't
Translations
The Torah
Would you later grew to include many of the rest of what would be the old
Like Joshua Judges Ruth in the lake
It also contains books later sent to the suit
U-Pick reflect obit
First through fourth Mac
Furbies
The scepter game is nothing
Special release
Just a collection of translation of already exists
Religious texts and writing
That was a result of a project started in the proxy
300 BCE
Conclude around 1:30
2 BC
The name is derived from a story of how it came into being
Allegedly Ptolemy of Egypt
Progressive 72 rabbis
Translate their texts for him
Greek from the original
So he could have a copy in the Library of Alexandria
Magically because God
Each of the seven
D2 working
Independently created identical copies of the Translate
This story is generally thought by Scholars to be both
Give the traces back to
The letter of aristea
Which do today
Styles
Contextual Clues almost certainly could not have been written by the person who claims beer
Princeton Theological Seminary Professor Bruce Metzger describe the letter A
Most Scholars have
Vandalize the letters
Concluded that the author
Could not have been the Manny represented
But was a Jew who wrote it
Fictitious account in order
Importance
Of the Hebrew scriptures
By suggesting that a pagan King
Is there significant
And therefore arranged for their translation into
So
Most
View the letters aristea switch
Has
The colonel.
The beginning of
The story of
Deceptive
As being one of the early examples of religious prophet
So
Hey guys
All this is fun
They are coming
Based on the comments from way back then
A little bit
Really
What is Comic-Con
What do you mean they make
I don't know much more
I mean I think that distance
Right
Easier to see through Scientology than it is to
To see through Christianity
They require scholars in
Contact Telugu esposa Quest
Stupid talking about aliens
How easy it is to
Jim Bakker
Some
Religious figure even in Christianity from 1700
So
Jordan
It is it's just interesting
It really is to know
VidCon
Has been going on
For thousands of years
It's the same fuc
Different angles
So now you're
There's various cons being played sort of
It's a cam that's evolved
But ultimately what it is is it's a short circuit
Of
The human brain
The human brain simple
Cannot get
And that's why this Con works
So you you
See so many people getting conned in the same way
And you can take comfort in the fact
People like this
Have been getting caught
Birth of humanity
And the con always
Ends up being about money
That's also true
Outback
Maybe I don't look
Putting that aside
The end of the last clip before we got off on that Jim doesn't understand that the apostles were illiterate and what the Septuagint
He said that 200,000 more dollars
To open Lori's house
EBay that harsh a won't even give them the go-ahead
And now that makes it
That much weirder than he says this
He starts preacher
Turn this track
Is really f***** up
Can you do that
You just talked about aliens portal
Demon reptiles
And then you're going to try and
It's more important
Very recent
A couple minutes earlier on the show
He was asking for $200,000 to finish Lori
The sun in the moon going to be dark
We are here now
And you must
Get
This book 2
Kmart
For any inquiring minds
Find anybody who really wants
And this is Bible
Back it up
Slack stock
Well
Find out
Read the Bible
Find the portal
Start stopping
Stop
People in the pulpit
What is right and what is wrong and what is
Without
A whole generation
Anything else
Literally
Immature
In the last
Several decades
We have become
Lovers
And the Bible says
The root of all evil
Is the Love of Money
Change
We have another gospel
The real gospel nobody really wants it
Rough start right there
That is the most
That is if you are not going to say this as soon as I am that is the most Alex Jones being thing that he could ever have.
It is first thing he says
Right
You can't
Trust anybody unless you go verify it in the Bible
Now of course I'm telling you it so you don't need to go
Check out multiple times on this episode said things that are
Chris biblically
Because I said them and then because I told you
You to go check whether or not I said them you can trust that I am confident
That you will
Go check what I say
Because we both know that you already checked what I say even though you didn't need to
Maybe second
Nothing I would point out about that click
Then we get to the money part
That's crazy
Is a Alex Jones to the f******
F****** prison
All people
These days is money
With their money-grubbing all they want is money
Most of them haven't gone to prison for fraud
They want the money I'd
Just have to live in their world
I know how to live in their world because the Bible told me
To take their money
And you don't even need to check on that because you can read it
But like in the church for the last couple decades
People who are into money
A couple technical G went to prison for that
Don't bring up yourself
The Prosperity Gospel you have on your truck
Very clearly to Prosperity Gospel
You are but what am I
It's crazy to me like what are you
Saying
Now
That regard
Based on what you just said
Please accept me when I say
If you buy that s*** your
In your life
Way
If you're not like if you don't have that phone have a second of like
Maybe this time
You know what I say
Disgaea
F******
Clearly loves money kind of loves money
200 g for faucets
And then bitched about how everybody else was all about money
Weird weird
The very
The Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse really
Is there going to be
By the
Disease from the animals what is HIV a where does it come from
Awesome animals
Animal
What's iPod
We're going to kill people
But it was
One word
What's wrong
And we have a lot of
I don't understand what that means but it's
Not that important
It's so weird
I can tell you that what he said before that clip started.
I've no idea
Hold on hold on
We are people trying to say the bubble God wants you to be rich I do I bore you with that thought but it's
Want you to be rich
Right
Holyshit
What the f*** is happened
That's going off the rails now
Him to get into heaven
That is just fact the Bible says that pretend
Please why
$200,000
F****** sinks
Do you understand that what he's doing is
Is he
Basically
Refuting
A lot of the
The ideas that he
The General
It's a seed you're planting you give me money at the end
He's refusing to be rich
You should give all the money here
It's got to be better that way it makes me feel like he's in
Trouble
Like maybe he doesn't need that 20,000
For the snakes
Maybe he owes back taxes
Is there something like that
Miles
He's not a he's not a church
He still got it
No he's still got it
I didn't know what he gets
Tax exempt status
Man it would be wild if he was
Prison for fraud
Exempt status
Churches
Very political profit-based
Go to same thing with that Courtney Brown with the Pharcyde
Right
I love that we've added Jim Bakker
Because
Jim Bakker is the pretzel
Did Alex and Kara
Right bro answer me Alex is
Alex is so Money Motivated
That is kind of boring is there
And Carrie Carrie is Money Motivated but she also has a little bit more of that Love of the Game
She like being wild for being wild say
Jim Bakker is the perfect mix of the two that is the most hungry no money-grubbing man and at the same time
F*** yeah let's talk about reptoids disagree
The thing is
What time
I don't know this is
I don't like a lot of Wes Anderson
Too cute
All of these are fair criticism I don't like the idea of them children act like adults I think that's
Stupid
Whatever
Be that as it may one time I was talking to my brother about it and he
You said
He really appreciates when you look at the
The bigger body
His work is that most of the movies
You could take them and they embody the
Spirit of being assertive
So you take
Like
Give me the movie I'll tell you that
You're at
Like aimless 20s
Okay we're like I should have amounted to something
Calm and you did sort of struggling through a cloud maybe I'll become a bank robber
Maybe pop
Possible that's the life for you and you entertained
Stupid possibilities
Spiritism
Captured all right
Moonrise Kingdom is when
You are like 12 and you fall in love with somebody and it seems so epic
When it's really not
Play out the theme of it being like
This profound beautiful things you have to fight for in reality it's not
It's the idea of your fur
First love
Is embodied in Moonrise Kingdom early childhood
It's sort of like a
Kind of don't buy
And also
And also this. Was this theory was Pitch to me before that came out
Do we have a prepared Royal Tenenbaums
And your parents get old and die
Your whole life has become like the disillusionment of
The past generation
I mean the the the life
Aquatica
When you come to the end of your career and you realize you're no longer useful in the way that you used to be
That sort of struggle
To each of his movies have like this
Profound
Not right of passage necessarily but this Pivot Point
In people's lives
Profound
Moments
Allowed me to approach
Appreciate some of the movies more away that you didn't
Watching of the movie your kind of like
This is webull
I hated them but I didn't like them that much
Long winded as hell is that I think we have
Different periods in a propagandist
Career
Depicted by these three
You just had that all together
We have Carrie who
I mean in there all probably around the same
Bakery
How old is Jim Bakker
Methuselah is a million years old
Bright that guy's going to be calling long after we're dead
Presumably 45
Whatever.
Gary's R50 probably in Baker 7
Age of side
You have Carrie still
Searching for the truth
You have Carrie at
He's crazy
And still like
I will talk to
Like I texted you earlier I listen to
The dishwasher
Why would you do that
You're f****** hungry
And you're hoping that he's not lying for the
That's a big swing
You're going to miss most of the time but a couple times going to be home run
Willing to cut
Then you got Alex Jones
Who is just like
I'm in the middle of this
I've made some
Some mistakes
Imma s*******
Whatever
I don't care I don't care
I fallen in with the wrong crowd
I'm in the middle of this
I'll try it
And probably get Redemption later
Currently resign he's like I am this is my
And I am resigned to
And then Baker is the guy who's
DD's over the hill he's still just doing this because it's what he knows how to do
Good attitude if you go to prison for and then go back to doing it
Yes
Exactly what that's the only thing I know is late career he's the Steve's
Yuzu of the con
Not bad would bring it back
So there is that right
Appreciate that
Picture of these people that like
Different
Stages of the con
The life of the car
Is a pecan
There's a to-do list
Yeah that's true I want a young man who's got
Castellan a message of
Hope it's hard it's hard to find
Cuz all of the young cons now or all about
Get them fired from Disney or whatever the
They do.
The twisting of the
Is really hurt
The convent
Has become almost a magnet for those people
To get your s*** not hard
Get your s*** reposted like
My crazy ass say the right inflammatory
I'm so these people
Very easy like if you are a Converse
You're obviously more motivated by
Publicity
Yeah I'm motivated by traction than you are from actually
Substance
So we are like the the Fox News 21 year olds like Laura Loomer
Or something like that
What are what are the ones that are like
I don't even know their name Lorraine
Just a talking head on
She couldn't do it her on her own
You can say like a Ben Shapiro or something
Yeah he doesn't he's not he's not playing the exact same game
Other difficulties to that like
Jalen Jordan rate whether or not somebody could become a good kind they have the chops
I think I don't know man like there is
Looking at
People who come up on in Fort Worth
From time to time
Anybody got
The goods Shroyer doesn't have now
If there's anybody who he's had on his like
Do you think it might be a problem I think is important is
If you're going to
Become a legit person
In the vein of the the trio that we talk
About one of the most important pieces
You need a backup
Support system
Yeah so far carry it's people like Mark Richards
People like a weirdo from England to Banks around with an alien in Alien
Alex
Now Rodger stone for that Larry Nichols
Gerald Celente
All these guys
Robert
All these weird Prosperity Gospel preachers
The come in like the Tom Horn
Siri
Generation of the con
Our generation of the con
Like it's a it's a collective mind it's a hive Minecon
That's who's coming up
It's the 14 and 15 year olds
It's a 25 year old or 35 year old girl
Pretending their fourteen-year-old
And they all Amplified together
Nearest Walgreens
Same charismatic
Charismatic leaders are going to be
On the other side
Or is it because of what I was talking about earlier with the mag
Amortization of all this to the right
Not happening towards
I have people on the left or Connie
Presumably
Ostensibly
People like to Louise Mensch
The left
I don't think there is
I don't think there are valid
Media folks on the left who are doing
Is it is it work I think there are Fringe voice
But like
But if you're on the left
Lexicon is ultimately a right-wing
The cam is always AIDS
Nobody
Connor's always I'm going to
Convince you to act
Your own interest
By making you think that your interest
The interest
Sure
So like if you want to go with your you're like Alexandra
She is not your Cortez f****** con the s*** out of people but she's on the left and so her I
Idea is
I'm going to take your
And I'm going to make them my in
And that's where all going to be moving forward
The reason that I have paws
Always been
Tableau
Yeah
Don't extrapolate
5 years
That might not have been
You know what I mean yours on the left
You were trying to make
Michelada
And a lot of them do that they aren't there more in Trench
Winston like Mega
They don't have radio shows
But that's probably
Just because
That's where they got a gig
As opposed to the right-wing
Is so entrenched
Through the Koch brothers
I don't know it
That's an interesting conversation for another day hours
I think a little bit but we can't because you're you're
You're right in a way that I wasn't
Expecting
Not like
Think you're Dumber wrong
I do
There's something to be said for that
The idea of the crowdsourcing
In terms of these message
In reality
Is
There will rise
Some other Khan
YouTube
Form I don't know
Could be could make his own channel or some
Something like that is a damn prophecy is what this is
Probably the most natural progression history right you have
Examples of people like Mike Stern
There will be someone who creates their own thing
And it won't be that
The 4chan
The Reddit
All that stuff all that crowd
Will be the con
Unnamed
The backdrop
For the con
That'll be your pretend
Xavier Stone
Exactly
But the problem is that in the reason why I think that is a Unser
Sustainable economy
Is because
What makes it work
With Patron
What makes it work with Rodger Stone
Is that
They will show their face and
And talk right they will be on the show and say things
That Alex can use
This is this is evidence of where is it rabbit message board
Again you're right
Creating samsic face
Right you can't really bring them on his guests
Unless you just
Kamal anonymous
Representatives Brenda and that doesn't
Carry the same weight but that's when we start getting into
I would say so
Fair enough
What's a hundred percent bail myself out about the connection here maker
I mean the most popular
Version of rhizome Theory
Like ghosts in the shop
Like that kind
Out of the out of the
Out of Fortune
Out of this
Nebulous Mass
Hive mind
Will come a
Represent
Qanon
But but there will be a person who is the embodiment
Of this Kuna
Who
Well that will happen once we're able to really protect this
Facial
Like
Pacino movie
Like that Al Pacino
There we go
Alright alright
Look at that
Where we talked
What is mostly move faster
Went off on that too
Dude
Jim Bakker
Archetypical example of someone
Using religion to make money
You coming on and being like
Doing it
You are the archetypical example because of when he went to prison
And now you're
Still doing it baby and that's why that one
If it weren't for you you were the Trailblazer
You f****** a******
I don't know why I need to extend
Did the con
Paula White
Cool
A really polite team
With the con
In many ways
Prosperity
Ross.
Work yourself
Into
The presidents
Thought year
She's not doing
Conwright
Because before
We did that at
So you had no idea who she was
What you think most of our listeners had no idea I was like
She's a
I didn't know who she was until you said
She's purple into the influence
So much
Into the pit
The pr
And that means
He's not in the
She's a power player is very very clear
Like
Once you start stalking you know the game
Kristen like Beltway Paula
I'm trying to pee is a word talk
If you follow her she's got
Sponsored content that you don't know
Exactly
I think it's a different kind
Alright
We're still doing the show right now
One of the things that we always talk about is like trying
These worlds to each other which
Decent job
In this era stations
Who's gone off on
But I already say that
There's another one where Tom
Boy this sounds like
Something that could
Just be set on Alex's Joe
Any of them really
Become
I've leaving their fix to stay that's what Peter says if what Jude says
Somebody in the spirit of incarnation
Forgot
Speak into existence like
But they participated
Hazard scientist records
The genetics unique
It was something
I'd of the divine order
So
He said
My boy talking about chimeras
Is my boy talking about
Talking about genetic alterations
B Team
Chimera adjacent
However
They do know the basic amino acid structure
Capable of altering
Don't you dare
Like if God's Line in the Sand is like you can do the same thing as me but I can just go do it like
Not sure
Not sure this is a good vision
I think that's why were God I would say
Reserve that power for myself
Darken Watchers it sound workaround
I found
Waze
Anytime you get really into the weeds of theology
Sooner or later
They always point out
Loopholes in their own belief system
Lexus
Of course
It's always like they create this
Did they create the
Bulshit
God
Brennan is God is
To have been created bulshit
That allowed the dumb things at the dump
Stupid make
My minion
But I created them with
All of the abilities
Now their argument to that would be the goddess super into
Free will
Choose not to do that
I'm pretty sure that
What about
He's not real dad
What are you talkin about the lullaby
Abso
I was thinking
I guess I wasn't
Like I said
My boys
It's not a cow
Knockout
Since I first
Yeah and that means
Angel souls or whatever can get in there
That's why they were going to kill us
Could be a I don't know what you were talking about
Xerocon
Nope
You can just say one word was wrong and then not say what that word cuz he started jumping off into like everyone wants money
Vetline of
Really clear they're talking
Inference humanism in America
We are creating animals with human DNA inside is not from Missouri
It's his upper Missouri cuz if he was any voice you would have said Missouri
I know that much
That's my alma mater Aika
Tell you with almost categorical CertainTeed
Are not doing 100%
They don't have anywhere near the funding going to happen
154 the somebody emails mail so don't actually book
Novella
Assert that they are being created around the world
Reaching human
Exactly
Cuz he's friends with Steve Quayle the same thing all of this goes back to Syracuse
God dammit
Crossbreed
Open the show yesterday sing
Would know if I said what about CERN what do you know about CERN
Right
How many people know the stories around the world we are creating Human animals
They're supposed to be destroyed
Origami
Call Bing.
Destroyed
Would be like a new form of methylene
This is just a less charismatic version of galaxy
I hate to be Petty
But it would be the islands
Do doctors Marrero
Much much like it's Attorneys General
This is just another example of them warping
Things about science that are weird
These f****** people
Stevequayle.com
Unfortunately read a book
CERN
We do
And this is
This is pretty fun
When the angel comes down
Over them down there which is not worth
Apollyon
And of course.
Door into another universe
Wow
Correct
The other part of that is
That's f****** dumb what does churn mean
Translation
The name do you got
Cerm
I know it was originally
No I can get it
First of all
Dance the long pause and then I used to know I forget not great not great
Initial
That's right
It was a French acronym
What time is it
And like I said was a French acronym
What except the name
What my question is what does sir mean could have
I mean could it be connected to something else as well
What's interesting that in The Weeknd Faith there are two main
It's called the horned God herne the Hunter
If you look back to the conventional name given to it by the
The seltzer
The name given
Is
You're not
Actually the god of the underworld
So he is ready blog
The most Wild
Disconnected bulshit I think I've heard from somebody who is scrambling to remember
How to get rid of
Zach
How is it that you can say that it used to be a French acronym but then you
You cannot say what that acronym
Good for
You too and it takes its name from what the group was originally called the concert
Yale European poor little research
Nucleaire
Believed in that acronym was
Substantially better than what they would have ended up with when they change their name
Do the organization European nucleaire
Oprf is a perineum
Acronym when they change their name from
To organize seal
So like
Councils organization
Yeah you know what sucks
Because Council suggests that it's a small group of people making decisions
Fargo Boise
Yeah
It's been the organizer on European pull research nucleaire
Since 1954
They changed the name design but if kapiti the abbreviation
Concern
No because
Cuz the Celts
Forward sucks
So one of the reasons the idiot conspiracy theorist
America are probably more prone to targets
Is because we're not a member of the
Associate
We have Observer status
Which was held since 1997 but we're not an active
Participant
Rankled some feathers
Sure I put
That's what it is so there's some sort of anti-American
Projection
I think a lot of people like
These folks are feeling about this
And you can feel it in the same way there's like I think it's
The French acronym
It's a French acronym for
The Council of European Research into nuclear stuff
You're not like it's
Most
Simple acronym that you could know if you did
Annie
Any understanding
Siri search the French acronym
French acronym like
Look like in French means
Sprint then he
Like he's saying it's a French acronym as though
Who knows what those people think Akron
Weirdos
But it's that
Anti
Anti other
Mentality
It's it's
Crazy everywhere
It's crazy to me how we
Began this app
Episode
With Jim Bakker saying
There is only one God
Jehovah
And then at the end of this as well as we continued on through this
Jim Bakker believe now that every mythology is real
He must yeah or at least every every God from everywhere service
Celtic now why
What
Celtics
Actually
But let's username is
Some of that though
You were not unpacking correctly
I think I think there's a
Decent amount of that that is
Put up with that sort of thing
There's a little bit of
Ascribed
Subscribing to
Every
While he still brings
Fear of everything
I think there's some wiggle room it's not great
I'm going to you know what if it was like once
Add more lean towards you but it seems like they're bringing up all
Throwing everything like we got Shiva in there we got the
Son got in Arizona
We got Apollo is the one who's going to come up from the ground
God knows that Apollo is there like
Everything is real
Deep within the Earth
What happened on
Deity
I hate that
The celt I might even write a review
No one
Is
There is
Cernunnos
And his other name is Larry Bird
Perry rapist
So the name cernunnos only exists in one place
It's on the pillar of the boat
Which is something that was from around 1st Century be
Ciara, naira
You said I'm going to make you boaters at met
Anime Kubo
Motorboat benintendi
I'm losing it towards the end of this
Certain
Exist only on this pillar
The name Cyrano says existed or nowhere else
Great antiquity
Deny that you've told me that that's going to hot
Probably put theirs
Is so fast
You just ruined my life I don't remember what the word for it is but there's a whole collection of like
Words that only exist in one place
Play sever
Yeah we have these like
All these texts from history
One time that was a one-time word
The one-off
This name exists on the pillar of the
Which was
The first century CE
Discovered
It doesn't really matter cuz their nose plays like
7th banana on that pillow to Jupiter
And a host of Romans
Garlic garlic
Yes
Conjecture that he was your friend
Historia
Conjecture that he was the Lord of
Animals or Wild Things based on
Scorned appearance
Chimera do you have horns
Sure
But there's a lot of there's a lot of DVDs overtime
There's a lot of chimeras
That's right like a bunch of other people have asserted that he's the god of
Fertility
And some subways
God of the underworld
Is also in there but it's
1 of 12
He's not one to one associated with the underworld like Zack
Who's dumb
Is thanks
So dumb
Now it's interesting because some forms of Wicca
Have taken on recognizing Serna
But only as much as they will take on about any God from
Nothing against the wiccans out there
But you love a hornet sound like
And so I thought I feel like
I don't know this Universal I don't know what you're going to say and I
Do what I think you're going to say it doesn't sound
From my experience with Wiccan
Go to high school
I feel like the horns are going to be important
No no
I have some
Anakin
It's not a blanket
It seems like
People who are
Drift drift that direction
Also where people who are kind of nerdy
And like obscure things
So I would
I would suggest
People who are attracted
Two wiccanism are also people who dude
Reading into
Various cultures around the world various deities
And probably someone was like
I found this
F****** obscure horned God
I meant certain toast came to be
I know Zach is making scary things
Because this one bowl image
Killer
It was stuck in fairy.
Underground
This was all a chicken laid out in the prophecy by Douglas Adams called The Long Dark teeth
Oh my God there's a Babel Fish
His books he's probably means he's Illuminati he stepped into the
God what
Jerk
Efeis
Yes
I wanted one more clip
But I didn't cut it cuz it was pointless
The apostles read the Septuagint
So
There's one thing I think
Lowest number
Between our worlds yes
Project Camelot
Alex Jones
And
The Jim Bakker almost had created a parallel universe where all of these were
On this exact
But I think there's one
On
A deeper level
Connect
Alex Jones
Scary Carrie cast
And Jim Baker's
It's not
It is this trend
Constrain
About his genetic
You mentioned a moment ago
Of the field
And you said when you were in prison
Spherion
Real quick
The part that Jim Bakker was talking about
Very clearly cutout it's episodes
That's not something it's reference back to
Also I don't know what Greek word he's talking about but let's
Butterfly
And the reason is simple
Translated these
It's because it essentially means
Like Mike
Stop it
5B
About
Maybe we'll come over friendly animals but
If Michael
Dangerous
Maybe that's
The 4th
Maybe it's something like that
Did you ever see the movie I Am Legend with Will Smith
What to use vegetable for people so real quick
Virus real
Nothing but the dreams of man dead
Elucidating
Trends that are part of the human condition
What is a metaphor allegory
Everything was just
Trippy weird
It would be
Walking fast
Very clearly misrepresented this
So now I'm at the one with Will Smith
That's right
Dude that's
F****** he's old enough
Vincent Price
Rush that
2K for him to talk about
This
From all over the place
That was.
A butt
The Jesus of
I Am Legend
Is very worth okay
People understand
If naturally immune
Create
This
You take that back
The Antichrist know
Does the antithesis of Jesus right
Jesus was the Son of God the son of the devil
Somehow he is the amphitheater called his doctor
Well
Jesus also said
Communion the Antichrist
To create a situation where is sweeping the world
People are dying and there's only one
Is naturally immune to this disease and it turns out to be the Antichrist
From this disease in the form of
With the blood and flesh
I see one problem with this Beyond Myriad of problems
The Antichrist
My Flesh and my blood
Wouldn't it be just like
Drink your blood to survive
The way he's working in a metaphor is
Is troubling because there's one guy who's
Has Jesus
Nearest idea of that being your fee logical
Argument it wouldn't be
Just like we aren't surprised that one just like the Antichrist
Omani
F******
Sarah all the way
Do you like the Antichrist return
Fishes tequila multitude of Loaves and Fishes wifey Antichrist to raise Lazarus from
Exact same thing
How f****** stupid ass a fire long before
In the middle of it you're saying that God and Jesus is the one who say unless you take of My Blood
And my flesh you will die
I think you're like
The bad guys going to f****** do that and I'm basing this on a metaphor I'm making of misunderstanding
If you would actually
Read the f****** Omega Man you another the reason that he is Legend is because he's
A bad guy
That would make far more sense because if you wanted to
Work in the idea that these zombies
Really bloodthirst
The zombies
Dave community
Relationship
They are only monsters in the mind of the person
Abused them is Monster High
Then you might accept
Is a better metaphor from the I Am Legend Omega Man
Being the one who's trying to trick you into thinking
State you are cumin
Or whatever
I do love
So much
All of these people are just like
Have you ever seen The Matrix exact it's all that it's so much
Like
I get it
Movies of fun reading card
That I struggle with it
Like the other night that Carter page came out
Man this is a lie
Suck
Warrants are bored I wish there was a movie I can compare this
It's just like that I don't know.
Is lot of shortcuts
And propaganda
Oh my God
So I don't know we've learned
Thoroughly learned
That
Chimeras are real man
Chimeras are real if you know Steve
Also
All religions
Are real
There's only one God the all the religions are real but they're not God
The Earth
Absolutely
Bigsby amongst all these shows
Near that someone licks their lips run
Run
Close to
You f****** fail
Bale
What else
Marketing campaigns are lure
Right not hard you don't look into the apostles couldn't
God
It seems like 200,000
Is too much rest
Big time
Yeah
Imagine imagine the amount
A wheelchair ramp
You have to have a Federal Regulation but the girl all the way around all the way up to
The doors and the windows.
Just how that fire marshal work
From being in the
Is open
You did get that $200,000
What is shock
What a show car show
Fantastic
I don't know if we hit all the things you hope to recover but
Weird episode
Appreciate it so much
Go to knowledge buy.com
Rob
Can go to iTunes download libreview you know the stuff the podcast I've always said to you since
We're terrible at marketing
If you want people to like our show
Tell them that we were actually named after
Flooded out
Is what we would call it
I got it
Has been a lot of fun
There's so many
F******
I'm going to have to go with
You lying ass dumb motherfuker Tom Horn goes
Fuc yourself
Holding
Alex