Alexandra Thurston color
Particular
Showed up to
Who made the recommendation
You're hearing that we had been
Novelty Inc lesson lagunita thing more
Cherry jeans
Sour ale brewed with Turkish delight cherries
The Turkish delight cherries is what really worries me is someone who I grew up when I was growing up
Wardrobe
The book so much
Cuz you know my parents were they loves
Is better than one or the other thing
C.s. Lewis
Stephon Tuitt
Turkish Delight in what gets Edward to flip and go with the ice cream sound like
Be amazing
My mom was like I'll make you some
You can make it hard to make Turkish delight
I don't
It's sort of like a gelatin
Take a little bit of a
Powdered
Like a little treat it's very sweet
The flavors
Legitimately
Same situation except I've never actually
Target store
Whenever I found out that
Edward
Was willing to sacrifice his entire
As well as as well as Aslan
God on this Earth don't forget about toughness
Willy's
Right now
That's a whole different story but he was willing to give it all up
Turkish delight
Sweet
Really really shows the deprivation
Hydrate
Terrible
But I found it to be really underwhelming
I think now is the time for you to take
As far as c.s. Lewis goes did you ever get into the other Trilogy that's the one about
Like
The allegory on
Venus I did not read it. Read I read a lot of his other ones about like
God
Like a lot of those weird Christian apology book
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I was really smart when I was like
14 reading
College k-life L Owen
Alright
All right you were
First I was acting like Alex does
Understood remember understand
Super thrilled that I understood it like me
Must been like 30
You're So reading
He's talking about the idea that like when you
You see waterfalls
You call it the blime
If you do something within yourself
But that's what you're recognizing
Because I'm not in a great mood but
Maybe it's the same as looking at the waterfall
The opposite not terrible it's not terrible but this is not my style of beer
Like the band
Necessarily
It's not terrible I got
Just not my snot my
I'll drink it
I understand why someone would like it
There is a lot of
Too much Turkish
It's like a
Whatever you get a Coke
And you're like I would like a Cherry Coke in there like we don't have
But we'll put a cherry
Cherries
And then you also put in some
Alcohol
Like that's what it is
Second
That'll be positive
Emergency episode that's on a Saturday
Chaos
Alex Jones
Infowars
And this is a rare
Where you do know what we're talkin
Most news sources
Everybody's kind of miss
Sing of the point
A little bit I think
I don't think we've ever said that about the mainstream media covering
Couple articles
Nikes
That were like this is bulshit
You know like this
Too little too late
In terms of any kind of puny
Is measure against
Because Jordan knows I can't imagine anyone not know
Just last week on Thursday and Friday Alex suffered
Meaningless blows
He had on Thursday
He had some videos
Taking down from YouTube streaming band
YouTube the song is
Who cares this is like it doesn't
Matter good for videos taken down
He wants
Emma streaming stuff doesn't really matter
Yeah
Although I did listen
Thursday just
A star with a blow-up
A little silly but I promise
Realized
From this place is going to be so great
I got a narrative if you don't give me money now
Going to do the job for these people are doing is more or less
His hook
Like four people
It's only going to work for people who are already in
Tightening the grass
He has on people who have already bought his b*******
Map to some extent
I go back and forth on
Whether or not
That matter
You know like
If those people are in your not going to get them
No matter what
You do right
So
I don't know if that's
Sara Lee a negative
I don't I don't know if you should allow that
Facebook YouTube Twitter
Play but I don't know but I do know that
Doing what they are doing
Stupid
His financial dealings
Thursday
We don't need to cover that and I was in a bad mood on Thursday if I didn't
I couldn't do it episode
And then
On Friday last night
Facebook
Decided they were going to
Everybody's having a good
I believe
Conviction tell me that it
Because they're cowards
YouTube made a move and they're like well this gives up
Discover to do something
Kicked off Facebook for a month
No there's a personal account
Play right before we started recording I went on
Infowars
Still has a blue checkmark on Facebook so does the Alex Jones
Public figure account
Spencer this s*** I mean everybody that knows you is on your Facebook
F*** off no impact whatsoever
Run those
Account through someone else's personal account
Or just be like hey Rob do you got a new job for a month
Just run an advertisement saying guess what are the globalist we have no power at all
You are now able to advertise off of us
Forever we only have an interest in covering our ass
PR optic smoo right but it really is advantageous
To you and your rhetoric
And all that
Put that because first exactly
Alex Jones Alex Jones
Actually did anything
Slightly more money
I guess I guess it's kind of almost like they all know that and they're all sort of Plan B
Same game
Wherever one Hedges their own bat
No one really makes a move
The people who get hurt are
You know Youmans
We are you know the human people write the people who is rhetoric Alex
Actually affect
People who
Things like that
People who get hurt
I've been a longtime proponent of
Don't kick Alex off
He's committing a crime
Or whatever
Financial crimes
I don't know it's not my job to figure that out
I hate to punch on it
Because I should have an opinion but I don't really because I don't run Facebook
I don't run YouTube
That's not my decision to make
And quite frankly if I did run them I would have
Kicked him off long ago
It's not a question now should he be kicked off right now we should have been
It's even ask the question
In the moment
It's an absurd question
It doesn't reflect reality
So I mean did you ask me what I would do in this situation I would say I would never let myself
Be in this situation
Warise Facebook or YouTuber
You pulled her up from the route you don't snap a little bit of there please
And whatever Financial incentive any of those
Is dwarfed by other
Video game channel
Gusting rhetoric
You know I mean
Text snowflake Zumba 91
Glitter just like hey why is stardew Valley great cool
Fine
To try
You know like the weather it's my dear Irish friends or the or the buds
Diversionary attack on all of their videos
Great
But that idea a couple years before BuzzFeed start.
And I pitched
Groupon
Back when I work there I will go try all of the Groupon
Lisac's
Experience and make a YouTube video that it capitalizes on
Fear of missing out
State
Comedian
I'll be fun why not do that we'll get a lot of views
Free marketing for Groupon
More less
They're like
So I mean
My pettiness aside about that those videos
Farm
Really make sense
Stupid
Did
What you do now with this
Facebook
Does YouTube penalty all you're doing is
Is taking away your own credibility
And your own ability
Anyway
All you're doing is
Making it
Very clear
That we will punish you in
Symbolic
Wrist slap only
And nothing more
It's D2 things
Some extent
For their own
Apathetic
That's insulting to Kabuki theater
So
I think this is
This is sort of stayed most of my
About these
YouTube
And how like
All they really do is
Display in Dallas
But the one thing I thought was interest
Thing was when I heard
Can be banned from streaming
That goes through the Ron Gibson
Some Channel
These are going to do it there
So on Thursday I checked him
Also
And that made me think like maybe they are taking this very seriously and trying to chop off the little tentacles
Psycho you're clearly getting around the band
But Ron Gibson
Yeah so he just started a second Channel
And posted a link
In his
On Friday
Streaming
Second Channel
So they are taking
Kind of seriously what
Which is fine
But again as we already pointed out he doesn't really have that many people watching
Interesting
Because his second Channel
Ron
So he jumped at which
Okay on Friday
Stream don't
But about an hour and a half
Which clearly kicked the channel
For streaming
He's going to end up
Probably
Gab
Or video or so
Interesting
YouTube was at least
He has multiple times
Yeah
Facebook
Infowars actual pages
Still up and running
The public figure Alex Jones pages
All of the Infowars personalities are allowed to go
A little bit of the
I guess
No I don't even think
The convenience of Alex
Yeah
He's slightly in
He has to log into a different
Bright that's it
This all stems
Basically
From a couple of videos that
Decided
Did not
Follow their community
And I
Prove that these are
The exact videos
Infowars
Paul Joseph Watson posted
The videos in question
That
The band
Yeah therefore videos that got taken down
Mysteriously
Free on the article that
The PJ dubs posted
But I guess
She's busy and I'm not going to
I don't think that's a
Conspiracy
But so one of them is Alex being really mad about a cartoon called ragtop
Which is not really it's not really for kids
As part of RuPaul's Drag Race
It's like that band for a video about
He's correct,
Children
Right
I really just
To me I look at it
Sturtevant
This is like My Little Pony the new one
Dido
It's not for me but
It is what it is
Valances
Anti crossdresser anti-trans
Content
It really doesn't even
So drag tots
Was there a Line in the Sand
Not all of the other s*** I can come up with
The video dead
Territory
Because he does run footage
Do children
From a show
About kids who like to cross-dress probably some
Documentary series
Maybe
I don't know I have no f****** idea
Identify
You know they were on that show
It shows their names
Stop
He's running the
Did she does get into
Like
His gross pedophile
Demon Rancic
I could
Stupid people watching it
Identifying the people who are on
Screen
Is being
As evil as Alex's
Screaming about
It's really nothing different than I've seen him do
Many times before
It is
He said we've been talking
For 10 years
Yeah Boy last night from from 2000s
What is Extreme it's definitely more of a focus
That's probably just be
Because it caught fire on the
Video is clearly over a month old
Shaving
And all it is is Alex talking about Muslims taking over Europe
He's commenting on a video of a
Emmanuel macron
Speech
Something really different from his normal stick but
He does say that after Muslims take over Europe they're going to blow up the planet
Those ones are going to kill the entire world
It's cruel it's manipulative and
Deeply bigoted
But
The past
So I don't care about that I don't
What's up just they're just going to take over the world and then blow it up or they're going to blow it up in the
The implication that he makes them
New is bit whenever Muslims get in charge of something with everybody
Because they're somehow
I don't know genetically incapable of peace
Weird
Horrifying
Disgusting
Not out of line with Infowars regular content
Absolutely nothing
Were they just stolen somebody else's viral video
Little kid flexing on a grown man
Right around with him for a little bit
About after about 20 seconds kids start hitting the guy
Another guy grabbed the kid by the neck and throw them to the
The kid starts wailing
I'm not either
It's weird and they're playing it with some weird music behind it but
The Highwaymen Silver Stallion I could see an argument that this would be seen as child and
But only because the video is titled how to prevent liberalism
Which Wich
It implies in some way that the guy is standing up to the aggressive
The child that represent
Liberals
I think what gets in fours Off The Hook from my position
Is it the very endearing mcbreen comes in doing the voiceover and says quote
Prevent liberalism used
Condoms
Which makes
Dosa
Zero cents
I know it's comedy I know it's an attempt at comedy
I was going to say you you saying that it was
Very generous
If you use condoms and I kid wouldn't be there maybe
But that guy clearly wasn't the kids. So that makes no sense
Is the implication that unsafe sex
Create liberals
Because
It's clearly a bulshit attempt at being funny
I give this a pass
In terms of like why you would ever Center their channel for it
I understand if you are writing person YouTube
A video titled how to
Prevent liberalism and then a grown person assaulting a buck
Child how to make
Conservatives are grown men fighting children
I think
Early reports on it might have
If implied that Alex was the adult in that video
What
Make that
Mistake is
Is that
Alex and that guy have
Oh that really shity beer
Only persons
The only actors
Could get to
To really pull that off
Was it him
It was not did he say
Dial not liberal
No it wasn't that I don't know the only reason that I think
There might be some
Claims
The people said it was him
Is it
Antarctica
Probably head of Correction
That's it
Initially reported Alex
In the video
No one else that he could be other than the guy who stuck in throat
Everyone
Covering Alex Jones
Because if you're covering him
I don't know if they're the most reputable biggest name in news
But if you are in any way cover
And you miss report
That he is the person assaulting that child
Even if you immediately make a correction you have just given him
The greatest gift
Could ever give yeah
You have to play
Very tight
These people
Because
Make a mountain
You make about them is going
He played for Sasha
For them
So anyway
I've been up being kicked off for videos that incite bigotry
No s***
But he does that all the time
If you're going to
If you're going to make that a serious
Complaint your levying
Go through all of it
Give him strikes were all that throw him off your f****** platform forever
Reply
There to everyone
Denver
What is giving me pain
Yep
Further
I have heard the the
The statement date
Is being charged
Is a child endangerment
Because of that video
DHHR
Peace was never that he was the person
Making the video
Yeah he's make it you will later in this episode
Make it seem like that
People
It's more
That
The child endangerment affect comes from
Him presenting
This guy assaulting a child is sort of
Positive
Which is not good and that seems to be his
Main goal in life
First video about the
Where are you getting it
Really dicey territory
Where he's doing his
Is demon screaming over actual children could put them in a position where
1 mi
I don't know if that
Based on all of these social media places actions in the past
Maritz
Kicking him off
But I mean I get the argument
And if you don't not up
Just actually kick him off
Then just stop
Yourself
All this is nothing daddy shooting people
Provider the house
Sweet
That's brutal
Chokeslam official video that they made
It's not like they grabbed
Specifically
Produce that they didn't write
They didn't do anything
Nope
They stole it
Copyright issues
I don't know if
27th episode
Things about Alex
Play satellites
All the drama
All of the
Articles that missed the
The point
Define on the 27th of probably Alex screaming
I probably didn't like
The globalist are afoot they're going to take us
What I'm more expected
Over the course of this episode
You'll see exactly what I mean
I don't want to tip my hand
Too much but
Alex
There's not a contacts dropped from Today Show
What
Just for
N-word
I had the videotape but Alex
Also I want to do this real quick I'm sorry we had that bad that bit of a 25-minute intro
I don't know
You don't believe
That's my boy
Shout out to
Eva
Thank you so much thank you so much for joining up skiba
Acknowledge
We jumping Today Show the first 5 minutes of the show
Because Alex operates is
5 minutes
Is optional on what station
Because a lot of them do news at the top of the hour
Great songs
No not at all not at all
The songs are just
I can tell you that's random on the clock that's just because he really have
Now because he has this clock that he operates off of
The first 5 minutes
The show will be him
Doing the best of what's to come
Imagine if John bowne has a new video out
Hilde Foothill Place
And then coming
6 minutes later
Today's episode Mark Dice
Is doing that doing a little bit of
Little Mike Tyson business
Hey how you doing
It shouldn't be but so Mark a lot of his videos are him
Doing really bad man I'm just
Street
I know I know where
Who is it how is your nose
I mean
I mean like I know we've been over this 10 million
And I know it's
Looking if you
You're going to go after
Alex Jones
Why isn't Mike cernovich also
Pile of garbage
Is
At this point
Bradley or least Morris
Like what else
She's kind of like
She knows his brand really well
And he's not going to go after somebody that people will like really stand up
You're not okay
Like with this James Gunn business
He's so much like people
Yeah that's
Sucked up
Like what
Posted with really sucked up stuff
I know it is a joke
You shouldn't be
How to task for that but
I'm not going to waste my energy on this one
He knows to do that he overslept level of like
Really dude
All the problems that we're going to go eat
Tops of the list
Other s*** overextended himself when he tried to
Represent those fraudulent
Documents
Yeah that's true
He did that
This is the level of pain we can pull off
So instead
Mike cernovich is just
Duke
He's just a little a******
Who puts out his periscope
And then he spends all his time or his minions
I do it for you
Going through celebrities that they don't like Twitter
I'm trying to find things to be like
Like him and Laura Loomer were complaining about Patton Oswalt putting up a bunch of tweets
Find that we're like the Nazis were right
The contacts did not like it was the second tweet Nusrat or some
Unfortunately cut off at exactly
Edward like
This guy was in red
Composition of the ad say
You'll know
Interest in what reality is you just want
Score points in
Exactly. And they're like
So do you question why don't we deal with it
Because I am not that
I'm.
The two I know I mean like I understand
Probably
In the same position of life
He's going to run out of
I think even the right
Missy's through a little bit
Idaho
Like you doesn't have much of an adult
4 people showed up
That's like most
Reporters aren't real people
Just as people who are
Yeah
Your point I don't
Mickey shows up much anymore on it Alex's show
Falling out after that breaks
So I have a good first album and then you get the stuff
He's never had a good first album is Mark so he starts off
Doing this video where he's making fun of how Anderson Cooper
Ncnm decided to start Facebook live stream
Apparently there's a cop putting out
On Facebook
Creator on Facebook
Can point out to the point where this
Makes no sense
Joined by Jim Acosta
Interactive
So two times and 30 seconds points out how do viewers they have
Just we know I watch Alex's livestreams all the time
If that you know like it's not
This is this is a really bizarre line
In terms of like humiliating
Something like that also with his voice shouldn't
A green suit
With dollars.
Free money from the government
He is doing a real f*****-up like if you see him on the street
That's the only thing I can guess play
Operating principles going on
Making fun of
Because they believe
Maybe the right
Behind
Kicked off of Facebook this wrist slap minor punitive measure
CNN
What is Brian stelter do pieces about like
Why is nobody
But who knows if we actually
Had anything to do with it
Imagine a better
But who knows
Mark Dice
Terrible not going hard
He's going to hard and doesn't realize that he has
Nothing like he's a guy who's like you know what
I'm really going through
Disable
74 miles
Crazy commercial break
After that for Alex
Commercial
$3
So I mean they play variation
That same commercial a couple times it's is Rodger Stone straight up
If you don't want to buy our
Bulshit
How about you give us money so we don't even have any overhead on
Taking that money
Great deal
Yeah probably
S*** like that
It's very different
It feels weird
Reno
And I don't I don't know if
Depict
Actual desperation or just
I'm sick of this
Sales are down on my supplements do need somebody coming in to look good like we can't
If we have no money coming in and our numbers are dropping whoever is bankrolling the operation is going to be like yeah
I pay you
To spout these narrative
Because of the people listening to you ain't even even more like
It's like a laundromat
Through a carwash that literally
No one ever goes to
You're like this is a little bit to suspicion has no listeners and somehow he still got a $3000000
Studio The Jig Is up a little bit
But investigators will be like
Reported a profit of -1000000 dollars
Very strange
So there's another commercial
There's another commercial that gets played
Strong
Glimpse
Where
Alex
Forest
Infowars with you wherever you go well now you can do just that
The best part
So they're pushing the app
Commercials for that all too regularly
I think they have but it's been like a real piece of
The s*** like a real
Betacap
Yeah I think they might have got it redesigned or something like that but I think that they're starting to realize that like
You know what
They're started like
YouTube and Facebook are starting to give us slaps on the wrist
We can't afford to change our Behavior
That's a gamble could just get kicked off the App Store
I've everyone else started to make moves like real
Stickley tour
Marron
Places
Which cab was an attempt
To do
That didn't work right
They're just so loud
People who
Go
This way
But the problem is
You create those spaces that are specially tailored for
This world
What you end up with is all of those loud
Were there not restrain from
Saying Nazi s***
You're not restrain from Edwards around North races
Like it's sort of a gentleman speak freely
And all the normal people are like
Damn
Either that or they don't agree with that and they're like
Look I still agree with Infowars
Dissociate
That being what it's
It's really about
And what they think it's real
Right and so anytime these like
Niche communities
Get started up as a end up drifting
Towards the fact
Drifting towards the big
Cuz that's
What is about
So
It's an unsustainable Market
You can't grow unless more people become bigoted or more people are like
What's a
In terms of the Infowars audience
25% monsters 75%
Stupid or trick
Or whatever or people watching
For entertainment value
Once you get them all in the same place in
Not on Twitter where they're
Fighting against
Quitter you can sort of
Have a lot of issues get put to the back burner when you're fighting
The system the system
And you're like oh all of my fellow compatriots really just want to drop 1488 references right
I don't know about this anymore
Mostly going to leave
You're going to end up with maybe that 25 + 5
Percent 10% to get shifted gets flipped over that you left with nothing
Are so cancerous
Let no one has any entry point to it
Because of all the people that they push it
The only way to play Both Sides
Greece
But they're not
They're not comfortable like throw in the end
I definitely want black people to be slaves but I don't want to say the n-word anymore that's a
You can't you can't make it to overt
Without
Alienating
Because that's
For these people
Then
Student Connect
The ideas that they're throwing around
Why is it that I agree 100%
With people who are happily throwing the end
Right
Seem like it reflects well on me
And then I
Without feeling bad about
Subway
But I also think the more important point is
Is this is the truth behind
Argument
The people like Alex
People like
Most of his gas
And co-host
About the idea that Twitter Facebook are monopolies
On social
Square
Square of modern times
Go talk to your friend
If you think
End all of public discourse
Then I'm afraid that that says more about you than it does about public discourse
Publix
Just be
It's not because other things heaven
Tried
It's that other things have fun
Fail
Yeah cuz of intrinsic problems with
Groups of Nazi
Groups of racist come together
And they alienate people on the fence
And that's why you
Can't have those sort of community
That's why Stormfront has like
Their community and the members who have been there but
I don't think there's a lot of new members
Except for people who would already be
Coming of age to be on the internet
The whole other thing is it a whole other thing though very related but unpacking how's that
Has led to a lot of this
Is something
Much smarter people can do and if we try to take us all day
Night to being like it's not that
So
Now we get back
To the showing
Finally get to Alex
You know how much ice
Because
Only had like four thousand viewers on there there
Gets into that a little bit here and a little bit of like I understand that I don't really
Explain it away
No sooner had they
Fishing nets
Anderson Cooper total failure
$4,000 on his new Facebook show the million dollar store
Force-fed and push notifications
Millions of people
They shadowban us
Videos of hundreds of thousands or millions of years
Force
Is he crying or laughing
What's he doing
His Heart's Not in Matlab
So it's a very different version of a class than the lot of them
Yeah
He's like I've got a really ham it up for a full sentence I'm holding back the laughter so it sounds like I'm crying
And you know that that's his
The small part of our audio
It's a bit
It is and it isn't
Coming back to In terms
Of this whole episode with his
Is watching streams
A small part of his body
In terms of like okay so there's like two thousand people screaming
That's not a negligible part of his audio
More than sure are probably as
Like engaged
Maybe
I've already bought product
Right maybe it's not the most important thing
Where is like his videos will have like 15 thousand views or something like that
He posts them
Which scandalous salacious bulshit clickbait titles
What they taken away
Relatively small piece of his operation
Compared to what they have life
We'll find out at the end of this hour
Click hell yeah
Done is basically like
You know
Just leave the larger
Syntac
You can sort of impunity
Small piece
Operation who really gives a s***
What's going on
He's allowed to make fun of himself a little bit
Only because the bigger picture is making fun
Anderson Cooper
If history
He probably be presenting it is
He is only able to do that because it
It's now gone
So
It's kind of fun but
Yeah
Weave
It's super in
Christine yet it's all just kind of like
I don't think it's true
But
I think it's actually more of an embedded
Atlantic
He kind of gives away that
He knows exactly
How to benefit off things like
What's happening
Is beyond a dog dropping its Beyond fake
This is after he's done like maybe 30 seconds on Like You cover a dog s*** and fudge try and feed rag
Notice for tortious interference
Lawsuits follow my followers I can win them out a percent
April of last year for Alex Jones
When he was up in court against said
I will win this
Or I will die
And as we all know he won
Topology
Political
They are on television about what I said
Publishers people fired
Because
Hilltop
Live Neil Strauss
Future
Secret history of the world in the war for the future
The Superhead
Of course publisher cell
Yeah
God dammit
It's still on his own
Damn right I mean it's not a scam but it is like
Paul Walker
It's not a trap
It's just
You know it's getting outrageous
Why whenever people are
Ban Alex Jones kind of mood
Guess you're probably consider what the actual outcome of that is because he probably has
The only thing he doesn't have a name strategy
Literally Banning
Kick him off YouTube
You do kick him off Facebook
Keith f***
His Radio engagement is not nearly what he claims are there
So if you kick him off
Legitimate
Ban all the Infowars
Correspondence from Facebook main page
Kick it all off
Takeaway streaming capability
Like have someone on it
Like be able to clearly tell
Oh this is a dummy account that's being put up in order to
You get around the band have someone there to cut off the temples as they come up
Phoebe Fox
The only thing you can do anything else
You can't do what I'm advocating
For now because
You already backed yourself into f****** corner
Stupid
Great tracks should stop being stupid about the
To the point where it seems like
They are in on it
It almost seems like
Email Facebook
Hey I got a game for both of us
Let's do the two-man game on this
It seems like maybe Alex
Gives Facebook $10,000 a month or so
In-N-Out
Promoting post
And stuff like that and he's like I don't
You know
That's going to go away or something like that
There's got to be some sort of a calculus to it but
Whatever it is nobody's active
Right now
Neither a wenis
Have the answer
I don't think we've ever
That anybody's
Right let alone us
The Bill Ayers
Killing it
Here Alex Jones to the store
From all this stuff it's that video about
You talk about how
He's talking about the viral video of the kid
Yeah
I guess KVUE
That was dumb
That was a different time
And they're holding up the article
People aren't doing that
His ex-wife is doing
It's not like strain
Because no one else has standing
The file that stores
To presenting this as some sort of a concert
People lying about
What you did with this video
It is if you were if you follow his ex-wife on Twitter
It's a continuation of exactly what she's been doing for quite a while
And Alex presented as like the media is a blank
That's really what Kelly has been tweeting about
On Thursday night Kelly went down to
To the courthouse
And was filing an emergency
The order
And I don't believe it was because of that video
I believe it was
She'd had enough
Yeah
Micah
Not our business
So
Earlier Alex
Who's pitching the app
Stanza in this next clip
You pictures something else
That I think is more indicative
That lykinos that
Do you need the backup
Source in the world
She's pushing the newsletter
Newsletter
Email newsletter
Which I actually signed up for it a dummy account
Because I figured they're going to start sending a bunch
Like selling my address
Account did not do anything else
It was all just Infowars
But it was bizarre I thought for sure like I'd be getting tons of spam tons
Unsolicited emails
Not doing that there's a lot of abusive practices you could be in
Again we are pitching ideas for should be no money off of it
Stream that you're not
Maybe they know that now
Yeah because they're about to start I don't know
Because I don't know if that's the case
I have not heard
Livestock
Maybe a month or so as long as
But it has pretty much as long as I think
Yeah
Never really here lots of
Commercials for the
The newsletter
44 the app
Or anything like that
Either
You've never
Play them for me in the past
That seems suspicious
If I never heard an ad for the newsletter
Which I don't think I ever have
That is after 8
Year-and-a-half of doing
Bananas
For literally every
Commercials for stuff like that back in
2009-2010
Cuz you have instances of like
At that point
Are you selling Infowars.
TV prisonplanet.tv
Subscription
You can get the video and stuff like that
If you join this cuz he didn't have a robust presence on like
There is that
Bitten
IHOP his muscle
But because you may
How much money are supplements and all that stuff and
Whatever you never did like it fell by the wayside we have a situation
Cease
Maybe possible
That they're going to f***
Record
Remind me to backup plan
Let's build this app
Make sure more people get on the newsletter so we can email them
And scare them
We need
Define new tentacles
Also has to have an adverb
Absolutely
Most of this episode has been
Serta dealing with
And what have you
I think I said
I think I've said my peace
I think you said your peace
I don't think there's going to be much more of it
But
The rest of this episode is clearly indicative of what people
Should be talkin about about Alex Jones
This is very important
Because this is not different than ever
F****** July 27th
2018 episode
Where he is
Responding to being banned
We will hear
Monsterous ship
Sabine Bandits
Even more van worthy who is first clip
Really necessarily
But it's absolutely
Conversation about Alex Jones
That most people are missing
Tucker Carlson
And
Steven Crowder
Because otherwise
White
Lose weight
Just like they say every hour on the hour
Trump hates Hispanic
And said they're all right person
Star
Donald Trump and Hitler
Yes
Swimming
This is all about
He's spread nmds
This is just
Spreading white Spears
Someone against took a pickaxe
To the Hollywood
Star outside Grauman's Chinese Theater
Not as good as ever
Let loose
Betsy DeVos
Yacht
That's my favorite thing
Such a good thing to do
I'm disappointed that it wasn't burnt to the ground
At the same time that carries over water
Fair enough
That carries a far larger so I respect
Alex talks a lot about this
I don't know if we're going to hear all that much more about it but he talks a ton
About this incident
The Hollywood
Star
Just like
Hispanics but here they are
That's all
Text to beat up lights
Okay fine
Whatever
Like what
Everybody situation that I didn't know about these pugs and I couldn't even beat up these two
Dudes
I just don't
It's so standard for him but at the same time
I don't get it
It's more fun in this kind
He's clearly
Felix
He's acting like he's up against the wall
Closer to him actually
Normally is act
He's up against the wall do you know what I mean
He's at the point where he does
Feel like
I could be up against the wall
But I'm
You still going to play it
But now there's a little bit more elevated
Slightly different in the near future
Close to a wall
Not since humbio Lucaya have I been up against there was a window we could crawl out of Woodruff
Alex if nothing else
You start to realize
Pretty good gambler
Like internships
Someone bluffing
Cuz almost all the time these people are bluffing what's
At this point
He's dealt with so many people
Or just weeks he can just like
Velocipastor
Like
No one ever calls this s***
You know it was never adequately explained to me about
How is
An apology illegitimate legal agreement probably also
I don't know all that stuff
Problems released about that says
To be able to
Use Somebody
I'm sorry
Millionaire
In a billionaire
Can you just want
Someone to be like
Brought low in public
Cuz all he was doing was lying about
Super negative to the guy's business or anything like that punishment
Kind of unnecessary
But it would be more fun
Honor dictates
Apologize
That's all you're really asked
Before I don't like gentlemen
Yeah I don't know
Friends bulshit
I don't know what to tell you
Shadowbanned
I don't know if we need
Need to get into that fully maybe we will a little bit later
Another guest
Shows up
We can talk about it at that point
But here Alex
How to get them fair enough
I want in Missouri a month ago I didn't
YouTube
Be spending all his time and energy
Americans are the enemy
Obscene
Just a trumpet set
Good
Good read
That's not dangerous at all
Just like
People don't run
Understand
Americans
Against the
The Free Press
President
The trust anyone
I'm saying is that if
Trump
You know my whole family and all of the Multicultural people I've ever met or like
You are evil for supporting Trump and Trump was like
They don't respect you
And you should murder all
Almost
Looks like there's a parallel
Who sings almost like there was a
Cruel cruel con man
Seem to like
Attract like
Was reading of one of those articles about Alex's band and they made a really good point
Send email to
Really not done too much
Three like Alex Jones
Is great
That's really
Not intellectually you're not in terms of like the argument
They're still clear overlapping parallel but like
He went on in
2015 inside your reputation
Is amazing and all that stuff
Scentsy elected I don't think I give the s***
Alex is one of the contractors that Trump has used in
Building
Moerlein
Episode
Copyright
Trademark
Super male vitality
Super female Vitality all his lap
He hasn't renewed those copyright yeah
But I found some new ones
And one of them was Firepower radio
I believe vagina tonight
Same cut through the b******* gives you a boner
Remember if it was Firepower radio or something something like that and then the other one was honor roll
And someone I apologize group posted that
That's obviously going to be the name of Rex
The show
It's going to be young info Warriors and I got terrified
Yeah that's a great name is Alex's copyrighting or trade market
Too close to Howard Dean
Not going to work
So
But
Suggestion was made of
Holy s*** that is a really good possibility
For what this is going to end up being
My first reaction
Trinidad is obviously Alex will not do that
Because that's a great idea
And once again
Infowars
I don't know
I don't know but in this episode
For honor roll
Which is the news
Then you've got honor roll dishes why it took us a couple years because I got a little something I said
Aw colors we have done it this baby right here just the nuclear option
You want to give your children the Boost
I do that
Real quick
Playlist like an advertisement in more like a f****** break down and real music
This is a prepackaged
Oil
You see those clear oils that look like water
Disgusting you see you later
They look like urine that's even grosser
Gorge
Orange
So
I just love that like
Option for your funeral
It's official
Recently been debunked
For the Millions
Terrible
It's a little overblown
In the same way is like a ginkgo biloba
Or something like that or any vouchers
Call Matt Marty was texting me earlier today cuz he was in an Uber
The driver was Infowars
I would so like all God this is awful
So rare to have like in the wild officially I can't
Do like
I will say one thing I don't think
I don't think ill of people who've
Drive to Alex's belief
Necessarily
I think there's probably a lot of well-meaning this life
People in that group
But I will save the ones that I've ever met
Not made for the service
I will
I feel
I feel like that stuff and then I also feel like
Probably tough issue
If you're someone who works
For Lyft
You're kind of in the gig economy
It's weird for you to Zendaya propping up a propagandist
Who is really super into keeping you in the gig economy struggling and driving people around for Penny
That's the trick
Conservative movement
Check the billionaires have pulled off
For so long as they're like
Your interest
Parable
You need
To have my entire
And my interest
Army making a lot more money
And you making not
Believe that you suck it allowed to have
Believe
That you will all I know
I was texting about this earlier that's kind of something I'm worried about with
My new favorite show
That I've got you on apparently Phil Rosenthal
I'm out
I love I watch
So if you guys are not watch this I recommend giving it a whirl
Delightful and Charming
There's a PBS show called I'll have what Phil's having
That got branched out into a Netflix series called somebody feed Phil
The guy who created Everybody Loves Raymond
Is a billionaire
Pusher he goes around the world and
He's trying to extol the virtues of
Traveling
And how food brings people together.
Beautiful things
For he goes in like has these
Top chefs around the world making meals
But they never in any way
Address
The fact that he's a billionaire
He even in the I'll have what Phil's having
The entire premise of the show the beginning of every episode
You can have what I'm having
You f****** evil if you can afford it you can't travel like that
You can meet people absolutely
So like a parallel for me like I went to Greece
With my family when I in 2007
And for a week of Italy
Concurrent
Who's kind of a bummer
My dad was like working on archaeological
Kodiak bear
Yeah it sounds
Paul's Church
Little Shack
3 weeks
Kind of sleepy bar
Street where they have
Shops like
Chemical stop at them
A couple decent restaurants
But luckily my girlfriend
Her family was going to
To somewhere in Italy
It was close enough that she came
Degrees for a week
That is a
Coincidence
Really awesome
Sometime
She and I
Got a hotel
Modern
Which is the sort of
You can't call it
Metropolis
More of a city nearby
And a crop
Might be in Agoura
So
Norton modern
We stayed there for a week
Away from
That was nice
To get out of there a little bit so we met a guy who works at a coffee shop
Are we friends
Go back to the coffee shop and talk to him
Little bit of a
Dating Miss
News 5
If you wanted to stay in
InTouch is my email address
I don't
I don't know if you're going to be able to call me from
Right
And then heater
Oh no email me I don't know what the deal was there was
Start of a disconnect but like
You can do that
What do you think about that
Go Buckwild you can have those experiences all day long
Level
Or you can f*** around and find
Some cool underworld bar or something like that needs some weirdos and do heroin
If you're traveling
Episode
Something
His eyes lit up in such a way that I got caught up in the moment
Oh my God this man
Truly is
Neurons are firing and I feel beauty and then when the episode
You're f****** millionaire
Of course you're happy
What do easy to be happy when you're jet-setting around the world on somebody else's dime
Well you're also still a millionaire
That's the problem with the show but I don't see the problem with Phil
Like I really think that even if he wasn't all that rich he's still be just as happy
Like his demeanor
I don't know there's no way to prove a counterfactual
But like
I think
What the thing that draws me to the show is that beautiful
Love of life
That he embodies
Is it really
There's an innocent
Great
But at the same time you can't take class out of it gets really great
Enough to live and eventually you pay your cards right all this stuff
Maybe you'll be one of those people who capitalizes all capitalism
In the same way this show presenter this scenario where it's like
You can do all this stuff and
You f****** cam
Yeah there's just a delusion embedded
I don't know why
I just don't want I don't want
All day today
We're recording much later than normal
Sour beer is acting weird but it's growing on me a little bit
It's kind of
I don't I still don't love it
But it's growing on me
Text a little while
It's like one of those sour candy
Yeah
What are those
It reminds me of a warhead
So you kind of kind of grown up
Grow on you
Is Alex's neck
This guy
We are joined
By Pastor Logan Robertson
Nope
Agreed
12 years and the Lord blessed him without children
What's in the news
Horsford
He's from New Zealand in Australia
Started harassing a bunch of Muslims
Go back to
And I'm not I'm not
Tatoosh and slightly better than ours because they do reserve the right to do
Report people for being a dick
Here to defend
Another country's decision about their deportation laws
I know every country has their to differ
I will
Alex ends up playing the video of
Logan Robertson
Talking to people outside a mosque
I certainly don't think he comports himself
I mean not in the video that he plays but
Very clearly cop to Call of Duty
The playground Spider-Man
Enough to get you deported American music
Well that happens all the time that I talk to Baron
Man drops that crepe
To wrestle with
We talked about in terms of the United
Quite a bit because of Tommy Robinson
Is it Australian Donuts
Cuz they're different country
Just to remind all the info Warriors out there
There are other
ESPN
Do Australians already have freedom
Do they have freedom of speech
And if so what does that really mean to our day-to-day lives
Despite all the debate in the past two years by priests
It's not a right
Protected under archons
Institution in fact the only social freedom is guaranteed is religion
Australia doesn't have a Bill of Rights
Which is where freedom speech usually gets to find a
Protected in most western
It's meter incorporated in
Any federal
Legislation
Free Speech has never been about staying what you want
Being protective
From the consequence
What you say
Australia does have laws regarding 3
But they're all concerned with limitation
Is the position of Australia in terms of their
Government
Free speech
Fairly sensible
Protections that have come into place through court cases
About political speech being protected
So there are there are some
They're not like
The same way that we have it embedded in
It's such a
Session we have refused to legislated at all
There's there's a
Way2go that is
You don't have to be Australia you don't have
But you also don't have to
You know like you
You shouldn't be
Feeling on Free Speech
Ultimately comes down
Swear jar levels
I like if you are a dick often enough I reserve the right to
Like
Abuser
Get the f*** out of here
But if you're just free speech
Porcupine the line
I don't know
Alex
50 Muslims
Proves that they are sissies the Muslims
Because instead of having an interview with us they had to wring the media police
Just because they don't want their religion exposed for what it is
So you going around with camera and trying to be like a Muhammad sex with a minor
Well yeah but so did
So I don't know man
F*** a minor
I think it's behavioral s*** but it
Have any interest in telling
Australia what to do
You guys play by your rules I don't fully understand your government or your
System
Your football
Sure Australian Rules
So what I do understand is this
Logan Peterson had the option to appeal his deportation
But chose not to
You know why
Because he knows it is
Is the best thing that
Could ever have
You don't want to do you know on a second train like
Stan from my rights I'm going to stay here wave the ability to appeal it
Because he wants to be deported to have the victim status
Alex gets from these slap on the wrist
Punishments
Social media
Bucking
Conservative
Weirdo bigot a****** propaganda
Beg
To be punished
Because that validates
The victim status
That they've been faking
The whole time
So that's
The same boat that this dick hole is in
So now Alex is interviewing this guy Logan Peter
What are things that's really fun
I think
The reason I kept this clip-in is
I mean I say something
Disgraceful things about Islam
A little bit but we also get to hear
You if your Eagle ear listener you'll know that Alex
Usually has an interview
And while the other person is talking he's eating lunch
You can kind of tell here at the beginning of the clip
Sandwich in konawa
New Zealand is not as bad but Australia
Muslims in United
Frelich
Al 600,000 Woodlands
Certainly don't let him in by boat
That's against the rules in Australia
In Australia now
I miss you. Sweeney 24 million people
And what is increasing Muslim refugees
And
Do you mean
It's pretty much.
I don't believe you
Play
Opera house has to wear a polka
Cover
Can't be allowed out there
Like weird metal tits
I've heard repeatedly
From folks
Turnbull prime minister conversation starter
Australia has a blanket ruler they don't accept people by boat
So, you show up no matter what your status is they take you
They're like you have to get out
You coming here by boat
While
Clearly a specific
Okay never have the conversation
Fly there
That suggests you can't afford to fly
Which means keeping out people who can't afford to fly
Which is a very specific
Degrees in to have a
No boats
Whitney is fine if you take a trained Australia f*** off
Legitimately
Marketing
I can't argue with it
If you live in Australia and one of our listeners and you don't like it
I'll second that that's your business
Chances are you hate Malcolm Turnbull
If you if you live in Australia you listen to us
You are not a fan of your government
It's possible I don't know
It's too hot
Question question here
I believe there's a lot of people that I
Waking up to this in
Hearing the truth about that
It is wicked false religion
Sad
At the moment they might be a little peaceful and now countries but
When I get in I'm bizarre
You can say like in England
They will stop relaxing and never stop.
It wasn't a problem
Sure
That's what the leftist do they mean
This dude
Pastor Robert
F***** up stuff there
Alex
His responses
You bet
We'll get to that
Keep calling Pastor Robinson
And then
But yeah
Does he go back to a different I think he might have
Like a small Church
Online
I'm not entirely sure
Because
Important
But first
I just think
You know they're putting out is that yes Muslims are fine now but once there's more of them
Look out witches
The same like this is a really cancerous piece of rhetoric
Ditto
Is encouraged
Like
The only thing that people being around
You can't trust people who are different
You got it they will always team up together guy
Which is
Which is one of the big reasons
That I
I am
Furious
Add
For being like well climate change is going to be a problem
70%
Every refugee
The more refugees we have the more destabilize
Is other countries are because of assholes like this
Of course you should accept refugees
Of course
Fought and clawed and f******
Everything they could
To get away from a situation
Literally died
And you're like
You can't let him in because they might change
No no
Your playlist
That's the point
People that you're actually afraid of because those people are trying to kill
Latent
Colonialist feeling within people like Alex and
These New Zealand
I was talking about the boat
Like a feeling of like that's what we would do
Do you know there is
Absolutely right
There's a sense of like if we could get away with doing you Advil all right
Be afraid of the fact that there's more of them they're going to kill us it's always a battle
Between people who look
Always
Society is always
Write a blog why are you giving up the presumed advantage
Imaginary Danger
Crazy crazy enough
Imagine if ever go
Edmond
People showed up
We got to get these people out here
Maybe we have a whole different world
It seems like it's old school
A reporter
Well obviously they do
Which is Kill Everybody
As opposed to what they've always
Except us an Open Arms which is why we're able to kill everybody
And that's probably where this mentality comes from
Expressing a great point
Guys
Is as bad as any of those videos that got taken down from Alex's Chan
Right there
This Gap
Being allowed to
What he says
More Muslims are going to show up and then they're going to start riding oh and then Alex comes in
The Democrats want them to do that
Yeah those videos
And keep posting this f****** videos
So anyway
You know
There's a chance
You've got all of it wrong about this guy
Is Pastor Roberts
He's been misrepresented
No
I know zero about the guy and I already disagree
Do from a 27
20 nautical New Zealand Herald
My view on homeowner Ridges at the Bible
This is going to be a rollercoaster for you this is going to be real rough
Going to get way worse
My view on homeowner Ridge is that the Bible never mentions it so I'm not against them getting married Robertson says
Quote as long as a bullet goes through their head the moment they kiss
I told you it's a roller-coaster neighbor
He's fine with them getting married quote as long as a bullet goes through their head the moment they care
Because that's what it talks about not marriage but homo.
You know what
I disagree with
It's more if you want to go full-on Deuteronomy
Not the moment they
Kiss
But the moment they lay down
Bed together
Like a f****** standing up the Bible doesn't say s*** about that really talk about foreplay
Can blow dude all you sure about that
Some of these stuff in like the Gnostic scripture
Dead Sea Scrolls are pretty clear about
Where you can put
You know it's
Odin
Stephen Curry
Muslims
Kind of fun
This thing that's cool whatever I'm going to get talked more about how how awful Logan Robertson is
So there's this writer named Marjorie
In the book about his struggle with his sexuality as a member of a fundamentalist Church
Written this book as a way to try and help people who are in a similar position
I'm also sort of resources and support group
Because before
He's been married for an hour
His wife passed away and after that point you realize what am I struggling a
Not going away wrote This Book
Help people who are
Which I assume
Punished by the
So he reached out to a bunch of churches means
Promoting his book
Unfortunately Robertson
Received a message
From a 2014 article in the New Zealand Herald
Old Robertson's response email
We are not interested in your filthy lifestyler book
The Bible says your vile strain
Queer reprobate
Phil sodomite natural brute beasts
Made to be taken into
Destroyed I pray that you commit suicide you filthy
The child molester
Things bag
That was published
His response
That was his response this guy is a f****** a******
There's a monster interesting distinct
Monster
Music horrible
Portable
Yeah
So
Baptist Churches of us isolated
In the event
New Zealand
Good thing it's over there
So this is all against represent
Just said the following about Logan Roberts
Quotes
F*** that guy the Baptist churches in Brazil Android no way connected with or affirm in any way the comments made by
Self-proclaimed Pastor Logan Robertson of Westside Baptist
Bible Baptist
The New Zealand Baptist Union of churches are appalled by the comments
The Patriot of evil made by Pastor Robertson
Unfortunately the Baptist name is not a franchise
The name to be taken by any group or person that wishes
Use this long
In case of Pastor Logan Robertson
He's not an ordained or register pastor of any denomination
Do you not have a congregation or church building or meeting space
He's established a Church website there by claiming to be a church
Therefore his desire to conquer
The pastor is
Entirely fragile
2014 is a chance that he established
Also I don't believe you
Except if it's like I'm more.
Like I'm ordained by the new life
It really
Luggage
If you go to Seminary just like read the Bible and then your
It's like passing
It's like going to a real life Hogwarts in them being like
You know the difference I would say is very real
Level up
That's fair
If you go through the work that you have to take years of classes and Seminary in order to
Mean it
Yeah where is a like
Now f*** it I'm a pastor now 8 suck
You don't mean it
You're just
You're looking for a space
Got nothing
Hello hate preacher and
Past Infowars gas to his
Steve Anderson who we went over in episode
Open 2016
He wrote The Following about it in his blog
We had a full house again for the Saturday preaching service and Pastor Logan Robertson
Preach the short sermon on quote
How to be filled with the spirit
He preached his drinking and didn't hold anything back when he called out YouTubers
Marshall
Are there bizarre teaching on alcohol
Not only that but hearing Pastor Roberts
We're in a New Zealand accent
What a load of assholes
I don't think that anybody is misrepresenting
Mister Roberts
Robertson
You the f****** mods
If I were country I would
I'll be fine good kid go out of
I would like to know
So now I'm Alex plays the clip of him harassing most
To display this
Let you respond
If you
You say that
I know I'm not going to feel good
Well I don't know if you'll feel terrible much going on here
I think
There's adults respond
To a child with a k
His kind of what's going on
Alright let's not go ahead and finish up with this club
Call D'Amico
He dead
Why are you saying varidirect
Sure
There's nothing about this mosque but anyway like
They're harboring terrorists
Then we suspect
They're not even saying
Muslim
That's all of this is
There's nothing going on here that like we're going to make it
Expose documentary about something
Other than
How many only thing that's revealed is I f****** hate Muslim
That's the only thing that Robertson is revealing anyway
Are they making a documentary about something
Like specific Muslims
Muhammad
Documentary
Where in Vegas
That has nobody affiliated with it that has knowledge
Nobody
Nobody nobody doing or saying anything other than just like Bean Ahmad
A mosque
And knocked on the door
And said we hate you
Yeah
They probably call him a terrorist
I mean like really
If we wanted really slice through the b*******
Tommy Robinson
In prison
Meet another guy with an axe
That's what's going on here and he's got to go to the bank
Who hates Muslim
Detroit
Some contemporaries in the UK and none of them had
Not committed enough to
This guy has
Committed a lot of time
To be an Infowars Gaston
I meant look
Jamaican Jah Cure
I don't believe you
You're agitating
We're trying to create like you're trying to do a jackass
Pissing off
And when you say things like
In this next clip
I really don't think
You're not even for Europeans now
Madewell
I don't understand what you're saying
Hundred million people
Is Ludacris
What did he say 600 million
600 million people
Because I
Thousand
Cuz that seemed almost like
No go back
Yeah
600 million
The UN just called for 1/10 of the world's population
Move to the United States
Triple the population of the United States
Do you empty just put out an estimate
The u.s. building
Housing
Use some of this on use land
DM
Do you want to put out an estimate of likes
68 million people were
Displaced in
So what I think Alex is doing is a
Assuming that means
They want us to take them all
Protect ears
I think that's what he's doing
But I don't know what you're giving him a lot of credit for me and I just
Cuz I looked for 600 million people to the United States all sorts of combinations are worth
Couldn't find anything other than
68 million people were displaced 2017
Try and figure out what
The war propaganda math of this
That's the only thing I
I know
Preaching that
That's absurd
Even
The most ardent
People who are like
Let's pick folks in
Let's bring in 600
We should not borders
But when you say so
600 million people should come to the United States
Might be too much
Mystikal
I don't think we have the carrying
Capacity for that within our economy within our just our infrastructure
We can carry a lot more than we are
Easy animal Nebraska
How many things you need to do in order to accommodate
Possible
What is almost impossible
Two senators from Nebraska
50 house represent
I want all six hundred million
And I want to make sure that they
Control every voting block east
It's a wild wild propaganda lines that I just
The Electoral College would get real weird
So Alex made a prediction on the Thursday show that General Kelly
Going to get fired
So we can look for that
Next clip makes another prediction
You know it
It is all being planned towards this fall
Big Chrysler Chantilly want to send for those of us to reach pausing it
The fall of Rage
Just drag
Do you know this prediction we've heard it a million times
He was predicting the summer of Rage in 2018 were already at the end of July
Me too exciting
Fall of Rain
We've also seen over the course of years
Summer is
Waiting on the ground this winter is going to be f***** up
Well it's going to actually just be the winter of our
Content it's not really going to
More like
Always something
It's always just around
Just want to take place of the country music
Just getting them was the beginning of the
The victory was it again
And it's very sad to watch him
California
Country they want to be part of
Is the mind control
Pretty smooth krill oil
Pornography
Fish oil
I don't know what he thinks he
He's selling
Play silence bulshit
I don't know when you put those two words together with
Brain function
You take krill oil you be able to
Sing like a whale
I don't know man but sounds right I just love that I buy that
The raises hold on we got to stay
Cuz he heard that music coming to break
Break some kids neck
That was harsh
Questlove
I can't get enough of that
Do an episode with Jess
Gravis
Betty of a a gravid Marriott
Just going to roll with
The problem is
How many words do we heard all of them
How many is hundreds of them in my tablet
To do that
You would not be
Orcas
Can you gameshare with Alex Jones
24-second sorry about so
I don't know
But it is what it is
Standard as Alex
Prime
If you're going and then
Really hard at
We haven't been
In the present day without
To the point where
Going back in
True will find a way around
We haven't
Seem like
Lincoln 2009
Jim Bakker in
Doing a lot of
Different things
But when you go in
Present-day Alex
The race
Very very it's not
It's not jog weekly it's literally just
We can't let Brown pee
People in
We're afraid that
People will be
And there's almost an implication through like the
Like the globalist and the Liberals brainwashed minority population
But there's also a kernel of it is like we were stupid
Begin was absolutely there is a feeling of we've already gone too far
Side effects
That's not even America
It's
UCare
Yeah it's
It's it's
It's hard
It's hard to listen
A lot of levels because
Sure he's not dropping at
You know he's not saying I hate black people
Anything like that but everything
Almost everything you say
Legitimately
Darkly
Deeply race
Yeah
Stupid
This is another piece of
Like some of the danger of kicking him off of
The flats
And it's another further danger of giving him a super
Professional
Lame
Is that what you end up doing is driving
Further towards
The worst part of what you already
Yeah because if he does end up getting kicked off Alexa YouTuber Facebook
Permanently
Nothing is no f******
Skin in the game
Let's
Does make all his money off selling his own problems
Whatever
To really worry about any of that
So why wouldn't he
Even
Further down the white National
Like why wouldn't he
Cuz he's all he's already
Very obviously that guy
Yeah and has been for a long time
Perhaps the only thing that's keeping him from being
Looking out right David Duke type Persona is the fear of losing his social media
You get to see the math drop-in be like
Look
Hamstrung by social media for a long time
I've been trying to make it clear but I haven't been able to look
This is a white country
That is what I care about
But I think
You hit the nail on the head
Earlier that those
Places
By definition
Sorry that you're not going
To get the same audio
Be kicked off of you to
Because
Even if he
He does still survive
His Revenue will go
Unless there is a dark money
And that sort of thing
And who knows if that kind of thing
Is not going to leave
But money is there money isn't
Interested in
Stormfront
On YouTube and Facebook
Here's what you're not taking into account
Is that world
Bees are always a factor that you forget
My girl
You're not taking into account is that world
The storm frightworld the Gap world
What's a wack
Chiefly
Is
A really charismatic
Frontman
And if Alex gets pushed into a corner
You could just go to drop all pretense
And be that
David Duke doesn't even really have
The Charisma than Alex Jones
But Alex Jones could present if
Do you have to act like he didn't have those things to worry about
But imagine a scenario where
But he loses his kid
Whatever pretext
Theater is Waco
But
Or just a rhetorical situation where he ends up losing
Custody of
At the same time music
Kicked off social media
It rained in the rhetoric
Rick to some extent
You could
You come go hog-wild into just
Becoming the next
Metzger your leader of the white nationalist movement
You could
Bald dude
Via VIA
Sincerely the past that it would go down but it's really dangerous possibility
Because
You know
Harris Road
Great movie
Propaganda
Nothing to lose
Right
Find music
Status
Build it eventually into a thing that
Hanabi
Eventually the movement goes outside of her
He has a chain
Tries to fight back
Is then
Cannibalized
His own movement
His Redemption
Ark
Doesn't exist
Salt sounds India's hell
I don't know man
Most likely outcome but it's definitely one I see as being like
Opossum certainly
Logistically possible given the
The players
Giving dependents
I don't know for sure who knows what tomorrow will bring
Who knows
So we got a couple more clips left
Good health Ranger
Like Adam
I cannot believe
He is and
He comes in
Cific reason that I
Asterisk
If people want
The realization
From this Alex that you are alluding to is that no one is coming to save us
Out there that's going to save us from this political situation
Pedicure
Like
Literally
Weird
There is no data there's no God coming
Hold on
Talk about God all the damn time on the show as a like God will save us but alright
Your own religious beliefs
The reason Mike Saint is that
Mike Adams put out
Treatise
On
No
City nail it to the wall of the
The Catholic Church
Might as well if you posted it on naturalnews.com
Same thing same thing basically Mike Martin Luther Adams
661 have dozen of the other same Better Business
And it's V
Mainstream media's
Their battle plan
Dakota
That's the sort of
The login
I need to tell you I don't
Not into it this is called
Censorship master plan
Decoded
The Adams report
The blueprint
America can fight back again
Corporate
Funopolis
By Mike Adams
Naturalnews.com
Real. Video
Counter think.com
Natural pedia.com
M300 plus more website natural
Cvs.com
Astrakhan that
More credits
So I made the mistake of reading
Approximately 15 pages of notes that I took
Over the course of going to go into now
By Sunday
Posted on the website
He's trying to do here
Pitch this idea
Pieces of it is essentially
There's a mainstream media. He calls the liberal Tech Giants
Checking site
PolitiFact
Snopes
They're all together to shut down conservit
This time
Seems like it would track except for the lack of evidence that the mainstream Media or text Giants are actually
Apps that are liberal
No I don't know any
I'm also the other problems
Fact-checking sites
Not really on the side of the Liberals
But if you go to PolitiFact
If you go to Snopes
Very
Many instances
Like break
King down liberal-leaning lies
Real
Say real things
They're they're very much
Debunk both sides
If you want to talk about real
Let's talk about
If you want if your policy is like
I think tax cuts will
Benefit the economy
And mine is I don't think
Text got there going to bed
That's a conversation week
If your policy is like
I think we should make sure that parents and children are never allowed near each other
You can have a conversation
Political PolitiFact
Is all about just like
Things that are real
Otherwise
Yeah
Cuz I don't want to spend like an hour talking about all of the Bulge
It's just
Constant
Undefended
Statement
That don't
Channel 2
Yeah
Of the tech Giants are liberal
Yeah there's that ain't right no proof of it there's no evidence given
Don't need it
Conspiratorial
Like an eighth grade paper
Right really really poorly written
I was
Fact-checking
At the top of my notes it's really sincere like
I start to refer to him in the second person
What are you
So there's one thing though there's a train that goes through this that I think is really
Paragraph
I think is
There was a Time in America when one specific group of people was told to sit at the back of the bus
Certain cafes were reserved for whites only
Have you
Punished based on the color of their skin
Now judge people based on the color of their thoughts
And conservative Trump supporters and Advocates of Natural Health content or over
We don't serve your kind here
90s throwback
That's a little like
And they don't like that okay alright
Roundly rejected
So the part that I really want to draw syrup Focus 2 is
Cuz I was like
The color of their thought
I think that you're proud of that is a turn of phrase
Glycol
You get one
Also
Complains so much around
The times when
White male Christian opinions not being welcome
Color of their socks
Metaphor what
Like you said
I think it's Conkey for someone like you to use I'm suspicious
When you keep using it
Clear that you're worried that white men aren't being listened to right
Thought if you if you put it like like that is a 75% of the way through that's your
Turn of phrase
Boom that's going to take me home
Occlusion
I f****** nailed that what I mean
Is
Redzed
What I mean is like the color results
Red
And then
If you use it multiple times what it means
What it means is
He first used it
You get one use of that that's your f******
Closer
Does metamagic
The other things that I just think would be fun
Point out
AR
Just have constant
Complaints about like
You're not allowed
To express
Why
Christian Caucasian culture
I think that this argument
It gets brought up a lot
And I'd like to
Respond to that
You are
You're just not allowed
To do the race
Stop the part of it
If you want to have a barbecue on the 4th
Enjoy
That's good
Text super-fun or if you are come for broiling
Do you want to celebrate
Nobody going to complain
The problem is
Problem come
When the part of your
Your culture you're mad
Celebrate
Is the South will rise again
You know you're trying to rewrite what happened during
The Civil War all right
Is Dwight
You want to celebrate
The heritage
Understand
Thoreau problem
Gavin McGinnis one
To celebrate
Patriarchy
Which you would just described as like
Hey this is my male identity
The problem with that is
For decades
The patriarchy what it represent
Women being
Sing
Anyone thinking
It's not
If it's not larger than yours
Is it okay to mail fraternity of chauvinist and they scream
Call the patriarchies back
That sort of thing
It's really clear that people will
Hear that and be like
Really excited about is the idea of being able to hit
Me privately
As opposed to if you're just someone who's like I like being the guy
No one's mad about that no no there's a lot of people who are actually superscore that
LastPass
Just illustrates
Is Rampage 20
Monopolist
Claim that their gods
You possess the Divine reality
The claims maxo Journal cultizm
I think he's coining phrase there
Is no different from the delusions of the high priest of the Ancient Maya and Aztec cultures who also for
Proclaim that only a select class of divinely ordained individuals could speak to God and interpret reality for the masses
The holy of holies you were looked into Christian history
Sojourn occult
Thrown into an ism
G-Eazy
The Aztec and Mayan cultures or
That's the beginning of Christianity
Because you're a Biro communistic capitalist
That's what you are
You're a cam you alcohol acerbis
That does the blizzard and then I believe in public property of alcohol
Clear Lake
Sure
Hot nonsense when they are pointing the finger at the Aztecs when was the exact same thing the Christians did
It's so crazy
There's that whole section
That people weren't allowed to go anywhere
I would go in your messages
What one of the reason
The Jesus was
So Revolution
Marietta
Personal relationship
Through it broke down the Walls
Between the holy of holy in the masses
There was an ability to have
You could play a role in religion
Opposed to it being told to you by
Fractal
To this is some sort of different thing with the ice
I don't think you want to talk about like Christian culture and like
You really love
White male Christian identity
You don't even know what Christ
Stood for
I'm not saying you weren't a Christian or anything like that
Deposit
Bet you don't have an in-depth understanding
Or maybe
There's no truth
Greater than that
Evangelical Christianity as it is right now
Love every part of the Bible except for the parts where G
This is allowed
What is it like
Yeah just like you know all the stuff
You guys think it's cool
Stop it
They don't like the part where he's a new way
They want the Old Testament but with like
You know they want
Meat of the Old Testament right
They want the cash area of be like
Exactly
Being manifest
La Glory's all of us right
Arson
Being washed away
They want that stuff
But they want the f***
Really hardcore
Rules and they want that
It's like when Bush K today
And it was like
Oh this is
Compassionate conservative
Just like it does
Parts of the Bible where God murder people
Like you know
That's the stuff that we really want but also Jesus
Is there
Andy might have killed
That's true
Kerry Cassidy told me about that
So we have one more quick left
And this is
Familiar
I'm actually starting
Disappointed with my
Understand this
Game much earlier
Kind of didn't
Intuitively but I never was
Two words but it's back in
And we see it hear it
In all the time
And again
A little
I should have been able
Crystallized
Will share with you my worst-case sub
Clear false flag
Exactly
Trump
They blame it on
Patriots are they blamed on Trump's negotiations with North Korea they could say it's North Korea
Fighting back
But they take out Trump
And they take out 200,000 Americans at the same time
The Blacklist all conservatives all speech online and any dissenting views
This is the plant they have to silence you Alex
Before taking the rest got us down
Well before the election
Biological or nuclear event
See that's the thing
All they have to do
Is an enema
Show me my roster for Oklahoma to office
No nobody ever nobody ever know nobody nobody ever threatened
Humid
Nobody ever did propaganda
Complain about it
Nevermind
Never happen
Look the thing that I was referring to before the clip
This is official
This is just pre-emptive narrative
When Alex and
2009 is saying that
Attack of terrorism
Not Feliz spelling all that out yet much more amateurish about it now
Do you spelling it out a little bit too much
More specific predictions
I think it's going to be a biological or nuclear attack before the midterm
Much more clunky about this now but other reflect on it I realize that he was doing this
Is all the time that we've been covering
You talking about how they're going to attack the inauguration
They're going to fly a helicopter
He does this all the
Time with
These pre-emptive narrative
The track
He's laying
I'm going to head to my bed
So I will be able
Brilliant
Because what you do
Is you create this
Real
Serious thing for your audience to be afraid of
It's not going to happen
But
On the off-chance goes crazy
Senor Nostradamus well we talked about it
To the globalist got scared and they didn't pull the
So
The end of this what I want to come too
Is
I didn't expect
Let me just a little longer than I predicted and I'm sorry about
I didn't predict
20 minutes of top talking about
The fake bangs
Yeah
But
Everyone's really focused on these fake bands
And I understand
Everyone wants
To do a little dance
And be like
They want to do that
Because it's fun and it's gratifying
For people who aren't doing anything
I understand
I don't expect that our coverage out of the media
I resent a little bit is that the way they are covering it
Is an advantage
He plays into his house
And
In present day
Everyone's talking about that
People aren't talking about the fact
Said he had a New Zealand preacher
Who prayed that a homosexual would commit suicide
Being deported
Very legitimate reasons for harassing muzzle
And at the same time
Very clearly Express position
You should be scared of everyone who's not
All of this white
Fear
His very consist
People are talking about that
Nearly f***
I meant at the same time
This is just like
Nobody does
Yep
Yeah you don't then stop
Stop helping them
Yeah I don't know
Hard for me to put a button on this but like
I'm a little mad
If you're if you're going to pretend to
Well then f****** suck it up and
If you're not going to
Bother
Exactly what he
Hope you do
Because all you're doing
He's giving him 2 weeks of full-on
Guess what these m************ are trying to take us down you need to give us more money and then whenever you let him back on
He's going to do the same f****** s***
And then whenever
We are forever
More than ever because they're going to try
Leg is all part of the same
I would like
Playing poker against
Bluffing Epona
Yeah to raise them a little bit
You're doing a s*** raise
And then they're just going to push back with a
Yeah they're going to go all in on you
Then you're in the position of folding or calling their aggression
Either
Play
And push
Otherwise you're going to lose lose that f****** hand
Alex Jones
Is metaphorically a bully at a poker table
You're you're playing shity poker against
That's
That's all I can
Antioch
Shuffle Up and Deal
Try to do better now
Yeah now it's too late maybe you can
Well I mean if they actually right now
Because if you
Now or like a Alex
You said all the same s*** on your show
That you did upload to Youtube all we're going to strike you and now we're going to ban you
He's already late yep
Calling that all in bed
You know if you're showing you already shown weakness
Now all you're doing is
Can't do it there's there's no good answer for these
These
Fake
Supposedly liberal Tech Giant
They basically just helping
Altamont
Proliferate
Agreed
So congratulations everyone
We all
If you want to find us
How do you find a
Go to knowledge
Who's on Facebook
You can find a therapist
There's one called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
How to go to iTunes
If you wanted to leave a review Irishman
Liberty on Facebook
It is mighty
Potato Oliver
Go f*** yourself Robertson and I
I hope you get deported