Alex
I made it all the way
Just a couple of
Couples
Cheese omelette
Also think about the Narrows
Trying really hard
Destroyer Cambridge
Is it corrupt
So Jordan This is a show where we now know about each other's days and I know a bit about outside
That is correct play our little game
A little game
You know
Now I feel adrift
Read it I read
Unplugged and plugged back in everything on our soundboard separation for something we're about to unveil here in a little bit
Severe problem
In terms of our headphones thrown off a little bit by like my headphones dropping out
Going to be adventurous
Find
I have prayed
Thank you so very much
I'm staring at you
You and I both know what I know and you know is what I want to say but I know I know your B
Nope it's against the law.
Is Knott's Berry character I promise you that much
But thank you so much.
Knowledge fight.com
It would be appreciated
You could tell people talk to your parties at your policy want
People love hearing
About 15
Cocktail parties
I was just at home Association
They had so much fun
Conversation
Like how much does your condo cost
Great conversation
Price is Right
Condo
Yodeling
Play parties
Broadcast talk
What we're doing
What we in the past baby
Anna Thompson fun stuff
You know what when we go back into the past where
It's one of the good app
Weirdos
These no Darrell hamamoto no one will ever be
Now you are in some sort of infatuated love
I will never
Is gettable in Davis
Facebook
Post you made on Facebook clearly indicate
Like the moment they figured it out there like
We got them this time
I found a 10-year loophole
Before we end
Talking
Weirdo
Alright
Necessary
Apparently somebody comes after him and he's going to mercilessly get brutally
Has your best bet as far as it goes
Not
Whoa whoa whoa
Always carried a hammer with you
Murder somebody with it
Your nails
Road flare
Text Caleb
Do I dare someone with a road flare
I was hoping Alex would be like
Like you back
Think about things you should have in your car
Blankets
What if it's called your car breaks down
First sure
Spare tire
Water water
Couldn't hurt
Do something with it
You know what even better than that for drinking
Absolutely
We're going to start today on February 5th
Tried to trademark a name about Road
I'm certain it's a
Nice old song
At some point
Anyway we start here on this
17th and Alex
Geopolitics
And I brought
I don't really want to talk
Deeply about this.
It is yet another example of fundamental
Alex
Launching Terror attacks against
Sabotage of factories
Itinerary
Along with it all
These probes discard them up against them to have more intense
Iraq
Pocoyo
Alex knows people have a vested interest in trying to rile up a run
Which is interesting
Because that's not quite
Does think that they're bad
We've already talked about how the Iran nuclear program was peaceful
Then that
And then cut his boys start a war with Iran
Want to start a war with Iran parallels
Become even Starker in the next
Eclipse
Really weird how close this is to the present day
Hi
So far away
Chronologically
So here I always talked a little bit more about the situation
Is one of the reasons
Like this
I want the reason
But unfortunately I'm not able to
The time travel episode 4
America
I just think that there is a data path we're on here
Not quite a prince but he is the prime minister starts working at McDonald's
Turns it into a fascistic apartheid state
You can reuse a lot of gag
The first one
Indicative
There needs to be a journey
Just jumping to the destiny
False flag attack bottom-line
Brick
We got a false flag
Is admitting
Hitman sabotage groups front companies
It's very clear in 2009
Critical
Of the Israeli government
He's already been
Clear in the past that
But he is pro-palestinian
He believes in what they're they're up to
Right to assert
Pointing out that they're f****** with a run
Very different than currently
Very different than even I would say a few years after
What's interesting is that
Pretty much sure they've been pretty much playing by the same playbook for a long time
Trying to search it with Iran Israel isn't
The problem with the globalist is there against
Love it
I don't want the end
Play the end of this choose-your-own-adventure book I want to I want to follow the path
That the book is taking
Through where how does Alex get from
Cuz if we were to go and listen
We can make assumptions of what
I think I have a pretty good idea and you're so cynical
Repeated listening with assholes
But like there could be something along the way
Is a is a pivot point
I would be remiss
To not have it
Conversation
So
Exactly exactly
So I told you this is going
To become
Much more
Relevant
Present-day as it relates to it wrong
Quick
Here is why
The most dramatic element of the
Decapitation
Iran's top operations
Assassination of leaders
Oh where in your country were going to kill your leaders
Beyonce
We're only going up there dams are shooting your police chief
Isn't that weird
Isn't that weird does have an understanding of how things would go if what he thought
Thought was real
He's
He's putting out a prediction of exactly what's going on right now
Which is
In staying at this point in time
Because it doesn't make any sense
But if you're an insane person creating conspiracy theories
You know exactly how
People would react
Text to an actual
Firozi
So he's nailing it on the head
In this fake world and then unable to see it whenever it's part of the real
Perhaps
But he's very very aware of it
Too far up
That's probably more likely
Probably some dirty rocks up trumps
Dirty a******
But
Clearly understand
Comes out as like
Blustery
Rhetoric
Threats that are being made to him
And in the present with no trumps
Famous all-caps we're going to f****** Burke you dude
That only happened because
Mike Pompeo
Set that around as being run as they responded
Peace with Arandas the greatest peace is the greatest War which is
I would say a measure threat
You know even really a threat
It's more like come on
Let's do this because neither of us want the worst warts
For everybody
Wish we go whatever direction we're going
It's going to be extreme
You know like
Jeep or
Towards the end of that Spectrum
Because of
Extreme days
Play movie episode
Do that
I think they would be much more
Successful of fidgets
Comes out
Man is really one of those
Never going to be like
And then we go away
No not these days
I don't give a s***
That would be the response to that
The exact same
Scenario that played out
Impreza
Being gone not in a vacuum
From nowhere
Hitting the vale back of violence
Crazy things make sense
To accept that this
Is the correct crazy
But when you are crazy
Normal back then
You understand how crazy
Everything's crazy
If possible the Hannibal Lecter of conspiracy theories
Next clip
We get a little break from
Iran Israel issues
We get into a
Caller
Who's crazy
Which is just fun
But I was just wondering
If you noticed
During the inauguration
We know that
That they they always announce
What they're going to do
And sometimes you do that
Symbolism in doublespeak
Anna when Robert Verde inauguration
They messed up on purpose he was he didn't
He didn't
Stutter or
He was very purposeful
And he was so determined that he actually repeated
The oath
The wrong way
And I went ahead and looked up
Some of the words in the dictionary to see what
Maybe they were trying to stay and another definition for execute which is when the words it was missed
I'm placed in the sentence which changes the meaning of it
Execute
Office of President ultimate the end
President and it may be that they were announcing it
Obama will be the last president
And you'll bring in the New World Order North American Union and that end the office of the presidency
Fireworks
The Bible
The next
Well done
Good job look at that guy
Because he had some amazing
I have
Did you know
Exit
Acute has
More than one meaning
John John
Of course you do
You've never even looked at a dictionary
You think that the word X
Execute in this speech
Only means one thing in the dictionary
It can be more than one thing
Give me more than one thing
And you think it means one thing
They might think
You think it means one thing
You mean the other day
Doublespeak
Pour up
Definition
Call Alex's listeners
Alex
Goodbye
Global it that's true
Do not tell them about your you're
Losers
Maybe that's why they can never spell it right
Because there's only one definition for that never looked it up in the
Dictionary
I don't know about
Possessive
It's
Execute your office
Sevdah president
You don't realize
You are the
He's executing you to find out who are
Because he is going to kill our
Nope
F****** tell info Warriors about likely
The declension of nouns
About level of language is it going to all
Second study circles around us a grammar sentence
Training for warriors
Is is gone
No no no
That is an adverb
We are looking for the object of the sentence
Not the director
I gave you the object directly where you at when you say it
Hold up
Did you know
That the word Direct
Can mean straight
And it can also mean to control
So you guys are trying to direct my sentences and I don't need this b******* doublespeak
That's that's all good
I found this
Text clip
What I described as a
Overalls
Not all that far out
Version of a discussion
Situation
GM
In trouble
And so
Alex is talking
Sing about that
That's not important
Because why would I imagine that
What I was listening to episode
A couple times
I think this might be an embedded Chrysler Commercial
But I'm not positive
Tell me what you think
Is really weird put the bike down for this cuz
Chrysler Union
I got to say Chrysler's really but not some great cars last 2 years
Too bad you're probably going under
Globalist
Felicia gray cars
Charger Lubbock
Warriors
The first time
Great Cars about
Does Mike Fiers and not feel like that's not that weird
Cut off in the
The middle of a sudden
I drive a
Charger
Great Value there any
You're going to want to Value Bass
Shop at this point is we're in a recession
I have to ask you
Do you think there's any chance
Commercial
Ivan
He is just
They might go out of business
Outside of Chrysler's best interest
For advertising
Orbitz
Globalist company
To be afraid of
Exactly
Alright
Bad a little bit upfront but the reality is
Now all these wings are going to go buy Chryslers
Boom
They're safe
So you're saying that Alex is very weird
Of the February 17th 2009
I think it's more like he just really loves cars
And he was really bored while by what he was about to talk about just talking about Taco
Overnight 17th
18th overnight is this
Is it really weird
I believe on the Eve
The 17th
He does coasttocoastam
He's working all day trying to
Finish the Obama
Deception does the show that's on it midnight
Yeah he's f***** up
Later
He's just like
I would not be surprised if he's running on no fee
Yeah he doesn't even have super male vitality
Who's them up made by Joel Wallach
Veterinarian put on some of them.
Hoping for the best
A little bit
I think Diamond gusset might've stopped
Just survival
Yeah those were those were the days
Haven't heard
Sing from Marty Shack
All of those restrictions
He's writing them on his own
He's writing limericks that it turned out are exactly straight leg by accident 20 years ago
Like I forgot
He's reading them street over like Milton berle's dirt
In this episode
Me
Sofa
Mark
Excitement
Episode
Caller calls in
And wants to talk about how they're a bunch of occult people
Running the world
World leaders are deeply into the occult and they are Satanist
Does he
Think he is coming up with an original idea for this show
But not like real ones
Doctor confrontational with my buddy about this and I need to be reminded
Comes in
All this stuff is
Sofa
All of it is so wrong
This is like this is where it's at
Going to be like
30 minute
Cancel this podcast
Is all
You're busted
So here's the first one to wear weave
You got a great memory for things like this you
Mention some of these
Bizarre
The Antics that some of the world leaders like Blair and others that
Have not engaged in
Can you cite a couple of those that I put you on the spot
Tony Blair
Coronavirus
Tony Blair does ritual
My computer is working working working working
Alright
My internet connection is bad
Bad
Tony Blair's wife got brought out there
Remembering this s***
Apologize
Double x
About like a Palestinian suicide bomber
I believe
I forget
Djibouti had to apologize
Because you made a statement that was
Publix
I think Intel
We live in a world where Young
People don't think that blowing
Themselves
Is a good solution
I don't know what we're talkin
Something along those lines
Apologize
I don't know she's always right
She's made statements like that they're like that alright
I don't know too much about Terry Blair
I've read all of her autobiography biography
Sure
She does have a little bit of a spiritualist streak
Okay alright
Like
Totally
Making things up here
MX Player
Cherie Blair has a couple of friends
The mother and daughter pair name
Sylvia and Carole King
Carol Kaplan was a woman who was a style guide or style advisor
Okay War tortoni
Play the long-standing
Turns out
Sylvia Kaplan
World
Okay
Feel like if your style guide you have to also believe that you can
Can speak to the other one
Okay okay alright
The two of them worrying contact
There's with the other side
There's some credible
Citations and evidence
They might have talked about ghosts
But I don't really care
I mean everybody talked about
At all it's just sort of like on the level of
Who cares and also she has like a crystal necklace
Texas magical
That's not
You used enough sooner or later you're going to find crystals
The artistic world is like we're really desperate the world stock right now
I have a little
I still actually juice
There's something to it
If it's not about the rock being Makela Dalton
Projector
Something
Creepy Connie 14 it but it also is like
So interesting Lee
Carol cat
Younger one
Her boyfriend
Peter Foster
Who's main claim
6 countries
Ranging from medical fraud
Alcy had horse horse racing
Ocean's 11
Deported from Ireland
For trying to sell a franchise rights for 200,000 slimming pills
House in like 2002
I like any crime that actually from the country like Ireland
You're not from here it's just like God you're such a dick we need you gone from the entire country
Go you've been arrested in countries
Nion
20 years now for frauds
You're doing it here now
You got to lie
Weather we've had enough
If you get from one country immediately
Suspect in all other countries
Foster worked his way in
Carol kaplan's life
Because you was already
Blair's
Some sort of a con
Any got no raging
Good deal for the players on a pair of flats
Bristol
This was a scam
Because they got a
Weirdly
Cheap couple of flats
And it was all worked out through this
Property in London
Ungodly amount
20 years
The history of fraud
Problem
Sprite soy
For the public
Aspect of it
Geta publicity
He was much
Closer friends
To the Blairs
Investigation
Because he was dating their style advisor
Things like go to their house
For Christmas
Use that as a way to be like
They had me over for Christmas
As opposed to I went with my girlfriend who was their style advisor
Know why he's been so successful
Strongly unsuccessful
BrightStar Samantha of course why wouldn't you
S*** crazy that was his first car
Comment from her that was like
I would never fall for him ever again
But I was in my early twenties
Sky
This is life
So the issue here is not with any kind of
Cherie Blair in front of us
Is a bunch of really golub
Carol Kaplan fell under Peter Foster
Becoming pregnant
And the players except it is very clearly
Real estate
The reason
You're falling for this guy
What was in the character
The real conversation about this situation
Further
These people suck
That would be a valid
Because
Need to really be outraged by
It only makes
Mother really is communicating with
Stop if your biggest issue
His biggest issue was
How come I don't get to communicate with the spirit
If he doesn't believe
And talk to the spirit
I don't doesn't matter if he believes it
No that doesn't matter
There are world leaders
I was a fan of the labor bear
A few times
Aspects of the spiritualism
Turn on vacation in Mexico
Meet each other with melons in
Papaya
Primal screaming
Rebirth ceremony
But
Why are world leaders that dump
Ultra Primal scream therapy
Also they consulted
The feng shui expert about ten Downing Street and about Civic plant
It's all really super benign stuff
It might be a waste
The time that argument but otherwise super benign
I'm the only ultimate
Policy results
Has had
Quote
The government announced that for the first time since the creation of the NHL
Conventional treatment
Despite the absence
Evidence that they might cure the sick
This quote is thought to have been influenced
Play sherry Blair's interest in alternative Therapies
Alex theoretically is able to sell his pills much
Easier in the UK because of
World leaders so dumb
This always very fast
I'm most of it most of the information
That is out there
You're not true or gossip
Or
Embellish
So now Alex
102 break while his computer boot boot
Booted up
He comes back from break
About Tony Blair
You tell that one guy to Google
Great
Well we have our Board of differin
We are having a board of similarities
One of the other ones is not understand
Just because you typing Tony Blair a cult and like
100000 results
That does not mean there's 100,000.
Google found
Stability
But if you get to pay
Completely different
You have maybe
Six articles
About this
Blog
Every morning is possessed by the spirit
So he has epilepsy
So
Did Tony Blair have epilepsy is that what you just revealed
Maybe they
But I think more likely
We're dealing with bulshit
The only reference I can find
This story about the light
Yeah I'm very interested in this.
This is on a 2007 block
Claims of the time
Times of London was
Reporting to Tony Blair sought the advice of
Of the spirit
The block boys from Bohemia claims
In an article from
Wayfair
Clashes with Gordon Brown
He sought the advice from Kappa
Style
Hidden Force called
The light
Foster said
Tony and Carol would say I'll ask mum
To channel on this
You hear that at the
Fosters
Said
This is all information coming from
Peter Falk
Where you at
All of this information comes from him
Mirror the Blair's after
I mean this is sad unfortunately
Carol Kaplan
The pregnancy ended in a miscarriage
Sonic
Fair
Trying to save
Are you having an affair with
Smear campaign
Another one
Yeah
So
The London Times article that Alex
Blogger site
Builddirect
And there's a reason
Because the title
Quote
Weather
Foster Kiki Eminem
The article begins
The Australian
At the center of the
The fair has made a series of claims about the Prime Minister as he tries to
Promote a book
Covering his relations
The Blairs
Foster who is called himself the human headline
Has produced no evidence
All of this comes from another con man
Peter Foster
Trying to make a bigger name for himself the bigger story
Alex knows that
Have you ever looked into any of the sources
He's gone down to the Google
Locust
If you read the boys from Boca
Give me a Blog
Or something like that it comes from times of London
He doesn't know who Peter Faust
Cuz he doesn't know that
Look into it
You can just assume like all my God it says times of London
He acts like his listen
Extra
I think that's possible
If you never learn anything you're always right
Answer the charge
Tony Blair
Being a Super 8 today
I'm going to give that
Stop your bust
You know
You're embellishing off something that's benign and actually real but
The other stuff
Relying
Elsa having a style advisor is a
There's no way just where is this is a good
I need one
I definitely
Call me
What do you think about the world limone
What's the spirit
List
Hey we
What do you think about the French leaders
Are there any French style advice
Is there a new style drivers in the story
Inference
Night are they outlawed
Okay
What we learned about
How did
Hideousness
Spiritual satanism
Le Monde francophone
Which of already set
Remembrance
Specifically
You reported as ethically on howling at the moon
What are the Frenchman
Hey was actually
The architect
America
Ritual
I imagine that was just an open
Opening ceremony or something like that
Alright
Pietro Mountaintop
M on
I would like to take us back to that episode where he was talking
Have you ever taken off your shirt run around on a Mountaintop it a full moon
He's a guy who everybody knows
Did France beat Iran
What what who is this
What what to do
What to do
President
I need a little more information
Before we go
Howling at the moon
Ozzy Osbourne Bark at the Moon
True
Pyramid 666
The presidency before.
Jacques Chirac
Okay
So
Are there 600
That's what most of Alex's
Is claims come back
Singer that's an omage to the Great
Right besides mr. Francois made around
Just because meet around with present
And he
The pyramid was part of his projects
Initiative
Create a bunch of modern
Someone to upgrade the city
Being more of like a lot of people didn't like it
Fair enough
Pyramid does not match
Feel-Rite
This giant
American architects
Official schematics
As well as seven
David shugart guy who wrote books
Country code is real number
Counting six
Pieces of glass
Wait so the real number is 673 and he came away with 689
Official
This even a picture of the pyramid
You can just count them
So you
Unless there's like him
There's like some
It would have to be somewhere combined cuz all the numbers are over
They'll never find these last
You can see through
Number is based on a mistake was made in the tourism brochures
Constructive claimed that the number of glass panes
Unfortunately the brochure also claimed that the number of eye pain
672 at another point so it's really all over the place who really know
The reason that Alex knows about this was drunk one morning
It's not because of Miss
Printed brochures
Or because Francois meet around is a well-known Satan
Not
Because of the
G-Code
On page 21
Fiction novel
Robert Langdon the Tom Hanks role says to himself quote this pyramid
Francois
Listen to man
Constructed with exact
Play
Sick Pains of glass
A bizarre request that it always been a really hot topic
Among conspiracy bops
To claim 666
The number of Satan
This comes from The DaVinci Code
So why not
Probably
Cages cages
Top 10 rule
Aaron apology
That time it was explained that movie where the kids end up on another planet
I apologize about that
I really don't take this
Correction from that one
Francois M on because he was the first socialist president of France
Quite strongly to the left
The made the left of legitimate workable political
He pushed for the abolition of
The death penalty
39 Hour Work Week
He welcomed
Who is cabinet with
Super taboo at the time
Ushered in a very serious rise in popularity
French Socialist Party
Almost directly
Expensive Communist Party
Tommy's party numbers one way down socialist
The group French president after him
Jacques Chirac was found guilty in 2011 of diverting public funds
In public
2018 just very recently Nicolas Sarkozy was charged with bribery and accepting it
Stemming from allegations that moammar Kadafi
Euros for his campaign
In exchange for access
Savers
Gaddafi's son Saif al-islam Gaddafi
We funded it we have all the details and are ready to reveal everything the first thing we want is this
The first thing we want this clown to do is give the money back to the Libyan people
He was given a system
So he could help them
But he's disappointed us
Give us our money back
After that Fran selected another socialist
Francois
Or is he really that much
You got for president or socialist
Not in prison
Two aren't
Amanda
Or whatever
You get a 50 million euro loan gift
From the Gaddafi
And you don't
Stop and think I wonder if they have receipts on this I wonder if they're going to Blackmail
Take me to Marley even taking into account the other f*****-up
Sarkozy
Not entered history yet
It's coming when when they get there we'll put them in the box
He said a lot of really horrible stuff difficult
Did you know that
Well
Microphones are always usually held above
Where his
That would be so he never knows if he's
Ice Wars I searched prison
Planet internet high and low
Trying to find evidence
M on
Screen with the Moon
How old is the moon
Francois M on
Moon
Anyting
I also don't care if you yelled at the moon it's
You're so big
Lumiere's the sun right
French
So here's another question I have four
What is his name also equivalent to his eventual transformed
State
Play his name is Lumiere and it gets turned into a candle
Names
I can't imagine his
Given name is Luka
Go through all the names
Disney movie Beauty and the Beast
Presaged
And predicted the error that we're living in now
Alright
What is
The witch
But not
Asking our help
Immigrants
What are we
This makes perfect sense
That is why Trump is elected
Beauty and the Beast
Is the greatest
Most
And I don't know where it came from
Must have been an original story that was written in the 90s board
I assume that's correct
Lumiere was translate from French as light
Is a man who is
Candelabra
Lumiere
But you don't know if his his name isn't
Clock in French
Play the only one that makes sense for me
Because he was waiting
Was Chip
Born
Oh no
As a teacup
To have been alive at that time
So we got Miss pops
Yeah
She was the
Fred Berry
Alright
I unfortunately don't know any German
So I can't
I can't really hot dog on this one
It's also
Do
Yep
Germany to
German Chancellor and Powers
Retrospect
Before he was a German
German Chancellor
Ritualistic
Okay great that's
That's very helpful
Alright
He plays
Crazy
Study robot helmets
Probably does not mean helmet
I know that Schmidt
Is it very common name
His name is Helmut Schmidt
That is what I know about how much
Looks like you know a little more
I don't know
So how much was the Federal Republic of Germany from
74 + 90
Those dates are confusing the Federal Republic of Germany
Cuz that was before the Berlin Wall was a member of the social
Craddock party socialist
Which
Socialist also like it in Australia that the Democratic Party
Never trust it whenever somebody coops the name social is Social Democratic
Super. There's no connect
Because
Hitler outlawed the Social Democratic
And exile
How their party
Granted
Although he was throwing up or having a
So what kind of axe
It's a roller coaster there I don't know
Where we at
Well
A big part of my support
For politician
My research did not dig up any of that but I can read about him
You seem like kind of a
A decent guy well-meaning dude special
It's really hard to say what you would have done
World War II
We're brought up
Nazi Germany
No I think it's pretty easy now we know exactly what people were doing a Nazi Germany right now
Vulture
Sure I guess
History is kind of hard to
The square with music
Cuz he did fight for Nazi Germany in World War II
I really don't have any interest
Defending him that's early for that
Attack on those
For sure
Dance on those things
We could do it
But none of the stuff
Relativity
History that we would deem
Problematic
None of that really matches up with any of Alex's
He's he's trying to
Albert Schmitt
Connection with Bohemian Grove you'll inevitably turn up the washing
Houston Post article from
Clearly list
Business
Political figures
Congregate there long before Alex
Exposed
Further it offers
Pretty upfront
Today's Grove
Schedule accordingly
Included the lake
They're followed by Kissinger
An organ concert
Performance
Saturday offers
Shooting hike to the river a band concert
Review in which
It's in the washer
The post in 1980
Me too I don't like how our world leaders go to summer Fantasy Camp so I'm not a fan of that it's
Not like no it's not bad but it's not like
Sinister
And then later on have a weird gay orgy that they're not allowed
The health of
The world
It's not the actual activities
Secrecy
For the most part
If not just alike
Call Jon Ronson
Describes it
Adult
I'm kind of laughable
People with.
Whatever
From Alex over and go back to
About Tony Blair
If you had read the article and actually
It's titled
Con man
Attacks
Prime minister
It takes away a lot of
Is cachet
So he takes
Is blurb from that article
And pretends that it says
Bohemian Grove you take this Colonel of weirdness
It arouses
Takes it out of
So
When Alex does the stuff about the Grove
Recent stuff about helmet
Talk about the Groves
Schmidt's
He's talking about
Is literally quoting for
Script from his movie The Dark speaker
Some like primary source or l
He's quoting his own documentary
I didn't have the time or the money
Order
His book
For this episode
But I did find some people who had
Say is that
Even grow
But the reason given is
It's not because they do the rituals great there
Because the Curious Behavior
People like they're wearing polka.
Instead of suits
And stuff like that they're weird
Not that's not in line with how West Germans are having fun in the 80s
German sense of humor
Crazy
Clearly also makes
Appointment
It's like that which is very
He probably did Howl at the Moon though if he was going to
Also another thing
That I sound guy who's talking about it says
Doing rituals positive about that
Like I said I haven't read the
I would posit
In the stand-ups
People
We're kind of more blowhard
Do refer to going to open mics as a ritual
That sucks
But you can
I'm sure you've heard people
Not necessarily that's supposed to
Example but you talked about like
Going out for a night of drinking
Doing the old ritual
Or having a shot
Is the old ritual
Ritual that isn't like
Satanic ritual
Ritualistic
And so the idea of him being like
Describe it as a ritual
Vacation
Shrek are also in the Washington Post article
Just about how helmets made like the
What is it
You talked about in that article is that
He doesn't want
To go to places
Politicking
And so that's
The original
Union Grove Water
There right there
I was just artist
Was
Spiders come not here
Outside
Exactly
No lady
No report
Circle the first swing
No snitch
I mean all this stuff to me is
Is just like you chosen
Great like
Kernels of something
You can build fear off
But
Closer analysis up that like I would much rather Alex talk about the fact that
How much was a Nazi
In World War II
Career-wise
Why was he you know why did he not have any Nazi
Nations
Have a very
Documented history within the Nazi
Being
Not
Totally on board
Same thing with Francois
Like if you wanted to talk about
Francois mitterrand
Part of the
Vichy government for a little while
He could do that
But if you talked about that
To talk about how
That was only
Only for a little while
Eow
He was part of the
Vichy government and then became a rebel against the
Right right
And he can't do that
Exactly
He was a good host
She was a good show because
Deep dive probably into like the politics
M on
The party
Could you because
Would you think in like historically you know
Like 100 years from now if we still are capable of writing
Do you think people who fought in the American Army would be considered just as evil as people
Like what it what is the war on Iraq but concentrated
How many civilians in Iraq
Battalion
Coastal what like 30 million 300 million
I don't know how you have that conversation
Imagine what the
Even though we're far away enough
Beginning of the Iraq War
Contact
I don't know I still think you are on the side of
I think you are on the side of xylene
Camp stores being listed
Partial
Because
Hey this is true
Trump
Call time
The people who are enlisted are people who
No choice
Not because they're
Economic circumstance
The promise of free
Free college
People to join up
And then when they're in you sign
Contract
Ann if you're in country
Situation
You might die if
You don't kill people
Wrong way
Right you know right
So I think
To err on the side of not being
Fully understand
Intel
Like
Officers
Tea Party
F****** new bat
Can make that claim
There is a certain amount of the enlisted man is the gun
Not the guy Spiro
The guy firing
F****** chimney or whomever you want to go with you know she is
There are some
Of your metaphorical
Likes to go absolutely we're on the side
Trust
Faith
The individual is
Again until there's a
You didn't
End up like
Bignotti later in life
Is Nazi ideology
It just happened a progressive politician
Secret
I'm going to benefit them through policy action to make sure everybody has Healthcare
So weird
I'm going to become Chancellor of West Germany
Running
For a party
That was outlawed by Hitler killed
Alex's stupid spiritualist stuff
Chunk
Looking up that stuff
Tell you how crazy
Like he plays
Bark at the Moon
After this caller right
Did he play
Play Baka
It plays like a minute
And then it just abruptly ghost
Commercial like Alex doesn't even
Commercial
And then
Back
A commercial commercial is playing in the background like
They cut to commercial
But
Alex's broadcast
They were playing at the whole time
They broadcast
The commercial
After the commercials
They come back
With Bark at the Moon
It's a really hoping that it was just playing the whole time
Start sit
Can we come back from
Counterfeit
And a fraud
Nearest Target
What's baptism
Well I'll tell you right now
It's not a ritual
Ritual
What is the ritual
What is an emoji use my word I don't understand what you say
It is a literal
No greater meaning
It's definitely not a ritual
Rituals in the Christian faith
I'll tell you right now well it's whatever
We think that once you know what it's not even wine anymore so I can grapes
Blood
Okay
That's why I don't believe in transubstantiation
Now let's move along
To something else
Alex
Is now going to
To jump
Prediction
About the dire economic
Straight
Some dire strait
Show many layers of society show
Let's get focused
And worse and worse
Bringing a hardcore purse
Okay
Get your head screwed on in the right direction
Alright
Prediction about the financial situation as we know now
From being in
In the present
Stupid
Slightly
She's a trying to sell gold
Are also really terrible
Congress approval rating
It's a branding bait-and-switch
Very cruel
That's not great
I don't like the sound
The only reason people like that President cuz he's black
Like hanging out against Obamacare
Things like that
You said things are good like outside
Because the color of his skin
Everything that Obama did
Every other reason the people liked him every other
I can't think of any other reason cuz all of the
Projections
The people have a pause
Feelings
Profound
Yeah
I mean in a certain way
He is making a perfect strawman argument
The they say you're racist if you don't like Obama's policy
Is the best
Straw man argument that you could possibly make
Cover
People say you're racist
For this
Muttered under his breath is
Braces for this
The last one from February 7th
Continue
Alex is really stupid
Cyraq
I don't want that
Cowardice
I do
Believe that you could beat the military
The wrong people
Children
I mean
You have no idea how awful this thing is that I predict
They're going to hurt
Your children
You're saying to yourself
Right this goes back to that Revelation that I had much
That's exactly what are you saying
You getting to his audience
It's crazy
What is an unfortunate
He thinks we can go
The military is crazy
Literally
Strongest fighting force in the history of the world
Your world
Anytime
In a very short. I want to drop in here real quick
Conversation
It doesn't make sense
Whenever
Yeah.
Mumble
But he said there's no reason
If he really believes the things that he says
Violence is the answer
If you believe that abortion is murder only option is
Again
He thinks there.
Demon
Do you have a radio show is going to
Stop these
Demon
Literally have Supernatural powers
Well they're not human
So they don't
The same protection
I don't know if you do that or not that's the only way
For sale
Doesn't f******
Like I was really wrestle
If one believed the things that Alex
Believes
Literally there's no reason
Your life is worth
Meaningless if there are demons running the world
They're about to
Consolidate
Tyranny dystopia
Terrorist cells
Make militias
Become
Super violet
That's the only like a logical outcome of it
It's not an information will you can't have an information war against
General devil does not care if your life
I mean there's a difference between
Things that you say you believe in things that you actually do
Genuinely believe that
Climate change the world
8 years
Based on that I should be to prepare
Doing that
Figure
To some extent
He's not the same. Getting water or living somewhere
I'm flooding the is because I kill myself
That's why we don't have food in the home
I don't particularly live for the
Apocalyptic scenarios I like podcast
I like
Indoor plumbing
So good
Sono
Held beliefs
Are rational
In terms of climate
GameStop
It's further rational to know that any Lash
Passing out against
Tell me human is not going to do anything
In order to help the goal that you're looking
Where is
In terms of Alex
With rhetoric that you put forth like
I don't know I mean but like the big new Brzezinski is a monster
If you kill him
You can't do that anymore
Rational
Justifications based on Alex's Redwood for violence and the only
To be like
Don't
It's because he knows
And because he knows that he will be arrested
Yeah if people do that
Irene doesn't
So we're done with the 70
Now has come and gone
Yeah 18th
Comes back
With a bold claim
Absolutely
Tour playing two truths and a lie
They took all the money
Grabbed kenlay and then he had a heart attack
Before
He's not a Paraguay right now
Spokane lays in Paraguay
I did not know there's a limerick
Chipotle in Paraguay
Delivery cauliflower
To say he went down there
He lost all his hair
And now I hope
His death
I hope he ends up on Showdown with Bobby's wife
Is a miserable time
Throwdown with Bobby Flay
No
Fake his death
I think that is really
Because you such a con man
Unsatisfying
Didn't cheat. That's sort of like one of these things is like
You want a better end of the story they had a heart attack right but
Before going to prison cuz you also wanted to be punished for what he did
It's just an unsatisfying on ever again but in his other there is a sort of con man as
As Folk hero
That last time
Subway
Maybe
No no
You don't know
The bird that but if you're if you're doing the the conman is folk hero
You got to have that last trick up his sleeve
What is autopsy refoundry
Report its condition was bad
Begin with
Francois
Ended up dying
Shortly after
From a cancer that
Successfully hid
He wasn't power cuz he didn't want to
Course
Public affairs and
Stuff like that I think it's really cool I'm at the
Very selfless
Tough to do I don't think you could pull that off now
Probably couldn't
I'm so no Ken late did not
And further Alex did not report a year before that Enron
Was a narcotic
Money laundering
Also they weren't either of those right
They were just
Eva
I would be surprised if the old brick-and-mortar there's a big money laundering with some Junior exec who is in Norco
Or they were so incompetent that they were just putting money into laundromat
They were yeah they were one of the more corrupt history of American Business
B negative
And Connie
But I would be like
Absolutely
So I'll go ahead
Give him
You know what based on nothing
I'll be like you can say that it's a Narcotics money laundering
Not Gonna Take It
I will stipulate
The year before
I don't know if Hitler kick dogs
But
Judging by his track record
I'll let you say he kick dog
Why not
The other
Argument
Hat that I'd like to give
People along with being able to say I reject your premise
The other one is
Move on
I don't want to get into an argument about whether or not a narcotic
Accepted
That's one strike in a many strikeouts
It's just like a piece of information
Let's pretend it's true
Cool
I can't do a 7-hour episode about this about the time
Read along
So earlier in the last episode
Made a claim about people only like Barack Obama
Because he is a black
And I don't think anybody really prestige
Outside
Some people thought there's a certain amount of like he came up from
Community organizer
There is a fair
I'm out of outside
A relative lack of
Public
Black color
Years in government president
But there wasn't really like a long track record of
Inside outside
Whatever version of
I don't I don't think the argument
Some sort of a rogue
I'm going to come into it
I think I think that everyone had a pretty
He's in the system but he's also
Hey it's early embodying fresher ideas
Bernie Sanders
Coming at you like an outsider
Is it held public office
Use a consummate Insider
Insider the same way
Right right
Anyone who gives a s*** little bit
Stuff about Obama
He's right on that one
So it's sort of a weak argument
People to stand by their promises to not have any lobbyists around
Probably not going to happen unless you get money out of politics we're getting closer with a lot of these Democratic Socialist
Dark money
That make it so
Can't do that because otherwise it'll just
Next cycle
Mammoth amount
I'm going he's already
It's you out there
Yes you are
Sure
You know from Arabia
Muslim
Same thing
Shark
First ever president
The one who's from North Africa
Sure what Dad he's talking about
Around a lot of fake that Barack Obama's options for Dad
Accidentally saying that Obama's dad is his dad
I don't know what you think
That's not.
His dad
Part Swedish
Trump
He was a member of the Nazi party
Brilliant
I mean I don't
I don't care to comment on that past just
The playing of it
Whenever you get into like
Percentages of
People to score points
That usually means
And I don't
I don't
It's hard for me
To hear that in listen
Someone say I'm not being
You know it's hard for me to
Hear someone talk about
Percentages
And be like
Oh yeah you're real chill you're real cool well it's impossible for somebody to say
First Arab president
Like all Arabs
Muslims
How do you get 23andMe back and you want to tell me
Images that's not right
That's okay
But
Anyone else
It's probably going to be suspicious
You taking me
I've never asked and I don't care
I don't care about what percentages I just don't care
Who cares
I don't understand caring about it
This is not the crazy
This is a guest who seen before
The episode when Spencer
He showed up before
He's a guy who is really again
Immigration
He's very on Alex
He's a guy who set up shop down by the border
Pictures of people crossing the border
I meant sends them to authorities
With that information
A******
Big old assholes
Cheese that we talked about
Past episodes
His whole bio
No idea
I think
You're the glencer on the other popular
Take these people
And you realize that they're nothing without some
Someone like Alex
Like they are doing their weirdo thing where they
Like remote-control drones around a train harass
Refugees
But without
Alex
Ebony real Market penetration
Becomes very clear
Even if you agree with like
Illegals are coming
You're still give me like the guy who's flying drunk
He might feel it too much
So without without
Turn off
I-75 people online I got 217
You have a popular show
What that way
Multiple times from 7
Something like that
So like 130 people from Alex's show have checked over
Presumption
Alex
But that's for guys act like you've been there
I gets crazy
It's revealing
Because we also
Summertime
Times I've tracked like
Things he's promoted like GoFundMe isn't he
35 bucks
9 hours
He doesn't really have his much
Galvanize active audience
80%
But people Lakeland
I have nobody
Is oec big jump from Alex
F***
Yet
3 * 4 at this interview he's like
You got a big ol you
And it's not like the normal buttering Alex up and flattering him out very hasty
Genuine excitement almost surprised like
People who actually do things
Which I think is almost
What's the Border
The only human level it's kind of like
Schnucks
So he talks about people in my life
So I don't want to talk too much about what
Character interview mostly about how
They're lying about building
Yeah
To come up or much more importantly
We're going Spencer accidentally
Shows too many cards about what is actual game
I can't get arrested
Find a border for over two years and posting our results and challenging the DHHS
I know the press conference in the National Press Club on January 15th
Spent almost $10,000
How many people showed up in the media nobody
You rented out the Press Club and no one can you
Go fuc yourself
I can't get arrested
It's because he's trying to get punished
To validate their victim Stato he's trying to get arrested
I thought he was trying to get a rest
Like I thought that's what he meant where it's like
I've been giving out all of this information and they're not
Actioning on it
No
I think he's talking about educating flying around the Border like proving them wrong
Whatever
For his for his activity
Sure that makes as much
The context
Episode
Other is Boston Review
Big picture
Get arrest
No one will f*** with me
I keep trying to f*** with them in order to get a response out of them to validate my f******
May everyone keeps ignoring me I think that's what he said
Well
Does make more sense in the context of him being like
200 people are listening to me
We had that Logan Roberts
Temperature
Who decided to not
Challenges on deportation
The idea of being a
Be attacked or else they have nothing
Right and I know it I know it
Things to say like you got proud boys coming out or like you got sacked it
March and go give him a hug
But if everyone did that
Screwed
I'm not I'm not I don't think you should do that many other ways to screw it up
That would be far more status
Reality of the world
Itself to a point
Especially now we're
Not respond
But in a
You could just
End up being like
Whatever exit like in The Blues Brothers world
Everybody everybody else
Never just
The problem is people get hurt
Other people get hurt
Camille want to Light My Fire Boston all over again
That was fun
Look
I think it is going Spencer is presenting
Desperate
Dafuq so far
Episode
Like if that was it
I would have
It's a it's a waste of gas
Who cares
But then they get into this
Gross
Is there a complete upheaval in Mexico and I wouldn't be surprised if it was being
Orchestrated by their
Millions of people across the border
Here are going to be in a world of trouble
A lot of people
District on North
And you got a lot of very vicious people
Who wouldn't think twice about blowing your head off
I can't even
The number of
Racist
Images that were just
Spelled out there
The Mexican consulate
Give out as many fake IDs if you want you wanted
I want Steven Dees
Different names
It's only two
Unless you have somebody else with a fake ID on them already
Sir it is not tempted
Alright
That's crazy
The level that Alex
Spreads
Distrust of like all these other countries that are in America
Their governments are all
Kooky backwards land
As if they are
Well also
What item Mexico and their consulates behave that way there's no way
Country right now
Mexico cities with biggest penis
It is not a novel
It's not like some sweet like
I wasn't trying to present
Mexico is burning
Basically
Not real live in huts
What are you talkin about
Premier Hut
Make you up 100.
Cross the border
And then you get all the welfare you want
Which be documented in a million times
In the next life is
Glenn Spencer putting forth like they won't stick to
To blow your f***
I hate
It's not just down here
They're coming north
Again you Midwestern White's getting scared now cuz later it's going to be too late
There's a vicious people
Blow your head off what bothers me
Especially that
He is even if he's staying
Even if what he's saying is true
Write the government is orchestrating it
So these people hate living in Mexico
To admit them leap right
Like he's causing unrest
So
That means the people who are leaving
Are trying to escape
From unrest
And go to a place
They're not trying to cause unrest
They're escaping from
You are not getting the people who are trying to murder people you're getting people who are
Walked over and Syrian refugees
They're being murdered they're not running away from their homes
Because
The running away from their homes because their government is murdering them
Which
Escaping
From murder is governor
Are we speaking
The people who like
Doing the murdering and all that becomes
Envogue
Stickman
Now they're properly illegal criminals
GoPro
They don't generally flea why would they come to America
Such a feeling of their logic
Ozark Ruth
Pennywise
People who have nowhere else to
It's like the fish in a barrel of crude oil today
Razors
I hope you do come back I know you're dead
Don't feel bad about it
Alex
SpongeBob
Enviro cops
Go out
Brainwashing
You cannot let your children watch TV
Don't go to school
Don't watch TV
The outside world
Just
Listen to my show
Super Nintendo games
And I really like the zombie
My neighbors
New
Bentley's ExxonMobil
Idea of life
You can't trust
Anyone
Your family they don't respect you
The TV
Is lying to you
If you go to school they're going to take your kids away
Exactly
And then they're going to come home to you as like
Diversity
Diversity Dan
1 meaning
That's the one truth
Of the post
Inclusive world
Bald scary clown
He said before but
Properly
Blaine at the last
Time you did
Martial law
I don't think that's just the thing though it's not because there's always
People people are always going to be the problem
That's one population
I haven't heard you talk too much
Really
I'm covering up population
They want to kill most of us it's not all of us
I know that I I
I don't like being
I just like I kept that
My pardon
It's always fun when is
Will rank
Idiot
Weird because he just realized that even his listeners don't listen to him
But this show where you have
Just like
Frustration with the audience assume that they're either like f****** with you or
Or they're working for the globalist
Non critical thinker is in
Is this
Martial law in Concord
It came up
F****** stupid I don't know
I looked into it more after the fact because I was as big.
What I was able to find out
Martial law does not mean the same thing
Is martial law when Alec
Text talks about it
He knows that
It means they let Thurgood Marshall run things for a while
That would be that would be fun.
Use a Supreme Court Justice
Alex knows better
King Sooper irresponsibly whenever the fear of martial law
Staying
Congress is under martial law
Is
Huge Lie by omission
Not explaining what that mean
So there's a process that happens. So infrequently
Chris called martial law
As described by the hill quote
The use of Martial law refers to bypassing the typical procedure that requires the house to wait a day after the rules committee
Produce as a rule
Establishing
Floor debate parameters before voting
It's often enacted
There's a congressional break
Eminent and legislation is
People don't miss
It's a very
Regular thing that happen
Quite a bit
In September 2015
In the house is martial law twice
It's a month
Attempt to avert a government
Shutdown over
In March 27
Martial law was invoked by the
The GOP
Hoping to just
Bouquet rack
That one was less about vacation
More about the fact that if they
Savannah weather
Didn't have a chance
Read the legislation
They'd likely not him
Improved from where they were initially with
Two no votes on the Republican
Inside the Isle
Martial law is April
Edger in the
The house
Name the center
That is done
From time to time for strategic reasons
It just has the same name as Alex Jones as big as
I did not know that until I looked into it either
That's really interesting
If I were up because Alex
Lincoln stays at Congress
Threatened with martial law everyone putting a gun to the Head
Ord
Just sort of like
Do you know whatever
Tutorial
Control
People try to be like
Steve this is another situation
Seems to be all the time to complain about
Jaguars
Is
So I don't I don't
Use the idea of martial law
Of course
Yeah everybody
Abusing
We want to go on vacation but it's Bill's got it
Martial law in the house
Gotcha it's abusive that Alex is using it as them
Some sort of
Buzzword
On his show
He needs to explain every time what it means
Because
Martial law is such a p
Of the property
Yeah yeah
Doctor part of the
The paranoia the propaganda put out
He's made multiple documents
He's about martial law being on the street
Stuff like that
To the point where any time
He brings it up on the show
Code the audience knows what he's talking about from
Police state documentary
So
To me this is one of the most unfair thing
He eat.
So abusive to his audio
I just dismissed it out of hand because that's
Stupid the idea that Congress was threatened with martial law now that I know it's actually a thing
Yeah I think
The first time we went over it
When he brought it upsets
Start a car
We were operating off believing like you was talking about
Yeah so
Serous are always
Just do a layup
Your f****** telescope the Lucifer god dammit
I guess I understand just that's a good fun
It is good fun
But you just got to think for two seconds
People are going to be stupid about that could guess what
People are f****** stupid
Lancer problem people have that like
When you don't have ill-will
And you're just trying to live your life
It seems unnecessary to
WarGames thing
Yeah
Defense against
Crazy at the same time there's no way to plan for irrational actors if you're irrational
It doesn't matter what you do crazy no matter what
What are the feelings Alex
Nice transitions bag
Is that his listeners
Are stupid
That last call
Start up where he's lashing out
If that last call
Reveal something
Incredibly
Somebody comes knocking on the door want to talk to Alex Jones don't come to my house
My family room sleeping
That was upsetting I literally
Dizzy right now
I work this much
For several months
I'm working so hard that my vision blur sometimes call me
You lazy little preacher
I think it needs a nap
Alex
He's responding to that caller who's like you never bring up population
I don't mind him yelling at that dude but it's super f***** up that he's like I didn't
Sleep the night before because I was on Costa
And then I tried to go to bed and so f****** listener showed up at my house
But that's f***** up
That is really really f***** up
You should know
Urban legend
Sasquatch
Just go knock on Sasquatch
I mean I get it we drove past it for Studio
Same sort of like we were going to knock on the door
But it was that sort of saying like
Almost Pilgrim AG aspect of like
Let's go get into his face I am a little disappointed we didn't leave a flaming
No that's true
It's f***** up it's f***** up your audience would do that
It's f***** up that you had to go through that
Kind of empathize a little bit
Even if you are the
Who is created that vibe
I still is a human in lye
Man that's got
Same time
You know
He should be driven insane
Buy one single not every time his eyes closed I don't I don't disagree
But I'm just saying Isaac
I looked at
Great luck
Goes out the window when you remember like on a last 2009 episode
Respect
So like
Who else do they have to go to
It scares me the idea of like anybody showing up
Someone's door just because
Something to go wrong some misunderstanding
His wife and kids are they're going to like
There's just too much
That
Really think that's a horror movie
What he's described
Someone who likes me knocks on my door
The f****** horror
Right right
Baseline
That's a good
Okay
Legally actionable is
We get a team of paper
Roughly
Everybody
Every hour
Knox
Scott Pruitt
Everybody gets their own hour
Everybody has to knock like two or three times then they Runaway
I think it's not terrible plan but
Because we're talking about it on air it's
The problem is is that illegal
I guess it's like a nuisance but illegal individually for them because of like private property
Probably
Conspiracy harassment
Okay cuz we're organized
What we should do is go to the next one
Facebook where Alex Jones
Brings in
The arch weirdo
Okay
About this guy
Now.
From
Top
We've been waiting with bated breath
Stop
Now there
Our house
Stafford Lindsey tells me this I start putting feelers out
Okay
So the gas
Who is the complete weirdo
There's a
Prefer
Who is going to be on
The show
I don't like it when you say pastor and they are on it
Let's not going to bode well
So we're getting weird predictions and his stupidity here in a few
Website
Is a catalog
Of people's mineral rights
Because all that's very public
Information
You can find this
Information David Jones
A number of different oil
Course David Bowie.
Okay then
He owns a number of oil
Claims
And throughout
Area
What is that on Zoe's
Whenever you have
You own a claim
2 what's under the land
Share those
Yeah
Free People
Clearly is that
Someone's drinking somebody's
There's an artificial inflation of oil price
Right
Strike in
Disgust
The past fear of things collapsing in the Middle East
Ulta
Together exactly the same time
And led to
Hyperinflation
The price of oil
It lasted throughout
A bit like almost a year 2000
And the bottoms
The beginning
The oil holding
Estimated revenue on a monthly basis
From the
Atlanta
We're 55,000
$42
Monthly
$55,000
Just from the ownership of the oil right now.
Extracted it all someone else does all that
He just get six hundred grand for free every year
Yep there's the contract
That's who he's getting it from is from the people who are taking it out yet
Company owner
So now you go a little bit further you get into Where We Are
In 2000
The end of
You sneeze
Alex Jones Is Dead
Probably only worth about ten
Thousand
So you go from 55,000 town to around 10,000
And like as it goes on
That was a hit
It comes from the price of oil
Yeah
Migrated its foul to lower level than it was before
But they're pretending this
Hundred forty dollars a barrel oil is normal
That's be hyper yeah yeah yeah
It came down to like
3 something
I meant rebounded to
More normal level
It before that was a
It was only at like
Did you talk about 6230 that's still
50% drop yeah
That could be what you want to talk about but instead they use the
40 hyper number
From all these pics
9 months
It's super inches
What that discretionary income
In the Jones family
Disappeared
Right around the
Time
Need Monday bring somebody who has a lot of money
Again.
I'm only bringing this up
Because
Involvement
Is relevant
This information that I found
It's weird I mean like I don't know what
I do remember
Necessarily but
I think two dudes like
I don't get I don't like
I don't have a radio Studio that my parents are providing right
But I do think
Zet
Your family's life would change
If you lost $40,000 a month
It just random
I don't think that that's irrelevant at all
Think that's huge
Because is that
I guess dad has his job job
The kid's life job and then just because of the s*** he owned he's getting 55.
I mean at the same time though it was a
One time it was like a massive windfall
That you couldn't really budget so unless they went wild on spending
Entirely possible if you have a half a million dollars that you weren't expect
Think she'll ride around with Alex
Studios
But also looking forward very quickly
If you look at what
Before is that
Huge spike in oil prices
They were still under $20,000 a month
Like it went up in 2006
Peak jumped over the toy
$20,000
And then it was sort of
Leveling around
It always leveling around there in the high 10
Jump
South of 20,000
Extra dollars a month
So either you
Budget that and plan for it to drop down again which it was
Have to assume it would
You go ape crazy and buy yourself a new studio
Right and I don't know if
What is necessary
Become like
Super Thrifty I'm going to live out the rest of my days considering he's now
The HR representative
New like I think his dad might be
So much more invested
Sit in the company then anyone is really dealing might be a part of it
Yeah I don't know
I don't know
I think this
I think it is
These accidentally
Revealed
Well I looked at up the open
To look at like
Interesting
You for a year
Giant
I'm out of money coming
Your family that wasn't there before
And then after that
Your
Getting into a position where
Maybe summer
Of your narrative
.
Not saying I'm just saying
Anyway Lindsey Williams
Yes
Music
He comes in
I think he is I don't know
That this isn't one of those that I decided I was
Going to like call the back
Just church and find out
Because he's
I don't know I'm working
Concerned with him
Outright
He's good at one thing
Flattering
This is all planted by the elite
Let me assure everyone out there in Alex Jones
Infowars
Everything you are hearing Alex Jones say is true
Believe every word you hear every day it may sound unbelievable
It's very sad right but
If you're not talking about info
Believe every single thing every single day
It's very clear that you could camp
He knows how to get out of
Still like not Quest
Lindsey Williams I'm just going to flash this out as best I can cuz I don't
Do you spell Poseidon
Alaska in 1971
Three years later the transit last trans Alaska pipeline
I was beginning Construction
Volunteered to be the chaplain of the pipeline
Being a volunteer chaplain executive with the oil company
The world
That's your story
What
You want to know
What do you question
Is this
Standard practice
To bring the chaplain into hey we're f****** over the world
I feel like it's a
I feel like
I feel like you're either a shity executive you probably like
He's that guy like
God he's probably
Probably going to have a higher power than money
Let's not bring him into our f****** secret
Other side of that question
If you are an executive
Oh I'm scared
Maybe you should join my scam
And then we'll all together
That to me
I know your response
Set storage in Paso
The smell test
Anyway I don't know why
That one makes the most sense at least
Only because the rest of it is such b*******
What
Are you want
Okay great
Schneider the chaplain because nobody said
It's not an elected position if you're the volunteer chaplain
No volunteer chaplain
Executive status that have a man of God in there whenever you're built
Hour-and-a-half
DVD that he put out
He was telling his story
Add swiss cheese baby
There is just holes everywhere like
Is just
What what
Dwight White
Your chaplain they let you into the secret battle believe that number two
74th on and white
Right do you was doing that
Continue until present
So where's your information
People
In the seventies that let you win
The boardroom possibly have heard about scams
That they were doing
And you didn't tell anybody
On you
That's unless they left a detailed plan
This point
From that time
All the things
You knew about it ahead of time
DD's order
Post
Post facto propaganda
All this guy's got
That is all he has
Just talk
Think about things
Have already happened and it like
Oh yeah something about that
I do about that Insider source
Love it
NSX clip he's going to talk
About the per
They have planned this thing worldwide
In order to
To do what they wish to accomplish now let me tell you what's going to happen in America
Is happening right today
And you taking notes this man said to me
Person who knows everything 82 years of age
He said to me after I've been threatened
Go along with what you said
I couldn't even say on Alex Jones Show today
Keeping Network he said to me he said Lindsey
He said America will see a financial collapse
It will take years to come out of it at that time we didn't have the bank crisis we didn't have a real estate prices
We didn't have the big bailout packages we got right now he told It All To Me ahead of time
Because they had it planned
I wish I could shout it today
Believe everything you are hearing Alex Jones say even if you have trouble believing
Believe it anyway
That's a man of God right there
Hey YouTube you don't even if you do even if it doesn't pass the smell test
Believer
Just believe it
I know that I know that I know baby
So he took some notes he's hearing this plan
In 71
No showed up in Alaska
Haha
Write okay though it's because of that information
Nope
So you got different information
Eunos
He knows a guy
He said he's 82 years old some guy was eighty-two years old
He has an inside Elite source
Another
So he claims any of the secret of Insider sources told him about the 2008/2009 crashed that it was going to happen before
Problem with his prediction is the same with all of Alex's
Secateurs all of his death
Just claiming they were told it was going to happen before it did
The easiest Hong Kong the game
And only made worse by the fact that almost all of this guy's not
With predictions like there's going to be trouble in the Middle East
Coronavirus
Everything else
Watershed
He claimed that the devil's Messiah was supposed to show up in 2012
The dollar was supposed to clap the number of times
Global Currency Reset
Then they turned it off and on
Modem predictions about silver and gold prices
She also is pushing it
I'm as well as oil prices every specifically
But he's talking about
Because he's got it from the
Insidesource it's fun when they start to believe their own b******* and they make specific birthday
Like my favorite part whenever they reveal how stupid they are
Where is
Oh s***
I am getting all these things right
Forgetting
Predictions
Because
Based on his narrative
He was
Yeah with the elite
Oil Company in that s***
In the seventies and then telling him things that are going to happen they should never be wrong
He's not guessing
You know
It's not really a prediction so much as it is
Revelation whistleblowing
Yeah
Whistleblowing is a great Pretender
He's doing
So there's there's trouble there
I mean even
Executive and then Within Me
Crazy
You have this inside the secret to my success
Then the other part I've got this Insider Source was telling me all this stuff that's bull
How old is
Anybody who's not
Using him for their own
Gold
Would be like
Dude
Stop it
Is crazy
And this
I think is
Hilarious
The average American didn't have the slightest.
Structure
Off the
Price of crude oil
147 dollars Barrel 2
It went down from $45 per gallon
$2.50 a gallon in some states
Write down these two words
Text Rodger
Textra
Did the thing is like
It's not like
Gas is been
$140 a barrel for
More than a few months
It's been months but it's been
It's not like yeah
.
As a result of that
And others have walls
75% or more
Now that he's pretending that all taxes come from oil
Does not
Accurate adults
Oil
Specifically
That means that the entire Texas
Lost 75% of its
Which is ludicrous
I was just waiting over
All the money that will be given away in Denver
They going to
The College of the university in Denver
They're going to improve
Coming off of the interstate
They going to build a building
If they gave you say
10 million-dollar
And you were supposed to build a new ramp off of such-and-such of an interstate with it
Approximately
60% of 40
Stimulus package they have intentionally
And it's not a single Congress stimulus package
Because now
Updates going to be able to
All of these items
The other taxes
An argument for why the stimulus package didn't go far enough which is the progressive argument at the time
I'm so like
You got stimulus check
What you yelling at the GOP
Conservatory
Individual people get stimulus checks
Couple hundred
You know that that's how are they supposed to live for the rest of their lives
My stimulus
Give a man a fish
Doesn't cover everything
Play PID
Get to you're going
That sort of thing is the stimulate its motion
Push
Where's the red
Google have multiple meanings
No
It's like the idea of like
So this
Big
Like load of money
Gabe is going to pay for 60% of
Regular budget
Next year's taxes all of that makes perfect
Have you read this bill
Do you know what it does
I just looked it up in Denver
It improve their infrastructure
Which they need
And it doesn't
At a really high percentage
More people
Are going to be there.
Text money
Is going to be
Victory evil it's part of their plan than 60%
Improvement on
Infrastructure issues
Pretty good math
So I don't know this is just
This is ludicrous
Like the idea of presenting the idea that all taxes come from oil
For granted a lot of
Text Doug
I hope it's not all of it
Most sincerely
The other is the
I mean I like your angle on a
Better than
The idea of life
You're actually arguing it should have been more of a better attack on it
Snooze is showing all of the policy principles that Alexandria is pushing and they're like
He wants you to have
Healthcare
Betseyville
She wants you to eat
Bulshit
Things that you should be afraid
Healthcare
Education
Turn lights
For your family
Thievul
Williams
Dude
It's crazy
He's a gas to the racino
On the show
Like I said I watch
A bunch of his other stuff I was going to get clips from that but
Too boring
It's just
It's nonsense
I really want to drive home is like
He's not saying
These predictions are all
Like after the fact
They're just validating his nonsense
But the reason
Pull it off
Because he knows the game
The number of times different people that said what you want you please call this man back and get some more latest information I'm going to admit
Cialix
So that isn't in reference to
To this source that he has
People keep asking
Him to call him hey
Find out what
Alice's up
Too scared to call that guy back
You have now made yourself a public Persona that
Dependent on this guy's information
You call that a****** back
No matter what
All that assholes
You say you called that ass hold back and you make up whatever it is you want
Call me a****** in the first place
Spoiler alert
That's what he starts doing a couple years after 2000
I am I'm fighting to even think of what he might tell me
What do I make of this
The fact that they have accelerated that
Here it is
Just
Contact Steve the question
Is like
What do you think about the idea that oil has gone down
So far
Like it's gone down so far so quickly
Alex the reason they had done this in my mind thinking it's because
They realize
Program Blacula
Alex Jones
So many people
The American people are beginning to reveal
Washington control
I found that there was only one thing they were afraid of
I didn't bother them they had control of that Congress didn't concern them the president
What is the one thing
They are afraid of the American
Publix the masses of people waking up
And that's where Alex Jones Show comes in
That's where Infowars comes and that's where infowars.com comes in
Jim more than anything else in this world
When the masses of people wake up they don't have a chance there's a handful of them
I believe Alex
Reason that they have
Accelerated
Dag worldwide
Pakistan American worldwide
I'm going below $50 a barrel
The reason I believe they've done it is because so many
Amazing
That is
That's a badass
Licking of the highest order
Yep
That's a solid move right there a little bit
She listened to the show
He figured out what talking points were hot right now you Barrel them back
And now Dan I'm going to stay
He's going to get to the cell
It has like his DVD Empire that he does later
You end up coming back on it for the bun
Like he gets much more of his own Cottage Inn
Unfollowers go from 100 to 300
Much like a climbing
Never really spells out on the shows at the globalist
Crashed the oil
They're going to submit Revolution
All over the world
Noted pushed the price of oil back up to about $200 a barrel.
To reveal the secret oil reserves that they control
They pretended didn't exist until that moment she knows about from back when he was in the 70
Working with these oil Executives as a volunteer chaplain lower the price of oil
No because they get to under $300 a barrel that they have more oil
Then that would drive down the price
Cerveza I know shushing is little bit but yeah
Dial scale
Yep
Got a big problem years ago
40 years long
Cardinals hat
Bring the price of oil up really high
Normalize the price back down
40 year long
But even Alex's dad is it so bad that even Alex's fan
Keep him
Provost on real truth online
With the headline it's cracked
Berkeley unanimous @prisonplanet
Oil Insider Lindsay Williams is full of s***
The article is about a mini Rebellion that's taking place in the Infowars forums
Text Lindsay William
Quotes
The outrage
Seems to stem from the fact that William
The pop-up and make appearances on the Alex Jones Show every time there's a world crisis
What affects the price of crude oil
I have two claims I Williams is made about being in danger for his whistleblowing
Williams claims that he's received
Threats in the past bags
The obvious question
Why is it keep risking his life every 3 to 4 months to bring up his darling revelation
It's a good question, Sleep Center
Jones's information
If it's so earth-shattering after all that's what you'd really do be
Forget your whistleblowers
Information
I'd wanted to remain alive
Because
Cannot make a goddamn Penny if he's given up his information anonymously dollar
That is so true
He is trying to save us
Because the only way to stop the globalist
Is that the American people wake up
This is
An altruistic
Effort
Some comments from the Infowars for
Melvin
This is something he's not really do.
Give me some from the info Warriors themselves
The sharpest tool in the shed but even my granny could recognize Williams for what he is
A bullshiting opportunist
Alright I like it
There's another one strict and to-the-point there's a clear script in formula
It's not at all improvised
I think many are coming to the conclusion he's just trying to sell DVD
Another one quote
For the past eight years.
Sadly today I just can't stand listening to this kind of bulshit Lindsey Williams
Lindsey Williams is Alex Jones in 5 to 8 years from now
Early today I just realized that Alex is just in it for the money and I have nothing against him for making a living but
This is too much
It seems like a waste of my time
Was just mostly Cut From the Same Cloth
Look, they're like you clearly just in it for the money
Golden
And they do
There would be more informative than this guy
Nice
Question
Pass along information
From others
Ever be wrong even once
The World by the Arctic
For both enemies and allies
And Alex's
We got this guy
Mitre oversold it a little bit based on the content that
Please bring to the table
Is really fascinating to me like
Clear
Gino's
The game that is flatter Alex
You'll be one of his go-to guy
And Alex's
Falling for you
Absolutely
B like this is only
Six months after the episode where list
Because he comes back later
Okay okay
Where he comes
And he is now in
Introduced his line of DVD he's starting to
He's not doing much
Walking on this episode
He's laying the groundwork he's not in the rotation
He's laying the seats
We're going to Prosperity Gospel
For later grow
So
Brilliant conman whose actual call is terrible
But his game is good
What is salt
Is game is good in terms of like knowing
This guy will help me move
But the actual con is
So thin
Let The Listener see through it
It seems like you're wrong about all these predictions
Heavy cotton to pull
On Alex Jones listeners
You're you're bringing some weak sauce
Get into a rewrite just get into a writers room
Get in there be like what's up what's the best confer here
Why am I sucking up how about how about this
Have a couple Focus Group
They're going to go
If you can afford a $10,000 press
Room
That nobody goes to
Inside a couple your friend
Volume down
Figure out what cam going to work best
I agree
If I was going to become a con man
Right I would do that first
Get a basic
Business plan setup
Take it to the bank say look I'm going to be caught
Here's my scam the bank is going to be like we're amoral so it doesn't matter
Let's lend you $20,000
Dokkan tier Heights
Brilliant
Fuel saver good
Community in French
Realtor
I'll be fine.
We could all come
Comics
Open mics need to turn into like scam operation
No reason to be sitting there
Over and over the room coming up with elaborate
Damn
Why not everyone else is just like in the alley and being like
Has jokes.
You're waiting like 11 that's what we're going to be shittin
The back of the room doing nothing and slamming shots if I was actually
Alright
Bank of America
1 weeks
And it's a lovely tell her
Her name is
Wrong
Danica Danica is the one who's going to get us into the manager's office
Office the manager
Connecticut
You need to be right
I'll be sitting around
Figure out a way to come up with like a b*******
Diet product
Or something like that
Don't make much more money and it wouldn't be illegal immediately
L'eagle
You make millions of dollars before it actually
Another time to get to I'm sorry I can't take around for the rest of the shop
I want I want to tell you about what's going on in my cart right now
I feel like I oversold
Yeah
He's crazy too
Put on paper maybe a presentation
He's not as crazy
I think I think there's some
Obviously fun
He's a clear liar and he's
Brown noser
I think that I think I might I think I might be more into him
Ages are to be the problem is that crazy
Does not necessarily mean wack
I think a lot of people when we when you stayed like this
This Gaston Alex Jones is crazy
Most people are thinking
He's going to say some wild s***
Is crazy in like a like idiotic
The fact that
I've not seen any guests that there's been an insurrection
That's pretty crazy
Diploid
Was worse atalissa
Just because he
He was so transparently bad at this
Somebody stop listening to the show and now we know as we move forward when we hear him
Like we know
The game music
Play
And how he's going to be pissing off the Infowars
That'll happen
Clips
Call
Sky Zone
Hello
Master key to
I don't know if this has any bearing on anything
But you don't have 2424 Cipher
Barack Obama
Beach and Berlin
I want
Come out the rear of the building
And
Him and one reporter and one cameraman only
Anna
Excited
What was the purpose
Your speech needs it so Christian
Juice
And Muslims
Commercial Payday 2
Together
Because I'm a Muslim
He said he repeated that question
2 *
Do you think that that will have any effect on how he governs our
So hold on for a second and imagine imagine that interview
Why did you give us so we can all get along
Very ideas that is so hilarious
Play into their fears
I want to bring the worlds
Together so we stopped killing
Each other
Because I'm a Muslim
And you're like
So does that
So that's a good thing you guys still complaining that he's a member of Reverend Wright
Cuz he's a Muslim
Christian
Monster with and he's got Weather Underground
Man it's so funny
Is the idea
In my mind I'm picturing it and stuck behind this venue
I don't know how to play it out in words
Picture of my head
Alright
Obama
Walking out the back door he's got his bodyguard
There is a row of children
All wanting autograph
Comes up to him
And he's like
What
He's in the middle of signing an autograph
He's signing it.
Cuz I want
Jews
Muslims
And Christians all to get along
Together
Crabs
The autograph note tears it up throws it across a girl's throat
Mic drop
Country
It's already having a second look at the bill he signed yesterday
And he made the statement he said I was elected president I will drop the building
It's disgust
Bergenfield
The burn exercise
Running reporter down to ask
To admit that he was a Muslim man
And also one last point
About how to prepare
Power Probe
People need to start vacuum sealing ammunition
And Beyond
Wagon right now
You go look for it you try to find it
Kind of
So do you know
Do you know what happened with the bullet
Around this time
Savon
The government was just buying up all the ammunition to remember him
The 2008 election of Barack Obama
Increase sales in both firearms and ammunition
Reloading components
Dealer
She was selling
Semi-automatic rifle
You can put them on the Shelf
The issue was not ever that the government was buying up stuff
It was that these people these propagandist were creating such a fervor of they're going to take your gun
Everyone
Bought out the stocks do f******
Fast
There was
8 legitimate
Here's long ammunition shortage
So that was the 1929 stock market crash of
Yep essentially
I mean you can look into it there was a almost 5 year long just run on bullet
Cause of all this. Like you can't get it
Go to a gun show at any f*****
Pinpoint
Shows around
And I wish I could find guns that seems like the obvious answered cuz we got
So many
Is America ready for a black president
When you see the ammunition sales are
Stocks are disappearing
The answer is no guys
The answer is no
People are buying them or semi-automatic weapon
America is not ready for a black president not just
Also guns
All of it
It was because
These right-wing propaganda
Pushed
Tumi
I think this is a good place to end the episode
Because it's so
The
Narrative
Because they are
Because
They also
Are benefiting
From
The
Lack of product
Their rhetoric about their becoming a
After being a black president
He's what
Cause
Do you run on
Like the government buying up all right
Circle
HD ever
Tree of propaganda
That's f******
Gorgeous
And you see this order thing you're like
I don't think there's any hope
But this is no this is what's fascinating about
Because I do kind of think
Cuz we're we're way wrong
Here's what
They're really say
The entire propaganda is
There's a black president
Now black people are going to do to us what we did
So we need to buy
They wouldn't say that way but that's the real heart of all of their fears
Is there a we're like the more they get bitching about
I don't want to feel guilty for being white right what they really mean is I don't want to be
Punished for all the s*** that I know weed
I don't want to I don't want it brought up how much I've been in advantage
Because of Britain
And if
If we give them power
Which is the way they view it
Figure out
Then we're going to be
And you know what is wrong
For me
The last episode
Talk about
There's more of them destroy all of us
Is a fear of like
I want
To do that I think they would do that if they had one
It's like
Because on some intrinsic
That suggests they are well aware that people have committed
The worst crap
Know that they are well
And so it's it's
It really does
Crazy you can you can either accept that reality
And
Move forward with that or you can do the white thing
Which is create your own alternative reality where you're always the best
Investigation we are
Dangerously close
The beginning of the public
Very excited
See what happens with that will be there shortly
But
For now
What we've learned
Not a lot
Mostly stuff we already knew
Just whisk
How long
Real shortly
And
Big enough
I know
Liver of a
Is heroin much like it's learn
Away from being able to make this announcement all millions of those atoms
Absolutely
But if you like so please go to
Check the comment section in 2009
In five more about the show tonight
In case anyone
Other than
The show
Sponsors other than Elizabeth
Chrysler
This show
Is
We do not have
There is no one else doing anything
No very nice
Listeners whoever down to go to post
Pretty
Nothing behind us
There's no
Business
Sitting in my goddamn bedroom
Recording the show to the
Chagrin of my roommate
Because we are very loud
You guys want to support the show
Know that you were supporting
Literally two dudes
And that's it
We are at now that's right
Facebook
ITunes
Download show leave a review
Spread the word
Chirp
Don't snitch
Don't tell anybody my goddamn self
I don't use my personal Facebook account
And so I don't
I'm not able to
Respond to that
Ever so often
People who like mention
The show income
I'll see that on the knowledge
And then I can't
Respond
Like I saw
Someone was
Saying Casey
Woodmont private
I saw someone comment on one of Derrick's
Comedian Derek
Post
And they posted
You should check out knowledge fight
And I wanted to like
Hey I know Derek
But I can't but I still appreciate
People doing that
In the suburbs
And afterwards a dude came up to me who had been living in La for a while
Oh man great job
I want to follow what your Facebook was your Twitter what's your Instagram
I was like I don't have its G
I left Facebook
Kind of have a Twitter
No you got to Branch out your a brand and all that so that's when I immediately deactivated
00 social networks right now
And it is exciting
I also my brand is really suffer
I guess we've come
The end of this
Today sir
Who you going to go with
Yeah there's a murderer's row
Mother's not
I don't know I think the last guy with the X-Men now the guy with the the collar with the exit
Can't do it
I've got
Okay
Sir
You have
Completely lied
About a couple people who probably don't deserve the benefit of the doubt
Look
The Blairs are not
2B deified or thought of his Heroes
Situational because you are such a flagrant conman
You invalidate a lot of criticism against
That is very real good point Roberts
Please do the world a favor
And please go fuc
Yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color