Alexandra Thurston color
Are you to describe this podcast to our eventual of eventual Overlord
Murderous one by one
Slowly
And they were like
You don't really
Let me listen to this podcast
Garmin today
Soil fish water
We made it
Actually what it is now that guy stop listening
I only know what you tell me about Alex
Does not matter today
Because today
Project winter
Every now and again off and on Wednesdays we like to take a little bit of a break
Scrum
His dribble
Con man around the world
The weird right-wing internet break from reality
Project Camelot
Kerry Cassidy orthodontist
Secret space program
You got a very
Even
Departure from
That's to go into
Superfund
Delightful
But course it is
This is
Man
All right I want to hear this
Say hello to a nude
Selmer sponsor
You are sponsoring reply
You are all better than Coca-Cola gave us
A lot of money
Do you know what I do appreciate it because this comes
From the heart
People actually supporting what we do as opposed to Coca-Cola
Just trying to
Cash Cola really does support
You have never list
I'll believe them
Cassadee Pope
Secret space program
Maaco
Anyway thank you so much for showing up
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Support the show button
Help
Please do
So Jordan
Please.
Sort of made my Big River
What is the Project Camelot episode no big surprise
Write me to click this button
Are you to hear Karen Castillo
The setup it's not really I'm just too
Is underwhelming cuz every episode starts with her adoption
Sometimes it's a surprise on the
It's not at all so it's not a surprise Kira's carry opening up the show
Using us to what
Is going to be
Hi everyone I'm sure Cassidy from Project Camelot and
Sorry for the late start here we've
Just had all kinds of
At any rate I'm here with Ben emlyn Jones
And I'm very happy
On the show
There's
Such a great amount of
He's been covering and
He's an investigator
Fascinating woman
Call Ellen Duncan
And as I wrote
On my
Below in the chat basically she
Her story is that she was
In prison
By Ian Fleming Fleming with the help of Ian Fleming
Oh boy
I was
My first thought when she
She said Helen there's a little Plaza
Is it going to make a documentary about Helen Keller
Tim Burton
I don't know I don't
Blame
Probably the misconception
Monkeybone
No no it was
It was directed by the person
The reason is
Monkeybone was all about like from the director of Nightmare Before Christmas
From Nightmare Before Christmas
And then had nothing to do with monkey
Exactly
So
Nightmare Before Christmas
Implied
Bratz movie theater monkey bone came out
Everyone was
Furious they all like all these nerves one of their money back
I couldn't blame them but I'm like popcorn I can't help
Churchill who is the Raven Tim Burton
Yeah that could be
Yeah I'm still in together
Conspired to make his movie
No but I feel like I did
Like I knew the name like the names
Familiar to me but now I
And now I just don't
Not certain
Viewed wood
You like
I don't know
Duncan was a spiritualist in medium operating for
I'm about
26 and tell her ass tonight
She's creating harmless hoaxes for a really long time was left
Largely to harambe
Only occasionally running afoul of the law generally resulting
Minor signs
For fraud
People with seance
Along the road
Right I have a lot to get in
About about her
And this was in Britain right
I believe one of the reasons that I might know this
Because
This wasn't like I was reading about Harry Houdini and how he was
Essentially ghost busting
At the same time
Feel good
And that became a whole thing and there was a guy who did that
I don't know is anyone necessarily
Did that with her as opposed
A lot of
People
So
I'm going to let this play and then I'll get some information
Because I'm not sure exactly where it's relevant
You know I want this Ben gentleman
For him to hang himself a little bit
Nope
Why
Or it could have been a quince
I don't know why she would have been out there the story is apocryphal anyway I don't know
Willington
Randomness any of those things are much more likely
I don't know maybe your dad was a cop
Even like it just would
And involve just the police looking for
So
Dial talk a little bit about her adult
So in November 9th
Where she claimed that the
The spirit of a sailor aboard HMS Barham
Had appeared to her and told her that the
The ship has sunk
This is a bit of an issue
Because I didn't formation
Was not made public until January 9th
This information was only told
The family members of the
People lost on
HMS Barham
61 people on board
Reconsider how many family members that makes
You consider that all it takes
For one of these
These people to talk about it for the secret
To get out, this is the vision that this information wasn't
Researchers
Nation nearly a secret
Is the government
Many people know about
Before
So the fact that she knew about it means that
But you just had her.
Some like loose talk
Bob and decided to use a jaguar
Seances
Get the government's attention
So they started to look into an amazing way the spirits
She allegedly was
Contact with
We're often not real dad
Is one example of a like a guy who went and she was like
I'm talking to your dad
Beybladers like I found your sisters
My sister's alive everybody
He has a bad that
From time to time right to her and all this
There was little sign
The came along running afoul of fraud laws in
And stuff like that
Obscure old laws
Actor 1735 to throw in prison
All right I don't like right now I'm not on anybody. All bottles
If you're if you're using the Witchcraft Act
Charger
To charge the 1944
And because was kind of trumped-up bulshit
19:45
You promise to stop holding
He was arrested for conducting seances again in 1956 and died shortly
Listen
This is a lot of like this
To give you the
Basic
Picture
Of like why were the police
Draw the suspicions of the government
I haven't
Shown
You yet exactly why I'm positive
The fraud
Trying to get the sense that like
Okay someone running seances back
Pen for money
Was probably the one that gave it away
The run-of-the-mill stuff
You know that you know John Edward kind of
Levels of like yeah you guys are all
You guys are all running back
And you know what we all kind of know it's like everybody goes to the Sands doesn't believe in that shape
They just want that comfortable even for a moment
Helen
Further
Helen Duncan
Was
The LeBron James of seances
Killed that Aunt and then Seance the f*** out of that ants
Metaphorically
Is it clip
Then
Power for me
All time
Which is manifestation
Manifestation
Physical objects
Or Slimer from Ghostbusters
Interesting
You know
Way to look at it
There's other way
So Jordan
The way her seances Woodwork and this is he
Made clear there
Apart from other mediums
Is the cheek
Said she could manifest things into the world that work there
So she would create this ectoplasm they would come out of her mouth Jenner
Plaza would be connected to apparitions
Showing up in a very dark room
Where's your conductor seance
Photographer named Harvey Metcalfe showed up
Flash photography
Covered in a sheet
Discovered
Somehow this Revelation did not destroy Helens business model and chic
In 1931 the London spiritualist Academy started has some questions about Helen's meth
I would imagine that they were thinking. Hey this person
Do things that literally no one else
Can do I wonder what's up with that
I'm so they open
Examination
Very quickly they were able to determine that the way Helen produce ectoplasm was by ingesting a bunch of
Throwing it back up performatively
The room was dark and sometimes she would lock herself in a cabinet
The most usual method for ectoplasm however seem to be butter mucilin or cheese
Cheesecloth probably swallowed in Woodridge
Distressing choking noises were sometimes from What epic app
Cuz she couldn't throw it up
They used to give people a lot of the benefit of the doubt
A crazy about this magical stuff but I have to go make throw up noises
What are you doing
It's pretty crazy
So once they figured out that is probably how Helen was doing
The most surprising piece of evidence that Helen was full of s*** was literally
Kool-Aid dye pill before performance
Crystal clear
For some weird reason she was unable to produce ectoplasm that night mysterious
Blood-stained look everybody
Still alive
Seems imperative
Wait till
Deed the spiritualist society
Believing in spiritualism or they like let's not do those spiritually
No Heroes here
They were like
Hold on
Means that they're at least on the right side
Well I was at Panera
What I am
I am far more believing
People who were like communicate to the others
Cuz f******
Find there's multiple dimensions
Is it. Then you start having to talk about
Actual physics
Like this is why ghosts don't exist
There would have to be a particle
Something that can interact
But the physical world that's foolish close by manifestations Van that
Breaks all the laws of physics and every single scientist
Would descend upon you
Is this even have the whip
Obtrude
Well yeah I mean to some extent that's true
Because you can break the the simple law of matter cannot be created or
Destroy everything is out the window once this lady throws up the cheesecloth
Hair world
This guy named I
The director of the National Laboratory of physical research
PayPal
Right Use the sample of her ectoplasm
The definitively show that it was
This passage
Maybe one of my favorite things I've read about one of these tan people from Israel
On one of those
At the conclusion of the fourth seance
We led the medium to aesthetic
And I called for the apparatus
That's effective at the lady promptly went into a trance
She recovered but refused to be x-rayed
Went up there and told her that it was pain
She jumped up and gave him a smashing blow to the face which sent him reeling
Is your husband as a woman in the in the 20th or the 30th but also
You can hit me up
Then she went for dr. William Brown who is present
You dodge the blow
Miss Duncan without the slightest warning dashed out into the street had an attack of Hysteria and began
What are bursae undergarment
She clutched the railings
Scream scream
Her husband tried to pacifier it was useless
I leave the reader to visualize the scene
17 Stone woman
Lock to the railing screaming at the top of her voice
Collected
And the police arrived
The medical men with us explained the position in preventative
Prophetic an ambulance
We got back into the laboratory
To be x-rayed
In reply Dr William Brown turn to mr. Duncan and ask him to turn out his pocket
He refused and would not allow us to search up
There's no question that is why potassium the cheesecloth in the
However they gave us another
Control
Piece of Tower Plaza one of the pier
Of half-a-dozen man each of the pair of scissors waiting for the word was amusing
It came and we all jump
One of the doctors got a hold of the stuff insecurities
The medium screamed in the rest of us and the rest of the telepathy
This time it wasn't
They proved to be paper soaked in egg white
And fold it into a flight into
Could anything be more infantile been a group of grown men
Wasting time money and energy on the antics of the email crook
So that's a little
That's a little rude
Admin
It's a very rude unnecessary but I was going to say when you said 17
Also it did help
Though that he called her fat because I was like 17 Stone is that a lot or is that a little
These measures what's the BMI on Stone
Hubris
And the fact that immediately they knew that like oh yeah
Some sort in order to
To cover for your like passing office
The evidence
So excuse me ma'am we have
Seems light of hand before Soca
Could you
Could you not yeah that one simple to call
T31 prices Report with
Was issued whereupon
I miss Mary
McKinley
Came forward
Choose Miss Duncan personal made at the time of the seances
And she made a statutory declaration before commissioner votes
That you used to purchase
For Miss Duncan
She had to wash off before essay on
She also swore on oath that mr. Duncan on the night of the scene at the National Laboratory
That is why I said quote Pastor role of butter mucilin
To handle when they were alone
So that's confirmed her maid making a statement
I can't
Like without this being a visual show
I can't stress enough how comical
Pictures of her
Because there's just a length of cheesecloth coming out
Like the pictures but that guy duet The Flash Photography they are just like those cheesecloth coming out of her mouth
How's that lead up
To like a big puppet
Crazy how easy it was the clown people disappear 70 years ago at 81 years old
Yeah
Because a lot of
This is so heartless
For the most part you're just a scam
Doable people out of money for the seances
She was mostly left alone through most
That gossip
Better Business that you laid out about the HMS bar
Like that's that's really where she like
You stepped out of line even that she went to prison for less than a year
That's more of the government's fault than anybody else I don't I don't disagree with that at all
There was a research study done on how like keeping us
Secret and every person that you add with knowledge of that secret it like
Geometrically become more and more likely that the
Going to get out if you have the family members of 8
100 people
It's going to get out there's no
No way it doesn't get out I can't remember who it was exactly
It's not really relevant to the bigger story
But researchers who dug into did Vines
Specific examples of
People who
Admitted that they told you
We're just
Guessing the people talked about it before with me public
It's not guessing
Information got out realize that I wasn't
Let's say you're the mother of one of the sailors
Family members
Maybe the secondary relaying the information doesn't have a part about it
Lendup
To substantiate that
Into the ghost sailor
I was
She had like a p
Piece of one of their hats
HMS Barham
The ships just at HMS
Years old like soldiers current uniform
In further like
More likely
So anyway
I mean she's a
Just cheesecloth of course you can make a
Killer fraud woman in Lake
The 20s 30s
Pretty bad mouth
You know what it's like when they played baseball in the twenties the fastest fastball was like 70 miles an hour
Drew
Throwing 70-mile she's throwing meatballs now but if she was f****** blowing
She did not allow black soap most likely like American baseball
Speaking of bigotry
Resigned
Came into the world
Spirit
I'm a video
But I found
Really
Down the rabbit hole
David is coming
The three Bells
Before was much more like
You like lizards
About some stuff I've said that before like so much TV
But as we go along
I do think
That the things that I would like
Are so minimal compared to the bigger issues that we sort of look at
And the fact that like David Icke things
The protocols of the Elders of Zion is real
I think that I was remiss a little bit
That's not fair
One who woke up Paul Joseph Watson
He's the guy who woke up this dude can we not use that
Nobody should be allowed to talk about the Matrix
I'm calling a moratorium
We can use the red pill analogy
They were in The Matrix
Which is the least crazy
Simulation Theory
I can find the specifics on this way I feel like I can only relay this as like
Secondhand dish
I can't
Spend all my time digging through all sorts of Messi
Boards but I did find a number of in
Sentences of
People quoting
Ben Jones
Message boards
Denying the hall a
Talk about
And like the gas Chambers were gas Chambers
Why wouldn't you
Inasmuch as
It follows
David Icke
Having beliefs
But I don't want to say it specifically cuz I can't find the original
Reposting
Of things that
You said to have posted
Because might be real
Yeah but not enough that I can be like
I know you deny the Holocaust
It would work in a Civil Trial not a criminal trial
I ate so much that I'm not saying I agree with everything
Line
Is touch the same thing that
Republicans do to like distance themselves from people that they totally off
They sat on
But it's like
Nazi running for congress in Illinois like Nazi
Republicans are like well I don't agree with everything you said isn't even like
Everything says
But
Do that sorta thing where you're like
I don't believe in everything he says which allows the brain
To be like you do believe
Explicitly tell me what you do
Include
The global deniability
Weak ship
Very very lame
We heard at the beginning of this episode Carrie
Was saying that
Who's involved the bond novel
Corsage
You might
Think after listen
This clip that
This is a house built on a foundation of sand
Around 4
Ian Fleming James Bond
Oh
It was Fleming
Who was involved basically in the D-Day
Organization
So you already said there's no evidence
To Vapor say but their circumstances
Connect to it
This next clip says more
That's not good
I don't know the name of this book I cannot read it
No I don't know the title of his book and I have it ready
Riddle book
Football books
Universal knowledge
Actually is working on it right now
I want to watch that thing
Describes it as a stream-of-consciousness at 1
Filled with lies about a liar about a conference and who you're just taking it
Sweet face value
The Bible
This lady I absolutely haven't.
Holden compulsion
There's no doubt about it
It's not but there's some reasons to be
Vicious
About the circumstances
She was punished by the law cuz she said
No
Cuz the influence
Fleming
And put that aside
But it's so not important to the bigger picture of thing
There's the reason
Be suspicious
I'm get to them here in the next question
Yeah
Yeah that is
Which is really strange
If I were a judge
I would be like
How dare you
You want to do a seance in court how about you go fuc yourself
Is not that easy
No place in court for a seance
The opposite of a seance
She could get in
Trick
And now know existed
The other reason you run into
Two issues that you
You open up a can of worms
Allow a whole lot of
Yeah
Going to be like other half
Maybe
What the judge
Is setting the precedent
That sounds were real
And then
.
Admissible in court for Alta
Witchcraft law from the 1700s can be used to convict her now
Then so could seances be used to
When
It's like I don't I don't think there's any chance
Nightmare scenario where
She gets off and the Seance
The situation where you could call ghost
Also that was at the eclipse started right after he went in
Be quiet
I got that is an option
Improving the cheese at Giant
There's an interesting
Schism
What's going on on this episode
And it's very
Because
So
Ben believes
About Winston Churchill
Kari he believes the Ian Fleming
Behind all day
Terry believes that Ian Fleming is behind it but he was reporting to win
Austin Churchill
Directly
And so
Didn't know about the letter
To the prosecutors asking why what's going on with it
Yeah.
Baccano
She knows
The Churchill was involved with you but I have to say
In terms of my understanding is that Ian Fleming
Recorded Church
And that that they were trying to hide D-Day and D-Day Trisha wasn't charged
And
JB it's a very old book
I don't know
I highly recommend it if you have it
Cuz it it really does reveal at Fleming's involvement
Very deeply involved
In D-Day
OPG
Nice abbreviation
Operation
Facebook
Has roundly
It's all you have to give her points for knowing and having red
It's almost clear
The publisher added a note to its
Readers
To make their own judge
That's about what they believe
This book is a thrilling story from a remarkable man
Cool
Say the same thing about everything Larry Nichols
Absolutely basically the underlying
Story of it has to do with the idea that Martin bormann
Did not die in Berlin in April 9th
It was carried out to
Flip and tell the British where all the
Because Martin bormann was involved in the
Cuz of that the right
Replaced it with a look-alike who has been killed
Kind of hurt by an exclamation of borman's body
Cuomo
Djb wood plane has to be a look alike
Martin bormann
Until I hear from him
So now the new story is that that investigation and exclamation is a white watch
Because it can't
You can't give up
You can't just give up believe in reality
It is that thing where you get trapped in a sort of logic
Leave something
For no reason
Because it's something you just want to believe in you
Then whenever counter-evidence comes to
Do you eat zoezi
Blackout
F*** you man
You made the other leap literally every time I
All kinds of
It is actually
Coming out of her but it's like you know if you have a gun
Without a bullet
Swap in order for it to come out as ectoplasm
Okay alright
Sure
Only comes from
This would be a way that they couldn't reach cogently argued that very clear evidence that the ship
They're talkin about is fake or not
Ignore the idea that like
Well she was proven to be
Beacon person on a number of occasions
You start asking yourself questions and eventually you're going to find an answer and you like it
Paper mache mask on Willow
Become a ghost
Become cheesecloth so
New red pill
We're not using red pill anymore we're saying they became chief
So
D
Isaac
Everything is pretty
But they're going off on
I mean you know Ian Fleming was involved
Intelligence
He's Able he's able to write
Bond so detailed and reportedly
Homophobic
Most of the villains
With p**** Glory I'm not going to lie to you I don't know if anybody
That name lot of bees
So I think there's a little bit of a
Fitness
To the evidence so far
That means all
And it wasn't that bad
Terry mentioning that book gets him to be like
Well maybe that's true which shows the depth of these people's conviction
This is exactly like whenever she f****** let the other guys like Alyssa
She's going to try and do that.
Because
She's got to pull into her bag of tricks
And pull out what I'm
Literally her only source
To say that the sort of
Photonic
The Nazis
Many other things that we're going on during those times
Of course I have other evidence
I've got a witness. Captain Mark Richards
To I interview I in prison
My right ear is his name
Yes.
Vayase have gone to the prison and interviewed him actually eight-time
Which of these me I would Trump's you knowing his wife
Assholes
So that means there might be one coming soon
Oh yeah
India
Of a Numark Richards episode
Well she's trying to bring up Mark Richard
She brings up a new
Piece of information that I
True
She has family that were in Britain and
Pacifica
The Dutchman
Hell yeah
What you might say to a cult that he has a boy was going to parties on Churchill
And there was a heavy duty this is not widely known
As part of his work
Revealing.
Churchill and
Members at that time
So Winston Churchill died in 90
Went to parties
With
Winston Churchill
If
I don't remember how old Mark Richards
B-58
Hi to be alive
Yeah I think that's possible
He might be over 50
Which means he's going to parties
Churchill's estate when Churchill is a year from death
I don't know about that
Is Google's market
Churchill
You don't think
Winston Churchill
And the Dutchman
Him from Winston Churchill when he died
So what he remembers
Is actually
And idyllic
With his real father
Jason Churchill whom we all remember as a grape
And then the Dutch
Stolen
I just
It's possible situation all over
To figure out Mark Richards
Sage here which is chopped
Or the conviction
Right and he was supposed to be like what 20 20 something in 1980
Tough for him to a party as a kid
Believe that
Because if we point that out
He is at
Traveler
This is bulletproof logic
Also like if he party with you know
Winston Churchill with his dad
When he was a wee lad
Why was he running like a tire shop
When he committed that murder why was he
Ended up cover
For his time traveling and off-world
If he if Minerva
Was
The only way that you can hide a sentient spacecraft
Is if you run it cuz then people
Spacecraft
Coming in and out of their true
Beyond credit
For me to accept
Space Program
Going on with offworld mission
Is that the Dutch
Save the world
We need to drop
I find it almost impossible
But that person would organize a murder for like five grand
It's very difficult for me to believe
But someone who is that
To the world
I would be in that kind of financial strain
He was framed and
Brain
That one carries a big guy
We know that
She tosses Marc rich
Just wants to impress these people and let them know.
Slouch
Yeah she knows Mark Richard
Personally
I really don't understand any of that
Any of this world at all
It's just on that we're even that guys like
Yes I know his wife
No you should know
He's on the circuit doing these weird like awake and aware conferences The Very Organized
Because these people
Is not good enough
If you just have a web show like Kerry Cassidy makes a lot of money from Project Camelot
Other people don't make much
On their shrimp
Come together and
People
That's annoying
Autograph
Except for at least wrestlers did something real
Bike which I mean
Perform fake stuff
More tragic
Figures generally them
Nissan people because
Right
So you see them now washed up and down on their luck and maybe
The pillows
Probably a lot like Margaret
Drug trade
In prison
Compel
He was on
Speed and shake when he went in and maybe like
His brain just hasn't regulated
You know he's like an addict without a drug
Is addiction is Manifest by lying to
Sicario
Resources
Next clip she accidentally brings up
Another one
Helen
Which they are very similar
This guy is someone who I
Terry's interviewed of a bunch
The time I brought him up
If someone mentioned
In the
Brought up
I've been putting off doing the full episode about him
Cuz he is like
I would describe him as the big boss
Almost the big boss Mark Richards
Is not difficult
To get to the bottom of
But like we know that
There's records
The rocky was really
The time of the murder and all this
It's not that hard to get around and his stuff
Fun
He's talking about
Spacecraft wrap for chocolate Superfund
This guy
Sean David Morton
Is
So
Hardcore of a con man
He's not as fun but there's no Raptors that there is
There are aliens
And stuff like that but it's not as Whimsical and not as fun
So every time I've sat down to try it
Do an episode about him
Very hard
Because like I have to
So much b*******
In terms of
This is
Very difficult
Some of that will discuss the other end of this clip
Pretty f******
Okay well there is another aspect
That I I do look at
Which has to do with Sean David Morton I know this is going to sound extraordinary but
Sean David Morton
Chicken has been proving this for many many years
And of course very public person and he got thrown in jail supposedly
For overstepping certain
Associate
Somebody that
And I was actually involved in
A group that and I lost money
But I didn't blame Sean because I know sort of the machinations what happened behind the scenes
And so on
But I have to say that there were people that did and I'm not sure whether that
Contributed to his theme
Things run in prison
But I do know that he's writing a book
That is just closing
Drew who was running
Area 51 who was running the scene here on planet Earth in terms of the Ichie
Situation and so on and that this this man is Story Goes that
There's a whistleblower who
Padgett lawyer give all his materials
Please turn this into fiction
No and don't reveal Who I Really Am
Sean wrote these three books called Sansa
Airtight airtight
Whistleblower right now
Has been thrown in jail
Fascinating about all that is is is the link up with what happened to Helen
Yes they are both
Fraud
Ran afoul
Fraud laws
Sean David Morton
Kerry Cassidy
According to her partner Bill Ryan
Carrie lost about a hundred
$16,000
Amazing
A major chunk of her mother's inheritance
Which helps support our living expenses in the start-up of Camelot
And I also lost 25
Not a penny has ever been returned
It's a story that
Not been told
Carrie likes
What he did was
Run afoul of some investment
Applause
That's not the full story
Hear this from an article about them
Hermosa Beach residence
We're taking into custody yesterday after being indicted by a Federal grand jury on a host of charges related
Scheme
To defraud the Internal Revenue Service
Which included passing
Bogus checks
Cinnabons
Themselves and others
Perfect
To the superseding indictment
Income tax
For the years 2005 and
M2010
It's not millions of dollars in refunds
Melissa Morton allegedly filed several false tax
The indictments
Specifically alleges that Sean David Morton file default 2006
Income tax return
Requested
A refund of
9920 $1
Wow met in 2012 he filed the documents
Minnesota tax
Refund of
634 dollars
For 2000
In relation to
The scheme dream big man
I love it in relation to the indictment alleges that Sean David Morton on multiple occasions
And submitted to the IRS document
She called quote coupon for set off settlement enclosure
Any amounts
5286860 $7 + 8 million 400
$29,000
Fictitious financial instruments were purported Bond exchange for the refund
They sought from the IRS Accord
The indictment
Sean David Morton
Can you get away with this
Cuz he claims he's quoting not a 14th Amendment status
Is all Sovereign citizenship
They believe that the federal government doesn't have jurisdiction of doubt
Until he was certain
Going court and be like yeah I did that
I'm just trying to get my money back that the government
Sovereign Silver
Believe that
Tyler gold
Are we are we are
Just say the right word
And file the right document government
To give you that money that they have an
That's for all of us are
Human person right or corporate
Just say the right things the government like
Have to give you the gold
Jesus
Do an elaborate Financial
Claims this
I assume sort of like reason why he did it
Sea-Monkeys not a criminal
He's actually
The truth
I knew he'd get in trouble
This is all this is over
Is he still in prison
How long does it take for a while
Wonder if you have to go interview him in prison
Piece of gold that he wishes the government had given
Absolutely
So
This is an interesting thing we had
Has 116,000 f****** dollars
At least give up on
That guy
You can still believe in everything else but let that
Kygo
Yeah
Description of how they lost
The money
Claims that it wasn't
Wrongdoing by Sean
David Morton
It was negligence on his part that led to them losing all that money
The story that is
Not
Telling but
At the same time
How to talk yourself into not blaming
You f******
You look into
To the other X
Auricular is that he was up to
Oh
This guy is not a guy who's Act
Is a person who is
Operating
Very illegal
But psychic
So now
Mark Richards
Where Sean David Morton who's also in prison
Both of them both very credible
Now
This
Revelation
From Ben
But this thought
Prison for a walk prison but
This part is something that he should
To do a little more examination
Phone situation
Somehow end up in jail
It's generally fraud because I was a murder
Probably committed
We're all comment why do we keep ending up in prison
To do the next step on this almost like lying to people and then taking their money
To be involved
Sure deregulation of liars
If you want to make. Org
That's more
Next track
Good this is Pizza Hut
It depends on what class you were in
Regulator
This is the pathetic angle
Do not
You know like
The better question
It's like the government is really again
What's the topics that we cover
Why was
Parks in elected office
Why why is he not in prison
I'm sure she would make the argument
Popular I'm too famous for them to take me down
That's where things like I live in public and that's why they can't get me
She has been
Prison if their narrative was true yet
Specific people who go to prison
Million-dollar
Cuz he filed the paperwork he would be a hero b
Write a book about aliens
Pretend your whistle
Blower
No one cares
Defraud millions of dollars for the government
We're going to start tearing
What they are not connecting
Which is a bummer for the
Please answer if their narratives are true
Is not that they are too
Popular
It's the exact
No one's listening only going like they're only going after the people
Who are players in the game
Which means you guys
Nothing Terry Cassidy probably more
Notable in this world than Sean
If you know that world
He's a major player in
Conspiracy
Where he went on the boat.
Do recommend everyone watching the video of him dancing on the boat
AutoTrader
Excuse about doctor arrested by federal
Hilarious
Psycho
So good
So earlier you were
Suggesting
Influence the narrative
She did with Eddie page
The cock of the alien world
Everything
Yeah he allowed carry to walk him down a path
What is narrative
And
You know what
I don't I don't know if we just missed her doing that in the
With other gas
But she does
Whenever she's
Whenever we're doing a mark Richards episode
Now that's why I
We find out she's the evil mastermind behind all of this s*** that's why we suspected that she
Sweden microchip
Episode
It might have been the first steps
Super soldier
Space Traveler.
Notice it more but I didn't
Terry was leaving
In full control of a narrative
Is soft
Now it's interesting what happens here with this Ben Jones
Character
Tries that
And it doesn't really work
You can see
Benz
Sing
I'm in Cary
Wheatley take it
Try and mold it in
She wants it to be
I am we'll see what happens
No Inn in your case
Maybe I misunderstood when you were
Talking about
In in the documentary but I got the impression that you actually
Not to pursue the story
By other p
In your life like at the time when you were thinking about
Pursuing it or something
Not true
Somebody
This is something
Chicken bowls
Responsible
Exactly what someone might have said to me when I started this
I don't know Dan
Someone threatened
You're warning me
Maybe
He has a job you notice Porter
So I don't know what that means
We have a surprise
We had a
Custodian dishwasher for NASA
Recently show up on Keurig
Hospital Porter
Which is
Variable what a porter could
It could be a nurse's assistant
It could be a nurse's assistant or it could be
It could be anywhere either Realm
Hospital
So he's just a guy who works at the hospital and he's
Got a night game
Write to another orderly at the hospital
Nothing like that
I don't know
Seems like
But here's what he responds to that very benign
Threatened I was born
It is it is to me
Because it's so interesting
Interest me because it's so many years later
That they wouldn't want to reveal this
Which of course makes me all the more interest
She's already trained
What he is
There's already moved the goalposts
Within like
Because again the parallels to our time
Answer the way they also stigmatized
Conspiracy theorist
So now she's trying to argue that Sean David Morton
Because of
Parallels with
When she's lying about the story and lying about what happened when Ben decided which is why
She had him
The first most
As being there trying to class
That person is being crazy
They've actually
Timcast
Apparently on some of us and found out that we have higher
People out there.
You know kind
Allay any soda
Skepticism
Now
Allow for this kind of
Perception
Certainly not mediumship question is very important
Aspect
Screws but in terms of
Your own
Sort of trajectory
So you were warned
Slightly embarrassed way against
Doing this but you continue to pursue it
People search
So he's not budging.
Already coming a little bit
Layoffs in business
I don't know how much I like the evil mastermind
I'm not
Know whatever she was just so but willing to believe everything
And now this is Alex's an idiot
White nationalism
Yeah so once you see the real picture of the
People the face drops
You start to get abs
The games are playing
More sinister
Patrolling the
Meredith
We like to imagine
She's not a reporter
She's writing a book in real time
I'm forcing other weirdos
100-percent that's the perfect metaphor
So
I didn't even hear about this earlier
But
Did Helen Duncan
Granddaughter
Was going to call in
The medium
Jersey
That would be way better for her granddaughter away for her granddaughter to call it
Still with Bruce at to me
But
So
Helen
Duncan
H2h
Cheesecloth madam
Oh yeah
Her granddaughter calls in
And this is not
This show
But boy howdy
This
Is wild
We are going to start
How to connect
That could not possibly be a mansion so here he is just a beginning
The granddaughter calling in
Her name is Maggie
Because
Makes me think
Colin Hay song
Straight Talk
Hi Maggie how are you
Yes you're on on on the show hear your voices
Hi magazine
I guess I can't watch
If you try to watch
It's Justice probably better if you don't but you can watch later
I like
See how you did
What am I to do
Memory are again
She has nothing to say you just
I'm starting to
Some feedback people are liking whenever I start talking music
I feel like I should talk a little more about Maggie
Great song
Makes me tear up Alright Alright song
Look this is not a Dan reviews music
Alright
This dude has
Talk stoop
To her granddaughter
Of course
So
That's why we're good I just didn't know I thought it was thought it was going to be
Call the
Obviously that's a stupid
Did not cross my mind the only family
Remember or any person involved
In contact with
So
Tell you what
That's not the only
On the show
I don't know how to set up this clip
It's one of the weirdest things I've ever
It is a long clip but Mike down
Weird
This Is War
Here
This is
This is insane backstory
Question
No we had
Veal at the end of this clip
That is unbelievable
A couple of things
That are
Deeply problematic
It also makes it also makes
The story of Helen dump
Still much more robot doesn't want to go there okay
And I would just want it I was just saying that that could you
Explain how you got
Reconnected with Eddie page was because you're still in touch with your grandmother is that right
Alright
Research my grandmother
My grandmother
I got to come in real quick
The argument that people have is that
King was killed
Because the p
Police raided one
Promise
Rock-a-Doodle
She's not doing it again on the low
She's calling people in a
Rum and so the argument goes.
Because she was interrupted in
In the middle of a train
When she was getting ectoplasm out
Debbie ectoplasm
Burned her
Bennett College
Like exactly ended up dying
Months later because of it
Perfect this is horseshit
Choosy as we already noted that that
Review of 1%
Unhealthy woman it was the 20s
History of heart
More like being interrupted
Interfere with someone in the middle of vomiting up
Cheesecloth
Epic card
So I stayed away from this
Nothing
My grandmother
I don't believe that
Egyptian gods
Found it
Appleton Museum
My grandmother
Grandmother
Cheese Apple
While she also a racist
Baby
Responsible for
Responsible for some reason
Can you believe this
His backstory
He's amazingly
Helen Duncan
This crazy con woman fraud from the 20s
Speed Run 4
Ends up accidentally running into any page
The two of them together AV crazy together and then
She ends up
Hooking up Kerry Cassidy with Eddie
Resulting in the episodes we went over it
Big old racist alien
Then comes on
Deer in the episode about Helen Duncan and review
She's an idiot
It's crazy
So happy
You cannot do better
Of all the crazy things that I know could have happened
Because there's no end of the possibilities
Who is The Bluest of the Blue Sky Thinking that would never have shown up
Of course the granddaughter of a con woman is also a plea 80
Exactly
I mean
There's no way to know when it started in the bar
10 or 11 inexistent no no no no no there's a bunch of
But not his brothers
Sisters
I call him my brother
Cuz they're both
Suggested maybe she's one of the
From his 10 or 11.
Even according to Eddie there's more pleiadian
Adjust those alive
Or whatever
Okay
So
First first class
How do you spend 30 years researching Helen Duncan
Even an hour to look at you like
Refuse to
That's better anyway amount of research necessary
Only looking for research that prove she's a real
It's going to take 30 years to get anything
You're going to run to
Weird-ass document
After you've encouraged a racist to call himself a
Pleiadians
And then
No cuz then you know what happened
You know what happen
She was
Holy s*** you're pleiadian to
Yes exactly what happened
Corner
You limp noodle open
He's weak as f*** so then he calls her and she's crazy
She's somehow also been conned by your dead grandmother
Gross so far three and they're all on this
You might just be a gifted opportunity
Getting reception already I thought it was really funny
As I listen to it
They are
So incredulous
And just alike
Despite all evidence to the contrary they believe they believe in this magical
Towards the end
And I heard that I was like
That's amazing
In our world
Wonder
Under so much about
You know I don't believe I don't necessarily believe that there's something magical about
Like really weird
But he wasn't like some sort of conference
He's pretty weird
Does any page does have videos of himself
I'm back in like the nineties and hypnotic regression
He's been around for awhile
Just enough
Evidence
From the
Sarah is not really used yet
And of the granddaughter of a famous con woman
Would end up meeting each other in
England
They should be married
There's no doubt the worst
Children
Be so dumb
Biggest Liars joke
It's awesome
Here's the movie Pitch
We find out
That the granddaughter of let's go with matahari
Alright
Granddaughter of Mata Hari
Falls in love
With the grandson
Of Ian Fleming
It turns out that both of them
Are simultaneous
Police spying on
Each other
No I think I just wrote mr.
We could remake that soak up a lot of celebrities who are really hot to get together
True lover intellectual property
Great intellectual
Much like
Hey you want to make mr. and mrs. Smith together
We might be sitting here and saying like
Told her that she's
Two-player games
But unfortunately it's not
There's proof
Right
Alright
One we're talking about Helen Duncan
Not you
Man it's awesome
This is like
I
I love the way
You listened to this show
Of this Project Camelot episode
You just hear stray names and not really know so much but
Because we've started covering a bunch.
There's so much Robux
What's going on
Each other up
No
We all know we're lying
We're not going to call each other on this fair and very
Clearly
Themes
That is
Oh it's
Houses on iron
Alright because Iron Man popularized the Marvel Universe
This is all Iron Man's fault
I'm going to believe Iron Man for this
DC Project Camelot
Yeah but I don't care
Free dating
Yeah but they haven't
Cinematic
That's what I'm talkin about
Right that's exactly right
I did not even consider it I also get a month
Perhaps
Superman
I love the snow
I love this
No steak
Sing about
Unfortunately found a couple of likes fairly heavy
Episodes
Jim Bakker like with
So that's not even much of a regret
Necessarily from the world but like
Getting a
Getting a juicy episode of Project Camelot
Sweetest apple
It's been just such a delight there's no steak
It's just a walk in the park laughing at weirdos
Did braces until proven otherwise have implications of her facilitating
So that's it.
If you're prepping up racist
Then you at the very least sympathize with
In a way that's condemned
Find no evidence from this episode the papers
That like Howland
No evidence
In Fleming was even
McKay's
No evidence
Churchill
She had any real gift that worked
Is a hand or weird
Conn's like throwing soda
All this stuff is
This awesome remnant
The past not to discount
I'm pulling it off
Put on her
That's worthy of a documentary freezing I agree with you I think
I don't know man
Cuz I
Really high
Cunning
That sort of thing
Cunning I would say
More than any
I think you hunting and creativity
I always
Cleverness is kind of a part of
Yeah I think it's a form of
It's a lawgiver like
She's haifeng
Live like that
I dyed my hair
I am living the life
Entire
Work
Is dedicated to laugh
So it's difficult for me to be like
Just because it was a woman in the 90
T29
It doesn't really work
For me as much as I want
You know beat Super into like
Elevating class
Piano classes
Group
Because Italy
Broad
You know what I don't know
What I want to know
Is a
Detailed list of her client
Because if she's Robin Hood and if she's only defrosting a no
Ladies I'm fine with that but if she's a regular
Michigan
I'm pretty positive
From everything I looked into
Very normal
I want I want the Robinhood
That's what I want I want her to go around to like
Kerry Cassidy it's like wow
Buffalo State
You one good turn deserves
You losing $113,000
Bitter fruit
That's why that's how it works
I don't know if we come away with any larger
If you like the show please do check out our website
Absolutely
If you're if you like have like
Art
On Facebook
But if you like knowledge fight
Please just
Join the group
I don't know how to say this without being really blunt about it
But like
The ways Facebook work
If I post
Something to the group
30 of our fans will see
Or something like that unless
I pay them
To promote
In the group
Everyone sees
It works just
Separately the way things go
Tribute distributor
In the group
People sleeping
So if you actually want to keep up with the show
The group go home and tell your mother you're broiling
Our Facebook page
Is largely inactive
Inert
Cuz it bums me out
Really hard
When
No one sees any of the ships
Just never post anything on there
It's kind of a dead
The group
Where all the apps
Convey
It is a private group but if you request
To join
Just lucky
And that's a message
Although you're still under suspension so give me a shout
Moderator
Okay if you want to email the message.
And all of this s*** like
10 million f****** journalist
The first time a couple times but that's well no one gives a s***
So many
So many no answers like even when I was
Even I was trying to
We're not in
0 notes from
And I was talking about with this
Burrows came over the other night
He'd left in the
House
He was asking how things are going but no one cares
Absolutely recent messages
People in it
It makes sense
This is a crazy
There's no reason
Could we actually looking
Eagle on it
Cover I email indirect message
Cover Alex
To be like
Man these guys are probably crazy probably weirdos
Differing of
Philosophy more by this to end like
Whenever I used to try and get published as a as a writer whenever I was like 1920 and I was sending out
All of the short story
At least I will get a rejection letter
Yeah yeah
Bother all the people that I've messaged
Enough for them
Just send me know and then I'll feel good
Where's about them
Please feel free not to harass them
Send a message to crazy
DIY
Okay
Richard supporting the show
Did I feel very
Turn about it like
Like the emotion
Sensation
Of it is like
When I used to run comedy shows and I send out press releases
Whatever
Whatever I didn't get a response
This is like the event page of Metro mixer Joe the reader
Every goddamn comedy shows probably sending them
Boilerplate trash
Respond
It feels different now because
I know it's probably not
Springfield purse
It feels like they say
I think we're crazy
Bethany is such a bummer like
Like engaged
The tiny bit with what
Like what we're trying to bring to the table
Do you like no we're not
People who think that
He works for Israel
Go down the dump
Chris Brown help
You know it's actually is
Consider that an
I always thought I'd like it legit
Responding because
They're not interested
It never occurred to me that they're not responding because anybody who message them about Alex Jones
Of course they're not responding it's absolute nevermind I congratulate
Listen to everybody who has not responded
You have learned your lesson well unfortunately you missed the boat
Some other thought but
Some people have pointed out that Kelly
Alex's ex-wife
Has been on
A bunch of shows lately
Stuttering John podcast
That's not what I'm talkin
Implications of like
She's been on a lot of shows
You come on yours
No
I want to be clear without saying anything
Specific or anything
She would have come on our show
Good for either
We never were really in
Like a close contact
But
I know for sure she would have come on our show
And I'd I made an executive decision that
It wasn't good
It wasn't good for her.
The cheese trying to achieve I would never talk.
Yeah, Moto
Open
I think we got a
If you're out there
Get me home
No reason that we can think of nevermind
See if you can find out
Jordan has been a lot of fun this has been a lot of
Does your turn
Amman
Well they're Army Heroes
It's on you
I would say to the guy who
Cruise
Yeah but I'm really hoping that he's going to
Put that second cruise together and call it be
I do like that name
We laughed I don't want I don't want to ruin that possibility if he hears about this
You not going to take my idea to make
Make a mediumship
Offended that I don't
Super large
Forget the result
What's up where the middle
Surf
Man I'm going to go with you know what
I think the True Villain always comes back
Yourself Mark Mark rich
Whatever Raptors
Alexandra Thurston color