Alexandra Thurston color
They celebrate National
Sponsored post on Twitter
Is National IPA day if you're an alcoholic like
Turn off
Start gas do we do
Too long we've been doing that.
Frankly since I've completely blacked out
What is the show about and why am I here
You're here because you
Knowledgeable
Because you startle easily
You are yours
The audience surrogate for audience
Climate change
I'm here because I spend way too much time looking in
Into an
Researching
Swimming in the pond that is conservative
Propaganda
That sounds like a really interests
The reviews are in though no one wants to review it too long
I assume that's life
Interesting show straight up
MC skat Kat
Ooo
Episode
It's going to be
Okay
But
Hopefully good
But I am not into this episode that I listen to today I am not into it I did not enjoy it
I love
Peterborough
Dude these people are mediocre
RV Colbert coming out I think we're going to be alright tonight
Okay
We have a lot of people that you're really not that excited about we have built
A
Everybody likes
You don't want to exercise bikes
Cuz I think this gentleman is also
From Sweden
Based on the fact that his last name includes the windows OS with a dash through it
Vianney
Number of languages that aren't necessarily
American English
Very excited also because a message that included
You don't need to respond to
If people tend to respond
Just let him know that there's no pressure
That could that could help things
No pressure
I appreciate
Thank you so much Chris
I'm a policy wonk
If you like sports and go to our website and click the button
Appreciate it
That they can donate not on a monthly basis and I understand that's not
People would
Maybe
Payment is kind of
The commitments
It is something that maybe you forgot was going to be on your bank statement and if you're like us if you forget something
Sometimes you're going to get an overdraft sometimes it can be trouble if you are exact Camp there
Now you can.
Please to send us a message
Or I posted it in our Facebook
I don't want to put it on the show cuz
Private
Email
Jordan today we're going to be going over the August 1st 2018 episode of The Alex Jones
Show
In reality
Bears in present-day the world because Alex's
He's going to court this week
Love people talk
I'm not supposed to know anything
That there's like
A boy that family
He they're going to get them
Trials beginning
If I understand correctly that the earlier this week he had
Emotion
To get this thing out of court
High hearing
Sick of going to work out
Did the lawyers
I read a bunch of articles about this and from what I can tell the lawyer's argument
Boil down to
But you remember
When he was last on trial
It's great that we're talking about a guy where Alex Jones
The last time he had
To present himself as
A performance artist in order
To have
He's on air ramp
Not be admissible in
In his child custody
I'm just joker nobody important
For his lawyers to draw that line
Because if he's not playing a character in that really is him on air
Relevant
Are
It's who he had to walk that really fine line of like I'm performing but
Incredibly fine line
In order to not alienate his audience
But at the same time not put them in the hopper where
His videos can be played in court
Would not go well for a Ryobi table saw
The new struggle in the new line.
But he's having to walk or his lawyers are is really
And it is
I think we're
Still act
For his audiences
Right
No reasonable person would believe that he's telling
Alright well then you do want him to play
Videos in court
Yeah that would help their case
Screaming nuts
Boyer's debunker
One of the issues
That is one of the main parts of the Sandy Hook families
Argument
Things like that lady
Partner
Because
She watched it
To be a crisis actor
You get them off the hook
For influencing her
Who is the crazy one
She's crazy cuz she believed
But if you make that argument
Then
You're leaving until like oh
No one should believe anything
Really fine line
And I think that's fascinating
Sing because
What
These cases
Intentional
Going to build up a body of
Weird lines had to walk in court
We already know that he has to walk the line
Performance in reality
Then then other case that
It's pending I believe this one also had a
At some point this week
Is the guy who was Miss identified at the park
Alex
That one is Alex
Reporters
Are being sued
Because they miss
I represented this guy
He had like an ant
Antifa shirt on or like a communism shirt
I told that use that
The triumph conflate
This guy with the air
Actual Nikolas Cruz
And
Do due diligence
Any journalistic outfit would have done it
Reverse image
Search that
And find out
It's not the same guy never report
Well
We accurately reported on something that was posted on 4chan
Which is not journalistic due
Which means that they are the ones who are at fault and in fact we were not reporting on the
Parkland shooter on the reporting by
Fortune
Really troubling possibility
I think it's a really good point
And if that's accept
Any Infowars reporter could anonymously
We post something on 4chan
Thursday
Self creating mechanism you
You've established here if you allow that's
So what
Probably
I have to walk there is like a my really a journalist at all
Do I do I have
The protections of Journalism or am I just
The dick hole yelling
Is there any reason
Time for me to
Have to follow
Blake basic standards
Of what journalists
The next
He's going to have to
Jump over with his his lawyers
I don't know how do I get my quick-and-dirty episode
We can't be an Alex Jones podcast and not sort of diving
This a little
So I'm sorry
No no reasonable person would believe
Which protects him from the consequences
That no reasonable person
Would believe what he's saying because the people who believe what he saying are unreasonable and therefore are going to make
Any excuse to
Continue believing what he say
Start of an Ouroboros
And that's because the truth
Is unreasonable
Is it like he had to give up apologies
Hamdi ulukaya Bellefonte PA
The post
Videos of him
Apologizing
Like I never
Imply
Right
They're looking for out of
But I don't think at the end
I really don't
See how this is going to really negatively affected with a
The people who are already on board
Right because what you said
They're on reason
Exactly
Who knows
Alex Jones listeners
As Witnesses and just started asking him questions
Oh man anybody that no reasonable person would listen to
I don't know what that damn it I running
You established in court that he doesn't
Have any
Responsibility because
No reasonable person would believe him
Then where does that leave
That leaves him free to say anything you want
That's not good
I don't know I don't know how it's going to play out but
That was just defeated
Against
Against them
Mia kind of like a
Clearer idea of where this
Everybody's like yeah we agree they f***** you over but surprise
Nothing that the justice system
The justice system is inherently incapable of
Injustice
Situation and that's the real nightmare is Alex Jones goes to court
Against Sandy Hook families and somehow
Yep I in the wrong you know
You never want to open up that
Possibility as like
This is a potential outcome of that
Because then
Right
I could brag
Is if we were ever to be soon
Our defense lawyers with
No unreasonable person would listen to
Continue to call for violence
However
Because our show is so inherently they would all reject it
Well that I'm not going to actually wish violence on somebody
So we're a listener
Murder Jeff Bezos in his home and
Look at how reasonable our listeners are
Even if even is Alex Jones
Indian parody I know like this August 1st 2018
Context drop
And Trump is about saying you're powerful you're beautiful you're an overcomer you're amazing
That's so christ-like I mean
My my gut
My gut.
Trump is christ-like
I think it's more like
You better
Another one
Then you got to
From the critic
Keys Auto Care I Love It
It's great show
On August 1st
This is rough
Beginning of the Alex's episode
Spock
News
The concerted effort
The characters that's name
Job
And I will see where it goes
The morning Show's viciously lie about me
For 10 minutes this morning America's Newsroom
I guess the young ladies on the program
Are just absolutely living on their own planet
What I said
Actually never
What I do it
They just sit there and regurgitate the same anti-free speech
Garbage
The issue here is
In
Some days
Saturday
He believes
The Sandy Hook
Was real which is all good and well
Fight what he doesn't do is ever say I did say it was fake
You never said that and what people take issue with
The damage that was done
Cuz of his actions
In the past
They're not saying
Keeps saying it's fake
Although
He did for a really long time and just because he says no one ever plays click I wonder if we're going to play the Clippers
Also was Oregon a false flag
About there's a
There's one there's a definite to cool cool cool
The other issue is that clip that I take
Very very serious issue
The way he presented as like
I've apologized
But what he doesn't say is I apologize for what I did you said I apologize for the media lies about
Written that down I just written down for the media Rippy misrepresenting
Like in that video that he put out trying
To reach out to these it was all about I'm sorry that immediate hurt you
With lie about
So manipulative
So evil it sits next
And I don't
Sure
I think it's great
That he no longer gets on air and says no kids died
I think that's
Wonderful
Not good that it's a
The end result of
You should probably started there
Possibly
But it's really
It's just a Bomberman it's a real serious bomber that he refuses
To own up to
Except
What he was
Porto's
That's it
That's the conversation
The people are mad about
And the fact that he won't
Like it would hurt him
Not at all
To come on air and any of the times
He's done his fake apology
I'm just say
We f***** up
We talked up
You know we thought
We thought we saw something that we didn't see
We thought Anderson Cooper's nose disappear because of
The green screen
Compression error
It's only in one version
The video it doesn't happen in high-res versions
We we found that stuff out
Everything
East Mississippi
Cuz we thought Rob uncle
Saying that he said was investigating Sandy Hook and how we
Thinks it's a cover-up
I'll just look we f***** up
People suck up from time to time
We're sorry
Will do better in the future
That's all he ever would have had to say
No one would sue him
Be in the clear
I bet he could say that now and make this all go away
If you want
I don't
I don't understand I don't understand why you go and all that s***
I still don't
Slice it there
I don't understand what
People can't just accept like on that one
He's not a guy
It is it is a fundamental issue with
Hubris
It cannot be defeated by the person experiencing
Yeah the whole point of only used for people who can help
Definitely into their
Like it's it's what's going to happen
It's fascinating
Buddy's on his own petard
She's really
Try every channel including Fox News with Bill hemmer
Is up there just spewing
Total absolute lies about me
Never showing eclipse
Never showing in proof of what
Telltale sign for you
The fake
Outrage
Without low-res copy
Shaking camera
Illustration of how these drawers work
So
Conversation
Use a synthetic
Completely
What actors
In my view manufacture I couldn't believe it at first
Just shows how far
That they clearly
Used
The even ended up
Photos of kids killed in mass shootings
The sky is now the limit
Pieces
The b*******
Spitting go ahead
So
He's really comfortable with
That's outside the statute of limitation
That was in January of 2015
You know you can't be punished
So
Denying that he
He said any of these things
He's going to play fine
Lucky only be used
Current
Of him saying
Disrespect the lawsuit that was your big deal is that the issue is
There's a statute of limitations on this
Until all the good stuff
They can't use what they can
But they can't use it the way the
It should be they can but only if the court establishes that is
Statements
That fall within the statute of limitation
Illustrate
To say it was
They still can't beat like you can't
Looking for that clip
To establish a pattern
And I
I mean it's just
It's just b*******
I mean
You know that you said that Alex
Over and over again
It's not
This is
What's the price
Steve pieczenik
Steve pieczenik has been on his show
Alex is probably like been threatened
I don't know look
Imallexx
Steve pieczenik
The dog house
So are the hurricane has
So that was excessive but I just wanted to
Well Alex
Complaining that other people don't play clip
I don't show these things
I know that we played those clip before
But
In case you haven't heard those episodes
We do that is why
He will never f*** with that
Because he can't use that argument
Anyway a lot of
This episode is him talking about Google being
Evil
Fair enough
Knock knock
Too much issue with that
But here is the clip that goes
Into some weird places
Is after he
Is complaining
Google
Shut up by
Supposedly
Today
So that was from the video that got taken down from YouTube they want about
Write an article in the daily.
They said that that you would attack
Children
That wasn't about
The video of the guy who attacks
They make it clear that he is a
Attacking these
Trans children
And they don't say that he's physically attacking them or beating them up
He is attacking
He is
Coming at kids
Pretty hard
In Alex
If they were saying what you were saying
Eli's
Yeah yeah yeah
That's all strawman
I can go ahead and do it sir but I don't think it's smart
Because they'll just keep me
Profile
Trump on Alex Jones
And fully aware of the
Okay
Excessive perhaps
The First Amendment
VIP
Consult with CIA agents about whether or not people are going to use Alex Jones against
Trump in election
No f****** s*** yard
What is there is somebody who's worse than Trump
I guess maybe not worse
But like
Surprisingly worse than Alex Jones by a lark
Relative terms
Power I mean like
Just as a human being do I agree
Worse
Absolutely a little bit
Media-savvy
Things that are negative
About him into positive somehow just deciding
He's just going to
Remove all media but his own
This is like kind of
Angry
Combative
Whenever things are not going
Miraculously it seemed to work but he doesn't win
Somehow it's push
Is this weird
Unsatisfying
Like at the poker table would you like
You both have H Jack
Sike you thought you were going to win hundreds of dollars on a hand then all of a sudden
That's what it is
He's taking these gambles and screaming about how everyone's coming after him
Then he ends up in court and has to do an apology
And then
It's just
Deflation over over
Oh my God this is going to blow up
It's going to be crazy
Just us slowed
Of the balloon no tension release
So disappointing
Yeah
Do you know what that's a
It's the one he said though it has kind of made me
View something a little bit
He is not
What is he doing
What is he doing when he saying that if Trump needs to throw him under the bus
Then he's fine
Like like just
Did he believe his own bulshit on this
If I were to get into his head.
Which is sort of what I have been doing
In this whole time
I think what he's doing is trying to show off
A little bit I am such a loyal person throw me under the bus I understand
Performative
Because
F*** yeah I never have to throw that guy under the bus right
Yeah addicted
Yes
The short answer
He does believe his own bulshit
Yeah but that's not the
That's not I'm good I mean that's not like that I'm the last
They're trying to take me down
It's like
Subservient in a way that I don't find acceptable from Alex
Can I don't
Where is
What this is why I hate modern days because Alex
Is
Tail between his legs
I will say there is a moment is coming up where
Alex chose a tiny bit of backbone
But it goes away
Pretty quickly
Pretty funny
It's one of the few things
Oh Nelly
About to
Google
How they're helping
China
Read The Intercept
Play Google
He's like Okay so
China's doing all this
Evil stuff
And Google is helping
And then everybody's
Response is there a private company they can
Can do what they want
Extrapolate from there in a rather unfortunate way
There's a response
Google wants to go over to China
Buddhism
K w
You scum
Quotes
Another word quote
Did not say that Alex has Hitler can do whatever so we can report on that
The news
Has not replied for comment at time of pressing so we can't be sure
How to f****** up that metaphor
Because perfect
Big time also he f***** up the metaphor the simile because what it would be is like Okay so
Google is
In China who are doing horrible thing
It doesn't make Hitler the
The company equation
I'm people
Who helped the Nazis like George Bush
Is Dad
These people who helped the Nazis
Should
Reflect
What's Google as opposed to Heather itself
So it's almost like
Be being an English teacher
People mess up live
The f****** act
Or fail either of those they're just
Relative benchmark
Okay fair enough
But if you do want to say that is metaphor
And you start talkin about government as
Contractors
That is essentially what the weather supposed to be like
The UN OSHA
Good-by and instead it is acting as a private contractor
At this point in time cuz they're not really cuz they're what they're not even for-profit now.
To for-profit companies
Between private companies and B
Acting as a private contractor and their act
Illegally
Or are perhaps
Hatefully or you no propping up
God I don't I don't know how many regimes like Saudi Arabia founding weapons
That they're sending it to use in the fight against Yamin
And you could say that
Capitalism
To disregard human life and instead to f****** maximize profits over every goddamn thing out
So Alex
Why we should abolish the one thing that he says is the best
Ding ding ding
He's really dumb
Also pretty dumb
Churchill
At least 30 million people by their own parents
And then another
40 million
David Rockefeller
Rockefeller
Editorial praising mouth
What images
Why are you
Preachers in the first page
So go to Google
Don't click images
Duty version of it
So you google David Rockefeller like Alex's bike
The article
We know this is right
Coverage
You Google it it's the first thing that
F****** comes up
Drama China Traveler
It's the number one response on Google Express
Oh my God there's so many other versions of it that has been posted here on and then also a bunch of really
Weird
Was that
Good Auto
Obituaries
All publicity is good publicity
Also Alex said that it was when mad died he wrote that that article was written in 1970
3 MI.
Patty I know I know I know
So this might be a little patio in a sex with Alex tracer
Does he use crisis actors to demonstrate how different
No no it's it's
Kind of smells after I have watched his transformation
Weather forecast that anomaly
I believe that the shooting happen
Pictures later
It's been misrepresented what I've done
Lawsuits
I said
But
Michelle shocked
Prozac head
Who is Alex Jones
Quotes
You get your recycle
The anti-gun tragedy
Over in the media
I just like referring back to the clip we just play Tori said they were all actors
Pile of s***
Proving that nobody died
Who is convinced
Complete
Time
F*** you sincerely from that clip it is like
Think about how
He later said that it didn't happen
Which is fairly accurate
He did come around to that eventually
Maybe because
Getting too hot
That's not the
The issue as you pretend
Never did
That is the issue
If you just deal with it
Reality
You don't have
Have to lie
That's all that
Oh
Infuriating
You know what I
Consider this
If
Trump
Came out
And just was like
I didn't know it was happening
Talking to my family
I just found out that it was
Then you know what I'm saying
Sincerely sorry about that that was never my intention to collude with the Russians
As for these people who did it without my
Knowledge and said that like publicly and
Sincerely
In Alex's case there's no one but
Jim self
Like
Has the finger pointed at them from his admission if Trump were to say that he would be
He throwing his family under the Bucks
Doesn't act
Do you like any of those
Why don't they
Sure but that doesn't matter like
That would be an admission would work again
These other people that could events
Swept and be like
He's lying
Do you Game of Thrones term
2 Benz
The truth that's all he has to do he just has to be like
I know that I said these things
I f***** up
That's all you have to do
There's no
I don't want him to go to prison
I don't want him to
I don't want to kick I don't want any of that stuff
Come correct
I want him to be right with the con
Cuz you can still lie and defraud people and not
Like lust like this time in our Project Camelot episode
The problem is that you like we were just talking about
You can front
Pullback
Icarus these people fly to
I know you can't agree
Prison that's white Mark Richards
In prison
Greed
Right
I mean I think there's a cautionary tale for all these
Con man
Is this as old as time
If they studied
Pantheon of Western culture
They could probably help them out with that
You know it's almost like those were some sort of like
Tale about morality
And
Should user not you
Sort of like
Is trying to teach you
It's very weird
So I'm going to skip somebody clips
Because I think we've
Pretty much beat
The dead horse of Alex
Self-defense
It's about the Sandy Hook shooting
Like he doesn't say anything all that like
Because he knows he's in court
Gino's
So he's just doing this like
One word at a
Quotes to make it look like I said something that I didn't know one has any clips of me blah blah blah blah
It's kind of boring
Let's get let's get past that getting to
Just some juice
So you're complaining about being in
A couple years back
I was going to bring that up
He went to Davos right
Can you play Uno with Trump
Is weirdo ding dong
Going to Advocate the role of
World leader
Will help out
That was his orders take pickups
The slack and try and help with world
Has a very different idea.
Don't even
I don't want you to be part of
That's fair
But
That's not that's not where Alex is
Coming from
Because he's going out to break
I would say
This boy is
Shook
That was a sting to the end of that
You guys
Essentially Alex Jones's now
We need you to attack house
If they were otherwise will fire you
If they were to attack Alex Jones legitimately the only position
He's like
Plagiarism
Yeah exactly it would have to be some sort of like xfr
Porto's
They could attack him on Merritt
Hey what's up
Quit being racist over there that's my job
We've claimed
Very weird
Are the people that you want the Westin
Trampoline
Alex you're very full of
Displacement
Fears and anxieties about what
Carlson is now
Done possibly a better job cuz he does
Yell all the time
More palatable space for your race
Have been
He shaved
True
He doesn't have a weight did Alex
No no
You know once you shave doesn't grow back
I'm kind of character I liked
Play improv games
She said it real quick
Anyway so we move along this next clip Alex
Coming back from break after that
He had some words
About
What's
Islamic
NFL games
Just reminders whatever.
Problems with that I think
Itemized
The first coming at the end of their life
Yeah yeah
Protective
Children
Bet that is absolutely it just a standard
Legal
And journalistic integrity you absolutely Under Wraps prices
Let one
He's golfing about the idea of like protecting childrenswear
Something's privacy
Second
US law
He's in England
I don't know why you brought that up, you ask
It doesn't means that you have First Amendment
Next week
Issue
US law brexit issue is the prison without a hearing
Because he had a suspended sentence from another time he was harassing a bunch of Muslims and the judge was like
Do this again we're going to put you in prison
We're going to let you off this time
But you haven't
You don't need hearing at that point
That's basically you broken
Control
You will go to prison until you getting another pyramid on that
You have waived your right to not be
Put into a cell
Fourth Amendment
Fair enough
My fourth problem is the idea that
He wasn't covering this. I mean I guess I agree with that
He was Rebel Rouser
Witches
Much like that Logan Robertson
How many gets video of it
He was doing the single version of throwing a brick at somebody window
You're the victim whenever they're mad at you
Do something like that
But even okay we're going to f*** with
People I meant pretend that we weren't
So it's still ridiculous like
Those are my four issues I think you beat down three of them but one stand
Not much I can do about that
16th Amendment
What about the booze
Does 18
So
Little bit of bulshit little
Nonsense
Mostly
You talked about China
Not
Any subs
He does
Did The Intercept bring up Greenwald about
Specifics of things you just talked about like
Of course I already knew.
Now has control of the entire cloud
Please bring me a
Sims that are pressing it
From
More reputable sources than him
He's trying to combine
He's passed narratives in
Newer fresh
He spends a lot of time on it and then
Screaming about the falun gong
And fair enough but why don't you ever talk about the rohingya like why
Where do you draw the line what's the what's the issue like where is political expedience
Care about Alex White
Roanoke
Buddhist
Via the following Kong folk or not necessary
Reason at this is just a throwaway
A lot
It's because of yet
Because the Rancho
You hate China and so he's right
Some victimized group in China get
Precedence over
Some Muslims were being
Slaughtered
In a country that he doesn't
A little bit
Your response iPhone to be
Much more direct adapt and I would say better than mine
Which way is your response was like
I need Kanye
That will be Google but will Center everything on its own
And
And then you said
Yeah course they are and I was like
Why would I ever consider that
Remember the true version
What Alex about germs
Bobby Clarke
The real version of that is that they've given the Chinese
Clarky's Overture
Exactly
Credible
Could be used by the government
The fact that people came out were like this is a really messed-up thing for them
Believe anytime I hear something like this
Incredible back in
Intuit
Yeah no s*** Google wants to control outfit that
I don't think that means that they're going to
Who is this
Version of it in China in order to
To get it back
No I don't think that's reasonable
Unify the world
You just get some dragon
All of the rest of the world I've been
Brushing backup
Oh yeah
So that's what
What's great about that is that just hit
Tonight China is that
Just today
An eighty-year-old
Not activist but like
F****** critic
Unfortunately
Make it 280 died of hearts
Did 74
Books became president in 2016
Where are the bears that sing for joy
Critic reference
84 year old 8-year old 8-year old was giving an interview to
And was literally
Arrested
During the middle of the interview
Like they actually went to his place and f****** place him under house arrest
His last words
To the interviewer like
Hey I'm allowed to do this right and then it was cut off
That's that's the situation that were talking about
Google's
Search results like it is it is absolutely immoral and
Insane for them to ask
Do this but why would we expect anything else
Why in God's name would you expect
A massive Corporation
That is global that has no allegiance to Any Nation or anything like that
And is purely about making profit which is what it is
Supposed to do
Why would we ever imagined
There is no
Where morality
Your stock
Yeah
Why would any business really care all that much about
I did my best my best goes like I don't order anything from
Like I don't want Jeff Bezos to have another f****** die
Like that made
Means anything
More to the point what you're saying is like because of the better thing is
They're real dirt. They're real problems
Regina
And the way they behave
And stuff like that in terms of human
Freedom in terms of
The kind of world we would like everyone to be allowed to live in
And it doesn't do service to them when Alex lies about
Because the serious issue was under
Haircut by the
But he's like
He's just bullshiting
And screaming in order to make
Make himself LOL
A truth-teller or whatever
Get out and if that's a thing
It's going to play out in a played-out over
This park
History
Like Alex Jones does a disservice
Real serious issues by
He pretends he's on the right side of it and lucky
Against
Kathy loves Liberty sure but that conversation
Be much better served by people who
Have nuanced thoughts about it
Don't scream all the time
Don't yell this is World War for America is under attack
Your that's or what was
Don't worry about it
Probably Cold War I don't know
There's a secret word
I don't want to know
I don't know what he fixes
I kind of know but I can't really
What is the general
The themes World War
It ended with Trump
It's like saying that word
Found a top 10 war broke out again
I was I was Arbitrage
Eloquent
People who are
Crazy make the point that you could argue that something like
Cold War weather World War
That we just weren't
Actively
Is there where the surrogate War
Make that argument Fairplay to
We're not in World War 4
Hopefully we will be soon
Fingers crossed
It's because of this
What the globalist
Bet
Ion
Islam
Just because of demographic
People get mad for that something that's now
Demographically they have
Decided to make the smoke it's just beeping. We've been sold out
Commercial
Relationship
Yeah
I thought it was I thought it was reverse missionary
That's a bad that's bad for the weekend
Panama Canal gave him that Canal looking for
Like all of this stuff
We we already talked about in the past episode the idea that they run all the University
Chinese
It's very sketchy on a lot of University
Not the Run
The universe
Implanted running it
What's going on
If you look at the truth of that situation
I wish I apologize
In front of me
We went over it before
Oh yeah this is
Weird
The reason that universities accepted is because they don't have robust Chinese
Language program
Until they accept offers them for free service to the school and they get hooked
Into this possibly the
You know they also have ROTC programs
Nobody wants
To join the f****** military but
You know they're going to give us some f****** fun maybe we should have
Better funded maybe we wouldn't have this issue Alex
If we had
Public University
Since you are the most paid Evan public servants in this
Football coaches places like that
Wild
Anytime he says demographic
And then we
Most racist thing
Demographically
We've been sold out
Dodo
Yep
No
Chinese people in Americans are akimbo
Because that's a very terrible
Compatible
Something very
Lauren Towers
If you talk about the four quadrants is that is that it Colorado New Mexico
Guitar equipment
Call Giuseppe's
White
White people
Break chill out relax for a moment
Take a drink from the hose as it was at football practice
Taking me white people
This is actually really fast
I think there's another answer
This later not the exact same thing
Fascinating thing that Alex does
Rhetorically
He's describing what
People do
These claims beyond the
The business end of it
But in the clip he's asked
Actually doing the thing he's accusing other people of doing
This is this is remarkable like I listen to the sound like
Set high-level Jedi f****** Judah right there
Even knows he's doing it
Oh you don't think you knows I do it muscle memory
That just either
Shut off everybody
Praising
Suck off everybody
Warriors
They're just mercenary follower coward what they're destroying
Universities in Hollywood
America's Best
Teacher five-year-olds
Execute you
See see what he did there this pretty amazing that's a good gymnastic maneuver that he pulled that was
Astonishing
Kill people
Every Muslim is a terrorist
They're just trying to demonize there anyway you can just take what he said in that quick
They hate the mother and father living
You're demonizing your enemy as we speak and then blaming other people for demonizing their enemy
War
Now we're going to get into Newsradio what is it good for
What is a good for I don't know when the super karate monkey death car comes to my house
Absolutely nothing
Response there supposed to be
Say it again
Or a game
Also going with
Saint but I did
I'm so
Pedophilia in Hollywood
Great Bridge jump on you here in the middle of the episode
But Alex
He knows that he's got a
You do not talk too much about his lawsuits and what have you got to do
What he does best
Which is sensationalized
Real-world issues
I didn't doing so he ends up bringing on a guest that I think
Delete to another lawsuit I don't I don't think
I don't see any way around like I don't think this is like I don't think what he does at the end of this episode is legal in any way
Like I know he
You keep practicing it by saying that like I don't know if I should have gone I don't know if I should let him say that
She is like at least
Mizuno being like
Might be really bad I don't know what the definition of hubris is or whether or not I am flying to close
Frank
Like isn't it double jeopardy where you can only be sued one time
Like you only get one lawsuit against you and your entire life
We get into it here and then even the topic for a bit and then get back to
This is where I kind of start
Do you want to brag a bit about his in-depth knowledge
Hollywood
You got a screw
And
Hollywood
Yeah let's party so cool
Germany
I want to get out of here for the kids
Rustico
K
And then
What
What restaurants are here
You don't know
The back room of the restaurant is very clearly
To puke like anybody who listens to his show and believes his world
The backroom
Birthday parties
Stuff like that there was something
The backroom restaurant
Well he may not be talkin about that that is what is evoked
In the mind of the listener
Now what he's describing their as a Hollywood A-list party that he's been to that story three times on this episode
Does not give any more details than what you just said there and I would argue
More accurately represents
Planes that that one dude and drop run
Cofc
Guy wanting Alex
Leave a party
If I have to play Occam's razor games
I'm going to save it no one is going to go to Alex and be like
Hey there's going to be some kids showing up at this party
Unless they want him to leave cuz he's bombing everybody out of the f****** party
Everybody have a good time
Building 7
We got to get him out of
Right so and we can't confront him
Turn your head to the ground
Rabbit turn off
Because that Goblin mode
Heatwave
Then he's not called about drugs on this episode
Golden Goblet
He watches a lot of movies for somebody who hates all the
Yeah yeah for sure
Lord of the Rings
Goblins
Until you're in a coma
Analog of
The dwarves they live underground in
Mountains in Bell
Goblin Hobgoblin
They're generally just considered like
Weirder people
This weather got the hob
Exactly
VIP Auto Care
This line
I'm sorry I'm sorry that I don't really have a lot of fun
Another episode
That's better that clip is foreshadowing
For things to come
Possibly run spray of the law
Yeah
Play a little bit more self-defense
Recently we didn't cover the song episode
You know it's all you can find it on right wing watch
Media Matters all them covered
Alex
And I did some finger
I was threatening Robert Mueller a little bit
If you really care about that go back to the clip that we posted where Larry Nichols a literally threatened to blackmail him
Exactly literal illegal
Just use metaphors
He's got a he's got to talk about that a little bit
But he's got a
Explain himself
Ends up doing
It's crazy
This is so weird
Cuz he takes you inside
His mind
Who's doing when he said those things I would like to know what he's doing is very
Very weird
Finish criticism Tucker Carlson hours cuz they said well Allison perfect the one that's out of context
Get oh my God the stuff you know
One thing
Belmar
He's a blowhard douche
You give him a little bit of a path
Not not that he deserves much of one literally
Write using an attempt
Cuz he's
Anyway
Like it would be like if you had your your cernovich
Right-wing blow up every go through
There's a reason we never talked about like Nick DiPaolo on the show
Or something like that
Yeah you can meet
There's a lot of not a number of like right-wing leaning
Comedians is no reason to ever like look at what they're doing that
Cuz most of the time they're trying to be funny and they say things that are f****** awful
Do you know that there's an attempt at humor there
The same way that like
I don't like Bill Maher I don't think anyone I know who's on the left
Likes Bill Maher
He's a s******* yeah but he's
Trying to be funny llama
Islamophobic master
Problem
You know
Did the statements he makes about wanting depopulation so there's less traffic
That's just a hockey joke
Populate the world
If you take that literally
It's a month
20 years ago
Different delivery
Politically
There's a reason that it might want to
What's a victim first
The worst
Ignore survive
It's not good because
He would turn into a victim strong
Really want to kill him
To kill him
It's not worth it for me
But the other thing is the reason that is brain comes up with victim
Before
Is because that's what he
Teacher
He cherishes his victim status
Artificial
That's why he's mine
He doesn't
Offensive offensive
Spontaneous
At first sight
Passaic trials breaking Constitution
So crazy
Express
13 year old
XX Islands
Witsec
Witsec sheets
Got a sexy
The Iron Sheik
Say that five times fast
I prefer sex boat
A great song by a rapper friend of mine named
Remember that were Fred Smoot
Define confirm
That's crazy
Music
He's pretending that in his head what I did is I made up this bit on the spot although I had
X wrote the blinds for the battle rap ahead of time I came up with it
It's fun that he's trying to deconstruct his mental process
Which I think is ludicrous
Clearly lying about what people are
Complain
He gets to the meat of it
Which is
My story got out
Because I yelled about all that stuff
They covered it
Because of that
And so whatever fictitious narrative I was trying to push got so much more traction because you all covered it
And why should why does anybody speaking care
Right that's why the president f****** said I hope Second Amendment
People take care of Hillary
It's the same s*** he threatened violence
Why would anybody give a s*** now it's Alex Jones
Yeah why didn't you give a s*** of Alex Jones
The president f****** doesn't on a daily basis
Sarah Huckabee Sanders wouldn't even say that the Press wasn't the enemy of the
Free world or whatever
Gives a s***
Kids giving up their games
His violent rhetoric or all of that other b******* I give up the item on pissed off
But the fact that he throws around exactly what you just said
Because of that
They gave me more coverage
He's allowed to say exactly why
And nobody's covering that but he says the ship
I wish people I wish the people with larger platforms with people who are
Supposed to be the public
Watch Dogs would understand a little bit better
Cookie
Great know it's like anybody
Kind of two loose-lipped will ever like just say I
I mean does it all the time if you just pay attention instead of just going through
Like the
The Chosen clip outrage
You stepped into my trap
Yeah I don't know yet we did cuz the other options
Do a we do
And right when watching me matter that way more traction
Tristan that now
I mean I think it would be interesting to see an article
Alex Jones
Explains right-wing media whatever it is I want as long as I make a stew
Stupid dumb thread and then people paid
I only have
X amount of
Can go on
Name two putting out the thing that I want
To put out which is Robert Mueller
Was involved with the Lolita Express in Jeffrey Epstein
People have sex with kids
Yep you accidentally. Accidentally
Put that message out into the world
Through your coverage of his sensation
No fake stuff which is
I'm going to have a political Showdown with them
In terms of like the times that he breaks down
And I actually think that there is
This might be a tiny bit
True
On and on his own like that he's doing that intentionally
And part of it is saving
Cuz I don't think if you watch
Like a times that
Said that he was doing this
In the past a lot of times you can just be like
Outer unhinge
His face is not thinking at all
Like almost spitting from his mouth in
Red
So I don't think
Uno
This possibility is much better actor than
I don't know
Play I don't know if he's a much better actor
I think you're good
Stanislavski
He went to
Victim instead of murder for a reason
Is relevant
Next clip
Most
Most persecuted radio / TV Transmission in the world friends
Vitalize by friends
So I mean all you hear there is coming back from break and wearing your faults victimhood like a bag
The idea that people supposedly lie about it but active
Thinks he's persecuted
Is what gives
Invalidity in his own mind
And what he projects on to the mind of his listeners
Idea of claiming the space of victimhood
So f****** important
Without ever
You know really
Playing that
Hard
In his world
It's so weak to be a victim
That you can never be like where the victim of all this stuff
But you have to say everything but
The only way it works for
You're the victim
Simply because everybody else is
So weak
Everybody else is so much weaker than you they feel like they have to like
Gang up on you
When you're even
Even then you're so much stronger than them you can survive being the victim
But only because you're such a
But there is a
Absolutely
Continue to exist
So earlier
We had that clip route to talk about the globalist
Islamic
Like how it's that sounds kind of races
Besides
To take it to the edge
Degree
In this next clip
Hibachi like
To go to get away from all the sectarian Wars and year of the rest of it
Megalodon
Handsome
Seems to me like there's a small chance
Might now want to get into traditionally white Protestant countries is that those countries
Centuries
Sweetly decimating and strip mining the other countries
Prophet
Maybe that's the reason
What countries are now in the position of being it in
More comfortable better
Then countries in sub-Saharan Africa and in South America
I don't know
Maybe
Is you know what was
Interesting to me is that the people who wanted most to get into white products
Really
Wanted to get in those countries
Is before the white
Took it away from them
You know like the Native Americans
The First Nation
Really wanted to get into that white Protestant country of North America
Independent man somebody stole it
It was weird just f****** murdered all of them and stole it and now somehow they're like
You only want it back
Because we stole it the first time Dan
You just triggered
Like a thought that I'm embarrassed
We have not brought up
What's up
Alex always talks about how the Muslims are so evil because of
The Crusades
And like them
Spilling into
To Europe in Conquest
Extensible Academy like 700
What happened with you
Western people coming to America
I don't know what you talk about
I've never really
Cuz I was too busy like
You're looking at you like
Nature of things in Europe around that time
Zeinab lines of demarcation everywhere
Every five years or so and they weren't really even
Lot of places were city-states that point
There's no real combined.
Like Italy or
And I never even put the pieces together of like
Best example of this
It was really but white people
Exact
Thank
But everyone wants to give away prizes
Can't take that away from our
Really wish history hadn't
Well history
It seems like his like in defiance of reality
Not true
For real like have we considered that we might be the only people that are
Not of this planet
No I mean physiologic
I don't know
Evil gland do we have
Is the pineal gland also Evil 4
See the problem the line that your walk
Now is that you're going to end up a demon
Before too long
Territory is Alex
People need to be banished from this Earth until
And then maybe we'll find out it was good or a bad idea but I think you got a
Do stuff
First
It's better to ask forgiveness
From
People that you jettisoned into space
Senators asked for permission
You I would fit right in with that New York Times that lady
But the right-wing is all fake mad I go to bed
F****** piss your pants somewhere else degree diaper
Yoga Fest
Go home
There are no Heroes here
Home history
I only say this because they're fairly close to my lady
I do have to respect a group
Built around the idea
Just leaving
What's the most part and they're also built around the idea like the Amish and Mennonite my family come through released
From Mennonite
Andy
Anabaptist
Tradition
Their whole idea was that you don't baptize children
Because they don't have a choice in
Accepting Jesus or not
What disagree in Europe
In Western tradition
Because of the church
Adult baptism was illegal you had to baptize every baby
He died you know before they're in adults
Adult baptism
Yes absolutely
So at the time because they refused to baptize children
They were slaughtered and run out of countries and that's why
The that the Mennonites
The Amish
I ended up being
Victimized class
They were killed all over the place they became nomadic people throughout Europe
And a lot of them ended up coming to America and settling
There's a bunch of like hotbeds of
Amish men
Memories
My grandpa was actually a Mennonite
Preacher
Southern Cal
California City California
Fresno California
Before that
But
There's an interesting history to the
The anabaptist tradition
I did not I knew though I knew the history of the Pennsylvania Dutch and the lakebed
Did not know that the Baptist
Mennonite Church
Because they're mostly a bummer
Fans
Kind of we lived
Columbia Missouri which was a city
People don't believe me when I say that
Collegetown
Preemptively defensive
So there was like neighboring cities like little small towns
Community of all of those
Two Cities
In Columbia everyone would
Commute into Columbia
Like when I was younger
10:11 or so
We went to the
Mennonite Church
Bummer
Like all of the
This isn't his fault
And isn't even really necessarily Mennonite
But the preacher was in a wheelchair he's a quadriplegic
And he spoke through like a trach hole
Get a microphone at his trecole it was terrifying as a kid is just so awful
The kids at the first were so much more evolved than me
But I was supposed to be the city kid cuz I lived
Yeah f******
Like 12
Horrifying
For me in that situation growing up
So I always had a really negative feeling about Mennonite
And a baptism middle
This is a good if there is a version of Christianity that's a good
It's probably this one
They make great pies
Yeah
Child baptism is not
But also you should get re-baptized as an adult if you do
Uno with the world and personal capital
Personal choice
So there's such a
Emphasis on service
Within the Mennonites
And the Amish
Ideas like doing things for other people
Even if you're not praised for it is really important
Like as an adult
To like I wish I valued
Religious upbringing
Things that I had
More
During that
Because later we ended up going to like
Do that
Liquor store
Something In My Heart
And all this is just to say Alex is about to lie about the
Well that's nice I have no no
No sentimental feelings about
Any of my time in the church
Ever
Ever your cult was a little different.
Not even that just like even from when we were past
The Colts and we were in just like regular as churches
Sure well
My life's experience
Was
With the medal
Alex is going to talk about the Amish
And there are
Absolutely
The question whenever people
Amish with electricity
There's more flexibility in terms of you can wear button
Do the Amish
But they are allowed to wear like teal shirts
So that's better
Reformed Amish stuff is very Progressive
Colors
All this is to say that I don't know everything
About all of the
Whether it's Mennonite or Amish
I'm pretty acquainted with it
To know that Alex knows nothing
The Amish don't know I know
And they live longer
And they do not have autism
That is not true
Propaganda
Bulshit absolutely Community the Amish community all of them so they do largely live
Separate from
Urban center
There have been studies that have been done there is autism
The Amish community
There is vaccination done all this
Is
Cruel nonsense propaganda
Just trying to Bank off the idea of other
The other nest
The Amish
It's absolutely been debunked
Also why not
They live longer and everybody looks the same until they're like 95 and then they get real old real fast
Liberty spikes
Because they all right
And this one
This is bogus
They have some secret programs
I talked.
Dutch
Stud
Their daughters
Sheet between like Orthodox Jews
Everything
What's a lot of money
Had a nice time out
They're just so much to know
I'll tell you I'll tell you this
Knowledge is a dick
And you just want to learn and learn and learn and learn the truth
So there's a number of problems
Was this the first the first
Devout
I would not ever allow is out of marriage sex
To f*** their children in front of them
Who's the sheets
Do you know what this is
Comes from message board
This comes from Anonymous post on message boards Amish fiction
That has to do with the ideas
Different that world
Exactly
Is that like are believable enough
The people who know nothing
Record on a little bit in the internet world
The moment you said you know like Orthodox Jews
All right well that somebody who threw in a bulshit thing from what Orthodox Jews do and then
Just threw it in the
Creative
Movie ideas like a
Is it cuz there's two problem
What is if this daughter
The Amish her against
Premarital see
Secondarily is she is married their super against infidelity
How expensive is real is because of
Again what it comes back to you if is this other ring of other population
Well there's probably not many people choosing to become Amish
We must be
Completely isolated
Community and they must all be
F****** each other
At a certain point you're just going to be f****** your sisters and your brothers like all country Folk
The problem
Tons and tons
Separate communities around
The country a lot of
Fairly close together
Like the pain
Pennsylvania Dutch
It's not one
There's a right
So often people will.
Write your part of this community over here Community a
And often they will be a mixer with community be
And you'll meet someone and marry someone from
Community beat
I meant you'll have kids
I meant the kids
You have with someone
Community
Community C
It's not
Going to necessarily end up indirect
Inbreeding
Because it's not like
Community a b or c is just one family
It's not it's not nearly as small as Alex
This is all going to
New generation
It's going to be all inbred baby
It's not an emergency like that
Even if
Even if it was an emergency
Whose idea was it well let's hire a duck
Soldier to f*** our daughters
Problem solving skills
Something like a like a
Pennsylvania Dutch
Came from
If I remember correct
Joyce
Yeah exact
He's just using like the the
AAA colloquial
As I as an expansion about netherlanders issue is what I talked about
Driven all around Europe
There was a nomadic
Choose the people
To the extent that their Dutch or German isn't
The full picture
Right there is like a multi
Nationality
Lineage 2 that
Population is a religious thing
Country
People who get
Forest around
Wichita
Deaf
U.s. crafts
Gospel say that word Anasazi why I'll get it right
Ocusoft floating floors that most people don't think of slurred it's crazy
So
Just to put a fine button
Shout out to my
Miami Meadows out there
Amish
Or listen to this podcast
That's true but
This
Is one of those things
I'm driving this home so hard
Because I like I have a hangover
Yeah yeah
It's so offensive
As of how much
The narrative
Invalidate
What those people
There's no way they would choose this as an option
Because their faith to begin with
Secondarily
There's no way that this is true because it comes
Second message
That's such a
That's such a thing like we talked about
Times where it's like
Of course you assumed they would do that because you have no belief in your actual
So you're like
Well yeah why wouldn't they sell out everything that they believe I would do it
There's that piece
And then there's also the fetishization of the
The community you don't under
Very attractive
To do that is very hard to
Yourself from being like
I believe the weird thing about this group I see
And also you would watch a Dutch Soldier f*** Amish lady
Echoes reality shows
Came out there were like that
Amish Justice
Guy with a big stick
I would go round and like
Terrible reality show Within
In the Amish community
Give people f***** with them that they had Justin
Enforcer guide
And like
I was like
I watch that show like this.
F****** tree
True at all
So I asked my dad
Communities around
And he was like this is one of the most laughable
It's absolutely one of them
It's literally like believing
Rock of Love is how people die
Literally that level of stupid
Operating off that world
I'm not offended
But
Dates
Are you talking about
Rockets
Bret Michaels
The Rock of Love bus there's another right baby
Groupies
That's a good day
A little bit about pizzagate
He's supposed
Because
Admission
And thousands of emails about the kids
Talk about this episode
And it's the FBI code words for sex with kids
Talking about $65,000
He's completely editorializing on this hot
Email Victor he has turned into some
Something else
This is all bulshit he is
Caesar's rhythm
Budget
Spell prostate
He's not watching sports dinner 3 hours today
Okay
He's got
UShip
Can we break that down
What is
Start that
I want to tell the audience that when Alex said Obama's having sex with Tim do today
You didn't your face didn't change
Whatever
Very idea
A good sexual experience
I mean there's going to be diminishing returns cousin
Refractory.
The first time is
10 minutes
So let's let's
Pretend the each time it takes 3 minutes more
Orso okay
+ 13 + 16 right
Now let's imagine that you're doing all 10 at the same time
That's going to take even longer
Because each of those tend to
Attention
And you can't give attention
You know
This is Ludacris
Okay first stop
He's probably watching SportsCenter
You
I know your skills that is a man
Who can
Tom softendo
In a heartbeat
Please look at even in his presence
Are you with orgasmic rage
Tumi
Could not control yourself
The day that's different
Because
Cuz then
Look at it
There's no
Sock rag
There's no refractory.
You know what I'm saying that implies that his dick is involved
Nut 10 times
I'm saying that there are a few has
The aura mental powers
Lava lava
Power that we cannot
Imagine what's the pleasure
That's a good everything is about sex before
I've heard that from Janelle Monae
I just
Which is actually the worst lyrics
On her entire album
Computer is Phantom
Lyric anyway.
Continue
I know I have nothing
Continue with horse
Alright
This is what Media Matters and rightwingwatch decided to cover
So to give you some con
Yeah of like what
He's talking about and has talked about already
We have
People want
To get into white Protestant countries
We have
The one that has white Protestants stole from the people who want to get in there now
The demographic Lee chosen Chinese and Islam as their way to go us
It's almost like
Western countries.
Right
We also have Alex talkingshit on the office
Unnecessarily
Recover that you do a little dance on his face with that if you want that beef
A further thing that they could have covered if they wanted to is Alex
More popular
What this would be a great thing for them to cover
Likert scale
Yeah
Even bad what he does at everything
Anything in the world to do is go down to a boardwalk
A lot of different reasons
What's your name
That doesn't work anymore
Mafia or
Kill somebody
Italian mafia the same way
You got to make your bones
Sure but the Hollywood
Got to make your bone
13 year old girl that's the bare minimum
Roman Polanski standing ovation
What a good friend of mine is
Is casting age
Vision Center
Is very production companies involved
This is serious
Show
We work for losing weight
Yo
We are for Lucifer's so
Again
I don't believe it
If it's true I would assume
But it's someone sucking my dick
Set timer
Link in the game of telephone
Lake elines Alex
To embellish
Being like
You got to be a
Lucifer
That's more you being like
I don't want your
Mark
Mark we we like your show idea but I'm going to tell you this right now
And you listen
I like your
But I got to go up to my boss
And Lucy is Nautica
Huge fan of it
She's really nice
Lucy
That was
I don't know this is so stupid
I was trying to like
Play with
What might actually be talked about it's kind of like
What are we
The boy
We work for
I don't mind
It's right
Perhaps
The most
Silly thing
You could possibly present is
And then the second level up
Who wants Mark Dice
Gina
The literal
This guy has
Second
I want him
But you got to get them in the
Cool
So f****** stupid
Much like Alex is like lack of awareness and
Playing games
Accomplished
The same thing with
There's absolutely be
There's absolutely child exploitation rehab
We're not making fun of
And I'm the second piece of it is
The way that I went to Jones.
And talks about this
Real issue
Like Ronan Farrow is doing lessmore fez's
Screwing much more serious
Nuanced workthespace
Austin reality
A disservice to all of that
By bringing him so much
Bulshit
Image next clip
Alex brings up
About what's bad about being
Yeah it's really bad about it and his
I was like
I can't imagine someone coming up to people in a dressing room
Like maybe if they're underage girls at a beauty pageant I can't imagine what kind of idiot would take to walk in
Into a dressing room
And harass people I can't even imagine that no president would ever do that certainly
Have we considered close to Ralphie May
Remember he's dead
Nitin karagounis
Some friends of mine
Yeah
He came and did stand up
Open Columbia Missouri different like he had
So many different stories of like
He was ultimately the most mean and then
Currently the most generous
All the sudden he's been like
Entire life
Recipe for Elsie Mae
He did have some f******
Awful jokes
Work
From time to time that Club in Columbia Missouri with the name of it
They would have those like
Remember When
You were hosting at Zanies
You were
Is going to be a long video before this
Month from now
Coming in a month-and-a-half whatever
And then
Every time you coming
If you watch that video
So bad
The Joker
Videos talking about like how he named his daughter
April June May
Do you know what to say what your wife think about that name
Anderson
Achieve
Like
What is that a joke
What is that
Why is Devon the sizzling
That's going to get me to come to the show
You hear something like that you think I got to go see what the f*** is wrong with this guy
Yeah
And then he's out his opener
In the video like legitimately he comes to Stage the giant orange suit
I let y'all get
Used to this amount of orange on the stage
Hey
When we would do sex
Are sometimes like me and my friend
Things would be at on the
Show together
And I one time me and very funny
Not doing stand-up anymore but very funny
You can find it on the internet
He's a very very funny dude
Wendy's
Video Play-Doh
It's so goddamn
He got to go up first
No I'm going to stand here and let you
Get adjusted to the kamado Joe
Laughing my ass off
There's nothing better than a comedian wearing something
Crazy it is that he wore it
That crazy
I don't have any of those
I don't have any of those drugs
Because I
You only
Like you got to give it up to those guys for at least writing like eight new hours every year whatever the f*** it is like
I don't have any of those jokes
Anyway
Ralphie May is from Texas
Because ostentation
Okay Austin
I get it I get it but he's brilliant
We spent a lot of his time in LA
And we know that one thing from this next clip
That is what la
As a torturous route but I like it
I can't go
Even to LA to audition
That's what's up
Degrees it maybe had a tough time because how hard he was self-medicating when he was a
Wasted
$10,000
Addition
I bet it's a good cover for why you're not in any
Yeah we're good
In this audience
So now Jordan I've been teasing this a little bit because Montreal is on fire
Bingo does mentality
I've been teasing if there's a guest coming
You have no idea who this is
The name is said
You'll have no idea who this dude
Here's Alex
Turn off our survival Instinct Hollywood as her main weapon
I want to watch
You figure that one out
Whatever
They tried to induct
Isaac Kappy
Which I actually kind of suspect is Buzz Marketing for Super Mario Odyssey
Cuz the new character is Kathy
Who is ber
He is like a spirit and body is Mario
Throwing around
Is the new character
Did another
Number of reasons
That I don't I don't think this guy is sexier
The number of supporting roles
And somebody said that they didn't even get into
What Rosie's been in because he
He's been in so many
I don't want Tales out of school about what roles has been in
IMDb big blockbuster hits on the other side of this clip
Because I would rather let Isaac Kappy
Respond to Alex's allegation that he's a big movie star
An elected
Spell a few things you said
Not a big movie star
Movie star
Also I really would like to get a friend as I never threatened Paris and in fact I reached out to her yesterday we texted back and forth
I know you're a good person I don't want to bring you into this
They are trying to draw you in
Can use other people around and they don't care who they hurt
I just bring them in
Relevant
I'm just sitting here at your an established
Paris Hilton
Jack
Pencil lead
This guy
Where
It's being reported
You never know how like
Beer
Celebrity news
Because
This guy is
Is clearly on
And mentally ill
Yeah and the allegation that he
He choked her is much more serious than say
Paris Hilton
Aurora weird
Shirt at a bar
Gossip I was really originally I was
He's trying to find
Cuz my first I was like
Wait did he threaten the City of Paris
Entirely
I was going to I know people heard me say I was going to bomb Paris
Yes but I'm not going to like
Betty people come
Like
The globalist
The powers-that-be towels all over there
Alright
From Paris Jackson
He choked her at a party
I don't know if that's true
I
Going to guess based
Behavior that
I don't know I don't really
I don't have any skin in the game
Being a big movie star I do like his lack of ego about it cuz he's
He's been a couple big movies
He was an Ironman
Liquidator salvation
But his roles were like
Guy at store
A couple of movies
Short films that are on his I am
Baby resume
He's done
Not a whole lot
Working any
And like the last year and
2 years
Sure
You could always be extra extra in Marvel Cinematic Universe
Howard the Duck to you
Alright
Nautical or not
Got ugly
I love you
I love every
Alex has already entered in the introduction said that this guy was
Going to be inducted
Do this Titanic order
Is like a
Very large movie star witch Isaac
Send it like I'm I've been in some movies I'm not really a big star or anyting
I'm not going to I don't want to
I don't care I don't want to
Just want to let Isaac speak
Explain why he's on the
When did James Gunn stuff came up
Liars
Is it a pedophile
Is a pedophile he told me he was a pedophile okay
Call Stacy
Ripping apart our country and brainwashing
People
Legally actionable
Seth Green is a pedophile and he said
Cuz we're going to get into his explanation
The Key Arena
Refute
Even though he Kate like
Really
Caveat B like
I don't know
If it's a good idea to have this guy on the show
Beyond your program
Literally leave legally action
Legally actionable
Isaac Kappy
Now he's already said these things
In his livestream
Haha
Egos on periscope
He does some of that b*******
I'm and he said
Lipstick greens pedophile and all this over and over again
Steven Spielberg
He's doing all this stuff but
But if you keep track of it a lot of it is stuff
Weird Pizza
The gate dudes
I've already been making accusations about
Well it is only in the sense
Does noseff
He absolutely no Seth Green
Game nights with Seth Rogen
But then you have to also take
Consideration other things
He's accused the Rothschilds
The cannibalism
Rite Aid thinks that pizzagate is proven and documented
All right how are the other thing is like
What I was saying that I'm not sure if I believe
Gossip sites
But
You know
You can take take this for what you will
Based on
What he did
Need to Paris Jackson
She has had to
Because he knows where she lives
And he kept trying
Contact
If I mean I don't know if that's
Seems very plausible
The world
We
That we you like wait around in
You are pretty much guilty until you prove you're in
Maybe
Let's let him
Existed
Let's let's let's let Isaac
Cafe
Give his story
Before we judge too harsh
I know what's coming up and I think the schedule s*** huh
But you don't know that the audience doesn't know that I'm getting a little ahead of myself
Alex Jones Show I will believe whatever a woman said about you ever
You are coming from behind
Okay
Currently like
You know what it is
In the night it's the ninth inning
And you have to pitch
No wait
It doesn't work
Yeah I know
Is it the bottom then you get a chance to tie it up
Neuron neuron
Metaphor
Alright
You're a goblin
Yoruba
3 / X
Anyway let's my life campaign speakers be part of his story that is
So crazy
When did it get to the point
This this child showed up with a man and a woman
Maybe their parents
Maybe
Supremes friends came over with their kids and
Who is out of the country at the time
Call Mandy wants some blackmail honey they they want it they want to pin me down
No desire
Cool cool cool
It sounds like you do.
Where do creepy Warriors
Fairchild
Yeah I understand
15 year olds in
Just hanging out and playing board games
Beach with your family in the fifty-year-old stinks of beer
And you got scantily-clad girls
It is
What are you guys talking
What's happened
Drew Barrymore that part of the a thereunder
Cutting their own argument
Might be there and they have their lawyers there because their child
I don't know what Alex
15 year old
Who's at the party playing board games
With you and nothing happens
The cleaner undercuts V
Always suspicious of a fifteen-year-old
The party
The beginning are we talkin about a kid showing up with a dad
Conceivably yet lookastic looking for Seth Green when Steph Curry
Country
From being anything suspicious
Because if it was a child delivery
F****** know that he was out of the country
You don't risk that kind of thing
At least
At least send a text
Exactly
Maybe you don't want a paper trail right
Literally any sort of missive karaoke
What are you talkin
Why is your first thought
Okay
And screens out of the country
So obviously they're trying to get me to f*** a kid
That is the type of project of a man who really wants to book a kids
You're looking at it
Just someone who is
Either
Grossly opportunistic
And is trying to make a buck
Probably or is mentally ill and has
Insane delusions of paranoia possible
And I will give Alex from credit
Like I said I brought this up a couple times
He had misgivings about the idea of talking to
To the sky
Has misgivings
To him for at least having that
Kind of
Vino in
That's what we're honest
This could go really badly
Alex is trying to
Get him to
You know do the narrative
If you want to bring up Mark.
She is already
He's trying to leave in like I've been
Parties
Let's get the vague narrative together that I want right that's probably illegal
Picking might be able to sue you and then I've got to get to post he's other goddamn lost
Is what he's doing
He's hope
Yeah I think that's another thing that I think as we go along and
You will see a little bit of him
I'm trying to like
Write the story
Kind of like
Just tell me your goddamn it
Information
Like because I think even he heard that like
A kid showed up and there was a man and a woman is that green wasn't there
That's weak I think he thinks that's weak
Even for Alex this week
I think that Alex has been burned
In the past by people like
Yeah yeah yeah
How to film a video where he apologizes
Tell me your information hoodie do it is Robot Chicken
You dude
You do a little puppet
Come back into play
What's the data
Williams returned
Experience what you saw
What they say
Real quick
Alex asking for the information
Have you started weaving a weird Tale
The outro music play now.
Recap here before they went to
I was going to keep both clips
Just for context
Alakazam
Today
That's very close to ADESA
Set screen at his house
Afterparty we're all kind of drinking
Secret bookshelf
Alright
That sounds like someone who's not being
Sincere
Sounds like someone who's like who's been professionally funny for a long
They're the top
The top floor in that Malibu house
Was covered in stuffed animals
Is that a guest room for maybe that couple with their kids
I didn't know you was a room for somebody who doesn't show
With puppet
Toys and Pacifica
Collectibles of the nerd culture stuff fit Seth Green's entire careers
Alright that's it
Laugh it off
Because it's hard you know cuz you trust these people
I love them
And I got fired
Robots
A very young child or the show Robot Chicken
I don't know what more
Data people want
You have already solved the mystery
Pedophile code word that nobody is ever used
Or maybe it is been used but come on
If
There is a thing that says green might say with the use of the word chicken
I'm going to go with
His show
Robotic
Right you'd like if you and I were
Dan or like if I
Out
You know like maybe we go meet up with a bunch of contacts on my want to fill in for you
Fight
Exactly what Fight Club
But on some level you could
Could be a way I might drunkenly presented somebody or
Hey like we had talked about chicken
That is awesome
Hundred percent of people specially based on the other week
He had a secret rooms
Even witches
And again the bunk beds part like
Physician Electra Cruiser
Like I don't
I hate that I said b**** their blankets so stupid
You haven't you could easily
Like if you have a mansion
The idea is like
I know
From
Stomach
Experience
Mansion
Watching
The lifestyle
Right cribs
Okay
Have
Rooms that people can stay in
That they know from their life before they were rich as they're rich enough to be like
You can stay with
In Malibu if you come in vacation
You have Acts
To my mansion that I can build a room for you to visit
Human
Maybe some green has a lot of friends
Maybe like this day and like maybe
You would want to allow the kids to
Have their own room
That would be in my house
Yeah because I have enough friends
That are close to me
That are now married or on their way to heaven
Like it let's say I were to
I don't know
Perfect world
Lendup
We become super successful with this vodka
To the point where I'm super rich you're superrich to we all have to work anymore maybe you stay in Chicago at
Decide f****** I'm going to
Should I get a big old house
France your girlfriend get married have some kids
We do the show over Skype
Keep things going everything is good
Dedicated so when you come and visit in my chateau
That is something
Like
That makes perfect sense
My brother
There are rooms in that house
That Arch
For other people
Specific
That don't match his lifestyle
At all because he has people come and stay with him
This is the room for others
Weird you don't understand though in this fantasy
Sad face
Scenario
What I would do if I were rich
Which is
Test the limits of the
I would go around committing
I would I would burn down
Anywhere
We could go anywhere I can go do you know how
People get away with
I would test every single f****** Limited
Try and put me in jail
Trying I'm so rich
I don't even give a
F***
Burn It Down
All of your lies you know what I'll pay for the prosecution's lawyers a mental picture of Youth like
Worsening
$100 bills is how I would start fires on other people's homes come out of the house
Checkbook in your life
Build my Redford
That's horrible. I do like it I do like it on one level cuz maybe they didn't like
The house they were living in
And because of the numbers you could write on that check
Joyriding Robinhood is what I'm doing
Stop on the backend pack
For a while your house down
You're going to come watch
Damn
Restart feel like I'd be a better rich person
Korean president
Penny-pinching Rich vs poor
You have
You bring a recorder
If you watch the House burn
Is it that watching
How do you feel right now
Any memories you think you're not going to be able to recover from that guys welcome to the new episode of real estate fight
Smith family over here we're watching there
Funeral home burned to the ground it was built by their grandfather by his own hands I know you're crying right now
You have to keep in mind that you're going to lend in a better place
You're going to have a better house
Shoes with it but
I think I could be a miniseries on Earwolf mementos or do I have to stipulate that they keep it all
They can only keep any copies they have
The DVD of Mamma Mia
Everybody else has got a bird
You got to go Survivor
Fever watch Survivor one of the things they get to bring one luxury item
Everyone who comes on the ship gets
To bring one
Bring a razor
Get the one item
We'll talk about this and then they'll be the crackling of
Willbros marshmallow be fantastic
The best idea for a podcast this is right up there with
TV show with the
I can save the show
They're the stand-up show the we pitch
Be so rich we could be
Anyway
So Isaac
A lot of this stuff on the fact that
Seth Green said we need to talk about chicken
Dinner party
You really resembles the show that you do
And I got to be honest
Alex
Finally
Shows
Somewhere with all as a journalist
Props to Alex
This is this is as close as it's going to get to Alex be like
Good job buddy
Maybe they thought you were into pizzagate I thought you were funny they knew you they were teasing you
He said that conversation
Why would someone say we need to have a conversation about you
Walking you're interrupting me brother
Someone saying
Is is is is that good
Okay
He says we need to have a conversation about zika
Eating
This this wave of dread cuz like I had
You know my house like they might the end of this stuff they might be into the stuff
Children I asked him if they were into sacrifices
Who knows
He never real expresses a little bit more about the aliens
Clearwater
Go fuc yourself
Fake conversations that you had
Based on
Did pizzagate fear that you already had that you brought into it
Inform
This conversation with someone who is
Decent enough to let you
F******
No-name out-of-work actor into his Circle
You're just trying to
The cash in on Seth Curry
Celebrity
Trucking
Do you know what
A week from now it could come out that Seth Green the monster
I still don't believe this guy
I'm not defending Seth Green
That's all
And I love that Alex
Like because he's been burned in the past is like he said chicken
Whatever I'm listening to I feel like Alex
Is getting out a lot of
The frustration that he has
With himself
No
With his shity underlay
Ligate so much like
For real you're going to bring this marked it at me like I already have people who are
Have you heard
Motherfuking these people talk
Have you ever talked to David Knight operation
He said chicken
David Knight real news and then we got in trouble cuz I was
Leaving walking Quaalude what are we human
David nights like I just want to call it something else I don't think I don't think that's going to be well
You know what I deal with having a talk-to-text motherfuking coming into my goddamn show what am I in
Twitter already guy I said
It's a good idea
Now I do
Naming Seth Green
I would love to have this
At work now I have to
Trichotillomania
Oh my God this is the problem with this not this is the problem with this
Stop being alive show
If every one of our every single one
Is that hurt that ran
That was like started f****** clapping that was perfect
Nobody understands Alex Jones better than you
I got the tiniest bit
Usually have nope
We can't swear on the
I very rarely ever hear some almost
Like I was writing in my head like oh he didn't say f***
Upgrade
Alex is going
Russian agent Adam Schiff
By the way you go to fill your hand.
Click sports shop needs help
The other thing dude
Is that like
I've made it very clear
I think this is
Descendants 2
Not good
It's not good but he comes up with a rebuttal
That I think is actually
Worth exam
Bouillabaisse
If what I'm saying is
Why would there be such
Effort
Shut me down on every platform that it's called state
Control cuz it's libel
Cuz you're slandering someone
If you type it
Even weather
If I
You are without
Evidence other than he said chicken
Mickey
If I had
Why would ever BB
Trying to prosecute for me
For murder
Come on doesn't murder somebody why would everybody be trying to save a timer
Because it's so true
Wrong that's not good
You're too good at this
I was hoping to
Like I was hoping to like never discussed the
Chicken are in the
Robot Chicken for dinner
Could have been on air for 13 years
Premiere 2005
The reason that I was hoping to like tea
Cheez-It outage
Just because
They don't
Bring it up for quite a while
Until Alex does in this
Let me ask you this question cabby
You're really good buddies we looked it up we just believe
Seth Green going back for years
Charlie against TV shows called Robot Chicken
Chicken Joe
Is this not the ultimate out doing Sacha Baron Cohen
I would like to dispel this one more time
Cool
I like
Alex is like
I'd like his
Beer
You don't ever say you don't like I like
He's gun-shy
A little bit
Because he's wrong
Crazy
But I like the idea of it like because
Everyone
But now he has to be like
Really on his guard
The chicken strip
Some sort of weird
Prank
What's going on is
I'd like to know I know
I know
I was
That's like that's like a child
Find The Rock
But interesting solution to a problem
Alright so this
Fifth Circle doesn't fit in
But the cube
Will fit into the diamond hole
Well if we make the
V2
Bigger the circle will fit
They're thinking
That's creativity at least
That's how low the bar is ballot
Intimately please
Then he actually brought up Robot Chicken at all
Of course you would bring up robot
Chicken and then
And when you said it used
Surprised that he pushed back at all
Oh yeah
Of course because if
Chicken would never have come up at
No I don't
I don't know I don't know if it's
Burned so many times
This would be such the thing where he's like
Let's throw into let's go let's go hold let's go all the way
Peace
I didn't bring up
Kind of unnecessary
Conversation
It's relevant
I think one of the biggest reasons that Alex is like
With or without Sacha Baron Cohen
Would be pushing back against this guy a little bit
Goody's getting sued
The Cuban on world and like the reading 4chan
It's about him
Are largely like don't trust this guy
Like most of the internet
Conspiracy Community has
Red flags on Isaac Kappy
Okay
Because there are stories like about him choking
Right because there are people
From his path to Heaven automatically posted on the
About knowing him and
Kind of horror guy
Yeah then also there are other stories
Peter Parker
Football I can't really sort these out or not
I'm only reporting this in as much as
Why
These internet commute
Please don't trust
He's tried to
Private message
Get people
Who are quote-unquote whistleblowers
To identify themselves
As if it were a dachshund Opera
Like trying to get private if yeah yeah
I don't know if that's true but that's what they're saying on the Wind about him about him
I think Alex
Took this on as like a
I'm playing
Another goddamn poker
Metaphor but I'm playing
Maybe something weird will happen
You know he's accepting this interview as like
I'm coming in with a bad hand
I can walk away from
Fold in the middle of this there's no big deal I'm not I'm not emotionally invested in this
But if it hits
It's going to hit big
But the weird thing that happened
Is it like
Alex pushes back
And then he's like
He has a show called Robot Chicken
Sacha Baron Cohen
People right now do you understand what's going on
You get so are you f****** with me yet
That all out of his sister
And then
A
Said it is
It's almost like
His hot-headedness
Cool
And then he's like
Yeah I know they are f****** kid
Hollywood
It kind of becomes like
Yeah
Really aggressive Isaac is like
People f******
Use the right
And then Alex
Just like
Yeah right you're cool
You didn't say anything
Yeah
You still out
For like
Turn our it's crazy
It's crazy
This
There's not there's no more me
Yeah
We've got what we wanted to get everything else that Isaac
Abby says is all just like
The same shed
And like I think this
I think no
Yaddle
Yeah so we we've dealt with him I haven't
The child delivery
We've heard him say that Seth Green has a
What animal
Yeah and that you talked about chick
However
This is the most important
Obertal
With two dudes
Who are both trying
Two light
Coming to Loggerhead
Okay
Why doesn't
Blackmail material
Private
Maybe 16 I mean
Habitat
And
Clips not done
Eclipse not done
But that's the greatest thing ever
Don't you dare
F****** know Seth Green
What is your age
I don't
Call Honey
I haven't pointed this out
At All by the way
The guy in studio
Co-hosting with Alex
Who runs
The TV network that plays out like he has some sort of like maybe a satellite TV channel plays in
I haven't played any of them cuz
It's like a booty song.
Just an idiot
Sitting next to them
First of all the whole thing about chicken
You know hey
Yeah I'm sure you've been to the parties but you're not like
Good friends with you like that
I know I know a lot of
Today
So here's with Echo
No one wins
Because Alex is trying to
Talked him out with the actors
The Producers tried to get me
I meant
Very
Correctly
Cathy Hughes like
Steph Curry has a giant production company
Player in terms of being able to get things made
Fair
Wasn't just about the
Disturbed concert
Go to bed go to bed you guys are doing
So at this point after
The pissing contest
The guy who shall not be named
Forgotten his name
He's not important
You know what in Hollywood what it is
Jesus really did all these people who didn't have
Friends in high school get to rise
Prominence
You know like all these people who are really auntie
Social didn't have any friends
Find themselves in
Deposition
Power up
And I mentioned this earlier friend of mine who I'm not your name cuz that's
Know their business
But I'm friends
I don't know if they're still at the same place
But they were working for
Largest
Casting agencies
In the country
Right
And I talked
Experience
You know like what they go through in
From high school
I knew
They were like
And I'm using a
Ambiguous
Was pronoun
They don't need
They were also
I was I was a so
I think
Yeah they made me
I feel very
Very welcome
Comforted
Spokane
Long time
Chronological
Right but I which is why I don't have a job
2 years
Actually had a real conversation
I care about them very much
Amazingly
Social
Which flies counter
To the little bit very dumb
But
Hollywood
That's a big giant
Fly zapper a big web
Where they can now be in charge
And a cheerleader that wouldn't date them
They're going to crap all over her and make them
Like a pump talked about
Super Princess Lakes
Makes me feel
Mateys
Right
Floating
Booty shorts
They crap all over
The agency is on you
Write the crapper and the crappie
Yeah but that's metaphorical
Politically
I don't know
Dammit Godzilla jail what is going on
Are we don't know
No adults around
This is a Friday show because it's sort of like on Friday we let it all hang out
Retroactively
What are we doing
I also love to like
If we can just take
The brakes he's talkin about
Can people eat
S***
Richard
Confirmed earlier he said that
Track mean something else with which weekend
Imagine if the prenup your ass I have no idea I don't know
The issue that I Come Away With It Is
Isaac Kappy said f*** on the show he's like his family
No it's not
I forgot I forgot
Like Scott Aukerman on Comedy Bang Bang as a joke
Felicia
Don't you know how the family gathers around like
The I hate
I hate him in the
President because there's
Nothing really of substance
It's all of this
Nonsense
There's a part of me that likes it on some level just
I can't finish
His show is A Prairie Home Companion
Except for sometimes they talked about
Make
How to give a like abroad predict
Going to make somebody
A broad abroad
No ice
Video of the things that I'm going to forget you
Be the thing
The things that I'm going to predict
So there's three there's a police record
Dear
Is that
He's going to from these lawsuits has learned his lesson
That like
Do this
Civilian
People in power
Care
You can yell about Soros being a demon all you want
He's never going to sue you
You didn't care about whatever bulshit you're saying
If you knows it's not true and you know it
So whatever
Just live your life until you know enjoy it
He can do this to the pope cuz opposed not going to sue him for
Pope has much bigger things to do like recently
The capital punishment is
Is no good right
He's also said that hell isn't real
Hey big
Issues on his plate
Through
Eating a bowl of s***
Like he was doing while he's like
Capital punishment
Cannot do it
Audi
I'm still going to protect child molesters but
What report
Crudite wild humane
There they could smell it
Smilax
Verity
Landing on Obama around his mouth as the Pope's
So I don't I don't know what my point was necessarily about like what the
Value of press
Today is
I guess it's
Nothing alike spread Maybe
But I do like
How
Weird
Who knows there's this last clip here
I think it's a
There's nothing
Like legitimately
This doesn't
Come out as like
A natural inorganic
Evolution of the conversation
To go like
18 seconds
Before to give
It would actually make it
More confusing
Because the guy
Who runs AT&T
Network
Completely
They sent a transmission
There's a transmission, emanating out of
Spiritual blackout
Planets
Kill yourself
No do not listen transmission
There's a bigger transmission from God
Sing don't do it
Alex
He's not saying
Believe
He's arguing that
From a black
There's a transmission that's trying to say kill yourself to a bunch of planets
That are unoccupied
We are getting the transmission from
The black hole thing we should kill ourselves
Because we know Alex Jones enough you mean
Give minorities rights in
Liberal with
With the
Accepting
And because we already know
Trump is Christ
Do what Christ would do
Which is
Be a monster
Explain to me
Real quick
Black hole
Which they believe
Right
Send out a
Spiritual transmission
Which would be tough to get out of the Event Horizon
To get a message
Of the things that we've all read Einstein's theory of relativity
Tivity we know that the only thing that escapes The Event Horizon is the spirit
Messenger
Show me the f****** message
Read out a spiritual message willy-nilly
360 degree
All over the place
You know the black hole
Is like a Russo's transmission
You so more
Give up all hope
Right there.
So-so
Is that a thing are they
Black holders the black hole
Is that
Tasmac
Like what's going on here
Most concerned
Jordan
The black hole
You got this
Perry
Probably a Muslim
Who hates Western Civilization
On the other end of that black hole
Just look at the center of every Galaxy there is a supermassive black hole
The center of every supermassive black hole
There is a supermassive Muslim
Right or non-western percent
Obviously and Alex's brain
Representative
First swap
Well it black all is probably the best
I love I love this because we've done now
We walked ourselves backwards
Listen to like what
He's the perfect been
Garrison cartoon
Still
He's riding a bar of gold offered the distance for no reason
Yeah why not what the fuc
I love it though man that's nonsense
And also it's really fun way to end an episode where Alex is
Like we spent the beginning of this
With him defending himself
About these
Really real lawsuits that are happening
Disgusting
In-N-Out
The best of our ability is Outsiders
Involved in his court case
You probably should be
To the stand maybe great we know what we know and what we don't we don't pretend
Right
And that was the beginning of it
I'm in the middle of it you got it
Clunky b*******
What about the Amish
And then
Do you have any
Weber tow
Talk about chicken
Video
I don't mean to I don't mean to like
Undersell that
No
I know that he's already in the
GameStop in
Like periscope
Is Growlithe should not have let him on the show
Because he
He was going to say
There's every there's every
As a
Show
Curating
A presentation
When you have a guest on
You have a slight responsibility
Understand what they're going to say
Yeah and if they
Commit libel
The little on you arrivals usually an issue
Two little on you usually
Now that liable is
Slander is
Is that what you say
Right
Alex is still bogged down in lawsuits
Who gives a s***
Busy for awhile for sure
Slide Seth Green
Something litigious
Hey
I look forward
Nothing the next season of chicken
Which is a
Very different
Never hearing about this dude ever again
He's going to be in the new season of
Coming into talk s*** on his
Erstwhile friend of fun this has been a lot of fun. Sorry this month
But we have a website
We called that out of pianos
Where were technology.com
To find
Not the best Twitter presence in the world
Entirely so I am
I'm not good at
Social media
We think that there is
Consistent activity
We put the word out
To go is the group go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
We've seen a lot of traffic come in Racine
Walk
Listeners come on
Hangout
On the page
Not going by where the action was
And I appreciate
We're up over 300 and that group now
Maybe it's not that many
But it's fuckingawesome weird Community hell yeah comedian
Set doing stand-up in the middle of Chicago recording the bedroom that's pretty f******
Not bad thank you all for joining
More tabs
What's actually happening
Private group
Crest
Is
I think all it would take is
Is just me quick
Cuz I already submitted
Spotify super specific
Pacific
Great job with that stuff either
What else do we got
Cheer terms
No I just say that every time
I don't know why it is
But
Episode
Tumi
It seems like it's one guy's fault
And I'm going to go with
Being such
Alex had to call in this m***********
Mark.
Yourself I'm fine
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work