Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
About Alex Jones
Hello
How would you
Describe this podcast
For the first time
For some reason they found this podcast
This specific episode had never heard
Already
5 minutes in
Baffled as to why other people listen to it and somebody recommended
First of all
Aggressive way to start
And I'm sorry cuz I kind of
Alright alright my friend
The Jordan here we start facts
Landed him in the present-day sometimes like today
Bring the plane into the runway
Program weirdos
Pretty good
Specific
Continuing that would be going over February 9th
Cover a wider swath
Trying to get to this
Tea party Breakout
We were were like we're on seven or eight episodes
Maybe I thought for sure we'd be able to
3 days
So
I'm very excited
To tell you about a couple of
Today
It is a bump it up a little bit
Meadowstone in Austin
So what's not even a stranger
Welcoming
Into the realm of
The globalist Chris thank you so much and tell your brother
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Thank you so very much Chris
If you would like to porch.com
There's still a button pressed
Frankly this point we should just have to tell little we've updated a lot of cars at wework
Click this button
The donut you were saying you don't have many hot for your blog lately and then I
Call Myra
About Alex
Has been so focused on this side project that I'm working on that I like
About like
Stupid
Impact value
We should just change the website to a big
Flashing
I want to write
And then I get
Like
I finish it
Read it back and I go through the rest of the internet I'm like
Who the f*** cares what
You think playing God's name would you care what I think
Everytime I see Conor friedersdorf name in the Atlantic I'm like
Quit it's that guy's allowed to have a job f****** we should all quo
That's this is why that person judging the show 5 minutes
Dead on you are absolutely guilty of the same problem
In the neighborhood
He is we brought it back
Fred Rogers
Different thoughts about Alex
My Jordan this is so big
This is so big for the longest time
Flirting around with the idea of
Being able to take phone calls
And now
Do
Disaster
For now how is not doing a lot of episodes live or any Prince
On a trial may be
But we have a phone line now
People can call in and leave messages
Right now we have a situation
If you call this number at any time
You can leave a message
We might scream them before we play them we also might not there's a low probability
Jordan going through phone numbers trying to find acronym
What you settled I'm not it's not perfect
The runner-up
Is it spelled out tug fail
Club
Little too risque
For our show my favorite Robin Williams movies
Alright
So Jordan
Yep
Would you like to know what our new phone number
It is
American
Dialing code 1
Area code
No
American dialing code
Neon nips
530 Neon
Hit us up
If you can leave us a message with the better
Is real
I don't remember
It's on any phone
Calculator
Phone number
Do people give the thing to remember and then the actual numbers to it's like a reinforcement
Okay
Tell me
How do you call for Feldco
Great
For Windows Siding & Doors
I don't know what the numbers are I will never be able to call them
Do you have a phone bro look at my phone
You're not going to reminisce second Google search results right now they wouldn't remember them but they going to remember me
No but they would have to reference when they wanted to call
They also have a f****** phone that has the letters on it it's a lot of 6 it'll take
Probably should have written it down.
Bright
Area code
530 530i California number
Then
A bunch of sixes
Some of which spell beyond
Neon
All right nipple
We'll wait it's me on mitten
PS
If you dial the number and you add an extra number it doesn't matter
You could give
Nipples nipples
The phone stopped recognizing
It doesn't matter
Our number is neon nit
Yeah
I wasn't going to go with you I wasn't to go with puzzle Club
Free f****** hours
Just looking at phone numbers
And you know what's really hard consult our board of directors
Which consists
You and that I have a qualifying vote that is not better than one of the real difficulties and
Complain about
Make a word out of numbers
Don't have letters
Any phone number
Automatically
Became is really difficult pick up like
Define cities in America that don't have
The first three letters included
California Chico California
Yeah
Alright we're going to we're going to do that for letting you buy us we're going to have to
In order to make sure that wherever it is
Chico
Welcome your two newest has
Like a city that is
Me like maybe somewhere in Missouri or like my dad's from
Fresno and Baker
Bakersfield California maybe I can find one of those
Be ready for today's episode
Okay so if you're not ready for today's episode call American dialing code
Contact drop
From today's episode
That was a lot better than I would have
Terrible
But from Alex
That is like
Compare reading on a curve
That was not bad
Yeah but he's also sitting with a couple of guys from Australia
We're still on brand
Casino viral video
Ace of Dick Van Dyke
No no no
The guy who has a
Conspiracy
Triggered Alex
Novelty here there was a
Someone opening a digital TV converters
A microphone
Now we can go out camera microphone
Documents
Important
I like I like
The sentiments
But you know what's going on
About forever and evens
Even had
To say we can't do this
No
Defame
Is from like way early in his career
Kion are opened up like a cable box
Show that there was like a microphone
Like it being one of these things
Was one of my first Rebellion
Make sure course it's from like way to backup
Far back if there's any video of
Me to go find Alex's cell
So the idea that this guy is putting out a viral video that's very similar
Alex's greatest hits
Say something
Police he's got a police that space shuttle B
Remedial
I do enjoy how Lowe's
Yeah yeah
I'm taking this guy down
Beautiful was
Believer
BlogTalkRadio show would probably like 20 listeners of America
Like mixed up with Trump really engaged with us probably before all this
Love his show when he's not trying to defend
But its fake steak
It's like chopsticks
Leon nip
Illusion
Does fuel mistakes
Fuel hire for him but we know it's all a charade
Emotional
I don't mean that I mean as far as
Somebody who's listening to it
The stakes are much higher in that
I can listen to him talk about this s*** or whatever it is
And I'm so emotionally detached
Random nonsense
Talking about anything if he's lying about it
President it still reminds me that the president is not going to reunite those f******
Can kids with
Starkid
You're defending of
Legitimate monster who will go down in history
As being the dumbest person
And also the first person
3 burnt alive by the entirety of America at the same
340 million people all standing around in a big circle
He's a
How tall do you think it would have to be to get
Everybody to be able see
Like the tower that pyre
In order to make sure that the rains come
Sears Tower is really big
More than
3 miles away
Super Bass
Well I know if we build it too tall God will Aquarius feel like
Again
Yeah I don't know
Where you're trying to
Articulating
Like
Back then
His rhetoric is very similar in
Like that
But it's kind of important
Defeat throwing out into the world
Where is now everything he does
Isn't service
Reinforcing
Even if he isn't
Really apart
He's just trying to attach himself
Personal gain
It's still
Is there
Get rid of that and then go back to that feeling
That's why I like to start the week
2009 stuffed Rosie got worse as the week goes on
We jump back to the present
Bummed out
Here Alex talk a little bit about what happened during the
The election
Therein
I didn't know about this
Dial tickets
But man
Bedtime
Rumors
German
Like it's been a month
At this point
I have to stress that
You're not Eurasian was like literally a month before
So
There's a difference between criticizing
The president
And then burning an effigy
Yeah one of those
And the other one is is is pretty cool
Generally the time. Immediately following Obama being elected
It was more the latter that people were doing
Puppets
Later than where we are
Because a lot of that was part and parcel of
The Tea Party protest
Broken
Images
People's hearts already a month but perhaps that wasn't being
Publicly done
Have time stamps
I do a picture
Oh yeah
Alex is so excited about the Obama Deception
Coming out in March
Coming up March 5th
He's an ounce
Yeah he's so excited about it that what he does
If he decides
C-SPAN
Entire
He spends an entire commercial to commercial break
Goes to commercial
Does another half segment
Just reading from the script and one of the things that really struck stuck out to me was like
This is
Same topic
Endgame
It's all the same
Cool of the things that I talked about
I'm going to just repeat my material
Burn that material
Late night again
That is dirty pool man
This stuff on TV
Put it on TV it's burned so
That cut that out cuz
Who needs to look for that if you want
Does he do a good voice over
Since I haven't watched any of his documentaries into endgame
Never will
Hankering
He does say
The whole lotta
He's released
Maybe second-to-last
Kimberly squatting documentary Loose Change
Purdue student director write that one
Robert Evans
Great movies Watertown Rosemary's Baby
Great movies directed by Jason bermas
Rosemary's Baby
Another one of those but
People who are satanic
Donuts
Download a documentary like we should never cover them
Cuz they were made on like
Shoulder cameras
Very
DIY
Like shoulder cameras from like the 90s
For my broadcast products
Respect
The hell out of that muscle
Cuz when I was in high school
Who's program and like you are the coolest
Circle
In doing it we have those cameras you put on your shoulder
Father super-heavy
And you had to go for
VHS tape to tape
Like you had
It would
Was a disaster
Time consuming
Compared to like digital item
Really put in the times
To do all that
I took my captured the content is terrible you know that's why I professionally
That's why professional operations used beta long past the beta Wars had ended
Because Beta had
Timestamps
Make editing a lot easier
Look up even back then
We live in Chicago Illinois
Michelle
Alex
Call from a guy names
Chicago
And I'll tell you
From Chicago is from Chicago
But he's one of the bad sounds a bit like he's from
Sounds like one of those apples that you mean
Welcome
I hear a lot of music
Okay cartoon
It's just lunch
Cartoon satire about the chimpanzee
This is a like a
This is like an editorial cartoon that come out where Al Sharpton is a chimpanzee
So keep that in mind.
Al Sharpton
You might just be using that as a jump
But what I'm calling about is that
There's an article in the Washington times has u.s. powered Leon rate
Back about six months ago or whenever it was
I kind of figured that this was going to be a black power grab and I said it was
I could go
Excerpt some of the comments here
Criticism from conservatives
Tom fitton
Conservative Judicial Watch
He says
Quoting I think we're going back
Going to revert back to the old days of the federal government pushing quotas and race
Consciousness
Policy
Public policy
Yeah that's terrible.
He just Rambles from there
Pick you up. You're going to drop the clothes
Like I love to let you go
Realtor
A branch of Chicago racism is very rich
I've smelled that before
Oh my God I'm having flashbacks and up and then
At least after the show
You're talking to
Chicago you're a real funny guy
You heard this joke
Steve's from like some sort of weird. I'm guessing
Chicago
Alright
Anyway my my issue here is like
I think I was let him talk
Too long I think once he said this is a black power grab Alex more like
Cuz you can tell kids response
Has nothing to do with
We don't listen to the news on my news program
Before it got too harsh
Real bat you and I both heard after the first sentence but the n-word was coming
It was around the corner
Hard
And who's going to be the Chicago or which is even worse than the regular
The deep dish
And talk about
Nothing
Primarily
And then he gets
Back to the topic
Race
And racism
Gets
Trouble
Modern multiculturalism
Shrive
Problem
I would say
Most of what Alex talks about about his childhood
Is either how many people he had sex with
How he's never been
Alternating I've never seen whites do racism
And then I was such a
Victim of racist
Also just as Monterey
I don't have a parcel
That is so like
If there is a wrong place
To take this that's probably yet
Licking
Like I said earlier I admire him shutting down
Introspective
And that was the worst that he's like
Look the moment
Feeling like
So you know how racist is whenever they get something
So obviously wrong
What he said so called differences in Pigman
No
Difference
That's a normal thing I don't have to speak politically correct out
We're all cool with that if you're starting from a
Let's put this whole called pigment difference out of the plate
You're like oh you're super race
It's a little facetious a little glitch
Preemptive
I would definitely
In response to this
Brought by Steve
Chicago
Right
Whatever but then he says that
Austin Texas
That that
Your people want to be around
The bordering areas words
English
Couple problems
The French Duo
Definition of
But Alex's
Just throwing around all flippantly
Legitimately
He said tomorrow
He's Mexican.
Mario is a quarter of a town or city especially one with
High poverty level
It's essentially Club
Still a lot of these.
Water move it I like to see of redlining that is existence inside
They want to move there
It's a it's a choice
Also think about what exactly you're comparing this do
Cuz they're art Barrios or the English speakers in like a
Quebec
You say that
And you're right
Poor areas
Exclusively one
Mississippi living there in
Quebec French Barrios
Yeah where you going where you got what you got
Take that
Show me
Alright
I know a little bit of French
Guillain-Barre emphasis on little
You are revealing this up
Thursday. Thursday on Friday
That's pretty solid might have enough
If only we had
Endless possibilities
Friday I was like
Single serve coffee
I might have
Have to move
At the end of it
Where am I
My living
Situation is a little bit up in the air right now
To the point of on Friday I was
Legitimately looking at
I would like
Legitimately on websites
Conversion
Euros to
I believe the text I received was that the rent in Lehigh
Countries
Blown Away
Your Healthcare
You have to get a job
Alright alright
Tuesday
Trying to dance around. Talk about Alex being more racist
You do continuous.
Turn it up
Programs
Just a huge distraction and diversion
Talk about race
You
Individually
I think emotionally equipped to deal with when I have a massive chip on their shoulder and think that
Anybody who's talking about race relations
Systemic racism
Power imbalances
Are just trying to create
I think it's in your world you you probably already for it
But
Everyone else I could handle it
And I think that's our conversations about race are not like
Hey look at you looking at skin on here
Look at yours
Some sort of weird like
It's about like hey you know it be interesting to understand
The world
On an empathic level 100
That you don't have access to
The top part of your experience
All the time
Keeps on repeating over and over and over again
I saw story just on
End of last week on democracy
A girl who was eating lunch
For college
And someone called the police
They said that she didn't look like
Black
She posted about it
The only thing I was doing was
Black
Like I know that
Stories keep happening
But there are those things
Outside of your Experian
And if you don't talk to Pete
People about racial issues
Everything is about white guilt
You'll never be able to understand
Always have
And then
You end up like Alex
Well just just on Saturday my
Girlfriend my parents came up to visit we we went out to take
Eat lunch with them
Afterwards
We had to
Continue talking
Because
Hyundai
My my girlfriend just
Told my parents because she grew up in South Africa
And so she told my parents the story where
This
Boots black
Person who worked on there
Just how everybody
Did stuff
And her dad
M11
And the ambulance that shows up says oh I'm sorry
We don't handle blackface
You're going to have to take
And my parents just heard that and we're like
I saw their faces and it was legitimately they never thought it was real because they've never heard of a person who
Neversoft
You always been
Defensive whenever you heard exactly
Troubling
Sad
Reply to sexuality
Nationality
Immigrant status
They make me feel like genuinely if I just brought all of my friends
From varying backgrounds in to talk to my parents and tell them
Tell them one story they
Like
In a week maybe like oh shoot I think there might be something to this whole
We are years behind on this thing
Not only didn't help
It made you want to
Kill yourself
Great God
To put a button on all that cuz we're out of the races
For now although there's another one
Coming up don't get me wrong
There's just a Lackey
Willingness to engage that's all
Narrative
Just someone new
Just is like
This is my opinion
I'm going to take it
The front on myself
Outside of
Whatever I believe and also I'm
Supernaut
Black
Just don't like him for other
Totally not
Having a so-called different pigments
Really long
Becca problems
Is the idea that Obama said that
He wasn't going to
Having a bunch of
And I would say
We agree but is that guy
Entirety
Complaining about
Facts about Obama
There is like
He was going to bring
Home day 1
I maybe he aspired to but then when he got in here Eliza
That would be
What
Follow through with
Closing Guantanamo course
Quagmire is it
Which I think you still should have done
Take the hit
Bite the bullet
I mean that's something we can relieve we can read litigate Obama's presidency for forever
Possibly understand
Exactly
Complained
About
Obama
You should have the same
Complaints about
Zoe
False
I don't I don't
Because it's a black bread
Get away from that
Has to be a part of
The way he interacts with race
Beatles
About being made
Feel guilty about white.
And the fact
Plane
About Obama
You should complain about trucks
Will get the f******
But like it just doesn't
Track for me
It can't there has to be a bigger
Reason
And it's not
It's not that Trump is against the globalist
No
But Thursday row way to look at Trump is Perez president and not sink
This is
Because
A black guy with president
And the white panda
F****** rise up or whatever it is
Alien
Get rid of
Transition
The Thinker
Awesome talks
About
The alien Rodin
The space monster Rodan
Both of the rapper
So I can wrap reference about the
The Sculptor
What do you mean you didn't realize that
What do you mean
Which one was Rodin
Brodin wasn't the Dragon
No
Monster
Know the King Ghidorah came from a volcano
What's
From deep within
The monster is zero
Destroy All Monsters
How dare you
Trying to pick
Mothra was mop
Mothra was about Mothra was actually the
I have a lot of thoughts
About the Catherine
Characters in the Godzilla universe but also was specifically
By Pharoahe Monch
That's why I call right
That's what I started
Infowars
But is on
And
We made this point
Before but I think that Alex got a lot of his early narrative
From Alan Watts
I think that he is responsible for a great deal of these
Fake
Information that Alex
Because their interview is just rehashing engaged
We talked about him
We have the exact same
The lights just went out a little bit
Resigned
It did that earlier today too
The global is coming to get us trying to turn off the light
I wish I was exploitative
Just like
Power
I want to go to France
Just calling
That's what I'm saying
Neon nips also
French
Naomi
Alan Watts
Also like the thing that really stuck out to me
Because we covered it so much
Endgame cover
If you want to go listen to that
Sony archives
Yep
We don't need to ask we learned our lesson the last episode of like
Doing too much
We covered this already
Cuz they
Alan Watts
Has a very specific
Reading on the club
Chrome because I've read there
I know that he's wrong
But I also know that
Exactly what Alex
So I have a working theory that Island
Is the one who has like let him
Ocala map
A so-so he's Alex
Is Pez
Yeah little bit
Because I don't know what he's like in the same thing
He's much less famous
So there is this
He's also
Clearly
Appliance
Kind of like if you're like a famous, can you have a friend
New spot
But he never made it
Who's like yeah you're like
Never heard of that situation
I think it's been a lot of movies about stand up
What but I wanted to let him
Presented on this episode
So I have one clip
Alan Watt
Which we have not heard
Before
Is Ludacris
Something that was discussed over 100 years ago at World meeting
And and that was
And go against their agenda and and get it published
All of them
That's also part of
Extreme process
The same thing with a drugging of children mini young meals
School betrothal different Roxy get them Redlin excetera
This is to Giant
Their diagnosis being hyper because it
Questions about Happy with advances to get
Nakagawa has leadership affect agenda
Has never ever faltered from
Set down a hundred years ago there they're right on track
So yeah
The end of the clip
Why are you so focused on
Maybe it's because
Leadership
Is that leadership only exist
Within the male of the species
And it's just it's
Fear is more than
But
Christina's Restaurant Moore
Current
In 2009
2009 but
He is not as like
He doesn't have
He does not trust
He doesn't hate them
Really weird
I hit a lick in my
I would like every episode being like
Alex does not think Muslims are demons
I wanted to keep a running tally of it but I have
Prison cell
He's still not brought up Soros
And of course it did
He thinks that
National sovereignty of an intellectual Elite and world bankers is surely preferable
Termination practice
New World Order
From David Rockefeller
What do you think about that
That first especially what do you think of that last word
I mean generally called an ombudsman
He's trying to combine
Omni budsman
Rockefeller in the definition
Administration
Even more Petty
Supranational not super Nash
To be further Petty
Sometimes
Really shaky attribution
Just started appearing
The year or two after
The most from
Where did this quote originate
Cuz it's not recorded anywhere it's not
Like like solid reporting it was pushed very strongly by
The national front
A publication run
National front
Which is
Political party that was run by Marine Le Pen
And what they mean is
Vichyssoise
Dude I don't
I don't know I just wonder why I don't want to I just want Alex to f****** pick a side on the Nazi
Why is why is it
Ronnie's like I love Hitler
If you're going to do the Nazi thing then just
Embracive
Living the
Half-measure
Bulshit
Because everyone
Pizza nosh
Yeah so they have to publicly.
And complain that who they don't like are the actual
Jesus people rhetoric brilliant
Against your
Globalist anime
What have you
I mean it's
It's a good game
No nothing
Always punch
I agree
And
If you can find
When cops are
Four Season anti-anti
I thought
Weird footage
ProTech
It's almost like there's a concerted effort
I meant predictable
I know right
You rat you I read that Guardian report.
Oh you guys are surprised
So I have a couple of film crew
In the studio
At this point
Cuz apparently the IFC is doing like an episode of something
About
Conspiracy theories
The independent film Channel. Correct
He also has been Aunt Australia
Who are doing the show called
Hunter
Which dried
Very hard to find online
Number one answer on the board
Subaru
Didn't become a shows because it was actually about a guy who hunted conspiracy theorists and Alex
You can't you can make sure about it
Conspiracy Hunter if he gets killed by ex first
Van Helsing the shooting Van Helsing
It's a difference
You guys were working on spec
And then they got the footage together and people like
For the History Channel guys
Not going to wait around another five years and then you know Alex was on that show bread
Meltzer's decoded
I think I
There's two guys named Meltzer one is a wrestling journalists in the others
Conspiracy theory dude
I can't remember which one is open
Smeltery bubble titles
I only noticed
Those are two
Topics that I talk
To Marty DeRosa about a lot and that's why they become
Consulted on that show and it was on the History Channel
History Channel
Alex
He also was on Jesse Ventura show
Fair enough
Also
I want to go
Embarrass
But I was just thrilled that he has this film crew in studio
And he accidentally let something slip
That works into one of my theories
That had been out till this point
Everything that's not strong.
Jamaican look like
What's going on in here
Transit time
The new studio
This is only important because it works into my theory of they moved into a new studio around the time
Yeah yeah
So
It works from a timeline stamp
I have nothing concrete
Keep this up but man the circumstantial evidence is starting to pile up
Boil
Is always actually including Transit time
Even when he's saying
Nada
18 hours a day plus
You know it's no Dinklage
You're digging around half the
The time being race
Right you're just texting weird
I don't know
Now that
That's our history
Episodes of naked and afraid be like episode
Miracle Whip
Why did you do it
Tastees dip
Premier equipment
So you sweat macaroni and cheese what is that smell
In my life
Because of
Time and we couldn't enjoy all the
Eclipse
Suggest that Austin
Police chief
Art Acevedo
Turned out like the only
He's the only police chief I've ever liked
Talk about how is this going to end
Which is a Quinn
It's been a month
But then
Further
This guy named Bob.
Who's Austin
Local
You say his name I hear Bob Fosse
Right
Cannot
Not think about it like there is
The only thing I see
There's also a great improvisers been on improv4humans
Name is Bob.
Bucket list
The great episode with just ham and
He's actually Brendan dassey
Problem
Finding out what the
Murderer is
Within
What is a murder podcast but if you want
My buddy Kyle Ayers
Has made a podcast called
Give the word other cop
To do a podcast about making a murderer
But you never told them that he had not watched it
Watched
We did a miniseries of that
It's really fun
I recommend
And also Mike Rivero
Mike Rivero is calling in from Hawaii
He's the guy who has
Is the show called what really happened
Send with Mike Rivero
GM's up maybe
Leaving
Alex
Because he's like this guy
Puppet of Israel
Mike Rivero hates
Cuz that makes
This progression works out
Yeah but anyway
Hawaii
Is in studio
Bull session
Weather today in Obama sucks
Nothing substantial nothing mean
Meaningful
We learned that Bob.
Runs hardware store
Wait right
Wait what
So he runs a hardware store
Hardware store
I don't give a s***
They presented as a
Mom and pop place
He's just a manager doesn't run
Perhaps
Alex
Maybe has a stroke
I'm turns into a character
Much like someone might do on him
The other one was
He might do a character that goes this f****** long
Hardware store
We have a hardware store in New Mexico
Real quick work disco's on Wild
Dixie not there's nothing no this is this is nothing set up at all before
Resist that leads to believe about to do a British guy
I'm just trying to talk about
Screen doors
And I sell guns
That's how I restore anymore
Google call Guns hardware store
Yeah probably
I would like a Whole Foods gun
Still going on my displays
Barack Obama
Civilian
A rattle spider
Are you okay
Mike Rivero still hanging out on
Are you
Should I
Asking if you're okay is your home
Another minute of this character
Got the taste
Is ironically saying that
Play shouldn't have actually
Literally saying that
Because
Look at people and other this Associated groups have power now
They're saying that I have done
Enter with Echo
The very real crimes that white people commit
Actually happening
Person once again saying
Of course you are doing this to me because this is exactly what I would do to you
So Def
The only other thing that happens
Predict very specifically
That within a
A few years the dollar is going to go
Arrow
Which
9 years old should my watch nine years later
Still got dollars
What is the conversion rate
To the Amero
I mean it
Infinity
1 million percent
So now we move onto the 20th
Is the Friday
To get the week.
A w come
What's come hard on this
This Friday
Notice
There wasn't a lot of talk
What is
The predominant narrative
In dispatch
February
Which is all of these states
But their sovereignty bill
He's naughty get back to it
Start up the
But we have more gas
Representative
Berman
Rights declaration
Amtrak
Why are using radio show and others the last two weeks
What is
What is that
What does intent
Better
I don't know what he isn't
I don't know what his goals are half
He's just
What was that British voice
That's true he is having fun
There's no call he's just
Really matters right about isn't real
He's just drumming up theater in order to sell his Wares
And you've got a stable operation going
But it don't
It's this weird
Like terrifying grounded he must be walking on wherein
In order for him to stay
Okay
As the economy gets worse
He has to pretend that the economy is going
So he has to
Keep being really negative if things are going to stay positive on
So
It's a very weird
For him you like everything
I don't really care and that's why he allows himself to do
3 minute long British
Compression
Yelling about you entry
Texas
House concurrent resolution that doesn't mean anything
What do ya
Untethered
He has no agenda with this other than just the like
Is bigotry
But I mean like
We can we can let that go because now he's just being a
Dick for no reason
Guys even coming on a Shell Knob like
Stewart's from Revolution
But I don't think it was an elitist
Doing there I think
Like it's almost text me with
This bill is getting introduced because
They're so powerful
State Legislature and make the
That's what I
That voice
I don't understand
Is British accent
This is
I think it was one sounds British
Alright
We have more gas
Plural
Berman
Rights declaration
Because
Alright do you know what
Because we're coming right up
The heels of the British Acts
That was on me
I apologize I appreciate
I accept
My incorrect
I really care about this he's just talking about how
Their people are cracking down on Swiss banking
Workout
No but I would also say that most people
Because of
Banking laws
The only reason to have a Swiss bank account
Is if you want to
Nouveau riche or not
You know what
And it's not even popular anymore
A great way to hide money
Unless you are
And you are about to go.
Or incorporating in Ireland
Over it
530 neon net
Dumb
Super
This might be drama
Okay
College Doctrine
I am 2,000
It's all public
This is sick
But
Pentagon
Wham
1 problems
No I can't think of any problems
I mean I know I can't think of any reason why that would be different also big problem is I read a bunch of interviews with the witch
Lisa bling about this
About
You know the inspiration
Any thinks like that might be
Hinted at
Sister Sister
You know what I mean
Conspiracy theorist with The Shining you're still like
He's raising his eyebrows all the time
Use that I read they were all about the
Ideas of Buddhism quantum physics mathematics
A lot of cyber
Punk influences and stuff like that there's a Akira anime comics
They were saying
Is there a bunch of direct references
Point of people
Kind of Justice remix movie
Alex
Is the idea of
Like it comes in
Into his concept of predictive programming
Where you put up
Movie The
The science-fiction
And it's just preparing the public for the reality
And if that were the case
I would argue
Would have had a
Much easier time making
Cuz if you go look at it
The interview
Hear about what
It took to get that movie made
They were not able to secure funding until they had
Design
Like the idea that they were able to act
And then also had Keanu Reeves signed on
Funding it was a predictive
Programming situation where the government wanted this
Message to get out they probably would have fast-tracked it and made it a lot easier
How did you
Get the funding
Right I think it was Lana
We have to go all over the world
They had to go
Had to be jump through in order to make that move
I'm not into
It's a way that's like
Thank God they did it's the best thing ever but if you think that that was a cakewalk
You are an idiot
Siri
Keanu Reeves works with
That's possible every movie he's made has been predictive programming
Because what else what else has he made
Underground fight movie
Now Doug store does not
That's just Joy
They work for
That's what they work for
What was it
Remember I can't even remember the name
That one is not from the
Okay about that project
I actually emailed the envious track 43 November
No cuz we're eventually going to live in a world where John Wick is
Who isn't going to be
At the end of June
So that's fine
I should say I've Not Seen
Anyway
I'll see you then
Every single person listening to this podcast
Through their headphones on.
They threw their headphones to the ground
Netflix
Rosenthal and Confused
I want to finish it
I realized the other day that I spend a disorder that amount of my time doing things that I can watch
Things that
I'm not a
Clip
We meet again
Legislator
But it is another guy
Did the Texas legislator show up though. Comes in late
But before we meet him
We need a Montana Legend
A discount do they have lunch
But this guy
Learning about this man
Stories in the past
Did I didn't realize he was a PR all
F****** connected god dammit
In just one second
The charts
Now
Wyoming
Are moving
Do you know anything about Jewel bonnick
What are you doing
Montana
Haha
State legislator
I would say probably right around 9
Redwave in Montana
Definitely not whatever it was started
I don't know.
Okay
Well
I'll tell you a little bit about
Don't pull your f******
You just lean back in your chair like you were f******
Stoked about yourself I'm so excited disappointed
Pretty amazing. You're alright but he's lived a f****** life
So many times
The people who were putting forth bees house resolution
End up going nowhere
Who's going to be wild
Because
I generally don't
White dude
Victor Street
He's mighty
So
It's interesting this guy has a bit of a career
Trouble
Joe banach was found guilty of corruption in banned from participating in future elections
And ordered to pay fines over 50
$4,000
Alright
For somebody
You might be asking flula in Brazil and that was all trumped-up bulshit come on
You might be asking what
Some of these Behavior
I would be interested to know I like to read
Bozeman Daily Chronicle article
You are such a big country
You're such a coastal elitist
District Court judge
Corruption in future election
Grateful District Court Judge Gregory republican from Livingston
$60 income
Contributions from tradition partnership
Conservative nonprofit corporation
Which conducted a direct mail campaign
Supportive
61 primary election
The judge
For the appearance of a Grassroots
Campaign
Fealty
The corporation
Carrying out the direct mail campaign
Moorings Realty
Fleet opposition to union bosses 100% in favor of your gun owners right
100% pro-life stance
At 100% off
Opposition for radical Environmental
But that's just standard Republicans.
It's like you didn't even you don't have to swear fealty to that
So much weirder
This is so weird
Buy only the only thing I wrote down was a grand
How quaint
Well
Wait hold on to that thought beautiful
Respond to this allegation
They hate Liberty and they hate conservatives
He called the judge of fraud with the political agenda and said he had no plans
Court admiralty law court because they're also corrupt
My careful
I agree Jabberwocky by pitsky
Courtney Treat Me Like An Enemy of the State because their agenda is socialism
I don't fear them anymore
You don't get attacked by the system unless you stand against Injustice
I have the courage
And I speak for the little people that are powerless
I'm a servant of God
His protection I stand on my integrity
That's all
One defensive man
Defensive state representative
I need to I need to tell you that
This story goes
Oh there is Thursday
13 pretty clear that
Yeah and from the court case
Pretty clear that accepted the illegal campaign funds from the Western
Partnership
Not where the story ends
A 2012 propublica came out with an expose about the wtp West
Tradition partnership
It is downright surreal
And I quote
The boxes landed in the office of the Montana investigator in March 2011
Found in a meth house in Colorado they were somewhat of a mystery holding files on 23
Interstate races in Montana
They were filled with candidates
Paid for by the campaign
High-flyers and bank records from outside spending group
One folder was labeled quote Montana money bomb
The documents pointed to one outside group Springs
A social welfare nonprofit called Western tradition partnership
For the WTF
So are you tracking what's going on here
There's a money bomb
Apparently the wpp is
Record
And all of these conservative politicians in order to eventually later on
The influence influence
The sort of
Get the paperwork that without the box of evidence accidentally mail
Build it to somebody
But it isn't a mess house
You curious
How did wtp
Legally speaking is the
It's against the law for them to
Many investigators and experts who look at the documents
Recovered from The Smokehouse
Say that is a very
Conclusion to come to the WT
Teepee with essential
Pulling the strings of various State Legislature campaign
In Montana and Colorado at
So quote
The group is now locked
I'm going to
With Montana authorities rules
The nonprofit should have read
Political
Have to disclose its donors
WTF
I serious that for March
In the meantime the group is chawla
Same to American tradition partnership
This month
It sent Montana voters a mailer in the form of a newsletter called the Montana Statesman
The claim to be the largest and most trusted news source
The front page of the democratic gubernatorial candidate
They were just like that's not good
Names to this
And then we're going to pretend to be a news organization
Can you show me
Can you use lie like that
I feel like you can't just lie like that right
You can just lie like that like you can just send everybody
Everybody in Chicago if I want if I had enough money I could send them a newspaper
Say it was the most trusted news source in Chicago every never existed before
Chicago I mean you're not wrong
This ended up going to the Supreme Court
And
They won did they win five
Before he died
It was an issue where they're like no
It would infringe on this company's free speech to not be able to give unlimited money
And like
Pretend that they're not actually
Campaign
BottleRock
Show
You might be after cuz this is you know 2010
Stopping my PS what is it
Specifically
The documents 2008
Prudential Grassroots membership
Confidential Grassroots membership development proposal
28 Montana State Legislature
Rode into office
In one hundred percent support of w
Responsible development agenda
Yeah you know me Joel bonnick
Was first
Tootie Montana House of Representatives in 2008
Where he weirdly raised
$9,060
Progressive
For his campaign efforts
In a race where he was running unopposed
That's always going to be a little bit suspicious if you're running unopposed and someone just gives you about 10
Generally speaking
They clearly were
That's one of the reasons
For me to like
We are hook this story back
Because
You could be telling yourself like this happened later in his career Scott corrupt
No no offense in the first place he was from the jump
Note for 10 Grand Am that
Way too low to be able to buy some
You shouldn't be
Look
Show me make a lot of other money through other side Hopper
I don't want to be correct
But there's a number
You know there's probably a number for me
Correct myself or some number I just hope it's enough to feel justifiable
Tulo I want to be corrupt
I mean I want to do an album with Dez Dillinger
Now anyway Jordan that we're going to take those away from
Tire push
F****** weird man
A felon found documents in a meth house
Right
And asked around at the meth house and no one really knew where they came from
Eventually he gets to talk into somebody and they say that they think they were found in a car that someone hits
Accidentally found a treasure Trove of documents
Proving massive corruption on a Statewide scale
Wandering around a meth house right
No no I actually think that they were getting a little bit creative
Night Like This
The dude is he was looking through the document
And he contacted the Democratic people who were being smeared by the WTOP
Will know I don't think so
I want to find
America's first
You should at least get a little
You should get a vehicle 8950
Houston's it to one of the democratic people who was the target of these people's campaign
And they're like
That's f***** up
The Minnesota and the Montana investigators already had an open case about
Like rampant corruption
Escalated
It again appealed to the Supreme Court
If that's okay
Who was the guy who might have stolen the car
Whose car was it was the car stolen or was the guy left
Well a lot of it is
Kind of vague
And I can't really Park
What it is
I read the full propublica story in like trying
Put the pieces of the puzzle together your site
But if you want more information as to why Brett Kavanaugh should never be allowed to BC
Supreme Court Justice
Let's just go with this b******* story of what's goalie has brought upon Humanity
More about jobana
I'm not nearly done nearly done
He's the guy who I talked about before you guys famous for
Always this guy the guy who repeatedly calls himself the living man and accused the judge of not being qualified
This is the guy who win the judge leaves the court
Cuz you so frustrated with him he's like and leaves and goes out to
Another
Contempt of court charge
So you get the charger
Contempt of court for leaving
Handcuffed
I'm taking it to the observation room
The trial I love it
He's the Prosecco
Because he was a lawyer
Because right I don't know if you know this
Sovereign citizens believe that because they use the
The honorific
Title Esquire
That means that they are British nobility
Does esquire originally was a title under British nobility
Part of
Is that the
Federal government
Can give no nobility titles to anybody
And even though Esquire is not
A formal
Title for lawyers
Sometimes they take it on
Weird tradition that
No one really knows exactly why they do it
Sovereign citizen
Hate lawyers
Cuz I work for the British
It's amazing
And this guy Joel
I think literacy is
The good thing
There are times
Where that belief
Because what if I couldn't read maybe we'd all be better
Well know he is a big binders full of things
You claim to read
I don't want him to be able to read
If he's if he's only capable of likes
Whenever he was prosecuted
Design little drawing
Here's what I
Let's go back in time and just destroy the Gutenberg
Alex
I don't want people to be able to
I will be
Whoever's whoever's listening
I want people to be able to read well
That's what I want
Like if you are able to just
Read a sentence
I mean that's good that's a starting point
But if you can't understand what
You are reading
You end up being sovereign
You might as well not be able to read
In the first place
Exactly
We're not. That's a great insult your a waste of literal
I like it
Courtroom
He was holding
Ever associated with me ever
Wait for it
He was hauled into court last year to answer charges
To get to his house but it's area where a forest fire was burning
I've had been evacuated and blocked off due to the emergency
As a devoted
Authority of the police
To keep him away from his private property
Also during his encounter with the officer before he crashed the barrier
Gun
Prosecutor
Such a menacing way that they fled the courtroom
Over the courtroom
No no no
No
What he's declared himself
Music video of this guy
Decreed himself innocent of all the charges
Eminem parentheses
Before the bailiff otherwise brandishing his own before the bailiff to run
The bailiffs told him otherwise
It was like get down I mean
I love the bailiff told him otherwise as opposed to
Did the bailiff being like
F****** dude I'm here all day
Come on man
Guilty and given a fine
Is giving a fee of pine of chips over $1,000
About what you got from the wtpa
10 days in jail
What you didn't end up having
I mean I get like that kind of crazy
If you see that video I wasn't able to find it again but I have seen that video
Is pretty amazing
I don't think the judge and prosecutor
Scooters that have to flee for their in a courtroom
But get killed
Murdered by the cops
For selling
Cigarettes
Don't forget it
He actually stands up on a table
We need to clear some self to Regents goddamnit
Like god dammit little boy
Just want a basketball tournament a hard yet
There's a bunch of room
Bananas
Genocide
Some folks
I know is it like
I know from all his language and I'm the Regent
Discord
Much like his friend the living human who
Bolo ties right
The best
The hardest laugh that I've had
Probably in the last
Few weeks
I was watching the videos of the living man
Horror movie
When is Slender Man a real thing that have
When he has to come back
2 quart getting handcuffed and taken away
Cuz he won't stop interrupting
I cannot stand up do I recognize your Authority
Pick me up as I pick him up
Eminem
I would like you to give my bolo tie to a friend of mine.
So glad he called out the bowl
At least he's a man who knows with him for
Alright
Christ
Are wild
Chillum
Shobhana
Caleb
I love
Whenever we get a guest at pops up like I can really sink my teeth into you like that
You didn't get reelected
Lieutenant governor in 2000
Because
Sexton come down
An advance but he lost
Z's Auto
He is
He's dead
Deprived
Republic
So at this point Alex's bow head
This weirdo on
F*** that was a fresh weirdo
Familiar weirdo on
And
This is
Nuts
Because I think Alex is in a bad mood
From gen-i Temptations interview is not
These are all very pretty
For the most part
The second half of this
Interview is very pretty
But generally when
It's all business
Because it's a commercial
That's why he's there
What's going on with
Good mood and so he just
Freaks out at 10
For a while which is kind of fun
A lot of my guests
I know you're a pushover
And you know that I sell all your gold tonight
I'm texting you for a little while
Dirt bikes
Yep and you take away the guns of the people and then
You gained full control
Let me nuts
That's where you ready for the concentration
I'm sorry I mean they're arresting they're arresting the people that are using guns to defend themselves
And
And letting the criminals out of jail
I mean that's what's going on over there that's what that kind of Logwood do here
I mean we need to have our
Vase over someone's head when they're raping them they don't want
Government is Criminal
I'm sorry Ted
I think that might be one of the commercial breaks where you ended up throwing a chair or something like that
Real mad
Steel pitched
And ruining my day
We hate doing this but this isn't instance of like
You got it
You got to give it up to Alex
Tiny bit
In terms of like
He's not lying about gold prices
He's lying a little bit
Besides that they're over $1,000
I've been up over $1,000 for a little bit during the day
9:50 or so
And that might be a small distinction
Because it never reached
Until like
Like as a stable prices throughout the day
Closing price
Soho
You bought gold in February
And then sold it
Number
Even if you had bought it from
You might have made money
Please because of their like service
Still have made money
We have to talk about
The logistics of gold
Which I still don't
If you're not a failure because
Do it right
Yes
Crazy different arrangement
But yeah
They do have like lockers
When when were looking at this
Chicken
September of 2011 about 8
Announce
I'm so if you bought it when Alex is telling it down there at like
I guess I made $900
From that out
Over 2 years
Yeah cuz I'm terrible
If you're going to drop that money
You have to have money
You know what I mean
Like
We are getting a 100%
Return
12:00
After
But like
You would have made nine
A hundred dollars on this
You cashed out
In September of
Covid-19
Hundred dollar invest
If you're not buying in bulk
If you're not buying in bulk that's not a meaningful transaction over to
Anyway
To the consumers that are probably listening
You know I'm saying
Like Ira
Well I'm telling you the gold is rising
And they're not lying about that
They are kind of lying about
Is it that means
Did the game
To buy any meaningful
Cuz like you know whatever money
You have around like I say you have $300 tip
$300
At this point
Sturtevant
And then
2 years later
It's worth six
Is that really life-changing
Even though the
Prices gone up
Double
It's not really no to buy a lot of it
For that
To make a
So
Screwing over these
Buying a little bit
Get out of the wiper
Understand the gold Commodities Market
No matter how many times you explain it to me
I'm still going to get stuck on like it's for very very
Bromas Sunken Treasures
Understand understand how it makes any sense
You know
Traders
Maybe on like our goals
Something like that and I do not understand this
When we could do
Sometime
Okay
One piece that I think
We've been remiss and talk
The EPA massive
Ambassador
It makes sense if you're a billionaire
Gold coin
Vampiric Lisa
Exactly
But at the same time
Like
Pretty similar
To a stock
It's already
Like even if let's say
The First trillion-dollar Corporation stock
Years ago you really a investor
Make enough money off of
Them being a trillion-dollar company
In order for it to make any sense for you to do so in the
First appointed inaccessible to most of Alex
The funnel
Conduit with which they
Gideon is a shade
Business called Mike
So they're screwed on both ends
I got the third thing today
Is it
This is exactly what you would expect
This track upward of gold
It what you would
Expectancy after
A financial crash
Let you know after 10
People are panicking a little bit
Gold prices
Ashley wood rot
Has gold prices are just f****** gold prices
It seemed almost untethered
Guess what you see
A lot of time
Price
And some of that scares
A little bit artificial
Always talking about how it's really hard to get it done
Well it's not because the government doesn't want you to have a gun
Because all you're creating all this
Sphere in everyone's going in buying gone yet and then there's no more
Versiti is why Venezuela has a 1 million percent
Inflation rate right now is because OPAC
And other oils
Producers have
Artificially deflated the prices
Productive
Tobacco
What he's doing
Whether or not
It's not just him
This gold
When there is
Beer in when there's anxiety
So what they do is they end up having a lot of pee
People who are buying gold
And that makes the price
The goal to go up
Yonce
In the same way that they're artificially creating
This
Pretend scarcity of gun
They are
Feeding into
The scarcity
Gold
That ends up raising the bicycle
It's kind of a selfie
Perpetuating
Ends up hurting
The customers of Midas resource
I just
So
Let me get this
Really really straight like down from the very bottom
Gold is expensive because the shot
Well and because of it
Electronics
They're a bunch of like a cables
And stuff like that
We need gold
For gold hasn't like a semiconductor
There are like
Functional reason
Gold
Is it because of his idea that it
Invaluable
For a long time
You still really
Sharp
I know about the hunt for escape
But that's not the primary driver of the right
Is that there are people come from
A million years ago whenever it was like
This is shining and there's not a ton of
Easier to get
It was hard to get
For you and I but
The companies who could get it
Controlled
Supply
Write in order to raise them
Did everybody kind of know that our economy is built on
Magic
I think
I think I want
The idea that our economy is just like
Smoke and mirrors
And if everybody just realized it like a refrigerator was more valuable than gold we would
Lose our minds crazy
Flex Foundation
I was in
Freshman soccer
My buddy
About my buddy John
I found out that his dad
Carnival
And it was usable
The government
Need him not gross
Because if
Did grow thing
Reply
Corn prices
And so in order to
To offset
The government pays a lot
I'm so he had the thought of
Weather
Out there and we would go
I guess his dad
We kill a deer every now and again
Immediately
Loser
Add note like because of
Best of that idea
But that was part of
Modifying
Price
Vic goes into
The food
2 gold
Obvious
Getting everything
It's not an evil man
It's a stabilizing
It's that I think that I think that that is an important line to draw because
Any manipulation
Could be seen as.
No I get that but
Even that manipulation is a test
Acknowledgement of the meaninglessness of the entire
We are doing this
Because we know
That if you know
That this all means nothing
Assignment
Like you know
90%
Society appointment
We all live in imaginary world
Because of maintain
Status quo in a pleasurable way forever
Ideal
Where is pleasurable comfortable
Sad forever
You hope to get
Get to that point
With the
The illusions of society
Because whatever
I don't think any of this
Where is Chicago at
South suburbs
Giving you the Orland Park
Call PizzaMan
I think I might have met him
Local jokes means local
Local
530 neon net
We have now
A very large story
But Alex is going
To get into he has a big narrative
But
Intero Iowa
Pause real quick
I don't know if you've heard but Alex gets going
Yeah
I don't know why
I tried to track through the episode of some sort I think YouTube
He's just got
You think he's just playing his Michael Jordan Flu Game
Like he's bringing it even though his is
His skill level isn't at the level of
16/2 hours a day
He's fighting
45 minutes
I actually
Probably would be able to find out exactly I know his address.
Bulshit
Figure it out
So
Training
Careful
The National Guard
The purpose of
They suspected weapons dealer
According to Sergeant Mike Notch Readiness NCO for Alpha Company
Marine Corps officer
Nothing
In Virginia
Northwest
They are zoman they are I read this article that he's talking about
To find weapons dealer
Living
Really close to Alex Jones
Crossing the Rubicon going to solve all of our problems to call the Omni
Barrio
Is from
Daily Times Herald probably but he's actually reading
Not daylight
Doesn't really backup
Inflamed
Role-playing operation where
Small town
In this case Arcadia Iowa
Who's playing an illegal gun dealer
Like
So is he
Is he like a half-orc
No
Straight human
Street view
That kind of role playing in role-play
Okay so give me a rundown of his skills and abilities
Charisma charisma
He's a rogue
I don't play these games all I wish I had a child
Business
That means that his wisdom has very pretty
Is going to come into this town
And whichever has it
Consent be involved in the role play
The issue is it the Iowa National Guard needs
Train but quote
There are no active duty bases in Iowa
Right
In order to get that large neighborhoods
Steeler Citi Field
We have to be creative in partner with our community
So the way the roleplay would go is like let's say we live
We say no we don't want to be involved
Right
Inconvenience of tiny bit
While they're running around town doing that
Write this is a
But where are they
Just go around the roadblock on the grill
So do they
Start with a hundred gold pieces
Scizor
Like 50
Be prohibitively
Okay alright
Alright
Not in the mood
Not in the mood for RPG talk
I'm not I got no references man
I'm going to let it go
Just felt the country
Where you couldn't
That's just all I needed I just needed it for my soul
Feels like that very often.
This is fun
I would
Love it
Point out to like the way it works
Is that like the people
Who are
Disregard
Officers were coming into the town
Don't know
The person inserted is
Who's playing the dealer
I'm so they'll go to the
The houses that can
Ml like knock on the door and other picture and like
Missguided
The house but like
All right it's like a whole fun party
But also the wave
Runza
The searching of the home
One of the things they're training
There is
How to do that
Respectfully
Because when you're in Wartime overseas
You might not
Treat that foreign citizen with
Respect
So doing it with
Fellow citizens
To do this safely and responsibly you treat people like people because you
The people who look like that training for
I wish it wasn't like that
If it is you
Your first time
Catching a house let's say
When is
Hi state
You might
Really fuk up
I would much rather
People in America
Do a fake search of their house
To train troops
Do not murder foreign citizen
No I don't think
Is anything wrong with this
And I mean
All of the fears that Alex has certainly haven't been
Materialized
Question
Do you have to
Recorded them as well
No okay well then
Probably a Ramada Inn
More about this situation
I'm here
Mostly because
Cuz he doesn't funny
They're going to spend 4440 something billion quote for the
Us Media
Brainwashing
Activate italics chapter
And I've got it on video.
Internet
I would also be like
Look what you know what we're doing
That guy is trying to stir ship
Happening in Austin
Agreed please come search my house
And then pretend it was a real searches like that
Asked about whether or not you have done
That's just an editorial like
Bums me out to this place
Where
Kind of agree with no I know it's tough because
Glamorise in the military is f****** weird
I was at the Cubs game watching the game and they had this whole life
This is your other servicemen everybody everybody
Stood up and f****** Standing Ovation didn't like
F*** all of you what are you f****** idiots doing do you not understand what the f*** is going on here
Biscuitville military and you a million dollars to advertise you loving
How much we murder everybody all over the world what are you f****** idiots doing
Canvases
The secondary points
He has no business being right about things that don't matter when he's gone by the thing
Well
Something like that
And I don't mean new in terms of like we have
Before
You still in a lot of gold
Various
Boy
Surly bikes
I want to bring up
I'm like wait
Kids already been on the show when Alex screamed at him
What's going on here it's complete in Woodstock tonight
Never
Ted and Bob not be a personal deal
They're always running to me
Weird what are they
Still on hold no he's not. What the f***
It is also a half an hour later in the
Alex Rambles a tongue about that Iowa shed
National Guard on
Guys like
Because the guy is just like
That no
No I've been a member of the Iowa National Guard for 20-something years
In Public Communication
Know what you're saying
National Guard
Trying to
Issaquah
The National Guard has now been
Federal
How is
Well yes
We exist as a federal entity
When we are activated
Gargos
We are in some sort of
Defensive capability
Yes we become
Come-a Federline
10% of the time we are under the direct
Action of governor
Of whatever state we are the
So we're kind of like Federal
Yeah
And he keep
Bring that up
Malik has nowhere to go with it
Any complete
Conquers all
His narrative
Like the idea that these people are all just
Under the sway of the
Yeah which is essentially
Black president going to make white people feel
It doesn't
Really really
Disappointing interview
I thought about cutting
Some clips from just
But it wasn't
Although
I do wish I had
Just One Last clip
Like literally
Right at 4 hour mark the end of the show
Alex
Chucky here's the exit music playing
God is still on the phone I don't know how
Hung up yet
No regrets
Vietnam is very polite
I'm So at the end of it I was like well you've been lied to and I'm sorry that I'm sorry that I
Rehiring hopefully one day you'll see the light to joining us
Replaced
Nicely done
Go out to the Dismount is what that is
We are in
Michelle Bob chapek
Ted's already
Talking about what are they
Well let me out who is a Nazi
Save a fashion statement real
CIA operative
Alright work at the massage so
And got a pickle of it is real realize then
Now that's what they want that's what they want
Holyshit
Did you ask
Crazy Bob
Nut
Well I never really expected the settlement to the
Guy guy
Netanyahu's a Nazi
Wow
That's bananas
Crazy
Game recognize game
Directions to Aberdeen
Multiple
Essentially
You know you know when you know when enough is in power
You do not not but not your monkey
I appreciate you
That's not a negative one
That's good bro go push
Alex makes
What I can
Can only describe
Something good I'm so glad
I'm looking at the March 23rd 1770
I'm so glad he did
Oh yeah
What happened
I know that he's better at Reading
Then he is
Present
Would you call that the war is inevitable speech when it's really the
Give me liberty or give
Give me
The Warriors
Inevitable War inevitable
Andy says Give me liberty or give me death
Because the word
Isn't it
No
No I remember that speech
Give me liberty or give me death
Think of the word totally
Even that totally that was a weird thing to say
#inevitable paragraph
It's an answer to extenuate the matter piece
Is actually begun the next Gale that sweeps from North will bring our ears.
Clash of resounding arms
Our Brethren may already be in the field
Here idle
What is a gentleman
What would they have
If life is so dear our peace so sweet as to be purchased
Purchased at the price
Chains and slavery
Almighty God
I know not what course others may take but as for me Give me liberty or give me death
Paragraphs
It's not bad it is inevitable and also the title is the war
But be there
All like
Look he's not wrong
All I care about
A couple words
You did fine
You did good so we'll give you two or three more read-throughs in your f******
Yeah just voice over
Not everything kind of comes full circle
Bob Chapman International forecaster. Composting check the side out
Information near Nashville forecast
Thank you so much
Thank you Alex
See you next week bye-bye
Coming back on
No
Cuz he comes back
And Bob is gone now
The guy who has to make you afraid of everything needs
To come on before the guy who tells you what
The solution to everything
There is no doubt that Bob spent the last appearance on the market
Incredibles
Before that clip
I think it's so
It's not I've never heard
In my life
He brought Ted on
Just yell at him for a little bit
We got to talk about gold price
Dude after the break
I've been
After
They do the thing that they do
All the time
Maybe Bob was at
The f****** store
Kroger
Humanic that's when Joel banach called
Called in 5 minutes yeah there is some sort
Most reasonable situation here is Bob was
Sidelines
And then
For whatever reason
I mean what is this
Like if you if you
You consider the episodes on Saturday
He's probably the 45th episode that I've listened to
2 from 2009
And every time Bob Chapman is on
It's to set up 10
Saudi ideas
Kind of f*** that game up a little bit on this one episode is
You like that
Alex G
I feel bad
I'm telling you this world is going to hell in a handbasket 10
We are waiting for
Calling and texting you are living in a world
He's going to he's not called in yet
Stock at the Kroger
Kroger
I don't know
Yeah
Call Kroger
For no reason
We both pulled Kroger
Kroger in Idaho
For whatever reason
I have
My brother and Coronavirus
Columbus Ohio
When I told ya
I could have said
Tonight's grocery chain in Central Missouri
Jewel-Osco
What about it
What about
Anyway
Snook
We could we could sell your double coupon
I would have said but they are out of business
Jjp
I always
Feel like there's
Business
So this
There's another guy
It was the text
Does legislator
Who's still
Coming up
But also throughout the show
Teasing that there's a surprise guest
That he's hoping can come on
Okay turns out that guy
All right but
Get that guy's friend
Alex I can come on I'm still here I've been on hold this entire goddamn show
Steve from Chicago
This guy is
Friend
Guess that Alex hope
Skit on rich
Disappointing yourself
Friend very disappointed
I was trying to make it work out
Mailed it out
From now from England he was supposed to get out today
What is happening right now
Good afternoon Alex is nice to be with you
Actually as we speak
Anthony John Hill has been released
And he was allowed
He was actually Ransom
For the sum of 3500 euros
Again this is for sending out a
DVD
Are you sure it's not just
Isabel
For sending out a DVD
Who he sent
A jury
A77
Jury tampering
There is there's like a law
Voila juries in deliberation
You can't
Influence them because that would be some sort of like
Find out how to contact
To the judge
All this is like
Looks
That's just bad jury tampering
Kind of
Real Jason
Two jury harassment
If you got to go to the
You got to find out what jurors kind of react with
What facial expression
And then only send it to those jurors after doing a lot of
Every search and finding out where they live
Come on man you all right
I'm just I'm not angry about the tempering I'm angry about the encompass
Guy friend
Anthony John Hill
You made this documentary called
And what's interesting about that is if there's a group of 7/7 bombings
Text called the set on July 7th
Truth campaign
Let this to say about his.
As far as I can
Materials in the ripple effect
Available for a good
Two years so I'm curious as to why
This film has been really
They believe that the official account of the sub
Tire website catalog mysterious inconsistent
And irresponsible or something
He'll make the news
There's literally no way that she's in prison for revealing
Forbidden information
It's because he was jury tampering even the skeptic
Are like
You're wrong
Yep
Even to people who make us believe that we're wrong
That's how wrong you are
Now you cannot I will actually
To give you mine
Now I would have left
And said this is irrelevant
To talk about this guy
Friend
But
This guy
And his other friend
Dance
My list
Bad
Have a good rest you got mine is 1
He is the guy who we talked about in the past
Who calls himself guwahati
Yep
Couple episodes
Return to a Goddamn
This
If this goes down ass and Wormhole I will tell you that right now.
So that's the first reason that epicenter
Text breakstone
And not only that but
For people that don't know much about him
This is the same man who spent the last 10 years
Trying to raise the Ark of the Covenant
In Ireland and knows the exact location of the
Tyrrhenian Margate
Down to a 6 ft by
Put G2
And they're not about to let him dig it
Because they know
It is there and they know that he would be the one to bring it up
British Lord
Research
Could you save Alex
Good good cover-up
Bass
And he also knows where the Subterranean entrance.
I'm going to say this right now
That was the
Best job Alex
Does Everett
Ever ever
That was incredible engaged with that
None at all and
I barely notice
I barely noticed we had been watching the show for a long
If we hadn't been listening for the whole time out of in life
Is where the mergaite is I've never realized
He just
Pivot it away with
No
Was that
Project
From Chicago safe
You didn't cut it off immediately
The Strokes
Group
It's much like jackass
First episode
I let myself
Absorb
It's like it's like how Paul is
If you're going to make a reference I get to make
Find
Brit-brat loggerhead
For now
We sorted that out
Nothing is wrong
Denmark here
So now we move on
If you don't tell bobcat mix
Stick roller coaster
The friend of God
Frankly I'm mad that that wasn't what he led with
I'm so now we get to the last
Clips from this guy
He is Leo Burma
The guy from the legislature
At the top of the show
Not to be confused with wonderful person and friend of the show Leah Berman
Fantastic
Atomic
Chicago
She's not one of those
Chicago Chicago
So here's Leo Berman
Martial law
ER
Alex
Play can't be with you at actually next week I'm going to
Defile another Reza
And now that resolution
Same thing however it's going to cover both the 9th
And the Tenth Amendment
The US Constitution
Great I mean they're already in the concert
Institution
They're already in
You need to do that
Nobody
It's absurd
Okay
You know the 9th and 10th Revolution
You think you know the 9th
You think
This ain't your daddy's next
Has anybody ever covered them for you
Has anybody ever written into law cover of the 9th Amendment
Nobody ever really sat down and wrote
How long was
White desk
Shcr
Not very long
Not very long I can read the whole thing if you want
Compare it with the length of the war
But it's all good
Using this longer
At least this
In Texas distance
Really funny
I looked into
I am too like a lot of those other ones
What about these house resolution
Concurrent resolution
The committee never got brought for a vote that's okay
This one
Cuz it's
Well
Well they passed
Because it was required
To have a bunch of rewrite
And so what it ended up doing is this
Basically
Davis talked about like
So we like being a part of
The United States
That's everything
Resolve the House of Representatives
Concurring
That the 81st legislature of the
Reaffirmed
Both are one and indivisible National
Union
$90 one and indivisible
Resolved that the clerk of the House of Representatives
Is direct
Send a copy of this resolution
The president of the United States of America
The vice president of the United States of America
The governor of
Sister State as a
Expression
Of the affection for R1
National and indivisible Union
I heard that
And all I heard was Tex
Secede from the Union
And declares its sovereignty
No my buddy it's the opposite
Henry Wright
Being like no no no
We're not going to vote Yes for this
Until you rewrite it
All this is a declaration of love for the one
National electronic elevation of love
Never heard of states secede more
If the Opera
It is them saying that we are sending this as a proclamation that we love.
No
Where are you guys
We love all of you
The Attorney General from all of these days
To get a note
I want the president
You got to know God
We love you
Also
All the time
Meaning of this house
Resolution is
Hey
The federal government is
Because the big part of the Constitution
The idea that like we know what happened
Kansas Bill gets a touchdown
To being like we loved
This is really awesome
But unfortunately Leo
Talkin
He said something
I want to see like damn I want to
N-word
Stuck out
And if you're going to mandate anything on the state of Texas
If it's not fully
U.s.
The tution
We're not going to do it
And the reason we're doing this with taking a
Because of the
We understand there's going to be a federal handgun registration
We don't want
To know where all of our guns are here in Texas
What's the word
Show me to go with ham
Call Manny
I'm going to go with
Him
Did you not want the government to know or did you not want
Helio
You're showing whatever it is you're showing
Sniffles and four of them
F****** face
Are obvious
This is bananas
Man that's a mess
Him
We don't want
That made me say so he would have said that obviously during the any other way
I want to find out about Leo Berman what's up with him
I bet this goes down a very short Rabbit Hole of a man who is loves his family
Has never committed any gross
I regret to inform you
I don't regret that
2011 Texas monthly
After he appeared on CNN's combative
Leo Berman
Is a birther
What produces birth certificate
It will take someone like Donald Trump to really determine whether the president has pulled the greatest swindle
The greatest hoax in the history of the United States
What
What year was
Cuz that was when Trump was on his birth or s***
You start leading the charge along with now
I know that all the big monsters I know.
Just don't
Understand
The ideas
Human being
I would say it would
Someone like Donna
Pittsburgh
Statement really to make
Because it would take someone would like Donald Trump
Lack of character
Ciro
Truther or anything like that
Jesse would take a pure cycle
It would take
F****** Unabomber
Serial killer
To have zero human empathy or actions whatsoever
In order to reveal this
It would take Leo Berman
Uline garbage
Pilum
F****** s***
It would take you
Pulling this b******* on National Television
For everybody
Is monthly to be like oh finally
8th kind of the bad version
Like what
Project onto Donald Trump
Add version of that like
Are you a bad enough dude to save
The president yeah a little bit
Sponsored encouraging Texas
Taurus 2011
I like it
He also made Headlines by claiming Court the judge
Also in England
The use of sharia law is being allowed as well
This claim was made almost
Creeping Sharia
Christian missionaries were
The annual Arabic International
Festival
What if
Discover
Nocuous
Soto
What creeping Sharia and
The Christians were charged with disorderly conduct after police received
Volunteer
Working at the raft by the group
It wasn't even the Muslims or the area
It was a question of course
Coming to America
31 more clipped ear to listen to
Pile of s***
And also there's another bill a federal hate-crimes bill
Open up your old test
The Bible and read the book of Acts
That homosexuality is an abomination
Wikipedia charged with crime under that bill and Robbie what's happening
Canada right now
Could have been the wind
Stop the Constitution
Don't tell us about it
Don't ask us to do it
Milk
I just never liked was the Bible in the
Like you're talkin about government
It's like that one of your first go to Zyzz
The book of Exodus
Hey look
This old ass book
Abomination
Is that a hate crime
I would say
No ice
If you're privately enjoying
I don't give a s***
Enjoy your life
If your
When you're yelling it at
People that it becomes an issue
You know what
Bring out that it is
To lay with another man is an abomination
But if someone who right
Part of the LGB
Community
Baby you are harassing them
Being a dick around privately believe it I wish you would
What you going to do
That's your right
To believe whatever
So
I would
I've never read any
Hate crime
Legislation
You doing something to someone else
This idea of like
Go fuc yourself
Hello fear
Yeah but I ran out of steam.
Little bit
That is exactly what is going on
I don't
Okay
What is this what is this guy thinking is how is going how is this supposed
Do it so if you think if you
How can you both believe that the constitution is absolute
The Bible in Exodus
Committing hate crimes
As being an overreach under the
This doesn't make any
Read any book
This makes no sense
This is
Wheatley
Separated
I'd like Concepts from all directions
Somehow being
Like I don't understand
He'll let gay people
A washer doesn't make any
F****** sense
You think you need to engage one of the realities
Or something like that the only thing that person
To yell at gate
And I think I can't
Why are you protecting you make it
I don't understand
Well I do understand is because on some level they realize that other human beings are like
You can't do that anymore
So they have to say
But since you are going to let me do it
I have to create some sort of Fantastical reasoning
That might convince you
As to why I should be able
Feelings about themselves
You know other people's emotions
Feel-Rite
They still care about themselves not being able to
Do do certain things
When's like
Legislation
They don't
See you later the sensitive like understanding what
Yeah
Field
So because they can
Experience any kind of
For other human beings all they can
Experience
Is
So
Used to be able to
And nobody would stop
So you're taking something away from me
Even though
You're not
And I shouldn't have been doing it in the first place
And I can totally live without it
Do they
These people know that like
Their lives
Be unchanged
Lego
Like how many people are there
How many people who are like
All the worst thing that you can call
White person is racist
And if that's in a slur against us
How many people
But how many of them Regis realize like
No you can just be fine
Like your day wouldn't
I know
Bother you with it
I think that
Modernaire
So much
The advice
It is
Letgo
But it's not that
But that is
Like what you're saying these
Help
People who were like
Just realized
Stop being
Everything would be
Yeah but that really isn't letting
Bingo
They don't know they're holding on
And that's the same
For a lot of people with
Unresolved
Issues
Play Simple
I don't care anymore
There's a process UK
Can go through
Involved
Go
Shaking off the bird
Whatever you don't need any
Red erasing old soft
Where are the senior operator
System
But it did
You don't need it
Run your computer
One of them big
Misogyny
Is one of them big
Those are those are homophobia those aren't those are
System
I've been updated
Because they're their Antiquated and they're glitching
They're glitching and people
Computers and date
I kind of
Actually I'm going to go back to an argument that Alex made my metaphor
I think you did a great job
I'm going to go
Back to Ashley
Weirdly enough something out
In order to explain why
It is not something that they can just
What Alex said whenever he was talking about
Bring it back
These so-called changes in pigs
He was saying that
People in power are using it
Divide us
Which is
Frustrating
Because that is
It's frustrating that Alex
Can say that
It is a true thing
And yet he's the person who's doing it
Play correctly pointing out
Like part of the reason that
He's because
All the problems
Complains about correct
Play like post-reconstruction are you know you don't want poor white people and black
People to get to
Because then they're going to realize
Together
The poor
The poor White
People can hang on to the fact that hey no matter how poor we are
No matter how much we starve
At least we're not black
So that's what all this racism that people
Can't let go of it
Is it like
Look
I'm actually a living a shity life
And the only thing that brings me up
Security
Is that
At least I'm not
Gay
Great you know
I agree that that might be sort of a psychological
But
Time
That doesn't
Really
Substantiv
You know like if you are using that to like soda.
You let it go
The reality of your life whatever your paycheck
Is whatever your right situation
Doesn't actually
Right maybe you have to find new friends
Hang out with those
Text
Adjust
Have no friends
You know
Meet new people
Other than that
No I don't buy this
Yeah
I don't know
I don't know either
Anyway all this.
For fun
Shout out to
Providing me with
Nice story about meth houses
Pacific
Record
American American number one
It's active now
If you are listening and you want to leave us a message
You can do it anytime
Weird thought
Save it in your phone
Save it in your phone is a number you can just like if you're out drunk
He wanted to leave it a drunk message
Go for it
Is revolutionary
World
Go to our Facebook group go home
Apparently Dan is going to be working to get us on
Spotify
Could get on but they gave me a real serious warning message
That like
If you have any
Copyrighted material
We will throw you right off
Spotify under fair use
He plays a lot of music he has contract
I know from posting things
YouTube
Like
We posted the clip
Along with the highway
And I got a message
On YouTube
If we monetize until all the money goes to
Like our CIA
Play Highwaymen
Clip in that player
It's not like
Christmas too many Highwaymen
So I think you were in trouble there
Stitcher
Maybe
In time but they have to figure out how to hook it all up
Do
All agree
Is it yours
Yeah I know you
You don't like it
No I don't really mind
It's a challenge
For much longer
Okay
I'd like to hear it
And then I
Alright
But go ahead
Vestavia
Of the fremen
Okay
They have been oppressed
As well as the imperialist
Such a long time
You know what this is a very important story
That you need to hear about right now
So the fremen
Only because their land egg
It's a whole morality talenti it's basically an allegory for the imperialist
Polonius treated the Native Americans
My biggest issue is that Leo Berman
Tingles
Alexandra Thurston color