Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
You heard up top
The sound
Cork popping
Absolutely ears to the globalist
It's a mild celebration
The thing the trends that we're seeing are going exactly the direction we expect
I speculated that
Friday would be a
We break down for Alex
Wonderful
I want to give a little bit of baby
Play Michelle
Okay
You don't know anything about Dolores
But
I know a lot about Infowars you too much info
One day we're going to figure out
How to do this smooth
Anyway the show is me explaining what's happened
Infowars at
One day in the life of Alex
We're just really excited
Very prompt
So
Covering today
Write a March
In the Life of Alex Jones
In the greater World outside of him
Is that everything
Coming out
To be not accurate
And all of these
Allies
Is that he had built up around
Themself
Address
These things
Head on
He can't talk about the session
Except
To say
You was doing his job
Like that
Address
The fact that
Met with
Russian ambassador
Be in Cleveland
And he traveled there
Fun
What's a great idea
He's legally there in the capacity as a trump surrogate
Service
Because there's no wiggle room
Kushner's
Situation with
Why the f*** was your son-in-law in a meeting with Flynn
And the Russians
Listen to me because the whole like why the f*** is your son-in-law anywhere near this
Totally
Kennesaw the israel-palestine conflict
Can address the Kushner situation he can't dress Carter page
He can to try to pages
He may ask
Actually be a deer in
Like I literally
He was on one of those new shows on MSNBC anyway
I will not deny that I met the Ambassador
Meanwhile
You smiling
Laika
The canary
He's a man with
The secret
But it's not a secret that most people know what it is
He's being set up to be the Fall Guy
I don't know about that
Situation
I think that he might be able to
To pull it off
And get away with a lot of money
And run away song
Somewhere I think
So we're saying the Carter page is our Kaiser Sosa that's what's that
He looks kind of like Kevin Spacey
Alex Jones also cannot address the issues with manafort
Ukraine
Address
Suspicious timing
About the GOP sauce
Its position on Ukraine
It wasn't
Suspicious he literally said
They said that the Trump
Trump himself said we need to soft in the
Soft
Ukraine meetings with Russian
Sew-ins
Chico's
Buckwild
Turbo lie mode
Everywhere
And to that extent
This episode
Getting an order for the clips
To go in
It's going to be a little
Scattershot in Kalamazoo
Should be representative of what it is that you listen to
I think that's exactly how the
A-listers to get a taste of what it's like
Alex Jones
I unfortunately don't have these in chronological order
Starting to learn
Is the
The first hour of Alex
Is usually born
OK Google
Good sour
First hour super boring
Will it start when you got to warm up
Yeah it's been warming up let's warm ourselves up
With a little out of
Bubbles are open women
Documents about it
They're super run tool
I just love that
So uncool
You're just going to find one
Drop every episode
I have a second one
F*** those stupid liberal
Liberals
I like sounds like a five-year-old
Does he does
Big lies
But he throws out
Is breaking news
About Obama
Have you grab you use the
Department of Justice
Steal billions of dollars to give to act
Groups
Breaking news
Glue
Here's a who who's that
Here's his narrative
Okay
It's worse than we thought
In Florida
Which department high-level operative
Any mail
On the ground
Cause riots
The division
Fox News is reporting and they've got the documents
Michelle Whaley
I mean that's a very solid
I tried to hunt down
Give deep as I could following the link
Fix the paper
But it never really ended up getting anywhere so
But I'll get i'll get here
Let's finish this and then I'll get to
Water
You're so giddy
Obama transferred billions of dollars
To Eric Holder
And the Department of Justice we're getting the video report right now
Cam right now
Obama doj funded billions to liberal activist group
Billions of dollars that is so illegal
Department give money
The group secretly.
Political groups
Got the government funding and sound
Kill cops
This is the government
Local and state governments
Is any the truth everything I covered yesterday
Turn of Obama
Like not even a little not even a little colonel there he's got more fear-mongering
But Obama's coming
Just to break this down what do you talking about
He's acting like this is breaking news and it's not
It can't pause
Just lose billions
The dollars until a year after your present
There's an article that I found on Breitbart
About this from 2015
Solid news source
Years old
He's coming out with this now and making it sound like the biggest deal in the world breaking news
F***** Well it's worse than we thought
It's exactly what we thought it's exactly the same
Dope is exactly what we thought even references
B Bank of America and what's the other one
Citibank
Even reference
The situation Envy article
It's a little bit weird but it's definitely not illegal
One of the things is when the government sues an organization
Appeasement
When they get payouts it doesn't go to the
Usually the payout
And donated
To charitable causes
Or things like that
Universal across-the-board it's not how all of the payout
When you lose against the government
But in instances
This money is going to
Radical liberal
Service Groups
Which which ones are they
Blacklivesmatter
Maybe some of the harshest
Fringe parts of it
But that's not what the group is about
You know to say that is
Is wildly responsive
Very racist
The types of groups that are getting money are like the HUD housing
Which is great especially when
Housing is part of the issue that the
These Banks
People for clothes
Yeah
30 million dollars that year of that money that was
From Citibank
America
Go to the HUD
The Housing and Urban Development Housing Council directly to the people that they
Yeah but it's
I understand now I know
Directly
To the people cuz the people have no standing in court
They aren't the one
You are suing
These organizations
Yeah
That's why I said it's a little bit murky
There should be a XXX victim status
Court
In this case
Go to groups like the house
Council or the other one
I was the Legal Services Corporation
Which helps
Provide
Legal Services
Does the under-privileged
I would also prefer a more ironic as opposed to just a monetary settlement out of log homes
Yeah
Bank of America
They get your husband
Like that
They live there now
60 poor people get to live in your mansion
Exactly
The story is it broke
Conservative
Paranoia blog
A year-and-a-half
Old is not news
It's not real and it's not true
Great
Distraction cuz nobody's paid attention to that nobody paid attention because it was announced
Story then
So you bring it up now and
It's like we've got this bombshell but nobody cared about nobody cares about and nobody will ever
Website for
To do is for every episode
Provide links
Do all of the
Documentation
Of the things that debunk what he saying people could hear us if you like why should I believe you
Write totally fair
What about his marriage breaking up most
That works
Mentor
A text
Facts about Obama here
Not not super
Something to get my pass
He's coming
And he's ready to roll
This is the New York Times you name it like he's God
From president impeachment resignation
Quotes New York time with them admitting
They leaked the intelligence documents
If you sat
Perfect did you see what he did there I hope you're pointing out what I was going to run out
They are reporting
He's ready to roll
It seemed like they were Altos
Out-of-context quotes from Politico in New York Times articles and then
Twisted to be like Obama's got a bunker and he's going to be the
The shadow dark government
They really don't want to
I use that terminology
Exactly what they do
Just
I believe
Is the better that better turn there
Is that if you were writing that down
You have to put quotes
Around what the New York
Attributed to the New York Times
Then quotes around what Paltrow
Attributed to Paul Joseph
You you can't
See him hold up his fingers
Free for life
He's playing Mad Libs with the truth
Excited to see what's going
To happen
In terms of this all falling apart
Because I really don't know what Alex Jones does when his team loses
I don't know if he's going
Call for a revolution like
People on the street
That is a possible outcome
There's other than he would
Open
I think it might be illegal
Syndicated radio show
Legal situations about to come up to them
I don't know if there's
Enough time for
Time to get off the trumpet
Like it no time is he does he have to have some
Catalyst
Trump does
I thought you was for Liberty
Prosperity
But I don't know what that would be
Makes up
That's true
Where's my where's my war games on what Alex Jones
Alex Jones
See the writing on the wall
Cease what happened
His
Narrative then is
Another phone call
Time I realized
Find me the whole time
Rusted out
You know what you can really ride Alex Jones for so long before Alex
Jones
Is it out I disagree that's
But would I think it would be is I have had phone calls with unnamed high up
Sources
The government
Okay
General
Flame
I think he brings this up in a clip we're going to play
Later he believes
But everyone was painting
Flynn unfairly is a Russian spy
This I'm out of here
And he was just so offended that people thought he was a spy that's right
America it's not even worth
The coverage right right right
She's like the Russian Ambassador they're giving him a lot of like
Recruiter with zero
Turning
Trump is a Russian agent
The issue is that
They had these conversations
A long time ago
Policy changes
When they were not in office
And if they were in office
It would have been fine
Inflate the idea of like
Chuck Schumer met with them
It's completely not the
Conversation
A lot
Think that Jeff
The Russian part of it is the
Piedmont with of the French
Ambassador
We're getting into
About Obama
I kind of want to see what Obama does
I want to see Obama's this morning on Saturday morning
We did a bunch of stuff about Obama tapping his phone
That he got the information
From a
Yep
Through a spokesman responded
Everybody
Who knows anything knows
Then I mean that there was probable cause
Sabbag
The Trump Tower
Is that
Under under the law
That we know of
Whether or not
Because the Feist Accord is basically a rubber stamp
Well.
You're probably right
Green light for the one
I think it might have some
If there was a bug
She is f***
Tax return
If it was a bug there was probable cause
Signed off on it
Is there
You the f****** lunatic
Who believes everything he reads on Breitbart another problem
The other problem
There though
Is that
Either way
If it's real or not
He's a f******
But
We are talking too much
Not getting to the clips so let's get back
This is the first instance on this
Michelle
Alex Jones
Co-hosts with him throughout most of the show cuz
You need the babies
Okay
And it's interesting because I also
Start to feel a little pity
It's similar to
Key for the devil
He also has he has to stand next to next to him
Who's the guy who we haven't brought up in the pattern
Just kind of boring
I don't really know how to do
Describing is a soda
Bland
No
I think he's better
Is a little more engaging
David
He just has like a newscaster who happen
Comes to work at
Infowars
Surprise
I'm not saying pain center of him
Lycamobile
And then for a bit
Owen Shroyer is in for a little bit
Black ice
Sucks like I is the worst
But we deal with Owen Shroyer
Single
Fairly similar to our friend Betty Ryan
And then also he's just
Like in the same way to Paul Joseph Watson
Is so manipulative about
Social
Just Warriors
Progressive
Causes
Bullying
He is using that same
Camp
Young
Attractive dudes
Alright
I just f****** ear alittle bit on the year using your powers
Evil kind of motor
Anyway I feel about Leanne Mack
Millie Weaver
I don't find her all that attractive
Back for a minute
They sent her out to a protest
I bet they had a bunch
Clips of people like
Telling her to turn off
The camera I don't use this footage
Don't put me on here I don't want to talk to
Weather like
Hugo
Clown she literally is dressed up like Trump
This is about
More stuff about that. Slush fund
Alex
Legit
Freaking out
Great
3 billion to the social justice Warriors
Not social dress
Warrior cause
Is a lot of it was
Housing Council
Stuff like that
Literally no.
Invitation that any of that money went to the end of the black lives matter
Antifa stuff nothing none of that is
Go to that
I can't prove it either way
Absolutely no proof
Claiming it is alive
Prima facie
Social justice
Flip a coin
Do you want to try and get poor people housing
How's the homeless your social justice
Just Warriors
You can get angry at Social
Well it's not because it's a trick try to get you into communism would get you into socialism which isn't real
It's just a globalist
Slavery
Spiel
Hundreds of millions of dollars in some cases was 386 billion
Wells Fargo
4 billion stolen
Then they take the money and they give it to social justice Warriors the country take our guns
Upon upon upon crime they shut off almost 1,000
Don't forget Obamacare
Don't forget it
That's Darren mcbreen and he is he's just sitting there the entire time like
He's doing little takes to the camera and stuff.
Out here too
Thunder stop
Smart
Is he listening
Everybody whatever you here
You got to finish your drink
Weather
Tell me I'm fat.
I'm the opposite.
Sentence
If
What do you think about them
What do you think the plan is
He does not use what is it what is it
She comes from the rainbow smash
Improv good normal losses
Possibly thing
Text to Alex Jones as it goes like
Ruined
My
Possible career test
I can't go anywhere else
Like I might say
Have been on Infowars as a reporter
I'm done the only opportunity the only option I have
Yes one
The only
Jettisoning he could possibly do is start his own like YouTube channel
And kind of go
A little while
Play cuz there's no credibility anywhere to be found
If he does try to get a job at like
Call MSNBC
They're going to take it
Play that clip
Also he brought up this
Fake news this weird narrative
You were confused at the 20th Century Fox theme.
We're so lucky that there's the internet though because I'm thinking a lot of that lot of what we're seeing right now is Backlash for 4
Trump being elected
And getting Trump elected
The internet
That would probably be looking at a Jeb Bush presidency or God forbid
Let's not start
They celebrated the course we all celebrated as soon as Trump was elected and now the battle has just begun
He goes a little bit further about their role and Trump
Election
Later
You want to make the argument you're not a propaganda
Number why Admiral got ripped
Like the idea behind
The fake news
Meme or the term is
Propaganda
It's not about like
All these
These weird websites
Say like
If you
This weird berries
It's not a
Just called propaganda
To me is more like
700 tallest terrorizes Infowars Church
Yeah but the onion or something like that
Berry or something like that
Alright Alex does propaganda
He doesn't
Understand that that's what people are saying
And so he
Dutifully serves
Every propaganda
NTR
The fake stream media
There's just no Escape calling the propaganda
I got to find this
Equip your cuz like I said everything is out of order
And then call Trump a liar don't call him he's making up alternative facts
1880 for every single day
Making up words
Newspeak b*******
Buganda it's Americana
Articles
From The New York Times
20th Century Fox used fake news to publicize a new movie called
A cure for wellness
Put up
Fake site
They were filled with advertisements for their movies
With
Knowing that people would repost these articles
Rapunzel movies
But just get the
Disseminated
Irresponsible
No I don't either
But there
Trying to
Lander Infowars or anything like that
Rationalization
Confirm this article
A cure for wellness is a movie about a fake
That makes
People sticker
Their statement said
As a part of this
Campaign
Health and Wellness
Wish.com
Was created and we partnered with a fake news
Creator to publish fake news
Fox News
Alex
A cure for wellness was directed by Gore
Skiing Stars
And Jason
Isaac
Both made jokes online about the phenomenon fake news
The film opens on Friday and has received
Mostly negative reviews
What critic
Of the Daily News
Describe it's Preposterous Gothic nonsense
Sound more interesting
Preposterous
Samina
Clue was set in Transylvania
Preposterous
You get with like we're making a mountain out of a mole cat
Yeah
If I work all this article also
Has a list of
A bunch of the headline
Are they are they wildly obvious
In there fake attitude
Stopwatch
Leaked Lady Gaga halftime performance
The future Muslim tribute
Kind of believable in NFL
Done that maybe California legislature to
Considered abortion
So basically they just have these Hot Topic but you shoes
And they know that people are going to be like
Read this s***
You don't like I agree with you 100% that it's bad
It's dangerous
Yeah it's definitely not weed it out and they're like
We add more as a sort of parody
Performance arts
Okay
Marketing I'm not okay with it
But if you take Essex out of it
I'm really smart it's a really smart idea
Alex is treating it as like
This is proof
That everybody every everything
20th Century Fox
It's made by the globalist
The establishment
Discredit Infowars
Which is on The Cutting Edge
And that's not
Situation at all
Diesel
He doesn't even understand the story he's telling
Darren mcbreen
Is on the show to break this news it's just
I love I love how he's on the show to break this news that has spoken all of 10
The end where
Pivot
The conversation weirdly to say
Play some really bad stuff about CIA
Exactly right the mainstream media has been caught red-handed
Create a fake News website
That's not that and they're completely made up stories that were spread online
People on Facebook and Twitter
Because
Alex
And feel like the real thing they look like traditional mainstream media websites
That's a fair point but I never saw any of
What's the weather forecast for maybe but not within our Circle
Somebody's going to share some dumps
The champagne start
Feel real good right about now
Check out the names of some of these websites
Salt Lake City Guardian the Houston leader
Sacramento dispatch
New York morning post and the Indianapolis Gazette
I guess it looks and feels like a legitimate website
Trump spotted at Swiss Resort
The election
Inasmuch as like
That last one
Especially is really yours
Possible to discredit Infowars or anything like that it's strictly
Ted mark
No we don't
Really need help from them
And it's not the mainstream media it's a corporation its threat
Can Corporation to realize me
Connect
Studio
Wiqui Gore verbinski made a hot pile of garbage
Some guy
Probably came up with
You know what
Everyone shares bulshit online
What if we could use
Totally get it in the head
With all these ads on these sites that
Said that good
Goodmark
Did that guy will not
Is not want to be the one who's on that the dogs
Also like
I didn't see any of these websites cuz they've all been taken down
Course good but I would have to ask
Person
I know there's not many of us left
But if you went to the website
God dammit
Thanks for this cure for wellness little strange
I don't know if I trust what's going on here
Is everybody
I can't tell from these answer this looks like preposterous.
Go back to the Clippers
It's so great when he turns on the CIA oh my God
Sacramento dispatch
A news organization that does
Not exist there's no such thing
California Federal support in midst of a natural....
That's their clickbait
What happens if you don't got one side
On Facebook and Twitter
64 popping up a lot of people were sharing them
Totally oblivious to the fact that they were sharing
And spreading fake news
Here's the headline
Mcbreen has Dumb Friends
The story
Because his friends as well
Curated friend very well either
I've gotten back on Facebook just for messaging purposes but
Couple time
And I'm so glad that I unfollowed almost everybody before I left
Facebook
Cuz now if I sign in
It's just Bobby bud
It's just Chicago Comedian Bobby bugs
Just jump on after jump on when he's going to post me this fake news break
And it turns out that these websites were created by 20th
Century Fox
Wow
You got there
Stories about
Alaska
Directions run drudgereport directions run Alex Jones
Directions run Jeff sessions the Russians run Nigel farage
The Chick-fil-A in foreign countries
That would be legal back then
Had three thousand plus
CIA agents imbedded in mainstream media growing up in Texas and Dallas
You couldn't swing a stick
Was electronic back then
Best and brightest
You were the top of your classes Seattle
And
My dad
Alex Jones come from a family of snitches
Classified information
You don't want to deal with that
Alex
You are not being recruited by the sea
He was younger
Yoked
You wouldn't imagine
F******
Hot I hate that I'm saying these very positive body
Anger at Alex
His argument is there they're in control of it
Agencies
Domestically
Filled with all the Liberals and social justice Warriors that have been packed in there under Obama and under Bill Clinton and under
And they literally are Waging War against us
To run wise against Trump
As even in their own examples most of them we're not
Trolley Hop On
One of them is California gives tax cut
Abortion
Keep in mind that question
Find out about that
I want to know where you found out about it also keep in mind
Spring break
Nobody else
Promoting a new movie that's coming out called cure for wellness
But like I said
This is I think it's more than that
Because
It's not slander also it's more than that
Promoting a movie
Also
Oh my God I'm making up for some Admiral Ship
20th Century Fox
Two fake news combat their fake news
Yeah
Okay
We did it
Bye-bye is snow blown
Holding out of fake article not telling you it's at the bottom
I can't confirm or deny whether it didn't
Because you really should
That's inappropriate
That isn't
Well
The onion doesn't have
How to say
At the bottom of every article and by the way this is not
Information
This article
It's absolutely
Well New York Times cover did Washington Post cover
List
We're going back up
People
We know where you got it
That trumps order the CIA
All the soldiers all the operatives
But they're in there with all the
Trouble
Hold on
The stories the stories about to tell is hilarious
It didn't happen and Alex
Even like
Alright it's so great
Just enjoy this b*******
And then literally analyst
Wood carved American flag
But they're the ones in there
Alex does
What kind of lame like
Plane ticket
All of his b
To go away what the s*** was that
Utter Insanity American flag
Yes and then they were like wait till Obama
Got them the wood carved America
Trump
What was the reveal at the end of that there was a receipt for the reveal was
Foundation chicken neck
These gifts and then they're like oh
Used government money it's a bribe
I want
People stay behind and show them a receipt that proved
Trump paid for it with his own money
April 8th couldn't get them
With Miss
What
Play-Doh poop
Okay
If you didn't hear what could possibly what kind of water
Aveda near from Trump I don't know where that could have come from
AC coils
Dumbass
Also that the analysts are there
And they're excited
Thrilled
Trump
Because he bought them a total of like $100 worth
Wooden American flag Americana
They were going to licking their lips
Using government funds
Knick knack
And we got
Supposed to be all over this
So stupid
Bric-a-brac
Know that
White also
If I know me
They were prochnow
Probably very disappointed
Not to have receipt
Steve their own breaker
Bric-a-brac as well I'm not sure if
It's unclear from the clip
Nobody knows about
I should be talking about
Right
Could not
Possibly be lower let's be honest only kind of makes Trump look good
Good
It's actually kind of funny it's a funny story
If there was documentation of these chicken Nick analyst
Freaking out
Kind of indicate that there is some truth
That there is a schism
Give me a community
Some people want to take him down and some don't
What anyway
Interesting so far off course
Time to pay the bill
We got to go to an adherent
I think there's some indication
We did sell out of all the Ronald Reagan
Donald Trump lithograph
We're about to sell out of Tennessee
Firearms lowers rimforest
With public reborn 45th president of today's
Donald J Trump
They're only a couple hundred left to those of the one out of 1000
It is a collector's item
You drill this out this is your airline this is for you that's how you legally have it with the ATF letter there
Metal check your local laws it's all there infowarsstore.com
Yeah
Check your local laws
Probably don't even know if that letter is real
A policy wonk would probably know the local laws
Actually all of the analysts inside and forwards were really excited
They're like
We finally got you on this one Alex Jones
I love you so awesome
Towards
So yeah I don't
I don't know if
If it's legal or not I don't really care
I know that it's only a matter of time
Before they sell guns
If it is legal
The
Idea of a human being
With a republic Reborn
Donald Trump
Camp gun
Lady pantsed
Scariest
Use to murder you and I
What is an ironic
Swing about fftt makes it through this this whole thing
Republic 2
Donald Trump
Who's my second favorite
D&C after delivery
Either the conditioner
Cuz Alex Jones
I think it's talk
Talking about himself a little bit and
Miss clip
That wasn't an ironic
That was a fitting
Ironic does not mean
How to engage
Globalist
Okay
The only winning move is to not play
They set the rules they set up a
Cultural construct
That breaks the social
Contract
Any is anti-human
Slavery based
Technocracy base
Throughout its entire
System
Specific
Dixie laid out at the end there necessarily or him talking about himself
But that don't engage
Do they have a fake world
Sacrifice for us
Quite literally
All he's ever done is engaged
Global that's right
What movie not one-on-one
Maybe not actually debating
Putting himself as the the opponent
Okay so so git ology of the
Basically his boys don't do what I've done
My life
To think there are those quiet moment
Those moments where he's just like
Just laying in bed with a soft dick
Waiting for the second Super male to kick in
Movies like
Was it worth it
Did I am I cuz I think I might
The idea that he never had that moment of doubt
Terrified
Me more than anything
Yeah
To be an imposition
We're doing this now I have a moment
Are we going to be in terrible moments of insecurity
Sometimes
Very fast
Trust
Myself
Is just the natural byproduct of it is like
He's cool with weed legalization
I think billionaires are a group of global
Maybe we're wrong
Stuff
30 and then the big
Corner city being that we are
Aggressively self-aware
To the point that even with abs
Absolutely 100% right
We will
Really yell at ourselves like
Maybe wrong
Baby Alive critical
Skills
Digging we're doing into him
We do ten times more to ourselves
Anyway
The next freakout videos
This one's good also
The Russians
Situation
Now my note that I have here is
David Knight
Studio
For this clip
David Knight
The fuckout starts
You just can't get a word in
This is on
Believer
We just keep learning more and more and more and more meanwhile the big Scandal go to this town
Mini more life
Specifically
Tops
Just revealed why it is it what is okay and what is that what do you mean
She had all of these meetings
Add all of these meetings Obama had all these
Sessions only has two and then he lied about it
Wilshire
Is the Russian
Based on what
And it's not true
How he would respond
Attorney General
About it
These things came out
Which is even crazier because then
Denies having nut
Which is very suspicious he doesn't answer the question
Different
Look Brown
Surrogate before
Used campaign funds
Nobody else
Committed
His record
Silver price
Things are about
The contact
Text Matt
Right now
And the lying part is a big
I have both
Come out
Address to these sort of
Argument
What he's yelling about Alice's yelling about is about a post on Drudge
The Trump also saw and tweeted about you
You talk about how we need to invest
It's like okay you don't understand how logic
You think you're doing a syllogism here you're not
FedEx
Colon
Iran
The most logical person in the world
Years of college
Most-loved
Understand
How logicworks
But I'm a little bit
No problem
Is impressed by you knowing about love
You can't brag about learning about logic
Nobody's like
I just I don't even like you
You saying that word
I just need to be clear that ice I have studied
System of logic and how it works
And when people misuse it it drives me
Me crazy which is a big reason why we're doing the show
Look it's like I think one of the big problems with him
Is that he looks like a cold war-era spy
He looks like the word from
I'm not your body shame Russia
They're derusha
You should meet with the Russian Ambassador and I'm sure he's a cool dude
How many parties
You're the guy who comes over here and
And he's got great vodka and I'll be very stereotypical
I bet he would
Hangouts
What was discussed
And why
That's also super big
Obfuscated all he wants about other people meeting with someone with
Schumer and Pelosi of both come out in
Try to
Explain right there's a difference
Between public meetings
Private
There's a difference about
To explain there's a reason they're two different words
What's the difference between being a sitting senator in your official capacity that the media is
Informed about meeting with
Diplomat
Being
Legally speaking
Do to your youth
Campaign funds
Trump surrogate for the campaign at the time
Foreign affairs
So like
That would be it would be
Pantanal that's
Foreign services
Even in the
If you just said oh yeah I'm at with him a couple of times
Address
Nope
If you just said
I would take very seriously and whatever information
Comes out I will deal with impartial
Unfairly
If you if you just
Even if the news comes with Russian
He has not perjured himself
What's up committed zero felony
They're everybody's so stupid
He put himself behind the 8-ball
Dog that ever goes out
CheapTickets
Bespoke
Poorly again
And I didn't have a chance
Inline
Like interest once he falls I don't know who's that
It's all good
Come down
The sessions
The administration
Into the hole
How did Kushner
Could be next
Mandala
You seem like a text
Such a dick
Yeah
The point where Alex
Really freaks out
Just my favorite thing in the world
You lied you met with a Russian
AJ
The judge
Again you didn't answer the question that was stupid
But this doesn't make any sense
Directions
Again use campaign funds to go to the RNC which takes him outside of his role is
Contacts
Being a part of the campaign
Alex is lying
Any truth
While Hillary and our people are all the Russian Chinese payroll
Irishman
Blew up on
He didn't
He's talked about that are always whatever he says
I watch that episode it was the one where it was
This is a clip from
This was
Weldon interview
Jerome corsi
Was over Skype
Welding
Some of this stuff
He believes
Hillary is
Surrogate
I need
Information that he was going to come out with
Did he come out with it
No do it seems really important for that second
He had a meeting
To get to
At the beginning of the interview
Time with me I know you have a meeting to get to
He stormed is not mad after interview
Hillary works
Chinese and that his family had been
Threatened
In the past
Do you have a meeting
So you did have polonium
All right now
Anyway
That's not
Characterization of that interview with her 12 in is just natural
Threatened was the Vegas f****** thing I've ever heard in my life
All that works out about even his family being threatened in the past
So like
I'm threatened
Making a f****** Mountain out of a molehill.
And
Explicitly
Say what
He's talking about how he's full of s***
Like you just angry
Classified
So now we're
Okay
I assume
Is a Chinese,
But she was also paid off by the Russian
Yeah
So will the Russians thing is you talking about
Representative
There was
Canadian company
They have access to
20% of
Yeah yeah yeah
Wasn't that whenever Trump
There's like
Geranium
Nuclear weapons out of it.
Yeah but it was a deal
It was a deal between a Canadian company that owned these resources that happened to be in our country
Russian company
Quia formality
Have no authority to stop it
Is I understand from everything I read up on the deal
She's the only person the only person who could have actually been like no absolutely not have been
Have
And I assume that's what he saying about
These she's bought off by Russia
But she's actually
Chinese
How
Hilarious would it
What'd happened
Instead
Is if Hillary got elected
Instead of this
Chaos with Russia
China run
Happy wild screwed no matter what happen
I would love to
Hillary
First thing on my agenda
The rest of those frogs gay
More present
That pad in their first address
Schedule
Hillary's a Chinese
Has come out to their Chinese
Directions
Route of control
Storamerica
And a lobbyist
And the government
Jones & the lifters are they broadcasting
2 plan
Swimming and water
Into something that it wasn't as you point out he said yeah
I'm in Washington about the campaign
The same thing is true when this was he's talking to him
The best
He's clearly feeding off of Alex Jones
You can see in all of their face
Places
On in another Studio
And we're both looking
They both were like
Do you think
He is
Gotten a switch from a tree
You're right that's
So
Domino's one ended with a nice lie
It's just now he's not in an official capacity
We can
Take a little bit of a step back
In terms of investigating him
SB investigation
Proceed
All of his eyes are part of
No one is
Like being
He's not in the government anymore
Security
Ahead
That's why people are like okay we can breathe little sigh of relief
This guy who's
Clearly
Vincent
Fuckedupshit
He's not in the government
We can deal with him
Adorama
So that's why it feels like people
Care
Because we have other people we need to get out of that government
Real heart
Is there any adult
I've been reading
Constitution
Go Bragh
Can we
All agree
To add an amendment
That just says like
Sometimes
If we get enough votes
We're going to do a do-over election
Can we get a do-over closet
The Constitution
Idea of being able to vote no confidence
Confidence
I think we'll be a really good person we're still relying on the public
Like to know what's going on in there the one
If I can put Trump in
The first place
Based on strict
Numbers
Here's more s*** about session
What happened
Has the u.s. ranking Senator on the armed services committee is the ranking Republican
Directions
Absolutely I've met with that other top generals time
Just as Europe met with us
File
The last few years
I posted that your Senate session
These are public meetings are completely aboveboard
Chuck Schumer
Map of the very same person
Public works together right now
And the Republican Party
Donald Trump
I said just let us have planned
We'll get him off your back
Chat with the Democrats
Dead matter
Who's this patriotic at Americana as basically John Wayne
I believe that's code for white
Being the handlers of the Democrats
He's talking about like
Stuff that happened
VY qwaint
Durance word
Okay
Right
Sure sure great point
Not really
But also the Democrats were
Against
Civil rights at 1
Yeah
So
You know the whole parties
History of the parties they
As a party
Both of them have gone so far back
Fourth
Absolutely
And people have switched from one to the other that
At the boat you know if you replaced both parts
See how your place to sale your place of that
At the end of all of that is
Still the same boat
Even your body
Yeah exactly
Every 7 years your a completely different
To stay like all the Democrats
These are the same as
Is the Democrats
Today it's stupid
Make an argument and appeal to 70 years ago
Years ago you're just
I mean you're not even
Trying
If you were to make an
An argument
About how
Let's say
Slavery still has effects
Jackson you're like wow
I wasn't
Slave owners
Set the timer
It's it's like
Even if you make your point
Successful
It doesn't matter
Who cares
Also
He pitches
One of his nice Fanta
Role playing
Scenarios
Was in there
Pent
And a republic
Came up to Trump
And they were like
Give us blind
Is this
As if it's the f****** that the people in Judea being like give us Barabbas
The floor and then rising up out of the Shadows you're just going
Everything will be fine if you give them Flynn
No
Maybe maybe sacrifice to the
Advisers are
Are f******
Stupid
Baby
If you have
If you had a bad day
Let's
We talked about
The MoMA
It happened
Or right before that happen
That was a terrible
Strategic move
Not admit of
Anything other than bad
That's not like
Someone who had his ear possibly
By then
No f****** biennium
Anyway
Pescatur next clip
This is a about
Tennessee a running Steam on the Alex Jones freakout
Gauge with anything real because if he does
Talk like if he's actually
Do you have to talk about all that stuff we talked
The kushners
Situation situation
The world shrinking
Himself
He has to get to strike
Anything
Comes up to fit
The bulshit narrative
And yet
Coming to this with all the anger of the world's ranking in on
It's really it's really kind of fun
Tweets on Saturday morning
BBC paranoia and anger Alameda
Kim Wilde
Susan Tyrrell
Is if Trump
Any good advice
Any good
Advisors
He wouldn't have
Phone
All the time
According to
60 switch
So this clip is Alex responding to a video
Did someone posted online
A guy in Muslim Garb in the UK
Getting into a little bit of an altercation with with a
I watch this video about 20 times
Is not at all with Alex describes
But I'll let him say his piece
Before I describe what is actually going on
Does Cana
Shift gears once he's called the
He's talking about the guy they have a little bit of an argument and this
This very huge British guy
Kohl's
The Muslim Guy racist
Cuz he's like
Clipper his outfit
I feel bad even making this up
Well you know
We don't have all the information
But this guy is is like
Say you look like
Pork
To the guy
And that's what Alex is
I mean
Does he look like pork
Sure he's the other white meat
Anyway
Is okay
Alright
Set up
This is the power of this made
Understand
The mayor of London
So he then runs over to the woman
That's a short clip but it just everything
This guy anyone United States
This guy would have been laid out his jaw broken
Just like that
What about smashing really fast when you get a woman
Allow women
To be attacked
Because
The new
Culture
Is the be a coward that lays down
Alex
Unless you're a mass of other liberals
Then you attract women
You will know them because they attack women whether their islamist
Whether they are
Weather blacklivesmatter
They Revel in Cafe
Cat sanctuary
Interesting
The Blue Cat Cafe cats
I was so thrown off by that that I had to look it up
Cafe
And Austin Texas
Okay go and drink coffee
Hang out with cats
And I believe as I understand you're able to adopt
Society
Hangout
OK Google
It's like a it's like a dick spot for cat
Which is
Obviously what are you talkin about
It's breaking news
This is no other news breaking news
Was greeted by
The protesters who were rallying against landlords FF
Real estate
The cafe
Is adjacent to the site of the
Traversal demolition
Pinata store jumper
Which is also
It's f****** East Austin
Something you could really have a pinata store and its controversial that it's being demolished
Who was the author
And I love you so much
I love you
So much Austin
This pinata store Jumpoline was also owned by fnf
Is now being used
For the cafes parking
SMS run by Jordan
Darius Fisher
Southwest party in March
A greater food trailer and
As I understand it
Facebook
Austin
Incredibly weird because my parents live there
Is kind of involved in a lot of
Used to be very
Anti-iraq war protest
He's engaged
Community
And there is a massive problem of Ghent
Vacation around.
Of course there's a lot of building
That are being put in areas
Destruction
Classically
Diverse business
Supremacist
Pinata store
Crazy
Massage
What would market research could
Could you possibly have done
For a pinata
World stores are on every block
If a pinata and a latte and I'm good to go
I have no use for it but I will
This thing about them
Attacking the cats
Actuary is really about
The
Problem
Of gentrification in Austin
And a bunch
Independent businesses
And low-income housing
Asteroid
How to put up condos
Parking lots
For sxsw
Like how the
F****** world
My dad is
Some community
Boards I don't know
I can't I can't speak
Specifically about what he does
Cuz I don't know
I just don't know
Neighbors read up on
In terms of Maine
Businesses
The neighborhood threat
Stop
That's what this is about
Did they hit a woman
No no
Did Muslims
He's reference
Singer that tripped out
Women
So why did you bring up the f******
I just want
Protesting
Demolition
Of the business next door and unfortunately unfortunately
Slightly
People who wanted to go to
Cafe
But it's
They were chanting outside your cat's if your tea on the ruins of Jumpoline
I'm an ulcer
F*** you
Save East Austin also wear a lot of
The worst
Yeah
Arthur and the argument of the protesters
Chris were
Animal Welfare work.
Don't mean it's excused
From accountability to
Community that obviously is going
Through struggle
Which is
Now the cat sanctuary their argument was
We wish for the best
For the business owners
Nextdoor
That isn't like
It's not art
It's not our job to
System
That's the world we live in
Auntie
FIFA black black protesters are attacking
Cuz they hate nice
They hate these cats
He says more about it
But I just wanted you to have a
And protesting every week
In the past
Put super glue
In Bowling in whatever's weakest
Dexter spirit
And so this is what the government of England Thanksgiving
About
That's what I was most interested in trades
But like I said I watch this video
Exactly what was going on
Okay so basically if there's two cars
Muslim guys car is
The guy has
Just his car
So there is probably a minor fender-bender
Starts with the Muslim gentleman
Take a picture of the guys license
Play I'm getting harassed by the wife
Okay tell her we're off to a good start
In supporting Alex Jones
Conclude exactly what the white guy says
But
I can assume it's
I'm sure it's offensive
It's just hey excuse me sir I would love to
To pay for the damage
To your car
Disseminate
Seems
Unrepentant
About a cat
Sounds like a
It starts with the Muslim guy says I'm allowed in this country
So we can assume that the first thing the white
Is it something along the lines of
I bet the original clip
Was never
I bet
There's a longer version on someone's phone
That isn't online
Of course
Because
Evil Muslim
He's got his car hit
And this guy is being a total
SD level of eggs
Essential fear that that guy has
Nice to have
Now
Every single day
Is
If I ever lived
With that
Level of
People are
All day everyday on TV
Shouting about how I'm
Personal way
I would not wish to lose my s***
Even if that guy was
Spine
Terrified
I'd like you're reacting like a like
So how you could only find it posted
On account
That were like
See how evil Muslims are
Nobody had it posted in like a positive light
But if you actually watch the clip
The only active
Violence
He does
You look like
Pork scholarly and that's kind of fun
How is that racist
I think I feel like that's more about
I told you seems like it's more like
Even if you want to make the argument that it's racist
That that's like signaling you know like hey
I'm not offended either because I know that if I were in the situation
I would approach
I'm so sorry I hit your car
Which it clearly is in the video
He ends up knocking the girls phone camera
Which is italics
Knox her camera and because of how
Videotaping work
Whenever you hit a phone it looks like someone
It doesn't she was doing
Well then
Immediately not on Hurst
Little bit of a Down
He's like
Deteriorate
And the lady start saying
Obviously obviously isn't response to him being like I'm allowed in this country
Of course
You're not allowed
I'm here you're not white
He is offended by that goes up to her
I can't tell exactly
Exactly if you was going to
Just spit on her or if he's just so worked up
He ends up like a loogie in a little on himself
And then he was like
Get that phone out
Okay anything wrong
Yeah I mean
I used to like them
Worst thing I can
I'd like a mile
Estimation the worst part of that is the whole
Brost
Like at any time he did
Being like
F*** you guys I've got your license
Play time just
Can I get the f*** out
The only the only thing I can think of
Dude that's not Muslim toxic masculinity
That's just dude
Something that they say is b*******
No more dude
Always comes back for Alex
It is an attack on his masculinity
It is sexual for him
In some ways
I don't understand I agree with you that
There is a better way to have dealt
Yeah but I don't want to be mad at all
In the perfect
Quiet
Situation
Here is the best
Probable way to do
And somebody had just come up to me
And exploited the very
Been told every single day
On TV is coming for them
A reasonable and logic
F****** crazy
Blaming a religion for that
F*** you let's go to a couple of quick lies
This one is about the radio station
Trump said the fake media
They are
R-Truth
Well they're losing control of the media because of Independent Media because of the internet
I mean these Theon six big corporations that control 90% of everything you read and wassergass Road
Capture the internet they need to gain control of the internet is so that's what they're trying to do with this as well
Done.
Because I don't mind
Whatever
Also don't let those because there are not as many of them anymore
Episodes as recent as a week or two ago Alex's
I'm still work with
Gcn Genesis
Communication Network
Clearly lying
If you want to take some heat off
That the Genesis communication Network
He's a gold sale scam
The his morph
Into a
Steel sales exactly
He wants to take a little bit of distance between the two but if you're paying attention
We are seeing Network
Yeah and his bumpers at comeback commercial he said
He's trying to go both ways
I like your style
I like is boldface bullshittery
Serious but new ones
We learned boycotted
Local area and then the globalist even find out
Termite 170er top was not listening
Here's another lie
4000 radio station
Oh s*** are we
Literally every second radio station
Anyway
T-Mobile store
David Knight does make a good point about the factory
Six corporations that own everything
Let's agree wasn't exactly
They are getting rid of net neutrality
Break
Really ironic
If all of the things
All of this blows over
Trump gets his whole agenda
Envy
Cuz of that Alex Jones gets kicked off
Most ironic thing like
Ancient Greek style
Video about that
You laughing or is Icarus flew too close
The entire play
But I
Like this idea that like
If you don't list the affiliates
Kick us out
When I was younger
How easy is it
Define those affiliate
With your local
You could just ask around when I was about to
20 or so
Maybe a little bit older than that
Timelines a little vague
College ugly
Anyway
Michael Savage it started saying a bunch of really violently
Muslim
Anti-muslim
My dad is a religious studies
Professor and is very plugged in with all the
Community
And along with the Muslim Community in town
He was involved
The campaign
To get Michael Savage
Taken off of the local radio
Okay it was a Grassroots
Local things that happen
Weather
We don't want this
Make money off of
Him we will not
We don't want to be a part of this
Yeah it's awful
I got the show taken off the air
Bright but so his argument that it's the globalist
Coming in and like targeting little local radio stations
The globalist
Because he doesn't listen
The globalists with their Nayan in
Resources
Still can't
Right
Alex Jones listen
And I don't believe for a second I like radio stations
Are but if yours if you like he was saying that very protest
You just described
Is threatened
Getting the radio
Yeah that's what he said he would probably
Forces
Stop listening then because there are a lot fewer
Yes absolutely
It's a community that feels threatened
Offended
For no reason
Will not put up
They have every right to
Yeah which is great
It's a fight for dignity you dumb f***
It's a knowledge Warfare fight
So they killed seven million hours
As a colleague takes place the next few decades
Rival them properly and show them that you've been subservient
Some of the chores for the diseases they been
Dumping out pouring out upon us
He sounds
Like right now
He sounds depressed like this whole nightmare scenarios
Him being like
A million laughs
Is there a
They're going to take out 85
Percent of my money
He's being the writing on the wall in this
And it's in the tone of voice that he's got right here
Doesn't matter what's really important
This idea to Ted Turner
Kill 80%
What was the first thing you said was Ted
Turner I didn't hear that part I just started my weekend
That's a good point
Turner wants to kill 80% of the population
What
Explain
Just give a reason
Ted Turner
The Atlanta Braves
God
He didn't interview
Diu did an interview with Audubon magazine
Where he says he's an ideal population for the world would be
About a 95% reduction
Which is even more it
Stream Middletown
If you just
Snippet it sounds
Is actually
How we should have cheese that
Is over the neck
Encourage everyone
Children
In order to Mass
Sibley decrees
Horizon popular
Which is a terrible idea as we already soft
Bree is the worst
What
It's not about killing tons of
People it's just about being bored
Judicious in terms of our future who wants to kill 85%
The population
He could have gone with literally any of Bill Burr special
Now
Another thing
Very clearly
Is
All of it has to be
He says
How old is ideas would have to be implemented
Voluntarily
I don't want to force people
To do these things
So that
Alex
Beyond that still a weird interview to give every weird
I want to get to that
Is crazy
That's right I forgot about
It's not a nefarious I want to kill the world argument
As much as it is a crazy person
With a
Fairly reasonable idea that could never be implemented
Great
Terrible
What are my favorite quotes is he was talking about his wife
And he was saying like
I believe the question was about his
Make a frequent marriages
You know at the end of the day
You live
Like I never did anything with any kids
Are slightly paraphraser great quote
You know what. All of us could say we're so lucky
Lexus. What are you saying is right that you want to insult him by getting married multiple times
Yeah you know who committed
Very few
D'usse
Well I mean to Ted Turner
We we are coming up again
Because I don't get out before too long
Okay
Caught a couple clips
But aren't import
Get to the next one where I think Alex
What is
Talking about
Himself
This is
Another Mass
Distraction
From the real issue
This is stupid
Very
Very very
So stupid
Manipulatives
You're coming up
A TV viewers
But
Degenerative male or female
Augmentation orb
Face surgeries
I'm a celebrity
A carnival show Freak Show
Not being part of the human system
Humans look at you and think there's something wrong with you
Mental illness
This is another psychic
To further accelerate the downfall of civilization
Organize together recognize the disease in the filled the poison breaks the poison Berry
Others not to eat of them
And enjoy from the poison fruit in the Garden of Eden we have the knowledge of good it's the
That's okay so let me try and
Get through
Bounce from point-to-point the weather
So 100
100 genders
People are getting body modification
Things to look like aliens there was a story that came out about a guy
Got surgery to become a genderless alien
Yeah
Uncle that I'm fine with it but it's also texted media does not
He just read transmission
Describing but also the media.
Hold up that case
How awesome
Isaac most of the reports about are much like
Girls you got plans
Or
Willingly castrate
Themselves as well
Instances of people never even acknowledged the existence of men who would win
Can we do that
Understand
Whatsoever
It's not that
Cuz you can't
Have the knowledge of good without the knowledge of evil in the knowledge of evil without the knowledge
You don't get one or the other you have to
To have both
So once again understand his own theology
At all
He also
In a little bit here
He's going to
Really make it
It's just
Stupid distraction
There was someone who got surgery
To publicize themselves
Prayers
What a blizzard out of 7 billion people we got one guy who's like I want to be an alien that's a really good
The government has to pay for it
Also I've been I had
To start looking up tattoo
Turner quotes
I'm a very good thinker
Sometimes grabbed the wrong word
I say something I didn't think through attic
Secretly I mean
Just didn't sit up there and read them off the
Teleprompter you know
I Winged It
Sounds like a drive-in
Alex Jones would absolutely love
Really really good
And I'm not
Sometimes
If people get all the sex they can handle their so happy
I mean
You never feel aggressive after you've just gotten laid right
What's the sex forever solution to all the world's problems
I am in totality
And somehow inexplicably
And this is
This isn't 78
Okay this is prior to all of these other quotes
Ted Turner
Where's the upside in opening your mouth
Actually 8
A cautionary Tale
40 years later
Ted Turner
In the guardian virtually Limitless
That might be because he owns a bunch of fight is Buffalo
Anyway
And wrong
This in this clip Alex speculate
Basically most crime is
Isn't real
Human Liberty
Also
I got to stop it because we have another f******
Song it's awesome
But he uses which is George Strait
Amarillo by Morning
Read about today
What song is this
He's remastered why does Hilo
He's a man of many contradictions
How could you not
Attorney General
Amarillo
Any symptoms get knocked out
But
Infowars.com has a story I haven't seen anybody else report
Southway to Jewish Community Center
People
We've seen an uptick
It could be coincidence
Correlation is not causation
We all know this
However
It does seem highly likely
Set an
An anti-semitic rhetoric
In the White House
Does kind of say that it involves anti-semites all over the place literally the first
Presidents
Since World War II
To not mention the Jews when talking about the Holocaust
And what
They feel like
Now we got one of our own in there
Also in the same way that Alex Jones
Feels like now is the time to strike again
Exactly
There's never going to be another opportunity we have to go now
Dear of a false flag
Jewish person
Defiling Cemetery
Silly well unfortunately
Weather
Cemetery
A guy
Trying to f*** with his ex
Yeah he wasn't Jewish
And that is unfortunate because it gives some Credence to the idea that all the other ones are also fake
Edgar
Yeah so we already know this dude is
The reality that we have to deal with
Dick holes on the left and the right are both
Assholes once again
Not left or right
Dudes
This guy is doing jilted by his ex
Kohl's in Toms River
The Jewish Center
To f*** with her
Which eventually
Very similar to the beginning of game
So this is
Awful cycle that we're trapped
Basically
Is these really angry dude
Men
Right and then you have Alex Jones
Wale net
Trying to
To misrepresent
The news that's happening
In order to
To fit that narrative
Once he starts doing all of this
Like
All these racial crimes are fake I've never seen white racism
Also
But not Caesar totally not racist
They're happy with me
Pitching White
Genocide type narrative
Tyler Snodgrass was filling in for you he asked
Alex
Supremacist
And at the time I answer was
I don't have enough information
Information I'm not sure and at this time as
I don't think it's a deaf
But man I'm watching
I mean
A r star Charter
Very difficult
You going to stay things that
Suggest he's not a white supremacist
As opposed to every
I don't know I'm just
Ivan
System like 3%
Always
White supremacist
Does
So whether or not you said you know it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter if you say like
Or even if you're cool with your black friend
Expression goat
Two more after
I'm just
Let's pull back the curtain you have a show tonight
I don't want to ruin that for you but
I'll also
You tried to make the argument that this
About
The guy who called in
Everyone
Obama anti
Trump
Opera
Hanna Reservoir Jewish Center
Bomb threat has an anti Trump Muslim convert
Oh my God
Attack
We see out there are false flag
What court case latest Austin where
Portland
Social justice Warriors
This makes me so sad
Chocolate made me so f******
God names
Is he talking
Are false flag
Everyone just wants it
Attention
All sexes
All sex isn't rape
There's no way there's a lot of rain
There is
A lot of it
Culture he doesn't believe in
The idea that they're unlocked
Believe that there's unreported sexual assault on campus
Pentagon
Did the entire the entire theme of this episode is
Alex Jones
Blaming everyone but who's really at fault which is
Dude that's not this episode
Examples
You was talking about maybe this entire show is
At like all of this is a distraction from
Toxic Mass
I'm becoming more and more convinced every single islamism
Dude
The whole thing
Is Eddie possible distraction from the fact that
A lot of dudes
Bad s***
Anyway he brings up like
The Duke lacrosse
Thing in there that's what he was reference
Mike 444 White
Yeah sure that was that was bad
That was bad
Cool so are all the rich
Just because one on the board of falsely accused of rape
And then we've got
20 million on the board of accused of rape
Facing any consequences
The best actor and our present
Silicate
Just because we're
It's almost impossible for us
I can't I can't say enough how much
Really
Anyway I have to I have to
My spot
Because we you know we got it we got to get in what needs to be got in and this next
Play
So fun
This one's fun
This one
Is a lie about him meeting
A military
You're going to find out
Super weird
About
Again
Kind of masculine issue dudes
We're on over 200 radio station so we don't let cuss words go out
Cassandra MCC regulations
He's not president anymore
And so we enter into the next problem
We know
I apologize I pulled out the wrong Cliff Obama and Hillary
It's like they've got nothing to do with nothing
It's still going yeah
Anyway here's the right click
Psychologist
Schneider jobs
The big four Banks
American Airlines mobile app
Famous conversation
Steal my catchphrase
You didn't
I famously came up with that
You think people will
To fight the system
Admit they're going to
Given whatever we do as long as it's incremental
It was in the shower you with your business dad was retired General
And
But
You have to adapt
And the man that works troid with the ones that got to where they liked it and the ones that are destroyed
That's what they do with the public
And then get us to adapt
The highest knowledge
We are not submitted
We're trying to adapt to actually overcome it for people and build a better system
Well neither do I
Trying to
I do I kind of thing
Think he has a good point but it's only applicable to how
The GOP is managed to convince
People to vote against their own interests by
Aiden
Extrapolate
Amphitheatre
Would you be impressed by a guy who is wearing his clothes
Looks great he got up and everything
Turn our on a plane
Talk to Alex
Is gets up
You got a gray suit you got a great too
What I am more into
There's two things that
What is
He's glorifying the idea of being
Cool with killing
Military like
To kill people
And
Start to like
Like to kill people
Even for a military
I like the idea of killing
Having to be done
Sometimes
Judiciously
5 ml
I do not like the idea that like
We love calendar
That's f***** up I don't like anybody
Who says that
.
Cuz it while
The second thing is
He talks about this military psychologist
Off the Record
I think means
And I had that I told
Pics of a conversation
If it was off the Record
That's not the important part
He's so cute
He's so arrogant only chicken necks
He's not a he's a dude
Alex's
F****** problem with people being arrogant
And quotes
Things are better than me
He's projecting
So much
Yeah but like all these people think they're
Smart better than me
Look that's in your head a****** I'm starting to be more and more convinced by this
If
The people in like if the New York
X would just be like
Alex Jones
We think you're so smart
Push him in the right direction
Like what like with Trump there is a part of me that believes
If we give Trump
Positive
Feedback and candy
20 sounded presidential or whatever
You give him positive
Feedback
Maybe he'll start
Like we could push him in the like a cuz he just wants to
I want people to like it may be president
I don't want baby propaganda
It's not workout
Children their small babies
Possible that by the time this episode is aired we will have a new president no but the situation on the ground will be
It is just on Saturday
We haven't we haven't tomorrow could be a wild day during the recording of this episode
Neither of us have checked Twitter
It might be an entirely new situation by the end of the recording
Very possible
And this one
About
10 minutes
We can break it up
But the reason that is important is that Alex
Loses
About money
While talking about not caring about my
Accidentally being
Unreleased
He talks earlier earlier in the show this is a Christian
Program we don't cuss on it right
What
In this next
Literally
I think everybody
Who goes to church
And horrified by what he says
We'll talk more if you're really giving people go to church a lot of credits
In my life
Route
I feel like
The people that I knew
Executor of this sort
In my heart of hearts
No depths of depravity that people who go to
What's the longest
And you just
Use the term heart of hearts
Church credibility I know the language
There's a nice sales pitch
That goes bad
And always have
Bring in Georgia
Covers this like it's a good thing and
So I mean
We do have a fight on her hands focuses
Are you see how far we've come
So you skipping a break
Is very
Which would be a commercial
It's a 9 minute commercial
No you can't possibly
We have over 40 million people to listen
And that watches on YouTube and Facebook on a platform
4344 million people
I think I'm doing good jobs that I'm selling a thousand t-shirts a day
$5 or $4 Jamaican t-shirt
I care about those shirts in the streets
I got to find myself so I'll try to make $5 on them we have the new Trump
20/20 show
Will it save the world
People instead of 100,000 people
A million people
On the street with Trump is my president
Trump2020
Keeping America America First 7076 infowars.com it will send shock waves across
Will break the last record thank you those that did order their Village
Call Matt mobile station in become a sponsor or send them $20 a month
Worship
That's literal sacrilege
$20 shirts
You know what I'm saying you here and I will tell you
I'll tell you this right now
There is a
Location for it
The mega churches
The whole thing that everything that he's talking about if your author of the Giants
That is sacrilege
Sure
The Jesus Christ Our Lord
The most brilliant lie I've ever been I've ever been part of
Pastor Creflo a dollar
YouTube
Now your point though is that the word
Hive to him
Is the big one
That's a big one
Text f*****-up
Is f***** up cuz tithing is giving 10% of your money
Berkeley to
Create good work
Against
The church is the people
Ulta Comenity
If Infowars is doing the good work
Well then Infowars is your
My friend Infowars is the
The community and all of these churches are just
In that
Like late 90s commercial where the guys getting it
Text Branson all that too
First of all
We have Alex morphine
M2 facelift
Alarm for political
Smurfing in
Game 2 is he going to try and get
Tax exempt status
But he's he's turning this into a church
In front of her eyes
Maybe that's how he does it
L.ron Hubbard
Well Alex Jones can't do it
But as we discussed IDI back on the page
Just taking atheras
Transparent and lame and
He's trying so hard
To make it not
Sl1000
A million
Streets
List money that year
I want you
Where are these
And make a movement
Now admitted
That means you're going
Going to give me a lot
Yeah
He's waffling between those two ideas
For this
Entire clip where
Mcbreen it was in there tries to talk about
To make adjustments
That's let's play this at
Apply to promote Justice
Somebody
Just read the links for the Articles reach out to people
Class I would buy just one shirt
In different sizes give them to people
That's basically multi-level marketing
I love you Alex Jones by a bunch of shirts and selling to people
F****** lunatic
Gospel
Shirts
Just get the shirts
I honestly think of that it might be an indication that he has too many
We got a movie search
Everything
Percent off that's fair I know we're going out of business he's also started a new thing where if you sign up for their newsletter they
Loft coupons
For a new thing
Now we're going back on the angel
Everything he's doing
Kind of make it sound like he's broke
No
I'm still waffling myself in the middle of like trying to parse
Exactly what is going on
Brokenness
But I don't
I don't think
Second chance
He's going to
Like
Screwed
Inferno
Call Tina
Alex when we went to the pro pro Trump rallies
All across the country
Full of Infowars
It shows the MSN the real power it shows the Trump people
Also exercises free speech
In the face of the bullies
But also people that are scared
I told you I had a conversation with my older brother who's a traditional Republican
Establishment Republican
Sinusitis
Hundreds of millions and billions of taxpayer money
The fights on now in every
Five years two years new Alexis it's on the war is now
I love that so much
Oh my God
Tell a lot about somebody by how they treat
People they work with and how they like
They start interacting he's comfortable moments
Is Alex
Does Ocuvite
F***
About something when he wants
To go
What do you wants to get on the roll it's
Got to go
But now that's a dick move
I'm like a
Child like a little boy
Like he's at the
The Kids Table Thanksgiving
Hey
I also would like
And then get right back
I bet he tells him to stop.
Everyone
Where
Daron Tyson
Well proud when we went to the
Pro Trump rallies that every fifth person had an Infowars shirt on and then it seemed like every
And we were like rock stars man they would recognize everybody from Infowars
Listeners
More than half empty
My brother about that and this was before the election by the way and he says well little brother I don't really see how that's hell
Helping him too much
Worked out
I'm telling you I had no idea
Trump
Your email will send you
Anime wolf
That's a Honey Trap
Stop
Nope
I know right now
Over a million right now
If everyone of you went and bought a 995 shirt
We will
Tell a million of these
He is Jessie from Saved by the Bell
He's losing it he's so excited so excited
So scared
Focus
Knowing what's happening
Everybody go get the trump-pence
It just goes up it just goes over and over again because we're running out of time I want to get to the end of the clip because he jumped
F****** loser
It's so hard it's like it's one of the great Alex Jones
Jonesy of the last 3 months
Percent
The 5% that won the Revolutionary War
AAA 2533 139 and get that shirt
Flat I said of the shopping cart shuts down just stay on there
Infowars.com
It's gorgeous
It's so angry it's so loud for no reason
The dude is right next
What was his face like
He was not as excited
I don't know if there's a human being alive
Also our number four is when Alex
Stop hosting the show Psych
Or something like that
But anyway
Nonsense
Freak out past episode of March 3rd
I can't wait for Monday I live
Gentlemanly think
He is going to
Continue this
Good morning
Just going to keep
Keeps writing stories from 2015
Terrible champagne today
Hopefully as the news
The champagne will get better
If we get to watch
Trump get hanged for treason I will I will say that
If you just did
I had a cigarette.
If trump.get impeached
The next episode
$100 bottle of
I will do the exact same thing
I don't want to hear it
People can follow us that knowledge underscore fight on Twitter
Leave a review Giver review
Reading
We have shirts
We no longer do we have chairs
Do we have two shirts
We can no longer sell shirts and
You can also email us
Knowledge fight
At gmail.com if you have any
Useready
Any feedback if you're mad at us
You think we're globalist
Just a couple of
The weeds
Is policies
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color