Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages and talk about Alex Jones
Oh no it's a big day for you
Oh
Virgo
Village was way better than I expected
Beer in the United States
This is one of those nice Facebook murdered
This is one of those
Senses where it would be impossible for you to not know
Nearly every we got
You maybe
I imagine Mike Mike Adams new video 3
Streaming service
What are the Scorpions doing the show is
Or Monday episode
And you know it was from a 2009 episode that Alex
We put it out I feel
I feel good about life and I wake up Monday morning
Just everything all over the places
Alex's band from
Spotify Pinterest kicked him out yeah it's so like
Everyone's going to probably be searching for Alex Jones by accidentally find us
We have a new episode out today and it has nothing to do with that
Hazel's like
I got to try and put out an episode
Come out
To come out on Tuesday
On top of it
We can get it at our regular schedule no need for an
We people
Yeah
Because he's been kicked off even more things
But even just
Before we started recording today
What you were kicked off y******
Earlier
Just a little bit ago you got
Kicked off milky
MailChimp
Cuz it was it sounded a little bit sound like
MailChimp trying to get some points
Generally doesn't comment on individual user accounts
Exception today
MailChimp notified Infowars in their account
I have been terminated for violating our terms of service
Make it clear that we do not allow people to use our
To disseminate
But the ship
We did that
Touch of that
I mean none of these places really have much of a leg to stand on
Tolerate him for as long as they have
I know this whole thing is Magic
I think we're on the same page that is like
Sarcastic along time ago you doing it now only
I mean it's going to actually hurt him
I don't think so I think he has
Couple other moves
Okay I'll text you this part
Just to finish the thought
The reason that all of this is happening is because one of these businesses whoever
Flinched first
And just decided fukkit he's gone the rest of them could use that as cover
And they're like we wanted to do this let's just go
Look at the plan or anything like that but I
One of that
Companies got off their ass
And the other people.
Like once I was okay everybody like
Be the first one to be like today
List of users you know
The Facebook
Community Wiki
You guys there
Chick hours it's ridiculous
Alex's Tire James Gunn
Is that what you think that my immediate feeling
On Monday was look into this another bulshit thing where
Expires
Like videos were ticked off or yeah yeah
Severe
Response was I had to sit with us for a little while
I think the Alex's fate is now in his own
More than it has ever been
Okay because
Where he goes
Success or failure is entirely dependent on how he responds
If he responds with well-reasoned argument
Passion
Maybe trying
He could turn himself into some sort of like
Deceased
Bruce
He has the opportunity to do that
She is about
Actually give him an opportunity to put on the back burner
That's true but alternatively if he
He's doing exactly what he
He's doing without the social media platform
He's in serious trouble because without Facebook even though he has 11 pages and they only got rid of four of them
Guys Without
Being in the iTunes Store
Although and Alex already subscribe to him
You can still get it if you have an RSS feed
Beacon plugin
It's just not
Searchable
You can't search for Alex in their catalog
So that's even sort of
It's going to hurt him
He's awesome
YouTube in terms of
His 2 million
But that doesn't mean you can't
F*** with the rules
And put like I found this episode
On YouTube
Yeah
Little weight but it's going to be severely diminish
And now with MailChimp saying
They're not going to work with him that's probably
It's only a matter of time before
I don't I don't know how he runs his website that he's stupid enough to have hosting not be on his own servers
Infowars.com
I think it's super unlikely
Play fight
He'll have to
Find a way to
Be his own marketing
More than he has been in
And I don't think he's very good at that
I think he's very alienating to new people
I think he's horrible
His own hand
If you can pull off
Some sort of amazing
Triple axel
But otherwise
Be he goes back to
About the
Market penetration in the relative popularity of likes
Of whatever somebody with 30 radio
No I mean
I don't know it's sort of
I doubt it
Time will tell if Alex
Goes along with
I think
We will see
This is real bad for him
But it's not like a knockout blow I don't think
He's going to have to really fight
To get out from under there
Especially when he's already having to deal with being sued
A bunch of other places
And his ex-wife is
In court with him but the custody stuff
I think he is
I think he's going to be hard-pressed
To fight the way he needs
To fight in order to save the operation
Are you there are you fighting on all fronts
Actually right now reminds me of the Alamo
In Tavares
This is entirely his fault I've been in this situation to begin with
He's going to be overrun and kill
Angie's the Bronx
August 28th
Generally this be the part of the show where I say thank you to a donor but
We have got the piece of mail the first piece of mail from
Before we open it up
I would like to say
Before this very generous gift
The Clarion
A raptor princess
Someone sodomites
Caribbean black
I don't want
How to read
Control
I bet you money
Abused
Joseph Stalin
Welcome to McDonalds may I help you
Thank you so much
Jordan this is going to blow your mind
8 ft
Oh yeah
It's only
Three fingers
Somebody's foot images
I really imagined to be much heavier than expose holding the package
The man look at that
Isn't it something else
Very much something else
I feel like what we should do
Because this is a very bizarre thing
Is I don't know I don't know we do with the foot
But I would say with the hand
We leave it in the middle of the table
If you have a point and the other person needs to shut up directions to prospect
Are you going to come this is an emergency
Much better than I expected
Irrelevant
This is actually
Because the pinky is
So we have three fingers
4 wishes
Tragically fulfilled
If one of our wishes was we got Alex kicked off of Facebook and everything else
Then the way that would happen
We also lost our heart
It gets kicked off
Because he's created an even better Facebook that would be a monkey pop
Tragic
It's come to my attention that
30 New York Knicks
Might not actually work
1530 Neola
We have received only had as lost
Is pinky finger still too now has our phone number lost
And we only have one
We have received some calls
Have you listen listen to all of them
I'd like to be a surprise but I thought
I'm going on
Call
Hayden Jordan
Chico California
Veracode ice type
My phone to call you
Chico
Amanda
You come here and Alive show
Security disability
Richard everage
Thank you for all your hard work
Keep it up
And work
We don't care
Call started I thought like
Well maybe this isn't the fan
Phone number we still like they accidentally
Either that or I was like this is somebody from like the Civic Department
Hey guys I think you're f****** around and we do not condone your behavior you have
Call
Also we are now huge
You don't believe that
Chico
Fair enough
Bear
I don't know if I can handle the airfare for that
In the future
We love to do it but
Arabic
Rent a Winnebago
Jesus is a lot of fun call
This is fantastic what a life I've never been happier in my entire goddamn life because Alex Facebook
No monkey paw there my friend so we've given a little bit of like our preliminary feelings about to Alex
Getting kicked off of
Reviews of these platforms
And that is what we're going to discuss
Well I have found the August
So when he was freaking out about
The Facebook is all that stuff and come out
I have YouTube all that it happened right before he got on air
A couple hours to get
Used to the idea
Azar all of this
Contact drop
From August 6th
Sociopath
Alright
That's good to hear
He's not mad
I'm sure they will be borne out through the rest of
Yeah we'll see when he gets into the big news which of course is about him
Said it was terminated
Spotify
Sometime last night
BuzzFeed
Freddy's playing games
Because this is
Country
How do you engrave the First Amendment
Do you go with a ground war
I wouldn't
Are you sure so you would start with what like a drone strike campaign
Nougat start from nukes
Absolutely
I didn't human it can't be killed by Conventional Weapons
You have to use radiation if you want to kill the First Amendment
I read that somewhere alright
Emps will deliver temporary
Alright
Cool
Alex be kind of heard this talk before
Repeating his narrative
What he was afraid of happening as happen
So the idea that
Country
I am sad country
Spotless
Absolutely
I mean that's not all that excited
He has to be Petty while he's doing it I guarantee I guarantee that conversation with the other way around
No don't worry about it they don't have the courage to do
Dude we are going to get banned his lawyer is probably telling him
Hey dude you can't pay me anymore if they kick you off their platform
Alex's
Abnormal behaviors
But
Interesting
Half
Through a lot of this episode
He blamed the Chinese
He'll sort of two angles on his getting kicked off everything and the first is the most aggressive of them
He blames China
You asked why why would you blame China
Sure
What
Chinese government devices
Everything
Everything transferred
Y******
Divorce
Members of Chinese intelligence
Public University
Call Mom
Terminator
That's right guy that do they don't even beating all they can do is send back at Terminator for the pasta
Dreadlocks
I don't understand that
86 on 86
I haven't heard that one that one
August 6th
Titanic
I think that's a headline
Nevermind
I'm so all that other stuff we talked about before like the Panama Canal is loaded
Private companies Panama Canal
Part of that
The deep-water ports
All that stuff we did never really talked about in those narratives does the office of
Personality
Bottom
The massive hack
India FBI office
Personnel manager
Edit sounds
Really scary
2Pac of tons
Vic potentially
Tons of information
How about people who works
For the government
Possibly spies
Who had applied for jobs could be blown that sort of thing
From the office of personnel management hack
Has never been used
According to Bloomberg quotes data on 21 million individuals
Including Social Security numbers in Fife
Mcmillion fingerprint
Masters 2015
Packers against the office
No management
Doesn't appear to have been shared or sold by the purple
Says
William evanina the head of us counterintelligence
Whoever took the day they were pretty confident they haven't shared it evanina whose title is Director of National counterintelligence
Security Center
Set an interview Thursday
The conclusion that the Chinese government would be
Behind it is suspected but no one is proven
Quotes for Security Experts believe the attack
Carried out by China
Though evanina says that the USA has not
Reach that conclusion
National was arrested
But they have not been able to prove that was
Dirt is still unfolding
There was like a loan fraud case that was going on with a lot of
Speculating with connected to the
Information that was stolen but outside of that like like none of us ever
Blackmail
These numbers of people of people have never been reported as
So I understand the fear that Alex has their butt
Currently b'nai Google and YouTube have merged
Apple has merged with the Chinese government
Officially
You can't report that that's not true
In the same way that like the office of personnel management hack
Is the potential to be something really really sucks up put in the 3 years
Hasn't materialized into anything
Really negative and there are tons
People investigating it
And they have not come to the conclusion that you have come to
So your information Shawty
You are demonstrating what
You get thrown off
Because of this sort of behavior
He's like I never did that and then he's like
When I did that
That was fine
You just admitted
The question of whether or not you can criticize
You can
Google's not going to throw you off for criticizing China
Common things people do all the time now
Just bad when you are also
Alex Jones
Because of all the other stuff
You're going to get a cake walk
Did you know that all of China's prices
Oh my God.
I can't even
I don't know if the club now
So Jason's up plan
Panama
What's it called
Palindrome palindrome
That's right
Anyway it was that clip Alex complains about the Chinese more
Frankly it's only made us stronger when it comes to core basement floors Lester's taking action
Understand
Programming the world because we know the truth and the tricon's want us off the air
Google Facebook Twitter
Cares that much about the Patriots in America in the much the same way I care about
About applying American law to other countries
Ann Arbor
All white countries have the same voice
I don't I'm not joking at all really think he does so I agree
Freedom of speech
Hinda in London
You don't even very different view on here
They have very specific rules
About that sort of thing about
In France Marine Le Pen getting in trouble for
Talk about Muslims
Occupying
80s
You don't like it when people talk like that
What
How little do you know
Are you interested in nuance
If you just think all countries have
Disable laws
If you have group them together in your
It's not absolutely crazy
All come from Hammurabi
Where you at
And he might
I think he
You're right in one
You use write a couple times on the show ready for that
No absolutely not
Has been kicked off of all of those
You've never heard of before
Cuz they were kicked off too soon
No because they just were like maybe somebody yelling the n-word
Plenty of dick Euless
You think Facebook hasn't been I know it's
People but it's never Band-Aids never censored this is like a show this much
RadioShack
Yeah
People allowed David Duke which is another reason why
Hi this is such cowards b******* about the top of the show
If you're going to do it
Do it
Yeah yeah yeah
Because they're also hate
Teaching
Actually walk that back a tiny bit
With the I don't know if David Duke still has a radio show
We were talking about when this was all still kind of hypothetical
Set a precedent
Are you set a standard
Regarding your
Impossible to live up to
You can't possibly
Take so many people
The most
Like I said I text you this most
Dystopian surveillance
Algorithm or whatever for YouTube or 4
Google in order to purge
Infraction
I agree with you on that front on the other hand
You could f****** make a day
Will you do something about this s*** but they won't
Most likely
In the same way that day they're all f******
They're also
I'm done with the
I don't know
I don't I don't know what to
No generalize it more but I
I think the kicking Alex off is a good thing
Too late
It's too late
But it doesn't reduce more problem
You're like for these companies
Expected to be
In the future
And it's not like a thing where now the Liberals and
All are calling for blood and they won't stop until every conservative or anything like that
But it is a situation was like well now
You've established this is what you will and will not accept
And therefore you have to live up to
Well that's why I'm so recently sent Breitbart
Because he is
Slowly falling into madness
It is not your belief system
You know what if you want to believe in conservative lies that's fine
Send me a Breitbart article
In the same way that Alex Jones is a con man
Who is f****** stoked your fears
All of his
Nefarious
Nobody at Breitbart believes in anything
They're all f****** insane people
Like there's no nobody shares your beliefs
If you want to send me an article from somebody like the the f******
Spectator
National Review or whatever
Bulshit
At least those guys believe their lies
Breitbart has gone downhill since Shapiro work there
So that tells you a lot
This is what you're trying to
But to me what if you say my dad sent me a Breitbart article
I hear
My dad doesn't know that this would
You crazy
But as an article it's like he doesn't know that I know that this is bulshit
Articulate like
Don't do that
I've spent the last two years with dance
You can do it you can do that give me the freeway call Paul sweater
Because it's it's a whole thing and you got to you got to just
No
Batman what are we going to do
Wait it out
This mix
Alex
When you know months
To go Alex announced that he was going to be interviewed by Megan
Jim Kelly
Because I would like to do interviews with
The mainstream press.
Getz clowned all the time
He pretends that the Wynwood he goes on that BBC show
And they call him an idiot
Stuff like that
But he still doesn't want to do it too much
Cuz it sort of wears out the charm of that
Surprise
I got another surprise here with a interview
And then because
This really dumb
He's got an interview with Cassidy
I would have a heart attack
Cheer on Friday
Basically follow me around
Person
Platform
Intelligence operation
I want to get my hands on that tape
Cuz I'm going to guess she asked that it was a hypothetical
I'm guessing she was like what
These media Corporation
And actually do what they should be doing
What's your game plan what is your
Endgame if you will
How are you going to respond operation that you built is really great very impressive
But you are beholding to a lot of things that are way outside your control
I don't want to say that this is the reason I don't use Facebook or Twitter all that much
But I would
Beer nightmare situation if I was him
You have such a Reliance on
Other people's businesses for for your business to run
I think you're fine cuz I think that most people listen to
Subscribe
Common
End up liking it and I think that's probably how it works for us
Somehow
So I don't know I don't think
We can't do it
Bubble is going to my
Oh no
The guy who Santa exploding drones at Maduro is going to find out
He hates
Socialists
Verb
What are we doing I'm not sure but the New York Times
Lady who gave an interview Dallas probably was not stalking this
And also
Cap'n Crunch
Like that
Okay I know this is about to happen to you
So she probably
Cuz it I mean this
Everybody
Even me
Nobody expected any of these corporations to staxup cover Alex Jones
In the
You're like a Media Matters right wing watch Pitch speed
Kind of taken aback by
Except
Forgive me
I know it's a little comical
But the idea that you
We're kicking them off
What do you like a
Subscribe member of you born and he's no longer allowed to lights out
I don't know what you're
P*** sites around and noticed
Is that a lot of people post non-pornographic
The content all
It's so I think that's more what it is we will kick off any videos
People upload of
Infowars
Yeah I got
So I bet I mean that extent is pretty wild cuz
That could be
Like all things
But it would be a very interesting play
To be like streaming on y****** partnership
LaJoie Ryan of propaganda enjoy Ryan
The pro wrestler who had a partnership with y******
I did not know that
Yeah it was great they will they allow him to
Free cam
For now I think he's got his Periscope cuz that sounds like Twitter and Twitter header
So Peter is not
Kicked him off and dab
Now it's recording
Twitter is not made any
The move and Periscope song by Twitter so he's streaming on Periscope now
And that'll come up
A little bit later
But yeah
Joey Ryan by the way the guy who
He had his finishing move with people with grab
His dick and his dick was so strong that is Dick Wood
Was that the guy who
Remember storyline in the Attitude Era
Well as Val venis
Finishing moves
Pretzel
Yeah there was a
Very racist storyline rather special
I do not remember
It was real bad
Val venis
Who's not
I don't know if he's a good wrestler
I can't do that but I do remember most of his storylines being a bit embarrassing
And that one is profoundly
Gotcha
No he joyriding his
Regressing
Big strong American dick
I'm not totally sure either leave that one alone
What do panthers
Starting to show up you brought up Colonel Travis
He probably will too yeah it's kind of like he has a preoccupation with him
But also doesn't know most
Colonel Travis
Bob so he brings that up here
He knows history
But only the headline
Ameno
I made the conscious decision to take action
I need the conscious decision to draw their fire in
And
Should I try to punch your buttons all day but don't forget the financial support
Immature love your support sunshine on our faces
I don't know if that's all that work
Infowars
Store.com
Come on man
Defeat the Mexican air mattress
It went down at pivot
I told you that I thought that you just continue to do the same thing he's just dead in the water
Currently doing the same thing
This is going to be
A dry spot
Essentially you have your audio
You have no access to new people to scare and all that stuff
And you've already taken a lot of their money
And I don't know if they're going to give you any more
At least not the millions that you need to run your operation
Now you don't have dark money coming in then
If you don't have to worry about
Dark money coming in
Why would the dark money stick around
Well I like if he doesn't have the penetration I have a I have a theory about that
I think
Should wait until the end
Episode
No is
No
He's no he's no Joey Ryan
Mostly
I have to do with
You can still do that from the shadow that's what I thought about that
Alright
This eclipse is just about how he still on iTunes if you had the RSS feed
This one here
Which I think
Why they're so bad
Cult of modern leftism
How the human soul forever
They're scared
Yeah
I think that's just their scared
Kicking me off I'll just a scared
It isn't the action of a scared organization not doing it is the action of a steroid
Redoing it is the action of people
Trying to do with what they should have done a while
Responding appropriately
Yeah absolutely
2015 he's already
Encapsulated all the worst parts
So what would you say
Value
Free Speech defense value in Alex
From like a 2013 2014 episode investigation
9 years ago I don't necessarily think of it just be
Being a racist
Is
Enough
To get you kicked off some
You don't like Facebook and YouTube
I mean is there a decision
Make that your decision I mean I don't want it I don't want that to happen anywhere I would rather
But if you make that decision
Put yourself in
Very precarious position
Now racism gets
You kicked off of
Twitter Facebook
YouTube whatever
Purge o much
Contact
I'm saying
Again it's what I keep coming back to you it's a matter of logistics
As opposed to
Morality
Houston time zone
Appropriate
Racism
Rape is less
I think it's a standard
Probably should be
Activate page
Near like active racism constitute
Gacha life
Stuff
Is action
Like someone having a conversation about black people having lower IQ
Like they've read the bell curve and they want to expound on it or something like that
I don't necessarily think that I think that's racist
For sure but I don't think that's
Heat
That's just stupid
Exactly
Racism does fall under that
Category but then there's also a another aspect
Effect of his haste
Where is
Racism
And there is an aspect of it that
Replies action towards
Particularly Muslim
There is a part of it that's like
That it is not
It's not your grandpa saying s*** on a chair in the end we need
Just save Western Civilization from
Consider
I think if there's a line there
The idea of
Implementing that line
It's so
Weird to me
I don't know what to do with
And I'm glad I don't have to decide
Yeah
Wrestle with those things
Head
Literally
And it's not a free speech but only 45% of Republicans think that Trump should be allowed to
Outlets
At the same time of course
Alex Jones being kicked off of any
Because the free-speech Lots
It's about
State States
I was reading this article on Democracy Now
EPA announced that it will freeze obama-era fuel economy standards 2020 level
Do you have an average of 55 miles per gallon by 2025
But now the industry will not have a real
How to do better than
Interesting Lee and probably a very problematic
It's also being reported
The Donald Trump
Administration also plans to revoke California's Authority
Tougher automobile emissions
So
Why
Well the federal government has a right to regulate the states
How can I explain in anyways it Trump gives a f*** about Stacy
The state's right to you later by the federal
It's it's
It's crazy to me
Like it
Great you read stories like that and I know they happen pretty frequently that one was just such a in your face
You can't ever talk about that
That's true but it's like so many of them are kind of ignoring that aspect
They're like to California
City point
Weed California
Let's move onto sound
30 years too late
To do anything about it
Oil
Isn't it weird weird
But
Avis Mexico
I would say I'm going
Checking out his YouTube channel after it has been kicked off
You found something there that
Did not approve
A big middle finger
Live
Cuz I was asking for it
They're just regular
YouTube
Used to be
You said this account has been terminated
Violating guideline
The community
Backup plate
Open
That they're going to shut us down around four months doing it
Lying and in false flagging
Give me the run
Making up stuff
Nope no
Which of course is holding a putter
No
BuzzFeed
All the leftist garbage
You know why they did that Alex
I would say 40% of your videos have any of those places names in the title
Algorithms
Back-and-forth beef with Steve Colbert they must be
An oversight of
Just mechanization
Automation temperature
Because Isaac
I think Alex did it to himself
I don't think this is like you said a big male singer because he also doesn't
Say the other
I've no idea what they are
As he was scrolling through the related channels that are like
What do you want
You want to bring up with that is
Call could be
Princess videos
Oh my God
I found it I found it
What time who am I
I found a YouTube channel last night
I am
So conflicted about
So I was watching video
Stoic Irish people videos of people eating really hot stuff
Ended up on this channel
That I'm not going to
Either names
I feel like I don't know I don't know
Crude Brothers
Okay it was
And Maywood
Like hot peppers and stuff
Now here's the part you can call yourself
He's incredibly Charming because it's clearly like each other
The kids like 13
Time of like this kids
Got to get beat up all the f****** time videos
Doing weird stuff how old is he
I know that I'm drawing a real fine line here but they did want that I want
That looks like a roulette wheel
Who is the hot peppers
And he gets bell pepper
Healthy eating Taco Bell Pepper 13 years old
Get the Carolina Reaper
And then died
I was very worried for him
Took it like a chain
Just sitting there like
You are the Dead
A red bell pepper
That's true there should have been somebody
You stepped in before the next
Because their mom is dead
3 a.m. wake your kid up
I was
Not enjoying
That much all I was impressed by this kid
The trooper but it was like
I was
How is this allowed
Not like I want to stop them necessarily but
Well it's protected by the first
Is there a sibling
Or the Bahamas
Anywhere like someone should
Put a
I don't know why I brought that up
Did you do a disclaimer that you're under 18
Help the f****** kid
The kid who's actually
There's really hilarious
Dad got like
God dammit it was a scam
Is it a
Venom back on Deck
I'm super worried for that kid to like I can't even imagine
The bullion
He's okay
Symptoms
Seep delightful
He's alright you got a good father-son relationship that will take you far in life
Which direction bakermat up
So
Some sort of self-defense
Do you need to plan
What does
Nor love
Everyone must make memes about
And everyone must lift Infowars up as a standard
Decided to put out
You know how well that free Milo hashtag work when Milo got kicked off
They did it he's back
100%
Now you still gone
So yeah and also everyone was dunking on Millie Weaver earlier
Cuz she was. She made a post about a Facebook is a
A public company
Posted
Screenshot of
Wikipedia page
Public
To think Facebook
Is a privately owned business
There's a thing called fact-checking
Facebook is a public
It's publicly traded
Using that argument to justify Banning Alex Jones doesn't work
Confused by that
Read a book but also write the reason it's not about being publicly traded
Public or private sector
Those are very
One of them
The other doesn't
True
So
Although that raises the question of
Have been correct
Female pronouns
Should should Facebook however be considered a public utility
The whole other conversation
Think so now I'm pretty sure that she was trying to get to the federal government should regulate
Facebook because that it holds perfectly with their beliefs
Facebook doesn't have a monopoly on social networking
Because there are other sites
Like Twitter
That dude very similar things
Additional
Gab exist
There were other weirdos social-networking site
They have tried to make it
And you know what the Market's not there for them
I understand that but I'm just saying this
Because bears
Monopoly
Because our other video trading sites out there in the world
As far as I know Alex hasn't been banned from Vimeo but haven't been Dailymotion he could get on there
Any of these other places now you can say
You're not entitled to a ton of people looking at your s***
If you are as popular as you think you are
Emotion
Those people should follow you you should be able to elevate Dailymotion then
Comcast Monopoly
There's it there is something there is an argument to be made about once you reach a certain market share you are essentially
Operating
No
The reason
Cuz
The issue comes down to essentially the monopolies that you're talking about
Utilities have to do
As I understand it largely with
The ability to build small town
Them exorbitant only person who has Type go to them
Pools
Citgo corporations and Market because
You do that you can price gouge for electricity
And the sky's the limit and don't have electricity
Weather going to be in trouble.
Have to step in to regulate that sort of thing
World Series
Serious trouble
In the same way with Xfinity or RCN Cable
In Chicago
The access
To the internet not things on the internet
Itself that are important as a utility
Having a website with a lot of people at it
Pets.
It's not
Fit incredibly
If you're a libertarian
Incredibly stupid a libertarian
These laws in terms of Monopoly
I respect that if you're a Libertarian that is
The stupid argument in use
You should never be
Would like to eventually become
Dictator of them
Have to say
That I would be great one
And I would regulate Facebook
Now here's the issue
I would too
There is there is an aspect of it
It has nothing to do with that
The unlimited
Potential for screwing it
That a company like that
Possesses
Monopoly necessarily I think the I think the version of Regulation you would have to bring into something else
Videos
You are essentially creating a nuclear bomb
You're creating a different version of a nuclear bomb but it has the same destructive capability
With all the data mining that you're doing
Cambridge analytica
Absolutely it is a public safety measure I'm not sure if our society is ready to allow that
To grow any further
I'm not in government
I don't have to come up with those answers
Again we should really be ticked
We should
Okay
Here's the thing
You will be my policy
Because you're measured and
Right I'll be the frontman I'll be there
No no no
Alex
I don't know it is
It's very difficult
Question and I hope not
To get into that at all because if we so much into Alex's version
About like
Their Monopoly of the
You should probably
All things being equal
Not allow these companies
Become bigger than they are or even passed
They should be broken
Like Instagram being bought by Facebook
That sort of thing
Is it is trouble
Greater argument that is
Evergreen
Which is that
These guys are
Music
Until it happens to them
Hold now you need to be what you need to make sure that these people can't do this
Like it always happens that way
Small tip of the cap pretty consistently
Against the idea of Monopoly capitalism
I'll give him that
Freddy's
Hopefully not
The idea of Monopoly
Social Power
The only threatened by the idea of disenfranchised group being treated as equals
That it brings.
To me when he's like
These companies Tampa
Monopoly
Play that logic elsewhere
I told you that Alex had though
Is first sort of Ali was this is
They're to blame
Is a good start with
A new sort of
I think it's weaker
Apple Facebook
80 this election meddling looks like
We on Facebook
They treat the conservative
Members of the House and Senate
So did donation time
Because really
Also I don't remember any Executives from Facebook
Ever publicly saying
We're going
To crush conservative
Enabling conservative voices far beyond
Public
Somebody
I don't know I think that's awesome
Talk about it more but any more thoughts on it
I want to get to this next
Let's do a video of cross-dressing
Crossdressers dancing
And keep being around we talked about that.
Sucked up gross
And that was one of the videos that got kicked off the first round
Decides to get defensive about it in this Cliff profoundly weird
Place this is my town
French
Little kids doing that that I had her a sexual thing I'd be freaked out by it
Elk today
Teen episodes theories on Toddlers & Tiaras
Also I just want a quick
If you saw the video that Alex is super like
Open Arms about
And you think it's sexual
That's you
You're the one who's making it sexual
Don't let us do that
Internet
Or I guess you know
Enterprise
Thousands of years ago in cities that got a little while
Whether that was real or not
Story of the wrong point
That story has a very important lesson about how the Bible is f****** b******* in it
Will you know that
Story is correct
So far as what you said
People did come
People did knock on the door
If they let us refuse
Haha
However
What you can rape
Is my daughter's hooray
Raped
Uncle Ray's
That's not sexualizing children
Weird
Also
Two and three-year-olds
Dude
That's a good that's a good 2.2 I really take with that clip
Except for upper body strength
Antone
The the cherry-picking of biblical lessons
Boy did he get that one is possibly believing it's real
Star Trek
Great episode of Star Trek
Specifically
And Spock
Captain Kirk are the two angels and then they just stand there and they're like
This is a weird f****** place
We have a policy of non-intervention because of the whole thing
Reply to have been a like extra star system
Level three
Dude I don't know
Underneath It All saying cross-dressing in transit
Destruction
Tire City just because you're there
I mean I know that's just like an implication of what he saying it's like
You know you can say something
Chikhli without stirring
People numbers
Follows along a conclusion that you are making
Things must be true along the way regardless of whether or not
Position in a row
Yep
I know we are out of context drop
We heard that Alex
He's not scared at all
Next
To believe that he's a little bit scared because he's
Turning this into a much bigger deal.
In terms of
The world
President-trump
The central
Issue
So
Trump is sold out
If he doesn't get Alex back on Facebook
No
Not a chance
Is this one a political capital what's the weather like
For him to just be like
Bikes that would work
It'll be embarrassing
We're not going to do that
Is this the moment where Alex
Finally realizes that
Trump has no wait 0% back
The head it's
Might lead to the on the cross moment why have you forsaken me
Okay
Albatross
Does not care he's a psychopath and you're an idiot if you think otherwise by a lot of dudes
Comment
Steelcon
It's
Kind of part of the
Steal like he's scared because he's turning this into a trump you need to make this
The biggest issue with the world
Absolutely not
But in his next movie actually talks about something
He's scared of
I don't think
My girl
You scared of my girl to terrible sequel
Is it there is a sequel don't worry about it
You scared of something else
I would some this next flip up
Just to say Alex me
Please go to therapy
Islamophobia
That's just some
I'm actually scared of
Somalia
What is Amazon public
Transphobic islamophobic and Bullies children
Children
Was like
What's
And she went
Just cuz BuzzFeed
Moses's BuzzFeed
BuzzFeed says drinking milk is racist
Just kidding it's a weapon system
The less derangement
I hear there is you
You need to talk
Talk to somebody
This is bad
Like you're rambling about
Kelly
And your child custody case
Don't want to be
You know you have these
Too much on air
Islamophobic
He's trying to say that he's scared of radical Islam
Afraid of Muslims
Right and it's like dude you need to
You need to go and feel better
What 5 minutes
Is how long
The average American last
Call Total in Somalia without being
I did a lot of research into Somalia I was going to do a long
About the history of Somalia
Halo
That's why that's absolutely why
In the Quran whenever I read that
Has nothing to do with them
18 years old
20 years shorter than it is in America sounds crazy mortality rates are 10
I can't imagine what is through the roof doesn't have anything to do
The population is
You know what
I think Somalia is may be justified in kidnapping any American that lands on Somalia
I don't know about Justified
You get it
Yeah
German is not our people
This government is not the Russian people but
Kidnapping
Ikea in South America
Rashes of kidnapping
Because it's a robust economy
Documentary mom dybala
It's a great documentary with this guy ended up going and hanging out with kidnap gang
Yeah and talk to them about
You know that whole
Incredibly f*****-up
Necessarily
I don't want spoil the other best.
So good
Yeah it's easy interesting that
Completely different documentaries
It is interesting how the the capitalism
Is
Perhaps a better indicator of the
Pure
Carnivorous energy of Kappa
It has no qualms
It is all Market
Only if
Few years ago
In the greens
Scheme of things
The part of the free market
The free market and capitalism involves telling human
Like on a massive scale Doug are still
Pockets of that and white slavery still exist
Is well-liked there are still remnants of that pathetic
Used to be above board business
Vic major countries were involved in as an economy
Yeah like yeah absolutely
The Cruller
Enforcer
Parts of
Capitalism still exist in Black Market places but it's because
Exactly interesting how
Strange really
White people be like
And they make you work
What is crazy
That's just wrong
And let me tell you something
We would never do that
Now
We all we had
A lot of years of doing is great we made a lot of money
If you have any
Flight Griffon history then you can't beat
Confused by it because
The reason that people did that back then beyond
Not giving a s*** about the lives of the people that they kidnapped
Because of economic
It's what they gain from it
So the idea that there were these kidnapping gangs whether it's in Somalia
South America the idea of it
Is it an economic system that works with these people that don't have any other access
I'm not saying it's Justified
It's good but you don't understand why
Look at the root cause of it as opposed to just stop
Senor
An idiot
Yeah
Cool this next clip was very tough
Because
As
Longtime listeners of the program no I haven't talked
We ended up starting the podcast is that I watched
Infowars election night coverage
To the dark heart
Bright
Primarily what I saw
Version of it
Is a lot of
People mostly white men
And then Millie Weaver
So they're all hanging out drinking champagne
Owen Shroyer smoking a cigar in the studio
Vera aggressively laughing
Videos of very diverse crowds at Hillary rally
YouTube
Mister B's
Is Men Women
People who are
Clearly queer identifying
People Transit dividual
And they were laughing
Because they were crying
Anytime really
Sharp Focus
The fact that this is.
Conspiracy
Oh that's fun
It's a cruelty
The cruelty show and it's also
So much about
Sort of stuff
Position
Bournout
Every single trial
That we've done every single episode backs that up
At least to some extent has been proven just
I'm so
When I was listening to this episode
Of aleksandr
Good line
It's not bad it's not bad
Was watching this expected him to be
Freaking out and being like
The globalists are out for blood and so far we haven't really heard any
It's all about blaming China and then trying to make these weak ass arguments about like this
Violation of a
If you see laws or something
Sharp pain contributions
He's trying to work some sort of game we didn't realize that
He's up against it
And part of that might be because at this point MailChimp
Diction
We still had his
Probably
Ratably huge email list
Blast out
Maybe
He said he wasn't freaking out
The way he probably
Chitwood normally
Yeah but I never expected
Was him to bring up
The election night
Because it's not you
Turning Point
My life
You know what I mean like
This show is my life
Doing the show studying Alex
Yeah because the last two years of my life is so different then
What came before it
18 the last year has been different than the first
Yeah that was struggling
Here just like
Outside
The show to figure out like
What is going on taking in too much
Information
Have a way to synthesize it fully yet
And so
For him to talk about
It's off all these
Platform
The very moment
That was so
For me
Almost made me cry all over again
Listening to the ferry like
It's a willing to that clip
It was a witch
You are pissed
How do you say the things you said I said sure as hell didn't lie about wmd
Actually
Cherry on top yeah
Yeah yeah
He brings it up all the time
Give himself cover for the wise
And all that. Oh that's crazy
You know that's
That is a
That should be made and then summarily to
Misfortune
We're not
No but so many people are
You know like that is a that is in
An interesting question to ask about whether or not
Hey we are engaging in the same kind of
Behavior that no pleasure from
It was good fun
It doesn't tickle me the fact that Alex's
Kicked off stuff
I mean any we look at
Like the point is
His rights are being taken away
A Supreme Court Justice that's going to
Cell for the crimes that he most likely is not going to happen
Because of him
Yeah because he got kicked off The
Look at in terms of
I don't
Find any
Interest
In looking at what
People are doing on Twitter or Facebook and then
Flying bat
Nothing I don't retreat
But like
If I see someone who even if there's someone who
It has a voice in a lot of followers are making fun of Alex Jones
I don't think that that means everyone is making fun of Alex Jones lot of individuals on Twitter
You are certainly
I think it's
People primarily who cover Alex Jones most regularly are right wing watch
Media Matters
Not generally rightwingwatch
Is the source of clips
Let go out to Media Matters go to places like
You know
Play The Goonies web shows often take their clips from
I don't think
Necessarily
Relishing this
Or anything like that there's no like
There's no post that are like
Hahaha
Or anything like that
But at the same time
I want to be very clear about
We haven't finished the clip that we're listening
To right now
We haven't gotten
End of this episode
And I'll read you the headlines that they have for Alex Jones
Hear Spotify cancels The Alex Jones Show Apple Facebook
Open YouTube.
Infowars
That's the only headline
On rightwingwatch
That's a big news
Fair enough
On Media Matters we have MailChimp confirmed
Terminated the accounts of Alex Jones Infowars
Alex Jones
Is Donald Trump
For help which is Eclipse that we heard earlier
And does continue throughout this episode
Periscope still hosting video or Alex Jones
Pantomime shooting Robert Mueller
To gain we already sort of talk about integrity
It's owned by Twitter
Yeah Twitter dozen active Periscope isn't
Tucker Carlson
Infowars Alex Jones
Right-wing media defend Alex Jones at 4
Infowars banned from several major platform
Like all of their head blown
Headlines are about Alex but I just
News
Yeah
There's nothing that's like
Hahaha you dumb prick or anything like that
This is dry
We think that they're doing a disservice
Because
You could drily report some other things
But I think are more important
Like
He said
I'm an islamophobe
Does Muslims
Not enough click
Nautical I feel like that would get some click
You would think
I don't know I don't know how the business Works clearly we get to click the weekend
Who knows
Fair enough but let's finish the club because I set it up with that long story about election night my don't want to
Forget what we're talkin
Election night
Physically ugly people
Have they distain for Successful People good looking people
They're just a legion of scum
If they could just defeat culture and Society
Superiority of Western culture and ideas
Could be somebody
We've got to be out of the way
That's the nature of authoritarianism
Scratch
Superior to take out
But only starts the persecution will subgroup first
Very strong message plus everybody needs, and yet
T-shirt
Get t-shirt
Motherfuker
Physically ugly
Difference
From me
They always want to take down dinners
Superior that they think
As opposed to that they think are
F******
Nowhere
Exact
Everything
Everything in there was such deeply
Coded language
Sudbury
Very f******
Specific
The idea of what
You saw them on Election night I want your goddamn show on Election night I know exactly what
You were watching on Election night
In the studio and what it was
With a bunch of minorities cry
Bunch of minorities
Cuz it was a diverse group
And if you sir
Mr. Alex jumpster
You don't know anything else about these people
Jamiroquai
If you are saying
Physically unattractive people
What you were responding to
He's at there's not enough White
Because it was a
Very diverse group
And those white people should know better than to hang out with all these weirdos
That is all that's going on
It's so f******
Crazy
Unacceptable
That he's
Bring the
And then
Further
Very acceptable that it turns into a t-shirt
That's exactly
Tangible
No predictable yes
I accepted because that's all this guy's gun
Astro cute getting thrown off of every f****** platform he's on
And he can't stop doing the activity
You can't stop doing it
You're not on here anymore
You're not on YouTube
Unit streaming on periscope
Rick
Your radio
Arkansas
Enjoy
Give a s***
I'm bad now
I'm actually mad
I know I love it
I am
Curious
This guy I've rarely never interested that's true I didn't have to go for the
I'm so it bums me out so much cuz it's suction invalidation of
What you would hope
Is
Licking
Illustrative
You know like
You would hope
One day you could
Show Alex the video of election night
Be like
Hey look at that look at your crew and it look what you're doing
You know you'd hope maybe one day
To come
Terms with like what
What's really going on
Use of the
Fear of the other
In order to sell
All about
All this is
Bigotry and shirts
Yeah
Glad we have
I haven't either
For a while
Literally
Not metaphorically
Two shirts
Maybe maybe I want to
Too far there
Getting a little bit
God dammit
You have never gone too far
Bums me out
This was that was perfect
Yeah
You just ended the
The clip
In any other way
I probably would have
Liking
In a much more
But I think he's a little bit
F*** this is the same bulshit you're peddling I can't even I can't even engage with your racist nonsense
In age because you immediately
Degrading when you look at it
It's kind of like
He went goes from like
Abject
Infuriating Behavior
And now you're you're pathetic
Niger Ville oh my
My feeling on it is
Is like I want to get worked up
Danielle about it but at the same time because of the activity at the end
Any rate
In person
Person is going to be
Convince by me
Screaming
Appreciate it
Does everybody
Skip it because it's just Alex talking about how like
Hey Owen Shroyer hasn't YouTube
YouTube channel couldn't do it over there
That sort of thing on some level aware that you can
Can make it really
And that's part of why I
Disaster
And now you have to look for other
People cheating
On his behalf
If you actually don't want
Infowars
On YouTube
Then you are
Almost
For everybody's exact
You have Jeff
The weirdo
Take down these channels
Have a lot of followers
And wait for these other ones too
To get built
Then
You're not doing much except for the pushing them back
The minor setback
And it's just
Defected David Knight s*** is still allowed to be up it's just like
No just summarily ban Infowars don't like
Interrupt
Is a much more restraint
Broadcast
Yeah because he has nothing to restrain
You sucks
And he's like he's still as
You know until the whites
He would never say
Good stuff that Alex.
I would like
Of course
Whatever
No David Knight would not
Say that people were crisis
I don't
He would do that
So maybe he gets a pass because Owen
Shroyer is a young
Buck and he is hungry
Ready for it so you would probably go along with it
More of the Hague
Old
I've seen David Knight in a while I watched a little bit of him accidentally
Hour-and-a-half through the show or so maybe 2 hours
So David Knight fills in for the rest of the show
Looks good
Great looks good
You better look terrible as I go sort of pudgy older man
Probably a good 20 25 lb
I hate to say it but they denied
Griezmann
I don't hate it
I'm happy you're healthy
Can you imagine if Alex potato soup
Oh man Alex wearing a suit to work everyday that would be tough to handle
Batman wears a blazer
Usually but the top button
Button up shirt
Super male vitality
Alex Jones
Text Cliff
Back
What's the time
In order to create a business
Is going on
I've always said I'm going to solder 10% until they would win
That's near the end of the fourth quarter and you get
You're already so exhausted
Alright
To disrupt
That's what I'm here for
But you read the danger of that
Did all of us speak
Globalist
Weekend
Kind of
Connecticut
Lost in thoughts
Completely different subject
Anyone telling anybody about Infowars ain't at a library
So you can just stop
A black tail people at a library
Is not going to work
Go from stopping traffic to tell people in the library
That is indicative of a huge
Is it like earlier the show I told you why the idea
What Alex
A sort of himself
What I'm here to do is disrupt them
That's
And I think that if we really take a step back
And look at
The bigger picture of what
They're all con men
Certainly
All the people that we talked about
Is less
On this tip
But certainly Jim Bakker
Alex Jones
Maybe even more of a kind
Much better resume
Not it's not as big as that one horrible monsters woman that he had on there
Paula Cain
She's the premier conman so far that we've had on our this conversation
Perfectly
Because
I think that even beyond the con
Is what we talked about
Create a note
Breakdown
That's the car
These people are running but even beyond that
With their primary function
For someone else
Like someone else
Invest in them
But I don't think anyone's invested
Terry Testa
The reader
Them
Money is because what
The primary
Is to normalize
Ideas that we have already decided
That's true they
Create a scenario in a situation where
Alex
Get on air
Yeah f*** yeah I'm afraid of Muslims
Amen
Then what
Yeah
The public sphere as an acceptable thing to say
Overton window
To some extent I think it
I think that there is I don't
I'm not going to sit here and tell you that I think
That is
The entire game that's
Played
That was the goal all along
You look at what these
People have done
And you look at their careers over
Time
They're deeply invested
Isn't that sort of thing
Like the idea that Mike cernovich
Text from
Gamergate guy pickup artist
Community guy
Jumped over to
And then ended up
Alex Jones
Disciple
Kind of characters
But the things that we're going on in those different
Segments of his wife
The only real thing that connects all of them is making
Really f***** up things not as f***** up
Accusations
The pizzagate saying that your enemies are pedophile demons
That's true gamergate
Making threats
Doxxing that's
Just a part of
The normal
The cautionary things you have to deal with online
And then with Alex
He's playing
Escalation in that just from gamergate was about
Route a
Just a just a
All the way to James Gunn getting fired
You know like
There's there's definitely
That's definitely become part of the / Overton
For sure
Perfect
Bike path
Anything like
Deal with the most
Social media is so awful
Because
A lot of those things
Things are so normal
Like
Ideas that are being said in August of
5 years ago would have been
The f*** out of here
You're absolutely right
45% of Republicans want Trump
To be able to just close down media Outlets
You have to take
Guys like Alex Jones insisting that you can't trust anybody in the mainstream
These people
Their years of backstory
Abusing immigrants
Sort of policy
All of which is
Fine and you can't even
And
You are still offended when somebody calls you erase
Even though
Your guy is
Putting together whitener
Yeah so I think of that
To me is the best sex
Because I
What I said many time
This world doesn't have
Someone else like our
Like I know the pains up so much
But he is a talented guy with his heads in the right place
100 different distraction
He's really
Good
At being a propaganda
Yeah
Charismatic
Kind of funny from now and now and ask
He's the meme machine
But there isn't anyone else
Like Pacific
Absolutely.
Can't even f****** handle Alaska can't handle that
Todd can't handle that
Evnroll
Right Rogan isn't that like he is
He is a big part of normalizing a lot of these
These these things
Yeah
He also is somewhat
He's not
Toe the line
Not verleye
Exactly
He
He is willing
To just like
Drop it all and go Toad and you know like
This is what I'm going to say because this is part of what we're supposed to do
That onyx
Pushpak
UB that line
Now it's time
We've been
He still deserves a lot of criticism
For having these people I can't Peter Schiff on
Is crazy
He had
Recent Dave Rubin
Candace Owens
And both times
He asked them
Like real pointed
Questions that they could
Couldn't answer
Really embarrassing videos
Like to the point
Ruben we're both on his show
Not able to
Foundational
About what they
Just walked
F***** up
I'm so Joe Rogan is kind of an unwitting accomplice
I think
Because if he was awaiting accomplice
He could be doing
So much
Right
Who is Candace Owens
Candace Owens
Turning Point USA
She works at Charlie Kirk
You probably don't know who he is that's right
That's how she Rose
Prominent
Before that she was a celebrity
The the alt-right community under the name red pill black
And
What her
Beginning story
Was about
She was a liberal
And she was posting some
Chi-Chi's
Be good on her feet
Generally in
She has okay like
Camera presence
Question
Too hard to not really all that great
Liberal comedian
He works for the little while
Probably tired I have no idea
But now he's
Become
Conservative comedian
I got he's a YouTuber called the Rubin report
Disaster
In terms of like stuff we would want to cover
Because he also
In the same way that
I don't want to talk about like Bill Maher
Even though I hate him
I still give Dave Rubin a little bit of like
Decorative Benefield
And I don't want to sit here and read litigate your
Joke
So Candace Owens was making
Videos
Also
Nope
I got my timeline
She was running a company
Start a company
Believers on Kickstarter
A companies that would
Would lead into dachshund
Aware you would be able to find out the p
People who are harassing you
I don't remember the name of
But she was
Anthozoa
Send her a message
Yeah that was too effective like
Don't do that
This is the worst idea
Could possibly
This will only get
Get people to attack
I don't understand
Well it sounds admirable is
The sort of thing
That will
Wheatley blow up on these online to me right
And they will go after you super hard with no knowledge of who she is or
She went ahead with it
And then it blew up in her face exactly the way Zoe Nixon said it would
I can find her with Cynthia
And then to make matters even worse
Candace Owens
Relieved
With no
That she's ever given publicly
She believes
Zoe Quinn
I need a potato chili clamor
Where the one in Six Flags
Genuinely and artfully saying we want to
Protect you
Man she is stupid I've read a bunch
I've read a bunch about both sides of exchange the other side
And there's really no way to look at it reason
Knox
Is
Laming opport
Yeah like
It is
Absolutely no sense
What you know of
Essentially shook it off
As being like you know what
This is the world that I'm going to make money from so I have to accept that people are going to be
Extremely at Hollister
No I think what happened probably
Was.
Time
She probably got approached
Maybe
Maybe she started getting attacked
By the
Please troll Folk
Don't like the idea of a business
Get in the way of their trolling in
And I think
Even Docs
People who are
You know monsters online
I still don't think that's the best way to deal with
Like I think that's still
Could lead to
Bass
Yeah the doctor dangerous you're opening up a can of worms
Rid of bunch of arguments on like the defense of Shame being a powerful tool
That kind of stuff
And
If you are in a community where you're dealing with people
I think is a valuable tool
If you are in an anonymous cute
Community
Shane blind
Leaving to
F****** horrific
Justin
Stripped Away
Thursday
Equinox
Probably someone approached
I was like hey you know what
That's only a theory but like
I don't know
From that point on
She became a figure
Sort of a black
Supporter
Yeah absolutely amen she posted a bunch of dumb videos
And maybe some of them aren't that dumb I've only watched a few and I could
Mnui Kanye West was like I like the way she
She thinks
Sutter
We got to get out she's an above-average conservative
Is based on
Demographic
I said it essentially the same
She's a huge cat
The man somehow demographic utility
Is a really
Heart does good stuff
Talk about
Fridge conservative they have to go through
Well shofar
Big-time white sprout
Somebody everywhere
That is the
Is shadowbanned
3%
That's unfortunate
Because
You did put up a
Enough sites
Shadow Banning
With a
The headlines
Eliminated 90%
2 top conservative websites
Teen election
2017 Harvard in Columbia journalism review found that the Gateway pundit was 1/4
Most influential conservative news source
Because of this we were targeted in the scene are numbers related to Facebook and Twitter declined dramatically
And every single Facebook category our numbers are down
And Paige visits our numbers were Skyrocket
Before the election
Then in three numbers were cut off
That had nothing to do with the quality of our posts as we have proof that are generic
It off tickets go categories provided to us by Facebook our current numbers are below their linear projection
Of what we should be
In February Facebook launched another algorithm change their platform
With these changes with our traffic
We weren't the only ones affected
The algorithmic change caused President Donald Trump
Engagement on Facebook post
Plummeted whopping 45%
In contrast
Senator Elizabeth Warren has suffered a copper bowl
Decline in Facebook engagement
Unfortunate
Around
Facebook purchase accountant box
The idea that you're getting less traffic is probably because of less automated activity on those social media
What you're doing is basically putting out a study where you own your
Yourself a little bit you play yourself out
Because if like legitimately
If there was a 90
3% drop
In there traffic
Coming from
Coming from Facebook
Open Twitter
What you would hear
Is
Unbelievable outcry
People that were looking for it
And isn't there
Like 93% of the people who previously were all about Gateway pundit
Now
Nope
Way pundit
It would be
Crazy hair
Now these people complaining
Don't get me wrong
Certainly not proportion
93%
Has now been cut off
Did the audience isn't concerned about it
You are everything
You know it's because
Cuz that was fake
AutoZone L on this I know it because of that image
Is a study
The Gateway pundit did follow the traffic
Chick from Facebook
Four numbers website awful ones like Breitbart Daily Caller and Gateway pundit
As well as something that you've never heard of like one called
A hundred percent
Never heard of that and the only thing that the study shows
Is that they have dropped
Considerably
In Facebook engagement
Now if that's true and we trust
These stats
They're not
Necessarily authenticating but siding
They put the numbers
Interceptor all go ahead
You know old stipulate that those numbers are true
I would say if you guys had a real good run
A weird reason
And I bet your numbers are coming back down to where they should have been based on the quality
Hope you're clearly not
Tru report
Ikea
That they would have had a
During the 20
There's just no reason I can think of and there was that
Are articles it's very clearly pointed out the
Sharp uptick in traffic to Breitbart and then Sharp
Drop
Almost to the exact same point
As if there was
Fake engagement
And you have
Who was who would want to do that
I don't know
With the resources and the know-how
Influence
Who knows
I guess total mystery
Completely
Blindsided by this information
Speaking of total Mysteries
We now get to again
Store Media Matters for
I would like either of them
To have
We problematic
Most like them
To bring up
This interview
This is a guy we have not necessarily seen before on Ark
Understanding the threat
The nation
Winterizing the tailed assessment
Counterinsurgency strategy
Oh that's not good
That's the only website that allows you to find out where Muslims live and
Show up at their house and f*** them up wheeler alert he also trains
Cops
Notably
Maricopa
County cops
Why isn't he
Well I don't know I don't know
So he sucks
Already we just know that from
We know that from Alex's intro
Maricopa County
Bankrate
True
Few things and then
His life's work
What I think the problem is the biggest threat Alex
Izzat
And I don't mean you and me
Find me an hour leadership
That has
Forgotten
And been criminally negligent and I wish you'd stop there
I couldn't we could have a Baseline
Of like
Yeah yeah yeah
In defending their owners of office
Which is a
Legally binding
Understand who we are I think
If our leaders understand who we are
And what the underpinnings of the Republic
Then when the marches and the Communist in the Socialist
Any Islamic movement
The jihadis
Come along
We we easily
Shrug them off as being absurd and we won't let him in our society have any play
Okay
Bad
Not great
Negative
Output
Column
-4
Cuz you have no idea
John Gandolfo
I don't know
Is FBI background to lend himself credibility for his training course it was l a
Civilians alike is the controversial manner in which he depart
Did the federal law enforcement
In 2,000 resign from the bureau in disgrace after a number of ethical breaches in business
Contact
Including admitting to having affairs with female FBI agents
And confidential Source he was assigned to protect during the corruption case
A former US rep William Jefferson Democrat from Louisiana
He also solicited that witness for a 75,000 donation
That's not good
From an article in the New Orleans time
Picayune
According to court documents unsealed last week the FBI and it's office of professional responsibility
As far back as December that the relationship with a confidential
He thought could damage the investigation
But they never passed it in
Information to the US attorney's office Prosecuting Jefferson
Who was the lead FBI agent in the investigation
This is just unbelievable said George Washington University law professor Jonathan
Is the FBI was aware that an agent
Improper relationship
The confidential source
Should have been disclosed to the court
It's very disturbing said Harvey silverglate a Boston lawyer and author of recent book
Critical of federal law enforcement
First of all should be having an affair with the government
Informant
If it does happen course it must be disclosed because it because it could affect the credit
Ability
Yep.
Mod that's the informant that he was playing around with
I included in the unskilled document
She said she gone do engaged
Mild intimacy
In New Orleans in April 2005
Occasions Gondola McCook in propria sexual advances in a car
A townhouse and her parents home
On one occasion she said he was overly aggressive
But she fended him off
Once or twice then between April and May 2005
From there
He resigned from the FBI in disgrace
I began inciting hatred and fear of Muslim
From a lateral move
Help
From a 2012 article in the Associated Press
Virginia-based
My group is leading the training being held this week at the World Outreach Church
Murfreesboro
During a conference
Controller said that local mosques
Front organization
Thanks for the Muslim Brotherhood
They do not
Have a First Amendment right to do any
Cordello's said then
He did not return a message from the Associated Press seeking comment in time for the store
Muslims are never First Amendment
These people who love the
In March 2018 Southwest Airlines
Condemned John Gunn.
A former FBI agent
Getting his Arizona law enforcement agencies and controversy
They they called him what he did
Inappropriate
Target
Unemployed
Controller poster
Tweet picturing an unidentified worker
At the airport as he traveled
Western conservative conference
I wish this were shocking
A Sharia adherent Muslim on my my plane
He wrote adding the hashtag quote Sharia kill
Suggest like I
Just like a person
Yeah just a random dude
It is a deep history of June this year
In September 2017 poster pictures he took of to TSA employees
Just based on the fact that they looked Arabic
With the caption quotes
Am I the only person who sees a problem with terrorist protecting us
Nothing like
LaGuardia Airport TSA uniform
What a f****** pile of s***
Can't put my finger on it
What a monster it's almost like
Judges people
Like there
Content
Instead
The color of theirs
Right
I agree
So we had we have a guy
Who's going around
Touting his FBI credentials in order to
Do these
Anti-muslim law enforcement
Anything
We really just
Heap book
But it's not about some sort of
Fear of radical Jihad or anything like that
Get triggered by the idea that anybody who might be of Arabic heritage
Is working at an airport
Taking pictures of people
It's not like those people were like
Conversation
No talk to them
Muslims aren't there clearly pictures that were taken without these peoples
Camera
Probably
It's crazy like this guy is a
Dick Alex is having him on the show.
Talk about these
Threat
Like socialism and Islam in America
What
The movie crime
Right
To anonymously and then posts
Blessed weekend
That's true professional problem
With what
He does it clearly
It's not based on actual
Evidence
Based on hatred
While he was
Working for the FBI that almost jeopardized
Investigation
That's grounds for a mistrial right there
No because what we just talked about earlier
Yeah I know but you should be that should be then like a
And they're like
We're going to either invalidate this thing or read
Cuz our justice system is great
The case was
Successful
Against
What was that guy's name
William Jeff
Person represented
The corruption case
And when they try to appeal it on the grounds that they didn't disclose at the
Immediately
Stocked up
Like I think I think that it's probably
Fair
That they decided not to rehear the case
Because it was not
Necessarily substantiv
The case itself
Of Korat behavior on the part of an agent and that's why he had to
F****** hit the brick
But like a
In terms of the actual case
All he was doing
Was driving her to meet with him
And posing as
The driver
So their relationship wouldn't have actually
It wouldn't have changed
The outcome of
The information that was gathered by her wearing a wire talk to him
I understand why the appeal would be unsuccessful
But it is
The epitome of
Unethical Behavior
Ask
Coming of someone who
We hope
Would be in that position
What is a
They still killed Fred Hampton they murdered him
Right
Just f*** Fred Hamm
That would be great
Probably the worst
Song is this
You know what I'm
What
Anyway it's grounds for a
Has but otherwise
Repackaged
Avis exit we get the last little piece of John gondolas
And then I have a
Real harsh criticism
Of the narrative
He's putting out there
Talks about all the time
Sort of his Mane
Deeply deeply
Police log
Millions of people are dead
From
Marxist communist socialist movement
Millions of people have been killed
By The Sword of Islam
In the 1400 years that they've existed
And their Doctrine supports it that's the difference
Neighbors
Neighbors neighbors
So Jordan
Alex and his guests have brass balls compared to deaths
Socialism
Marxism
Consider the statistics
Ignoring the number of deaths you can easily associate
As a direct result of capitalism
Or Christianity
The USA is responsible for between 10
15 million deaths in Vietnam Korean and Iraq Wars that we had
Very subtle proxy wars in Pakistan
Other places around the world
So just was pointless Wars that we've been intimate
World War
Between night
29 million deaths
Children die every day because of the direct consequences
8 million
Thirty thousand a year
Consider the idea that there was a very robust Native American population
In America
Consider the
Entire slave trade after all look the more capitalistic
Then let's talk about Christianity
34-in Archbishop of Bremen ordered the slaughter of a group of
Setting
Leaving to between 5,000 and 11000
They were there because they were
Intersection of Christianity
Capital
Jesus said that directly you know what he was all about
Money for the church
Catholic Church killed about twenty thousand people in The albigensian Crusade which they launched because they didn't like
Cow the cathars had
The cathars in 1209
I would have difficulty telling the difference between the cathars
So the app
Kill them all the Lord will the Lord will recognize his own
Then there's the other Crusades all the inquisition's all centuries
Witch hunting slash burning
The history of colonialism
Failed missionary Activity The Mysterious look Hibbetts in
The genocide
Pretty regularly
Top commission Eric's Behavior
The Spaniards found pleasure in inventing all kinds of odd cruelty
They built a long
Long enough for the toes
The touch the ground
Repent strangulation
And then hang 13 natives at a time and honor
Of Christ Our Savior of the 12 apostles
Then straw was wrapped around their torn bodies and they were very burned alive
Population of Hispaniola was reduced from 400000
They killed so many natives that they had to begin importing slaves from other Islands
Quote unless the normal lifetime of a single human being
An entire culture of millions of people
Thousands of year residents at their home
Had been experimenting
And I'm going to say
In fact
The problem
Is not religion
No problem
F******
It is not
They were the ones
Between Christianity
And Islam is
F****** patriarchy
There's a big part of that
Like at the end of the day
F******
Man
These people are f******
Apes they're not
Human beings there they're just a weird like
Mix of all of The evolutionary behavior in the lizard brain and
Dude that I want
Is that
I don't think
Like communism has killed
The amount of people that Alex
Pretends they have probably
Because a lot of it is mismanaged
They always over-inflated statistic
Text to include like
We talked about that
No doubt No Doubt
Unfortunate byproduct of
Miss manage
They also
Because of me
Natural trends
What happened
On the ground
The idea of
You know 22,000
Children die every day
Because of
Like Direct
Poverty causes
That is being done
By capitalism
Like that is a direct result of it is the violin
End of what capitalism.
The thing that you don't want to look at
I don't think that I don't think
Christianity
Islam is responsible for the other death
Either I think it's
Like you say it's dude
Evil dudes
Use a system in order to in
Powers are evil
Yep
Now this is really its fault
East Capitol
Because
Greed
I mean
Yeah absolutely
No I think at the end of the day
What were say
Is that we should all go to Seattle and murdered
It's not what we are all saying
Again
A real dude
Go to bed
For like 20 years
You get out of here for a while
But it'll be too late
I love
Learning about his history
No problem
I ended up
Running out of time because I was like oh my God
Capitalism
Christianity
Responsible
Very f*****-up over the
The years that Alex doesn't want to talk about
Almost ended up
Like we would have talked about that for now
Just because I would have been like
We can get off that
John gondolas gone now
And now
We come to the end of Alex's
Cuz I like I said David lights
For the end of the show
Getting out early
When I said earlier in the show that we're doing
Did Alex is fake
Is in his own hands
Victims inspire
Like I don't think
You don't think he's got this
This is what
Coming
On the day that he gets
Kicked off everything no I don't think
This is good
Globalist
But I don't like Hollywood
Carsponsors
Your sponsor
But they got a price
That is a price Barbarian
What's the price
Advocate all truth
Instruments of racketeering
Only then will you be
But even in terms of time he's done that exact
Same thing in the past
You got I got bored I got zoned out a little bit
I kept thinking about how maybe it's
Because of cake that he
Me that I wanted to live
Where are unlike any other band
Much better
Not really
Cake is better than all those bands or anything like that but I don't see any other
Around that time when I was at 8
The same way
I think cake was
Very unique
Not like
The distance necessarily
That's not my the right where I live
I love like a commissioning a sin
Symphony in C
Not necessarily of their sound but like what
Makes them
Weird what makes the really great the opposite of
From there
Quotes no no no no
For Honor
What made that song
Great.
In the other songs like this
Or I will survive
What is a better Zone.
Conversation we have about Alex
Turn to do like a
So here's why this music from the 90s wasn't as good as you
A boring facsimile of Alex doing
Demon voice
Uninspired
It's not like
There's nothing behind it that we haven't heard
Before
It's like
So I am
What was the MTV for like forever
S*** now I'm going to lose my mind a Long Jacket
It wasn't
They were a bass driven band
In a world full of guitar-driven
Play pool
I don't like that like that world
Is there train was built around the vocals of that guy because they were so terrible
They're strongly disagree
Because
I'm telling you right now this will just walk around in circle
That was why that was what
Anyways
Lineage
It's based upon.
Getting off the hook
A good that album wasn't that great
Okay so singles
Soul coughing
I'm telling you this is the greatest show
Single from 1994
Heard that song
Down to this
North
None of these Charter
None of you started except Circle
Baccarat notes very different but but he
New York Louise is listening
Obama's was fine
S*** I used to listen to the track all the time soundtrack
Demaree
What was it
Now I can't remember I remember listening to this
And around
Whenever I was driving
Going to go visit a bunch of colleges
There is this song
Wherein they talk about
What
What's the name of the I think you're probably trying to come up with
What is no more parties in LA
Kendrick Lamar
What's the name of it
How many lose my life
Will lose my goddamn mind
The distances
The best ones
Sheep go to heaven that was
Yeah that's about it
Let's talk about it now let's talk about tonic
It is
No it really is
Notice.
But love is surely better when it's gone
S***
Everybody
People are going to post in the group the song that I've taken
And it's going to murder me
I hope it's just
Talk about how great
Noah
But I did love that song when I was younger
It's one of those long rambling songs
Is it one of those long rambling songs where the guy talks
It's where he talks about losing my mind anyway
We got it
We can't do this anymore
From so
We're coming to the end of this episode
Yeah
Alex Matos
Is this mouse has done his
The demon voice
And now he's going to try
Mistake
On people
Not defy
Really weird
Because they see whatever
Existing
Problem but it's perfect
Overthrow
The internet
Everyone in Street
Socially conformed
What is the token of travel
I said we want you to
Don't promote Alex Jones
So everyone
What Pole
I mean Alex
Attacking him is the market
The token of travel
It doesn't help
That's true
Everybody else with a large platform has
Essentially ignored
Thank you to everyone who does like our show
The rest of the world
It's not like some
Magical golden ticket
Willy Wonka Factory of
Search engine optimization hits
So like
This is cockamamie
It's one of those things
I love it
Having to dig
Deep into his bag of
Trick
And bring out all of these things
Like he's bringing out the idea that like
It's the market
The Beast
2 attack
Then also the colonel Travis metaphor with remember info
Stuff just to rationalize like
I got to keep people on board
What I see here
Ice-T
You know I don't I don't
I don't I don't know if it's just
My awareness
I see a guy who's been bluffing
For a long time
Who like realizes now
Play poker table is
Nicole
Like you realized
October point it didn't look like YouTube
Facebook
And it didn't look like they had
We're going to play nowhere
The Riverhead
And they made their straight
Or whatever
I've been using way too many poker now but like that's what's going on
He's like
I know I'm going to
Afford
But I'm going to sit here and
For a little while
She brings out some of the familiar narrative
He has on his llama photo because
Keep the status quo going
You know it is
Honestly I wanted him to freak out
That's what I wanted to
That's what it would have been it seems like
Yeah like I think
You surrendering a little bit
Maybe that's a monkey's paw situation
Is
And so we have to
Scramble to find somebody else
No 2009-2010
In the present day
How things got to
You know like I do
I don't think the present
Day taking down of Alex
Except
It's harder for me to find the ax
Episodes
You know like I am through hurdles a little bit in order to find them
But that
Think that's a small issue
Alex Jones disappears tomorrow
From every single platform
For whatever it's that happen
We can do this show for a very long time
Right
Uncovering like
How did this happen
What are the transformation
Like we could do this year for the next five years is going back through his archives
Interesting history
Because the present
He's not that interest
Even if
Kicked off all of
These platforms isn't that interesting
What if we
Exactly
Very absolutely
The people are accusing
Strawman argument
Celtic Defender
It's nothing
It's not different at all
It's boring
Either he does or he dies
I think I'd like I said
Yeah
Probably I'm really interested
Begone because
Because he failed to evolve
Yeah like
Laughter
When you are in this game
Pretends he's the best at
You got a key
Keep swimming got to keep going
Embarrassment
Going along
Pizzagate man have
Apologizing
But if you don't play by that that game
What you end up
So reserved
That you aren't you have no traction you are
Cutting Edge you want
You aren't interesting
The idiots that are your Market
The problem is he's playing
We're so used to him always playing
Offense but he's trying to play offensive
Yeah but
He's yelling
Chinese dentist
King-style
To be Rodger Stone
Like the the playoffs
Book of always attack never defend works
You have been doing that since
Seaward
Or something like that
High-stakes level
Alex
It's not really had any real pushback
Tell a couple
Like I know that he had people who are like
You're a chance f*** you're a show you're an idiot and yet like that
But it's the same thing with like I get comments on our website
Think about
Blogs I wrote
Stuff like that there like
Soros is a demon you should know that and like
Fair enough the next
Existential crisis
Hello anyway and this is how Alex
Pizza the show
To go out a little bit dramatic
A little bit longer but
I think
I left
Okay
Everybody's fight
My podcast
You do your child
You were transphobic
We organized the last
Number one most important
This is about coming after you're free
This is about the big
And
I could go for an inch
Your friends your family
Everybody work with
Talk about yourself
American
What
The shot everybody else down so
Why don't you be afraid
Infowars.com show
Announcer iPhone ad
I'm probably 15
YouTube Facebook and Twitter probably the next
Everybody else said that yesterday
Why do you see links on the Articles podcast
You're not going to take advantage of the pig
Action Auto
That's how he decides
The M.G.'s time before handing the Baton
To David.
Do you know what
I heard
He should probably not bring on a meetings on air
No
The same
Tone
When we did our lives showing off
That was the same tone as his last episode being broadcast live
So you're implying
And we don't we don't know this
He knows
You're implying that he knows that there's more to come of his downfall
Is not
Yet been not having
And we are recording we know that
Is gone
So yeah I mean I don't know I don't know what else in the world can do to
Cuz it's not like some organizations
I'm going to be able to take away is short
Or something like that
There are things that are just intrigued
I will put this out
And if you will Re-Boost it
Then yeah
There is still
Still Market
Access
But it's
I agree with you though
What I hear is resignation
Yep I hear
And I dunno
The next week
Maybe it's a bad day
You know maybe the day it had maybe the day it happened
What you expected
Becomes in guns blazing
And he's just like
F****** tired
So maybe it's like a thing where he shows up
To work is like
To get with
Writer's room
Come up with like a Rodger Rodger tell me what to do
As part of the coverage of the manafort trial they had a picture of manafort
Fan Rogers
Stone and
Some other assholes
Probably
I'd like the 7th
God Rodger Stone looks
Like a
F****** rat
Sane
Bring me Rodger Stone documentary
Because
Propaganda thru-and-thru is anything
Interesting
Because the town that they were setting up
Turn this off
Way to fry
As much as I Rodger Stone
Loki Behavior to be
Loki was described
The show Neil Gaiman
You're listening
Justice
Cuz he was mentioned.
I don't want
Information that's what you can turn it off
Honestly think that we said most of what we feel and most of what we need to say about
This episode The 86
He's fixing episode of Alex Jones 86 on 86
Now that it's not bad even though we set it at
Couple times it's still has a real great
I don't know what the future will bring
I don't pretend to
Even as someone who studies in my town
I can't predict
The future
I can and I think you have also felt
Weakness
I'm like we said
Maybe it's a maybe it's a momentary lapse
Swinging harder than ever
I think it's probably in Plaza
But
I don't know
Really matters
Because
What Alex Jones and body is it still just as dangerous even if he's
Not on
Facebook even if he's not on YouTube
The reach
Is diminished
The people who are being abused by him
Are still being hurt by
Yeah those people are still there
People are going to
Become more radical
Because they feel that these orders action
Reinforces married
Yeah so you end up in a position
Well yeah you know two steps forward one step back
To some extent
We've Ended up further down Alex Jones
The timeline
The Narrative perhaps
Don't think that is what I'm talkin
When I said his fate is in his hands
He should realize
I think he does on some level
This works
He just doesn't know how to make it
Right
Because certain level there is a real opportunity that's actually become available
That he will not
Know how to take it because
He believed that if
He's doing what he's doing
It will work out now
Because it always has
He's gotten into somewhat of a holding pattern with him
Yeah yeah a little bit
Would really take for him
Get
Through this
Val venis
Sure
Get those Japanese
It would really take is for him to get more extreme
Same
Similar things to narrative a little bit
And cut it out with some of the
Stuff that really is problem at
Like we're talk about active races
Write that sort of stuff
That's all it would really take if you scaled some of that but that would also probably lose
Bunch of Azadi
I don't know
Here's what does
Here's how he does it
Alright
He
Goes for the Redemption
Narrative
Healer no cuz he learned that everyone realize whatever
The Redemption in like we like
I mean he goes the full opposite direction
I've been fighting this whole time
The Republic Tavern
Protect
Was going to save us and at the end of the day
He did not speak for me
And if he doesn't speak for me and you know what we really need to do
We need to send a message not just to the mainstream media but to the government as it is who has
President-trump
And he listens to our power until he
We will fight
The circumstances are almost perfect to that story that I brought up about
Restaurants
I hate
The idea of this climate hoax
But bulshit can't make their own rules make a principled stand on
Against climate change
But what matters
That's yeah I must
I must
Philosophically make my break
More likely is within
End up on Project Camelot
Cuz he's going to realize big Kerry Cassidy now has a bigger reach today
So we can look forward to that episode
That'll be great one so fun
Can't wait for him to show up as a guest on a bunch of weirdo a****** YouTube channel god dammit
Anyway Jordan
If you wanted to find
We have not
Many social media
No
Feel like you pointed still not willing to hold
Well they're not willing to do a lot of snow
You can go to my Facebook
Members join the group
About that are Facebook
Page is not so active
But the Facebook group
Please
If you like the show
I appreciate you liking the page
But the group is the way to go
Ross on iTunes
Rick Williams that's pretty excited
It is your turn
But I'm going to tell you I have a
You're going to
Well I have only one cat
He's a
For me
Adorable
This one
He wasn't on this episode
I hope you
Burned alive
You know what I want alternative dolo isn't from Arizona a latrine
Like I just want him to be held in a hole while everybody
Everybody
Just
Does their business on top of
Drake Jordan drones
Is a stickler for language
Make him
Inside of a train
Arizona just did some training with the Maricopa County Sheriff's Department
I know I would save it my person
Who's the worst
Is that the commander from
Who told via Catholic K2
God will sort them out or go f*** yourself
Alex