Alex
Beverages
Thoroughly by Alex Turner
Twitter
We came up afterlife
Episode
Being
If he had done this thing
Same things
Then he did on those other platforms on Twitter when their rules are what they are now
They would kick
Take him off which sounded like a pretty good argument
Like
I would believe that Alex
Cuz more careful with what he posts
Okay, but it turns out it's not
Cool revealing themselves
To be first up
Not because of this incident but Twitter has a hardcore history of being that that
Alright guy
Hardcore history
Another podcast too long is the only one that we can really
Knox
There's only so many hours in the day
I'm not sure if you have time for us
Is good stuff good stuff speaker good stuff
I know a lot about you
That's why I would like to give a shout out to
Very exciting
Stafford
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Last
So I believe
Another Chris
Confused
What would we got we got a bunch of Georgia
We got a lot of Georgia's where the biggest George podcast
In the world I think
We got we got a lot of overlap
That is okay alright people let's fire you from the New York Times or whatever it is people are doing now
Early advocate for white genocide
No judgement
Damn you know.
Mike those are
Those are your McDonald's
No judgement
You didn't choose it
Picture of it started off everyday
We talked about Alex Badoo
Give a plug to our phone line
You can call us and leave a message
530 neon nip
Anthony
Restart the show at like 2
Hard for this
The greatest thing that ever happened to you
Hi Danny this is Jack also from Chico California I can verify that policy block Devin is
California
I also believe that you may have come by this number by some sort of criminal action and I am
Coming for you
Make all of this go away
Still mine and policy demands for Elijah go in Chico California
End of my audio Ransom note
Do Morton Baker episode
Wow
What up what you want to call
Only playing call everyone you must call
Phone number
I will take a hundred percent those both came from 530i code so it's not like people pretend
Pending
From Chico
It's not
How many of our listeners are American
I can't figure
I could give you a firm number on that was it
20%
Chico's
That's not after people from
From the town of a random phone number because of
We probably have as many people who listen to Athens
Chicago's we do in
Chicago
I have to wait a little while to play those
Set the chico out-of-the-way Forest
Will never clear the chico.
My friend
To go through call
Bzak
Information source
Secondary
We got to do this show and Chico baby
I don't think we can do
About
You were too rather than
Like
And say that you'll go to the
Authorities
To take us down
Instead go to the authorities
Tell them to pay for RV
Sure I will do travel
Operator
So I'm the first call to the other Chico
Episode
From Zack
Has Jim Bakker ever been on Project
Not that I can tell
But
We can only honor one of these people's request
We can combine them like
Speculating might be possible
Let's see which one we're doing
We're so smart
Look at the mess America's Inn
Blithe
You have made it about
We're so smart
We control all aspects
And look what kind of bachelor in business crazy
Real interesting parallels with the World of Alex Jones
Specific
That will get into as it goes along
Crazy
So it's going to be
Anderson
I am dating your contract hair with
Because of the bartender
Surprise
Is Mark Zuckerberg
With that
Familiar
Intro jingle
And welcome to the Jim Bakker Show
Please give a warm welcome to my dad and the baker
Welcome to Grace Street
Today
Good to be here was the co-host
She said she was a cold stuff
No she's not even enough and also a singer
I don't think they play Tai Chi like
If you go back to the
Early stuff on Jim Baker's youth
YouTube channel
She's fine time in a day
Can do with it
And not
5-minute videos of Tammy Sue Bakker singing head to get a pass
She actually is
Concrete
Yeah it's okay there
Okay
Just passed away
It's sad
Left up eclipse for Jim is talking about it
Because it's so gross
To hear like
Human moment from him
Haha
Survival box
It's not it doesn't seem sincere
Hey I had the best in-laws in the world or whatever
Later he's going to try and get you to buy
Can ionizing water bottle
13 years of
Actually drove me to not include that stuff
Humanizing in some way even though
Brings a little bit
Shoei
Is that I watched another episode of his show
Yeah it was
We're not going
Was it was after Hurricane
Harvey
He was running a
Promotion
Did you buy a bucket
You get a bucket one goes to Hurricane Harvey relief
Anyway
Gross which makes me wonder what the markup is
It's probably
Exorbitantly heard the name
Billet
It looks like
Looks like boy
But its Billet
No I have never heard of Mark Bila
No one has that side
Very Fringe weirdo community
But he's on the show cuz he's got a book
30 +
Interesting Lee Jim says biswas
To do its business model
I have something that's been
Affected
For quite a while
I stopped endorsing books
Six months or a year ago
Yes we said absolutely no more books
Because we lost our shirt on books
That's pretty
Pretty wild
Budget Rental
Reply I'm ahead of time usually and then if they don't sell
And ever since we've been selling more books than any Ministry in in in America
Is that crazy
But this is an unusual book
What's
And it opens up are you ready to go on the most thrilling adventure of your life
Good to me there's nothing more exciting than a treasure hunt
And where about
To embark on what we're going to do that
On this program.
That's exciting is this Jesus Vines
So I don't know if you picked up all the pieces there but what happens if books on
Spec yeah Consignment prices
Hey what's up
He's not been able to move these f***
So he's been taking a condom
With the book
We're just going with the bucket
Can't do the books anymore
These weirdos to come on my show are not good enough writers
We can't do it but this guy
Mark biltz
Lured him back into the world
The book
Because I
Differently I guess iPhone
We're no longer endorsing book
Because we lost our shirt
And ever since we stopped
Losing ever since we've stopped
Endorsing books
Now we've sold more books than any other Christian Ministry
But you have to
Considers that he's an old crazy rainbow
Doesn't make sense as that
We stopped selling books
It would imply that they could all of the books
That they had bought
Before or whatever
I guess it's an inch
Interesting business model
You running but it's the same thing with like the America
For Prosperity buying up all of like Shawn
Books
Stuff like that it is or the right-wing me
Media model
Betty's doing
So
In effect what
He's doing is paying these people to be on his show
There's a financial incentive for them to come on the show because those books are bought
Jim Baker's buying those books
They don't have to worry about the audience
Yeah they're not buying books
From the guest
Anymore
Once they come on the show there
Jim Stafford
So
That's a really f***** up relationship to have
People's book
Is because he's selling his own
Supply
To be an advertising
Tool of gyms
Yeah
Gratitude
10000 copy
So you're saying with Americans
A prospect
Towards how many books are sold to the public hasn't sold them
There
I mean ten thousand bucks
I'm going to get you on
In addition to other places they're probably doing the same thing you might be able to rack up
Something close to a best
It's all very
We still don't know exactly what Mark is talking about imply that nobody
Who watches
Jim Bakker knows how to read
There's a worse percentage than the general public probably correlation does not equal causation
But there's a high correlation
Forget how to read
Emergency with this guy's book is about
Partially
Mark biltz is here with us he's the manager
Discovered the blood moons I guess
And
So much is going on
So much
What's happening in our presidency what's happening in our country
We are in serious trouble
I believe
America
Has got to stop mocking God
President who wants to stop killing babies
That's what they do that's what about in this country
Oh yeah
Who ever heard of
Destroying a president
In his first week
It's really it's really fun cuz we're 2009 and Alex started making The Obama Deception
Before and Audra
Negative
Seagate
Ready
But it's a thorkell revisionism
Episode that stupid
But I'm probably not
Insane right
Of 2008
2010 probably did give Obama a chance
But it's probably such a small
Meaningless population
Compared to
Creamy
Lynching Effigies and burning them population
Yeah I bet it's kind of
It's kind of moods
Give that tip of the cow
TV conservative
Republican party is gone
Benefit of the doubt
The blood moon
I was wondering how you could discover those
If you were born after the year
Z
Negative
Like what
Well 200 how old is
What are the evolved from multiple sources
Million years ago and they've all kind of
Enter Brad over that time.
And spread about
Enzo Iowa
System of
Astronomy
Will probably be
Probably
To guide
No
I thought it was is that what it is
Full moon
Eclipse will end up looking
Refracted sunlight
It seems like that it has nothing to do with that
It sounds really scary that's our blood moon obviously
But it's very innocuous space
Phenomenon
Was
Most likely coin by Mark Bell
He wrote a book about it after
Aftermarket already written
Talk about it but what they're describing
Call diluter tetrad
EarthSky
The word is
Describe four successive
Total lunar eclipses
No partial lunar eclipses
Between
Each of which has separated
From the other by 6
Lunar moth
6 full moon
So
You understand what that means
I did are they describing
Is it another like 666 situation here
The numbers do sounds like it might be going that direction
Target
It's a thing where they are
Whenever you said six months
And then I was like
Six months between
Time there would have been partial eclipse
The partial eclipse that falls in
Full lunar eclipse
Right man just happened
Sent the Year One
T2 times
Next will happen over the years 2030 to 2:20
What's the lifetime half before this one
67 +
68th and before that
For that was
2008 built
Notice that the lunar tetrad
I was coming up with
Jewish holidays
And began pretty
Second coming of
Jesus was Eminem
In the fall of 2015
It's a pretty
Yep
He predicted that in the fall of 2000
The beginning of the tribulation
M.
Jesus's return
So that I don't like the Jesus return
Is simultaneous with a Blood Moon, election
Splash blood moon 2018
Was the beginning of tribulation
I don't think he ever fully
You no make that
Jump at least I haven't heard
It is interesting
Ideas
Before that
Weird story
Man
I want to find this episode so bad but I couldn't find it
I really want to watch this
You predicted that the blood moons were coming
And
I wouldn't tell
So much
But I'm Jim Bakker so I have to
Few days ago
I had a man come in my audience and sit right there
And in the middle of the program and we were typing I think
Several shows that day
Yeah when you started yelling at me
Cursed me
Did you go to
Is it would be allowed within 20 miles
Told me I should be stoned to death
A man who
Was quoting scripture
Did he threaten little man that does sound like this is what's crazy
Did he threaten to pee in your throat and God hating our president wanted to destroy things and
The church people fighting each other
He was accusing me is
Accuse me of
Lying about blood moons
Noah
I love it I want that episodes
I know that
Keystone
Men
In his defense
I am almost
I don't know what
So
I assumed at some point you're going to explain
Why a blood moon
Is so
Important
Because
Blood moon
Question
In the Years 2014 and 2015
Happened
Jewish
Days
According to Jewish calendar
Calendar
It would have fallen on
It's whatever whatever holidays in September in the one that's in April
Because
Landed on those days
On the exact
Yeah but that is actually not that
The Jewish calendar is based on the moon
Is a lunar calendar
So the idea that the holidays
Pacific Cycle
It would be surprising for regularity
Guys wrong but
Now we just get to enjoy him talking
Soap in this next clip also
We've already sort of
That was a couple of
Preliminary objections
Guys.
They start with a very
To us
I'd like to do a preemptive self-defense
Over the idea that this is Billy
How were the blood moons of 2014.
Significant what was the significance of them
I know and I'll talk to the rabbi about it too
Great
And yet you got people who want to stand up and say
What's going on
What's going on I got enough Warfare without fighting church people
First off you remember it says it was in the days of Noah
And as it was in the days of lot also be with the coming of the son of man
It says
Was speaking about
The
The destruction coming
He was as one who mock
So that's almost like a preemptive warning of like you want to be like
Your own peril
Hey
Going to be a disaster
Well I'm going to go ahead and block not necessarily God
God
How
Rebuild an unmovable map
What I don't know how that joke again
Wilmer Valderrama hosts of The Great MTV show
Yo mama
Yoga
I've tried to add God into it and it didn't go well
Your God is so good
How
Response
If you start it and then I have to say how fat
I know what comes out today
Not on f****** wild Williams
Next clip
Hear what Mark is like a man
Give you a warning
That's all
I mean a lot of people first off
Was the first to discover the blood moon
Guess what the connection is
That's John Hagee
Did they put the sign Bridges out
What to say
Calendar
Would you be surprised to learn that he's on the show selling a Biblical calendar
Calendar that would almost
Great work
Is that
He doesn't make
Prediction
Other books
You know people make those
What is 7 2018
He predicted that Jesus was
Coming back in the fall
15 and we're in 2017 now so he's obviously got Jesus on his guests
Elation started in 2015 praise God we know we are now safe and have another seven years to get more
Work done for the
So that would imply that when he's on Jim Bakker Show in 2017
Figure five more gears 5 more years
He's on the map
Who is dated 2017
And Mike is this just a repeat from 2015
Cuz why is he talking about all this
Stuff about the blood moon
2 years ago nothing happened especially when he's already
Because it's a repeat
Do the talkin about being president
So we have to have been in 2017
It's very confusing
Like I said he likes to pretend that he never made a specific predict
About the end times
Blood moon
Timer 2014 2015
But unfortunately the publication
Show
Prophecy in the news
The news are probably in
45-minute drive time on the Dan Ryan
Jesus is coming in about two weeks.
This we're going to see in 2015 on the first day of the first month it again on the 1st
7th month
Mark biltz
Exactly
The interviewer
Which is the Jewish New Year and then
Concludes it is tishri 1
That concludes the sabbatical year
Felt
Yeah
Interviewer
Wow
Built yes
Interviewer
It's time for the Messiah to show up right
Built
Yeah
This is like a tennis match
It's so excited!
Well that's
Alright
Apple I will not allow any! In trance
Turn on
All caps
But all caps
Suffice it to say
Make predictions
Soap
Okay so what I don't understand
Utterly normal phenomena
That happened
Regularly
And has happened
I would assume since both the Earth and the moon have been in
62 *
Tetrad
Not what he's talking about them falling on these specific
Jewish feast days
8 * since 16
Right which is the first time it's happened
Jesus's
Apparently
Hey using the exact same information
Uses You could argue the blood moons or just really about bad Blizzard's hitting
Chicago
1967 and 2015 there were two
Ratably bad snowstorm
But then Chicago repented so everything was okay
We're no Lots over here
All I can go to Big Lots over here
It's
I don't know
One of the biggest issues
Did I don't think he ever deals with
Is the fact that
The lunar tetrad
From 2014
He's using this based on
Hebrew calendar it's all about it
That's what it's all about
The first three of those four eclipses were not visible in Israel
Which kind of hurts the fear no
It's like doesn't mean it's not
Signal
About you know how
Build it during the road
Oh I just like
Three out of every four times
You make it is invisible part
Bring that want to bring in the supermoon
It's because often they douche appear red because they're during the eclipse and refracted light from the sun
Okay
A red eclipses more often in specific
Generally speaking when you have a full moon that is an Eclipse which is necessary for the lunar tetrad
Partial
Eclipse General you're not going to have
I don't fully understand
But apparently when it's a full moon and a lunar eclipse
The moon will end up
Okay not always but most of
Vasotec
Like a lot of variables
Yes
Right
Like that kind of time that the moon is red
Have nothing to do with it
Yeah people got to let this whole movement
I don't need anymore anymore like
Because what we're witnessing here on the show
Is just like
They're behaving like our ancestors
Do you know like way back
That's true ascribing coincidence
The Moon
I mean the moon Doug control like
Hides and stuff like that the time
Missouri
We're like that
Yeah
With my gravitation stuff like that
I think I don't know
Go.
Could be God's turn was looking for him
That's possible
This is all ascribed
Cars 2 Quinn
You can't really explain
I trying to make all of these different
Pieces of information match up with
The dumb Theory
About
String of
Which is an evolutionary Behavior
Which we've also overcome
A lot of us
Alarm
A lot a lot of people have lunch
Enough
To prove
Possible
You know we don't have to do this anymore. That the number is far lesser than we thought it was
Was
Will be back to its
My life's too short to research this I just punted on this one but this sound
Very dumb
Batumi
Just like you're talking about
What I thought was fascinating I saw this in the news the other day you can Google this
Voted 95% for Trump
Interested
So
That's pretty f***** up that's pretty f***** up
First of all
Lunar solar eclipse
Percent of the people in the path of the eclipse
Search it
Cuz I don't know what he's what is that what is that mean
Does that mean that only people who love
God who are repentant I was working at that that coffee distribution
And I remember what happened I looked up at the we all went out and looked at the eclipse
From Chicago
95% for Trump
But I mean you might be talking aggregate
But I don't even believe that
That's impossible
What polling company that
What polling company was like
Okay we've been doing this whole random sample
We've been doing this whole representative
How we considered the path of the Moon
And they did it and they're like purple
We nailed at 95%
Nail in the coffin God Believers or whatever likely
It was a dumb blog
And they had no information no more likely something like
Baton is like well that's obvious
Jim Bakker
He's got to let him say all these crazy s*** on the show recipes never going to move them
You know what
Screwing over people who can't afford to do your dump
But that's like
That's like believing that a free and fair election whines up with 97% of people voting for Putin
Like I don't understand how you can even buy that for a second
Do they only count votes
In the path of the Blood Moon
I believe it 100%
Also this wasn't the blood moon I don't think cuz the time
This one was like in
During the blood moon in 2014 and 50
Are you here before the election
That's a great question
But also
No one's doing the reverse switch is the normal pole that's also not asthma
What are the
People in the audience is going like
Well that sounds right
I promise you I'm not cherry-picking stuff to make them sound dumb
Legitimately have tried to do my best
Constructivist as like this is
The things that they're saying
Like I did cut out a bunch of times he's just a list listing off days in the Hebrew calendar cuz it's like
The Tuesday the 4th of July
Early early before like 9 a.m. on a Friday
That's also a Jewish holiday
About so
Earlier
Mark
Jared
He does not make specific predictions
I can't wait
I want to know what do you think this means it's a strange
Well I think it basically
Sodom and Gomorrah
How many righteous is needed for America
The Gentiles go by the Sun for their calendar a solar eclipse
Represents judgment coming upon
Refers to judgement coming upon Israel
First rebuttal
Israel is a nation
Solar eclipse
On Nation
On the lunar eclipses
Israel
Cool
That you're making this up Mark
Partial eclipse
Everybody else
I know that means if we repent a little
It's like a mood ring
Depending on how eclipse the Moon is he's like oh you guys are brown or partial eclipse
Call your mom
Full moon music drunk guy that a good month so drunk you start apologizing
Messenger
So
This is baffling to me
5 time for a few questions
It is
I'm not even address that I reject your privacy alright
Bravo
Isn't it 2017 when this is
Is going on
Can't you just think
For one second like
Oh the Moon is probably not God mood ring they need to sell book
I know I'm not talking about doing there
And both of them know that this is
Complete Bowl
Jim Bakker
Probably
But he would be stupid enough to believe it he just doesn't believe anything that anybody tells him anymore because he knows how full of s*** he
I've gotten away with this for so long
Aldi's
Are you almost done
The people in the in the crowd
None of them
Not one of them just like they don't ever just show one person going like
Dumb
Some people are just here for the ride
You know I don't know
That does sound entertain
We should take
S*** ton of mushrooms
And go watch one of these shows
Today will be amazing I wouldn't survive
Absolutely wouldn't survive
Great radio disaster
Why would you throw some
I'll probably get with him about how he's lying about what
It was me
You don't even know what
I'll show you a blood moon
That's that's
Where that was going to end you could have stopped it before
Lakers
Explain
Started
Of 1914
And there was a total solar eclipse over
Eastern Europe
And the Ottoman Empire
And what happened
It even went over Nineveh
Wow it even went over Nineveh so I left the Nineveh in there because he talks about Nineveh a lot
Specifically
Exactly what Alex
When the election
What's happening
He says that Trump is a
Like Nineveh
He has given that he is like
He's woke save us necessarily
But he's given us a reprieve from destruction
And always says
Like Nineveh
ESO
I don't think that that
Specific is enough for me to argue like
Hey they're getting this from the same place
Weirdo Christian metaphor to me
Jonah in the whale coming out good stuff
Because they agree to go along with stairs
Right
So now the other problem there is that he saying that there was a big
Eclipse
It happened right before World War I
Cliff
14 happened on August
21st
1914 mobilizing against Austria
Tails
Country declared war on Serbia
Sure Luxembourg on August 2nd
Declared war on France on August 3rd
Declared war on Germany in August
4th April
Not matter at all and not match up with you clips of August
It's because we had our clips
And they were like dude
Not a good time and a half years wait
This is your part of the blood
Saying it's some sort of whatever it already broken out
Didn't mean anything it's an arbitrary
It started in July when you build a road
Cuz you're going to be doing construction ubuildit a ways away from there
Sometimes you also build it
Fart
Road work is done
That way people always on their toes
You got to wait
Until after War has already started I'm listening
Can you speak in order to
Better oats
This and that analogy
At least 25 more times
Because I am still mad at
I have stupid
Cirrhosis
That I mean that's a problem
You know just the idea of it like
Already broken out
You're using this to bolster your your s***
For whatever the dump.
Bigger pitching about
Something that didn't
Prior
I don't understand all this stuff I really
Cheerleader
Yeah I know I'm furious right now
I don't get why now
Get we deserve something different than 40 days to repent
Then be referencing like a like a
Situation like the 40 days and 40 nights is that what he's referencing I mean to flood does come up
But now I don't even by their own rules
God would do that
That is a part of it
The rainbow is the Covenant
What does a dumb idea I let my I let myself play myself there a little bit I got a little out of control
Faded
Sorry Bros bros
And I got letter to Paul the Apostle
Dude
I was my bad my bad
Yeah
What you telling is essentially just the Hebrew calendar
That is not a rare thing is it
What does it have like
Does it have a good reference
Okay that sounds good
Find anywhere but
Jim
Implies
We're going to
Have your calendar this week have it right now
For this coming year
Because
I learn more from the Blackhawk the Jewish calendar
What's the
The biblical calendar
Prison I learned so much
You have put one out like I found in prison or not very many around
And you just feel with
Back in the back of the
Counter there's
This
Major information about these holidays and holy days
Can find Hubert am when you're not in the joint
I don't get the I know that
Jim likes to say that like the time that he was
Imprisoned
The Weave that in
Whenever you talk about learning
When I was in prison
The s*** out of there
But like
I don't know much
But I do know that generally speaking I don't think he will come out of prison are like
You know that's crazy
And let me tell you why
Because
After I believe it was box they had an embedded journalist
Inside of a d America
The only thing you said
Lotto
Nazis love Jewish calendar
It was really weird
Lotus ship
Why is it why is it
When I was in prison I learned so much
Why is it more of a red flag for everybody
Do after you get out of prison
Because
The Christian ethos is about
All of the Smiths so much in there they like
Yeah I was a monster I was a bad guy on murdered people
Pull that one off
Cuz you was already a Christian preacher
But you can
Pretend that the lesson
You should have learned in prison where learn
My love
Composition
Do that because
Because the Christian
And it's very much
It's so built in
Brilliant
And it's one of the reasons
Christianity you are so right for Codman
It's easy to con Christian
Definitely because the stakes are so implicitly High
Just coming back
The idea of like you could die at any time or you ready
Right
So things are like
Very
F*** with people
Really easy
Lick that like with f****** blood moon
Absolutely a weird talk of solar eclipses
The blood moon
Then that
Anyting
Natural in the world that we lack
Explanation for
Did you end that comment about
Eclipses with an ellipsis
No
Fassbender's
Natural phenomenon
Natural phenomena
You're not going to talk about light okay about
Watchguard telling you about the white house because it
A few days ago there was a
A rainbow double rainbow over the White House
A rainbow speaks of God's covenant
And over the White House
I think God is telling America he's in Covenant with us
Wow
I think God is telling he's a cop.
Is everywhere is every regular how many rainbows happen
There's a double
Double rainbow
ThunderCats
Houston viral video
Hate this place
You know what
Esmad
As I have right now you know why
The intersection of rage and joy for you is really thin like there is a combination of
Alex is except you're actually mad at there's an anchor but it's not as anime
Fun
Manuel Smiler
Alright you may have
You have far better than most of the therapist I've ever been to a story
Is it
I am furious at this
Because it is
Storm how
Way less coherent than all the other b*******
I believe Mark Richards is inconsistent bulshit story more than I will by somebody being like
The clipse
Furious is this
It's just a
F****** it's a potion works
If you were another place it would work differently you are here so it works.
Dad
I can't respond to this
I can't respond to this because of quotes that will come later that'll make this worse
Look
This guy's got a good hot dog
Everything
Successful
Yeah man I think you selling
10000 books
I mean is that
If that's your entire economy
He's making more money than us
For sure
Self-publish
Only sell 10,000
Jim Bakker
You consider how much you probably paying
Below market value
Probably $4 a book whatever he's paying you around makes a little more off it
Accept no more books
Which was a smart move on his
Double rainbow
Well
The double rainbow is a sign of God's covenant
Are we talkin about more rainbows album
I wish I was
God wants to be with our White House and we should be praying for our White House
Instead of cursing it
America is cursing
They're cursing each other
They're crushing our president
You know what I want
When I was in the courthouse
They were sentencing me
To spend the rest of my life
In prison
Another one
But over that Courthouse
What's a rainbow
Kahoot
All the time that judge was sentencing me
Read about it
Doing the research for my butt
I was wrong
Nn
Announcer person they made fun of me they mock me
And so when I saw that
That rainbow
Here's what they did they win
You don't like them not doing very good
It's a weird is outer space and something weird you know what I'm saying
Market
Tentative
Also never throw his
No tired I don't know no idea
I don't understand why I'm surprising response
Yeah
What is it
You're just too dumb to live
If you're buying
Okay
It's not
You believe it then you are you
You would go off of broken bridge
You have no sense
Look like
Pictures of this is Mark level of like
This is this is people who think that
Carnival games
What are you doing
Oh no
Hello you're on the air
Hello
Dollar Tree
The real damage Jordan
Oh my God
And the dogs are excited now
Catherine
I'm doing well how are
Are you guys doing
Overjoyed and completely
Underwhelmed
I can't leave
The Reel Theater
You guys.
Crazy
What is snow
Deprogramming happening don't worry
What's going on
But
I'm in Round Rock which is just
Like north of Austin
And so
Actually I'm going to have to cut you off there were only taking calls
From Chico California
Mine actually
Lived in Round Rock for Wildwood
Cover bands are
But I'm not in like a cover band
Play what does it cover
I don't I think there was a lot of
Jackson covers I don't know I
They weren't like I was thinking of a tribute band
Anything they can play
This was like a like a wedding reception
Cover band
Contact was like limited to him inviting you to shows where you
Nowhere near
Okay
I am a musician
I would love if you guys have any segments
Things like that I could
Record like a little thing for you to send in case you ever wanted to use it like
We've never
Considered having segments on account of our Levi nonce
Rambling
Do you have the out-of-context drop
Deal as you got.
Is any any sort of
Voicemail of the weaker I don't know
You're better at doing our show
Alex
Artlist
Okay I'm good at something for you so my best friend
Not only looks like Lauren Southern butt
Eerily like Lauren Southern
And we were trying to figure out a good way to like take advantage of that
Wanted to
A fake Lauren Southern on the show
Pikachu
Here is my here's my pitch for this and you can take the
Single white
Female Lawrence other
Like just
Friends
Then kill her and take your place and we'll all be
Avril Lavigne
See there we go the way have gone back
Check through those albums
There is a there's a mark
Different types of birthmarks
Has long been that guy Jody
You know I love Avril Lavigne
Let's
InTouch
Email
Facebook
Send a message
Talked on Facebook
It's nice to speak
Let's Dance
YouTube
Some sort of musical
Yeah that be great
Musical sting
If you guys ever need hosting and you guys
What do a show and then Asteria Avenue
House with cool Renee Stanley as a big front room I also have really good
Audio equipment
Lots of stuff is open for you guys
I know this was Chipmunks
By the time machine man like I didn't know you guys existed
She's offering
I wish they would have known about you guys
2 months ago
For you
God dammit
And I am
I'm not ashamed
But yeah so that's an option are and then I also have some ideas for March break
Okay I'll let you guys work order
Waitress drinking tonight
Okay well it imbibe
What you need to
To talk through
The latest
Televangelist
We're taking a break from Alex for this episode
Voicemail like oh that's funny I guess
Alright
Realize it would do that
Call and try and leave a message
It's kind of a crapshoot
I have no idea have we lost their minds
Why would anybody
It's very foreign to our conception
Thank you so much for the call
Back on track
Back to blood moon
We have Mark
Have a bombshell
He's going to drop on
Jim Bakker gear
The clip gym
Is it a little bit
I didn't hold on you want to hear this
Are you ready
What's crazy
This is insanity almost it's so crazy
But this is calendar stuff
This is what he's trying to teach us
Calendar stopped
This is a bombshell listen
If we're talking about calendars
I don't know if you've ever had a word-of-the-day cow
An advent calendar
Calendar
I have no idea what I'd Garfield strips
This is
Ganttic bombshell
Jim
Thanks proves
Very specific complaint with what they're talking about
It was always held on the second Tuesday of September
That's why it was canceled
This is all accurate
This is all true
I didn't know that coincidence
Because
It was supposed to September 21st
Since 2001
This is never happened
This year September
Is Rosh Hashanah
The big one
In 2015
Partners For Peace
Guess what it is this year
Peace and safety
Wow
That
What the bombshell
What is everybody doing
Why do people
Then explain to me why people gas
There's a scripture that says the people will call for peace and safety
Suddenly there'll be destruction
It's
Burst out of I can't remember what book in the Bible
They're kind of lying
For the UN International Day of Peace
Quote together
Disrespect
Free for all
Which is a far cry from
Which words from the actual theme that apply to a scripture that they
Because it ends with
I meant Destruction come suddenly
No it's not it's exactly like
You divide that says peace
Safety
Get rid of the rest and then you have
What about that you could just say then that the thing is
Together for dignity
You could say that
Probably not I do that God has
On this one I think this guy's
Just a lying piece of s***
Love
When people are just taking random as numbers in the
Is this a what it what is this is this letter Jim Carrey movie the number 1723
In the high holy calendar
And 4 is the same number as
And then if you have to that's exactly as many as if there were four twos
Over 84 and that's why I Mexico
It makes no sense
The opportunistic ramblings of vague
Connections between things
I withheld one piece of
Information
That
Kind of brings into Jim Bakker did 9/11
You might have
What's a timeline
Publishers
Mark's butt
And and first-come-first-serve
We sell out of books
This thing I'm
I hope
Wnd
Has a lot of books
Because
We shall out
Wnd WorldNetDaily
WorldNetDaily because
Former workplace
Jerome corsi books about how Obama birth certificate is fake
System for a lot of Alex Jones guests or WorldNetDaily
Folks like Joseph Farah
Who runs world who actually I co-wrote Mark's first book
Blood moon
From 2008
There's a real fur connect well
Do Dwell
He is
Frequently published on WorldNetDaily as well they put out a bunch of articles
Blood moon
Theory
Completely separate world
And yet more simple
What convention
Situation
Ex-con
Print contacts
Did the queen know that Alec
Rodger Stone Mountain 2013
Right so we know that
You know the Kerry Cassidy
You've met a bunch of
These people that she talks to
Convention
They make their connect
They're so obviously yes a lot of these people
Similar circles
It's
They don't like the cause
Play
Yeah that's
Images
I want I want to know that might be Jim Bakker
Probably fuked Kelly Jones
Okay
Whatever
I'll buy it
For a dollar
From what
Jim Bakker
I bet
You think so
He learned a lot in prison
Carries himself
I feel like
He is
Daughtering
No Iraq
You don't like I know that that seems weird
Put on
But I watched enough of his show and the way he's
Mumbling
Through words
I just
Who's the guy
Knows how to turn it on
But I don't think
I don't think this is a guy who that's why we got drugged and
Kids are adults
Whatever
Propagandas for his buddy
You get
A lot of food
A bunch of unsold books hanging out in Lori's house
So this next clip I think is one of the most ironic things I've ever heard
Is this is
Is weird
False prophets in the world
Call Mike
To hear that
Clear that at the end
It looks like you're having a lot of
This is a lot of money
This is a lot of manipulative
God
God dammit that's the equivalent of like people in the Infowars world
Accusing other people
Earlier
About this
Just like
Branding
Eclipses as
Meaning some
Which is weird because
Using like the eclipse
Is being like
Going to start
Right
But his big
Foundational thesis
Is just about the
Blood moon
It's fall on Jewish holiday
I'm so
He gets into this
Next clip mark.
And it makes me
Even more
He was like he's really.
A lot
There's a possibility
Eclipses
Which is how long the Earth
According to his calendar
Amazon
Eclipse that goes over a nation
What what
Why is this position supposed to carry weight I don't get it
Even undercut his own argument by saying that
If it doesn't occur
Then it's fine because it is a feast
God is creating a piece.
So why would it matter if it occurred on a
Determined
Disagree
Does Great Clips has happened it's not God
The calendar that you
Conveniently
Every voice
To which I would respond what a way what are the other ones I've got doing the exact same thing a bunch of times but
Stop
Giving his opinions about reality tea
Maybe you're something like that words like
Meaningful conversation it's just God trying to vent some s***
When is Cliff's goes over like the Arctic Circle or whatever
That just
Fleurette on the mind
It's mind-boggling
Blood
Play plasma
Anthem
They put on the great name for a
Blood Moon Blood Moon
Mark my other complaints
Change the name to platinum
Please just whatever and you can't
Channel Time
You think that's
Awful
I was watching it
Hey I got to think
Bugasalt
Look at Salisbury
Yeah but at the same time
Who are these people
Right I think they're actor
The people who were guests
At least they're Faking It
In order for sensational
Like there aren't enough people that they
This very specific problem like I want you to do a lie detector test to prove that you're not sucking my cousin
You know or whatever did not you're not going to be able to make that show once a month
With
Adorable sampling of people
Hamming it up and stuff like that
At the same time
Some of them are
Amazing actors
You know
Command
Eat cuz I don't believe it's real
And that means that these people are
Incredible actor
Which I think should be a pool
Fur like casting movies
I disagree
The camera follows them
And I think maybe they could
Play the flip side isn't
Beaker dystopia
Except
I think we have to accept that their problems are possibly real
And then worse
The audience is treating them that way
The audience
Yelling at them and be like Boo
Stuff like that
If they're not all
Everyone needs therapy
And therefore I believe it's
And lost
This has been my
We're going to take my music
I will I will take the recording to the board and we will decide whether or not you
Sienna why everybody who watches
This is what happens I'm an advocate
What are we even talking
This is insane
Eclipse
A lot
And they don't always mean something something
And you should be aware when they mean
And by virtue of them sometimes meaning something
You can obviously discount the fact that they happen all the time because of course they don't always mean something sometimes
That makes sense
Yeah that's a perfectly logical statement that a lot of people only believe
I would say that's an unfair thing for something for someone
Just because
Before we started the clip that makes it more
Utterly baffled especially when he's
Already on the show talking about various eclipses that have happened over the time
The feast days
About
You know what this might as well be saying
Legitimately might as well be him being like
Well everytime I burp
Yeah
Not every time a bird poops on you good luck
But sometimes good luck
Which means that
Virtbiz lucky
Sometimes
Even more like slightly nefarious
Because it also relies on a schedule
That is very specific
Weekly lunar base
Pacific schedule.msu side if they poop on you on these days
It's even more
Failing to
Explain to people how lunar calendars work
They did
Did you know that I did know that
Cyndi Lauper
Cyndi Lauper never had a chance
I thought she was murdered
River couple more Clips year left
To go through I don't think we found any
Questions other than there than just
I-88
What is out of hand it's so stupid what do you what do you even respond to this with other than just like
Responded what I said
The first 20 minutes
Episode
Hebrew calendar is based on the lunar calendar exhaust there already
Phenomenon
High holy days
What a shock
SpongeBob dates here
For a bit
You saying it really is
Meaningless as you just give a long list of
August 4th
Let's go
How about
May
How do you feel about that
Good day good day
Good day as well be doing that
To serve
Prelude to what comes after
That was on the calendar
That's the 17th
100 years
Anniversary
You got the 50th anniversary of the unification of Jerusalem
This year
Wow
Everybody I want to see this
The phone gets so busy at the end of the show
If you want
I want everybody to order a calendar
See
Softest add pivots number
Yeah and that's why I think
Yeah
Mumbly add laptop
Look phone
Get real busy at the end of the show
Departed book
From the sky
The things or take a book plus a food bucket
He's gotta move those books is that he had allowed
What is it with
Loving
Round
Except
The same time
Random event
That occurs sometimes
Are also
Bailiwick
And then
Also but like
On anniversary
Play I got a big 10 system
Hey there is it just God does not have like a
Like like this user numerology kind of system as well like
He's like okay first off
Blood moon happens over 2000 years
No big deal
Right
Yeah yeah
Cuz he doesn't
Like been caught into this b*******
It doesn't happen like every 60
Years it's not like a round number
Right now but it is important
Hundreds of years go by sometimes where there are
Like
Here we have two that are 15 years apart
So so like we got that
Anniversary
This is like 50 years since mind 70 years since Israel became a state in all of this stuff
Does
Figure his s*** out for a little bit that's all
And their belief in a god that is
Bring the 50 and 70 year anniversary isn't that smart
Defender
If you are going off of the Jewish calendar
Then it's not exactly 50 years
It's not the
You're using
Bye-bye couch at least
Different calendars
Well the same time asserting that certain anniversaries on one calendar make sense
Well the same time in other calendar as
This doesn't make a goddamn benefit but if you buy a calendar will
The combines all of them into one
Dammit
So this next up I think is probably the most
Troubling
Peace
No there's a lot of people talking about
There's so many trumps in the Bible
They thought maybe President Trump might be one of them the last one
I don't know
Feel like the audience
Applauding the idea that Trump is the last trumpet
And then revelation
Really
Because it implies a real self-destructiveness on the part of Their audience
Fill the message
To be sent is
Let's get toward this
Like it's not good
For someone
Whose entire business model is about selling you things
To prepare for the end times
To really want them to
Succumb
Cuz you got it from both
You know like you got to assume.
Manipulating you with his rhetoric
In order to get
To buy the thing
It would be like people who sold
Security systems
Arash rahbar
It's the same sort of like thick
I get
You should not say those things
You know like if you are in that business maybe you are pulling for robberies to happen
Publicly
He was a business person
You are shady as hell I'm not going to do business with you
Boss comes to mind
Whatever
Torture killer killer killer
The guy who
Works for a security company
Enzo's new how to break it
People who
God everybody stupid
I only keep this in because Mark ends up
Prediction
Peace and safety
Destruction
The end of the September
We don't know
It's a sign
We ought to read it
What is it say
It says
Who invented
Who is this
They are saying peace and safety
My God
This makes me still can get about her
Destructions coming
So that's the scripture
You can get excited about that
Because you knows
It's not that's not
Indicative of Bonner that's indicative of like
This is how we're going to move the books
He's old
Just Dance
I can get more food
What age
What a bowl-shaped cop-out to
Anytime somebody says peace and safety
Distraction is
That is such a
The un's
Be the UN
The Bible
I was predicting
The actual
You're so sweet
Stupid
Even if they said
Right they did they did
I took that mean that used a lot more ultimately what they say
Destruction
Is Eminem
And Market in here saying
You know that mean probably by the end of
September
This could all go down
No one
Has ever said
Timer
Up until this point
This was preordained by God
In the intervening time. Of when when was what
What book was the
Okay so let's say
At the label
At the latest date was like Revelation error select call it like 400
Something like this
Sobor
1600 years
Nope
Do you wind it okay will do
Destruction is imminent
And you know what that
Guess what
Totally cool
Here's why
Why am I prepared
If you came to my house
Wrightwood United you down to my baby
You would see enough food for
13 years 14 years Broadway I don't know
And why would I
You're crazy
I went to prison
I wish you would have stopped there I wish you could stop
I wish I could give you the food in prison
Also
Go to like a white-collar prison prison was an infinitely better than its 13 years old
Again it Bears mentioning with
Lyndon larouche in prison
So much time
In this book called the whole
Then I became a fanatic
I believe it
I believe the date of Believe the time to bring the hour
Do you believe in life after love read it all is going to start harmonizing
I found the answer
In the Bible
To the revelation
Do with four people
In the last days
And here
The United Nations
This year
Announce the date
September 21st
Is the day
A piece
And safety
To the world
Mute
He was wanting
He was wanting that to get to like a
Selling books
Instead it died like a
Soft fart and then he immediately gets interrupted by one of his other co-host I've no idea who he is
What do we do
Which actually is probably another attempt
Cracker Barrel
The guy is just like
Mark Rambo the whole bunch
About Tavares
Stupid crazy stupid so I mean at the end of this
I feel like there might
Still be a little bit of
Fusion
I'm looking at this and I'm like I know exactly there might be a little bit of confusion I don't know what
Anyone here has said or is trying to say I want to try in at least
At the end of the
Answer any questions
You as the audience surrogate
Confused I can sit here as the person who did all the research
Well this is a game we've never played
Final question
Anything you need to clear it up
Okay well
None of us need to ask the question why
Cuz we all know why
Why is seltzer
Keep Trump
President or whatever it is right
They think they're going to get a theocracy out of it
Tongues are like
Going to work much better
My question
First off
Material
What is there evidence of
So
Thursday's Moon
Right there's the lunar tetrads
Two years prior
Episode
Okay
You know what
You've actually
You asked the most basic question into one I can
Because I
I looked like two and a half hours
And I don't understand why
He's applying these predictions
The 2017
When all these Blood Moons happened to 2014 2015
The fact that the UN named their day of peace
More mileage out of that than you need
2 stars or anything like that right
In the middle
I don't
Yeah I mean
Brewster's just
The random occurrences of
Does eclipses
Yeah
And I'm trying to cheat and make them fit your
Pattern
Right
So there's that
Okay how about
But just go with if we're going to go with God is super into
Astronomy
Actually that's my next question. I think you might be doing the wrong kind of question
Questions that are like
I realize exactly what I was doing immediately after apologizing
Is
So ostensibly this guy
Discovered blood
Snow
He named them blood
Already existed in the astrology of course.
This guy
Who
Has to have at least some level
Astronomy
Knowledge
Right
Just as far as a basic like I'm not whether or not
Put it out right 2008
Could this one is first book came out
So this is all post
Yeah I thought this guy come in like the 70s or something
This started as best I can tell probably 2007
The book that would be released in 2018
When he predicted the Jesus Christ
To come back in 20
This dude
Starts researching
Why did he's why does he start
I mean
Alright
Nobody
My question
Rhetorically is appropriate
You have a very clear reason
It was all so Random
Like I wasn't typing kind of a watershed moment in history is not end of reaction to it is not
Call Nick
Look like I was doing before
Following an incident with him like sitting around
Stoned looking at pictures
That one's really red
Or whatever you know there's probably something like that we don't know about I just don't understand why
Stupid question questions stupid
Do this
Fully accept that and I you are correct except
Criticism of that question and I believe it is also correct I think enough people go about their lives
To like learn about weird stuff
Let's Wikipedia.
YouTube videos something like that and then you find some like
Weird thing then you get deeper
That whole you start to find coincidences that you decide to ascribe meaning
And then it blossoms into a book
You're right with the founder of my world
God dammit
Stupid
Yeah it's it's probably more I mean like I think
Well I can't answer that question
Definitive way I can answer it
He probably just stumbled onto something.
Then it seems to have clearly
Spiraled into something
Because he has all of these bulshit day it works really well he has all of these
Bulshit dates where he's like
Oh well I have this Blood Moon
Siri
Now I'm just going to learn about
Klipsch is too because World War
What is this
He is f******
Banking
On Surviving
Until 2032 when the next tetrad comes around
I will put them in 50 that's it'll be around
2030 talking about
It's all good
Let's circumstances California is on fire
Right now
It's not bad
La Tanya's lamp.
I get all that
Let's stipulate to climate change isn't going to kill us all
Cuz he probably believes
The hoax
So in his mind
Praying that he makes
Because then
You get to do this
Game all over again
Wright's retirement money
He gets to retire on that 2032 blood moon
Also said like you should be able to
650i nobody
Oh no
Whatever
He's not doing a good job shift work
He's not working
World
Floating b******* theories
Are you want to retire before 70 you that's all
This is a weird demarcation of organized labor that I don't understand
I don't think there's a union for liars
No look there's there's spiders
Skyrim
Stop talking about it when I was great
You got to get in a great storyline
Gil was a great story
What ambassador
Okay
I love Skyrim
I thought it was amazing
The world is very open
Questions about
I loved it
It's not my kind of game you mad at me whenever you did find out
The hell out of it
I like
Exploring around
Yeah but it is certain
Point
Vulcanus of the largest
Love the game
Nostalgic kind of
Clear to me
I can I can never Play It Again
I can't go back to
Enjoy it
Cuz I know that like
Aldi's
Essentially
Nothing
You know like the Thieves Guild
Dickhole
Non-playable characters hanging out
I love chat
Bulshit
I want the game to the internet
I was hoping you would realize that you're crazy
That was the expectation
But I think the game built
The experience
Who's playing
Apple Maps
Like
It implies that
Vicious
Keep going
You know what's
You know it's crazy but there are a lot of people
Who felt that way about Skyrim
Rational
Do you know what they did
What's that they made more of it
Weather like
Made like a
They mate
Where is Starbucks
Now I will tell you this right now
Your dream of an infinite Skyrim
It's real
Because so many people felt the way you did they felt that promise of an infinite World where they can just
Exist and they can live forever and not ever
There is an infinite number of Mazda you can add to Skyrim
People are
Still making Skyrim
Putting f****** I can't remember the name of that
Oblivion
Enter the Skyrim growing more and more content in Skyrim
All the time
There's a rich community
I can't cuz I have it on the switch I've no idea how to plug in
This brings us to the end of our Jim Bakker
Exploration
Anna Skyrim
Until our next step
Figure out how to mod
What what would you like to still mate
You've learned I know that I've already asked
Dude ask question
What I've learned
No
What is wildly unsatisfied with this episode
Episode
Like I did not leave
Things out
Lineup
It makes it makes it like I didn't know I'd be like
In some clip from his episode that I didn't play or anything like that
Jesus
Maybe this is just all crazy
It's not like there is
There is no way
Explanation
Myself into the mind of The Listener who probably is like
Mcwethys like Wyatt
What were the
These people talking about that they're covering
And it makes me feel like we
I don't know what makes me feel like
Don't let me let me let me get
Even further to the heart of the question
I don't know
How there could be
That you left
Is incoherent nonsense
This happens if this happens literally every time we play Jim Bakker episode where I'm like
I don't believe in God
I don't believe in any of this
I think it's
My childhood self
Is offended on behalf of the Bible
I hope God exists to punish this
This is why the rules set down by the
Incoherent nonsense
At the church
And and
Double down on that
Whether you listen to the entire Jim Bakker episode
But we cover
There's no we making updates and then ascribing eclipse
What are you talkin about
Just my own it's
There's no way there's no way to make this make sense
Unless
Literally everything
Any scientist
Has ever learned
Is
But this this to me seems like science in the
Well that's like what I was saying is like what they're doing is our ancestors
Yeah they're being like
This is Elder stuff
Yeah
It's not
It's good
It's just random ass like oh and by the way also because women there's
Recycles are based around the Moon in
Women can't be allowed to have off
Like whatever bulshit that this is
Old Testament rules about having her.
Yeah but
I didn't I don't
I don't think he was saying that it
But he was saying that like the amount of days match up with some sort of
It was nonsense but it was again about like weird man
It wasn't about
Put the woman in the sweatshirt
Alright
Whatever
Exactly
No no
No
Here's my summation of this up
So whatever Jim Bakker is
App
Congratulation
Tumi
Because
Thai chili plant
Justice
I got one for you out there
No it's really good I'm not going to eat a pepper
No we're not going to do that I got to
Alright we might do that tomorrow
No we're not love it
God I hate you
It's like a habanero or something it's not that hot
But before that you can check out our website
Go to Facebook
Tell Dad we are at advertising we're even like Blurry
Plugs
It's talk to
Sit around and talk about opportunistic
Marketing sales people and then be like
Standard clock things at the end of a show when what have you been at the same time it's like
It does
Field
Are we are we supposed to
Supposed to
The show nowhere
Right
Do you know what here's the ears may be a better way for us
Close these episodes now especially since
Each one teach one is like
You've heard our podcast before you know where to find
And if they do great randomly listening to this episode and you made it this far
Holyshit
You're going to just Google now it's fighting you'll find all of it anyway
Look if you are a new listener
And you like to this podcast
Google I said you'll find all kinds of s*** about us
Also
Go to bed
And maybe that's
Themselves cuz that's so harsh maybe we tell him
Want to go to bed from now on
Go fuc yourself
Cheesus Christ
I remember his f****** name
Go fuc yourself
I'm not going to say
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color