Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
What up
Where was the last
Vacation
Last night took was last night
Girlfriend
It was weird
It was a vacation to luxury
Comedy on the road
The drop
Homo
Yeah I went to the weekend with the delightful nickel out there
Super fun time
Cook do you know a lot about
Starting out I'm not sure if there wasn't so great
A lot of people
I want
The few times I've ever seen
Infowars shirt in the wild
Really
I almost fell out of my
Oso
Taken aback
By this weirdo
That's true
Walmart
This person jumping off
Journal post doctor Dylan
I'm a policy wonk
What is
Multiple people with Advanced degrees
An actual doctor
Medical doctor
I Can Only Imagine
Getting the honorific title of
Policy walk
Good little something in the mail I know actually that this one is from
Episode
No it's not.
Oh no
That could be a very dangerous thing
Your friends over ridiculous
That sounds like what we would do with her without a card yet
Running
Free copy of the temperature for last night when we were drinking
Thank you so much we will run the next time wear
Doing something
Maybe after the show podcast
Getaround
Yeah and I'll have them people
Who cares
He'll just convince you that you are recording it's just really have
Like being alone
Just like
You do calling
You might end up on our voicemail
Here we go but we got segments B up top
Excited
Hello Dan and Jordan This is Andrew from Redding California
You may not know
The 530 represents many cities in reading and stuff
Mexico
So
All the way to Chico
Still alive show
I expect to see on reading
And also I just wanted to say
I love you
Indian canvas
Who sings Small Town California
Chico has like a
Population
Reading has
I made that up and I like the idea
To become
Sort of
Equinox
And we appreciate your
Logistics
Exactly
0 Neon
Yes indeed
From the 530 zip code you're the only ones whose
Voicemails are going to get played on the show
For now, cuz that b strong
He's got in front of us is
Current episode
Alright
No he's still left to his own devices
Haha so where I want you
2009 episode but something perfectly honest I can progress through those episode
To them
So if I were to come with
With the information that I have from the next
Few days
In 2009 we have kind of a drive
Episode
And on top of that I think that right now we're in a situation where I think everybody wants to know what the f*** is going on with him
I'll tell you what's going on with it
Not a whole lot
Who has been kicked off everything
Yeah now is just spinning wheels
Is weird
Found himself
Pizza
Over and over again
It's really
It's probably boring
Is it blaming China
Which was already doing that before
4 years
So I listened to his phone
More less waiting for
Pretend it's a noble death
Deep deep
Trouble
Event people brought
Is he
If he doesn't
Say on Twitter
10 periscope
Internet
Like there are other options
All those other
Right wing
Door even just lesser things
Dailymotion
Or something like that but there are those secondary video streaming
Is Herobrine kicked off Google Play
No one knows what's going on in Google Plus
He could stream on LinkedIn I don't know
I never been on a
Me neither
You should be a little bit more like
Fired up
He's not
I listen to the August 9th episode
And it was
Incredibly
Like this
Where are the feminists
Arresting him
Find the article
It's an article about how they aren't going to arrest Boris Johnson
Anti-muslim,
How to get a cheesecake
She's a slave under Sharia
So now we can pull that weight
What did
What he was talking about earlier controversy I didn't know that
Tractor Supply
Muslim women
That's pathetic
That's
You dude
In his defense I do think a lot of people view the Cheesecake Factory as the last great white bass
I don't disagree
I will say that I live in a neighborhood in Chicago that has a diverse population that there are a lot of
Walk-around
Thought about it
I walked by
Give the head nods that I give to everybody
Hi in my social life I can't imagine
What
Imagine irrational
Reason to be like
I'm scared
In public
Fabric
Because they
Using more fabric
The Middle East I got the textile market corner for
I think started they were just like we expect so much fabric
Excessive amounts of
Fabric
The issue that it comes down to it actually I saw this awesome article
Unlock
A little bit of
WhatsApp
There's a great response
Boris Johnson
Bruce talking about
Wearing
Covering refuse to take them back
Something to ban burqa
What have you
Who comic books
I totally agree
I would go further and say that it's absolutely ridiculous
The people should choose to go around looking like letterboxd
He also said that if a female student turned up at school or at a university lecturer looking like a bank robber
He would ask her to remove her face
Covering in order to speak to him
He added that humans must be able to see each other's faces
So
Some white people on his side
This one guy and Mark
Commented
Vet tech
Just like the Burke up but this
Just like the Burke up at disrespect
Death
Emerson
Whoa
Some good responses to the people just
Clowning on him after that on Twitter
There's one person wrote as a deaf person I kindly asked you not to
To wear whatever they want
It's their face and their right to cover it
It's weird how she ended that way but also I don't
Would you like a weight
I like where your I don't know which team
Josh underscore Salisbury you know who else
Literally
I welcome you all to go clean shaven
Respect for the deaf and hard-of-hearing people
Michael unique question about the
The response was we will find a way to help you communicate
So
Yeah that's pretty much to believe the general feel of it
So this is what Boris Johnson isn't getting in trouble for
I don't want to see any
Cool
You know
The thing about
Is that even if you let go of the bigotry
The ideas
I think it's ridiculous that people should choose to wear them
Is just a farcical thing to say because
Look at you you're ridiculous
The haircut choice
You choose to continue having that you can get
Close
Terrible
Unflattering
From a zipline
What do they mention that picture of him hanging from a zip line look like
Helmet on
I was hoping they would know,
You guys make your own decisions about who looks ridiculous
Yeah yeah
Straight up
That's just straight-up bigotry that's all that is
Where is that
That that's not fair
That's stupid
You're using them as a as a
But on the 9th
That actually is like
Infowars
Android
Nope what is their response now in the world
Screenshot of of trending
Go to the app on Apple
You can't use new one because there aren't new one
Extreme at you are number one on trending because of the massive growth that you have
Number three or number five on the other chart
And that's still good but if you going
You go and look at them now zip drops considerably because of those algorithms
I know this from
Talking to tons of people who do
If you see a massive spike in growth
You get bumped up the charts
It must be something that the Gathering
He's at the exact right time
To save this sort of
Even right now recording
That's exactly what any of people
Who were already onboard going to it
And then you're going to be too menacing returns
The plateau of
Actual people
So they were all people who are like
They were all people who for
Years were like
How do I get apps on my rotary phone
We can all
Radio voice
Let's stick together
You know what
Weather
Me
Old man
House phone
Three of us get together replace
It's a great time
Me and my radio volleyball God
I would listen to that for
She's trying to get the you know he's still aware that people can listen to the podcast
Even if they're not listed on
ITunes
Migrate people towards
Pocket posted this in our group go home and tell your mother
Facebook
I was trying to find his
Podcast
Because I was trying to find episode
And if you
You go to
Paige infowars.com
There are five episodes listed
All of them are January 1st 1970
Possibly being episode cuz he wasn't born
You know
With the amount of time travel we've talked about on
Do not rule out
Going back in time
Material landscape
Wildwood unfortunately did not realize it
That
The technology necessary to listen
Listen to them
Would not exist until much later on
Yeah
Brillia
People of people talk a lot about Marc Maron
Pioneering tiger
Because if you just Google Alex Jones
Specific date looking the video
Can you find an unmarked video of the
People just going to keep doing that but the real fun
Is that so
Get the sensitive like
Who is really sore
Check this out in various places
Re-life
There's no way I'm going to
Subscribe
Owen Shroyer episode
War Room David Knight no thanks
There's one thing
About the park
What's that
Infowars.com shogo subscribe directly the podcast gets free
Am I free
It's free
Hear what you're not supposed to hear
Show program
Rodger Stone indicted on troyer's for room my broadcast
It's all there and then finally
Supportive Spanish
Infowars.com
Please find us and listen to us
I am not going to put out a great product for you to listen to
Until you all find
More or less
It's a lot of a lot of blame the Chinese
Right
The B12 is or whatever
Commercial only for what he says
For the end of the commercial
Minutes
I'm talking about a product
Dollars right now it is $70 and 44.com Infowars life.com
Call 888-253-3139
We'll Never Back Down
I was here.
The part of the Du Hast
Flocking artificial exciting
You can't
I like wrap yourself up that quickly from
$70 but it's really good
It's so fake
Performative
We have discussed
We have victory in our blood
Weird
Silver in their shirt
Price of 50% off
All mattress stores we're going to be in business forever I don't know if I have the clip in 10
Eclipse
Feel like
Most of the stores free shipping
But the other thing
Is even in his diminished
And help naked that is all
What is manifesting
Stuff like
We're ramping up to the final Collision
If you're on board with him that's the sort of thing that's really going to stick in your craw
If that's the sort of thing that's going to be like
I better get my guns ready
I better be ready whenever
Good people
Violence or whatever
They're expecting him to eventually comes
Pencil
He says we're ramping up for the final Collision
It's almost impossible not to think that means
We got to take back the Republic
Like we've been trying to
Make s'mores no good cuz all these Chinese people
That's what happen
It's dangerous
Even with
Much less
Penetration
To the market and stuff like that
That's what rhetoric
All I can say
Music
There's like my Boost
He hates Because by the band
Europe
National sovereignty
I don't think he's wrong
They have been going after yes 4:30
Coronavirus actual
Air France V Orchestra Baobab
America America Europe
Animes of the Human League
That's Chicago
Chicago classically globalist band
Do non Global is bad to have that Americano band
Feisty horn work
25 or 6
I heard
I like that
Feisty
Looking for a face more like
The wild
It's just looking for a fight
Different
It's a broader
Definition
I see the horn work
Wrestler
Okay anyway
Look it up
Pull up
Sure
Let's get this settled once
These are the only things that I really thought were
Tristan guy listen to on the 9th
Cover over and over again
I'm talking about the
The point as much as I could
I'll say that the episode because I was like
You know if
This is gross or whatever more just like
I don't have the
I just listened to H & H
Of other s***
I don't have the time
With this Alex
And it was just so boring
Couple things that are worth
Mentioning a couple
Fitness
The. Did I listen
It just worries me
In much the same way as that final Collision outro from this episode
I think there's stuff to be worried about
Exploration of August 10th
With talking a little bit about David Hogg
What's the weather's more disinfo out there for them
I noticed that
Delete that stuff
Super high road delete
The Super Highway
Literal
Salute
It sure looks like that but it doesn't matter
Literally when they hang out with nausea
Comes out with this article about all the times
Breach Outfitters policy
You're all the times he broke his response
Dealing with that
What do you guys like
I want stand all this David Hogg stuff I was like
Yeah but they're going to miss
Interpret
Take it.
Super high road about
Like no you're not you're scared
Your f******
So scared
They're going to get rid of your Twitter
He's been
Effectively
Spanish
If what you say
Is doing is good
Facebook and Twitter
You really don't
Because if you have an audience of
What he pretends is
No no you have millions
Equality
People will respond to it
Then you don't
Other than the platform which you're putting it out
Word of mouth will naturally spread it
If you will be like oh my God this is really awesome and they'll tell their friends about
Through the natural growth to things that are decent
You don't necessarily need platform
What he's doing.
What he does is the journalistic equivalent of a smash-and-grab robbery
Because yeah by the time the truth is all like so disgusting
He's already come up with a
Inflammatory narrative about it
And that is
Just going to resonate with people
Listen to him
Did the comment
Common sense
Matter
He needs the immediacy of
Yeah social networks like Twitter and Facebook
In order to get people riled up with his immediate narrative
And if he doesn't do that then show like a day later and he's already
Beast oil
Yeah
Amplify
For Media Matters or
CNN or somebody to be like
FIFA generator doesn't have the reach
Because I think that a lot of those places are going to
I don't I'm not sure if they have already
Like we don't care about covering Alex anymore
That Alex is already preemptively creating a narrative about that
Houston
Can me down what they're going to do is start going after Steven Crowder
It was a guy you don't I don't know who he is but
That's the way of justifying why
No one cares to talk about him
Is the next
Hit Target
Whatever look man
Well I don't know
I lost my train of thought
Conservative blog and then get our own reaction
That's what we got to do the blaze
Glenn Beck after I pick it
Reach rapprochement
I'm sick of him not getting address
He could cry on our show in a sweater is great
That would be great
Woody wear a tie underneath
You might work
The Jordan did you know that the Nazis are not the only people
Football players commonly we're branded armband
To fill sponsorship deals
They're not allowed to alter their Jersey
Nazis
Morning
Which I think is a very easy leave
Good morning
Further there's a rich history of black armband also being used as a sign of protest
For example
On December 6th
16th May 65
15 years old Mary Beth handkerchief
18 years old
And Christopher Eckhardt
16 years old
Symbolize their opposition
The u.s. involvement in the Vietnam War
They got suspended
Tinker versus
Is Des Moines independent
Free School District
Which resulted in the Supreme Court decided
School violated
By suspending them for wearing their armbands
You could also make a really strong argument that fellow students wearing armbands
Particularly black armband
Might be harkening back to this sort of History
Student activism
Morning
All of those things
Come into
You play all together wear a black armband
Almost the perfect
Right now further expression
Call Black armbands
Which refers to abusive history that suggest
Free Multicultural Australian history had been a disgrace
Largely related to the horrible treatment of minorities
Namely the aborigine
Parallel
Sure
Did I
They didn't get suspended
The biggest issue I have is all of this
Makes perfect sense
If you just take a little bit of time to look at
Just take a little time what what is the history of a black armband
Is it always the
Waffen-ss
It's always
It's really not there's a lot of
Black armbands
And then on top of that
When the other side is calling people now
I do agree that sometimes
Little bit too
Capriciously thrown around
But
I don't remember who made this argument
Godwin
If you
Are hanging out with an ox
You're a Nazi
People in a Nazi is there and they aren't thrown out you are now in a group of Nazi
If you tolerate
What party
Totally cool
And elected one of them to the White House
If you are let's say a member of a certain political party
And you go to a rally leader of the Free World
Right
Espouses Nazi beliefs
It's entirely possible
Look around
What other every 8 people
How to make salsa
Please write
Right
Would you call them
The right could call them the right
It's hotter outside
At least they're not socialist
Amen brother
Alex
For what he's going to do in order to
To get his version of Rock
I got to love it
Because he wants something
Call
Yeah.
Yeah we're representantes is it agreed
Explain
The only thing is going to get out of his problems
Awesome s*** on
My statement calling for hearings in Congress
What's really happen
Birthright
Is that your Birthright
This is never going to happen
DirecTV for Conservative Republican
Spiders
What do we do
Cuz like their position
You like
We got it
Try and help him
What that mean
Mr. Jones
Could you give at least some differences between you and Nazi propaganda
Fearnow
Okay well there we go this hearing right everybody everybody can have different
Ever have a beard
Good point that is a good point
Necessarily
I'm not sure that I fully articulated what I mean but
To see if
Alex Jones
Crosses
That which they will do
You know like
Yeah
Republicans in Congress
Total
And they've just advocated any responsibility
Doing their job
The only reason that we need to control the houses because
The President should be the only one
People like who Alex
Idolizing
And you have people like Matt gaetz who went on Alex's show and then was like
But Alex is still alive
For him
Lakewood they go to bat
Are they
I want to know that
I do want this to
Every word we're past the Mendoza Line in terms of being a country anymore
It can only hurt him
I want him to have his Mr Smith Goes to Washington
That's what I want I want him to
Blame the entire system and say that it's entirely broken
And really just go for it
Thinking that he will never actually be kicked out
Will the rules say that I get to talk as long as I want right that's my Birthright
Today
Sovereign
They have advocated the courtroom
Yeah I bet I would bet
Anyting
That he's opening
Would be
The speech from that
Like always
Just Glory
Glory speech enough
I would love that
I know that
Is always like junk isn't more attention
He deserves much
Tannerite
Control contacts I believe this is the right
You know like they could do the research
Search required in order to
To get there like
Gotcha question
Alex work
Noemi
Wait is this
Treat me with kid gloves
I can't wait for the info
Go down
But he still hosting the domain for a while
Just has a blank page
Call Larry Nichols on it
Just recently saw Larry Nichols on another website
I think Alex
I don't know why
He's not on his show
I haven't seen him at all another show
Is he okay
No I don't mean that
But like his rhetoric is very different
I saw him on another Show when he was
Not nearly the
You clearly doing the character or act
Waze
B supplica
Supplicate
To Alex's it was interesting to see like propaganda
I only know from Alex's World in another
Nelson show
Empty holic
But you know yo
Unity animated
CNN
Broadcast
Have broadcast from the 6
Might make a diesel
Sandpoint here
Looks like him
They have to pay to be on the airport
Just really funny here Alex earlier in the show talks about how he had to pay
It's beyond the app
Alright whatever
Have your app list
Yeah so go f*** off with that logic
To be on everywhere
Hotel beautiful nice hotel
2 months ago
And there was CNN on on the big television
I just can't
Force-fed
Horseback
You know what's really fun about that there's a look in his face when he brings up the example that he has of being CNN's
It happens to be the Trump Hotel
On the Trump Hotel
You can play whatever the f*** you wants there pretty much
Powerball news
Better than Fox News
If you want some run-of-the-mill ship that's probably what you're going to choose I don't know if that's
Contract
Do better
Better that's so bad
That's shitt broadcast
Bro
Think just State the gym
Hayward
Local liquor go to a bar
Trump Hotel
I'm not going to wear your guy
He could even have his old hotel
Hundred percent Noblesville
Play theater at a Trump Tower
8 months ago
So after Trump is already saying that they're the enemy
WhatsApp
Kevin
Outrage
Okay
There's
Antifa is out there
They are definitely responsible for the most recent murder
No
At protests
The murders in the violence
Word
More from the
But not before that that one guy who just fired a shot
Into
The Ether
Stucco
Oh no he wasn't horrible
Who's only famous because he's stuck stick
Into are protesting hit people with a right that wasn't that wasn't
Ooo-ooo-ooo specifically targeted
Three white supremacist
To their own devices
Oh no they weren't now they were realized
They can make
Look like a people by covering their stuff
Better values that Ava tactics recorder
You know that's a consideration Foothill
Documents
Corralled
By Soros funding
Should the CIA staged
They just posted that insured me
Portland
San Francisco Inn in Charlottesville
Maryland the police have stood down we even have the documents in Maryland
Baltimore
Or that was made up of
Martial law for Obama 2015
Maryland
Document
You are just reporting all of this
That entire
Last-minute is all him just rambling
And expounding
Expanding
What he's trying to say based on those
Fake contract that we planned on for about half an hour nonsense idea that anyone would make a ton
Contract for that b*******
So f****** stupid and fake it's absurd
Any right-thinking person that would look
Unlike baby trying
Figure out where.
Start
Malibu is one of those plastic internet hoaxes
And Alex
For a long time
Reporting it is true
Is reporting it is real that there are
Contract
Soros connected organizations
To create martial law
It's not real
It's crazy
We've already talked
Dissected further but
It's nice it's
Nice to know this much
Is that the cops
Worth funneling the white
Two premises right that's Millie Weaver
No
That one side
Is going to murder the other side
So even then
What he's implying
Murderers
And they were being pushed typically
To commit the crime that they wanted to commit in the first place will now Alex would argue that they would not
Committed those murders
Or something like that
To the point of committing a murder
I don't know if it's still okay
Believe the same thing I do
It works for him
And I watch the videos of Millie Weaver put out and I've seen the
About wasn't there so I don't think that I have the right to make a
Definitive statement or anything like that
I know that
From everything I know about
These group
Somebody would have found the other one
You know whether it's
Finding the fascist
Feminazis or the Nazis bindings them it would have ended up happening at some point
And if they want a bra
They're going to brawl
The other side
What wants to stop people from
What is the murders
But this is where it gets all twisted
Alex
The label themselves as
Their fashion
And these people are being
Call
Nazis
Legitimate Nazi groups that are
Do being labeled
Anti-fascism
But it's so frustrating because that's what he got call the time
Also Unity the other thing that you could
If you were going to say that it's not that the cops were funneling them
Torrid
Cousin
It's because the cops as we now know are essentially an arm of the so maybe
Maybe they were funneling them towards them so the
Cops didn't have to
Murder anybody
Love murdering people let identity Europa be on the hook for this one
I get no more video of cops
Beating up unarmed black overtime
Looks like that guy with the stupid Shield
Any wife
Does not understand
The unfortunate
Sort of
Complacent other issue
This is this to me is like
Real strong evidence
YouTube just a dumb dumb
This is just very dumb
They propped up failed
American engine of Lies
The truth
Free speech and murdering other people's ideas
To form from basic services
But you better be okay
My electricity
Gracefully combines so many different issues
Like what's going on
Reason with the cake is
Because it protects
The classes
Right
You are very welcome
If you want
You are against the Civil Rights Act
Go for it
That libertarian should be but if they want to later
Mi religion
Does not acknowledge that gate
And as I'm sure you know there's a difference between gay people
Religion has never
Supported
Slavery
Matter what your religion
Know about the person
A person whose rights are either being acknowledged or violated
Electricity
No you have some liberals
World of Beer
Your electricity will be shut off
Situation like that and you'll freeze to death
Multiple old women have in the
Hey there is Alex has complained about the past while never wrestling with why is that a problem
Cuz all it is is
Being
Punished for his behavior in a
In a media space
Eddie's
Comparing it
The gay cakes
Situation
Cake wasn't gay
But also
Stand-up chops coming back
Like the Great British Bake Off is that you better make that cake
But
Conflating with Houston
Situation
Monopoly
Straight up
Crazy and I know that at the beginning of the show I said that if he gets off Twitter
In terms of his ability to
But I don't think that
Because
He ducked like
There is a monopoly of the public space
Booking Twitter
I don't believe that that
That's relevant
Come to the question at all
He's f*****
Because
He needs those
I need
He's not entitled to
Because of what
He does
Weaving how is he able to then say that they should be regulated
His entire position is if we talked we talked about that before
Monopoly
And stuff like that
Pretty hateful
Sure
But regulation
Whatever she doesn't mind
To draw but Doug Behrman
The only reason I bring this up
Even that
Which I agree with you
Monopolies are terrible
I don't think
Monopoly
We've had this discussion over and over
If you do believe that
Good for you
That's your biz
That means something about you
That is not about Twitter or Facebook
You don't have either really
I have
Like I'm on Facebook
Only for the group
That would still exist
Repeat whatever
But it doesn't help
I don't post it on Facebook and
Maybe a year
Yeah maybe you're even posted on Facebook haven't looked at anybody else's
Couple months ago
Even though
I'm posted on Twitter in for f****** ever
We haven't reached anybody with that stuff
Necessarily
Like if it works for us it would work for our
Lenhart numbers are going
Very high up we're on equal playing field we have
Podcast
We still have YouTube videos
They're old but they're up
It's punching upwards still for us
Slowly
It slowly
About regulation inside
What was the bottom
Little confused
Did Alex Wood before
Yes yeah
Enter. Of the show that I think
Profound
Dangerous
He loves you
Not if they're Muslims
Don't lose the baby with the bathwater as they say
No it's worse than that
Word of the day calendar
Cogitate
They're going to make their move on the next 3 months this is unprecedented
Infowars.com
Alright
Buy our products
MMA won't make their move
Fun stuff to do
Discuss
But like
Just like a
My response to Alex
Senpai is like a sleep
Just kind of like
Ridiculous
Trying to find your way to make people outraged
Why UConn
Might as well
Even to a plug-in now
The add pivots are so much more robust
Because
Getting people to
Infowars.com
Is so much more important
The next 3 months
That the
Just staying infowars.com
Go to can you ship
Absolutely
You can do that
He just can't have his own
Stop
Hey if you can post
Their videos on YouTube
We could do it
Stuff you can find it is it is
Loft for me
Not not
So much the Alex
But that rock
I wonder how he's
I hope he's okay
But the reason is because he would put out that without the
Commercial
It was so much
Commercials for
Cousin present-day there's no diamond gusset there's no
The picture
Almost
I like that
All just
Like little tiny minute-long
Clips
They're coming for Trump fire staff
They signed
X
Uses English properly
If you if you're that motivated
It is what it is but it's
Special Report
Really hard to
Where is OU have a must-win special report
Or Alec supposed to money
Right
Might but they're all labeled January 1st 97
So I don't know what the f*** to do with any of that
How old is he
What a memo
Yeah
Years ago
Ask his dad cuz
She probably has a
Trust problem
You know I think that
I can't imagine even if you're like if you're talenti today Tech
Garfield you probably wouldn't
Used to work for him
Even if the salary is okay
You probably like
Yeah I'll go somewhere else I can get a little less working somewhere else and not work
And you can't lie clean on one of his listeners to be like
An intern
Which is why the cast is going to fail
Believers
Hoping some of them
That's bad business
Joy
Anyway
Is on Twitter still
Reasonable
Butt out
How much was it
But this is what he said
Infowars is still on Twitter my Facebook
Play Spotify by Stitcher
Name some more spy webcam
Description
Call false reports
This is crazy he doesn't own his own server
Big
Are they
That implies
Very heavily
He is vulnerable there yeah
If you don't own your own servers Alex
You are
F****** idiot
I don't know I
Emails
I don't know maybe it is fine GoDaddy
Who knows that be hilarious
Right now
Twitter
We will look into this discriminatory
Even number of stars about
What is
Disappointing if that's the president
Yeah it was lower on my list my other thoughts
What that one of them is
If it was all these other places Alex's with engaging
Like Facebook
Can you text off that
There's no car
No clearly
Facebook haven't had
Putative
Thing from the president happen
We're probably in
In the clear
Then the second
Biggest
Is the idea that Alex's pitching
Did the only reason he's still on Twitter is because
The president
Of the United States
Threatens them
With a conspiracy theory that he believes in
Believe that aside for a second
What's fascism Jordan
I don't know
What is the definition of corporate power
Covid-19
Kowtowing to a threat from the president
What the f***
Given some sort of weird threat on the platform
About this shadowban
Conspiracy
Horseshit
Finley
That is
Alex
The case is cool man
Business School
I love the idea of Corporations bending to the will of the executive
That's not good
There's no way there's no way that makes it okay so bad
If
It was Craddock
It's probably
My theory is that the reason why is because of trump
Because of
Violating their whatever policy of
Then people can be like
So you did that
You know that the president has violated policy
Many many times and this is what I've been saying
I support Alex Savon
Who got kicked off
What I would advocate for
I would say it
Easier to leave him on
Then it is to
To kick him off
And then have to abide by the
Because you're right
Welder wire
Threatening world leaders
Bright places
Well maybe not cuz that my forces hadn't actually hit a button
Position as a social media operation
Where you do this now you
Have an expectation
That you should live up to
I think that might be what Jack is doing these terrible
Is awful
But I think it might be
I don't have rules
Really like an advocate
They should also
Maybe
Just
You straight up about it
Because you are like
Totally in the race
We will judge based on who matters
Right they could put that into the okay for them to do that
They could say hey
Some people
They f***** up stuff but
We can't kick him off
That's just part of the rules
Is a little bit
That is a little bit like my idea for the Constitution
Robert
The same thing
Toomey's
That I think
I think there's probably more
Like
Is cowardly.
Control
You know like
You see over and over and over again people who
Threatening
Over and over again
Who are kick-off Twitter
Threats against
Women are taken
Seriously
And women making jokes get them kicked off
So right
But I would love to talk about more another day
Butler
The real salute
Straight up about your rules
This bacon rule is
You are making us a lot of money
We don't care what you say if you were someone who's using this service for free
We might have
Ability
You know you might be a danger to our profit margin
Hey we're going to kick you off
Which is of course
Why they leave Trump in Alex Johnson
Every time
Quote the the president they're always like
The president
And Twitter's like f*** yeah we get another free advertising marketing
Every single time the president is tweeting.
You get rid of a lot of
Especially
You diminish
The effect
Twitch Twitter is
Changing the world and the world through the platform
Get rid of that
I think they
Good
It's dangerous
Negative
But it's
Fruit dessert
You come into this weird place where it's like
If you don't want
Chill like
Really just have a
But not everything
Struggle against
And Alex y struggles in
In the position
You're stupid
He is
There's really no other there's no
About it
This is dumb
Pacifica the right way to go about his
His situation
As you were saying
If you put together something that
People want to listen to
She's making Bad episode
Lexi's real bad this is when you got to step up your game
This is when you got to make your show f****** appointment
I think a lot of his regulars probably don't want to come on
Because he's off all the net
Bright not nearly as big a platform for them to go on
That's true
Jumping ship
I don't know
I don't know that to be sure
But I know that he has
As one of his guests
Hero of Benghazi
Alright alright alright video of Benghazi
But
I just think
Appointment television
With the
Like what he has it is
Disposal you got him though
He's got to remember that made this what it is
By being
Exactly
Jonah in the whale moment
And he needs to shave that be
Those are the two things terrible
I don't know if you ever read this article that there is a
Back in like
Maybe
I'm around there
There was a guy who's trying to sell like a tractor
What happened
Who is on the tracks to held him down
Shaved his beard inmate
And I wanted you to know that
You want to make him alright
Never had thought
If it weren't for this tractor do you think bad
Years ago
My beard
Larry I don't wish that on anybody.
How many crimes as far as
That was pretty hilarious
And I would do that Alex in the second
I will make other people eat other people
I don't know what I think about that but I do
Beyond
Like
I don't know how you do it
I mean where are we August there's no good Halle
Coming up
Remember to wait till October
Easter sale
Christmas is coming up here be great
Because then he could have the ghost of Alex
Or something like that
No I'm not saying is a bit but like
G-Code experience
Terms of something
Watches a clip of
Self
15 years ago or something like that like what
To do
The bigotry
Can do it different
Yeah and you can you cannot be
Often
Like stuff
Is because of
Slandering
Because of the threat
That you've introduced
The people's lives with your life
You can you walk that line for Years baby
You can do it again
Get back to it you're asking for the third acts of of his life in the movie of his
If you're either asking
For the beginning of the third Act
Where has that moment
Or the beginning of Mighty Ducks where is that the start of this is an Alex Jones
Is the fire in a barrel
I don't know man I don't know what I meant
I'm just
I don't see
The future going well
Unless it gets rid of the beard
Has
It can't be a crisis of like
Everyone's trying to kill Trump
Good
Where he was
The yelling isn't
Even fun anymore
The fun
But he's never do
3 minutes of
Silver Stallion
In 2018
It was that is why
The show
Yeah it's because of those things where there's
There's humanizing
Spawn moments
Is yelling
There's lies
There's all of that
Conspiracies
Everything
Come together in a bouillabaisse
Betty's appealing
Now he just has rotten
Food
It's put into this to
He's trying to sell it this
It is interesting that when we did our worst
So waiter isn't even if Waiters
Alright
In our 2015 investigation
Like the the thing that we continue talking about it
Why is he
Hitching is wag
Perfectly in the short-term
Ended his career
Like that's what we
Positive would happen
Lo and behold it came to pass
And I think
We cogitated
I think as we go further into the
The 2000s
Which is
Agnostic
I think we're going to
Even more
Where it went wrong wrong
I don't think I think the Trump is like
Laughed
Ruin
Much more before
Taking into
Consideration
If only because
We don't know when he starts talking about George Soros
That's not to say talking about George Soros
Is your career
It's just that mean some
Meredith
Secondarily we don't know when that meeting with the Russia
Was
Those two things
If we can find those
Much more of like
This is the
Definitive Dory
His career
Currently he wants to talk more about how
Because
What he said about parking
Piece of s*** about what
And the reason that he's doing this
Is because most
Attack
It's off of Twitter
Has to do with
Seaside about David Hogg
Which
Beginning
He's going to create some straw man
And then at the same time
He's going to lie
I was at home when the shooting started
And then the shooting was over by then
Wabasha
School shooting
Play those videos
Are a lot of other people
Videos
I wasn't it
School
They're talking with that
We talked about this already
Because of edited video clips
Skip this interview
In the evening
Got his camera and
Came back to the school
Or whatever
Came back
Obtuse triangle
Get some footage
That is nothing
He was with
The shooting happened
Screw up the timeline
This is
Literally
Intentionally misrepresenting
Because all that
If you watched
Select
Taken from
Came back to the school
If you watch the rest of it it's very clear
That either means that Alex has never watched
The entire clip
Is only seeing the short versions
Simplythick
School
He has seen is intentionally lying
Either way
The way he's behaving
Successfully multiples
So
David Hawk
Well I mean
I don't
I don't know what to say it's just
Yeezys embody and why he's a bad journalist
Like this
This is why
You need to know
A modicum of what you're talkin
It's bad
It's a weird place to be
Like this show is like
You don't understand
Turning this off
Because
Look there's so much just
You know
Yelling about
Contrast
Eli about David Hogg
All this stuff it's like
You're getting defensive is she
Is boring
You're a boring person now
Your s*** to look at
I don't want
I'll be fine I have a Mastiff
I'm getting ahead of myself let's play this next week
About David Hogg
Running around saying
Twitter
August crisis actor
On some young person
What's your definition
World
With Sandy Hook because I
Because I was looking at all the angles
For that
Repeal the 1st Amendment
News
Cumbersome process
Will get ahold
Right we have to go through
Recorders
Ratify
The Congress has to vote
Three quarters
We did however agree that the First Amendment
It won't go away
Commercials
Is Star Trek or Star Wars
Darth Vader and Obi-Wan Kenobi
You strike me down
Become so much more power
And I'm so he gets struck down
The shot of the the Millennium Falcon
That's great
Stupid
It's so stupid
The only thing I want to really say about that last
Equipped
Don't really
Deal with Alex
Talk about it
Yeah and I know everyone wants to talk about him
If you don't know much about him
No one died in park
Because he did say that about believable
So you might that out
Or something like that
There's new wanted to what
He was lying about
Have you just come in with that sort of like broad Haymaker
What you're doing is
Have something fake to
Respond
And I've definitely seen that with people who
Should know better
Definitely should know better and getting low
Sweet action
Off of
But they're real close
And if they just knew a little better
Knew what he actually
They could do a better job
But in the meantime
You probably stop
You can get a lot of points
Online I think
From
Being like
Hey Alex Jones
Parkland
Good for you
Enjoy it
Druthers retweets
Stephanie
More engaged
All you're doing is
People do it for the
It look for the gram Instagram
Got it
Doesn't matter if you restart a g Moore
Why are we are not a brand
We're bad at Brandon
Now we're just like a show
Back to Alex
Really into
Fear
To me it seems like what he really wants
Talk about
He already said
Take out Trump in the next
Three months
Right
For the past 15
But two years
Beyond that
He realizes he
Hey
And the only thing
You can't do
So
Warfare
They're not going to just burn trash cans
Congressman
Heber City council members
Call just
And then
People that are here
I mean it's pretty harsh
That's pretty that's
The idea that
Noah's going to come around
Starting up maybe not doing fires in barrels but they're going to start
So that's the first piece of
Now gets worse than this next
He's going to build this fear up even further
Apple stock market
Crashes
Stock market crash
With in October
Historically
October
October break
I just can't believe the globalist you're siding with Tricom dinner and Holly was doing mission that all these crazy people don't want America to come by
Everybody's globalist
You really should be joining the American president
They're going to go For Broke
All sorts of Sleeper Cell
What
Downrightnow
That's pretty f****** extreme
That's a bit aggressive pretty serious in terms of the I'm trying to scare you
I'm really trying to scare you
Stand on top of your place and pour chlorine down your chimney is that kind of what he's suggesting that
I'm so cuz it's not like
I have a window AC unit
Sears central air that's not going to work now getting side
20 minutes of is great
Find it was not on you it just didn't have any
Spoiler Jordan download a copy of Debs
But it didn't have audio
The audio
I knew what it would be like
Anyway and The Rock never fought that f****** skyscraper
The movie cuz I was
How to get home
Did he
Steven grew his foot
That's how great the Rock is in movies
The lost his foot
The end of the movie
4%
I got was unvaccinated
So is there
They're like 50-50 on the on the scale
What do you think about the figure that Alex is pushing right now
How do you feel
General feel like it on top
You know I hate ice
Feel like is it
For him
It's parody
Because no one even his people aren't going to believe that they're going to follow you home
And then put chlorine in your air running on
At 8
Y8
Do it when everybody's asleep
Or do it
During the work day before they get home
The furnace
Chimneys
Everybody everybody knows that Iranian sleeper cells operate under Chimney Sweep laws
Chlorine gas
He's trying to tell us something
Years ago
So there's a lot of fear going on here it's a lot of bulshit
Everybody better politically
By the way he does not say
You should do 20%
You just gets into his negative
So 20% of the time when they start killing political leaders
Be clear that I'm not like
Anyting
He never says what
Please do that 20% of the time it's implied
Get a gun
And get ready
They start killing political leaders in Patriots
This tradition
Ron Paul
Judge they're going to the Supreme Court
There is no
The Cold War was World War
New Congress is World War 4
Pick your side it's already begun
Embarrass
World War 4
I'm a noob
From the cutout Parks net worth
Meandering
Stop starts with this
You know they're going to kill cops
Kill cops
Stock markets going to crash in October
Is everything is going to go down
Chlorine in your air system
Going to show up
The f****** murder all paper at your door
30 seconds
We do not polite
That is one thing about leftist
When we do start murdering all of the Patriots
Are one of our big rules
It's in the by-laws
Knock politely
What what are we are we them
No no
Theodore
Love
Special
Or whatever when he's like David dogs in a man's world
Just f****** stop
This is
This is lame
Man
I don't
I don't feel the same way about like listening
2000 episodes
The 2009 episode that I were not covering yet
Little just boring
I don't feel that way about them I don't feel like just go
Go to bed go to bed I don't feel that way about it I feel like
Better tomorrow
Tomorrow
About this
He needs
Just
Stop
And let Paul Joseph Watson
He needs to get away from it
Let Paul Joseph Watson take over Infowars and let him be the guy
From behind the scenes
Controlling stuff never going to do it cannot be behind this
Have to have all these I understand
Living
He has
That he needs to
To give it to Paul Joseph Watson
None of these other dudes can handle that old Charger stuck stay with night boring as hell
Paul sucks also
Much more popular
If Alex wants to survive
At the end of the day based on what I've seen in the weeks
He can't do it himself
He's too self-involved
Like all this is so much him
It's personal
Too much
You needs to step away from it and unfortunately that's literally the only thing
Because
To be in control of it
Howie's
Easy
For disgrace Whiteman to have a Redemption
Another TV show
Whatever did everybody
Whenever a white man says I'm sorry and then continue doing the same s*** that he was doing
Set
98% of America story
That's what it is
So just f****** go away for a little bit
Lylo
Wow Paul Joseph Watson runs
Then
You're going to have a big guy and courageous come back
Whenever Paul Joseph Watson
Vista Pawn
Is
Without edging he stink
Yeah you got a heart of combat stable a leon.
Just.
As your beard is
Magnificent
Coverage
But some people have like a lion
Cheek where it's like
He has enough
Their butt
It's just
Look
It doesn't say
Does he need to like
Styling
No cuz it's not long enough
It should be
He's clearly trimming
Is the thing is making it look this bad
Like if he has that much beard now from
A couple months
I don't know what
The f*** you do
Boosting supplements may not be working
2 hour
If you are list
There is a bridge
Tiny little Ian Scott anthrax
Yeah
Crazy looking forever
Most
Caesar
Pretty In-Shape guy
His head is longer than Saturn
The fathead
Batman
Bubba
I would give him a
Exactly yes
Aggressive it's perfect for Alex
Ambrose Burnside
Yeah
Be great
Anyway
Beast
From heaven heaven to listen to
Alex's
Sir
Weather
Start this over again
New York Times bestselling author of death
Oh boy
Sister organization
Andover history
As opposed to
Conservative
Yep
The arguments that I've seen I'm never going to watch that whole documentary
Large
Due West
Misrepresenting the party swap
It's mostly just play how the Civil Rights
It's remove any and all Southern Democrats from the
Slavery
But yeah but you got to Union Democrat
That I can
Will not acknowledge the Democratic Party
Was the party of slavery
Yeah
Dude for real it was fuckedupshit but then we got the Civil Rights Act passed and all of those guys
Didn't get all the races leave for the Democrats
You guys want slavery
So
Mr. Sousa is the number two
Filmmaker of all time
I trouble
So I looked up his filmography
He's either right behind Allen Smith
Still in there
No I'm going to change
Call it
I honestly
Thought when I did my research for this I thought you said he was the number to documentary
You said
Number two of us
Edna super I understood it to be
Documentary filmmakers
Cuz I meant Michael Moore was number one
Lakers
So I looked into it and what I found was that the here are the top grossing documentary films of all time
Made 119 million dollars at the Box
Number to is Alaska part of the wild 100000000 directed
Number three
At the box office
Crazy
100 million
Number for PlayStation 3
93.3 million dollars director
Dinesh d'souza's filmography
We got
2016 Obama's America
33 million dollars
It was the top grossing documentary
Fortunate
Tickled came out that year
But there's other field in terms of
Documentaries
Am I got the three millions pretty good
America imagine the world without her
14 Milly
Hillary's America
Made
13 million
Destination just came out but it's gross about 3.5 million the first few weeks
Which is great for what is obviously a no-budget cost him $100,000
All four of these add up to
To about
7 million dollars
Right which combines
For his career
Second behind
It is so goddamn far from the second
Even
In the span of his career as much as March of the Penguins
Or the Justin Bieber concert
Hartefeld Never Say Never
Now the only person ever to Justin Bieber film great over 10 million dollars more than
Great and it deserves every penny
Azz beating Verna hurts
Yeah and Errol Morris Broadband Arrow Morris band
Didn't have good box office open
Like The Thin Blue Line
No
Cartman crying
But I don't take those movies also came out at time
Adjusting for
Inflation
So like Errol Morris is documentaries
Is the came out in like midday
Herzog
Around the same time adjusted
But they're pretty well I forgot
Here's the real comedy of that
I forgot that's Herzog did grizzly
Let's see what that grows
I don't like well I'm looking this up
You go to your phone
Squirtle
Actually that great
Hey 3.1 million
MSY
Getting 30
He's very notice
Like the fact that he has that in his
Catalog
Snot snot
To be ignored or
Variable
There
I don't know
Mysterious
Maybe because
There's a certain
Subsection of the population
Feels underserved
Conspiracy theories not being
Aggressively repeat to them by Hollywood
Artificially inflate the numbers of anybody likes
What is Kirk Cameron movie Kirk Cameron
Play make money
They don't lose
Jim Bakker
A lot of those are like
You'll have
Over-inflated gross
Just because of
Church group
And we would
We have buses
Of churches that coming for movies like
Carmen
Norco
No
Carmen was this old
Opera
No no no
Christian celebrity
He would make these look
Super low budget
Movies but sometimes they would show up at our
I'm so if we got that they would sell the
Because busloads
And they would just go see Carman the Champion
I remember my Growing Up When The Passion of the Christ
Every single f****** Church
My flashlight
Because of like too many
People it was because
It was all
Groups of two
Most
Movie viewing is
Update have bosses
Sykesville the parking
I did
That's fine
But you guys all want
I'm Foothill Furious I never got a handjob during
Furious
You have a girlfriend now
Right
Is it on Netflix
I don't know I haven't looked
It's too late now it seems almost organic
Coregasm
You know what is on it
What
Justin Bieber
Included
Netflix has two
Pay some sort of
Every time somebody has generally I think included in the gross
Comes down like
What would be considered in the grossest
Contract
It comes down to
Like if you were numbers
That's on Netflix
And get rid of
Right
Netflix just pays whatever is license
The top
OverWatch
And that's why
Really shity
50 boxes
Like everybody special
What
I've watched it like
Stillgray
Anel
Anal who's done anal
Fantastic
Perfect that is not a good representative sample of Rory scovel
You chose
Betty White
If I need to bring
The last time we checked in on modern-day Alex right after the ban
Kicked off of stuff
Made my poinsettia
He is faded
Can do whatever he wants
We'll see what happens
My point
It's his own fault
He could have done much better
Rambling about the
The Chinese
Complain about the Chinese
If you want to complain
Hey Nolan
Cover the Chinese doing stuff
That's f******
Stupid there's an article right here from the other day out of the China
About that
Demolition after protests
Weird
Authorities in northern China delay the demolition
Saturday
1000 people demonstrate
Local residents
Drive to Titan
Restrictions on religious
Across
A Muslim
It's part of a widespread attempt
Bring Believers in
So you want to talk about stuff like this you can't people are
There are news stories about that
I've heard plenty of new stories you can
Confined from
You know our Outlet
In America about
Brutally Tramp
International Trade rules
Is China
It's not like
It's not like no one is saying China's
Dick
Quiet
You can't claim that absolve
America's Best
The number one
Where to share in the blank
Much better
If you actually
Buddy.
Just
Diminished
Beer
If the exact same game we saw him playing
Years and years
And he's so true
Like a like
Pavlovian dog
But he is just
Doing the same thing
It's not going to work
Probably some domestic issues with his wife
He needs to overcome it
And then
Cuz then we might be cooking with Jack
Slater Hill
What did you just disparage Rocky for the greatest movie of all time
Rocky
It's like a movie
Here's the time where I tell you I have never seen any of Rocky movie
Oh boy, another $50 to the Patriots
Dan and I will do a knowledge of all of the Rocky movies
In one day
Providence
I mean
Please if you like the show support show do know it's shity after Regis
But we appreciate
We might go to knowledge buy.com
Corksport
We're working on
I'm working on a lot of stuff replace a lot of the content that we had on our website
Lot of the blog
You for your support
We are you should join
And tell your mother
You are really
That's correct
We are all these platforms were on
I think we've criticized the Chinese more coherent
Here we are
Still online so obvious
Question of
Who should go f*** themselves this week of all time
From Twitter
Go fuc yourself
You put
Alexandra Thurston color