Alexandra Thurston color
Alex
Dan
What's the last
Hunan
I've never seen
What is abroad
Play Hold by that I mean
Cific I saw my high school
High School in Columbia Missouri
Pacific
And I saw that and I was underwhelmed
Yeah
Closure
Off off
Broadway
It was
Kjzz
Who will hardtop super into
Who is super energetic
Cuz we are under understand
Drama Department
Junior High
Dial soap
Movie that was released last year with Gosling
Applebee's
Super Skate
Skate
Over ever-changing uninspired
Ouch
This lead kid does have the potential to one day host the podcast
Petro Mart
Is a good one we can find that guy
I I got out of there
I want to talk little bit about the goings-on in the world
You tell lost his mind
Who were recording this here on the 14th
On Tuesday
And he pretended
He put out
Yeah cuz what he did is he tweeted the feel like the Communists are coming after infowars.com you got to go to news
Wars in prisonplanet.com
And then infowars.com became just a
Big thing that says Infowars is under attack and then links to his other sites
If your cycle taking down there's no damn way to all of your other stuff
Senior site down level up
By the way
Infowars is under attack
Hey we don't want you to be able to do what you want with your site
Be doing if you took down his servers or whatever
Conscientious
Courteous
Will allow you to redirect traffic
If you want
Perfect people to do whenever they're taking down
Thoughtful website
It really undoes the the move of take it down
I would say I have
0 the big PR stunt
Rock that all I seen
People tweet
This is so fake
Yeah and that's so
It's very light
Go f****** gogoro for not found
But it is a natural progression
Narrative
Because the world is really like hey you suck we don't want you places
Some companies have responded
Twitter heaven
You know it's up there or their
It's that's all it is
He wants it
To be like they're all coordinated against
These are companies that have all made their own decisions
Vimeo
Rap
Or gif
Epperly reminiscent of a man exiled from a village and yet still allowed to have a bullhorn
Write him being on Twitter
You guys.
I want it
Going to bed
Imagine that
Do you want to throw in a row
We Haz jazz
Thrilled about this
Covenant
Democrat level
Very special shout-out
Nicholas
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites Italy a bucket of poop
The show
You can do so by going to our website
Sport the show button we would appreciate it very much
Jordans
We are going
He's in his own world and I don't really care about his scrambling trying to keep his head above water we've already covered into episodes
2009 plugging along. Some updates on that in the very near future but for now
I feel like you and I are probably both a little bit exhausted
Especially today
At 8
Run around the city all over the place on
Ehrenreich
It would have liked
I want to go check out
What Kerry Cassidy
He has for us
I'm not sure how crash
Airline closes the gate
Wow
This is the sequel to The okay
Numark Richards buddy
And I went back
Let me be
F****** total
Clear with you
I wasted a lot of time watching Bad episodes
There were a couple that I don't even like
I thought there was one where she was talking about Bilderberg
How to draw the Stark parallels between her and Alex
It's not worth going over in episode
Bilderberg
So there's that and then there was one
Eyewear she's interviewing
Infowars.com
The guy who pretends that he's a big
So I
A lot of time trying to find
Xfinity
He's great
But I
Timer
You know who never disappoint
Mark f****** Richard
I realize there's at least three of the episodes
Before strip that
If you want to go
I believe this was
2 years ago
You're so funny
Good morning there
Spend some time
With Mark Richard
Mark Richards episodes
Short version of it
He's a crazy dude who orchestrated murder
In California
Something years ago, San Francisco
He did he was gay
Kingdom
I work he was the king with over
A bunch of young kids
Who would be Lords or something along those lines
Did workout
His murderer was found guilty of it but Carrie cast
The he was off-world at the time
You part of the secret space program
When the murder was committed
Between
Hotels Cary
The stupidest I've ever heard my life
She believes all
It's nuts
We have now upon further review of Project Camelot
Besides
She may not
Told
As much as she says she raped
What she wants to get out of it
The good news is though
Is we don't really need to worry about our most recent episode spoiling the story
Bananas
Pieces within this episode that are fresh
That might as well be
Current in the timeline
Yeah scholarship
On Netflix
Who is this
It really doesn't matter that much
Coming up with this stuff
Then what she thinks you studying is crazy
First thing if she is
F****** around
It's interesting if
Accomplice to murder
Is
Manipulating her
If she's like
Oh this is probably what real people do
Hangout with Raptors for chocolate more fascinating still further I would say
Because we don't know that
And because she's not allowed to record it
She is never actually spoken to Mark Richards maybe she talked to him one time
And then from here on out it's just become Sixpence kind of stuff could be talking into the mirror saying that it
Mark Richards
Just making all this b******* up on Route I seen her in a parking lot that was allegedly the bridge
Sprouts
Joanne Richard guy
They don't get to record things
Visit Mark Richard
She's got to tell you about how she has to write everything down
Project Camelot
Interview with Captain Mark Richards of the secret space program
I'm going to sort of the recall of everything that we talked about
Ability
I should note that we had only small pencil
Paxil
She's going the graphite think I don't know
Mechanical pencil
That's what my mind goes to
How big are her hands have we ever seen her in physical relation to another human being
She might be
Books
But she holds up her also Giant
I don't know if those are commercially available
Giant books
They might be alcoholic
Seems like it's a possibility I don't know
Giant or not
Gel pens with ink
We'll leave that aside
Probably just me speak about it
Here's another thing
You can't trust
This is not the first time they've
To get over to the fridge
Time around
She has you meant to go
Something nefarious
First of all
Six months ago I was prevented from
Part of my face
Looks like
Halsey
Stroke
Just woken up I just woke up this morning with it I had nothing
Went on
I think you just got Bell's palsy
Happens to people like Jimmy Pardo
What is guana half of your face will just go numb
When you can't move it
Really
Did not know that that was
I'm not crazy I've heard Bell's Palsy said many a time I thought it was like
He's like Lou Gehrig's disease
You know like there was a guy named
Alexander Graham Bell
Because I'm on the phone
Exact
Apothecary difference
Potatoes
Alright
The ground
What servers are called Pomme de Terre
Apple's of the ground all right I'm done with
I'm done with your friend
Do we have any listeners in French
I see a come up in the analytic someone's listening
France
Well if you're listening in France
F****** get on it
Call somebody call your call macron tell him to change the name
Potatoes to just like potato
Cauliflower
No I gotta get all of the words I am frustrated with the fact
I would argue that are potatoes the ground around potatoes
7 degrees out there
Surrounded
Took a bite out of a ground
Probably
For the community garden
Potato potato
So
I would argue
Taylor weapon attack
This is
Bell's Palsy Isabel Baldi
Stroke I still feel bad but
Time I don't
Like 2 minutes
Capabilities
Her mental state
Physical or even before that pretty much the same person throughout all of her videos
I don't know man why would you go if you think it's a scalar weapon
I don't know everything about palsy that Bell's palsy
From what I understand
Mostly based on Jimmy Pardo talking about it a lot cuz he had
In some cases
Just goes away and it's
Some cases a dozen
Scary
But
If she
Didn't get any treatment writing
Possible that it would just
Resolve itself
You
Are really trying to make it seem like someone doesn't want you to go to Taco
Mark Richards
When in reality it's just
What happens
The people of assert
Such a big deal.
Look you can believe
You can believe all the conspiracy theories you want but if you go to a doctor after that
You're full of s*** you're a f****** liar
Live up to your b*******
It's kind of
Cuz it would imply a lack of
Trust in your own diagnosis
Bell's palsy
You did not
So
You know
She couldn't get over there 6 months ago cuz of the scalar weapon attack
Baba she finally does get over to the
The prison
Brouhaha
In the prison
I wanted to talk about was his current present conditions and
His prison conditions when I was there
Somebody had murdered
So
That's real bad
Also Market
Murderer
Believe
And yes, it's entirely possible that someone got shanked
Not everybody
The people who have
Committed
Rhythm for murder related
Okay so maybe the murderer
Murdery baby
Bill says that past behavior is not a predictor of future events
Why would you punish
He only rarely committed murder
I'm not going to listen
Then like actual adjective
Don't get me wrong
But if there's a murderer in the prison I'm going to make sure all the murderers
I'll probably in their self
Prejudicial
Do you not like stop-and-frisk
Same thing
There's a lot of profiling same thing just as murder one guy now you want to murder a bunch of guys
That's a false promise
I would like to change about the prison system
I think it's a horrible to deal with
The idea of
Generalizing
People who are
Willing to commit a murder right probably
What's another one
That's a good point
Especially people who believe themselves
Part of the program
Who telepathically communicate with rafters
What's even if it wasn't even him
It's probably Minerva
She got pissed off
We are going to get intimate earlier but
To the prison can do
This is
Nuts
Vista
This clip is
It paint
A bleak picture
There's more to the prison story I can tell you that when I was there Market
I had very little sleep for 2 days
Because they had given him a cellmate who was very dangerous
He was someone who was saying he was not
And talk to it and
Not like you saying he's not whatever but
These damn clothes more like marks Richards and he's been on
On a meth high for a couple of nights
That's possible also because this next part doesn't pass.
And he wore a Hannibal Lecter mask
He was a younger man
Possibly
Pockmark can handle himself and
That person moved
Because that situation was looking extremely dire
How are you going to get it
Hannibal Lecter mask
To recreationally where around in prison I feel like that might be something that the guard
You are allowed one piece everybody
Statues people wear plaid
Some people have
I know a lot about the purse
Obviously
I don't think
Hannibal Lecter mask
He's going to pass that even crazier
Gotta be like a little hockey
You can do better
Who's Roma movie
Come up with something else menacing but you know what this is
That's great
Pair the wine
Incorrect
Facebook
Just another copycat killer Dan
I don't believe any
A b b
I don't I mean that could just be
My standard
Response to every
Hold on
Does this mean
This is
Who is his
No no no his longtime companion
No no
I think I don't
That guy was ever his cellmate
Another guy in the
I can't remember his name
Carrie has reported that he has a lieutenant
Which is
Some young kid
At the prison
Kill the Selma March
No don't do that
And Carries like this
But he's a great guy like that
Did that already and that's why he's in prison
Psychologically whatever
Re-litigate in his past
Concept of Make Believe
Like in line with
Like basic psychology
Childhood
Play out
And have a better
Unresolved issue
Alcoholic
Alcoholics trying to create a better outcome for it
Universal but it's a
The prettiest
Specially with people who aren't involved
Recovery process
Epsom salt therapy
But I got you just needed
Over and over again so many of his fantasies
Kind of involved
Things that are like this is
Maybe an analogy for doing the stuff that you didn't realize what you're just saying
I like the idea of him going around recruiting
And telling them not to murder people that he wants them
Well I solved it I wanted that
But I didn't even tell those kids to kill him
I told him not to
I learned my lesson
Can I get out now
No no
The other your time
So now that we've gotten through this bit of
His prison conditions
Do the wacky stuff
Talking about
Artificial intelligence satellites
And artificial intelligence
British
When she said he's got into black night I was like
Martin Lawrence
It has wiring in a sort of which is unusual for
Boards and slots
I don't understand it
He says the wiring in place
Makes it very low-tech
It's much harder for the
Artificial intelligence out there
Two governments
Satellites out there
The three is
Noticed
There's no real further information about this
If you're curious cuz I have no idea Black Knight artificial intelligence satellites
God knows what the British
That sounds right though
It does spiritual like what
How do we break into that
It is
Meaning for wife
Well there is one other thing is
They're not wireless
Sure
Bored
You go that's why I carry traveling all the time
Powering such a large artificial
Intelligence cable
So you can't pull it
Timmy uppet
And get all the way up
All of these things
This is silly I'm not sure what else to say about it
Just really give any
Talk about other than
There's wires
I'm a big fan of winter blankets
Does not ask a follow-up just like
Apparently there are a three artificial intelligence
Satellites
I don't know
From the 70s
Now and when they get a little
They send a text
Studio I realized
Cuz now I'm curious about them as I'm staying on
To Starstruck
Okay that's awesome
So Jordan
You might know
About science
Do you know what time
I've heard of it the dreams of men I've heard that
Brian Herbert bulshit
Let me tell you about
I don't think
Frank Herbert
But
A very notable science fiction author comes up and Mark Richards
Azimuth
Later
Recruited by Mark Scott
What's
Then given information
To augment his sci-fi story
And this was to reveal what's going on in the secrets
Program
Currently there are several other sci-fi authors
Do the same thing happened to
However
I make sense
Why
Because you can't come out and say like
This is what happened
Securities
Fears
I'm doing drugs and I'm out of my house
Say that kind of stuff and I kind of
I don't know I've read a lot of Philip K dick
I think
Degrading
He's alright
It is
Geography
But that's just because
He's written like what
Novels you wrote a lot
What are you got
I don't know
I haven't studied his catalog nearly as much
But that's just because
My dear buddy Nick Rowley
Super 8 in real life
I have never read much
And I don't think that I think it's
Degrading
Uart
To use
The arguments like this like
Someone couldn't
Possibly come up with these ideas they had to be given to them by the
Secret space program
In order to
Service like
Preemptive programming
Because further I don't know
If you read a bunch of
You stuff I don't
Think it has anything
To do a lot of the time with
Anything real
Anything real in their world
You know there's just
Like I don't know
Man in the High Castle what is that at
How to do the secret space program
Morrow
Clearly
Christmas program and there's an alternate reality
Beat it in creating this
Realize that we can't have the Nazis running everything
The reality that could have been and then they approved him
Otherwise nobody would f****** know how great they were
What about flow my tears the policeman said
Are those tears
What do they what do they leave about then
No artistic title but I'll tell you right now
To me I don't know what that word mean
It's a bummer cuz I like I like
You're right there's a lot of trash in
Things like
Is amazing
Ubiquitous
Motto Palmer Eldritch
But these are really great
Books that are fun
And interesting ideas are interesting
But for them to be sitting here and be like
Yeah that's all just because the Dutchmen told him to write that
To me I hear a certain amount of angry creative people because they
This is so on creative
That's it that's what I'm saying it just like I just like conservative assholes usually wind up going back
Can finding out that they were shity f******
Comedians are trying to say
No my creativity in making up this s***
Is so much more interesting than your actual creativity
In making up what you made up
You have to tear down Philip K dick in order to build up your own all of his ideas
Reality mine
Rude
Creativity or whatever the f*** it is I don't know
I suppose so
Also I will all cops
Secret space program is
Responsible for
Together
Cuz I was not very good
Just about
What what is Philip
Racist repressed sexual desires
I don't know I don't know if
The books that I listened to
Goodwin
Is really just about like
There's sort of an allegory of like
Garden of Eve
Kind of thing
About weather
I mean it
Very of it
Hi Missy say it could be said to look at it through
Hero dolls
Crazy books about life
Space you know all this
This weird stuff
I like this book is very
Very basic
It's interesting
Well that's it
His career that like CS Lewis wrote a bunch of basic boring life photo
History of logical
It was not
I think it's good
Is alright
Did he did he wind up having five bucks is five or six in The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe
I was talking about
The Silver Chair Prince Caspian
How's work
I think is blurred line
You're stepping into my world son
I don't want to do this
I really don't want to do this
KSAT live
Weather all the dreams
Your cell carrier mark
Okay.
Just did a lot of
So is it
We hear something
Era
Is it really
Read between the people we look at
With the gilding of
Decorating
If possible that she's had a change of heart
Interesting that throughout the
Just the entire spec
Guillermo's like you know
Jim Bakker isn't
Anti-putin at all with the presentation that they are Christian Nation what have you
Super on board
By what their nationalist
Right now
Because they
They're no longer with the Reptoid
Now you can take that however you want to but
It's weird all of these people
Interesting
It's almost like they're all under the
This way
Some sort of PR machine
Being run by the Kremlin
I don't know if I've ever heard of Russian propaganda
Is colored
All of his say that and then we go back to the
At least I'm special
I don't know what I can't make a bra declaration
About this cuz I don't know who the f*** would be
Caring about what Kerry Cassidy
I don't think that the Russian government necessarily
Is super
We got a swing swery Carey
But there is
There is something
There's something
I'm not sure what it is
I think when you go
Through all of this FF
Talked about with
Especially
As a you know as it is
Pointed out before
She is racist
Towards her imaginary
Russia has a
Wait I mean what would you call it like a
Something similar to a white ethnostate
Bright
None of it is
You know what
Itself to be what the propaganda says it is
It is part of that like
Ideal to so many of these people of
White Nation
A white people black Nations for black p
People get over here Raptors get over here like every Wonder
To stay away from each other
And then problems will be solved
From all of the support of Putin is not necessarily
Russia versus
Let's make sure that
Ethnically cleanse
Whether it be alien or human
The fucken say most of the
These people probably
You know I mean we're all seeing
People who are
Caucasian
Who are the
Mouthpiece
Budgetary
Kefir
From Russia
Necessarily
White people don't have a lots of
Well especially in America
Especially in America in the car
Yeah that's going to be all that threatened does can't
On the global
Right
Switch to the Orthodox Church
That would be a little bit tired
Yeah the Russian Orthodox Church
Lot of rules that are about
I don't know I don't read anything about the most religions
I think that's
Picture of
Is it works its way
To wherever it
And I called everybody else
I don't know exactly what
To think about this
Move on
Because
Cinemark at this point
Formation about the
You're not going to get it
Or something about him
I asked Mark about the recent book
Devils
Chess board
And
Friendly and protective originally towards marking his father but changed his
That Mark was siding with Kennedy
Marcus became persona non grata
10 years old
Goodwill
Already he was already he's already being brought into the fold
Right right
Remember that much
I don't know
I know that Margaret
The boy probably was one of the most
Capable
Genius brilliant
100 books on World War
Second help kill a guy
Prison forever
Start lying about all this s***
But
I just
Timeline problem be damn cuz game we always talk about this
Time is a flat circle
Absolutely
It's funny though that Allen Dulles
You guys are cool
You like candy
F*** you
F*** you radar
I like imagining this conversation
She had with him because you know that she was like
I asked you about this
Any likes
But I'll tell you what
Dallas
Did not like us
Whenever we did
What was it Dallas was talking about
I don't know who is I mean I know him
Could you leave me on a little bit further
What I told you that Asimov would come
Coming up but I forgot
Eclipse
Clarke and Isaac Asimov were also people that the Dutchman
Information program arrived in all this
G stuff to
Build up their science fiction
She goes on to say that you was supposed
If you are thirsty
Clark
Speculating
Because they were going to talk to.
Corsican goes back to the scalar weapons
Sounds sounds
Yeah so sorry I forgot
Explain the three types of Men In Black
And they're out
Oh I thought they were all going to be different
Versions of Wilson
Guys dressed in black remember that
River face-to-face
Alright alright alright
The movie Caroline
So now we jump back into the episode
Mark of the Dutchman new Allen Dulles
They supported JFK
It is next
Mark is heavily implying the aliens killed
She also said that
Yes they thought Johnson was The Mastermind originally
Johnson was in pain
Either of them
And orchestrated by
What is nesting
Factions
And on a much higher level
Call Marquita
More about it
The association Leavenworth
Is a military prison with a
Much
More dire circumstance than the
Medium security prison that he's in
Time
Mediums
Show me
What about a private prison
The only reason that I'm
If
Mark Richards was in a private prison IV like
Prison where
The same as it is now but they allow camera
Cuz I want
I want to see that this interview amazing a reality TV show
Dart.org
The Pretender real start one up get a camera
Yeah that's the only that's the only
Ivory
If they actually recorded their conversation
What is The Voice
Give me a pencil
Google Play
That's one fat one possibility
Teenagers to murder four of those he was like
Not if he hit somebody with a hammer and then talk and then Little Star
Cars popped out little imaginary
Boring
If you see them doing a salt or something like that like if you see them through a crime
Oh you know
Kingpin
Who owns broker
It turns into a Looney Tune
I don't know
That
I got to stop to do that voice forever
I'm so now we get into some aliens what they're up to
What are they up to
He said the dracos are working with the Reptoid
Straightforward if you're the enemy and they want something or you're in the way
They deal with you more directly I like to know where they stand
He said the reptoids who are
Raptor hybrid
Are more nefarious but they are working together
He said the dracos are also working with
Undoubtedly
Attracts
Sure
That means the reptoids are all the Chinese
If the Raptors
Logically speaking they're all working
Right
Now
Here's the implication there though
Once you add human blood
Do something it becomes far less
Honest
Well you are near something
Will the argument is the Raptors are the good ones
Hangout
No but you're right once you put the human blood in their becomes a Reptoid
Play Rittz
Morningstar Church
I'd also like to save this is another point of similarity in these
These worlds Chinese are working with evil alien
And the Chinese are big villain
So
Cool
Now where you I halfway expect
Some point
Forever my crutches
To be like
Also did you know that the dracos vaginas are sideways
Alright
Joke
Although I would like that
To be the thing that's
Taking out if we ever get like big enough to be right wing troll
Are you going to take these down I want my voice
To be the one clip
2 taken out of context
Go for it
Nerva
Here's where that happened
It doesn't sound good
Minerva
He's aware of that and
In touch with her
Is the Futurama episode all over
In the solar system
Galaxy
She is specifically I guess
Somewhere
Alterra
Where she's in touch
In touch with
She's a
Huntress
Spacecraft
I choose as a life sentence in prison
Loved fries so much
You just disappeared
Minerva of course
Being immortal
But
There are a lot of other dogs out there
True how many of them were would be loyal and I will be filled with love
Enough
Fry's
Damn
This whole time
Tell other later on Joey find out that she breaks them out regularly
They still go joyriding
No I don't I don't know cuz I think that's all like astral travel
I think we speculated that if you have all this
You could break out of prison so I can do that
I think that was one of our
I'm through brains
But Minerva's in artificial intelligence
Or even if he did go visit her
They couldn't come
No because he's also biological
Biological artificial until
There's a crisis in the world
Refugees
I assume that not we're not talking about actual refugees were not talk about Syria we're talking about
About
Marc Marquez
Marcus V on map
You're the bleach take on this and I
I don't think
Okay
He said the first
Wave of Syrian refugees that you heard about
Of which there are around 2
He said
All the refugees there are because of
We rounded up and ended up on planet
Flavor food
By now
I don't know if
Better or worse than the reality
It's worse
You you
No it's worse but it's cowardly
Because what it is is I don't need to worry about that
We only need to worry about 200,000 pretending that the problem doesn't really
It's just like
Buy Raptors
Convenient on going crazy
Just that people are being right
Surviving
So I assume it's all been fixed
Binary translator
In the past all of these problems have been solved
Certainly not ongoing
Really
Pacific
Now we move onto Museum
The character want to
A little bit of information about it
Display she saw
We talked about the Anunnaki skeleton in London
I had seen this summer
I'm taking a photo of
He agrees that it wasn't
Disease and desist with probably inauthentic
Annunaki skeleton
Perfect
Healthy and
Good work
Westchester
Those f****** British
No no
But you know what
This is a very faint
Guy named Charles Burns
No
From 1761
To 1783
1 ft tall
The picture of the Carrie plays on the
Show you can find
The only reason
But this guy looks
Much bigger than
Is because they have it next to a smaller
So the perspective of it makes it look like he is like
It's forced perspective he's closer to the camera than the other Scout
Got everything is known about this guy like it's not like he's a mystery
History
Come from
People know about who yet
And one of the really sad things is that
So you made it very clear during his life that he died
If you wanted to be buried at
Do you want to be sent to the ocean
And
Against
His wishes
People have put him on display
Epic Museum
Honda place over the years people have
Bentley tried
To like start movement
To honor his wishes
Posthumously
And they've generally gotten like pretty good public support but somehow they've not
To this day not to follow through and actually sent him
Into the water
You wouldn't like
If you told him when he was dying we're totally going to bury you at Sea and he felt better and then he died
And then you showed a skeleton around
I'm fine with that
I don't really care he's terrible
That's a good point
Fair enough
In the world of Project Camelot
His venture
Probably not very happy
You've been on
I've turned into an Anunnaki people like every catheter coming in and taking stupid
Pictures of them putting the real world
If you if I was dying
And I was like my last wish
Is
Don't
Remove my feet
And then attach them to my skull
With
Screws where my ears War
Exactly
Then you just said to me
We will never do that
And then after I died you did that
I don't care
I'm already dead who gives a f*** I know that
You can't care
But I don't actually think it's
For the person
Who died I think it's for the
Communal Mental Health
I think it there's some sort of comfort
That we can get in terms of feeling like we are helping
Honor the wishes of the
That's why you have a wake
That's why you bury people it's bad for the dead person
For the community
To heal and come together and stuff like that
So the idea of you not wanting your feet
Need to be used in ears
Whatever dude I think you're in the clear their butt
I feel like that would make the community feel even better
My ear hole
That's about
Thanks
Don't care necessarily about your soul being if
When I screw your ears onto your
It's more about knowing that we are apart of
The grand
Write it something like that
It makes the people honoring the wish feel better
The value to that
I respect the position
I don't think that's anything mysterious or Ghostly
Just about
All of us feeling good as a community
You like to imagine that your wishes will be followed when your dad
Whatever some people will have feelings
Just because you don't doesn't mean that I should respect that position
Was going to say
Plus it also helps
The community,
Come to terms of mortality better
Because it's like I will want
One day I will be in the position of
This corpse
Respect in honoring
The living
Person who
The value to it
One day I will be in that position
And so far I have not
Any skeletons
Things with their feet
Screw into their skulls right
It constantly make me feel bad not
This is not healing the community at all this is her I don't follow the personal affront I don't follow
No pit stops
Tyga
Okay alright
Carrie's got something
You're asked me if I
Iceland have it's delightful You've Been to Spain
I've Never Been to Spain I want to go
This next clip makes me laugh
Place that things often disappear there
And it's one of those places on Earth without happen
He said
Basically that means there's some kind of dimensional
I think Mark
I think Marc Maron displaced something instead
Babies like goddamn everything
Something like that needs just trying to work
Everybody knows you lose one sock in the dryer from time to time
Spanx that's where they go
The best tourism advertisement
OSHA
Let's go see what this could be magical
Little bit of a shorter episode than usual
I think it's good for everybody
Especially awesome
But
Jordan
I think I solved the mystery of Mark
I hate to break
He isn't
Maybe not
What
I found one
I found one in this next clip I found
V1 way story
Checks out
Eric.
But
This
Quit giving me some sort of plausible deniability
I'm not certain
I answered
He said there yes
She says there are multiple realities alternative Earth
Parallel Earth
As well as multiple timeline
That he is aware
He says
Said he thinks perhaps
As far as this timeline that he may have actually landed in the wrong
Okay alright
That's the only way to Storyworks you know what I buy that 150
Because
On this Earth
You committed
If you aren't that guy
From this timeline where is that
Did you merge with that guy flying around with Minerva
And then they switched timeline
Schnauzer murderer Mike Richards
Is MBI
The secret space program guys timeline
And he's stuck here doing the time the greatest movie ever made
Because I don't believe anything he says I know that this is just like a really convenient way to get out of any
Kind of ink
Yeah
It's the next the next best way to tell the story
Disregarding
Mike Richards
Entirely
How do you feel about the most
I'm fine with it
Okay
That was an interesting Road
No I mean I don't know what
What are you what are you think
Like as far as as far as multiple universes
Is godtfred far as like
Principals go
Do you accept the premise
But there are multiple use they're almost
Timeline
And they are
Every
Make sauce
Branching paths
I don't know yeah I believe it but I don't think it is
Any utility to my life
You know like I don't think the travel between
Sing like that
I I would be willing to
Know what life
I'm sitting here with you and
It's very weird that we're in physical bodies
Able to speak
Light
Houses
A liquid that we need to stay alive
All of us have Curiosities the guide us
Through
Passions in life Hobbies
Career choices along with so many cultural tradition
Because they happened
Long before any of us were alive and Everett
So we value money
Adult
Just trying to gather up money in order to get resources
Seems like a really silly game
That we play but we do anyway
I'm looking at my hand I know to my hand is a part of my body
F***** up very weird
Multiverse
Very weird
Freedom help me
It also doesn't help me
Sit back and think about life
It doesn't know why the hell are we doing
Comforting it away though
No because why the hell are we doing this is a question that can only be answered with
Why the hell aren't we
Multiverse
Suggest to me
AAA
Kind of calvinist
But you're in your time
Decisions don't actually matter
Because all of your decision
Are already made
Number of all of this
So it's comforting to know that
Regardless of what it is you
You choose to do or are doing
It has already been done and decided
And there's no reason to worry about
That doesn't comfort me it also doesn't
Freak me out or make
Nervous I would say
Because I don't need that to get me to why the hell not do so
Okay
You know I don't need I don't need to work around
Forget myself
Inspired to
No I don't know man
A lot of that abstract
Hypothetical stuff
I'm willing to believe any of it is
True
But I I just don't
Like I don't know I I imagine
Ballymena give me an application where I could use it in my life
Gladly say it matters
Alright
Here you are
You're at the grocery
You are looking
At fault
What cereal do
Depends on the mood I'm in.
Get out of here
Maybe Applejack
What
Applejack
You know what I thought about Applejack
Cheerios
Yeah
Honey Nut
I'm just saying that it's comforting to know that in reality
You have in fact
Chosen to eat all of those
No
I can't do that with a very clean
No fair enough because I am an actual fact
I haven't
So it's not comfort me at all
In actual fact
You have
It's only in your reality that you
Right
I don't identify with
Myself
Another timeline
I feel like it only reinforces my belief that I am eating the cereal that I chose to know that
All of me has chosen all of these cereals
Petros in the cereals
Right here's what I would say to that
So there's a guy in Bangladesh
Never met
You have never met
Then we'll call him Kevin for the sake of argument
This guy is a stranger
Do you feel any interested material
Will you ask the question your care at all he is a complete
Well here's the thing
And then you no longer
You can find out what cereals
In the same way the mummies in different timeline
Complete strangers to me I've never met these all right
It means nothing if you are a listener
Named Kevin
Please call him
Neon
Let me know what f****** cereal eat
Because I am
Probably Lucky Charms
They're not allowed
Lucky Charms and
Freeze-dried marshmallows
All of this stuff
All right maybe I'm close minded but I just don't see
I don't see what good there is other than fun things to
And I'm not against
Because they're only funds
I think about like to think about Atlantis
But I think it lies you just choose
Things that you
What to think about that are outside of the realm of
Proving or outside the realm of
Be meaningful whatever resume
You go ahead and think
About that only becomes a problem when you try and force it on other people react
Actually
Concrete
You actually just undercut by saying that there's no possible way I could be
In what Kevin
Is
Do you ask
I did become interested or you going to serial Kevin from Bangladesh
What timing Kevin
Is living in Bangladesh
I don't know his story
What cereals are available
I don't know
Is very frustrating
And here's why
You have every right
I really not trying to just rile you up
I'm genuinely now interested no you're not never ask me the questions you would never ask
Are you interested
I would not be
Agree with your brothers I do as long as I don't
Think about it
You are not
Just to rile you up I promise you
I believe that you don't care about cereal consumption in Bangladesh
If anybody can find on that please
Send it our way
So Jordan to get some of his
Possible question
Answer to this
Change your life at all
Like
Not like
It doesn't matter
So even if
If you are kind
Curious about it all it is
Bangladesh
It doesn't mean anything towards like you and Kevin becoming closer
Not just that
It would almost certainly be disappointed
Undoubtedly it would be the greatest
Would be knowing what cereal
No not
Disappointment to find out
The mystery is what I'm a
And maybe that's why Multiverse stuff is really
Mystery that will never really
Crack into almost like
We never will
Well there's only one way to
We got to get markers out of prison
Know that
The proposed this scenario of the
Conclusion to the
Cat in the Box
You know the 50
Is to sit in the chair and
I have a gun with
And
Pull the trigger
Again and again and again
And if you continue surviving
You can prove yourself
That there is an
There is
No possibility
That you are not
Just existing in whatever Universe where you
You don't.
I know but that's because the only person you can prove it to is you put no You couldn't even to yourself
Because there's other rational explanation for why they didn't maybe the gun is jammed maybe there is a
Some sort of a failure in the mechanism of the gun
There's all kinds of other things
Could come into play
It's not like lost where you can't kill yourself
Right
It's alright for you I can see that
Knowledge buy.com
That's where we
Where We Are
Ross on Twitter
We are also
We are on Facebook
Bucking join the group
Later in the week with the Alex Jones episode
Summit Project Camelot
If you didn't like this episode
We talked about Alex Jones a whole f******
2.2 Project Camelot world is getting a little thin
Dig much deeper than I expected side stuff
Any good
She is not bringing the
Yeah we kind of hit like
We had an embarrassment of riches
Going to be first showed up
A little bit
I hope there's better
To be found
But for now I'm not sure
Sure there are
Someday
Nobody was my turn last
All we got this the prom with this episode and I got it we have few character
I got it
So I would like to see
There's only one person
Richard
You're very creative man
And I'm not going to
Begrudging
For murder you can buy
Terry
You get the Alex Jones
The show you didn't say any
Weirdly race
This time around
I would like to say
Allen Dulles
Returning on the Dutchman
Pam the Dutchman's little baby boy all because they supported
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color