Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
And talk a little bit about Alex Jones
If you could
Could fight
What would it be
Any animal I can tell you what I would
Okay
That's my least favorite animal
Annabelle probably be
Hydro something soft
No
Something
I know but I got a lot of body you could work
That's true I don't think
Generally
I don't know people swim around with them
Lettuce all the time as a vacation destination
That's true
You want to go with a man it would pain me to do it
Image for Glory
I want to make it out the other side looking for survival
Deadly
Alright what are we doing a lot about Alex Jones
Just about what I tell you! Bit more because he's in there
These days it's hard to escape
Things I would like to
To do is give a shout out to a new donor
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
Sprite.com
Sports show
That little button
We would appreciate it
You better bring me something else
Voicemails in the near future
You're going on vacation
This weekend to recording a little bit earlier than you
Going on a little trip
Our schedule is a little bit
Some computer issues
Look into the mailbag
Messenger
Will get back to him in Minneapolis maybe we'll do that at some point
Get through some of them we've gotten a ton
They aren't from Chico
Okay
I did get a request by someone who is
Gentleman
To visit us here in Chicago
Had a nice drink with him
User instrumental
And helping us set up for the show in Austin Texas
Just the other day this is a special congratulations
Him and his
Company
Qo
I will start up
Use that working in
Working on
I just got awarded a $100,000 Grant to put to their
OG ideas
Emotionally I am
Talk about this
Think about like Rico
Claiming my Waters
Would be giving out Trade Secrets
That's exactly
What I do remember from talking to his really cool idea and something
I could be very helpful
In conservation
I went there
The world
Whenever we talked about it I thought it was great IUI
What asterisk whatever you said
Right after like he got
I feel really bad about that
I swear to God I thought you're going to be like
They shouldn't have given him that money he told me about the idea
Terrible I don't know what people are doing
Congratulations
After John and Doug
And also
That's really cool the way they
Tell your mother your brother
And the way that to everybody's
Congratulate
It feels really good
We don't have a bunch of s*** head
Thank you all for being there and I we all
Support each other as best we can
Believe it
Oh boy we're back into
An interesting episode
Who's going to be there's going to be some
Nonlinear storytelling going on inside
No no hot tubs
Before we go
Text drop
Today's episode
Wall Street money never sleeps
That was Alex asking somebody
Is expecting the answer to be terrible
It's doing pretty well
We're still not quite going to get to
The actual emergence of the Tea Party
But it's interesting
Guisi
A couple of pieces that are very relevant
Alex is mine
Before
The ship goes down
As it were
The world or anything like that
What about
Alex
Is very concerned
We're going to start here on February
Oki 45678 stacks
I could spend the entire show on any one of these
How do you stories yourself
That's why we exist
News
And any one of them could last the entire show
I'm not going to be
Everything that I say right now but let me tell you something
Journalist
Congratulations
So a lot of the time
We're going to
To be looking at this
People very afraid
Britches
Iran
Although we just talked about spiders for a few hours
But
He has more info
Institutional
A for you to chew on
On the 1st
Before we're pretty mad about airport scanners
Body scanner
Baby taking naked pictures of your body
Slightly different take on it which I didn't know is part of
Here's another one they're announcing all over the country and USA Today they're putting in body scanners
Were you walking scans your
Naked body and puts it in
Izzy's airport scanners
I have your body
What instant ID
What's a body
Digital algorithm
Google algorithm
They were great in the 80s
Hit song
I don't know about that
I don't think.
Harvesting
Body digital algorithm
Street cameras
But if they were
Technology
The idea that every single Street camera history
Hooked up
Massive database of every
Body digital algorithm
The only way in fact that you could keep that information
Synthesizer
Is if you build an artificial intelligence that can do it even faster than you and now you have an AI that has every single
A person who can afford to fly because that's all that really matters
It will eventually
Controlla using Airport
And again only people who can afford to fly
Black Knight Meredith
Satellite map of the Earth
I don't know
That's also one of the strange things about those skaters is that they were all connected by one gif
Message
I had a lot.
To look up on the
This episode this one I punted on a little bit because just like
He doesn't explain what he's talking about
I like I don't care
I don't just doesn't seem
We get to this next
Clip where Alex
What the
Is all about
I like you too
To try and
Can parse out any
Okay so I need to figure out what the system
Okay
The system is
To go after good
Hard-working Americans
Famous cases
And I never saw it and it called the animal
People went to jail
Again
This is all about getting regular
Citizens in the net
This is all about capturing regular citizens
Because we're the ones that have money they can suck off
99%
I'll cover when I get back I'm up
Not that I'm aware of
If you do get back to it you phrased it so differently
I love that
That's so good if you're going out to break with that
And the bolts and never come back to it
Before
You were writing some notes
Explain what you think I'm going to say before I understand
If I understand
Him correctly
Right this instant
The system is going after real hard-working Americans
Because
What you notes later on
Exactly like how remember when that guy murdered rats who ate his potato tomatoes
Neighbors called the cops on him
Eddie went to jail
Right right
And then
99%
But you just broken down
Get the play-by-play which is
Inappropriate
What Alex is talking about is what we here
From him so often I believe
Depicting a scenario that is happening
Underclass
Franchise group
Can Americans in
Particular okay threatening that this is what the globalist want to
To do to wifey
Wright's the good hard-working people
Good American
He's using coded language in order to depict the
Nightmare scenario wherein
Using real-world
Stuff and turning it into a faint
You fear for his
Privileged audien
I do I think we heard you killing rats with a shovel
And then his neighbors called the cops on them
Maybe it was their pet rat
Maybe he was out in the middle of the night murdering rats with a shovel
If I look out my neighbor's window
And I just see a dark silhouette with a shovel smashing it on the ground
I thought the system
That's a terrible
Go to prison
Just for being weird
By killing rats on your own property is legal that's not like
Restaurant
I don't think so
What about those big rats
What the ones down in Lake the Bayou
What about the ones in Australia
Those really big ones
I don't know much about wildlife
That's not what this podcast
2009 where we know that Alex
This is about to launch off on
On a major
New adventure
Where he joins up with a p
Tea Party
Believes himself to be
More like
He's going to fold in all his Ron Paul beliefs
Into
Party
The different direction
He's been on already
I received these narratives
From
What we've covered already
With the pro-palestinian
Neutrality
Anti-police sentiment
These sorts of things are going
To continue into the future
The ship and the only other Masters
Do shift that we've ever seen
Alex Jones
Is the switch
And as we covered all of that
In 2050
There's one piece of it
And that is what
Everything
You clearly tell was guiding Alex and motivating
To make that switch
Was he was being
Popularity
His numbers were through the roof
Now what
Would it surprise you
You to find out
Today's numbers were exploding
Right before the tea
Tea party bro
Program directors Nivens
The doctor seemed very big radio consultants in contacting me famous people
Time people want you to be the number one show in the country but obviously the big corporations that own the biggest
Parking let you on the air
I bet they tell me that
Radio
Evenly probable executive her scared and know that there
Know that their time is number
Notice
Know that America is.
No that is anti New World Order anti-global espresso America
And that
Basically
Exploding
I'm just one small part of this
Everything
Hyperbolic right now it is exploding
Good to hear from you my friend
Does he literally Mimi he is
Over exaggerate
Exaggerated
Exponential
I would I would say
It's very clear from everything
Astro purse
Yeah there was automated
Bots that were over inflating traffic
Look at
Primary
Entirely bankrolled by Americans
Prosperity
Yep freedomworks Koch brothers Foundation
Stoked by Fox News
It was also an artificial
The Alex's numbers jumping
Again
It really hard not to
The Koch brothers bought you
Traffic
Yeah
They might be bothering you up already
I can't can't see that for sure
To be like if I were Alex Jones
Ever saw an increase in traffic
Doesn't have conspiracy theories about mainly because he attributed to
How great his own
Yeah so I don't know its interests
Like what kind of language
Normally like there's no way that happened Brothers villains in like real life
If we were like political strategy
Any stripe and we were trying to get Alex Jones
To bend to our will it would only take a couple of episodes
Really soft
What he's about
His own
If you were
Like someone who is working
Sing for the Koch brothers in
Strategy
And you wanted to flip Alex Jones
It would be incredibly easy
To just
Stroke the ego
And then I don't know have some
Functionary
Die with
Like Rodger Stone
Behavior salesman and then you have the artists
Growth in order to butter up his ego makeup feel on top of the world
Spokesperson salesperson come in
And double down on that
Maybe the meetings but he's taking with these high-end people saying his time has come
People are the people who are working
In concert with
False growth
Listen let me tell you something
How great
This is
Hold on
What do I got to do
What do you want
I need to be bigger
Alright you got it
You got it
$17,000
Also this is a used car
Oh
You know I'm picking my car
I'm going to get drunk and talk about it on there
I think at this point
It's still just a sore
Spitballing
There's no real
But that's what happened
Parallels of
We heard him talking about the airport
Is this
Describes a paranoid
Going to be patrolling North Dakota
They have
High-altitude blimps at 100,000 ft in Canada that us and England
Weather
They know your biometric residence just by the way your body move
Went from a shoot-down position from above
Resonance
Involved
I think
You can change your gate
Auras
It seems like he must but you must think it's
Some sort of AC
You know it's like
Snowman
Grease pencil
Beers like no matter where you are
You're one second away from this blimp shooting
You dead because of the way you walk in
And because they've scanned you innocent
System
You're never safe
Why would you be very unpleasant place to put your body
Did you read the
New York Magazine's headline
Trolls Park
Alien verse
Predator
The right
With
Predator
I don't know what year that was
The movie theater
But that doesn't help
Whataburger
Movie theaters
Biography of me
This episode little bit longer
Ultimately pointless
But I wanted to keep it in
Because
This is this is still indicative of Alex
Trying to have fun
Which is sorely missed
Humor
The royalty of Europe in what's scum they are and how low they think the public
Pretty funny
I shouldn't even get into it
The Queen of England
They claim a stops at 1901
If you Google it it's mainstream
The office last night didn't believe it
When I told him so they Googled it
And
My wife feel about it because she was also a history minor when she went to school
France
So she learned about the
Used Range Rover
I was just joking around during the break with the guys but it's just that are such, ladies and gentlemen
But you can't even
You can't even imagine
How did the
I'm not going to get into it maybe later this week when I have time to cover it
Break it down
Common one of the
Headache official nose picker
Hand and I'm serious who were they
Royalty
Has a toilet attendant and I'm just going to leave it
At that let's just say they don't touch toilet paper
Taken care of by somebody else
It's called the groom of the stool
30 go
Absolutely
That job have benefits
Oh man
Ridiculous
Because the groomers
The stool was a real position
But it was always held by like
Noble Team
Because it wasn't
Like about wiping
It was a
Super close adviser that would sit with him in the bathroom
And they would have liked meeting
Because back then
Being there half an hour
We're not great
Position where
Acceptably High standing
Close
Confidant
Don't know that make sense
Deeply trusted by the
Part of it is
If there's
You know there's an outside
Maybe there was some ass with all depends on what you're into
The office
Exclusively want
Serve male monarch
Elizabeth
The first and 50
58 it was replaced by a kazoo
Amanda
The position was neutralized
Year later
Queen Elizabeth
Is it worth
Well it did
Steward of transitioning
You just an advisor
Position but then when Edwards
Power
Alex mentioned that official
Became the prime
The lineage of these people it's like it was a public office
But it wasn't
You know so the list of all of the people who have held that position is available
The history isn't like something they
And they're all
Cool
I would love to
30 great from 8
12 Georges
9th orlova
The Gremlins
I thought he was dead
Oh no no no
Whatever
Marquis
But that is
That's where we come to the end of February 20th
To have them sit in a room while you sure
Blood because
He's very
A very vulnerable position
That's why it's always Duke
So we going to the toy
8/3
And job
That's just a fun fact
Always fun to learn
Hundreds were we
Is it going to take all day
So that we had to
23rd
Straubenzee
Very
I want to make
You scared narrative
Would local police
Michigan
Home store
Those are two very different subjects today
So even more f***** up is he
Not
Holy Alliance
He is lying a bit but
He's not like this event
Did happen
Describing it is
Sweetly off
Turn off of it
2004 article in the washing
Thrown by Reverend Sun Myung Moon
The article was written by Michelle
And so that is Stryker running to
Was not as subversive
Attempt to make
Homeschoolers
Poorly-written preparedness drill
The students involved volunteer
Most of them were members of the drama classes
There's School in folders after me
Makeup like they had blood makeup and squibs
False Flags
Crisis actors
This is the one time where the false flag
What's the weather
No
The kids were high schooler's there weren't children involved no bus
Blew up because the homeschool movement
In America
Is super defensive
Crazy and f***** up and they should not be allowed
Is actually why they're super
Because people have that position
I don't think all homeschooling is really all that bad
I think a lot of
Fundamental
Homeschooling a lot of their religious
I think that can be fairly Danger
Homeschooling is based on like
Be asleep
Yeah
Involve some sort of
The community
Involvement
You know like
Where you go out in
Have
Socializing groups in
I think I can
Be very damaging
But just the idea of not wanting
Go to public school
I think that there is there is an argument you can make that it's not based on bulshit
Homeschooling is bad
It is possible for kids who are homeschooled
But
Motels
Is brainwashing
Homeschool
There is a nun
Unfortunate amount of
I would say
So the other thing
Really funny
I lost the
OK Google I lost the Exacta article of it but it's
The guy who ended up writing
The drill was like I wasn't
To make anyone hate together it is what I came up with
What look
The group that you came up to be the villains of the
Rocco's
I think this is a great roleplay right now
This is a dmj D&D I love it
It's a little selves against education
Like
Taken poorly
I get what you're trying to do in terms of
Planning preparedness
X
You guys really should have done the second
Second breath on this gift
Back to the drawing board
Punch up yeah for sure
I don't remember his name it's not really important
This is just a low-level intern guy most likely
But all of the responses that
You can find
From homeschooling
I'm not going to come down on them
Two Harbors
Because I would much rather come
Come down on them
For being like
Muslim group
Why wasn't it a Muslim terrorist group that was the bad guys in
How come you were making
The reason
It was in Buskey
County in
In Michigan
Muslims
Under one
Percent
Muslim or Arabic it anyway it's a
Kylie White
The population
I'm out of place
Michigan does have one of the highest
Muslim like Community or one of the largest Muslim
But there are definitely aware that everyone
They are in the Muskegon County in order to avoid the other
2009 episode
We covered
A b a g
Was that
An interview that Alex has with
The member of the Iowa National
Alex's big narrative
He's pushing around this time
Is that there is this
Arcadia Iowa
Weather
Do this drill
Where
Houses with v
Tear to go along with the roleplay
Well they try
Define Vista
Arm dealer
Who's them
Prepare them for
To talk about it
Because I'm the 20
Alex Jones says this about that and
You know what what's going on
Hapgood
Friday
I was really interrogating
Okay
Love's
I started cracking up I was so much
And that's why you begin
Start the Republic
And that's why this is going to fail ladies and gentlemen
So when I heard that I was like
Bucking dare you how dare you Alex
Look Every Good Boy Deserves
Fudge
So I don't know about that I'll leave that to the I will say first of all
Near crying
No I remember we listened to it we didn't listen to
Good enough for me to just
Assert
That he didn't cry
I must play this for you
Illustrate
Exactly
Happened
You didn't cry
He was a
YMCA
White guy
Who stayed there for over 20 minutes while Alex badgered him
Total dictum
2 questions
To the best of his ability
And then Alex
Piece of s***
Actually important
Because I want to illustrate
How much of a liar Alex
America
2 something
There's a big piece
Did I need to go
Exhaustive
And I am but apologizing
Okay alright but here is where Alex
Starts to
Back to the 20
Flashing back to February 20th
When Alex had
Colonel Greg hopgood
He's already done before
Adduction
Start leading
Hopgood hapgood down
Are you aware that there's now a massive domestic roles
Regular Army National Guard
But I think you have to look historically is that domestic role really has been filled by the National Guard across
United States
A decade
And I will wear no different Princeton
Summer we had this incredibly historic flood
Here in the state the number one response
Force for many military is always the National Guard in their home state
More than 4,000 people last summer to fight bludgeon Iowa
That being said if there are other kinds of
Response necessary in the state and chip for the responses that we really have to do with
Are most the time natural disasters
Other disasters let's say some kind of weapons of mass destruction or some other kind of instant
I would be also called upon to do that so it's so I do have some visibility on that Duty as well
Colonel
Firearms unknown
With respect to any kind of Duty that we perform in Iowa it's kinda depends on on which
Battleships in about who we take orders from number one
If it is in peacetime situation
The vast majority of the time any
Kind of a request for assistance
Comes from the governor of the state of Iowa I can tell you that the order of which you just spoke
I have never been
Received by the Iowa National Guard
And I can tell you that you will not find stronger
Defenders of the Constitution's in a minimum of the Iowa National Guard
So if that sounds
IQ
Colonel
Kill the Jedi and more importantly the young links
I mean it's not far off
Do you know what he's
Where he's going with his
Badgering questions
So
Because
It would be unfair with me
Me to cherry-pick
Well that's the one part where you wasn't crying
He's on the edge of telling Alex every
It was hit the governor he almost even said it he said if the governor ordered us to take everybody's guns away
Obviously we
The tution
Andy doesn't mean anything and we're destroying it and we're taking
Heathens
You didn't hear that part
Did you hear the part about how great his grandfather was cuz then we can
Rivers engineer everything after
My granddad
No
Who is Meredith
And be like yeah right
I'm in the guard for 23 years and I've never heard of that
I remember the Iowa National Guard
1986's 1991 I do not recall
Evergreen infatuation
Marine
Please don't put me in the camp
I'm certainly aware that absolutely but I think you have to look at the role the National Guard's historically
Is that historically we are used in States
4 disasters overwhelmingly
And our job is to number-one you ready
Our mission
Federally which has to go to war and number two is to help our fellow Citizens United States of America
Farpoint rain for
The army war College
And directives on engagement with the American people under northcom
They were talking about
Remember that the National Guard 99% of the time is
Peacetime
Belongs to the state in which they are located
Only on occasion to become federalized one of those examples of courses being mobilized and deployed
About to go to war peacekeeping other kinds of federalized mission
But other than that the National Guard generally in peacetime belongs to the governor of that
Absolutely absolutely
Hair looks
Cry
He's throwing out the best
Calmly and politely
Responding
Important information
Terms of being at
The will of the governor of the state that they're operating
Almost all the
Batman they become
Federer live
Stuff like that
So the idea that their Federal
Relyance Bank
Of what they do
Even when they go into another
Ford like
Natural disaster relief
Stuff like that
Like let's say the Iowa National Guard ends up
Illinois
Is of the Illinois gov
They're being
To the state of Illinois
Respond or they
The chain of command
Illinois
Okay
So good
Answers for Alex
To calmly
Deflect his narrative
Well here's the real situation I understand what you're
It's not working
And it leads to Alex getting
What I would describe as
Breakdown of society riding right now
I mean what I can tell you is only what we do here in Iowa that's be prepared to go to war to prepare to help people here
United States
Those are the things that we do
Louisiana Mississippi
We haven't we haven't been asked to do that in the state of Iowa and history of our state we've been around 470 year
Militia
And like I said we uphold the Constitution advocate for the Constitution
Everyday and what we do and what I can change
70 years
The point I'm trying to make as you've tried it out to pray the horrible
Of which I can't possibly comment
All I can tell you about is what we do here in Iowa to get ready That's the pistol I'ma talk to you about
Appreciate
Because we're educated
I'm interrogating
Showing a little bit of his ass off to underbelly there
Because when
Hamptons like there's your bring it up there's no f****** way I could comment on Facebook
First of all probably I don't know about like other states
And then beyond items everything that's like
Something I wasn't involved
Hang up on me
I still got it
Which is this occurred would you take the aliens gun
Would you protect their second amendment rights
Text blaster
So now we get to
What
I think everybody
Every Space movie
Alright I'm sorry I'm sorry
So now Alex Quest
And then we will get
To a lot of information that I have
Clearly illustrates
Alex
Big dumb dumb
Germany or Russia
The military
Be like Italy or Japan
Again I can just tell you what I see here in front of me everyday
I seen 9,500 men and women that are committed to Liberty
Better Community United States of America
State of Iowa doing they can do
Temperature people that's what I can tell you about
Lieutenant Colonel guard trips to New Orleans
Yes we did
In fact I was there myself as well
We did send approximately 400
Catrin Mississippi and some that were also in New Orleans as well
We did not take part in any of those kinds of operation
Did you witness it
Did not
Mercenaries were also used from Israel
No formation about that
No information
Formation
Didn't personally see it
About stuff
Best
Probably his best Salvo which is
You guys work
Katrina Katrina relief
Did you take part in the gun down
We need to talk about that now there's a lot of writing
And reading
About guns and Hurricane Katrina because
Is a liar
The story of
Publicly out there and
It would do with all a good bit
2 RS
To understand the Dynamics
The idea that there was gun confiscation
After Hurricane Katrina is not based in reality
That was created by the NRA along with the Second Amendment
Dissociation
They were trying to create this image
Control Federal power taking advantage of
Horrible tragedy
In order to grab people's gun
But the truth is
More complicated than that
But their reasons for doing so are not
The NRA propaganda is largely propped up by an unfortunate quote from New Orleans
Police Department superintendent Edwin compass
The third who said quote law enforcement are allowed to have weapons
After struggling to retain a state of calm
In a city that was
Under percent underwater
Plagued by looting
And mismanaged efforts to help survive
He was a clumsy
Dumb thing to say you can understand his mental state
Either way he was no longer New Orleans Police Department superintendent a few weeks later he was relieved of Duty
No just because of his bungling and
I didn't look too deeply into his leaving office but I believe
Steps down
I think it was like a
Either way
A marine veteran in New Orleans police Reserve officer
The Katrina is going on record
There was not widespread gun
New Orleans
It was nowhere near as widespread as some would have you believe
I know I am count
Countless people with firearms in
Did not,
Single one
Neither did any officer I knew or work
The only time Firearms were seized
I wear when someone
War crime
No different than before the ring
He even goes on to say that he and other officers
Specific Instructions
Not
Take anyone's firearm
Alright
That is
Pretty concrete
Experience you know you can extrapolate
Whatever you'd like to
Because there ain't
Piles of shih tzu only care about gun
Glommed onto a couple incident
There were a bit unfortunate
Example an older lady
He was waving a gun around in front of officers were trying
Persuade
Leave her outside she end up getting
She doesn't just have a gun out and then her old lady status
Revoke it's not like waving around
Threateningly necessarily but even if
Nonviolent
I believe that the legal definition of Brandy
Finishing is EOTech
Finger on the trigger Zone
Something like that I don't care to litigate
Even her telling of it is like I have done in my head then I got back up
There is a clear cause-and-effect relationship there that makes that but
NRA
Like this
I'm a pseudonym
Police
Very closely after already to the rescue
Department revealed they take
Gun into their headquarters between August 23rd
Hey December 31st
According to police
These were mostly
Stolen guns
Confiscated
The terms of the settlement made it to the New Orleans
I have to do everything in their power to let people know
That they can come and get their gun
That was it none of this should have happened to begin with
Quotes in April 2006 police Firearms available to owners
Hard to claim if they could present a bill of sale
Weapon serial number
Which of course
Difficult
How does a person who's
House flooded provide proof of ownership of a gun probably was destroyed in the flood
What do you do if your
Do you just give guns to anyone claiming to be their owner
Basically the NRA's lawsuit in the settlement of lead to the resolute
The people would jump
Have to sign an affidavit that a certain gone was there's a
And then it was
So there are a few stories that exist out there in The Ether about people having their guns taken away from them
Aftermath of Katrina stories
Clearly involved
People talking about run-ins with in New Orleans
Police Department
Not with some sort of National Guard
It's been federalized
Or out-of-state forces of the government
And it was all over
Note every single person who had their guns taken away
Old lady
Now but we will get you one commonality but
Between them a little bit
Apple notes
They were running
To the New Orleans Police
Is because
Did investigation
Police department has a long history of stealing
People's guns
The traffic stop
Gordon Hutchinson writing for the Louisiana Sportsman
Said quote in the course of research
Search for AR book
On the confiscation of firearms in the aftermath of the hurricane
We heard a number of similar stories
They all follow the same thing
A citizen is pulled over in a traffic
Stop the New Orleans Police Department
There takes a gun from the city
An extra citizen if they have a receipt for the gun
When the answer is no the gun is seized and the citizen is informed
If they will show up
Precinct with proof of ownership they can have the gun back
When I asked a good friend to retired New Orleans Police Department Officer about the practice
He stated that it was a fairly common practice
To take on for motorist
Before the hurricane
This Is An Open Secret in New Orleans community
And if zero to do with hurricane
Katrina
Federal Officer
Or the National Guard
It was the behavior of an underfunded understaffed
Undertrained
Structural
The Department of Justice did investigation into New Orleans Police
I found it to be
Complete map
The kneaded essentially a
We overhauled
From their 158 page report
The deficiencies are in the way than world
Police Department police
This is the city are not simply individual but structural as well
For too long the department has been largely indifferent to widespread violations
It's officer
New Orleans Police Department does not have in place
The basic system
Don't improve Public Safety and
Constitutional practices
And promote public kompa
We found it
Deficiencies that lead to constitutional violation
Spam the operations
The entire department
From how officers are recruited trained supervised and held accountable to the operations
The paid detail
And the apps
The mechanisms
To protect and promote civil rights
Officers too frequently uses
Excessive force
And conducting illegal stop searches and arrest
Impunity
That was that was like in that documentary Bad Lieutenant Port of Call New Orleans
Nicolas Cage New Orleans cop for a while
So are they
Stealing guns to use
Like to issue to each other
Like it because the standard issue gun there no
It's like that kind of like old police cars
Power Trip
Incorruptibles
They're f****** crazy could be just also to you legally collect
Sure weapons
Portland Police Department has been doing that
Civil forfeiture
It's yours you can have it back that was guns for years
Isn't something that happened in hurricane
Caprina it was a problem for a long time
No this is a systemic problem within the
Department that was left on check for a long
To the NRA
Don't care about that
They only care about their imagine fantasies of out-of-control federal troops using
Disaster to take gone
And very
The people in the NRA's video with their guns
Taken by the police
Are all white
Fresno Police Department generally showed
Absurd bias towards targeting African-Americans
Racial disparities in arrest of American
Virtually all categories
We particularly dramatic disparity for Africa
Can Americans under the age of seven
Are provided by the New Orleans
Apartment
Did 500 African-American males
+ 8
White males
Under the age of seven
A serious offence larceny over $50.
65 a
Working American females and one white
Female in the same age
God damn even if you adjust for population differ
You're being arrested at a rate of approximately
Compared to whites
Goddamn also notable quote of the 27 in
January 2009 and may 2010
Officers intentionally discharge their firearms at
People all 27 of the subjects
Deadly force
Where African America
So it's very clear if you look at the pattern of the department
What was going on for a long time they were stealing guns from black people and don't care cuz they had no social power
USA
The officers taking guns in New Orleans weren't federal troops
Cops that have been taken
People's guns in New Orleans forever
Alex in this community make this such
Does the classic instance of white people receiving the treatment
The minorities were
Subjected to all the time
Also sorry their guns were taken away but also 1800 or so people died in that storm
6 days after Hurricane Katrina
Katrina struck New Orleans
Farmer killed
Two civilians
Seventeen-year-old James
Percent and forty-year-old Ronald Maddison
Four other civilians were wounded
All of the victims were African-American none were armed
Ignore had committed any crime
Madison a mentally disabled man was shot in the back
There's bigger issues to talk about than a couple people who had their guns take
In the same way that
Triage
Absolutely the smallest bill
So
I think I really need to
Winning
You strip some of the horrors away from it with a very difficult to do
Is it not
Nothing to do with
Federal troops coming in or National Guard troops
It's Deep by product of a years
Deficient
Police Department
No one has stepped in to get into line Orchard
Problems
They're behaving in the exact
Before the storm
And Alex is using it
Sort of like
This is what happens when the federal government comes in
No sir
This is City
This is state-level stuff
You are very wrong about that
If you want to get right with your narrative
Then you have to
To get right with all of the
You have to get right with the fact that this is a department that was running
I'm walking without hacking
Control now the further thing that Alex needs
To get right about
Is this
Because there was such an outcry by the NRA
Group
About this
Ended up pushing through a new code us code title 42 chapter
68 subchapter 5
AR code 5207
Which reads
Prohibition of confer
Gestation of firearm
No officer or employee of the United States
Including any member of the uniformed service
Or person operating pursuant to or under color of federal law
Federal funds
Or under
Control of any federal official
Providing services to such an employee officer or other person
Supportive release
From a major disaster or emergency and they won
Temporarily or permanently seized or authorized
Seizure of any firearm
The possession of which is not prohibited under federal state or local law
Federal law or as evidence
In a criminal investigation
They may not require registration of any firearm
For which registration is not required by federal state or local law
The only limitation
Is it nothing in the sex
Chinchilla be construed
Any person
From requiring the temporary surrender of a firearm as a
Condition
For entry into a motor
Interpretation
Rescue or evacuation
During a major disaster or emergency
Provided that such
Search temporary surrendered
Byron has returned to Ithaca
Completion
Said Rescuers activation
Hulk is like
You will get to keep your gun no matter the f*** won unless you're in an ambulance
That's not good that's that might be a little overcorrecting
Jordan
2009 listings
Alex
Fear about the idea that the federal government is going to use disasters
After Hurricane
Because the NRA propaganda
And what they were doing
The federal government made a code
Can't do that
You can't take guns
From anybody
At no Federal Officer working at
Capacity
Can take
Done during an emergency
Free because of the emerging
It's right there in the federal code
Alex Jones is going to use a federal code that he rattles off
That's Justice real you dickweed
That's the same Federal code to they can't
You can't do it
Now the other thing I want to bring this up because it's one of the sort of like
I believe that I think I've covered a lot of
Why this narrative is b*******
One more
Decent
And that is
Is that one of them
Millions
Things that people
In the government got wrong about
But what
Incredibly on 4th
I think
Because it leads
Is that the evacuation was
Evacuate
Yeah and one of the reasons for that is
Is because of the
The fact that 80% of
Underwater
The fact that people were talking about how there was going to be
Thousands
The Dead
Found in the water
And that
It was being had
With straight
Somber faced
Very credible
You know what it was
I don't know how we don't have a death toll that
Yeah
You have that service
Situation
The possibility for
Chemicals
Dead bodies rotting water
Stewie
Massive Public Health crisis
You need to clear your things out
Yes we had a mandatory
I think Mike
Have been
Not helpful necessarily the reason for it.
Another reason too big
Problem
Is because there aren't any
Concealed carry laws
Indoor
So if people are evacuating their homes
If they bring their guns with them
By virtue of them being out
Public with his gun
That is now an illegal gun
I think that
Some of these cops were already doing to motorist
Before the storm
Entrapment
To take some
Yeah
I don't like I said
People's guns without cause
B
Just say it was about the storm
National Guard federal troops
Is missing the forest for the trees in terms of
The story
And that's all I have.
Alex is not afraid of government overreach because he's only really afraid
Date of government overreach
Before they come to treating white people the way that we always treat
Tattoo
If you can't
Claims that it
Such a thrill
What we do
To minorities
Is wrong
Because if it happen
In even the slightest capacity
I will lose my f****** my
You're so mean
You are
Fine with this level of Mystery
If it happens to anyone who looks like me and I
I feel bonded with
Then I will create an entire world government
In order to jump
Spotify White
Is wrong
When I don't give a s*** if it's
Anaheim
Stealing this
Every
Phasers
Every black
Person
Every Muslim person
Everyone who is 91
Registers
Advise a gun
And the NRA will explode like an overinflated balloon
Royal Star Trek rules
They didn't you know they don't
I just didn't like the
Might you know what else they might take care of themselves
Stories about how they're not make
The fold
S*** like that
Edward are still probably about Evergreen Drive
Yeah that's
I've said my piece about Hurricane Katrina I don't think I've covered all of the bases
Irrelevant
To Alex's narrative
He's a liar
I think we have a pretty good job
Christ but now we get back to this interview with Greg hapgood
Who I actually looked into him
I don't know it's boring
Except the articles that I was able to find actually
Retired this year
Hurricane Harvey
And now I'm Houston
From the Iowa
National Guard out to help with the hurricane Maria
Out in Puerto Rico
He's been doing this forever
I don't know that
Just hit of his narrative
BisMan
Clinch
Martial law
Images
Anna population
All I can tell you is what our intent is in our antennas provide prepared soldiers so they're ready to go
When it comes time for time for them to go someplace very dangerous
For them to not only do the mission successfully
Survive and come home and their families those are the things that we doing what we see
That's a different place we're talking about Iowa here another one
I was just trying to move the goalposts and talk about
Off the Record
That guy can go by himself sure not ideal but Lego
F*** yourself later the National Guard
Doesn't
Interview from February to
20th
I got to be fair
Let's play the end of it cuz maybe
Certainly again
We absolutely believe in the Constitution
And are you won't find
Better Patriots and people in the National Guard
Freedom
Is what we do here in Iowa and what we see in our operations
For instance we were just asked
To take part in operation Washington DC
Our job there was to help me keep sure people got in the right places
Make sure the people are safe and those are the kinds of missions that were generally asked to do
Searching people's bags
No I didn't say that in fact it what I can tell you about the Iowa National Guard is were generally
Interstate status on operation
Unless of course were deployed for war thing we being a federal status but generally
We're going to work here in the United States somewhere
Generally on a state status of some kind which is
But we actually have gotten the number phone calls about this and refreshing summer that is once people find
At the actual mission is about replicating training
So we can go to war
Then Thunder okay with that
Martial law FEMA camps
Thanks for your opportunity
Wow
That is a
Dick
That's unbelievable
Next level
He spent like a half-hour talking to him and
Dungeon New Orleans
When
Airbnb
Nope
Can I respect your analysis and all of the evidence that you have shown here but I'm going to have to tell you that
You're wrong you lied about everything and you're the enemy
You have
R36
Years
You shut your f****** mouth dumbass
Yeah mainly because you're mainly cuz you're a f****** a****** and I hate you and I'm coming
On your show
To make sure that the people who would call us
Who are called
Shut the fuk up
And you're an a****** I'm reaching out because I know that you're dangerous
Actually going on
You're wrong
You're a betrayer
Crazy
That's an interesting interesting question
Now to me
Is
So he goes so ostensibly what is that lieutenant colonel
The entire way
Public Outreach
Part of the National Guard
Jesus
He's a PR guy for the most part at this point
New Years or whatever like on the ground in the National Guard
Your position
So that's why you so boring and
Answers that are like
What I can talk about is what Iowa does what we do in Iowa
But that's why
Cuz that's the only thing I know about
Classy
Because it would be very easy
Like fight back with Alex playing
He knows it's pointless
You could hang up
Use that is some sort of evidence that he's afraid of my question right
He does the only thing you can do witches like
No
Look
You're talk about federalized out
You do realize that
The book the role of the National Guard does have a federal application
Insert
Circumstances but generally were under the authority of the governor of
The no-win situation God bless him for trying
That's the question there is it so for him
His motivation
Is
He wants to
Like preamps all of these f****** phone calls like he's got enough phone calls now
Is spreading this b******* around
The end of the phone call they're usually like
Okay
Actually you know what you're a reasonable guy in that makes a lot of sense
Cool dude
So he's thinking
Maybe if I go on Alex's show
Once
MMA go on the train like a into his bye
Rational human
Come back he's a bad example of a rational human
David Lynch.
You come back
I thought that's what I thought this would be a conversation it was not there was
Just recently in 2018 that Senator Matt gaetz
Roulette congressperson iroc-z
But he went on
And then people will like
Yeah
I ate that was a mistake I was not going to do that again
I shouldn't have done that
I think that
Even you know
People get the message
That's it that's an interesting
What you want
So now you have to ask yourself the question
Is it
More important that everybody is aware of Alex in order to beware
No one should know
Or like because we
Situation
People go on Alex's show expecting a good-faith
Sprite
And then they wind up getting their ass
Is dunked on because Alex is a f****** lunatic
So you only lend your credibility
To Alex's show no one knowing would be great but I don't think
Possible thing that I think is appropriate
Is people being aware of him
Be wary
But you have to play his game a little bit even if you're outside of it and
Because
There are critics
He makes that are valid of cover him
Like the idea that they don't play the clips of
Give me saying xyr
Yeah like we talked about in the past like
Brian stelter doesn't have time
Play all York
So he's going to make broad generalizations
But you can attack him by saying
He didn't play the clip
Right-eo like ours I think it's super important
Cuz then you can be wary of him
I know what you said
I don't know I don't want to shoot our own horn but
The void that we
We can feel incredibly well
So that's why it's real solution to Alex Jones
Is for everyone to know who we are
It would help
Even if not everybody listen to our show necessarily
But just knowing that has a resource
Is there
I think it helps
Because
Go to Brian
Get
Breakdowns of whyalla
Posted on Media Matters are just
Clips
Script of it
Of something inflammatory doesn't necessarily breakdown
Why this is crazy
It's just crazy on its face
Right
To some extent by
I don't know we need every article about Alex Jones to end with a little end for confirmation
Sources cited
Should just be us
I need cuz I don't
Expect you to do this I need a much more robust database
Of the things that we
We've covered about him
With a lot of the
So people don't have to just go to the episode
Like right-wing Watcher or Media Matters is something to do that
Then
F*** yeah you should do it until then
I wouldn't do for
I wouldn't do it for free
I'm not sure that's good
23rd now
With this interview with good who did not cry out
Lying about that
He was a classy gentleman
And now we get back to
To the 23rd
Alex is back on his b*******
Trying to make you super scared
Wow he's trying to make you super scared
He's trying to build in a backdoor
Cuz he knows that all the things
Making you afraid about
Aren't going
You try to drag me off the back of a flatbed truck like
Okay
Back off
Sister cells
It was a bad recession
This is a cowardly way Alex
Presents most of
Fear-based narrative
He's making it much more overt
When usually does but it is
If we do something again by fear won't come
We're going to bounce back from the crash that happened
I know that it things are going to normalize and we're going to be okay
Was it manufactured event
You know it's because we stopped it right
It definitely isn't that it was just a bad reception
It's caused by
20 years of
Terrible f****** management after the deregulation of confirming propaganda which is
Dangerous
Because if you're dumb
Okay well with no matter what outcome Alex gets
2%
It's basically just
Exporting types of three-card Monte game that he's playing with his eye
Yes where the queen is all the time
He's f******
Please Google you will meet a stranger wearing red shoes
He might as well just be
You're you're somebody who likes to go out alot
But sometimes
Stupid
I went to a fortune
Tyler Watts
Yeah I got taken
A ride
Was it like the price
More than one
Pure to be advertised
40 boxes
Cuz your fortune
No it was
The Vegas pile of s*** I've ever seen
Your life
Is going to go
But they're very old
I thought this was a cliche
Made fun of for kids
Entire experience
Is this is really disappointing
Did you vomit ectoplasm
I'm not but
Okay that's good that was just
What is cheesecloth
Cheesecloth is fog made of
Think that's
True & Yeti
I really porous cloth
Do some research on your own time
I just can't
Is on
Thanks that was bad
Lost Mike collector
It is on our plate
Ready
To be devoured
So what's going on in the world in 2009 is
Is so foreign to current-day
Because Glenn Baxter
Like right looked at by right-thinking people it's kind of a goof
A fall from grace
But he has now wherever one
He still had a big fan base
And he was the Golden Boy
What Alex
View the zodian
Did you have people like Sean Hannity
And Rush Limbaugh for Mainline
Republican rate surfeited Folk
Radiohead Glenn Beck coming in
With not the
The same sort of libertarian
Jewelry that Alex has
But he had much more of a
Corner of the market
That was
Not the same as a Hannity or
Like the Neal Boortz
Which doesn't mean anything to you I just left
No idea who kneeled
Are you in a black sidekick
Kik name to Royal
What
Royals pretty cool
I wait what I love the Neal Boortz program
But you was also a Wii
Hey what are you talking about the Lone Ranger
No
Neal Boortz
I used to when I
We spent like ordering some
Supplies
Scheduling
You know planning
The schedule
What theater
Movies would be in
Making schedules
For the employees
Doing payroll
Balancing
Drawers
Estate
Stuff like that
Give me office
Large portion
Ends of the day
When I was
Responsibilities
On the floor Ministry
And so I would end up being there
Close the movie theater it like
2 in the morning
Life movie start
At midnight
You end up getting out of there
Hey by the time
About like 10
There's not
That much
To do a lot of
All the time except
Make sure everything's running smoothly.
I'll be back in the office and I just listen
Times Arkansas
I would listen to
Eagle
And they had Glenn
I'm back of the head
Eminem
Would have
Neal Boortz
And then they'd have
Is really awesome
Phil Hendrie
He wasn't a conservative but I don't know what he was doing on this station
You know Phil Hendrie
I've heard that name before
The hit show was that
What do you do
Is he word
Have an interview with a fake person
He was doing that voice to
He was doing
No actually I do know this because
Okay will look into Joe Frank and I'll look more
Callers
Or he's on interview
Use would be
Himself
The straight man host
Wacky interview subject to say something f****** inflammatory
I bet you would take calls and be both characters
If you would
And those people
Really and think about to go to my life I don't know what
I guess that's probably the you like
Marketing model
With Ted's of Beverly Hills
Well that's his restaurant
Beverly Hills
He's like his real guy I like a restaurant him on it was
Closed after 9/11
It was
Not far after
Have been within a month
Keep coming on
And he's like
Pittsfield
To have
The World Trade Center rebuilt
I'll take care of all of it
I'll take care of all the
Don't worry about it I'm very rich man
I'd like to help out the
I'll pay for it all
But there's one condition
And that is what I need there to be plaque
At the base of the new towers
The names of everyone who died
At Dayton Memorial eyes.
Everybody said
My daily special
I love that so much.
Brilliant
Brilliant like it's the best kind of creative trolling
Side listen to that
Coasttocoastam.com on
Because
Coast-to-Coast which are palatable shows
I ended up listen
That station born
Yeah I know about him
At that time
Going back with irrelevant
And I think that Alex Jones
Is a little bit jealous
Because
He's being much more successful
Towards the end of this episode here on February
Alex has a clip of Glenn Beck's video
Particularly
Decides to play it
Ione
Wanted
We're going to listen to a little bit of the Glenn back portion
But I think it's
Alex
Response
The end of it
That's much more Talent
I believe it's really interesting
You're going back to sound like
Future Alex Jones
As opposed to Alex's narrative
Where you like
Glenn Beck is always ripping
Right
See if you can tell what I'm
That's tied into what would happen
Muslim extremist
America
Deal with it
Very important
Classroom
And what you have in Western Europe
Is there no longer going to be able to be embarrassed
Twisting
Gas was
Insider trading
Financial collapse
In the USA
Operation
Wild
That is wild his Wild
Answer my new operating thesis based on special
And based on Alex's thing or just traffic is
Is he's going to get
His ego is going to get the better of him
And when he sees
Glenn Beck
Becoming the figure of
The Tea Party
He's not going to be able to stand it
He hates Glenn Beck
He's going to start adopting some of
The things
Just putting out to the world
A little bit more
Such as
I'm at that we heard there that is not
Super persistent
In Alex Jones in 2009
I still think he's a bigot
Particular hatred
Distrusted Muslim
Is not as
Focused as just even that Glenn's clip was
It's wild
Why is it
Sometimes Alex in 2009
Sounds like me now
7 years am I going to sound like Alex now
Is that how that works
What happens
No I don't think people like us
The first season of The Wire but we're not characters
Yet you're not okay okay
Spoiler alert in the last season of The Wire everyone takes over the roles of the mantle
Becomes the new bubbles Michael Padilla.
Parking lot
Marlowe is a different character
Alright alright alright you have that generational
There must be one
And it is interesting and fun to think about like
Your future
Maybe you become the next Alex Jones
Man that'd be fun
Like Alex Jones back then was crazy
F****** somehow
But you only after that because he hates
Glenn Beck
Think it's not like that
Genuine person
Contradict
Very soon narrative
Well he will believe soon I'm right about everything is because I
Guys who knows what I'll think
Picture
24th to be
Berkeley honest
Just get it done with
Cuz we need to move through this
Because of things to keep happening
I really hope you'll be there already but
Covid-19 we made it through like
Metro
Has a new thing he wants to scare people about
It's not new
The episode today
And that is
The public schools
Are going to kill you
The police
Let me call before a judge
A contract
And then Federal
Thousand dollars
Million
Dollars
Speaks up in class they're going to get on
Legal probation
That's exactly
April teale
Rodger
Go to prison
The teacher left the room I am officer of the Court
But then Alex gets into something that would
Coming out in the news at that time that is very real
Pennsylvania Rock by Jalen kids-for-cash scandal
A friend sleepover
Chips and soft drinks
Shortly
Unshackled
Like the class three times
Posting a joke about
The principal under her free speech
Red flag right there
Well it's incredible
Scroll down far enough on the page
But a fifteen-year-old
Principal on her Myspace page
This judge also with
Thirteen-year-old Shane Blythe
Trespassing in a vacant building
From his parents
Vitamin
Descendants Kirk Kroger 17 years old
Attention 5-month
What's a boot camp for helping
Steal DVDs from Walmart
Also he's an a****** f****** judge
2008 Michael Connor
Mark
B a l e
Recused
Accused guilty
Proposing
Auctions on juveniles
Increase occupy
For-profit
What
Which is really
Bop version of the prison industry as a whole
Not okay but the outrageous
You feel when it's being done to children
Also apply when it's being done to it.
Do you received money from people
Juvenile Detention
Centers
Sociopathic
That's all I'm saying
I thought maybe we should have a second
Maybe Jon Ronson should interview every judge before they take
Guy ferrelli
Who started the main focus of the day
Taking illegal payments
The nearly $1000000
From the youth center
Pinhead
The hit the
Pirelli was sentenced
28 years
Federal Prison
Because there was not long enough
Long enough
And the other guy was sentenced
Dude I believe so
Years because he played
So the issue is
This to a lot of
Are up to
5 South
Converso
The key is not
Because of
Finding out about this
The trials and everything
Is that they
Just vacated all of the sudden
Is that they had a
Issued over
Want a lot of money
Imagine the damage that was done
Suicide
On
What's the right word
You can't
Power know you can
You giving a reversible
The sort of the sort of damage that
It's just like impossible to undo
Is there a very awful
Which is like what how many people in Rikers Island who are waiting on like
3 years for a single f******
Trial like they're the right to a fair and speedy trial is gone
Yeah real big problem
The phenomenon of incarcerating an institutionalizing children is not some
New Norris
Something unique to this
Pennsylvania
It's notable because there's a
Clear quid pro quo
Is clearly receive payments
Spilled private room
The issue
As it always is with Alex
Cuz narrative
According to
To the sentencing project nationally the youth rate of incarceration
Bluetooth placement rate
What's 433 / 100,000
When compared to a white youth placement rate of
6 / 10
Overall the racial
Disparity between black and white
In custody in
Since 2001
5 times more likely to be incarcerated
And this is something that goes on in pretty much every state with no charismatic proper
Ganda screaming about how it's a
The globalist attempt to break up the
Alex doesn't care about that he cares about the case
In Pennsylvania
And it may be because it's in the news and he's lazy
It's just an easy thing for him to talk about but I would suggest
Something else
More relevant to him
Namely that the judge the city he was in Wilkes
Is 92.3% white
The county Luzerne County
96.6
Percent White
So this judge was doing it to white people and that's why it's
But it's also why Alex cares about
As is always the case that exceeds not care about the problem at all
Until he feels attorney white people
Bloody murder about it
I never recognized as a
Black activist
Impune
Have been trying to draw tension
Problems
Gears insurance
Anyway I would say Alex Jones
Is a gigantic
Yep
So no disagreement America is a giant
I don't disagree with that house there multiple narrative
Is on this episode that he's going through it all
Intertwine with this same business line of like
They're doing it to White
Whatever it is the gun confiscation in
Katrina that's that same thing
This
You know kids being
Detention centers
Because it's profitable
This is the same thing you don't care until it affects
His own
This is such a parallel to
To right now
Like
The idea of
People being angry is released
Omarosa
Yeah
He's still
It doesn't even f****** matter if he does or does not have an n-word tape
He's got most races
Like because of s*** like this because of this kind of like
Obvious
Racism
Why people would give a s*** if he says the N word is like
Why would you give a s*** if somebody owned slaves but never said the n-word their awnings
Slaves is the issue
Isolved
Interesting
Take on it I guess
Hate to bring up
I don't like text but
Argument
Because the media is so f****** lazy
And won't do their job
The idea that there is
To come out before
Be like Trump
To cover it that way because they're so reductive and can only calls
Media into a box
Where they
Couldn't do this
Dance around
That that's one benefit but other than that
Doesn't matter at all
The proof of the pudding is in the eating
Yeah
Everything they do is
White National
An arm of the KKK
At this point what are you
To make it even
More clear to what we talked about
This show
The argument that Alex
She's gotten worse
Absolutely you've gotten worse
This is always been
At least a decade
He cares about is
They're going to do
Your response
Family Court
We didn't have them
Earlier
Racial hygiene courts
The rack Warehouse rental apartments
Kill you
We did
Newsreel clips
Go back to our coverage of any more information about that
I think they're like now that Alex is wrapped up in Family Court
It seems relevant
That would maybe you could have put in there if you want to play then for the judge
You're not the lotto
But God dammit event is Mister Jones
Kill you
You can't play the tape
I'm going to have to call Dan Friesen to the sand
Who have brought a boombox
Because you are from the
80s apparently but go ahead and
Play what you have to say
Eddie Bauer
Is gross
I don't know why I
A year in jail and then you read what happened to these kids some of them died in custody others come out
Shock therapy
They thrown out on the street
Workforce
Your story
Tower 12 I got the fish fight
I know I'm crazy I deserve it they shocked me over and over again
Let me guess
That's your sickening degenerate
Family court is to blame for all the homeless
He wants to make a documentary about these
People is to use them as a prop
So what he is f******
When applied to the healthcare and just
This system is a fundamentally exploit
Dualism is the f****** problem
Everybody f****** makes money off of all of this
Why are you making my argument for ready
F****** idiot
At the same time I track
Like I don't think of that
I don't think the victims' family
Court or necessarily
Because
Most of the homeless
Follow his f****** argument
All about profit-driven even even if you is right
Exactly
Even if you going to be right or wrong you're talking about
Why are people black
Existing like him
I don't know it's wild
You're so f****** stupid
Yep
Another version
Is a color that is
Gets here on the 20
This list off what you would
Described as
The big globalist
Missing from this list
I think
DuPont
The Rothschilds
The royal family in England
Royal family with Dutch Shell
How about Bugatti
Including outdoor what is the biggest shareholders Knox
Petroleum
To the lab
70-year can rates
The world cost
These problem
And they've been able to profit handsomely by that
He's just a lot of that is just
Just another College
No Soros in there baby
So up to this point still no mention of that guy
No
He's not in the game
Why don't they ever
Even then
He added in oil come
Even tertiarily through Al Gore
Because it's such a part of Alex's
He's mirroring back a lot about
Yeah but you ain't if you even throw in one oil company
You threw in all the
The oil
Like they're all f****** doing whatever it is you
Rothschild
The way you think
They're just talking about
Economics and taxes
That's all they're talkin
I'm still I'm still
Alright fine
Is Victoria
Does not
The conversation
Need to check off the list
I mean who knows we'll find out
Who hates Taurus
Vladimir Putin
Concerns that I can off the internet is going to
Somehow ruined our show or something like that
Yeah don't worry about it
2 years of episodes on my external hard drives that I have not listened to
Front loading a lot of downloading plenty of stuff to go over
Because I need to know
In the same way that I
Did to know what happened during
The election
I need to know when Soros
Even if you turn into the next Alex Jones and leave the show
I will keep doing it on my own until I figure out
The f*** did he
Start hating George Soros
Villain backstory the only thing that keeps me in check
Like if I were let loose on my own
I might just start claiming all kinds of s***
I mean the sky's the limit
Most of it would probably sound more Bass
No cuz you do the same thing you just reference an article in the house
Most of it
Glenn Greenwald
Still better service than the washing
Mountain Time
I'm wrapping up the show here
Where to check in
No Soros in the narratives yet
We get
This which I think is it
Interesting
Referral
Revelation of where his head is at
About how like
You know I can't reinforcing Alex
Faucet
Espoused earlier about how he's
Time is now
John Cena politics
Okay
You deserve to be
The biggest foxes ripping you off
That sort of thing another 2 years that fox
Foxwood start ripping
More than that but
We get to this Alex
3 things
About support
Support that are very
Let me bring it to across to you because this is what I think it is
If fox has
Beginners
Following orders and beating the drums
War
For a conflict with Iran
They have all of your thoughts looks like that may be on the horizon
So they now have faked her puppet news frontman like back painting
Crazy real scenarios on Fox like the Bubba effect
Alongside yesterday retired CIA
And Military paid TV pundits is that not an imminent sign of times
In the very near future
Stand against
Security right now
Showing us what they're going to do
Ireland
In one Fell Swoop
I hate
Michael Savage
It sure doesn't support Michaels
Ron
Within the confines of
IGA
Right everything is great
Sports are on Andy believes it is real
Committing acts of
So that's where we are
Here at the end of February 24th
Can't wait for this
Just to change the
Because it'll be
Meaningful
Lot of
Degrees that is
A lot of everything except the whites
Everything is good
Everything except the whites
The only thing that is fake
Is white supremacy
So I guess that's it
Supremacist and he's been so from the beginning
Unlike any from Texas
Who would have got
What is shock
He's consistent about that if nothing
I do mean
Nothing
Except for his shadowy figure group of
That's you and that's fine
I am fascinated
Concept
Everything is negotiable
Except whites
Soupremacy
Like that's non-negotiable that's the only thing you got
A lot of white supremacy
I want to understand that point of view it's like I have no beliefs other
Like Central life
Lies
Other than
So I will let everything go I will play team sports forever
But if Trump was like
Which
He only even
Kind of begrudgingly 7:30
Which everybody already knew was a lie
The only thing the only thing that would be the only thing that would get people that support Trump off the Trump train is him being lie
Luther King jr. day a week
Like that's it
Process what you're saying
My mind is
Is rattling around cuz I'm about like other issues that are negotiable
It wouldn't really matter
Things like
Something like that
What I kept coming to in my head like with whatever issue you want to talk about
Is that
It's the same reason that I left the Lost
As a major
No in college
Go to take about the logic class
Formality
Concreteness of logic
Welsummer
It's not even the math part about it that I liked
It said it was deaf
If you're willing to contradiction
Can't do that
Philosophy
In argument
Based philosophy
You could make an argument for genocide
And I can make an argument against John
Genocide
Could be
Valid would be able to argue about it whether or not the premises
Conclusion
Just it doesn't make sense
Retina
Who's arguing what's going on
The only reason I bring this up is because that's
Feeling that I get about a lot of the issue
Shoes outside of
Whiteness is right now
Yeah I would like all those other things
Could make an argument
Diabetic support
White identity for or against
Welfare
You can create
The public school system
Improvements argument
You could do all of that the only thing you can't do is make an argument for a pluralistic
Society
Full of acceptance
The end that's why it's
The only non to go
And it's reinforced by the idea that if we allow multiculturalism
Creep into our society
What it's going to do is going
Diminish the whiteness
And make it
You were or whatever
And to them
To those people who believe those
That's something
Can't be undone
And that's why they've so vociferously
Defend
The idea of their whiteness
Because they're like they're trying to come and take it away and eventually it'll be gone
Can't get it back
Because
Then in what
10 sentences you just did
That I have
F*****'-a
How many f****** like
Good life in Trump country articles have you f****** red
About a million of them you just f****** in 10 seconds
10 sentences ruined all of their bulshit argument
That's exactly what it is it's brilliant
I was putting forth is also super vague cuz I'm not willing to come up with
On-the-fly what the arguments for and against
Certain policies
No that's
You can you could spend all the time you want writing those arguments but the point is
Your urinalysis
Is curry
So if I wanted early I can just compliment you and then we'll just talk to go
Do you have any
Final thought
Thank you or mad
I just want to make
Make sure you got
River
You needed to get out
Like
Brett
Things that we
We talked about
In three days and 2,000
I think shocking
Giving the contact
Except we live in in
If we did three straight episodes of Alex now
It'll be all the same everything
Yeah but it's still at least like oh you're talking in homeschoolers right but even then like
Schooler
B******* ties to drills and the drills then ties to the Iowa National Clark National Guard
Type to New Orleans size do police oversight
And all of that s*** ties into his
F******
What is prison industry
Like this
Message
What you responding to I think is that
He'd better writers
Or at least he was better at the gate
Like really
Focusing all that much on how
There are just a bunch of times he's talking about the state's putting for 13th Amendment right
But it's like we can't
Wake me up
In terms of what you cut
For us
To follow
You you have to agree that were you to listen
Listen to three straight episodes
What's today
You would never be able to cut together the swap
The things that we
Cut together in 2009
Not at all
So that's my summation that's my final
Thought process
I'll be back in Paris for a while
For the best
Know about our
Alex Jones
Feel free to trust
Rightwingwatch and Media Matters have you covered on that front
Or people tweeting
Stop
Whatever the outrage cycles that they're promoting
At this point
It's really the only thing that's going on
Deeper analysis
Right
CookieSwirlC
Shallow and I think actually
Hurting him in the present
I'm not it's not my primary motivation
Consequences
That's your urine
I think that the best way to do that is
Unravel
I think it's much more valuable
So we'll see
Anyway
Live website knowledge faith.com
We are
Which if your new is a reference to
Exactly
Beyond
That's weird
Jordan is your turn
Well
As much as I normally like to hate on anybody militaristic
Stance
As as you know
You know I don't like the military
Pray you know I'm not a fan of I would have loved to
I don't
Want to tell him to go f*** himself he seems like a good guy
Some money too
Standing Rock Puerto Rico and help people out
Anyways
The only answer is
Go f*** yourself the entire New Orleans Police
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work