Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Damn
What's the farthest you've traveled
One.
Have you ever flown
10 hours
Remember where we flew out of my tab in New York
Two parrots
I don't know just
I don't know exactly how long it was terrorism
And then we took a little biplane
You should never do that
That's scary
7 Southwest
Any f****** day
Feel-Rite
To be in a propeller plane
Review of all
Absolutely
Route
I'm sure you bring this up because you just got back from
They are weekend in Maine
Disclaimer I'm I'm off a lot of travel and from the airport
And I'm straight off watching the first
2 hours of SummerSlam so we're both
And then you go back
Second time because of the
Time zones and all the sudden
It is only six
Aaron water show
Chicago this weekend
Army planes flying overhead
People drink isn't that
The phrase that we have a Mastiff
Military-industrial
It is great
New donor
Not sponsored
A little stronger
Appreciate it thank you so much for becoming a
I'm a policy wonk
I do
If you would like to pick up
Do so by going to our website
The show button
I am in your home
The great you can also
Legally change your name
Quicksupport
Michelle
Can change your name only if
Poseidon
Very specific LegalZoom
Coupon
Giant
A little teaser
I've been back in the past
Austin 2009
Of the Tea Party
For you and our listeners
That the next episode will finally
All right on this Monday episode
At least once a week we should check in
And the present day and what's going on
Behind the curtain
And I'll see what's up
And so today we're going to be going over the Oggy
August 17th
2018 episode
My mind was
Blown
Wait what they're from a present
Yeah yeah alright there's there's a number of things that are going to happen
You're going to see on this show
That
What wild rainbro saddle takeover and hosts
For the rest of the day
That there's a lot of predictions that we've made about like
Going to happen
I think I think number of our predictions are accurate
But something is going on that no one
Could have predicted
And I don't think
Anybody
Except you and I
Would even have noticed
I believe are going to
Share some insight about what's happening you will not be able to get anywhere else
The first
Is that
This commercial
Plays
To do with money
Yep there's the money issues commercial plays before each
Chunk chunk
60 hour chunk
Is it hot
But it's just a recording of the screen
And each one starts with v
B h by Frederic Remington fully cooked Ready-to-Eat
Yes
Order
Turn yourself life bacon
Sizzle when it comes
That's pretty that's pretty wild
The diamond
That's what I'm liking now
You've got the
You got some ads
We're very much not there before
I have not been in the
Levi class
Years that we've been the show
Now we've got sucking
Navigate to the beginning of the actual Special Report
Paul Joseph Watson
4 minutes
Eating cured bacon as opposed to
You cooking it yourself if not actually where I decided
Fast-forward through it and I listen to it is like
They're trying to
To destroy Western Civilization
Starting off the ship
Something very familiar here but
Something else
It's Friday August 17th 2018
This is the second time within the first
8 minutes of the show that he's played the final
It only 81 days left until most important elections in US history
We are
All-out assault on Western civilization and America whatever you do realize the global
Miscalculation
Committed
Transmission
Whatever for the salt you can imagine
Hairstyles censorship in America
We are here exposing it
They're scared of this information because he answered
On this Friday Global broadcast
The most scary
Because we're the ones who can bring them.
If you notice that the beginning
He said that the midterms are the most important elections
Using US history
Is exactly what he said about the 20s
16 Alexa
It's not something that he said about previous alive
And the reason I'm bringing this up is because we take a glimpse now into Alex Jones
MB
What are described as a political hack
You know what I mean by because that's what
Sensationalist
People do all of the time we heard that over and over again
From people on these center right
Center-left
Right through the 2008 election even though 2004 election
This is the most important election of all time
Because they're trying to juice up the bass
They're trying to get people more excited and make sure the turnout is good
And now Alex is doing the exact
Thing which I think is
Coming of him
I know that I'm holding him too
To a standard that doesn't
But
There's a mythical ideal that Alex
It is above the rigmarole in the
You just finally found his team
Defense though
His world
This is not hyperbole
Like what he is because what's really going on in the in the midterms now is
A real situation
I don't know the answer is no
I don't think it's that important
But I don't think
I don't think that the Democrats getting a slim majority in something
Is necessarily going to
Republican
I don't think that's going to lead to running a bucket
Signing all sorts of immoral legislation
Any more than it already
It's not like they're going
Not still try
Right2know
It's still going to be like well now
Yeah push
I don't know I think it's
Incredibly
Fairly important
I am not I'm not ready to be
Be like
If the Democrats lose visit to the end of the world because that's sensationalize
In all honesty
2000 election was probably the most important election
America
That's for damn sure
Who is George h.w. Bush still alive
James
Old man who paints
Does he still want to live
That would be too far I think
I'm going to push the boundaries how crazy I can get
Imagine what that all
Objectified
So in this next clip
I think we see another thing
Is big
Volume body of partisan
Much more than like
A couple months ago
The left as I've told you for 20-plus years
Is brainwashed hate America and is trained by the high school colleges
The mainline churches
America
Is the ultimate Evil in the world because the globalist
America and other Western Nations
To enforce their planetary plan
Absolute
Incomplete domination
So the part that I'm referring to stop by saying I've been telling you for 20 years that the left
Brainwashed
You're in Tire platform
4 years
Was that the left and the right are the same
That they're equally bad and they are the same thing
He's not saying that anymore because we talked about a lot the right isn't the right
What is now the
Like the Republicans in the GOP
Crazy they said for the most part
These now it's not something that is like a political party
Political party
But the political party isn't what
Like
The GOP
20 years ago
Absolutely
If something is
Become beholding to
White
Nationalism
Justin Bieber
It's not a political party it's a
Exploitation
Crazy weird
Republican
Maybe we should govern the country
Instead of
Maybe we should strip mine and make sure the poor people died in the
Is it maybe this could go bad
Which did not do that
Alex actually has a really correct
Obviously
Losing
Everything around him
You've been sued
Buy multiple
He's being
Talked about more than ever
A lot of people are talking about him
It's being brought up
Like that
Because
Creating a version
And it's really interesting
No you can't bring that up how dare you
CB for truckers band
So here's
He gets into what he perceives to be what's happening
Thing in the world
He's not not correct
The West that is all confirmed
They're going to nougat
It doesn't work like that
You know what if Obama was
Alex
Kicked off Facebook
R&B on Alex's
Like it really was the government doing something like that
Write be on his side
Sort of support for private Corporation
At the government
There's no way anyone would accept government
Even if you were able to
To produce evidence that these like
YouTube
Baume & Facebook
Melky
Like if you can produce evidence for me that all of them
Together and say hey let's kick Alex off at the same time
I'm not sure I'm going to side with Alex
But it'll be different conversation
Absolutely
I don't believe that they are working
In concert
It seems very clear that one jumped in there all we're like we can
Cour de Lane
Not like in some way to take coordinated and had that planned
Bruise that then
Then I would have the exact same conversation that I've already willing to have in that is
These companies
Suppression of a three-piece cuz it's not the government
Together like if there was a backroom deal
What's the CEOs of all of those corporate
And they all agreed on something
That's where we get into like
Torches and pitchforks
Territory because that is
Tremendous overreach
Give a power that
Can't be allowed
Petition the government alike
To break in the
An information trust in the same way that all of the railroads
Orchestrating
Prices in the 19
Without us getting too deeply down this road
I still don't think that there's a monopoly of
Access on the Internet or anything like that
Like we got investigate that you've got to do an investigation on that
Ask some question also hey Bill Maher
This is so fun
What happened to Lamar came out
Alex Jones
You should be able to speak
And have like he was a cute against out
Because our expense
There's human to die Austin live traffic
He speaks for the left
Now Bill Maher's coming out it's being like Alex Jones should have been kicked off step
Play Pandora
But
From the podcast
Find the episode on YouTube
Two of them
With my Roundup of itself
Years ago has so there you go
I think I think we have some ideas about what you
Should be done with the
Website
Burn
Sort of
Information
Is a complexity
I don't know I never expected Alex to say something like this
We must stop this now by Congress.
Having any control over
At the end he was struggling so hard not to advocate for
Regulation the regulations
Replace them with regulations
Yeah and then
Did the congress shoot
Control the internet
Weird
Stupid were you so f****** stupid bizarre
Bafflingly confusing
Exactly what I was in I was in New Hampshire and I've heard I heard like
Four different people
People say Hey you know we don't have it
Sales tax
And then
Two sentences later they were like
I'm telling you man our roads are garbage
It's 121
Oh we're going to be sales tax but our income tax is through the roof
Play something new for us or anything really interesting
Your advocates
Doesn't make sense
But it is special
I hear something like this
Put your mic down
Let's talk about
The USA blue jeans as a kid remember
Hellyeah Hellyeah Diamond gusset
The first modern it's so great also there's another Diamond gusset commercial to Cabazon
It's the president of diamond
Does that mean
That
While we were listen
Sing to you the YouTube Rod
If you were listening
On the radio
You would have still heard
Local affiliate commercials if you're watching on
CBS Chicago
Here Local Chicago
I don't know.
I feel hear that
I don't think so I'm not entirely sure
But it's possible
Yeah that's what I'm say
Although your theory is
I don't know why they would have cheese dreams
I don't know
I don't know why they would have two streams
What do you mean
But this is what like where I got this from is one of the only places
That that audio comes
If he's not
Recording it to be released
To be released on YouTube
So now he's primary it is released but that's not his
That's not going that's not his
Primary audience
No
So if Direct
Streaming
To get to the the Millions
Then he's trying to get
As much G
Probably amplifies
As the amount of air time that the G
Commercial
Then I assume he gets
It's an interesting question to ask because
YouTube
Video that's up on YouTube that might not have
Have Diamond got the key
There's nothing to it
That's a bummer
Conspiracy theory and then all the sudden I come back with how they have the bizworks
You wasn't
Getting
Commercial
No cuz they're still local station
Things that have to have their own
Right right
Commercials
Blue Diamond
It's so good to hear those
Commercials
Wonderful
I do.
Even though
It's not just
The commercial
That
Me feel very weird about this
That is only one piece
But
Mother's Day
But I am
Alex Jones
Cries
Mission in America
Or you've been brought up
Glass 30 40 50 years in most schools
All of which should be here you'll fall history
You don't learn about the Trojan War
There's a deeper problem
Images of the Trojan War didn't happen
Little Teapot Road Reservoir
Like Heinrich schliemann found the city of Troy what has
Troy was
There was there was a destruction but it wasn't nearly the city
No good the homeric tradition of the Trojan War
Specifically just an allegory to talk about the Rage of Achilles
Is that is really all that is
It's more mythology going into it like that
So are you sure
I am out to saying people should
Sure
No
When they could be teaching fictional history
710 Freeway
I bet he even has a warped view of the fakir
Version of the Trojan War
Cuz I bet he just get that from
I'd love to talk
Is that Brad Pitt was
The mad
How do I
Not real fun about that
You really get down to it
The only reason that Achilles decided not to fight is
Because he had like
Concord a bunch of people
Stolen some women and then
Did the woman who had enslaved
I don't get the rapist
Ice cream look I am against all the the
But that is a reasonable position.
Like at the end of the day if that's
If you have to think of it as
Of their time
Turn up
Episode I would say a large portion of it
Coming out and saying America was never great
And we won't be great
Unless we
Deal with
Problems
Stereotypes
Some stuff like that
Stupid poorly worded, I think Cynthia Nixon had the best response to it was like
You have just tried to sound like a pro
You tried to sound like what you think Progressive sound like
And you failed yet
And your face
Better
It's amazing when you see the
These politicians
Haven't had to run for their office
For like 45 Alexa
Actions all the sudden
Like I'll just I'll just
I want back
Hey everybody a headache
Feel like a miracle
Suck a dick all the time right now
What are the wrestling world that's what's called
If you actually listen to
They are not cheery tomorrow night
Kind of response to it but later Alex represent
Struggles with this
Idea
Officially
I'm here is the beginning
For register.
America
German Russian Mexican
We go in five countries
So did you eat you were talking over to
We go in we fight all these wars and then we give the country's back people know what does that
Alex
Most of your career is based on complaining about Foreign Wars
Only relevant because of his AP interventionist
And pro weed Stanford
Despite the fact
What is a flaming racist
Publix Dempsey's whole thing
Even just a couple years ago he would be complaining about how we've gone into all these countries and we're still there
America
We go and solve problems elsewhere and then give the country back
Free that America's great
Disagree
It's nonsense
There's no reason
Is I don't know what point you're trying to make other than he
Efix Cuomo's
Which is fine
You can make that argument a different way you don't have to do this
My reaction to that videos just like
Come on man
It's one of those things I think I was doesn't have much you want
To talk about
Kentucky off on
But I think he's
He's in the weeds man like in terms of what
He's just versions of why America is great with that won the war thing which is
Against
Panama Canal
Lot of people
And then
We have building
Building
I think there's some other
Countries that have much more gorgeous buildings much more impressive building amazing the American build
Feelings are they
Centuries as we all know the greatest building
Of History
Thousands of you
Oh you were the American
Spirit
And then his other version is
Inventions
Sure we've invented some stuff
America is not in the top
Olympia or liquid
Embarrassed
Look
Whiskey that's all you need to know
Invented
Every pretty much everything
My response to that would be like
FairPoint about Cuomo
But everything else
Just talkingshit this is nonsense
And that's not even getting into the nuances like
The parts of America
History of data are terrible
You're not a good country
For a lot of business
Slavery
Seaweed
Invisible
I'll do that one thing I do
Is it
No I didn't he says them aren't really
Worth it for a clip
About betas here a little bit
Brian stelter.
Would probably be hunted
Crosshair
My alarms
Red heart
Paula White
Always getting stronger
With love in my heart and my eyes
Play supporters will be right back
That wasn't bad
Is it is what it is
I find that far more refreshing
That was a genuine like
Please support us not like
There's another Trend that I'm seeing here
Steven controller
That's not the best example
Coming up later
But he on this episode that I listen to vibrate
At least six times
Shut off in the middle of sentences by the bridge
You have to be
Working on a
Who's that's my presumption
It doesn't make sense
Like you so full of passion that he's missing
Know if he's resting on the radio
It's B he's not in can
Control anymore Genesis Communications
Work is now in control
I believe that
Seated that sword
Back to them
Where is he
In control
That's my working on it
But it's so glaring
Not
Because he would have
You saw the build-up going on now
I crawl and I grow stronger even though I'm getting weaker
Bleeding up
A
Pig sounds like
F*** I got a second
That's what I think Auntie can't
Skip a break
Yeah anymore
Why can't I believe
But he's lost some control of his own show
That's my working
He's falling apart
Yep and I think the diamond gusset thing is a nice thing for us to see
Here in the
In that ice
We are seeing
Somewhat of
Version
To The Pact
Like
This is on the pot
Yeah
So he's just releasing the live radio
You think that he would have figured out that you can edit
Your own ads into the into a podcast
You would think that and that is actually part of my
Consideration of why I I wonder
About
You know that's part of why I'm
I don't know
I don't know what to say
About that
Alex
Mode
I don't think it's true but
It's one of those things you probably shouldn't say on
I'm out here
Long time
I have videos and articles at all
Michelle
People shooting home Intruders
Incredible
Is that
That's Entertainment is that a no I think
Extra is Mark McGrath talking about people
What
What is a psychopath
Crazy videos
Sound effects over at
It's like that
Like that's what I'm stealing from Alex is the guy was like
Yeah but then the other part that I think is really fun is like
I think we would all like that
Forum
I don't know what I'm doing or with real
Go to bed
I like it
Enjoy
Big
A big narratives that has throughout this
It's a little bit trouble
Inasmuch as it is based on a real story
Alex is a terrible job covering it
I will do my best
To pick up the pieces
After he's done with
But just like you lyrics
San Francisco
You are the daughter father's arms
Just real quick and Kacy black
Haven't heard the episode work
About that because gun misfired it ricocheted off
The ground and shot her
Charged
With murder because it was
Yeah once again the issue was the gun not the
Masterbat
Is that he was
Mexican
Talk about it
He wouldn't talk about it probably wouldn't talk about it
You probably leave it alone
Since Bureau
Text Rose
Hugo free
And Muslim if you have been a white you wouldn't get in trouble
An underground
An underground tunnel
Who died in the ritual
For the local liberal government
Thousands of ton
Bulldozer to cover
The compound
He would not be in jail if a dead three-year-old
Releasing
On
$2,000 Bond
No money pay
Cash Bond
Respond to one of the points
Before we get into the
Over there
The idea that they're covering it up with sand and whatever
It's someone else's property was on
Is there choice
This been going on
The beginning of August
Uhealth done everything that they need to do
The physical location
Like there's anything
Myth
So the idea is not that they're there. Whitewashing something covering it up
This guy's proper
It's someone else's property
Breaking news
So this is an issue where there was
A group of Muslims
Who had a compound
Next
Was allegedly being used
Gets out of
Shoe weapons
Who died
That were being done because they thought
You would become the
Jesus Christ
Debbie fun
If they were right
From the CNN articles
Give you a little bit of a context of what this story is about and then we're going to talk a little bit more about the
The family fled Georgia for compound in New Mexico where they train their children and firearm
His father's hand
11 more malnourished children were later found on the proper
Family believed that once the demons were gone the boy would return as Jesus four months later and tell this family which
Get rid of
Eyewitness
Those who did not believe their message would be killed or detained until they believe the teenager on the compound set
According to an FBI
There's no evidence that they killed anybody
But all of them are charged with 11 counts
Child
It's being dealt with as
Very serious issue
Exactly what happened
And with my
Terrance Caldwell
And it was a
Christian
Hold on to that talk
Backroads
Militant
Islamic
Group or Muslim group
Call the local sheriff called The Suspect extremists of the Muslim belief
He later said that his statement was based on their appearance
I need it not want to imply violence
So does every idea or the kernel of where that came from
Is from physical up
Mexican
There are children
Mistreated there
Absolutely
There were children who were reported missing in other states
Who were they are
It's not clear whether it was parental kidnapping
Or
Or something along those lines there's a little bit of murkiness to that
I don't care to unpacking
Entirely
So from the judge quote
The state alleges that there was a big plan afoot but the state has not shown to my satisfaction by clear and convincing evidence
What impact factor
Plan what
Thought Judge Sarah Backus
The state wants me to make a leap and it's a large
And that would be to hold people in jail without bond based on again
Troubling fact
But I didn't hear any Kuwait plan that was being alleged by the state
This is a response
I don't
See evidence of the assertion that are being made namely that they were training kids to be
Warriors of some sort of the accusations
Of the prosecution was
They are teaching them to school shooting
And that was why they would be the rest of the public
What's right
So you're going to have to have some actual evidence it's almost like the burden of proof is
I believe the judge was
Clearly
Presented proof of
These things for I'm not sure that it would be appropriate
Based on troubling fact
Anything other than a child
Yeah so
Alex is entirely ranting
Just about the state
Grenade by the
The defense attorney
Whose job it is to defend their client
Well we shouldn't have those things like quote if these were white people of a Christian
That's not a big deal because there's a Second Amendment right
On firearms
If these were white Christian
Faith healing is
No
Because we have freedom of religion
But they look different and worship differently from the rest of us
Thomas Clark said bunt
So the argument that
Alex is responding to in claiming that the liberal government is making
Like bring all stuff in
Whose job it is to
To come up with
And you are correct
IPic
I think there's something to it
So
Here's the thing
Three-year-old abdulghani wahhaj died at the compound
Is absolutely the result
A very least
Criminal neck
The boy suffered from seizures requiring constant
Caring medical attention
His mother hekkema Ramsey
Previously told CNN
A trip to Saudi Arabia in October 2017 siraj wahhaj
That's funny
Siraj wahhaj
You said you wanted to
Stop giving us on medication and perform rituals
Demonic spirits out of
This is not really too far off from Alex
Distrust of psychiatric medication
Is demonization of vaccines
His belief in literal demon
These are people who largely
Just took Alex Jones
Put them into action
Now
Why that's important
Is because
Oftentimes
A dead kid
Is the result of the things Alex Jones believes
Yep in terms of don't trust medicine
Now back to your
From The Washington Post
Nearly one-third of the roughly 600 gravesite
Peaceful Valley Cemetery belong to a child
Identify how and why the children die before their Burial at the graveyard used by the followers
Words of Christ Splinter sect the practice
Delia believe the definition of God the corner and autopsy report
Former church members childhood memories of children needlessly dying
From lack of Medical Care
Bruce Wingate founder of protect Idaho kids Foundation
For children will die this year in Idaho alone
If lawmakers fail to lift the state's faith-healing these
Linda Martin
Former church member and retired Lane County Barber
Followers of Christ members issue birth control
Normally give birth at home infrequently Fargo prenatal care
Homeschool children go without birth
Making efforts
Subtract faith-healing deaths
The cultural rituals of the church compound the problems at Canyon County Sheriff
Kieran Donahue
He said followers have not always alerted authorities after a death
When deputies are called off and they find bodies moved washed and redress
And dozens of church members Milling about the house of the
Martin said that after Oregon remove spiritual healing as a
The defense in 2011
Some followers of Christ church members moved to Idaho to escape scrutiny of their religious practices
Some people look at the Bible as applicable law
Jim Jones
Former idahosa
Supreme Court
Justice
Is also the Independent to Western Co
They don't like government telling them what to do
There is this feeling the parental rights are absolute
Religious freedom rights are at
According to the National Institute
Health and the journal Pediatrics quote
75 and 1995 172 children died following stealing
140 of them
From easily curable or treatable medical condition
In one case
A two-year-old girl choked on a banana
And showed Signs of Life for an hour before dying
Father parents
And other adults
Prayed
So the issue is that
It's not a real issue and I think these people did some really f***** up stuff
But
Some sort of like a
Terrorist training ground
Islamic
Faith followed
Is cockamamie bulshit
But even you said as we were starting it fit in your
Community
Do you grow up in
That this was something that happened
I don't know if that's
Really want
Taken care of
Watch YouTube.
They did not
They do not do anything other than murder a child
Well they've murdered that Chelsea years the property
Killed him this is where we get back to the least
Institute and the libertarian ideology
Because they don't believe that there is a
In affirmative
Obligation that you have to give Your Children Healthcare
Are negative consequence
You don't
Which is stupid
Twisted
Idea that you would
Rather watch
Child died
God's will ever
Everett
Accept metal
God will
It's your weakness
Same to me
That's true
Isn't like maneuver
Maneuvers hates
The Valhalla what's the one where you
Valsalva
The valsalva maneuver
Who killed upwards of two people than someone who sat around and watched
My two-year-old girl choked on a banana
I think the murderer
Slow in covering up the entire side
I mean I still think he was a f*****-up person but I can't imagine the level of f***** up you have to be to see a child
Who is like
Struggling
Friend hour
Choking on something easily dislodged from their throat
Well if they die they die
And then they go suck.
Move on
Understandably
Yeah so anyway
I don't want to go.
And also I should
Play with this is still developing
Yeah yeah
Was
Because they don't pose
Threat to society
Is mad about this idea that the judge let them go the reason is because
The state did not do a good enough job of proving the
You must let them go
So Alex if you believe in the rule of law you have to believe in that
Unfortunately
You have different
Standards for white and brown
You
Or only mad about this because
Enjoy
Which is
Inexplicably
He brings up
Well you would
Be talking about it if
Was a white family
You got plenty of options to talk about white families
Homeschooling their kids
Teaching them how to shoot guns and then watching them die
You got so many stories
In the white
Community
Garita a little bit of this article quote
The parents of a baby girl who died because she didn't receive medical attention in favor of Faith healing took a plea deal
Travis and Sarah Mitchell criminal negligent homicide
John Foote
District attorney for
Clackamas County
So I mean
Exactly the same thing
I mean they're going to jail
I don't like you described him as a nice white couple facetiously
Alex Jones
But
Congratulations Alex
Harkening back to his
We still get to keep that tapered of Muslims because that's become so
Keto
What do we got to do to
People that religion
I do I did
Unfortunately
I don't know
Now he's back on
Eggs
Oh boy I'll tell you what
Tell you what
This is
Disgusting
Is it real
We will reach
Greatness
When discrimination
And stereotyping against women 51% of our population
Long big wave app again
Commercial break
Completely caught off guard by lost in that
Too close to your Bernie Sanders if I could be honest
Offensive to mentally handicapped
You know why cuz it was Bernie Sanders played on like 3/4
And the Chipmunks too far
That's
Touch
Not nearly as bad as what happened
There is a war on
I like for a while I love to imagine
He was doing that through the entire house
Imagine that he had at least one stop
So is that a girl
Identity three characters for him I don't know
Elizabeth Warren
Weirdos weird
Pretending that the audience
Chipotle word nonplussed
Ford.com
My wife
I don't have a job to I was 40 years old government
Job
Are we this is Ruth Bader Ginsburg impressions
Volume
Or you
That's great
In the middle of the character by Dido that goes on even longer but
Because he's not good at making
Can points and juxtaposing in the same character voice
Supposing is this stupid guy
He brings his narrative about why Muslims are bad to women
And then bring the mirror
Did you graduate college
Will you do all one or all the other have it both ways
Because if it's all the things that America is
Great about for women
Then it's
But if it
See all the things that Muslims do that are bad
Conception
Colleges are there to brainwash
World
It does
Interesting things on
Yeah there's a lot going on there because he does
Credit countries
For having like a lot of women to go to college in deposit
Let's go to college
Yeah there's a lot of
You scratch right below the surface and
But none of this makes sense
I don't know who
Exactly that voices
Defensive to other than like
Eight or nine different groups
Whoops Pacific
People Cuomo
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
I'm going to go with
Anybody
Anybody anybody that doesn't speak English
New Yorkers for New Yorkers
Captive cord
I'm offended in the same way that
But
Is he doing great burning
I have to go to though
Alex
Lies a whole bunch
About things are going on
Nautical
Infowars.com
Prosecutors have reached an all-time low
Official government
Number people
Record
Quarterback to the acid attacks in
Really reasonable
We can get around
One of them is
Repeat offenders
Factory
They're dealing with less people in there are more crime
You can do with that
Also in the last couple of years in the United Kingdom
Do Dilaudid
The new recording policies
For the police
Emma's light to
Horizon
In reported crime
That we're going unreported before
In reported crimes that necessarily weren't all getting salt
Right if you look at it in terms of the United States you probably see very similar trend
In terms of
We've had Criminal
Reformed police officer
Administrative reform
How many times have you seen in the past
Letting a sex worker gets murdered
And they just
They say it's a suicide or something like that so they don't have to investigator into it doesn't work with her like
Instituted the
Policy or whatever
Police
Forces indifference
Said he's had to now like
Keep record of their
This whole thing
And rather than
They just wear like Willits cheapest
Quota buster
She said
Send a text of starch
A common narrative
Like it
Consistent through Alex Jones
Tommy Robinson
Olive
These people they always talk about
If so
F******
Regular
I've never really done too much looking into it I was
Assume that there are overinflated
But
From the BBC
There's a common understanding of acid attacks
UK to go something like this
Charisma
Both are South Asian
And I should point out here I looked into like
Official UK
A statistic
Asian tourist
Categories that include Middle East
Right they don't have a separate category for Middle Eastern that I have black
Which includes African and Caribbean
European
Asian ant mix
Those are the categories that they have in terms of official record-keeping
The conversation that needs to be had but not
I didn't I wasn't by the fact that those with categories
Sister but I don't run the UK
No I don't think the base for on ethnicity
So understanding
Gmail
And the violence has something to do with the so-called on
Distance released by London Metropolitan Police
The BBC provide a breakdown of every recorded acid attack
Over 50
Senior. Buy a gender ethnicity Borough
Hate crime and outcome
This is the fullest picture yet of the capitals
Suspect
And victims
Here are the stats that it shows
The Suspect with mail 74%
The time and the victim was male
67% of the time
With only one attack ever being related to the idea of
Regions of the world most attacks related genders
Executive director of assets
Survivors Trust
International
Often linked to reject
Sexual advances or marriage proposal
However this does not appear to be the case in the United
Acid attacks are on the rise in the UK though so what's causing it
This is likely to be related to a rise in moped
According to dr. Simon Harding
Associate professor of criminology at the University
3 West London
He goes on to say quote
We've had acid throwing in this country for over 200 years
And there's been a new development of it's at dr. Harding
But it's not new and it's not important
So it's just a phenomenon that apparently is a part of London crime
English crime
That is sort of
To our ideas as
Is something that's very common
To America
Almost like that
Like a certain point it becomes a thing that
Somebody
And then it becomes an option
For so many other people
To take
Sherp like
And it's like a fat
Well I mean like
Is the is my point there
From the data was able to find
Tickets Knotts
Overblown
But the number of people who end up getting
Not nothing
It's weird
Everybody all the time
It's weird but also that you see
Be here there be mail 67
The time is pretty counter
The Narrative right there
Propaganda
And the fact that it's not a uniquely as the British
Categorize it
Yeah
Should give some pause and make you think like
This is there's a difference
Story that you can tell here that's interesting
Look at ass away from
It's not so much like the Muslims are running a bucket jumping acetone
Which is what I was
Because that makes them into a Batman
Think I can't visualize this
Is any other way now then like a bunch of guys
Riding on mopeds
With a pot
It's filled with acid
Either that or now I see
Squirt bottle
You know like a l I thought you might like a super soaker
Yes
Super Soaker
Reinforced
2%
Isaac version of with probably a horrible reaction
Let's just feel this once more about sound
Solid dude
It's due.
Too many dudes
This is another thing that always brings up because control
Find a way to Savage
District
UK include knives broken bottles sharp objects
Right
I should note that the HBO series sharp objects
Caswell and
You killed anyone with a D
The nuts in there too
Blu-ray
According to official data from the UK
Knife related assault
But put things in context the 27th
Numbers
Higher than the level
In 2010
Further the rise for 2015 to 2017 code directly related with improvements police made in
That is another issue where you see an UPS
You can make a lot out of it if you want to
But if you get to the root of it you look for explanation
What'd you find
Is that
That's why there are more
Right
7 years ago is almost the same as now
Came back up
Then you have to explain why was it that high in 2011
Is it possible that there were deficient
Season reporting that happened
Over the last couple years
Interesting late there were 200
M16 knife related homicide
UK during the year 20
How many gun deaths were there in the
But that
But number
The 250
Knife related homicides
Netgear
Alex Price
Representatives like there's a giant UPS
Murder at 12
There were 12 more
Entire knife violence
Alright
Homicides is like
Well
So there's 215 22
16 to 27
Yeah it's only two more than there was
From 2015
There isn't
Really
Increase
Substantiv increase
Cindy's crime
There's only you can sort of cheese
Distance from
Come up with your own explanation
And that is way
Way more intimidating than
Actual
Something like all all night
Attack
They're up like 20%
Wrightwood again a lot of that could be attributed to specific
Recording
So some of that can be taken away from that some of that candy
Just be considered
Perhaps
There's a certain amount of it
Basically irrelevant
So you take away
No some of that person
Mnu taken
Look out that it's not just Muslims that are stabbing people right
Generally speaking
Dudes dudes
And then also
I mean statistically
We have the same issues here
The stats that you can get about offenders
Are generally
Who got arrested for things
Right
The higher incidence
So
You know it's
Kind of tough.
To figure out what the actual story
But from all the statistics that are available
It's not as big of a like
Wave of knives
All over England here's another issue
That's all that's all propaganda find a way to make Knives Out of acid work
Here's another
When you use 6% in America
Gun violence
America that means there's
4000 more incidents
In England as you pointed out in gun
2%
Is
To do
Like that's the kind of a homicide
Because we're so used to
So much bile
Small percentage
To us means so much more
Also just put things in a little bit of a broader perspective
215 knife related homicides
In the same year there were hundreds
16 that were just people got be
934 strangulation
Or
Edward Browning murder
Maps
Like what kind
Explain
I don't know the
And actually it might be too
It's 204
I didn't write that one down
Anyway
If you drown somebody
There's a certain amount of
Respect I have
There it is
Ineffective
Inefficient murder
A lot of stabs or like a really good staff
Received very consistent thing in Alex and terms
Supplying and missing the forest for the trees in order to
To demonize minorities
Expensive
Glorifying
White people steal more
So now we see these newer things
Like
If not being able to time his brakes
Right we see Genesis Communications ads coming in
And whatever the case is
Isn't that whatever
This next clip
Is where I was like
Alex's becoming his
His past self
Okay no way
Did anybody who listen
What year is that
And not be like
Visitin 28
What the f***
Of the information War Alex Jones
Merle Haggard
Distilling whiskey
Chrono
You love to sing along with us
Music
Bruce Willis
What was the name of that movie
The one with mr. glass
Send the news no news no news
It's crazy
He's been doing this for a decade
Cuz I'm listening to the feet
It's right that is very different
Yeah I'm not just creating something
I have not heard him sing along like that since the episodes that were listening to
I think Alex Jones
Getting like
I think you might be starting to come to terms with
The fact that like
He's back on his own Hunter I'm going to I'm going to be
What I was again
The best case scenario I'm going to be back to where I was 10 years ago
And that's why even Pancho and Lefty
PC Matic Lee is
Good song for him to be with police in them
He only
He's growing old his subconscious is coming out
You singing along
It's almost
Diegetic songs
His life
Viewmatic
Crazy man
I think he does
And I think he's hoping
It doesn't go bad
We can still do that
Cut it overhead
Get rid of that studio studio get back down to your basics
How many might have
We could always use a little bit of that
I told you earlier that I was
Going to say something correct about Reagan
Yes
The state hospitals in the early age
What
I mean
Whack jobs people
You ruined it but you did get it
Kind of got it
Now what
Is disgusting
But this is a reference to
New Mexico
Whack job
Complete
State Police
Because they're signaling their people do whatever you want go crazy or going to let you out
Just like that part 2
He said the left wants to release all the criminals to do out of micro mods
The best fish oil
Cool
Yeah
Krill oil
Look dude
Well done mediocre
Realizing he's up against the brakes
Timing is off
I believe
Parton Parton Parton
Partime earlier the dinner with
So what's left
The death penalty goes away
So whenever their operatives go out
I'm at the revolution they can get them out of prison
Which online
Like that plans
That's a long-term plan that's going to help
If there's a revolution
Get it run out of prison
The rules before stupid
I don't know
He's a guy who's only really
Notable anyway because he was pretty early Oklahoma City bombing
Skeptic
Let's say
Who claimed the same as you put out a report
Exclaimed that the bomb
They would have had
Would have been
Too small
An unfortunate
Other people have done reports that have been very
Physics
Measuring the craters happened to write
And they found it absolutely it
Adjust a discredited Oklahoma City
Dixie National General
Yeah I just looking for his career but from what I understand
The service
Really take into consideration to just because someone's like
A former FBI agent or an Air Force Colonel or general
That doesn't mean they're also not
A bunch of the people on Kerry Cassidy show
Have actually been in the service
A lot of a lying about it
Actually have been
Preclude them from
Also being
Opportunistic
I don't care
I don't know
Like when people talk it when people talk about
Provoking
Security clearance for the people
Welcome I don't give a s***
I think that's very
And the reason is because
Complicit
It's a it's not about John Brennan losing his secure
Clarence
It's a message to other people who might
Speak out against
Any other way
I'm going to get rid of other people
It is
Threat from a desperate
I will
Cuz it's not just
Going to take clearance away from people who already are who are still in the job
They can't do their job
You know
Weird
Right
That's one of those things
That you don't know
Until it happen
I didn't know the president could just
Do that
I guess you can
Like is that a thing he can do, why couldn't
I don't know
I don't know why he
You could
It seems like a randomized
Did somebody just
Whitney be able to just be like all right
F*** you
We had normal checks and balances
Weird check we were planning on playing the weird
That's why
The Constitution people calling it like a
No you don't you don't get it
People are
F*****-up did they'll find a way to do some weird-ass ship but
Even imagine that
What president what person would founding fathers writing the Constitution
Well
Eventually we're going to have top-secret Clara
We need a plan for that
Constitution
Until we got to
We tried the village we tried the articles
The confederation
That had
0 security clearance
No Provisions that the president of the United States
Probably like America
You know what's really fun about it
Yeah I think that we do have a problem and that we probably do need to
In some ways
Is the Constitution
Now
But the problem
Again..
The idea of being able to change it
Never having another amend
Is crazy
Yeah it did
Constitution is set in stone by virtue of the fact that we can agree on
Absolutely
I would agree on that
Because people need
Who did need to be jostled into the reality
Like this system
Is stupid and untenable
But anyway
This next clip
I got to say
Blue my mind
Because
This
Infowars made
This together as a bumper
To come in from Commercial Way
And I don't know what the f*** they were thinking
Not your mother's talk radio
Alex
As v-neck
Little bumper coming in
Kicks in
That is nuts realize how
Very close that is to the
Drop we have for the rep
Makes me think you might want to try that
The other the other
Play sing-along
But it's so close
You make me think of do me and like
I'd like that more than anything he's done in the past two years I'll tell you that right now whoever is behind the scenes
Not together or something like that
The impulse
Estranged
Especially since that ends with like there will be fire you're going to hell
Really long interview with sibel Edmonds
Episode metal care to talk about it
Are the people who will still go on his
The show I don't think that a lot of
She she was a 911 whistleblower
Her story is really complicated
Highway from it a little bit is that a lot of
She is a legend
I'm already in
Report
Should have not been made public
So they're like a lot of things
She's asserting about
Confidential document unreleased by size
I'm an end so I just don't care
How to get into it because I
Really
Figure out the veracity of a lot
But to talk about
Antibiotics
Erdewan
How do you say flood
Muslims into Europe
Stuff like that
Hey Michael Flynn
Just wanted to
And the other thing is
Is it that I don't believe in
Scenario any world
Trump didn't know about that
Or there was
I'm some sort of like
Tacit approval
When we're at with our two wanted
Extradite
Still like the idea that they are now
Like Alex is now
Talking all this s*** about turkey
I get why
But you have to reconcile that with the fact that according to your worldview
When was secretly
You fighting this war against
The globalists in the islamists and one of the things he was doing was working for the other one
For now presenting is a horrible dictator
Flood
Europe with Muslim
Because it's in response to Trump being like you should probably
To go cuz he really didn't orchestrate that coup
Which lesbianas
Erdewan
You know
I know we didn't happen
When working for Venezuela now to bill
If you're white you're working for Brazil's f******
Ludacris government drive too far down
That well cuz
It's irrelevant.
Dolphin Reef
Up here all night
Suffice
And I don't care cover that interview because
It would take too long to try and parse out like why where's your where's your lying
He's mostly just talk about it
Because it's another way to
Some of the Roundup of stories
One of them
Is about to have someone
Out there is standing up for Infowars
That's important news
Tucker Carlson graduated
Yep
AR-15 are back one viral
Girl challenges all Apple Store devices to show infowars.com protest
Censorship
Video
Alex Jones Infowars from their it
Infowars.com
Everybody that stuff like that it will totally blow up in their face big time
No
She's doing now because like
In the last couple days
She posted on Twitter her outside of that school the promise school that LeBron James
Has come out and said
He's going to
Going to pay for college
Yeah stop for the parents
Some stuff like that
It's so she went to the school
She posted a picture of herself outside with the microphone
About how she's going to get to the bottom
Who's paying for the school
Hint it's not LeBron James
Which everyone started dunking on her because
It's a public school
No no he's not paying for the school
No for the kids at the school
And if they graduate paying for them
Bread
Which is even more admirable because it is going
To be funded and run
It's almost like a
It's a it's a public-private partnership that is
Very fascinating and it'll be really excited to see how it works out
Because
She's trying to
Is so
Stupid
Like it's like
You could just
Look at the definition of look at what the school is
Look at what LeBron James
Is claiming he's doing what his plan is
You couldn't find fault
With that unless
All you want to do is trying
Teardown of black man who's criticized daddy president
She's been about except for
Walking around and trying to get Instagram famous with guns
For her entire us short
Impressive career
And now she's
He's doing the Infowars which
It's not surprising at all
Congratulations Kaitlin Bennett
You are a disaster
And this is another thing
She's so young
This is something that I
Hope that she'll feel bad about later
Miss White
Really is hard for me to make fun of her
Continue through make a lot of mistake
And these are big
Peter big
Very public mistake
And I pray that you learned your lesson
Not learned her lesson like
She learns her lesson is able to
Live a healthy full life
After this
Because this
Don't go good places
Jim have a career after this other than being like
Maybe she gets to be another Tommy Lauren
And then just give
Dunked on
Constantly
Is a shill engine
Is the pretty face
Propaganda
It's not
It's a sad
A lady
Weeded
Dumb
Racist joke
And God
Plane
And then when she landed
She was not allowed to be
Be part of cyst
Society anymore
And
These people are allowed
Best banana
It's weird I don't know why
Actually going to give you
Bananas
What do you mean
0 most done here
And I know you're tired
I want to unwrap
Be up all night
But
Before we go
Alex thinks that everyone's taking him out of
And I actually kind of agree
To a certain extent
I believe that I watched the entire clip of him talking about have your battle rifles ready
And I know it's violent language
Prepare people for the idea that violence
Was probably necessary
Advocating going out in shooting
And people who are construing
I think it's a little bit
Unfair to him
He brought it on himself in this is exactly the reaction
But the news is covering in saying that he has viola
Stuff like that
I do think you could
Construe it that way
I think that is one interpretation
That is fair but Alex
Construe it that way that's not what I
Google so
To say
Sew in
In response to that
The media all they do is take one or two words
And Karma
And make me save Mad Lib
Which is a sort of complaint
Whenever people are actually talk
Wichita
Revealed
Descriptive
Deceptive
It's not a pedophile Lisa 90
Children and molestation cases
He just read quotes
He didn't say that
I got chills up my spine
Chemical Guys
Never said any of that
And their stories
Fill in the blank
They don't even have the words to put it together
Show
This isn't even
Here's an example
We combine those words
Let's use the same technique and see what Lester Holt
Criminal charges
I'm all ears
That's f***** up
I mean there's no other way to slice that
That's really f***** up
I get what he's trying to do and I get the
Point he's trying to make
Stupid ways to do that than that
I don't think it is audience
Understands necessarily the points
What he's doing in might listen to that I'd be like
Pedophile
I bet
I just heard that
I know he probably thinks
Itsfunneh
It's not
He probably thinks it's
Clever
It's not
And like we could do a much better version of that
With Alex
If we wanted to
I mean pecan already stealing our bed
He's been stealing our bit but doing it's so terrible
I don't really care
I think that a lot of this boils down to I don't really care
I'm really fast
Needed by the reversion
De Pasto
I think I would like that to continue
I would too
Much more in
Interesting
And not liking
Vikings the show better man
This more human
To a repetition of
Anger and bigoted
I kept listen specifically because
Justice
Genius
Absolutely
Okay
Donald Trump criticizes
Criticizing no wires and telling truth
You're the ones calling you do it the same
Program
Prepared still obvious
What year
Infowars.com
So what he's done is create a preemptive Justice
Application for something that you probably think
Is a very good high likelihood sort of thing which is attacking journalist someone.
Or something like that
He's now created The Narrative ahead of time
That all you guys are going to false-flag yourselves
So you look like the victims ahead of the midterm
Thereby clearing the conscious
Any of his wonderful great
Americana listeners
And militiamen
Murder somebody and they go
It has nothing to do with our rhetoric
Galati's guns and then letting them
It's not that
We can continue doing everything we want to do
Further its
The reason I say it's brilliant is because on some level I think Alex has to know that
You know if I were a betting man I would say someone's going to attack us
Has any kind of
Cover for yourself
You better have that narrative in place that like this fake they're doing it to themselves cuz they're all
Spaces for their way
And I know they just need pity
From people or else they're not good
Going to work and so
Themselves
And we're cool
I think that sucks
I think it's very lame
It's very smart
Your someone like Alex
Because
That might help you not get sick
So we've come to the end of this now
No
I still hate him in the present
But it's much more interesting when we are diamond gusset commercials
It's always better when we have.
Alex sing-along to Pancho and Lefty like he has so many years ago in the past
And then this weird wrinkle of him not being able to prepare for break
I think there's something going on
I'm not sure what it is
I don't care that much
In terms of mysteries I want to solve
That's not high on the way
I don't know why
We would talk to me
I don't
I don't because because
No no I mean like any kind of truck
There's nothing to say because what they are doing
Is
Implicitly recognizes
That what they're doing is wrong
And the way they justify what they're doing
Is by claiming that
The left is doing it
Or the other side is more wrong
Doesn't matter it does not matter what it is you say to them
Nope because all of that is
Is part of their paranoid fantasies
It gives them
To commit the evils that they are accusing you of committing
To continue funk
Like we are we are
Constantly talking
Can two people
Who are infected with this brainvire
And cannot
Ever break free
Unless there's something so there's some sort of
AAA
Lego Civil War breaks them out of this inertia
Because it's not going to happen
Talkington
You're right you think that and generally speaking that might be
But there are people who have
Forgotten
You know there are means that it's possible
So I don't think you need that occurred
Stream of a situation maybe you needs
Something
Stream
Like someone has to have a moment of
Crisis
Poop
What what is
What is behind the rhetoric
That might be extreme in an individual's life require a civil war
I mean it's
The way that they will take it
But if their needs
To be a national
Some sort of crisis
That jostles these people out of it
Sure and I don't mean the Civil War
To be some sort of
No matter what the outcome of the midterms are I think
Next year year-and-a-half or so
Will start
Still out of the
Coming home to roost
Action
There's more time you'll see more of the
The trade War stop not really work out in our favor
You'll see
You'll see people being
Banned from the country
As we're already
You'll see all these
Trends that are already
Germinating
You'll see the plant
Start to grow
Test case of
And this is something that's been reported on
For years now but
The people on whatever island it is
The island is sinking
Specifically because of climate
And they all voted for
And none of them believe in climate
Like it doesn't matter what's going on they're even there's their lives and they're just still
Trump is great
You can apply that to everybody
Yeah yeah
I know
Be a little more optimistic
I don't know I don't know
We can't predict the future
All we can do is inoculate people from this weekend's virus
All is calm
You can follow us on Twitter and I was on Facebook
I have a group called domicile your mother your brilliant you can go to iTunes and ignore Alex
Podcast
Is it my turn
I don't know there's
So many people
Like what's that horrible woman's name Caitlin Barnett
She can go f***
Agree with that
Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work