Holding
Alex
Little bit
What up how do you feel about the Big Bang
Rip them up for Financial Protection Bureau is unnecessary
Never been more aligned with Alex Jones
Homes for the wrong reasons so I want to crush the bank
Because it's groovy out of a couple bucks.
That's all it takes to get me to completely become a guy
You think that's part of the Yeah Yeah Yeahs
God it's so brutal it's so brutal to be poor and then has the bank
F*** you
Experience
Nobody even happen
It happened to me in the past before 2 and it's just it
Feel so shity there's like nothing you can do
They don't give a fuk about you they don't care
Their fault
They made a glitch and now you don't have your money
My soapbox for hey I got screwed out of a couple bucks
Absolutely don't want to create a like some sort of
We're talking about
F******
Come up over the course of this episode
Generally what we talkin about is how I know a lot about Alex
Tell me about Alex
Jordans
To quote
Mount
I try
Open the movie
I try to stay away from modern-day Alex Jones but I wish I could quit
So today we're in the car
We are going to go over the August 21st
2018 episode
I meant
Before it was over the course of the app
Afternoon
In the world of world you know with Michael Cohen pleading guilty to
Equally striking
Adeel wherein he implicated
The president in court hilarious
Could be considered my money is on
Middlesex standall interpass
Like first of all the court in court.
And then also
You know said it was for the
Like for the sake of
Election
Ikea
Besides those
Hey I'm guilty because of campaign Finance
Fried and
Some guy
Is that a lion and I was alone with him
Paul manafort was found guilty on eight out of 18 charger
He has another trial coming up where am I
It's so like there's a lot going on that I don't know if you were following the Donkey
Can Hunter ask
Paid
I don't remember his name because that
Name some made-up the filing against
Taking campaign funds
For personal expenses people have
Dunking on him because of all right
Be specific things
That are in the in the filing.
32nd and tiny little expenses that he stole things from
Before
Eventually
There's a lot of bad stuff
Conservative
Broke
In the afternoon
But I wonder if Alex
Knew it was coming
First of all he talks about any of it as a break
Bright on air when those
Staff is like at least check
Twitter every
To get in there
See if there was any
That's why we're still in the
Most troubling clip
That we have ever played on this show
2 years into the show
We played
So many f****** Clips better deliver this empty
Either is no way for this to fall play we have played clip
Where Alex admits that he spoke to Russian intelligence when I thought it was
We have heard him talk about killing dog
We have talked about
Larry Nichols coming on the show and straight-up blackmailing Congress on the radio
None of that compares to the clip that I'm going to play you in the middle of the show
I am not teasing the tooth much
You guys are going to love it
It made me gasp
I almost
Threw something across the room
Trump killed dog
No no
You kill my dog
The same time it makes perfect sense
That guy's crazy man do anything to do with dog in front of me
Psychopath
Crazy
So before we getting today
Give a special shout-out to new donor this young lady
The show and sent us back to the delightful little games
Congratulations Catherine you are now a globulin
Natalya brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Thank you so much thank you so much
Or any of our weirdo title
That we give people arbitrary and we will just be playing
Play glass
I found another thing to add into
I think I could make a new
Clip
Maybe I don't know
Extra
Appreciate it
$30
Text devastate you have that is like my life is not good
I was walking away from the bank earlier
There's other ways I can be living
This is a tight wire racks on I'm walking here
Go back
We are doing
August
First
From today's episode
We go out and get you the most concentrated insane very back on the market
That's a real angry sales pitch
One bad door-to-door sales
Level I don't want the vacuum
Excuse me sir
How dare you
Alright
A boy
Give you a little bit
Videos like
Good pretty desperate
Who's the back to refund
Looking forward to when you and Alex are unequal economic footing we're going to be about
Just sitting there looking shots
Call timer
I kind of believe that in like 20 years
You and Alex are really going to be the only people who understand I think so too
Already are
Cross
Yeah I don't know
Content creators
Sure
Broadcast
Yeah on Mondays episode covering
Disgusted the beginning of it
Partisan hack
And he's declaring that this next election
Is the most important of our lifetime
Doubles down on that a little bit at the open
Today Show
Argue the most important election in world history
For the battle
The future of humanity
Ragtag groups of individuals who love God who have million-dollar Studio
Complicated even though
Even the rebellion in Star Wars could afford x-wings come on
Diamond gusset stickers on this excellent
What is the biggest issue that I have with the World Star Wars is it there's no
Anywhere on the Rebellion
Product
In that world
Other than
I don't see any name brand
I might have missed
Study those Star Wars
Is there a Sierra Mist in that world
Sure
Palpatine
The midterm elections
Before Christ
Coderre Alex
Talk out his own favorite guy George Washington
What's second time
Default
To do
You know what it's like it's like in baseball anything before black people allowed
F*** Babe Ruth I don't need that which is exactly what I feel like with
The president
F*** it
Get the free and fair election at the end of the day
Everything's got Asterix all over X
Turn up
How did the Hall of Fame is no doubt
I don't want to I want to break this down
Throughout
Hitler that's another 1,000
Nothing I think it was probably when pooping one last
97% of the vote
To win with only 96% of the vote
And he outperform Landslide Landslide victory
A mandate is what that is
I think Alex is a little bit
Screwed
His little bit
It's all good
I played a baby
And that's what he doesn't
He plays his game
Pretty fun
We could probably take him up on this but it's absolutely not worth our
That's why I'm offering a $1000000
We need this
Contact we needed
There is no video
Its total
Lester Holt
Criminal activity
The judicial system
That's not quite right after anybody who can
You claim that he's like
Threatening the media and being really violent about them
I could win that
In a second
Throughout this episode quite frankly there's no video or clips
Give me saying
Take the battle rifle Fairplay Alex but whatever you're looking
42u
Either going to give them
It's a it's a hopeless Quest
But
We could we could definitely put together
Private more time was yelling at a bank called I probably could have put together a super clip of him threaten
It happens a lot more
But
You should know that they're lying
And that's why he's comfortable with his million-dollar offer that he opted
Which is exactly why testifying
Correct
To correct
Dino's as we talked about on the last episode
Because the media is about to false-flag them
Themselves
In order to blame the Patriots
Which is why again it's fine for the Patriots to go out and murder everybody at the
His opinion that Alex has decided to
Turn into one of his main talkingpoi
Everyone
American people
You can see it
And I told you you know firestick
Open Water
Houses burn down
That's funny
To do it
That's great that's not bad
The crazy neighbor is saying that
You are going to burn down his house
Beforehand
Or something like that
It has nothing to do with your house
And then he burns his own house in order to frame you for
Help your houses birthday
Is metaphor doesn't really hold
It kind of makes no sense
I don't expect
Make much sense because
Preemptive narrative building
So when something does happen
The shot of the journalist
Alexander
Conscience
It's it really
Really f****** disgusting
To know that in League with the guy who is saying that the media is our enemy
And they should be destroyed
Is the guy who saying don't worry about it because the media is doing it to themselves
Like what are you
You f******
Talking about
The definition of gaslighting should something
And even if it doesn't
But you don't
We don't really get to know the
Private goings-on
These journalists but a lot of time
Brett they've gotten
And things like that and you'd
Just have to extrapolate in your mind
How much more is it
That you don't
When people have to deal with that a whole lot
And they shouldn't when you consider when you factor in the
Matthew
Massive Rising hate crime
That have been committed
Trump was allowed to
Speak out loud German study
About that Facebook
Merkel Merkel who-knows-what
Keeping it away REI
Broad Strokes of bounds even if you separate
Sorts of other demographic
Features like
Class
Income brackets race
Political affiliation
They found it in place
Where
Facebook usage was one derivation
What's the typical derivation away from the center right
Then the incident
So they did like what a regression analysis that said that there is a correlation
It's not causation
Indicate that no matter what where you fall on the lot of Spectre
The inundation of b******* online
Radicalized
So I don't know
They don't communicate with
I think that makes more sense
Yeah we need to wolof Chicago
That would be an interesting for him to lose weight
Yeah
F*** Gary Indiana we got to get rid of those guys
Perhaps
You know what that actually might solve our gun running
It's true
There's no way that people run guns from one state to another
Would get around that
Impossible
Your idea for Illinois politics
Evolution
Another disintegrate
Use but I have to do this kronologic
Craziest clip
I think I've ever heard a little bit
Dog scream over there
Google
Google would love to have me arrested and killed
We got to go from the town Google Google
Kill
Technically one guide
Cheers bar
A guy that you want to hear
Technically I didn't kill
Technically
Finish the job and did you hear how it almost sounded like you said a few
You years ago
Was to it wasn't like I
You f****** killed a guy so he got so here's what I'm hearing out of that until I got fight of some
Health problems
Alex
Exact murder that guy
Alex killed a guy
Specifics
Kind of irresponsible
Accept what we can say is
By his own
I think you killed a guy kill the guy
Responsible for a murder
I feel like they should be a lot more going on if you go
Glycogen
I didn't
But but
You would never have brought it up and gone down there road if there wasn't some
Kernel of something in the back of his mind I did do that I am responsible
Murderer
Bart Lisa manslaughter
Children
He's a mass murderer by the owner
Alex is the serial killer we always assumed that he was
Throwing
Are killing dogs and that's the natural
Sort of jumping off point
For the first thing that you see
Absolutely
I'm I'm willing to
You credit as
Murderer Alex
So we got to start back over the beginning of eclipse
Because I think
The craziest clip I've ever heard
Is
The confession of murder
Like I think there's a part of his brain Psych
I meant you can
Turning kind of
Any jump
To like
I'm going to distract everyone so they don't realize what I just forgot
Google Google would love to have me arrested and killed
Technically one guy
Alex Jones was mean to the Sandy Hook family
Democratic
Kill the guy
Alright
It's like he's about to fall off a
Forklift
And then
New grip
Exactly
And hold any like alright alright I can climb I can climb from here
Gene Wilder's the ghost of the guy that killed waiting at the bottom
I'm just staring like
Holy s*** right
Who did he kill
No
Murder stays murder
Tell that story
God
Also recording
Coast AM
And if I'd heard this clip
Before that
You bet your ass I would have called in
Gildedguy
So holyshit
We need to know more about that I don't know if we'll ever get to the bottom
Congratulations Alex you just admitted on-air that
You probably killed a guy
He killed a guy if you are the guy that Alex killed please call 503
Yeah also by the way
I know
I forgot to do that at the top of the
I remembered we have a call
Listen to like
Jinx moment that's what is like
I don't know I did
From the podcast
Very few
Once again so that's
Cleanse our love
We got a very awesome
Is Alex mazzoni a killer
Maybe we did not get a call from Chico
Nor did we get a call that Alex killings
Somebody
We've got our first
International message
Hello
I'm just calling to say thanks
Airport
You can show that you do
It's that very helpful
Tuesday's at work so that's good
I know I'm probably
Tell you come here and do it live
Anyways that was about it. Just
Diminished expectations
Coming out your view of Europe
Country code
Is that why
Time support of the shower
You're the best
To hear your voice also
Why didn't you tell us about Allie
Killer guy Sonia you knew it if you can call a miracle you could have figured that s*** out way in advance
I thought that we were doing that to get us off
Excellent topic is hard to move on
Bananas so now let's let's try our best
Deal with it
Now we see Alex through the prism of murder
Prism of murder
Supremacy part of his rhetoric
What is Wikipedia
New layers of
And I don't know if there's any more
Gildedguy
How do we defeat him is the same person anymore when he's drunk
For Lauren it's no longer like
Some guilt
Over killing a guy like hardcore
Him after killing a guy
Excused
He doesn't give like a little bit of sleep because you
He's too busy working on the Infowars because
Someone jokingly
Assume that he had killed a guy
It is still jarring to hear that him say
I killed
Not technically
Yeah
Goodyear Auto f****** radio show man you just say I've never killed a guy no one's going to be like yes you have
I okay
Killed a guy with my car
Technically the health problems so drunk I was in the passenger seat
The time until problems all right
Temple murdered
Alright okay so now
Will get on to another topic here in that is Alex
Completely lie
About what is very clearly a timeline about
George Soros
Using a mouse Playbook
You think they're playing games
Playing games they're funded by collaborator
But it would be the MacNeil Lehrer hour back then but also
You didn't know about Soros
Before you didn't know about him
Since you were at
Velvet
Bulshit
Even 2090 list
All of his arch globalist his main enemies
Soros has never come up
I found one clip
Brings up George Soros
Alex
Doesn't register it at all
And bring them up is not even as IQ
It's just that he's a rich dude who doesn't agree with
He's not even in terms of like
He's a mastermind
Alex Smith
So
He's known about him as some sort of monster who overthrows
Piece of his
So I like that
I like that
Alex
Ironic defense
China
The mouse Playbook
So that kind of undercut
Flickr
The 48 special
Call swagtron
That's what I be great
Manta Resort Birdsboro
Oh yeah that's right we still haven't written a book that's supposed to make us money
Almost hit book-length
You don't have to buy
Yeah we're great
Anyway
He's not done talking about Sora
Unless episode talked about how
For Lauren to get him on SNL
Alex Smith
Free characters
Ed Sanders that are very very close
Are witches dicey at best yeah we're always remains tonight bring up that thank you
McDonald's
I take your order
It Direct
He's doing is a
The commercial from the
From McDonalds where there was a guy with Down Syndrome
McDonald's
Answer that is what
He's making fun of
Which makes it even more of a
To fair when we make fun of how bad that impression
Bring into it that he's making fun of
Man
He sucks
But how much better and worse of places
But it wasn't
Yeah
Jordan
We now have his third care
Yes
We have yet like I said
And now
George Soros
Lightly meat
Dracula
I'm disposed to rollover some crazy Nazi Collaborators
Woodstock battery worshipping you
It was happy making time
And I would help round up
I'll say
Right now
Not the worst impression
He's like
Right right I mean the content of it is
Hot bowls
He's in the ballpark of Hungarian
It's not too far off
Not
Dizzy
I don't like I don't like the mixing up
This is Beth at 2
Know that
Quality
Better
Done so much worse
And he's about to
In my life
Dracula's Forest
Chocolate
Is this delicious Pro Star Wars references
Germany
But not Soros
He doesn't get shipped
Pizza Man
Because he wasn't a Nazi
Hey Alex
Are you mad
Are you mad about that
I don't know why
If you're not see why are we deporting all nothing because we would get rid of
If we go for that argument I'm I'm listening
I'm listening right right sure sure we can do
Bye
If your Arc
Argument is
Why are we getting rid of it get rid of George Soros
I would say
Very substantial
He's not a Nazi never was
Right
It does make it seem like he does
Want that old guy deported
If his argument were
Like let him die
Then I'd listen
Probably not worth it to go through the rigmarole of deporting him
On the other hand
He's a f****** not see it if he's uncomfortable at 95
Yeah
I agree
Logistical argue
But I don't give a s***
And I also I'm not Charmed by arguments that are like why we deported this guy when we could do more
Profit loss statement
You got your losing more money to put in the guy that you would be if you just left him alone but
How to unlock
Sure sure
Yeah
Anyway
Alex
The world has become so f***** up that the feel-good story
Well at least we got one Nazi out of here or like 56 years ago it was
Tranquilized bear falls out of
Everybody can feel great about
You yell at me over
Circle.com
That's not good that's a sign of a bad times
No
Also that's a that's a real bad scoreboard for us in the Nazis
Still
We return to Havana president
Knows that
He is a man
You do that
So he's a man
He's not afraid
Like a
Monstrous idea of a
He's like bonecrusher
He's never scared
That's what I'm talkin
Globalist
But he's not afraid of them
Rambles about it
What
Sonata
Serious
Chivalry like that iodine baby
I don't want to be with you
Jesus Christ
And the father and the Holy Spirit
Across the world
This is our last chance
And Trump is a final
On the way to hell
Now at the end
Did Trump is good
In some way because
Eagles of liberalism or whatever that you have you only get two
Did Trump when you're really close to hell and hear that
Is Trump is a warnings at like
Take me down
That's where he'll go reference
Guess what
You're in my world now f*** off
Real weird
It's about like not being afraid and all this
Recite
That's Tuff
It's coming after they weird Soros Dracula impression
I'm just sitting here listening to this sound like
Why are you doing the show anymore
I enjoy it
Very very go
Murderers that we never know what we're going to find under that rock
Don't know if
Going to keep
Give me excited oh yeah
More
I don't want to seriously 1925 swear to God you two are the only people who understand
That's my mission is to
Just know I just wrote the best no Max
No no no
What is Hannibal
You're the only person he'll talk to you anytime
Alright I want a fish-out-of-water comedy where you take a your first entry level job at info
Hours and you're all trying to navigate your way to the
The top
It's great
Open for somebody who claims that he wants to go towards good energy
I'd be ever put out any positive energy on a show ever
Music
Marijuana arrest
What I mean like
Positive positive outcome
That's not a positive energy
Oh no
You know like there's never been a situation on his show
I actually feel good bro like when he even be yells about loving life in
And stuff like that it's
OK Google
Yeah
I don't know but you know
Someone about it
Yeah good as chakras
Mysticism
Use for a little bit later
Before we get there
Yeah who knows being amiss
Is talking about the devil
Is the final course
Your choice
Ermine
They're right
Honey
Chiweenie financial support
Future Telltale Grand specials
Special special
The same ingredients slightly different bread
Free shipping on it
Put Doritos
You guys you guys sign up for auto shipping
We're going to toss in a Year's worth of food
You know what
But you had survival food
Something between
How do I get my life involves like
Oh yeah this guy
Who's
Before this show the only guy that buckets was f******
Colonel Sanders dance
That's good
I don't mean that sarcastically
The timing wasn't right for me to last but I feel bad about it but I enjoyed
You're the
Bradstreet weather every mother's over here
I'm letting this go I'll just let this go away
With the brothers
Yeah
May I read a book about the
Those guys
Rockstar
The real cool
I recommend their biography they f*** a lot
Perivascular
Dick Smothers
God he must have
Killed a lot of people with that dick
Text Lyle.
The balls
Alright
Sina.com
I deserve that
Emmett next flip
Is that
The 2nd hour
But
What I couldn't tell if Alex
David Knight with taking over
Because he played a like
4minute long
Promo
The real news
Because it's the only one you can still find anywhere in the promo of it
Dick goes from like
I'm doing an introduction
Love your host
David Knight real news
Promo
Package
Involved
Coming in from break
Import of his real ship
What is going
Is very confused
But you didn't
The news is probably the only thing I
He's not sorry snowflakes Panhandle true eStore hose
Peanuts dharius snowflakes can't handle this s*** bro
Everyone can handle David night shift yeah I think so
Still allowed on all of these platforms
Everyone even
Even everyone who is
Piling on with Alex's light
David Knight
Usually no one can
0 there's no positive or negative he's just there has mostly most of his appearances Alex trying to
Also David Knight talking a lot about the
The fourth turning
Charge that philosophy that Steve Bannon
Describes to a lot
I read an interview with the
The guy who put that Fort Knox drives
Cuz he died in
Like how
Explaining
And they're not
They're not in favor of what Trump is doing
Necessarily
Lexus
These are not
They kind of lead to like this Behavior
That's being demonstrated by Trump is a naked
You think it only
More
Of the crisis
Everything believe this entire time is invalidated and
180 degrees from what
Trump is actually doing and they don't care
What would happen if Alex Goes On
David choe
Is it would you do that
Kicked off everything
You think so
I think it was a slow roll
On a
Because David Knight
I don't think he had as much
Sort of traction
As much exposure
Sounds like that was coming
From posting posted on
Infowars
So when
Taking away his
Entirely
So even if the show is Bill searchable on
XYZ I still don't think it matters
You crippled by
The same band
So I don't know
Stealth movie
Slowly take over David
That's not terrible
For the second
Kill everybody give me like
I mean we got him once let's just ignore him from here on out and then
Slow you just like an hour of your show no big deal
Fundamental problem is that Alex doesn't want to get on air
Good morning that is a big
Couldn't get out of bed
I agree that the only decision Alex
Is made in a long time that I
I don't like regular
Interview but I forgot there was this one clip that
Pretty interesting
About David
Contest contest but he ended up moving down here from North Carolina
When is family
Sweltering Texas
Orchard
Help change the world
Anniversary because I've been trying to shut him out and destroying
There's no real subscriber
He's a Dave Holmes of Infowars
Win the contest and yet he got his own are you telling me that there was a Jesse Camp
David Knight in this
Metaphor is
Mike TV in Willy Wonka
No but you know what I think
Lee Ann McAdoo
Well I know that you want a contest in order to become an Infowars reporter I know that
I really don't like the whole contest at
Captive whether or not you
You should die
F****** contest
Major what is
Play song contest
Unreliable
Unreliable you're looking for
Consistency for predictor of
Talent that's not good I don't know if you've ever been to Comedy contest
Not necessarily a measurement of quality or skill
At Deja Vu in Columbia Missouri
Yeah
And I lost
But I was on
There were two
Musically
Guitar comedy
That
Naruto was a friend of mine
Macadam cuzzo
Seem like I was cheating on him
But
So he wasn't there when the first
Guitar Aquanauts know
Wasn't entirely guitar but one of the
Is Big B
Was he would do a cover of Hey There Delilah
The other guitar cover
Allegra versus but
The chorus was
You got some big
What's
The first guitar Act
It wasn't exactly the same
Like I said oldroyd showed up
After that
No
And none of us who knew him
Knew that he was going to do that act until he was walking towards stage with his guitar no
It doesn't
Usually goes really well at that club
Clubfoot
The people who are in The Comedy Room
We're just under age
People who knew that they could
You have to go to the show before the party downstairs
Upstairs with comedy clubs
Business is honest
It was mostly drunk 18 year old
Who are in the audience
Look in his face when he gets
And doesn't Hey There Delilah cover
I think he's getting nothing
But confused
Looks from the audience
It was one of the best days of my life
Incredible incredible
Incredible story thank you
Missouri
Do things you can take away from
So I'm getting wistful
Because David night is come up
Hey we got em.
Alex Jones
With some of my favorite intro music
Super misplaced on his show
Good morning
Goodbye for children
Bring up the school
And I was exhausted and I was tired
Brush my teeth
Whiteface
Exhausted and I just never looked better
I just agree strongly disagree
No
Great as much as I'd like to
Busy look amazing.
Yeah
You got to stop playing Baltimore
That's ridiculous
I just want him to play a song and then
With The Highwaymen
Completely different song
Super gay
Lowlife
On my own like Tarzan Boy
The otter
Maybe he's really got some pipes
Monkey Business
You got to be so great
You do like right before the
Monkey Business
Jungle life
Love this
So good
So it's been speculated on our Facebook
Listen to our show
Because we have diamond
Commercials
Sing along with country music
The last episode the things that make us happy
Seems like a little bit of a
Bright
Everybody quit makes me sick
It might be something because the other thing that we really love
Is when Alex gets
Esoteric
And I think he's doing a little bit of that
That's because
And I just know I studied history
That's not really
This is so close to that guy who was on Jim Bakker Show
Baker was talking about there was
There was Alex about know before World War 1 there was that giant eclipse
Just that I like
Truly
Place where none exist
Absolutely
Buttock
Middle Country
Thermostat
Call Charlie
Let's be clear
He's talking about coincidence
Describing is
You're looking inside the window and you see for Birds but then for a week
Tina burden
AC for birds
You receive for cars
Get ready for cars going down the road maybe I care about people traveling together what a weird thing
But he doesn't get into message
Stop light
See all those cars
Name of the lights
Turns green
Bless cars go weird
He's not intimate
Traffic pattern
Fluid dynamics
As Above So Below
I just shot up in my chair and I went
With all these World changes going on all these Wars all this is Tik-Tok
Literal planetary alignment
I do have a touch
Maybe some big volcanoes maybe some big stuff taking off
Next few months and I need the bigger
Okay so we got a prediction there
But also Alex kill the guy and of psychic major thing
Story about son
Dreams where you the prophet or whatever the f***
Where you at the goddamn
Cuz you never believe it if it wasn't grounded in the I'm annoyed by my son wanted to take a shower
Either way now I just feel creepy about thinking about us out of the shower now
You've already heard a couple times you talked about like
For kids
He's kind of really ramming home that he has
I feel like it's kind of like a
People who make fun of them
Dream about the future
I'm not into mystical s*** also I have the touch
What
2 minutes but I should tell you for my entire life I've been able to tell the future
You stuff we did see him say that he had a prophetic dream and stuff yet
Kind of on a level that you can be like
Alright that's a one-off
Some sort of a weird vision
Bin Laden was involved with the original bombing he said he was going to do it again
Kurt Angle is going to happen
Does not require proper
But
Alex Jones
Was on Costa
Coast AM last night
Talk about a prophecy
But the other guess
Was talking about
So I think he might have listened to the other gas and it was Dora
I think there might be
It's so jealous
Send Patty and pathetic
Because I
Jungle life
Record a cover of that just as Alex
In Alex's voice
Karaoke track
Coming soon
So
Oh man
And you put it out there on the Arabic
Party props
Get on Aaron taco
I'm so it leads to
Just say that he has
Jeff he did literally
What is that
He said he has the touch
Is that like a colloquial thing for
Psychics in the south
You might like it like it has The Shining and it's like
You can see the future so you have the touch which I don't but it's like
Shouldn't be able
Heal people or something like that
He has the ear of the one who has
I've been touched
Oh okay that makes sense
To the lyrics in my head while you're asking
The question of the Shawn Michaels
Entrance music
Sexy boy sexy voice
I got the mood really move them
Haha
Remember if he says he's got the
Touch in there
He's just a sexy
I was thinking of
Touch
That's sad
Robot
Get out of here
From his dream of earthquakes and
Here after he Rambles for another couple minutes
I love this transition
I woke up this morning thinking about earthquakes and volcanoes
This is the big change this is the big deal
Reverse soul-sucker
We are dealing with spiritual vampire invasion
Slither activate
Monster animal
They are completely
Whatever this you know
What
Yeah that's right
Thank God you're not into Mississippi
Mystical stuff
Whatever out there in space
Demonic soul-sucking vampire
Some Venom shirt is there as you talk about Simeon
I don't know I think that's probably too extreme because that's right
Call that true
Really ghosts for an alien race 22
Because you
That's always been my biggest issue with
Spider-Man,
Too gauche
What about some subtle alien
Deer away from
Reptilian
We are spiritually not far off
It's a shame we're not far off it's that he's literally said
There are things in space demon that attacks themselves
And so on and so forth and it smell like sulfur in all that
Integrate emojis
But I'm not
Symmetrical
And I'm a psychic
That Jesus fights aliens on a regular
You know I can
Now I would read
Graphic novel
I'll tell you that right
Play Jesus come on bukhari
We we move on here from Alex's corner
Maybe we'll call it now
Little bit
Which is not too surprising
This is really funny
Nubuck
The worst comic ever seen
Another One Bites the Dust
Another One Bites the Dust Alex run like 40 radio station
Jesus
Something for him to have his Empire intact everything about Michelle wolf show getting canceled because
Position
It's one thing if you are doing well and have that schadenfreude like f*** you all you people who are
Badly
It's so delusional to be like all you guys got your show cancelled
Soda Butte
Show
Fox News you want come on man
Criticize female comedians that don't wind up being
Female comedians are forced upon you god dammit
Women can be just as unfunny as many as
To do with their femininity
I can't do it I can't do that
Dudes
Criticizing
It's not fun
And if you throw a female in there
Oh no that's
Now we got to we got to leave
He's gloating about them getting their shows
Cancel
He doesn't have a show and never will
Reminds me of Allah
Brother Ali
30 did with idea
Okay fun of him for like how many tapes
Sold
And I'll brother all these response to it in the battle was
You talk about my
You're talkin about their shows at least they had
Except
Fox News would not
Defending Alec
Never have him on
Which maybe in a week I'll have to walk back when he hasn't really possible
Why not have him on his again
Wouldn't that be the logical thing to do but no
No program no Fox News programming director
Is going to be like Hey listen
We agree with you
We're f****** racist to s*** to
But
No we can't do this
But you're a pro
For years man
And you were capable of evolving to the point where you no longer wear a bow tie Alex's
The shittiest bowtie vault
Maybe
They invited Alex on
But they were like
You got to say that f****** beard it's terrible no awful
If you want to go on TV ever shave the beard
Turn them down he would never stop.
I know that
You're right
Betty White
Get back to Soros
Interesting about him
Actually really fun
Get to
About Taurus
George Soros loxism
Double x's in your eyes
The man
Believes he is Jesus Christ
63rd Avenue
Demon son what I still think about you and your family
It's still groceries trying to do some ASMR there at the end
That's f***** up
You are very
Relaxed
Crinkly crinkly crinkly
ASMR
It would be
F*****'-a
ASMR Alec
Loyola
The world
When is the global
El relax
And they put him on a table
And they roll their hair
Smaller tables
And they put their parents
Turn the tables made out of their hands and I a bad at 8
Words I want me to say
Poppycock
Krugerrand
Succotash
Bouillabaisse
That's a very delicious cold soup
The best
Videos now
Books and stuff over the years has said that he believes himself to be
Christ which is
Accurate
This is a misrepresentation of
Quote from his book The
Premier Finance
I admit that I've always harbored in
Exaggerated view of myself important
Bluntly
Myself
Some kind of God or economic reformer like
IQ
Eat with his general theory or even better a scientist like
Are you talkin about the delusions
You talkin about the selfie
Importance that he felt that has been corrected
Maturing
Becoming older
There's a further quote from his book underwriting democracy
Ixora it goes like this
I carried some rather potent message
From childhood
The control otherwise I might end up in the loony
But when I made my way to the world I wanted to
Indulge Myself and I
The extent that I could
Ford
That is
Selected
The larger context of the quote where it comes from
From the text put it into
I began my work directed at opening up close societies about 10 years
I wasn't successful manager of an inch
International address
And I was making more money that I had used
I began to think about what I should do with it
The idea of setting
Foundation
Maybe cuz I had always felt that one
To do something
For other people if one could
I was confirmed
But I considered
Narrow base for my rather inflated cell
Right if truth be known I carry some rather potent Messi on
From childhood
Control otherwise they might get
The trouble but when I had my way in the world I wanted
Santa could afford
Messianic fantasies
Has he had
Just got to come from the factory
Did he survive the Holocaust
And the way he wanted to
To indulge
Is that he wanted to set up ways to help promote
Free Society
Another quote
From that same book
I realized I cared passion
Lie about the concept of an open Society
Which people like me
Could enjoy freedom without being
Hounded to death
Accordingly I called my Foundation the open
Society
With the objective of making open societies viable
Helping to open up
Close the
Massive
Depilator
Survivors
Channel that somehow instead
Into almost a
The only reason I could have survived
Is because
Is because I have some
Which is a witch
Very understandable
In the circumstances
And all the other context
Of his heroic father
Who wrote The Shining
Examples for real hero
Understandable
I'm bullet
Sort of that goes away with time
And that is what
Does
If you look at them and
Not today that he's a
But all of these things
Did they use to
Attack him
Aldi
There are
Reasonable critique
You could make and they
Some reason
Not sure why
The only
I don't know why that it
Very curious
I can't think of any reason
For me it's because they're lazy
For me I mean like
It's just the idea of being
Billionaire
Regardless of how philanthropic
You may be right
So we can just talk about billionaires but if you
You start talking
About billionaire
You got to start talking about
It's always like if you apply some sort of
Standard
Did your team as well
So they pick one
Fake standard
It's so far
Because like Alex
Throw around
Beside these study
I'm done about how like
Most Billy
Democratic candidates
And that he's actually Act
Sing but every study
You actually get into like the
Going to saying like
A lot of people on the right
Donate
Like hidden fun
Stuff like that like a donor fund
Stuff like that
Even in the
The studies themselves
They have like we have no idea who's giving money we're crazy
That donors
Who donate large amounts of money to
To the Democratic party
Interested in
Read the rest of the world people who donate to the Republican Party
To be in public
So
It doesn't really prove
There's a f****** Chase Bank
People
Feeling a little better
No more billionaires
I mean
More Lisa
So
Next clip
I don't know any other way
To tell you
This is great
So you start by getting it
His beams about like how he
Going to get blamed
Media fall swags themselves
Which is fun
Nobody
You could predict
It's so great
The Washington Post
Remember that that's already happened he was going to come kill everybody and then got arrested
Books-A-Million
Talk about Oklahoma City
Also the McRib is coming
Coronavirus
A fancy dining car
They're probably drinking coffee
And smoking big cigars
You know I knew I had to come and I knew I can't be free
Keep the blowing and that's what
Tortures me
Why was just the baby mama told me son always be
But I shot a man in Reno
Oh my goodness I haven't gotten to yet
Hey There Delilah
I don't know if it's a great idea
Making a connection that the no one else could possibly
Ablative
When he says he killed the guy and then he starts talking about killing a guy in the
Killing a guy
Conspiracy theories
It's just weird false flagging yourself
I don't know I don't know that there's any like real connection and Lord knows we
We can never know what goes on in
The minds of weirdos
But like dude
Out of nowhere
Reciting
Dramatically
Like most
Lyrics to Folsom Prison Blues
When
Very an hour-and-a-half
Earlier you said
I never killed anybody
Technically
Technically technically
That's f***** up
This is super f*****-up weird episode
Woodmore outside
He's now back to the point where you
F****** doesn't
You confessed to murder disrespect
I don't think it'll get us
The million dollars
Maybe a piece of
Is my argument that Alex's advocating violence
But
A just coming up for our families and everybody else future everything but very very
Firm
No pleasure
And the fact that defend ourselves
Pleasure
I want to call man cockroach I don't want to have a bunch of stuff
I'll come here buddy
Just crush your head
Trash can
Killing cockroaches
Add
I would never offensive
You know there's a rich tradition of
Calling your enemies cockroach
What
I think that he's
I think that he saying
You such a good guy
Enjoy it
Think about it really
Is it does he think that's in the plus column does he think that's in a pro like hey
I would enjoy murdering
Only dogs
Really liked it
I don't know man
Time yeah you know we all we all have
Get-rich-quick moment killing a guy
Having that ate shot who knows
Cowardly
Who sings No it's not even that
It's not even that it's saying that
Suggested
That these people are
Solo and so evil that my first preference is
To save them
But because they have gone so far
I have no choice
But you stopped them underneath my boot not only are you now Justified
Murdering them
But not only that you can then
Feel like you're taking the moral High Ground
For not enjoying
Feeling this one
As opposed to
Something that you Delight in like the f******
Psychopath you are cockroaches
We heard earlier him saying thesaurus
Thanks you're an animal
The only people I ever
Weird that's pretty that
Dehumanizer
People calling Omarosa a dog don't worry about everyone
Hilarious
If Alex call her.
September's other dogs
Islamqa too good
Is to feel real bad for that
Forgot
Did the cross
Live clip with couch
Defensive
That's how we get away with all this
Image next clip
What do you talkin about
I don't know how
Someone could hear this
Not respond
Thinking about like
F****** killed
So I'm not sitting here sleeping about Rockabye my bed
First of all
I'm going to stop there to say
Complains about celebrities having armed guards
Security I don't have a
Battle rifle
But not like it
P**** way
The left
If you do not
Open your chest and Neil
You are a terrorist
God
Defeated me
And then Jack Dorsey
Bible
Empathic
Zara's best
No
I just heard you say fake laugh while laughing while he hasn't felt
The people
That's gross
Message Judy started putting out there is that
These items that we
We have this
Vision of a
Be afraid of
They just want you to submit to them
Greatest crime ever but
If you submit to them then they're going to kill you anyway
That he's putting out that is with these people no matter what you do they're trying
Need to kill you
That is the truth
It logically
Follows that you
Kill them
But I know that he's not saying kill these people or anything like that
Martin
Nothing I do that
Most of the time
That is the message
It's important that like I know that
Can't hold him
Responsible for what people hear
Because of the way our laws work
Sure people are in on the side
Which
Support but it's ludicrous
To say that he's not advocating
It's absurd
It's not legally actionable but that is what he's doing
Deuteronomy
Dude is one of those Commandments o
Deuteronomy is the one that's all obsessed with
With laws and those f****** a******
Personally
I just believe that the Bible is a living true document and everything in it is literally true
Yes sure the Bible says
We killed
Want to do it
But
Absolutely it's a weird like cowardly
No I love
God
Right
To go against the word of God
What what am I some guy
Didn't he just give a perfect defensive why we should
Rise up and overthrow our billionaire overlords
Walk me through that
Is that
Of course
The only thing that they hate more than submission is refusing to submit and they're going to kill you anyway
Is that your only option that is
Right so what is what is our billionaire Overlord class other than somebody who is
Stamping on all of our f******
Throat coming to our goddamn home
If you borrow the rhetoric
Answer to tweak it a little
Yeah just like the logical
Chase Bank
Steal my bread
Came to your house more like
They had five guys stamp on your throat
Steal $35 from you
And then they f****** put it in your mouth and said deal with it
And I said
Hooray
Did you do a British accent
I don't do good
British accents
Corky
That's a good one thank you
In this next clip we only got a couple left here
It was not the result of
Ifun
But I wanted to keep this in
Because he that we heard and are out of
Contacts drop a really angry sales paper
This is how sort of
This is just an indication of how all over the place
GPS route to
Gross shower if you don't finances still windwitch
Text Isabella
Asthma specialist tomorrow fluoride free.
Percent off and free shipping
It's just
It's just wrote
Firestone
He's up he's up in these highs of screaming vitagreat the deals are and then like
Hour later
You know
I don't trust that the sales pitch of like we have great everything like
Never ever ever suggest
That we have
Great like every one of our episodes
I'm just saying like
Baker episode
That doesn't mean that
Think about your own decisions in your own life and what you want to do and maybe you'll like it maybe you won't
It's fine
Let's Roll
Maybe that's why I'm a bad salesman
Talk you back a little bit
I want to be like yeah
Redo
The salesperson was trying to not get a sale
I get it why you don't not
Spicy
You know like last night I went out and got some friends
I had to wrestle with like the ideas
Hey
You want one of these carrots
And like
I had to I had to roll with the idea that like I love really spicy
Stop but not everybody does
Right when I was trying to get you to eat one of my Thai peppers
But I had that I've grown
Man like it's just rude of me
Expect you
Enjoy that
Just because I am
And that's how I feel about her podcast
Why we are terrible we're destined for failure
Yeah one more clip hair Jordan
I told you the reason that I K
Came back to the present saying
Decided to stick around here for a little while
Alex's approached
To the color
Ford news the end of the show he gets finally touches on it
He's got a really
Rock Solid
Position
Ion Towing
Because the manafort's stuff hasn't broken yet
By the time
Takes over
We all live through right now and Alex had already hit the whiskey
Hot toddy
But he does say that
Michael Cohen
Hotline name it's not let one of his disgrace lawyers make online
Most have one lawyer who is in disgrace and caught lying
One of many lawyers who has been caught lying
What is taxi cab
Nope
Problem
Camping
Guilty criminal charges
Not
Organization
Portable baby as well
Where is your God damn analysis
Display
ABC and CNN reporter that have an ugly baby
Nothing nothing
What are you going to take a little you got like in that moment
What is it going to
Who are on fire like
Alright I get there
I don't know I think
You know it
Extra
I have no idea what
Apparently it was bombing
Killed
You know
We can talk all day about the
Alex
Who is the famous
Shoves Isis
He's now getting
Michael Cohen
Certainly
Sort of
Point on that and I think it's a fair assumption to
Is that Alex has kind of buzzed
You did all that stuff
Rodger talk
Reasonable the song
Equally reasonable to assume
Because of the way that Alex
Who got killed in the bombing
Cuz that's the assumption that he was
I was making
And then the next day when he found out there was any Rush
So I think it's
Equally plausible that what it will take
For him to
Is Trump actually attack
Or Trump turning on
Yeah I don't
Mean that to say that Alex
Russia or anything like
But the last time
Cortical turn on Trump
Most of his motivation
He killed a bunch of Russia
Soldiers
So I don't know
I don't know man
It's it's
Maybe maybe
Could turn on Ezra
I'm not sure this
I don't know if turning on Israel would even look like
Like what
Support you expanding your settlements illegally into the place where your illegal he's expanding your exhaust
Your settlement
What you just do another the right
Because Riley said other its capital will now be in Boca Raton
Wanted closed tomorrow Lago Israel is a
Come on over
What's your Holy Land
Brigiotta's nothing
It sucks because the joke I was trying to make was about the idea that that's closed tomorrow Lago
It's pretty close to Vacation sort of fun place
Florida
Out of where
It would just make sense to move up
It's Florida
North Carolina
It's funny that
Trump wants to
Drain the swamp
Places very close to
Here
That's my big boy abandon hope all ye who enter
Tell you what
Jordan
You come to the end of this episode
Yeah
Doozy
Here just to put a button on that last clip
Most of the
It's really funny to hear him make that sort of thing before it comes out
Bettencourt
Kid said that
He was working
Candid
Candidate candidate for president
There were Evan Hillary
There were at least four
Everybody knows Hillary would have loved nothing more than for Cohen to have paid off
And avoided.
Story that makes sense
Gary Johnson
He's The Mastermind
I think we will know very short
We already have no bread
Episode
Still in the show sucks
And most of the show that's
Just repetition
And yelling about China
Alex probably killed a guy
No probably
Play kill the guy
Murder murder him
Did technically kill a guy
It seems that way
Probably check
Technically
He killed a guy
So now you not understand fully why we had to do
This is very important to our investigation
Oh
Unforeseen
With a bigger batch
Nope
What to know
Got to get a shirt
Integrity cell
In the Albert
Look
Call Larry nickel shirt
Which does not exist and probably never will
Is just esoteric nonsense
Baseball
Piscina
Kind of
To the rhythm of
Alex killed a guy
The f*** themselves
Cuz I think that's gotten a little stale
Right
We end every episode by reminding the audience analysis killing guy
That maybe
I guess it's your turn
Website knowledge buy.com
Analogous
You can find it find out
Nope music
PW of fun here and but just end things are very serious note we need to remind you
Did Alex Jones killed a guy
Alexandra Thurston color