Alex
Birthstone colors
Studio right now he has
Cigarettes podcast
And he has clocked out for his
Little timecard
Locked up when you left
The floors
A little introduction for a bonus
Episode that we got for you
You here today
Privilege in the luxury
Sure why not
Pleasure
Sitting down
From the
The shitpost
What you can find all over wherever
But via be forewarned that
It is
But with the eyes
!
That is
Find it
And I believe that at the end
Wild West
I apologize
I was really great time
Real life realty
Sit down with somebody
I have a little conversation
Especially who
Spends as much time
Looking at InFocus
I didn't mean to
To the world event
What's Jones
I do
He also has
Far more
Scoped
You know monitoring
Looking at right wing
Is real nice real nice
Thank you very much for his
Please do check
Broadcast
Yeah I don't I don't know I was going
Go to the mailbag
Voicemail
As I thought about it I realize
Without Jordan
So we'll get back to you
You know some policy wonks shoutouts
The voicemails from
The good people out there
When he is back
Studio but for now
Please enjoy this special bonus episode of the podcast
With Jared Holt
Check out his podcast
Shitpost podcast
And to follow him on Twitter
At Ghirardelli
Will be back
With the regular episode
Real soon
I'm a policy wonk
Hello yeah it's great to be doing the show with somebody who
Watches as much Alex Jones as I do I don't come across that very often
Me too it's a rare thing in this world
You don't want me to do Family Medicine
You have
Because I
Yeah it's
It can be kind of tough right it's like
This is almost like an alternate reality and itself and I feel like once you get that in your brain it's hard to
Understand how other people wouldn't know it
You know you're the friend take mushrooms for the first time
And they are they tell you about like everything that you're missing out on
It's all just sort of
Illusion
The only person
Antimatter
A bit why is that
As much time listening to Alex Jones
Better part of two years
So I
Digging into his narratives really trying to unpack where they come from
Just doing my research into
What's the source of this
Something I don't think a lot of people
Care to pay too much attention
So have you read the book
Byron Johnson
Jon Ronson
Tons of interviews of him talking about Alex
And the perspective that he has is
It scares me a lot because I think that he could do a lot to take Alex out
Quite frankly
Or at least in front of his
I don't know if he does
Enough
Yeah like if there's one guy that I want to go on Infowars
I think it's him
You been on a bunch of times
Oh really yeah yeah yeah he comes on almost as amused Observer of Alex
I guess probably because he has been sort of documentary in the distance
He never is too pointed about like Alex you know you're making this stuff up
His face but
I don't I don't understand what he has
You know
Like Ron Johnson has that sorted documentary approach how did you get into this originally
Well I made the mistake of watching Infowars coverage of the election in 20
Coincidence I just saw the ugliness that was
Behind it
Use myself cuz I thought
The most part political
Is a little bit boring
Answer why not spice it up with Alex Jones screaming about stuff
Do you get to
You look too closely at it a little bit I think you see what it's really about and what I saw was
Just an organization
To reinforcing whiteness and maleness
The supposed other of equality
And it really bummed me out
I am.
So I just started I started trying to dig into it and at the time me and Jordan
I were hanging out a lot and drinking a bunch and screaming at each other at bars
So we just decided to
Do that
Please
Because what was going on is
Weird intense
Friendship that would last one night and then we wouldn't
And we were talked for like 7 hours
So this was for me like a lot of an excuse just a hangout
So that those those sort of things merged a little bit our desire to hang out with each other
Helps create the show and I'm I
My theory my working Theory from about 2 years ago that Alex
Was operating
A sort of chauvinist
Supremacist organization
Media Corporation
For my research
Nothing
Disproving that
Greatly
So if I get what you're saying
You watching for Wars for the friendship
Yeah yeah
I don't like the original conceit for the show is I don't know anything about Alex
What Dan told me was my entire entrance into the world
And
It has to say ruined my life in a very positive
Yeah that's
The slogan of our show
Unofficial
My life
You can relate
Probably.
All the research
About how
Becoming aware of these
These worlds
Makes you realize how much more there is even Beyond
You don't even know
Right it's
It's like
So I have
Sort of a similar background where is probably too
Two-and-a-half years ago I first
Hopped aboard the Infowars train
Popped my brain Force plus and sat down to
You just consume
The Alex Jones Show
Almost its entirety like
Everyday
And then on Mondays I would like
Watch the weekend stuff
My secret to it is
Playing it like
One and a half speed
PetSmart PetSmart
Figured that out yet I have actually recently I've had someone tell me that I should do and I'm
I think I'm going to have
Yeah I play it fast and then I skip the commercials and you can like crank through an episode of The Alex Jones Show if you're dedicated
It in like an hour and a half
Some of the stuff I picked up is really similar to the stuff
You've picked up
You know it's hard
Not to see these like white nationalist tropes
And also like you said this.
Chauvinist
Mentality exhibited on are both reflectix
The character of Alex Jones and also through
Some of the gas selection and some of the recurring themes that
Show up every week on the show
Just like most recently
Paired with the proud boys which is Gavin McInnes is through
Tip for a long time
And the only thing I really remember about 10
He was trying to make the argument
Black states with Reverend
Sexual things
Working Americans remember about that episode was making me aware of the
Krowd
Yeah
Yeah and then like and now presumably he's putting just having like random
Cowboy numbers on
Lifelike Rufio who was in Portland
I'm sorry
Can't get away from
Yeah I mean he's having people on that head
You know
Violent altercations with counter-protesters and stop headlight
It is
Sort of glorifying that
Became a national platform
I will tell you this the biggest mistake that you have made
Not
Listening to commercials because
If you skip through the commercials
Blessed left nowadays but back in the past used to have a lot of really fun commercials
Diamond gusset jeans is my favorite thing that has ever existed
Yet he had an Advertiser called Diamond gusset jeans that
We did some research into and found that all of their customer reviews were
I ordered a large but this is a medium
Everyone
Random pants size and then whenever I sent it back
The shipping was like 30 bucks and they didn't send
2009 or so one of the sponsors was the most high family ministry which is like
Illegitimate cult that was running a real
Operation
But I generally agree with you should skip
Commercial nowadays I quit the brain for stress
There's not much
Not much
When he goes into a screaming rant about how everyone
Coming to kill you
And they're going to take
Children
By the way we have
Easter specials still on shipping
Really good you can get brainforest you have no idea
Will destroy you if you don't give me money
My favorite person who does the add pivots is Rodger Stone whenever Keys guest-hosting those are beautiful everything
Smooth
Smooth daddy is Rodger Stone
View him reverently dancing around the Earth
Yeah yes please nature of like sort of gentleman brisker absentee father
There's a little bit of a feel like that
He's good I think
Rodger has a metal
Chameleons are taking on a lot of those expectations that
Alex already
Smooth transition
It's interesting to see that sort of like Infowars virus
Sex people
Owen Shroyer
We can watch him right now sort of starting to learn how to do the pivot
Now but still
I still maintain that the only person who's going to make it through this whole thing somehow unscathed
Gaston
Like it's going to be a cockroach at the end even if the nuclear bomb
Austin
Just like slink away fine
Yeah he just like crawl out of the sewer and be like we got some excellent specials in the Infowars store
Undoubtedly
I don't know
It's kind of interesting because
Go through
Approach
Alex
Undertaker
With as much of an open mind as I can open heart
I try not to condemn him too quickly
Without cause
I'm so
It's weird because every episode or so definitely we end up learning things that are
Sort of
Transformative in terms of our understanding
We learned
Not too long ago that he's had at least 10 abortions in his life
Impersonal
Paid for it
Some kind of
Mr. mom
Abortion
Reframes how you look at
The character and the man
Bring this up cuz I don't know if you were listening to show on Monday of this week
I'm thinking I've been a little bit busy
With other stuff and I have to go back
I'm trying to remember if I
Got that one I'd like to see if I can play a clip for you
Cuz we have a
This is something I think everyone needs to know about
Google
Google would love to kill
Did did that come through
Didn't come through
R-tech issues are terrible
Sparking SparkNotes it for me
What the heck
I guarantee Google
Wood kiln
Except that one guy
Some health issues
What
Get it always amazes me like the weird personal details that
Alex WhatsApp
Because like if you remember back to
Allahu Kasi trial when was that like
Good dinner
Goodyear
Yeah whenever his lawyers
Like Ada's
Deposition that Alex Jones is a character
Yeah played by
Alex Jones he like playing himself or something
You know it's it's very easy to see what Infowars is doing a sort of stage art and away
But every once in awhile
Yeah these weird details come out
That don't seem like it's acting
And
Little startling
I've reached my Malcolm Gladwell Tipping Point of time listening to him
I think I've gotten to a point where I can pretty well stuff out when there's like when he saying something he thinks he shouldn't
Or when he's lying
Generally find that when he's lying about something he adds a bunch of
Extraneous details and flushes out the story really well
Are you telling the truth
It's something like a tree like
Lead me towards
This is
This is not an act
Somebody struggling
It is just brings me back to that claim that
Alex Jones made that he likes slept with 200 women by the time he was like 16
You remember that
With a little bit of
Embellishment
You know it's probably more like
Right
Described
Was full of trauma
Terms of
When he was a young boy
You talked about one time he got stuck under a house and they were fumigating the house and he was just stuck to you like trash
Left under a house with
Extermination chemicals
Hit in the head when he was really young
There's like a cinder block
Houses
Kicked kicked him off her knee and said you don't get what
My favorite
Because she wanted him to be a man
He also may have killed his dog
A dog named Enoch
Describe
I think you take into account a sort of very chaotic child
It doesn't seem that far out of like what the consequence
Nosy result that you might
Expect from someone like that
You are very hot.
Yeah
Disconnect
He also
30 years old
Alex
Same to you have sex at 11
Whether or not you know you want to
Probably thought it was a good idea
No sexual activity
Elion has his own sexual abuse like he was truly sexually
Abused
Play the office like a
Describing is a child
Absolutely
He considers that a Bragg
So I be interested to hear like using
Do you have the perspective that like
Alex Jones
Has experience
Seemingly major trauma in his life
Salute
You know
And it's
It is
Pretty fascinating
To see that
Play out in the form of it
Daily broadcast
You know I
How do you say that
Play Outlaw Infowars segments
Manifest
Like really childish thinking
Create artificial cause-and-effect all the time that sort of thing
Inability to
Undertale
He always refers to primary sources and stuff like that but
He never actually understand the context of those sources come from
Very adolescent
The entirety of his show as a manifestation
Frozen in kind of intellectual Arrested Development
He's just not able to wrestle with nuance
He is very angry
He feels like
He's lost something
Some nebulous
Empty out in the world.
He feels has
Deprived him of that really does
If you so much about serial killer like backstories has
That you're like
Will at least you didn't kill X
Practically
Maybe
Alleged buyout
You kind of want to go
Difficult
Listen
To what you put out into the world
He's affected a lot of people
Was this like
Or did you just become fat
It was a little bit of both
I used to work at this place called Media Matters for America
Pandora
Collaborator
Oh my God I went to an Alex Jones press conference when he was in DC 1 week and it was like
Yeah it was earlier this year
Lucky Duck
That was that was an experience
And once you figured out who I was
Went off
Yeah he likes singled me out in the crowd and he's like that guy works for a Nazi
Elaborate
I think I saw this in the life
Yeah that was me
Yeah it's a
That was
A hell of a day
Yes I started
Doing stuff with Media Matters and
You know there is like
A weekly
What sort of mix of stuff I had to listen to like Rush Limbaugh Sean Hannity Alex Jones said I just thought the Infowars stuff was
What's more interesting
Or at the very least more entertaining
Oh yeah
It was like watching a daily Trainwreck
So I could expect that and now that
Do I do work at a place called
Breitling watch which for the money for the record does not get Soros money let's go.
I don't think Alex cares but it all
And
I just sort of stuck with it I guess in
I thought about like different ways I could approach it
Anytime he's in the area or
An event
That I think I might go to I try to work that angle into it and
Try to figure out how it fits into the broader Infowars universe or or zeitgeist
Yeah it's something that's like become really fascinating to me I am interested to hear your thoughts just sort of
You know this
Trauma
Inspire
Trainwreck that happens on air everyday
Like the sorts of people that it attracts
Because
Alex Jones has mega-fans and he has a lot of them that will travel
Tesla
Go see
Him or other Infowars host
At different events
It's always the most curious bunch of people
Who it's a lot of live streamers
First off
That was like
That's something I've done
Advanced assist people with their own sort of spin-off live stream
Right-wing conspiracy theory
Styled shows
Dad
You know are there too hopefully
Interview Alex Jones or meet Al
What's shelter try to get a job with Alex Jones
One thing is I think my mind is
Employees came from
Test
Like Lee Ann McAdoo and David night we're both people that came into the folds
Contest
Antagonistic
YouTube videos and he got in touch with the Alex
Millie Weaver's by believe fairly similar
Sexual employees
Feed the myth that like if you just go find him and you're doing something
He'll bring you aboard
And then even beyond that
Back in back in the day
Most of his callers
Call Anna B like the best question
Where's back
The day
Make a callers and they'd all be like
Hey Alex I'm putting together an Infowars rap album can I plug it was fine everybody
So I kind of like
A distribution center
The place that you could get your thing out
Encouraged ethos
His audience
So I'm not too surprised
Figure that now
Do YouTube streaming
Has become so much more prevalent that still the case
Like a douchebag
How much he openly disdains his listener
He hates his listeners like
Anytime somebody calls in
There is a certain expectation of like
Say some dumb s*** and I'm going to have to pretend that it's okay and he'll just often just cut
People off in
And acts like his own narrative is what
You were talking about
Is owned by dogs live in their own home
Of course I did
And that's why the Chinese are running everything now
He doesn't even to his own guess sometime.
Seeing that he always go
Prophet
Yeah you don't cut off the prophets is rude all the time
You listen to what Elijah
To say I don't even know if
By the way did you guys booked that profit for this
We have a
All right all right I'm going to move on
Something told me that like mine was going to be here but I don't know man I guess
I guess I was wrong
Profits are notoriously flaky
That's what I found
I would say is my favorite I think
Just because of the
Wrestled with
Are you are you aware of Steve
I'm sorry to hear that
Most people are
You're like Alex Jones ever he's on everybody's lips everybody's writing
Big write-ups about him and and all this and no one really
Nose
The nature of like one of the big sources of his narrative the most interesting with Steve pieczenik
Get a call from Alex in the middle of a hurricane
And for the first time Steve pieczenik was just like
Galaxy your narratives right now
Florida
Can't
Steve was like
Alex
I thought you were calling to ask how I'm doing
Personal
Yeah but
Steve pieczenik uses his like
Formula
Like State Department status to lend Infowars credibility
Which you don't know who he is and like how far out is that
Dad could
If your goleba like ass or susceptible new
So who this guy is that could be
A little concerning even as recently as like
I don't know six months ago or so he was on David Knight show real news and was talking about Sandy Hook
We're just kind of running counter to Alex's efforts
Oh yeah
Hit that Super Sonic
The only thing that saved Alex there is David
Too boring to listen to ever
Yeah I skip it most of the time
It's the division
Guys are human qualities of who
Co-host
Send all of his life
We all just like
You don't have it
But that's also part of Alex's
Hiring strategy is he's always going to hire people
Aren't a threat
Supremacy
Like the closest one is what's his dumb face
None of the bridge prison Paul
Call Joseph
Put on fire and then
Just peed on forever
Isn't even that guy is
Too much of a pain
Forever really
Intense
Toxic
Masculine
But
I do have to admire Paul's dedication to the brand whenever
He liked me this video about
Boys are whatever and
Someone pointed out that
The thing that he's always selling
Contain soy
And you just doubled all the way the fuk down
You unflappable
You got to respect
Okay absolutely
He has the has that kind of smugness
You can't punch out if somebody
You know like it it's just
Yogurt face
I just drive people crazy and he knows it
And that's really
It's great it really works with his like really fast edited videos that he puts up you know it really is good for
People in
And I
You know sort of invigorate
The base that likes to
To piss off other people but put them in front of the camera for like
5 minutes without
Fast Cuts
Is like
Understanding the attention
Cut and and almost
Himself
Go at 1
Like something really boring
And you're like
So I
You know
Paul his like
Yeah Master the
Arthur
Creating outrage in
Alex Jones I think attracts people like just
Because he's so eccentric
Restorative circling back to this question of like
Who watches Infowars
You sort of had that
You called it like a Malcolm Gladwell analysis of
Alex Jones
I'm curious what you think
You know the history in
Mannerisms of Alex Jones
Mikey Bolts
Tell us about
Shivpuri shape
At least in the most General sense
Dan has the serious answer to this one
I think it's probably
You know in the
Probably late nineties it was a lot of really hard core militia Folk
You probably could make a case
The mirror
There were a lot of people who are dissatisfied with George W bush
Steven probably had some weird left-leaning Libertarians in the mix
Has Obama got you saw
A real shift
You maintain a lot of
I don't know exactly when things changed because I haven't
Listen to all the episodes
That he's ever done
I know from looking at online communities now and hearing comments about him now
There are tons of people who think that
He's sold out
And is a shill
Particularly for Israel people make that argument
So I don't know I
The True Believers in terms of like his fan base of the of the like
The libertarianism that he embodied years ago
I don't really know what his fanbases like outside of
Sort of opportunist like those
YouTube streamers
People who are full of hate
I'm not sure exactly
Chismosa
Emblematic of the Republic
As it is now
Like his brand is
Overtaken by the the Fox News isn't all of that stuff
Because prior to Trump
Global monstrosity
His brand was
Cruelty
Whatever it is we can do to
The weakest members of our
Society
Is what we need to do
So now he's kind of left with this
This weird a conglomeration of
Stubborn citizens white nationalist
People who want to say they're not anti-semitic yet at the same timer
Anti-Semitic
A little course
Inflated Russian
What is my biggest theory is that
Nobody but
Actually kind of list
I think Dan who are the only people who listen to what he has to say
Doesn't
As background
Like what we found out is he
Now that he's off YouTube and Facebook and all that stuff
He's on like
830 radio stations
Give or take
Who's to say how many likes
200 population
Something
Might have a ton of little tiny town
Around the country
Of major and mediamarkt
Confound His Radio
Reach is much smaller
Yeah and
Something I've been watching it
You know app
Since Alex Jones has been pulled off
Aldi
Platforms
You know if there was like a relative spike in interest
And you know
In as result
Traffic to the Infowars site like right after that happened
Now it's starting to fall back down
Sort of closer to the normal range
And I'm wondering if it'll stay at that normal range or if we'll see that
Start to dwindle
Well it's like a black one Breitbart artificial when they had to remove
The there's an article about
Suspicious patterns
Breitbart's traffic
Almost
Vertical line
Is there traffic
Around that level
Another vertical line
Clearly indicates artificial inflation of traffic
And I don't I don't know
I don't know what to expect from Alex I knows it
Whatever interest he got like with him bragging about being the number one app and stuff like that
That was even overblown
Trending apps
Because everyone was running to it
Like rats
To get off a sinking ship
I needed something
Candy Crush
Or whatever it is probably
I think back to normal is probably where you going to be for a bit
I think that he has a built-in narrative about that
I think people are still invested in trying to
I see him through on whatever
Story
The storyline of this season of the show is his I'm a free speech martyr and that's
Conclusion
And then I think a problem
Either way whether the Republic
Terms or
They lose control of the house
I think either way Alex
Kind of
Loses a lot of momentum in a lot of natural interest
So I
Infowars being pulled off
Somebody's bigger platforms
Little bit of a disclaimer I had sort of
What ended up being
A little bit of an accidental roll
You were that you were the Spotify guy
Yeah but I was the one who got Spotify
And in that like to sort of snowball then
I had no idea it was going to turn into what it turned into but
Here we are today and I'm curious to get
Someone else who like understands that enforce universes
Kcon like
What now
It works like
You do
How does this affect
The Brandt
Simply on it as as somebody who doesn't study and it is only there to react on it and create my
Nonsense series
I think
He's actually done
Like I don't think he's
Because right now he's the cause
For so many of these people
And as we know from any cause
Twitter and and all that stuff is going to
Let it go after a couple of weeks
And once he stops being the cause
Hi there cost 11
As it as it was
He is just going to disappear
And it's just going to be people even the ones who are hardcore listeners
Bored
Cuz that's we've listened to over a over the recent
Episode
He's really kind of putting out the same nonsense
It's not as much fun
I feel like what you did believe I believe it was that you were
Like gunning
Or anything like that
I think that's what you were in essence was kind of forced The Narrative forward cuz he's in a bit of a holding pen
Pattern getting kicked off stuff you able to progressed to the next logical step
I'm a victim I am
The first Target in terms of free speech x y and z
And when they started to happen one of my
Firm convictions I believe
To use that as a jumping-off point
To do something else
If you need it not like turn on Trump
Really going full any Bruce
Like getting down to the brass tacks
Sitting on his show as boring as it may be reading over regulations reading over
Terms-of-service agreements or something like that
You know trying to like make it make himself
Respectable legitimate
Argument
Because he never does that
And when we started to listen to the episode Zachary got kicked off of like Facebook
YouTube
You just saw him doing the exact same thing and like it's just yelling about to try calms screaming about how soros's
Is evil
Just doing the same like I got to sell my fish oil all that stuff
I got the sense of it like
He's either waving a white flag of surrender or he doesn't realize that he's already dead in the water
There's nothing
There's nowhere to go past
The end of this narrative
If that makes sense
The most exciting moment I think for us
With Alex and
In present day
Was whatever he said that Trump shaved ices up in dirty ass hoe
That was the night that truck that Trump a bomb Syria
We were we were both watching him in this
Transformation from
Crazy guy who screams about
And then becoming just the guy who's
The partisan hack
The Republicans are great
Sister trying to kill you kill you
I know that night we we could have seen the real turning point for him
He could have changed his narrative
And become something so much
Better than what it is right now
No cuz that
Turn on Trump
And be like I'm going
I'm going to
Hero
And in reality what you need to do is shut up
You help
Make this mess that we're in we don't need you to clean it up he's like a baby who knocks over a bottle
And then doesn't know how to clean but it's let me know
You just be like baby go sit in the corner I'll take care of this
Cept adults need to step in
No I'm not mad at you
Yeah don't because like
What if I am remembering that same night which I presume that I am it's a
He didn't
You said to turn on Trump really defy him in a major way and said it was like Trump we love you we elected you for a reason but
But this wasn't good
No no by the end of the night he was very much like
We got it we're on our own now
He was putting out
Owen Shroyer biocides
To keep things going
Eoin troyer's look of surprise after every sentence eSATA just like
We should have had a projection
I believe in 1.0 and was like oh wait wait I remember this
Okay
It's a good thing
Slip on truck mode
And then the next day he got on his show and said everything is cool
We still support Trump
Furiously or called him all night
Trying to convince him otherwise
That's part of my mother.
Oh I think I found this is this when he's like
Donald Trump s*** his f****** pants of the f****** moment should all over everybody
That moment right
Strong work that night that was a real
Cooking cult for Donald Trump was a good night
Okay yeah I remember this
That was like one of the last
Most recent times that I've been like that Alex
Investigated 2015
Because
2 episode
Serious
We really streamline when we put out
3 hour episodes
55 hour-long presentation
I wanted to go back to
2015 exact date
Trump
Beware Alex jumped on Tori
To see you
Interesting
Even though everyone was saying that Alex Jones is the voice of trump or whatever
And clearly Alex was on
Don't have any idea why
And I wanted to try and figure that out so I spent countless hours at my job
I just going over listening to all the episodes
Taking notes
I found it was the most surprising was that
When Trump announced his candidacy
He was very clear about how Donald Trump was part of the mob
He said that Trump was a front man for Consortium is on the East Coast
He was a bad bad guy
He knows from
Deep deep sources
If you have a name like Corleone you get arrested if you have a name like Trump
You don't
She was just very clearly
Coming out with like I know that this guy is involved with illegal Financial operations
And stuff like that
I meant over the course of months we saw him
Go from
Is that position to
Jesus's guys meme
He hates immigrants I like that
But I still love Rand Paul
Yeah never wavered on that point at all for
For months and months and then it happened in a week
Well actually this is one of the misconceptions that aren't people
A lot of people
Rodger Stone
Alex
And that's not true at all
Rodger Stone showed up on November 9th
First appearance
And you did some good work
Get out
You like him
He carries a gun everywhere
Nordstrom
Until the middle of December
I guess you didn't even get on board with him and say this is our guy rampal's not good enough
Right
The hip-hop was much more complicated
It was really
Then it was a slow transition I admit
I do think that the rhetoric happen
Though
Very quick
Like even near the end of his is
Eventually
Love of trump
Eevee evolution that took a while
It was still like
Well you know rampal's my guy but I'm starting to like this Trump fella he hates non-white people and I
And then all the sudden
It went from
Is still
Is a secret
Leaper
He has been
He has been working undercover for 30 years himself
We all need to save us
Is the messiah
No you're wrong though
I apologize
You're my favorite what your recounting is like
Essential plotline have you guys read Jerome corsi book
Qanon
That killing the Deep State yeah
Admit I spent a lot of time looking only Warriors
But I don't have time
I don't have time to read
I got eight sit some excellent fanfiction
Probably some of the most creative type read in a while
Alex 2015
Was full of s***
And that he didn't mean
A president
Writing a book
Elvis fanfiction is kind of like exactly the opposite of what he was saying
Interesting
Did the reality though Georgia
Is this
This is it this is essentially or podcast
Explained
He didn't switch to Trump as our savior until a bit later
Because of
That narrative
Dementia
He's working
Behind the scenes
There's a deal
Tween
Assad
And our Rogue military
Counter to narrative is as we refer to it
That was being told to him
By Rodger Stone
Who are working together in a group that they have on are referred to as the 45 group
I'm convinced that the two of them
In concert to try and slip Alex Jones
Because they knew of his propaganda potential
And that happen
Towards the end
Probably December
Winthrop
Beard on in Fort Worth
Yeah I'm curious you know especially as we go into the midterms now woodenware
Recording this you know we've had
Sitting Congress
People
Encino
Congressional candidates in
That's where the thing appeared on Infowars I think just
For the sake
Of
The size of the audience
I guess it once had knotted
Haven't seen any like real numbers
Recently
A ants just ordered that idea that
You know it is a propaganda tool
I'm really curious to see you do now that
Infowars has been pulled from so many platforms if we're going to see
The same type of
High-profile
You know figures holding power
Who are trying to wield Infowars in the same way or if it's
Guinness Swordigo the way.
The Breitbart did
Arkansas get some gas
High-profile cast but
It's not this it's not thought of as the same like
Realty
Attack dog
Sort of
Outlet that it once was
Yeah
I mean
Gates was the last episode of sitting politician
Who's going on
Yeah and he went on there and complained about getting called
Conspiracy theorist which was just beautiful
Apologize for going on
Which
I think it's reach even within his own
Krewe of guests
Like Mike Go On
Just a panther
Like Matt gaetz
Was doing
I think that even some of those other people who are just
Will realize that
This is not a prophet
Affordable
Place for us to go on
Anymore
A lot of his like roster of guests will diminish
And that's one of the big things that we at least I have learned from
Alex's cast
Characters
Is that these are all con men trying to run their own game
Kind of hanging out like you were saying the the guys who are
Hangers-on trying to get their own YouTube show with
Alex's
We see so many different people who go from
Alex Jones
What is it
Kerry Cassidy
Project Camelot and then we've got
The same people going on Jim Bakker
Shelf and all of this stuff we find is
People running app
Khan and then the other comment kind of propping them up
Ecosystem
Confidence
Most of the media sphere
If you look at like who's a regular guest on Alex Jones it's a peep
Mike Stern
People like Rogers donut people
There people that you do
They have their own weather it's like some b*******
Book or
No like some of these guys have their own their own supplement line
You know or whatever through selling you do I
I grew that I think
Yep
I did not look at
Gastro Tatian and it's a relatively small pool of people
And
They all have their own
S*** that they're trying to do
And
I almost wonder if that's
Like another indicative sign of sort of like the stage of Infowars and its growth
We're
People are coming on Infowars to be on Infowars not because like
Anything substantial or
You know major Lecom consequential is happening on the platformer
That expect to wield like real influence anymore
I think it's some people definitely did
Before
We sometimes cover Project Camelot and Jim Bakker episodes
Do the same
Sort of, maneuvers
Episode of Jim Bakker
The guest book
He buys it
The ton of their books
And then he sells them
So there's a financial incentive for the guests to come on cuz they automatically sell this large
Jungle Book
And when you look at Alex Jones as business model with the Infowars store
Most of the time when these guests come on he's selling their books
Store
Probably I can't confirm this necessarily but it only stands to reason that a lot of these guests were coming on
End up selling
5000 books to Alex for the appearance that there's an in-kind
Version of pay-to-play
What's going on with
Like a consignment deal with hydraulics
A lot of people as we move forward
With his diminished reach won't see that as an investment worthwhile anymore
I know probably end up having to
Go way down the batting order
Smaller rotating cast of characters like when we go back in time with Alex
One of my favorites was what's-his-name general stubblebine or whatever he's dead
When he went on the show his wife was essentially selling a $25 postcard
With a magic set
That would get you out of any crime no no no it's gets you out of getting vaccinated
That's right there is even better
The kind of
Crazy
How bad
As long as we keep healthy
Ranger bike
I think we'll be good
Did you read his report that apparently got to the president
No I didn't read the Adams report
It was a it was a long day today
It was a
The state of
Conservative Shadow Banning
President
I regret it.
51st state
I knew that he was sending that but I didn't realize it was Health Ranger Mike doing it
What's the
Health Ranger Mike is allowed to do any of the
They are the proprietor of naturalnews.com
All kinds of your medical whenever you want to not believe he'll help you not believe it
Nothing like he he'll have health Ranger Mike on every once in awhile just to be like we've tested the supplements there
Fantastic
Also you don't need vaccines
Yep
Marcos
Hey come on ginkgo biloba
Deep Earth iodine
Although supplements
They're all brats
Do you buy.
He's a chiropractor
Website he has all the exact same products for sale just with different names that kind of sounds
Like medicine
Had a really interesting Dynamic of the two of them have where they sell the same stuff
Doctor groups sounds like medicine
Alex sounds like
Combat
Because
Thanos
I mean it's the same thing it's the
That's another version of the same Khan
It's like they have their own it's like they all have their own private label
Like they all buy it from the same
Retail
More likely doctor group buys all of it puts it all together and then
Alex
People's book
In theory
Soccer group
Stop on private label
Doctor group putting it all together himself like he has a workshop like that
I think we should go ahead and
Start to wrap this now that we have
Have finally
Discovered once and for all
That
You know the Infowars products really are
As good as they say it's.
SAR
I can't get out of bed in the morning unless I have my bone broth
I just
The only thing it might my big takeaway I think the big thing that we discovered
This evening is that
You know with
With fewer people going on the Alex Jones Show I think the Jim Bakker Show is about to get
Way
More popping off
I'll tell you it's already been
The lady
Who Paula White Cain
Who is deed single greatest con artist I think we've had
Europe has a
At least like in the originals
Definitely make sure to pin a note to your chest that says call
In a way that somehow she gave a benediction for
Whatever sort of personal preacher
There's nobody who could be less aligned with any kind of Christian theology that you could imagine Ramon
Keyboardist from Journey
Deathstroke
That's great
Screw
That's enough for me I don't know
Blika blika
I would say it is interesting that you're putting it that way Jim Baker's about
Papa
I think he's already reached his is sort of
Xena as it were
Plateaued
He's going to stay about where you
I say keep your eyes on
Something like
Project Camelot
I think I think that's much more likely to get really popular
Because that
Really friend
That's really weird
What space program all the time and have like weird Liars on and the biggest guess they have is a murderer from 19
93 whatever it is
The Pendragon
By the way
Just so you know anytime
You try and wrap up a show
We're going to wind up talking for 85 more minutes please just be as insistent as possible
Well the show
Stamps should I just answer everything with that
End the phone call
It's nice to speak to somebody
This is on this.
And now you're my personal life
Yeah it was a real pleasure
Wonderful
So
My podcast where the can they check out knowledge fight
The best thing to do
Is a Facebook group
It's called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant which is
Clip that I was talking about with Steve pieczenik earlier where he
Bitched out on Alex for a while
He just a game
Great you did a good job go home and tell your brother your mother your biliary your brilliant five stars
Whatever is
Bananas
Cool if you're looking for my podcast you can find it
It's on iTunes and all over the place
Exclamation
Yelling swear words that I did on your
It's called shitpost
The singer Pink
Yeah I tried to type the word s*** into iTunes and they weren't having it so
Motherfuker
Pizza Luce
I believe
You are a victim of
Tyranny
Online censorship run-amok
Undoubtedly
Because you can't push it onto iTunes also just so you know
Email
Podcast
At gmail.com
And instead I found out
That that is owned by a Mexican podcast
That just started
So we just started like a couple weeks ago or in Mexico anyways
You don't want to talk to
Local guys
All the best