Real quick before we start the actual episode
Because there's
Chicago Illinois that I would like
To draw everyone's attention to
Is episode's coming out on Monday
But on Tuesday night
If you are in Chicago you're one of our listeners who was in Chicago
I would like to
Very strongly recommend
Do you consider coming out on Tuesday night
Two at North bar
I think it starts at 8
Look it up
Baby show up at like 7:30 that's the safest way to do it
There is an awesome show that's going on there dear friends of the show
Far out and I9 couple of great rappers
Are going to
Be in town doing the show there
Jordan and I will both be out
Attendance having a great time
There's going to be some comedians who are friends of
The show people like a Matt Riggs
People like a Joe Fernandez he's not been on the show but
He has been invited
Now getting Patty
Is being stupid
But it's going to be a great show if you are
Considering something
To do on Tuesday night it starts early so if you have to go to work on Wednesday
Still an option for you
If you want to come
We'd all love to see you there this is a lot of Talent on that lineup
It's going to be an amazing
Please consider coming
But beyond that please get ready to have a
Very heavy episode of podcast
Frosted Cheerios
Anyway I love you all
I'm a policy wonk
Alex
When was the last time
You ate sushi
Never
No
Musubi
I like to do is make Spam Musubi
Okay right
Wraparound Sam
That is gross or watching something on the prolificacy of
Spavin
The areas and loved it
Sew in
You could say is that I know a lot about sushi and you don't know any
If you don't like it
Not everybody
Fish
He's totally cool about it
Shout out to a couple of new donors or signed up with the team very excited about this
Thank you for doing the team
Thank you Vanessa
Elevated levels
So much gratulate mix on becoming a globalist
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
I sent me a bucket of poop
Thank you so much Nick
Could you like sports
Voicemail bag a little bit here some messages
The messages down the road
Paces the bracket off
It's not it's just it turns out that sometimes we don't have as much time to dilly-dally on the show
That's a duty calls
Today is
Travel episode
Friend we've never met but
Has gotten ahold of me and
Is 2011
Give any idea of the significance
Of July 22nd
21 + 1 is 22 numerology
+ 1 is 21
* 2 is 20
So that's what it is
That's not what it is no it's not
Numbers without
Numerology I was just like look at numbers is nothing to do with
Today we have a very
Be horrifying it
Illustrative another Point here is a very uncharacteristic out-of-context dropped
From today's episode
Is that mean
Is that a colloquialism it's not and never heard anyone died
Employer Paul Joseph Watson to go Full Tilt Boogie on something
I'm actually given the circumstances I think that is very very tacky
So I guess we should do
Just go ahead and start the episode and then we can discuss
Why the date
If someone
Especially someone
From Scandinavia
Would send.
.
Other damage
Miniatures office effectively
People trapped eyewitnesses total chaos
Right now I'm
Why does Europeans completely
Norway.
And nor has it ever been
Part of the narrative is already a little bit sausage
July 22nd 2011 is the day that Android
Rezac committed terrorist attacks in Western Europe
Series of terrorist attacks
Across across Norway
On July 22nd 2011 Anders Breivik killed 77 people into separate areas
Attacks in Norway representing the 5th Deadliest Terrorist
2Pac ever in Western Europe
At 1525 central European summer time which
Is 315
P.m.
He set off a car bomb outside
Their time
It would have been 8 a.m. OurTime
8:15
8:25 a.m. our time soon
Car Bomb outside a government building that housed the office of the Prime Minister of Norway
The balm uses intentionally very similar to the one used by Timothy McVeigh in Oklahoma City
Eight people were killed in 209 were in
Approximately 90 minutes later brevik arrived at the Norwegian Labour party's Youth League camp
A island
Having taken a fairy there while disguised as a police officer
Rather quickly killed the camp director in
Security officer and our to terrorize
Is the people on the island
Before emergency service
It could arrive
No hablo police were alerted two minutes after the first shot their response time was greatly increased by the fact that they did not have a police helicopter
Copter which could have taken them directly
Liberty Island
Twice during his Rampage brother called the police and tried to surrender but ended up hanging up both times
It appears that he was toying with the police because he
Continue killing people in between the calls and after
Campers attempted to escape by swimming off the island
But a number of them were shot in the Water by Brad you will die today Marxist
By the time the police arrived you killed 69 people
50 of whom were 18 years of age or younger
It injured 100
When the police arrived
Reddit dropped his weapons and immediately surrender
When the police arrived the Tariff like a big baked the officers not to kill the
Since the original attack
Be carried out by someone
Policeman
Initially there were reports of an accomplice being arrested because the police wrongly arrested
Answered uko
A seventeen-year-old victim
The rationale was that his haircut with different than it was on his ID
And they felt that his response to the attack was different than the rest of the people there
He didn't cry or freaked out because as a child
He'd witnessed the massacre is in chechnya
And likely had some form of peace
Ptsb
Right arrested him and reports before circling and Alex is going to get into that the idea that they were most
Bullshooters which is based on this false arrest
Please put out
Hours later but still
Dicey
Fox
Yeah yeah
Immediately confessed to the bombing and shooting
Refuse to accept that he was wrong to do what he had done calling it necessary
Though initially deemed criminally insane a follow-up report by psychologist
Declared insane
He was tried and sent to
Sentenced to 21 years in prison
Good news about that is 12 sentences up they can just indefinitely extend it
Forever
The legal system barely works in Norway years for like terrorism
Murder is
The highest
And then opportunities
Yeah yeah yeah
But the we can only do that too
Today
Clearly and with conviction about how he did what he did was not wrong
Sense of remorse
He declared himself a modern-day Knight
I was resisting the invading
Muslims
Braddock showed a complete lack of remorse make one apology
He apologized that he had not killed morphe
6 hours before the attack Braddock posted a video on YouTube
Including a picture of him and military uniform decorated
With many medals he earned
In fact he was deemed unfit for service and was never in the military
In the video he depicts Islam as a trojan horse coming to destroy Europe
If there's ever been a more
Case as a relates to right-wing racist terrorism I'm not sure I've ever seen
Every single aspect of brother
To be confirmed into the front companies established
That wouldn't raise suspicion when you bought masses of fertilizer to me
Make his bomb
After being sentenced Braddock offered to provide information about the other cells of his alleged terrorist Network
Zelda probably didn't
But his offer was rejected so I didn't completely impossible demands he was making
Indicating that he quotes doesn't know how Society works
It turns out he offered the information on the condition that Norwegian and European societies be overthrown
In 2013 he threatened to go on a hunger strike
The prison to not give him a PlayStation
Is PlayStation 2
Because a PlayStation 3 had better games
2014 threatened that he would starve himself to death if we refused quote access to a sofa and a bigger gym
And again complained about the selection of video games he was provide
He complained in court that he was beginning to enjoy the reality show Paradise Hotel would be claimed as proof that he'd become brain
Honestly his life in prison sounds a little bit better than
Text 8:25 a.m.
The police arrived at utoya Island at 11:25 Austin time
Hayward Point brother can mediately surrender
Alex's show start
At 11 a.m. Austin
And concludes at 3 p.m.
There's no reason
For him not to know a good deal
Information
About what happen
Because a lot of disinformation
While there were
Misreporting in terms of that
Second possible shooter
A lot of these.
Had already happened by the time he got on air
A lot of it was unfolding
MVA Osso
We should
Hold him to a higher standard
Speculation
On this episode
So that is what happened on July 22nd 2000
And now we shall see how Alex covers this
And then I have a whole bunch more information coming up later
From some really
Really dark research that I ended up having to do for this episode
To imagine that this act is not
Terrorism done by whites
Possibly
Validation of every criticism that ever been levied against Alex
Just in terms of Alex's journalistic
Integrity
I'm terms of
Parallels that will be able to draw it
Clearlake I don't think this
Is bad because you trying to defend a white supremacist doesn't know what's going on
He's just creating a narrative that states what he talks about as opposed to being like
You'll see as it goes along.
Supremacist Mazzy learn
More about
Undoubtedly
Through the day off make it look like crazy
Doing the whole thing yeah and on this episode he does
He doesn't get back on but multiple times as we need Steve
Yeah I'm sure by Sunday
You got a chance and then they get the narrative that they need
Moving
Detail but I'm reading but I feel like it's important to know exactly the situation
That we have on our hands
77 people were killed by Duran
Man
Who hated Islam and hated liberalism and multiculturalism
Looking into how I'm very certain
About what he was doing
A little bit later
You don't
That
I am so
And pro prison conditions like in Oslo they have
Prison conditions that are
They have better living situation
Somewhat somewhat right in some in some respects
He's kept in like solitary
Confinement
Because
They don't want to
Set up a cell in prison something like that
Concerned considering he's one of the worst terrorist ever
Aunt clearly
I'll get to why I know this
Down the line planning this for
At least since 2002
End up getting into a prison population and probably
Hooking up with people and trying to
You get some for sure going
We've kept in solitary confinement but because solitary
Confined it meant is so cruel
Commission I believe
Accommodate the fact that they
They can't allow him to be around other people is that they have three cells
One is like a study
Video has one is like sleeping cell and he has allowed to play games
Amazon has an electric typewriter for a while
Computer but we know not allowed to be hooked up to the Internet
Accommodations I understand
You never even the worst people in the world you don't want them just rotting in a hole
More about us not deserve
I would never want him to be kept in solitary confinement I don't want him to be tortured
At the same time
He should be killed
He's like like that should be the situation
Write like a prison conditions
Absolutely I think because we had a chance to surrender witchy
I don't know if you deserve
I don't know
Like a horse that he did lay down his weapons
You can't then kill him
You know I don't I don't
Timestamp
Eva love like
No I don't want to torture you but also you can't be around anymore
Right you'd hope
I mean you'd wish that maybe we had like
Penal colony
Nothing like that
I don't know man it's it's very difficult
You know you
Your visceral reaction obviously is that like no punishment
Including a PlayStation
3 is good enough
It you preserve much worse than
At what at what point
Do we are we comfortable
Arbitrary
Much more severe punishment
Would rather he was just
Like
No longer with us
Lights
I don't want it I don't want him to experience internal pain or anything like that
It's because there is no God or Hell or anything like that but it should just be like a severing of your ability to be human
Any longer
Keisha Keisha
Yeah like that's what should happen
You shouldn't be allowed for all of those people
Which honestly I'm not sure you'd be able to avoid no matter what
You do
Do the Martyr as a political prisoner later.
You don't get to you don't get ticket status
Guitar
But he does complain that he only gets like
Childish game that doesn't get like modern warfare
It's so bizarre I don't know man I agree with you on a visceral human level
But I also like
I don't want to wrestle with those issues
I don't think I'm equipped to and I don't know the right answer
Philosophically opposed
Capital punishment
As a my butt
I also have no vested interest in telling the state of Norway how they can and can't meet out there Justice
Improved overall episode
Layout what is initial thoughts
This attack
I apologize that I stumbled up VI
The time differences and stuff like that at the beginning
I'm at 8:25 a.m.
Austin time Central Standard Time
Alex Goes On Air at 11
Everything was over by 11:25 I was I was really confused as to why you made it a point to
Forget the time
Down and then once
You put it once you put it
Together as like
Of course that's an important thing
You should 8.00 broke out while he was at 2 and a half hours
Before the show
Of like
Get your information together
Get on air
It makes it worse
This is where he goes
Stupid in that they'll at least tell you though the white narrative that you wanted
Start thing
Bombings
Collapse
Tell you what's going to happen
Criminology
Good luck
I told you last year.
So is the media reaction like this is minutes after the show start
That you know that this is a false flag
This is the government Bankers changing something to get you
To stop thinking about the idea that a lot of Europe
Punic on Emmy's are in trouble
Yeah right now
I would say that's irresponsible
I believe he already started in the first clip
Was used to eat
Compare it to Oklahoma City
He's doing a lot of like
Yeah he's trying to Anchor that connection in people
Associate unrelated things to this
To further his argument
Which is baseless
That
I don't know
Patient
I think you hate me Coronavirus
I love
So much right now
To get this episode together was
One of them
Most
I do like digging into stop it I like having a topic
Learn about and understand
Specifically
In the morning Linda Thompson
Was it was a Tuesday
I guess but I can weather it I guess
Yes there's something
Not great about myself but
Or good I don't know what it is
Belong to cover
And I don't want to
Necessarily
Predictions that he has and I would say that all of them are not
He knows nothing about oslo's prison system went to prison is like tried to sue the government
For violating human rights
In terms of its first case and then was overturned
Court over upheld
The appeal so they're like no we didn't
F*** that guy
PlayStation 3
F*** you a bunch of periodically about various
Steve Maynard like
I will save it from my research I knows it before the attack
He was very again
I use against
Hitler and the National Socialist
Because he believed that they
Got the wrong guys
No because disservice to the Germanic White
Because they
Created through their foolhardy
Israel Israel
He's not against Israel either
Straight talk to nail down and I'll do my best in all of it in due time
But he's against Hitler in the
Knox
Before the attack because
If they happen to try to do this genocide
F*** you man
Gee thanks
Because of their action
The blowback
Created the multiculturalism and the political correct
That he is so again
So he doesn't hate Hitler for the reasons
You should he hate them because
The aftermath of it
Has created the world that we live in today where there's a plurality of people's rights
People should be able to live
Together
And please so he's kind of more like a
I like those white nationalism
Yeah
It's tough to unpack if you hate
Bike
Chinese or black
People
Probably a lot of bigotry underneath
But the more you dig into him
Read things the people who knew him
Before would say like
Past co-workers
There's a thread of like he was a really good worker he's very competent
But he would really get bothered and annoyed by Pakistani people dating
And stuff like that
I didn't like just anytime Muslims would come up you get mad
And stuff like that crawl
About those Pacific
Xbox
Go to
My point of pausing this clip is just to say Alex's prediction of it being a drug.
Do not receive
Ezz clear-eyed
F******
Terrorist
Murderer
To the effect of I apologize I didn't kill more people
He's a psychopath
Adamantine Steel
It's not native adamantium
Help
Total chaos
So Alex is going out on a limb and saying this is Muslim terrorists and they were abetted by the government
I'm probably blew themselves up in the car all of you
Completely wrong
All of a sudden getting on air immediately and creating a narrative
Irresponsible
And based on nothing other than his quote on quote gut
Or whatever
His deep research that he does like every time
Like that
And it's not it's absolutely not it's
Like right now today
We are in a situation where in 2018
Recording is on Sunday there was a mass shooting this morning
Yep in the same way that we don't have all the details while we're recording this
You'll be responsible for us
To decide
And create some sort of a storyline out of that
Rack-O if we were they all look at this another way
Whether or not that is the truth that comes out we don't know that while we're recording this
Who made listen to us
So he's doing that about this and it's
Disgraceful
It's real gross
For some reason
We deal with his wife
Soupremacy
All the time
Deal with all of his s*** all the time but anytime he
He minimizes tragedy
The way that he
He does like after any of these Mash
People die
And he turns them into props
That are that might as well be f******
Mannequins
Isn't even worse now that you know
This is just such a
F****** punched
God yeah I'm sorry to bring this into your life but by the time we get to the end of this you'll understand
Much more fully
Why I think
As much as I
Learn about this year about that
I'm overwhelmed by how much I appreciate
Pointing Us in this direction
What happened because I think that we can
Can highlight
Something that is
Very demonstrative
Big
Big problem about Alex Jones
That I think that we have
Necessarily
Dealt with in the way that we shouldn't we're going to
Over the course of the
Pictures of
We talked about his b******* regarding
Hook all the
Big f******
So much worse
Nail right on the head that he seems to enjoy this
Like at the beginning of the episode the first clip we played he was talking about the shooting in the
With kind of like almost excitement about it do you like there
Yeah he's doing like a announcer revoiced
And that continues into this next clip I really think he's relishing
The fact there's some sort of tragedy
You know about that
Explosion went off in Oslo Norway
Housing Ministry
Call Mom
Looks like Oklahoma City
Eyewitness reports
She's doing that voice with
Almost
At lead this is bleeding this is going to leave that kind of thing
Which is gross and then
Bring up Oklahoma City
The idea that there was a
Make these make
Knew about Oklahoma City
And was third in terms of planning
By what Timothy McVeigh did and he was frustrated by the fact that you done it because
To get the bomb supplies that you need in order to
Fertilizer let's make sure we keep track of this for no reason
Zoe lamented the idea that
Yep god dammit
Girl
Alright so
The false flag
About whether or not this is a real thing
Children
Write about the Muslim
When the total collapse
Research right now
Norway
This individual
Rosler wasn't a country
But with the timer
I would check your percent
Percent chance this is real
So Alex's is correct is accurately read
From reports
That it was probably
Target prime minister
And the reason is because
You deem him a supporter of multiculturalism and someone who is unacceptable and a
Three classifications of
Traders class
BMW presidents or prime minister
But that was
Additionally utoya Island
From the Labour party which party that
Supported multiculturalism
And also a former politician
One of the big
Supporters of multiculturalism in Norway
Was scheduled to give a speech there
And she did go give us
Speech therapy but it already left by the time because he got caught in traffic and s*** on the way over to the island
So the idea that
Like Alex
Kind of Remy wrong about the globalist
Doing this
Absolutely was targeting these people
For the reason of killing and taking out the political security
Tubi
Supporters
Plurality
Culture
Religion
All those things
He thought was going to destroy Europe
So
Yeah
White
Come on let's let's
And let's get out of here
I know.
What is all on a f****** Arc blow it up after through the Journey has taken on
Like a slightly different meaning in the last day
Just relax
List
More seriously that don't directly involve
Cuz it does
This absolutely does
Like
Because I always do babe
Committed these crimes
But I didn't understand
The full picture of it
I think you did a really terrible job of explaining what you was about
And really looking at the full picture
Because you know
I think that there is a
Face the music
He was inspired by what his goals were what
The people who were
Philosophically aligned
Things like that I think you have
You have to deal with
What are commonalities of rhetoric
Is it safe to say
That he is a logical extension of that rhetoric you know what I mean like I really have to wrestle with issues like that
And it's not fun to do
It's really really not fun to do
Especially at 3:30 in the morning
Oh no
Hammer it home but was this guy
Who is inspired by that one dude in like the late
70s
Another guy more recently who was a huge fan of this guy who is like a
Political on the right
He was mostly inspired
In terms of his orange
Okay
Cut the balls
Put out a Manifesto
I will get into all that
Are you the one
Cartoon suck
You didn't force my hand at all it was more that I recognized that I kept
I feel like I'm teasing in a way that's inappropriate
I should just tell you
A lot of
A lot of questions
Jimmy Lee Curtis
True life
Walmart
Anyway
I celebrate his catalog
I swear to God it is still in the wrong
It's so good
One of the few movies my parents love you don't know why
I think we left the book
Nr2003 primary
Find out when Alex Jones
Started talking about George Soros
So far as we've got through 2019
There was one
Read that it was
2014 Alex
Would have jumped on the Soros bandwagon
Because
Involvement
Against
And Ukraine
Right he was a force trying to open societies up
The encroachment of Russian
Influenza virus member correctly there like there was something to do with his son being specifically targeted
Ya-ya-ya Alex
Before that we're going like party in Russia
Working Theory
I didn't think that was necessarily the case but it was open
For a possibility
I'm and because of his next life we now know it was at least before 2011
Because the bar
You could look for a
Criminal investigation
George Soros
Justice
Apartments
Investigating
This is ridiculous
Outpost
Adjust
Thesaurus
So this is about the news course
Cirrhosis investigation into bread
Also an issue of the vertigo
Lucifer which is a spin-off
DW wrestler
I just had to get our mandatory wrestling reference alphabox for today
Around a little bit
About Anders Breivik
Or even know the name or anything
About the doorway situation and ask her to dance is authentic
Topix
He wants to fully reinforce his narrative
A complaining about Soros getting
His fingers in pies of Investigation whether or not.
True I have no idea
He gets right back
You calling this
After
Doctor's office
Massive
Eyewitnesses total chaos
Music reading that exact same anything past that headline
You heard him read it like four times already
On the
Rollo Carol
A mockery of a
Just to remind you
It's a banker
Also you can find plenty of insta
Sentence of Terror
Attacks
And stuff like that if you want it if you want to save it like
You can you can
Point out of
Few times that there have been countries
Is in financial trouble
Terrorist attacks have happened
That is at best a
You need to do better than
Even further
If you are in finance
He'll travel and you see that there is a ruling class that does not
Share within that Finance
Cancel travel
It is much more likely that you're completely
Complete destruction of your life
Woodley tour they and idea
Well what have I got to lose there's a desperation
Kind of explain
But that's not
Hate hate
Here's another Alex Jones wants more statistic
Pixabay
0% of 5
100% Obama committed by brown people are Muslim attacks
Dentistry
Statistics
Still thinks it's Muslim
Funded by Stephen then the Muslims are false
You should know by now cuz I believe report that already
Come out
Any will
He still thinks it's Al-Qaeda
Or something like that
Here's a stat
Again
But I cannot
I cannot state
Any more clearly to all of you out there
Just
There have been bombings in Europe because
Nine times out of 10 or more
These bombings in Europe and the United States are completely
Yikes
Everything is globalist
Trying to
You know what he does a really smart thing he lost track of a little bit later and it's
100%
Yeah but
You catching his language in a really smart way that makes it
Incase
I get in trouble for this
All I said is 98%
You make your own conclusions from their absolute
But
He has it in the same way when he says I'm going to kill you politically
All steaks are off I'm not saying s*** it doesn't mean anything there's no consequence
Behaving this way
Saying this is fake
But I am also in
Flying that it might
Not be fake
But I'm telling you to
Air on the side of this is fake and definitely if somebody tells you otherwise
Where was the 98 % sure they're lying to you exactly
Hosta tistic Lee
They're most likely lying to you about it
So even if it is real you'll never be able to believe them that it's not real because you're
Crazy because I
I think you did a thorough breakdown of that that line of thinking there
Reno
In 2018
Alex Jones SNL real includes his
Chris Cuomo impression
His impression of George Soros life
Of course
For us to find out
Kind of like Bernie
No
Here's a clip
Bernie Sanders has released the FED audit
A partial Auto confirming 16 trillion
In secret
Dollars that's not a real amount of money
This is what the
They're getting paid off
So he has like a
He was the most popular politician
Yeah perhaps
Weather for today
Do that
Was a huge fan of Bernie's at the time he is towards somebody now
The more likely it is that in
There's a 98%
Everything that he believed was upside down
What's an exception of like Rand Ron Paul
But that's just because they
Right right
Roberto Cavalli specific
Seems like they got a pass and I think a lot of that
To do with Ron Paul's newsletter
So somehow I really want to know how he felt about Ross Perot right now
Just text right he loved there's no way we can
Call in Roxboro
Threatened
I remember that ended up leaving the election
Was going to actually pick me up
Accidentally
You do it
Is that Bernie Sanders you know what you know what's going on
From my childhood watching like SNL sketches
I don't f****** really know if I know that
It's between Dana Carvey impressions
I know that they're different I'm not sure I agree with you
I agree with you
Bill Clinton is Bill Clinton
More than Bill Clinton
Best of all of those though is that
Norm Macdonald Bob Dole
Until this year when you have at a minute
Adomian
Forms of political impressions
Alex
He still off the the doorway situation
I'm looking at actually you are
In preparation
Where what's going on
That's all
Partially reversed
They're going to be
Of the next solution in
We're not allowed to use the word up
Oh whoops
First question
Second question
What kind of Fortress are we talking like
14th century Irish Castle are we talking
Sheridan
Alright assume something along those lines.
The South
England tradition
Situation where I am
Truly genuinely races
I don't like the Welsh
I just don't like the Welsh
Probably not
No - 101.4 your bigotry
I'm going to build fortresses
And that it's fun
Like you're building a pillow Fortress
Also
The floor is lava
Your plan
No exam
I just think that's fun and demonstrates a sort of state of mine
Very serious paranoia
Differently
Because our recent episode we found from presentation
Which is Hill killing a dude
And that of course is going to come into play of how I cure various clips about his past violence
To go back and start all over again
Secret 2017 probably much worse now
So I am now here
Clip and I think
He might have killed a couple of guys
Going to rape your wife
He has a right to do it
I agree
Going to Dallas
Weighted grab-assing away and well
Fun
He left
Dallas and Rockwall and move to Austin and his sophomore year of high school so he would have been 15/16
Police report
That are closed because he was a minor
Those aren't accessible to public searches
Yeah and it's not anywhere
Internal database
I don't I don't want them to do that play anybody
I don't want anybody to do that cuz I believe in the
Do you like me
Criminal
And not because I got arrested or anything like that really good part of society
Right terms of like
You know you get arrested for stealing something as a
Once you get older if you haven't
I'm committed more crime your writing wasn't
No I respect
As we know he is still a child so it's true
His record
Should either be expunged
Also like
I mean if you killed a dude in a street fight
Like that's different than like
Feeling or something like that
Respect the privacy of it
Nothing to be said for the idea of like what he's describing here is possible
Self-defense
If he did get into a fight with someone who had a knife any
Right I don't think that
Although also Alex Jones is an unreliable narrator
Question
Once again to hammer this point home how do you think he would have been tried
Where he's not awake
That's true I apologize I'm sure Jerry Jones
I just that was my impression of him
I assume you said something like that in the Cowboys locker room I'm not sure
Anyway
It is next clip
Had previously
D2 there probably
It's important 2011
Before that
Publication
Some sort of
Indications that they believe that one
Things to be concerned about what's homegrown Terror
The idea of white people committing to
Folks to be on the lookout for
Good news
Was unfounded
Department of Homeland Security that but no thanks we won't be needing your services
So now Alex narrative
About Norway
Which is pretty
Breitbart
Fox News
Our story
Crown Vic
Fox News
As white Americans
Eagle 99.3
Call wife
Returning veterans
Does a real classified document
General
Also 100%
Oh yeah okay
Everyone drink
I've never laughed and I think we're a little shell-shocked on this episode
There's a lot of heaviness and desperately trying
Really shity
Sort of
Misunderstanding of what the Department of Homeland
Security was trying to express
Also it's really funny on this episode where we now know
That the terrorist attack
Norway was carried out by
Strictly
Non multiculturalism views that inspired him
Complaining about the United States be like
We should be aware that this is
This is a doorway
Alright
So now
We get a gas
Jordan
I'm going to guest on the show Alex's pivoting away from the doorway talk
Amanda
Encounter
In the past
But she is someone who has a real fun
Backstory for me to tell you
And more
Highway listening to her couple days ago
Drinking
Investigative journalist
Cool
I
No Janet Phelan
Why do I know her name
Mostly
Is biological weapon
She covers a lot
She's written a number of books one of them is called Hitler's poem
Which I tried book
Could not find a synopsis
If it's a positive
Book about Hitler
Book of poetry
It could be I have no idea
Just did it exist
All limericks
Hitler only wrote Limerick there once was a Hitler from Nantucket
I'll give you a little bit information about Janet Phelan we'll see if any of those drugs or memory where you might know her
Investigative journalist who largely
Specialize in BIO weapon
Reroute of arguing that the United States has consistently and wantonly violated biological and chemical weapons
The research that the labs are doing
What states are offensive or defensive
But she provides nothing to suggest that they are in fact
There's an appeal to the RN argument is
Both maybe but
Is there is also
You know those papers that come out their stories to come out to
Explain the research
Being done
In terms of
Creating virulent strains of thing
Write one of the big reasons
Defenses against
Specific
Self the question why is it that we have a pro
Particularly
Smallpox virus
The help
You know people who are fallible
Great you know that kind of
Because
The idea that we aren't the only people who have
Pictures of
Destroyed
The f****** world
You try and come up with as many inoculations as many
Cures that you can try and find ways around
Becoming weaponize
Bob's
It's like nuclear weapon
Nobody should have until nobody has them
People should have
At the same time
You think it's naive to think that we're not doing anything on that front
Uno's
You get to just play a game with yourself
And whatever you like to believe
When you ask what is the primary
Motivation
Primary motivation
Even then
What person is doing the research
Like we can't know the intentions
Until we ask
Meet a real mad scientist me like that's not good
Right
Behind her
She writes for and released a book called exile
Through a publication called
New Eastern Outlook
Politico describes new Eastern Outlook is a geo-political Journal published by a government
And run it runs headlines like
Ku Klux Klan dados new Ally
As the United States confronted Russian Allied Bashar al-assad
For using chemical weapons against Syrian children this spring
Quote proof
Turkey did 2013 sarin attack
And quote exclusive trip to Russia first
The Budapest Beacon New Eastern Outlook is known to be kremlin-backed a Russian propaganda
Outlet targeting foreign audience
An article in Sputnik with the headline quotes
Here's how Putin and healthy diet made Russian product
In China
Was based on an article from the new Eastern
It is a front for a Russian
State
The Academy of Sciences pro-russian propaganda for foreign audiences
Supreme
I don't know forces behind new Eastern Outlook
How to fight Western propaganda
Work
It's essential to focus on emotion
He begins quote
First they manufacture monstrous lies and then they tell us we should be
Is love objective is passion
Our dreams defendable logical and philosophically
Andre Iguodala
Andre goes on to ask
Do we counter that
Tactics and strategy of the destructive and ruthless Empire with our honesty
Research
Was telling
Meticulously investigative back
Yeah
He does not directly answer the question
Poetry emotionally-charged songs
I've always been more effective than
Academic studies all of them written by Hitler or political novels in film
Cartoons and posters
Someone
Because they're lying should we lie as well no
We should try to be as truthful as man we should try to be as truthful as we can
But our message should often be a bridge
So the billions
Not just the selected
If you can understand it
With the SparkNotes of reality and he's leaning heavily towards not the real one
She's one of the people behind
To do Easter Network
His article year
Very clearly lays out like
Yeah we should tell the truth truth
M4 murkiness effect
So
People react
More emotion
Run the World
Done
Yeah but
Guiding Prince
Baseball for one of the people
Who's in charge of the new year
I think identikit
To me that maybe they don't have a hard journalistic
Editorial
Knossos
Location that she works released
Foreign propaganda relationship
Alright so then I'm assuming that means
I can trust everything
She says in the center
Implicit
Any higher order thinking at all.
Respond as though everything
She says
Categorical
Play that clip
Ruckus most stuff like they can't possibly prove
Four biological labs and stuff like that
Color
I was going through
If we if we try and get into any of this
Time-suck
You can just sort of Pont
I am just say like to level four
Biological research
You got a sense of what I'm talking about that
Secretly level 2
I think it has to do with like the level of Defense
Surrounded like whether or not they have to be deep underground
Multiple times
Episode
Does it mean you break out in mice
No
But I'm assuming because
That's automatic
His narrative
It's an article and a headline in the New York Times that reads biotera researchers build a Morley
Apple Mouse
There's a f****** scary headline
The article
The article is about how researchers placed a single existing Mouse poxvirus
That would make it super
Preventive measures
Because it's often I how we develop protection for humans
The results show that the best defenses
Quite effective
And preventing deadly disease not only human
Exposed to customize smallpox
Of similar design
It's like a really huge
Benefit
Against
Spiders
It's a one of the
Who plays the other sort of
Credit One
Animals
It's nearly invaluable the idea of having the protection there's no other way to designs
Sound design in the viruses
Yeah
I think it's
Not gross but I think it's scary
The ideas about it and it's sort of weird to your thought processes like
Their scientists sitting around
Giving these animals horrible diseases
You don't like that thanks New York Times for the clickbait as headline you could possibly make
Instead of
Still working to protect you
Scared about the prospect of
Diseases like smallpox getting out
But from the article quote the leaders of the research said that the lethal Mouse virus would
Have no effect on humans
Even if it somehow escaped from the lab
Which they said was safeguarded at biosafety level
Gordon's hours
With no address
To my knowledge
Suggest this kind of research poses any sort of human risk
Said Mark Buller
Professor of molecular micro microbiology Saint Louis University
Who directed
Research of prologue to all zombie movies
Many experiments have shown the mass box does not cause disease in humans
Experts said both the threat of such developments
The federal Response Team part of the theoretical debates
Not something to worry about for now
They split over whether the research was prudent
So any kind of argument that happened in that
The
It's worth it is it good
Is this is this a legitimate risk that we are defending against
Vaccine for mausbach
For mice
Or is it
I don't I don't
Hello
Back to
The Norway
We're a little bit later in the show Alex's no reason
Do not know a lot of it
Details about it
Other than him not really
Caring to not really caring to do his job as a journalist right
You get back to it
And makes it very clear that
You knew that it would be jihadis
Norway blast Target
Total chaos
Helpers of the global Jihad responsibilities
I meant yet how helpers of the anode rod
Responsibility
And this is an issue that
Claimed responsibility for
That's why you have to always
Situations
You can't just say oh they said
Yeah so he's not doing that he's not following appropriate
It's for Isis
Is to claim responsibility for every terrorist bombing as though they are everywhere all the time
You know terrorists
Vic creating Terror
Right that's it
To help them when they take
Responsibility
She said it's really good because oftentimes
People don't survive
Because what are you going to be mad at you that you're lying
You're already enough people are going to believe you regardless
Whether or not
Alex
What's called like
A dominating strategy
And you have to do quick because another terrorist group from my
Do the same thing
First one
Recording very generally that they did it
Ron Perlman
Cowboys
This is why
Addresses police officer open
Now reportedly there's been a shooting
That we should have just shifted this earlier this is Shelby
In Norway
It was dress like a cop
Help us
Norway
T-jump f***
Guess what you can own guns in Norway
Don't they have
American Construction
But you ain't guess what
Hey guess what I know from reading his
He's goddamn Manifesto
He bought the guns in Norway
Legally
You can buy gun
Except for automatic weapons
In Norway
They just have some standards like in terms of if you're going to buy a gun
You need to have some training courses
And you need to give a
Some of the reasons that they are allow
Right Recreation
Self-defense
Our if you are employed in a like
Active
To own a gun
Alex
You are a gun guy
You should know gun laws
Guns are not outlawed in Norway
The same way
He would like that to be the case
Right
It's cuz they were on an island
There was a guard there
Anders Breivik
Smart enough
But he was aware enough to
Kill that guy immediately
So he took that guy out the guy with a gun right in order to neutral
Only argument is like every one of those children
Ever to be the world
Absolutely the wrong angle
Ifucking camp where they're learning and they're clearly politically-motivated cuz it's
Labour party
Political camp
A good time you got to assume that if they're like
A lot of people were under 18
Who are there
Probably f******
Nerds yeah I don't mean that to be a dick when I was a kid
Really hard to zip line when you have an AKA on your back I'm having gun
And if
Yeah you don't want them having gun
Because they would not know how to use them they're not
Sort of
Sympathy
Rambo kid that Alex is probably imagine
Discuss super clear
If you're listening
AngelList
None of
The only reason we are laughing
Because this is
Beyond
Comprehend
Put the prescriptions that Alex is making or f******
Doing is laughing about
Movie f****** don't to what u.s. Constitution
You can have gun
Any ideas like oh there was no 12
Protect those
And you don't want these
It would it would make for first of all.
I meant
Sandoval
Like like we're joking around about
Spell they don't want to
Have gun they want to go to
So
Sucks
Every part of being alive now
Yep
So now it's going to suck
I'm going to get into the
The Manifest
Alex has brought back up
He's brought back up the
Most difficult planning on how we're going to cover this episode
At what point do we get into the
And I I don't know I don't know if it's the best
But we got it
Embarking on the attack Andrews brevik emailed
His
Page Manifesto
To approximately 1,000 email addresses that he had Farms
From European Patriot Facebook account
Too long
He spent
Hours
H and
Farming these email addresses off Facebook account
Cuz he wanted to try and
Within
Superreactionary
Patriot
The base
European
Facebook
Pages
Various other sources
Did a bunch of stuff
Unabomber replace every time you said
The black people
With Muslims
Replaced
Trying to make it his own
Wow copy and paste
At least hundreds of pages
He only had like sex
The outrageously long document lays out his
Political correctness anti-semitism
Nationalism
Clear as day
It even describes exactly why he committed
These terrorist attacks
We plan the attacks
4 years before carrying them out
And how he lamented that you have to work alone
He couldn't risk
Anyone else being involved
Might give up
Police
Or whether or not
It would be a risk for them to know
About it when you go through
Could jeopardize a conspiracy
Is the worst
Right it's the worst idea
Illegitimate
Terrible idea
M brevik Manifesto
Overwhelmed Bible
I braced myself and dug-in but ultimately had to
Concede there's no way I was ever going to read all this b*******
I made it through couple hundred pages
With rambling complaints about history ranging from declined evils of cultural Marxism
Deciding crimes Muslims committed in the 1100
Is proof of islamism
Incompatible
Western
Put some cookie
Better actually
Well if your cookie
Yeah oh no I thought I was
I'd like
I don't normally like raisin cookies
But I heard that his
I wish there was
I would really big.
Like this
How much nonsense
I really wouldn't
Oh and by the way my favorite Sunday I like to wake up at about 9
She has like
Legitimate
Pages upon pages
A various different like armor schematic
You could use
If you wanted
Commit smash-and-grab terrorist attack
Cookie recipe
100 f****** it's entirely possible
You didn't even
Ice cream.
Like I said I read at least a couple hundred
You don't need to read this whole document
To see shocking parallel
The totalitarian nature of political correctness
Can be seen on campuses where PC is taking over the college
Freedom speech
Of the press
And even thought are all eliminate
Or you can skip the page 29 where you find this
Quote today the feminization of European culture
Moving rapidly since the 1960s
Continues to intensify
Indeed the present-day radical feminist assault
Support of mass movement immigration
Has political parallel to their anti-colonial effort
Is impart a continuation of a century-old effort to destroy traditional European structures
The very Foundation of European culture
Indeed the feminization of European culture is nearly completed
And the last Bastion of male domination
The police force and Military is under assault
An awful lot like Alex Jones saying that all these strong powerful
Simoniz just roll over there
Yep
At their very existence more trendy than boyfriend
Irene
This guy is it finally honest about the police in the military
Toxic masculinity white-dominated meals
Telling the truth about it until the truth about it
There's so many more parallel
Braddock to cry cultural Marxism
Quiet Revolution propagating the European hate ideology
With the gold
Destroying Western Civilization
And which one
And which was anti-god anti-christian
Anti masculine anti tradition
An anti morality
What are you putting all that list together that's exactly
Exactly a cultural Marxism is
Just replace globalist
Whenever he says cultural Marxism
Because it's the same
Put down to the world
Cultural Marxism is this idea that like
Classical economic Marxist ideas
Had to do largely with the redistribution of power
That sort of thing
Economic power
To the cultural mark
Closest idea
Is the idea of
Multiculturalism
Feminism
Racerite
Those sorts of things
Have to do with a cultural version of Marxism
Where you're trying to redistribute
The power forcefully
What they're trying to fly
It's saying
What they're trying to him
Plaid
Is bad
Vidi5
An equitable exist
Wherein there is no domination
By any one of these groups of all the other
That is a
Stealth way of creating bat-like
That's soviet-era communism
Which again
Economic system the issue with
Government
Set the minutes
Nazi
The concepts behind
Hey maybe everybody should
It was the oligarchy that
Once again
We live in such
Let's not go too far down this road
Apologize
Apologies
Alex tells about how their opponent
Refuse to engage with ideas
I just shut them down by calling them
All discussion Hippie Sabotage with the slogan
Prejudice and racism islamophobia
Take the struggle from the common battlefield of argument
Into the opponent's camp
His self-esteem as a member of civilized society
Of course ugly things
Prejudice in islamophobia
Are you recognizing in this Manifesto not only the everything
Represent modern Alex Jones
But also so much
That represent
The modern-day right
Didn't you just go to a pool supply store in like saw three Muslim women and he was like
Does this all right
Now
I've only it was that simple Supply
Superficial
His plan for the future is specifically pro-russia
Provided the Russia kicks out all the Muslims
He's also pro.app are tied South Africa
Coincidentally
If what is it supposes that he imagined
If it wanted to soldiers and Andrews Braddock's imagine
Exist
Traffic is a whole speech prepared for them in his Manifesto
Not laminate
The speech that he has for them
It includes the Thomas Jefferson quote
The tree of Liberty must be refreshed
From time to time with the blood of patriots and tyrants
Which coincidentally is something I was doing
Coincidence that the other has in his speech that these people are supposed to read in court is Mark Twain's quote
The time of change the Patriot is scarce man
He's hated and scorned when it's caused
When the Patriot
Cosmo
Alex says all the f****** time
People are using the
Exactly tropes in terms of pushing
I'm very idea of what they want the world to be
And how to justify their actions
All of which are perversions of the meaning of those
To some extent
Rambling Manifesto everything isn't Alex Jones talking
Quotes the patriarchy must be established
Re-established
News corporation
Controlled by cultural marxists multiculturalism
Engagement full scale War
Cultural conservatism in nationalism
For every newborn Muslim in Europe the cultural marxists Multicultural is to automatically get one more vote
And we all know 98% of Muslims give their votes to multiculturalism
Is King
The traditional family is under attack
It goes on and on to the point where it's different
Between Frederick and Alex's vision of an ideal Society
Reddick described his
Quote one
Islam cannot be present
And ethnic homogeneous people
An educated people with high average IQ
Cultural conservative policies
Nationalistic polish
Free market
All of this is exactly
What Alex would be in line
Whether he would be
F******
I wouldn't say
Play brave enough because that
The positive connotation
The weather or not he would have the wherewithal
To actually see things like
What I would like is Islam to be gone
What I would like is an ethnically homogeneous people to be around me
Whether or not he has the
I would say
Schnitz because you know
But he's trying to make money off
He does believe those
Absolute
His actions imply very clearly
Him and Anders Breivik
Exactly the same positive vision
What they want
64 * in the manifesto bread excites Robert Spencer
The anti-muslim proprietor of the website Jihad watch
Coincidentally Robert Spencer is a regular guest on Alex's show and Alex uses Jihad watch as a source consta
Reddick was a big admirer of geert Wilders
Someone Alex
Actively came back 2 hours
Alex
And said was part of
The Nationalist resurgence
Red excited Wilder's
He's one of the few who can quote claim to be conservative parties in their whole culture
Traffic also in his Manifesto expressing support for the English Defence League
Hopelessly naive
Before committing his attack brevik helps create a Norway satellite of
The edl
The Norway
In case you forgotten was created by Tommy Robinson
Alright personality Vox Dei admirers and love
Peter's brevik
He refers to Ramona's blog is think bread
That's not good
Vox day has been a guest on Alex Jones Show
As recently as
In August 2018
You read through this Manifesto in
The modern right
In our country
It's horrifying
This is what I'm talking about when I said I didn't understand
Like I knew he was a bigot terrorists and all that stuff
But reading through this
Manifesto
Inasmuch as I did
Is
A terrifying experience
Because
What you see
And I'm not saying that all of these people have read his Manifesto and are going off of it would be f****** stupid
Assume
But what you see
Are Proto talking points
Of the alt-right world
Zach we are experiencing right now
Which is
Which is the entire Republic
Complicated because we're specifically talking about him
Is because
He in his Manifesto
Although it should be noted that while he was in prison he did come out and say I'm
Who knows
Because he finally read
Nasty literature was like
Or maybe the tide had changed
The people who are sending him messages of support were National Socialist
Any realized
Well maybe this is my team after all I'm in prison what am I going to do
Completed your you're
Circle of coming around
The right to just simply be ignored and demolish
No
May be demolished but not ignored
I think
I think that what you see here
In 2011
This world was not
What it is now
In terms of
Alex wasn't
In 2011 in terms of his books
Open about it
The traction that
Game by organization
Like
Rebel media people like Jack
Sawbuck
People like Lauren Southern
Samantha has come to be such a
Part of our
Political dialogue
These negative and Ill
Meaning
Bad faith
That are clogging up
Our political discourse
Including
Goddamn president
Whether or not they know it
I believe that they are very
Very
Inspired
By the manifesto that and
Braddock put out
And I don't think in any way that he was
But I think that his martyrdom in quotes
Vic neo-Nazi
Anti-muslim Folk
Experian
Led to an elevation of a lot of the talking
That he put through in his
Manifesto
I think you got a lot more traction then maybe even
He realizes
From his self translating
Open
Obviously
Again
It's stupid to say
No they haven't they have a conclusion on their own
Because
There
F******
It's just got f****** jarring
Specific
People mentioned in the manifesto
Alex Jones
Respects and loves
It's jarring to the exact stalking
Pinpoint if you just replace
Cultural marxists with globalist
It's f******
The similarities that receipt
Very very
I think that's fair.
For confirmation of course they are
Are you looking at me
Like
That's fair
So they're really troubling because now it's time to explain the name of his
Manifesto
It's called 2083 a European Declaration of
Independence
Because toward the tail end of his very long very dumb.
Anders Breivik lays out his vision
What will happen in the future
Namely a 3-phase European Civil War which he believed he would help start
Leading to the
Reclaiming their world
In 28
Dirty thoughts
I don't want to steamroll you
My first thought
Is not to engage with the content
Document
What was all the refugees coming in from all the different places I think those are white
What the f***
Why are we
Are you sure we can't kill him
I can't
I know that
Yeah okay
Okay
Sonia
Note
Norway
Whataburger richforce
Friend Norway you got to have one friend in Norway I don't bother
Universal thing your calls for murder
Love you so much I want a I want a penpal
Who is willing to murder this guy
I think you have to Ocean's 11 is really high in the most highly secured prisoners
In the entire country
Yeah prisoner who's like the longest sentence
Because
I mean
If you read his Manifesto It's f****** clear his planning
Doing this for years
He started a company
Specifically
Get enough money
In order to
To do the attack
He ended up getting like 2 million
But it would have been a hundred thousand
The dollar is worth
A money from this company and then walked away
Because he was just trying
Raise the money
In order to
To fund his ability to
To plan this attack
Like it's an interlude Icarus
Level of like
Very specific
Information they like
Anybody who anybody who wants to be like
This was something that the globalist that up or some of that
They're not engaging with
Very very available information
From him
Do you have any
Indication of
Was there like a turning point
He's asked how old was he
I don't use 39 now
This would have been like it's 17
Probably some
I don't know I don't even listen I like 40
But I also feel like
People who do the
I would
Comfortable in assuming that they kind of
Create a heroic mythology around
Unreliable narrator aspect
Exactly why they're right
He says he's radicalized by the Serbian really all that was with to give him cover
And make him a
0 possibly
Still with him from the f******
Everything about it is Mom
I know about his mom from
Who's the Chad nest
DDD feels really bad about it
Is this your Manifesto
He has HPV to the family
Just consider his sort of a patriarchal
Views and stuff like that like
Turn kitchen
And not f******
Describes
Involves like
Lights by Pakistani
Anaerobe
Obviously that stuff was already in him
From the jump is more racism
Coming from pack
Sandy's in Arab stores white people ever
Pakistanis in Muslims are like that that's crazy I had a friend Junior High who hated
Started before the game a little bit
But the reason
Business
And he got
In a deal with
A couple
Individual
Arabic
And the deal went bad
And
The dad I guess
Complain so much
Middle School child
Extrapolated in generalized
To all people who are Arabic
Or Muslims
You read this
You read this Manifesto into stuff he talks about 4
From like his childhood
I think there's a little
Colonel was already there
I don't want to psychoanalyze
Say like you don't care about the Serbian bombing
His house f***
This f******
Yeah
If we could executed let's say 100,000 Marxist intellectuals in Western Europe after World War II
And all forms of marxist Doctrine
We could have prevented the creation of anti-european hate ideology known as multiculturalism
God
Do that mental
It's absolutely essential that we the cultural conservative Patriots of Europe to not repeat that mistake again
In all our efforts must be to Target and execute the Multicultural lift wherever we find them
In Phase 1 2 or 3 of the European Civil War
He goes on to Advocate against the deportation of Muslim vote for an even worse reason than you would guess
The biggest threat to ineffective and thorough lynching campaign to The Temptations
Commence the deportation of Buzz
This is why lynching for should only professional leadership
With a given unofficial and clandestine man no
No path
Pass no no
Ever
I'm talking about
I know and this is awful
But
My position is I'm reading all of this
Because
Tunak
Is not
To show what the lodge
Of this similar rhetoric
Did Alex Jones
This guy
Exactly point if I understand correctly
Is that if you ask
If you put the DeRidder eckhaus
Then this is the only way this is the only thing that makes
I'm not saying actions or logical
F****** hard
But if
Play Alex Jones's world
There's no reason not to
Dedicate yourself
Gears
To planning some sort of event that you think
Is going to kick off a civil war Europe
Against the multiculturalism
You think or ruining
White European culture
There's no what there's
It does
It doesn't make logical sense
Twisted mind
If he had never killed anybody Alex Wood
Treat him as a hero
She was like
Public intellectual
Who just put this out as a doctor
Jordan
Sorry
Freddie Gibbs
Gives advice on assassinations
It's much more rational and pragmatic also focus on the easier unprotected Target
Instead of sacrificing Good Men on an impossible Target
Explain
Cultural Marxism
Peppers
5 category-b traitors within 2 hours
You are usually always be caught so it's going home and waiting for someone to knock on your door
Move swiftly to your second target then the Third
Etcetera
YouTube
Plural thrower
Should you do let's Multicultural if politician
Noting that quotes
I severely burned category a arbitrator willing reality become a living symbol of what awaits individuals guilty
I'm trying to sell their own people into Islamic slavery
Is a deterrent
Contribute
Do I spread fear in the hearts of the rest of the traitors
And will just cause more ideological dead body
He or she will become a Living testament
Will happen to a category and betrayed
And everyone will learn that high treason is not without risk
You can't Call wifey
Never
Now I mean
His goal is specifically
To spread
Fear
Terrorist
Go to the
He thinks journalists are Traders just like Alec
Annual Gatherings for journalists in all Western European country
Few calories are considered the most
Targets for large-scale shakatak
He also legitimately Advocates using weapons of mass destruction
Multiculturalism
Play WMV on fighting the cultural marxists Multicultural estrogens of Western Europe
Especially explosive weapon
Barrack Buster types fertilizer bombs in the lights
Other types of weapons of mass destruction biological and chemical must be considered as realistic options as well
Dozens of pages of
Very specific
Instructions on how to make bombs
Include the detailed breakdown of all the various Metals people would be awarded for killing traitors
What is revolution
Kicks off
Family complicated operation plan
Protect
Is Extreme is bombing power play
He's been countless hours of his life putting together this Manifesto
And it's clear from the text that you knew when he was writing it
But he was going to kill a bunch of people
He wrote this Manifesto and carried out his attacks
He believed the same things that Alex
Namely that Muslims are destructive force
And they'll destroy Western culture
And they're being aided and abetted by a traitorous government Force
Anders Breivik calls them cultural marxists
Alex calls them globalist
But they're talking about exactly the same
Here's why the result of the utmost importance
Anders Breivik
Ames attack
Represent as I said
The Logical end result of the rhetoric that both he and Alex Jones
Employ about the world
But one of them is willing to put those beliefs into action
The other mostly wants to make money off train
Coke's others
Send to doing the dirty work for him
And that is my position on
All of them
My position
Is that I think Anders brevik
Was
Elect
Did President
Under the name
I m similarities he does talk about like
Paths where you can
Deport people
Lady does have like almost Trail of Tears
Free plans inside because
He's not talking about a genocide of Muslims
SAFE credit or not
Credit
I wish I could
Under no circumstances when talking about Isis
Do you have to give it to
F******
Myself
Because he's not
Does just talk about like
Two countries
This weekend then
Exploit
It essentially genocide through different
Our world and Alex
It's really important enough
This is the entire philosophy
Recipe from the beginning of America
This is what America is
Built upon
The word
If you can't accept it that's that's what the Constitution was written about
That's what it was
NFL to imagine that some sort of outlier
Some sort of like
Something so far outside of what the human race
Has ever even considered
Just really remember the 1776 is f****** Anders brevik
And that's why reading over this Manifesto was
Such a dork
Look in the mirror 27
Not but I believe it and like looking in the mirror I'm
Did the finger is pointing at me right
But you wish you would
Domino like you read the manifesto
And you see like
Like the idea of bringing back the patriarchy
These are large-scale things that he would
Primarily motivated by
Under the attack
On
Bicultural
By political correctness
Things that are exact
Exactly the same
I don't know what to do with this other than to say
F****** just take a second
I wouldn't
It was a dick
Very just
Night of my life
But if you do
You'll see
Artio
You'll see the stuff we talked about
It's profoundly.
Which is also why we will never become
I told you Jordan
Because my dark mirror is
I think episode 1 where that guy f**** Pig and I don't want to talk about what I did
But technically
Mirror
My episode is that one red one
Treadmill
I'm not watching the show anymore
Like this is
To f****** real
I'll go back
I want to tell you
Horrible
I were about to get very sick
Because brevik
1500 page
Festo
Starts the way out something of a weird diary documenting
Journey tour
Is perceived martyrdom
Noting that he started working on this Manifesto in
In 2006
5 years before the eventual attacks
What do you mean
Are you never a caucus Diaries
He started in 2006 on his Manifesto
Canvas compendium
You started
On his actual planning for
For the attack for years prior to that
So is 9 years
Of planning
For the
The manifesto
But this diary
It gives
Such a weird
And these days
Describe
F******
Yeah when you consider that he knew as he was writing this.
Is he's going to kill a bunch of people
Breeze perceived
He has but multiculturalism
When you read this
Disappointing
Sad pics
Picture of a person
Cuz that would have been really weak
My best friend Peter's 30th birthday
We're going to Budapest party hard for 5 days
You don't get to do that hold on
Hungarian girls are hot as hell
Relationships with a good of my mission
Doesn't hurt to have a little fun
And then there's an emoticon
With V8 is Manifesto
It's the two eyes
The Colon D smiling face
Teenage girl serial killer
I don't think I've consumed this much alcohol for many years totally awesome
That's in the manifesto
No no
From January 2010
Has become notorious as a downloader of pirated movies series and Games Etc
Increasing number of sites have been closed down lately
Stealing is bad I even made
When you've devoted your entire life to a good cause you can allow yourself some naughtiness
Especially if it
Can contribute to your lack of funds
Off
Yes guess no one's perfect
Colon
Multi-entry drama that plays out where he goes to Prague I share this isn't written entirely in ASCII format
Might as well
No
Dude this is my favorite thing
I want to say like
I don't want to like us often and make light this
Horrible horrible person
But if you actually read this diary
You get a glimpse of a really pathetic dude
And I think that's a part of it
Now but hold on
And this is something we talked about pre-show as to whether or not it should be brought up
In our in our car
But
If you want to go with a further parallel
Find it
Hard not to
Put this together with Alex Jones watch
Well you know what I'm saying
Before we got on here
Come up I don't have a real comment on it
Talk about it
Percy is meaningless to
Do people with no shame
ITunes
To focus on
Doesn't charm was like you know what let's just
Let this one go everybody else can dunk on him the way that they want until you brought it up within the context of this guy
Guys weird
Manifesto diary
Including all of this like all of this s*** that I espouse
You still got to get your rocks off
Like that to me is that concept
You should hold on to that talk
No not a quote with a smiley face with tongue out
That idea that you're expressing is going you're going to get matter at a later
As we get to
Is there is anything funny
And that is a Thursday multi
Drama that plays at work goes to Prague to buy weapon
Because he saw a BBC special about how they're a lot of hardened criminals in Prague
It starts with him talking about his fears of being killed
With transition sent to him being surprised
Police lights
Hey there aren't any Muslims walking around
He ultimately failed to find any guns
To buy in Prague
But reassure himself
Regardless of the outcome
This mission
Other great vacation
A lot of amazing architecture I've also partied a lot with people
Sonia get on a plane Keller
He also talks about f******
Two girls while he's in Prague because he was afraid
He's going to die on that trip
Really
Really want to make this clear he's Dona do not do anything like that
Please oh my God I don't want to eat them if you want it to look I don't want to be that guy
I don't want a specific like give give like no
He's like I thought these two girls in Prague
I know that I do that's not my kind of thing but like I might have it on this trip so I got a phuc
Dude
Just
Truckin live your life stop it with this s***
From a November 2010 post
I'm currently watching Dexter
The series is about a forensic mass murderer hilarious
I'm also playing
I'm also playing Fallout 3 New Vegas at the moment
After finishing BioShock 2
I'm going to try the New World of Warcraft cataclysm when it's released in December
Time to dust off my made
Manifesto is legitimately gamergate writ large
The dates match
I don't know I'd probably more like 2013.
Aquage again not to
But that's subsection
Of like that toxic masculinity
As it applies to any kind of nerd culture
A being a
What's fascinating
In the
Mass Killers there's always assertive anger or violence
And I'm not entirely sure but I'm not sure I actually see
But as I've already mentioned
He specifically talks about his mom
And his sister having St
Actual domestic violence
No one ever proved why
Masculinity is worse
Then people who
Xzibit the idea that masculinity is great for it
Yeah
Message from this journal
Entry in his Manifesto
No that was from his lawsuit against the piskies
Yeah I don't like my route
Blizzard I've got a PlayStation 2 I can't get any of the f****** Mario game voicemail
It's reasonable directly that proves your point entirely
Got that we weren't talking about Alex in this point
Specifically in his lawsuit
Complained about
Rayman
Rayman isn't
That's probably what
Relationship
Locate my plans and may jeopardize my operation
And I don't feel comfortable manipulating girls anymore into one nightstand I'm not the person I'm not that person anymore
Girls in Prague this is where
I brought this up already
Girls in Prague though
But that was mainly because it was a realistic chance that I would end up dead during the process of establishing
Weapons connection
I won't make any effort to try and completely justify it though human males are imperfect by default in their plague by there by
Biological needs
Nevertheless screwing around outside of marriage is after all the relatively small Cent compared to the huge amounts of Grace
I'm about to generate with my martyrdom operation
Couldn't hold on
It is essential
You do what is required
To keep morale and motivation at high-level
Especially just prior to operation critical mama
I reserved two thousand Euro from my operations budget
One week prior to execution of the mission
I'll probably arrange that just before after I attend by final Martyrs mass at frogner church
It will contribute to ease my mind
Play imagine I will be tense and very nervous
It's easier to face death if
If you know your biologically mentally and spiritually
Now
By no means
Am I disparaging the sex worker
Nor the people who search them out
Any number of possible reason
Knotel ever
In your Manifesto about how the patriarchy
Please don't
F****** elucidate why the patriarchy is terrible
Sprite and then also
I do f******
Horrible is
Is it to put that sex worker
Like she doesn't know that
Context of all this
The idea may be a couple weeks later
That she murdered
F****** god unfair to
To her I don't
I don't
Smaller
Totally agree with you I had a visceral response is much smaller than
Unsurprising
Pieces of in
Information to resign from his journal
Here's a revelation that he makes
4 years ago in 2006 just before I started writing this
Compendium
I decided to move for my apartment in frogner one of the most
Is attack
Initiate cycle weeks
Followed by three weeks of dbol tabs
40 mg
Verde 86 kg
No side effects cycle
Completed
I've never in my life been more physically
2% which will prove useful
There's a bunch of insta
I'm talking about his
And even beyond that he talks about stacking
Ephedrine
Caffeine
Just sort of over-the-counter speed
The entire time
Which does
You know if you look at the time
As off
Increase
Parallel with
Sort of delusion
Manic
Surveillance
Yeah all that sort of stuff really makes
Uuu Serta Parts through
The little details
Crystal clear
Entrenched big
He already has
The diminished
Capabilities
Capacity
He has based on his
Drug use
The clear psychopath e video
He has thing you can just
Squeem from his own right
But I think more importantly is all the
Very 121
Unparalleled
It is
Strange
Tumi like anytime
You tossed that
It does absolutely
Right
Is terrifying
Because
Somebody who
Up until I was
Properly medicated at
Like what
Experienced consistent
So you you look at that
And you see the possibility
Of
If I had those thoughts
It's entirely possible that I would have committed some sort of
Absolutely not on Pain Scale
Really terrifying
Note
Fat
Epi
Truly at the end of the day
This is a
Green
This is this is this is a disease
I don't know and so you like
He's like that
To be honest
The thing that I come away from his
This is unavoidable
Like I don't I don't mean that to be like no absolutely
No
Willingness
Consider this
The thoughts he was having
The place
The fact that you kept
Himself
Exactly document
City limits
He's unable to
Anyone else
Who's playing
Bring people into the fold
Yeah
The fact that he
This sort of thing
I really don't think that
Anything you can do
Can mitigate
Someone like
Yeah because
You know
The people with
Mental illness there's help
For you if you're willing to get it I would love to
Sickness opportunity
To get on a soapbox
Some say like
If only
Only someone were there
To help him at XYZ time
Stuff that I read
His writings that I've read
I don't think that he would never have sought out that
If possible
I'm like
Like maybe when he was twelve or so
Yeah
Earlier
Then people
Generally
Think we didn't once against goes back to Alex's rhetoric and I know that
Play like that going to neuter you
They're going to destroy what you think
Is AAA
And what in reality they're going to do is actually f******
Can help you be a human
Instead of a month
Find some sort of
Integration
Face reality
Yeah
That sort of thing
I don't know man
Huge bummer I don't
I don't think
Of course
I don't say
Mental illness
In the same way that I do
Think that the rhetoric
Narrative
Other very similar to ours
0-100
Santa blame for his eye
There's a
Complicated bouillabaisse
Is going on here
And the only reason that I think
M2r
Stop
Is that
The narratives are the
The part that you can
Yeah
Mostly upon you
Did we can't help people
Encourage people to
Stop saying your b*******
If you feel you need help
2 gold chain
Surprise yourself of the help that's available
If you've been married
The narratives in the rhetoric or the park
We can talk about this
It's all bulshit
So
Now we get back to the
I forgot we were doing the show
We have now started
Gotten into
Exactly what mode
Tyrone Davis
And now Alex
Saying that it
Please rashemi believe the person responsible the bomb
I wish we could arrest you
When they come out
Anime show the white people
Address
White tiger
Call Jay Nelson
Strawman
The DHS
The only thing you could process
Back to is like
Years prior there's a John Walker
Is avocado or the or they're like
But there are a couple instances of Park.
You know a couple of
Girls who are like
19 who was thinking that it was
But but
Other the bouillabaisse
Like they're does require a certain
Perfect Storm
Factors that go into this
Otherwise we would see this whole f****** lot more
Look
There are 7 billion people on this dump
Stupid f****** planet they better are that we're destroying
It is it is it leads
Positive
It seems like
Out of 7 billion people
To generate this kind of level of
Psychopath monster
I don't know I don't know if that's cold
Yeah yeah
F****** s***
Yeah
I don't know there was only like
Six hundred
So much longer to go see now you're talkin
Globalist
Georgia Guidestones Rudy globalist
Maybe the bad guys in kingsman the Secret Service just went about it the wrong way
Well that's because Samuel Jackson was the main bad guy
Is black Salve course
Idris Elba can't be gone
Did that last Clippers Joe weird shall we do his nuts
To do the show
Respect
Hours now talking about Anders Breivik
What the f*** are we doing
Yikes so I'm the reason that that last
Is particularly important
Is because Alex Jones
Gets a lot of mileage out of this
Al-Qaeda
I agree like I said better portmanteau but he says why you don't cry too so we have to go
You're further to like white Ida
You're that you're close to
That's too close
See there we go
Marvel
I know how to use citric I can write a script
Where is Starbucks is let's do this. I got a couple of friends who
Yeah it's really important
To me is that he gets a lot of mileage
Did he usually uses
Because
About white al-Qaeda in that last clip very clear
What are you talkin about is white
People joining Al-Qaeda
And that is the colonel and that's
General
However later later as time goes on
You repurpose that term
Into being away to mock the idea of right-wing
Yeah
Right
In that Westcliff clear he's specifically talking about white people joining up with
Qaida
Which is what the globalist are doing to make
Everyone's scared of people
That's the narrative
Which is plenty
I'm pretty bad
Especially considering the truth
That we know about this attack
Which was primarily motivated
Buy a guy hates Muslims
A group that could be described similar
The globalist is helping them overrun Europe
Alex Jones
The West
We got to we got to
Man
The rest of them
This is one of my favorite like the directions
What
No
That movie North is a mess
Stop
Look to do with set you up
You're you're consistently funnier than me my job is just to remind you to be funny I'm often
Accidentally funny
Never been prouder than
The one I called
Merle Haggard a muppet
Next clip
Is one of my favorite things in the world
She running operation
Because
You just do business meeting on air
Basically
He knows the Paul Joseph Watson
It's probably going to do a better job
About being a
What about stuff at least
Paul Joseph Watson
But forgets to put them on speaker
He is you might as well be on a bus with him
And only listening to his side of the conversation
Alex Jones
Because what he's doing is a business meeting on air with Paul Joseph Watson
Trying to spin the narrative that they want to put out on the website
Without Paul Joseph Watson
I don't know why he didn't do this
In the commercial break
But he's clearly coming out
But whatever the case
Here is Alex Jones being
The worst f****** content producer in the world
Running around shooting
The show
It's late in the show
So I don't know exactly all of the news
Come out but he's already
Dealing with it as like coordinated but separate attack
When it was the same guy
Wide as the bankers and plugs
Watson
Hey there buddy
Call John Mayer
Tracking
But obviously
Precision Productions
And that whatever
Shootings and bombings in Europe
Schedule for over a year with precision
What is an absolute emergency
In Norway
I mean this is just absolutely off-the-charts
I believe this is the beginning
Schleich Homeland others
Affair
It's just
What I'd like to contacts
Is that
White Al-Qaeda on speakerphone
Pillow talk with him
Amazon and they can't even get to selling gold Alex tries a couple times it doesn't
News
Call from someone in Norway
It was a listener
Who was there
The bomb
Sears nearby
And how does
Norwegian
Situation
But this guy just counting of the fact
Who's the new prime minister
Spell extremes over in and tries to
Is good evening
But I like Glimpse in that last clip
Because what we see is what production
Being done on air
You can hear Alex being like all right here the propaganda points that we need to have to
People love Precision predictions
And I've already decided this is white Al-Qaeda
I predicted that in the path
To make an article that sums all of this up
And make it make it look like I made a like a really amazing prediction even
I'm ignoring
The fact that details are still alive
Yeah but that's what this is how propaganda works
You're seeing how the sausage is made on air that was really
This is an embarrassing thing for him to
I'm so Ed hours have passed since he previously said
Yeah and by this point Michelle I'm not totally sure like another time
Stamp on it
The by the point we're at now
Well he said it was a false flag you didn't say it was
Which ones are crisis actors
Oh you did say it was staged so he said 98%
Real 90% chance of stage
Yeah but I think what you meant.
Happened
But it was a lie about
Howland and who perpetrated
Possibly
What we're doing
Is
Being far too fair to like what he
Right
But
It's now been hour
Point
It's all over
Yeah by this time that he's now on air
In the third hour of
In Norway
Anders Breivik
Latest weapons down in Pinterest
Presumably
The news reports are reporting that
Because we've already talked about the victim who was arrested as a
Supposed to
That
Fake news
Might be being reported so that's something
He should
Take a step back from but it's understandable if he wants to use that
Everything that guy in that moment
Because
If you're a cop
How could you possibly deal with this in a rational manner in the moment you know that's like that's like you're just
Just like
I see something I don't know what to do
I
Currently understand the mentality I hate the result
Have you want to do I'm like what
If you if you if you killed in the moment while you're on that island
He's a hero
He's a martyr he's really a Mustang
If you
Give him a PlayStation
What what do you got
What do you got
Who's the bigger who's the bigger person
Who proves what Society should
More than the country that is like
You're a
F****** monster and we will still treat you like a
A human being that's one of the points that I had hoped to get to
Is that the entirety if you look at the big picture of this story
All it does is disprove everything Anders Breivik believed in
Culturalism
The culture that believes in
Except
Is the same culture that refuses
Torture him in prison
Exactly the culture that keeps him alive and allows him
Play video games we won't go crazy
It allows him to have correspondence
Crazier
Did allows him to have correspondence with the outside world
Reality shows
Have a
Electronic typewriter so he can write his manifestoes
And things like that
It's A3 leaving indict
He believes in the facts
Society
Are able to
To deal with someone like you
And not be like
You know what
We are going to torture you ask slowly and
Is United States
What is it like what if I always I've always believed that like
The best reaction
Would have been like
This wasn't
A country
This wasn't a
Ideology
This was lunatic
Text if we condemn these f****** lunatic
But you know what
We're going to build these f****** Towers backup you have done nothing
You can't do it
That's what I've always believed
F****** kill him
Like a but what was the Iraq War other than proving that America is
Garbage
That mentality doesn't
Anywhere
Revenge digs his own grave
I don't know
Like I said
Commit white genocide and I've been wanting to for so long
Because restraint ism
I know you're a better person
What is illogical
Zurich
Nail this down
We're deep into the show now
Alex should have more information at
Is disposal
And what's see if he does
Norway seven dad
How are you
Rupert Grint
Earlier argument
Clearly that was staged f*** off but nothing is true
Globalist
98%
Whenever you can never believe it's statistically believing it is stupid hours later
He's being the worst journalist in the world
So now he talks about what the globalist
Call this would start
Al-Qaeda
The Roundup
Scenario
Domestic bobcat
Was trying to start a World War 3
Anders f****** brevik
It's clear
That's what he was doing he was trying parts
Involve these flash attack
He perpetrated
Which was in order to
3-stage European
That would lead with the repression
OVA
As a whole
Alex being like the globalist plan to do this
You're right
You're right in terms of vit
It was the idea of someone who believes the same things you do
Which is
More perfect
The
People who are
Most Simba
2 Anders Drive
Are the people that he ostensibly is
Like that idea of
Muslim extremist
Like that whole concept of like
Trying to start the end time
The only people who could possibly understand them
Are not human beings but
Christian extremist
The only people who can
Really get
Exactly why and what are the people who are trying to do it right
You're the same you are the
Sing
This is where it's at
Probably
Most fitting that I bring up another Passage
From his
Anders Breivik
Full hog on this record
Behind the game
I don't think so he's only have till bugs
Like Logistics portion of his Manifesto
Haters brother talks about the idea of
Like hooking up with Al-Qaeda
Because I could buy weapons from them
Getting involved with terrorist groups
Terrorist
But at the same time
If you read all of this passage
Did you talk about how like
This could work
He probably wouldn't it's not a Wise Road to go down
It seems they're in his Manifesto as a possible way to get like a wmd
He's like yeah we probably shouldn't
Do this
Right but it's in there
It in there
Possibility
The only people that can understand me are the p
People who I am us
Ostensibly fighting
Exactly
Create my own app
The Summit
Yep
Picking up
God dammit
This next clip is so f****** horrifying
Muslim
Please God let me know
Unicorn hair
Fake
I don't know why you'd be praying it was Muslim
Unless your modus operandi in your whole rhizzone d'etre
Is 2
Demonized
That that's what he's like
Please God let it be
We Muslims
I hear something like that.
F***
Dark that is
Is dark
Because it's
It comes from a place of flipping
Like he's not used talking extemporaneously
Here's kind of ripping around
And that's
Where his brain is stuck
I wish this was
I wish
Because
He is saying it is Muslims
But he believed that the Muslims are working
For the globalist
He's wrong
Unlike 3lau
Jordans
I remember
Set
Restart the show do you like
This is going to be fun
The great idea even crazy read we're going to laugh at it
Craziness
Yeah it's cruel but most
Crazy
You got to go where the information leads you man
I was a radical left
Music
2 years ago
Does dad know
Another step forward your cultural marxists
Globalist cultural marks
Dad
But I don't like
I don't think
So we look at Astor radicalized Rapala
It just has to
Inform what you know about
Which is that if anybody that you know is
Right wing
It is not
Sara Lee that they
Believe all of the
Sometimes it is not necessarily that
They are
Camp
Possibly Concha
Justly believe
Most of them because
At the end it's like they believe that they're good people
Like so many people so many
People on the right wing
Would see somebody who is Muslim who is
I saw them at a little bile
For a little while and then maybe we went out at maybe we were in the same program
Alcoholics Anonymous
For anybody and we got together we became friends
And yet somehow I wouldn't
Vitamin to my home
Still support
F****** pile of goddamn garbage that wants
Immigrants separated from their f****** families
Like
Who don't even understand that the underpinnings
Of all of their beliefs
Read the f****** corn
He's a f****** white nationalist
Terrorist
They don't get that
40% of America
They probably don't recognize
What motivated
This man
To do what he did
Is the same
Rhetoric
That informed
Maps of trump
Support
Most of the Maga base
I don't I don't like brushing with a broad brush with a broad brush
Not everyone
To all the same propaganda
But the people who put out
Most of the
Influential
Media
Are exactly in line with
Everything that's in this
Manifest
It's ludicrous
To think that like
Anytime
Like
I know that the right likes to talk about Bill Ayers and
Read there
Document
You were like
Oh
Oh s*** the in the same way
I would probably have to
Take a moment of pause
But they're documentary-like Destroyer
Not
That's not the point
Field argument
At this point
Alex is kind of
Floundering a little bit as being like
Sprint
Call to Lake Sardis synthesized like
Smarter
Smarter than Alex
And so Paul comes in with it
He gives
In line for a slap on the wrist
Bill
Palestinian
All he's done
He's laid out
Ideas
Is laid out Quinn
None of that
Implies any sort
Causation
Amanda
Not really
Representative
You know what it is
Childish cause and effect
Infowars
Rhetoric
Skip that idea of like
Mysterious cause-and-effect that we are presenting a
Has real
Pictures when it better than Alex
What's up
That's a throwback.
Evolutionary survival
Active
Create cause and effect even if there isn't because he will print
Always lay on the look at me
The Moose are out today
Creative
Basic like
2.5 million years ago brain stem
Creating those things we wouldn't have baby higher functions now
But if they're the remnant of it it still
Killings
Yeah
We try
Irresistible
Google Drive
Connections
Anyways
It's a full moon tonight Dan so don't be surprised if people start acting
Been crazy
We've come to the point of
The show
Where the news reports are
You're clearly saying
This was a white guy
Blond guy
Who carried out the
And may have had right
And so Alex now has to
The process that information
And I would say he doesn't in maybe
Worst way possible
Absolutely
Ladies and gentlemen right-wingers in Europe
Okay
Hey Alex know people that you align with in Europe
Hate Muslims
Not that they have a good point
Not that there was spawned into anything real
Right-wingers in Europe
Hate
Muslim government chooses to demonized
Actually that's why they choose them to commit their false flag attack
Text because then you would believe that all right Wingers believe that
Because Waylon
Who believed that
False flag right-wingers believe that putting a hat on a hat
Joking a joke
What is the set-up is bazetta
And that's a joke
Look at the ring is describing like
Ecosystem where
Right-wingers hate Muslims they would
Germans love David Hasselhoff
It's just ludicrous like
He would never say that now
He's saying that it's some sort of
Defense against the idea that this was
What
A hundred percent
Absolutely
But
I would argue based on the hundred
The pages that I've read
He straight up 8
He's more primarily motivated
Twitter your fit for a Muslim
The world
The thing that I think he hates
More is the multiculturalism
Cultural Marx
Which is
Code for globalist
Which is code for
Alex's worlds
Was primarily motivated by
But the primary motivation
He's also washed up
Do that
That worlds
You could easily ascribe to
He's afraid of
The globalist allowing Muslims in
Yeah it's the same thing
I know I'm making a really fine line
But it's a Nazi but
Anti
Nazi and Hitler
So it becomes more complicated you want to save it
He just hates most
Hate Muslims but there's another layer to it more
The traitorous
Government
People who are allowing the Muslims
And the only reason
I feel the need
To make that fine
Point is because
It is
Accurately reporting
And it makes it
More smart alec
But that
That's the essential underpinning
Into so many of those like
Justifications is
On the macro put on the micro it's fine like a good Muslim
Exactly
All of them in the large majority
The good ones
Like
F****** Dave Attell
How many f****** stories do you read
A small town is like
99% for Trump and then they find out that their buddy was an illegal immigrant there like
No you're not supposed to take him you're not supposed to take him he's cool
Check the magazine believe that most immigrants
They're cool because we're told that they're not right
I know it's a
We were experiencing the world largely
Coming to
Do propaganda
Over their own
Experience in that event
Great way of putting it really sad
Affairs
But I also think
For like
Conversation about
This recently about the idea
You know with diminishing in
Charter.
Travel
The world
Harder to get outside
Have your bubble
But at the same time the internet
Experience so much of the world
Leaving your desk
Right
There is a bear is a possibility for experiencing
Things so much more than you ever were able to
I without leaving
Whatever
Gets funneled
The wrong places
What ends up happening
Is like
Like you have
You said Dave
Let's use that
You have this person that you know who is
Very awesome
Who is
I meant you have
Your view of the world
Possibly a lot of it
What time is this negative
The world
No don't believe it don't believe it
But he's fine but there's all these others were
Like they want to kill you
Yeah
I don't know what the
Forward looks like
If your experiences
The world like legitimately is
Trumped by
By Propaganda
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
What you need to know about his Cultural Arts.
Right
To want to flood our country
Addendum
Want more days
They'll all vote for Multicultural
Exactly
Which is a generalization that I was like
Metaphorically
I think that it's
It's very
A lot of people
Still having
Immersive
Still understand
People from all walks of
And Coolidge
You know
That no one
Without
Drug abuse
Terrible circumstances in life
Orestes
Demonstrable
Crazy
Circumstance
Wants to hurt
Yeah like
Most people understand everyone from Every Walk of Life
Loves their family everybody wants
Have a real f****** good time hanging out with
Each other
You don't believe that
Then that's on you
I think I see
Most people
Like we talked about
There's that for
Thursday
I think better with those people
98%
Barr Lake
No matter who is affected by the propaganda
90% of people in their own lives
In their own small place
Just want to be
We are we're trying to be
Kind in a way
And unfortunately percent is somehow capable
Are somehow capable of
Creating this propaganda that can convince people
Otherwise
Wouldn't want to harm someone
The reason that there's a reason that there isn't that 40% of the country doesn't
Murder people
You get on exactly what I say
I think it's sort of like
Is 5 point
Perfect
Ideal version of society
The version of that
Myself
And one
The Miz
Like
Get rid of the Welsh
Number one
Number two
More importantly
Like we need to grow up
To a certainty
And recognized
You say 2%
In terms of like Monsters
We have to grow up to the point where we realize that like
There are just anomalies in society
Based on Howard Hughes
Bring
That we
Just absorbed
Yeah it sucks
It's doctors things
We can do to mitigate the damage of that
Which is
Number one
Stockton gun control
Do that if you do real hard
Buddy Guy
Get money out of politics so there's a lot of political things that we need
In order to achieve this
We realize that like
Yeah man
It sucks
Living in a society does involve a certain
Yeah because everyone around you
I want someone my
And it sucks
It does happen
We need to not
That is
Of
XYZ generalization
That leaves
But you need to say
Those 2%
Two paths are
Far more
Capable of manipulating
The system
To destroy the rest of
Look at anybody who's a billionaire
You're like well
98% of humanity is cool
But those 2%
98%
Right you don't like that kind of thing
It's because I'm not saying that their Perfect Analogy by any
About anyway
I'm not scared of
Because here's the God's honest
Is truth
Lake
People who are propaganda
Use these tricks
There are only so many tricks they can use
In the same way that if
You study logic
You understand logical
Fallacies
And so you're able to
Look at an argument be like oh no that's
Question
You know what you're doing there
Affirming the
What you've done there is not a that's against
Yeah they're only a certain amount of logic
Is that exist
Because of how distraught
Picture of argument
Yet
In terms of thin in the same
Propaganda only works
15.
Like there aren't a lot of ways.
Compelling to make an ARG
That are emotionally
There is a finite number of ways that people can
Rikyu
Into
Forgetting your higher brain and going with emotion
And the reason
Is that I hope
And how Society
We go along
Do-si-dos
I'm idealist
Well
Climate
But those sorts of
Fuel to
Demography
Appeals to
Unproven
The appeals to
Asperger
Is everyone just
Understand oh this is how propaganda
Manipulate
People right
We could
Undo a lot of damage
Is that that
Can do
All proper
Actors
Yeah like the monsters
Yeah
But I think you can mitigate the damage
Pretended we live in society where
It's not a pain
It's not fair
It's not
Your behoove
To understand
Play self
Because those
How do you argue against almost in verse
Of the truth
Which again is going to be a far larger
Generalization
But
AA the metaphor would then be only 2% of the population studies logic
+ 98
Population does
Probably
Yeah right like you use a logic
Analog and I'm using it as a metaphor
Is that how is it that we
Educate people when the 2% is so insistent about not educating people
I get those two percent are billionaires
And the 2% that isn't isn't about educating the responsibility
Sarah lot of good actors out there
Like I talked I complain about rightwingwatch and Media Matters all the f****** time
Their heart is in the right place
Foreshore
And they do a good job of reporting on
Xbox
Thing that the right.
Now what they do report
Foundational problem with
They're fun
Whatever we're not going to fix it on this ship
And I'm at the same time I wish
This particularly Media Matters
When they posted
Videos that Devin
Straight A
Very important point I wish they would
SA
That explains why it's an
Important
You just post
People like Vic Berger
Post really awesome
Like
Proof that Mike cernovich
The f****** monster
You have exam
Doing
The
The work
Sam Cedar Michael Brooks
They're doing amazing work
You know what I'm saying
But the in
Inverse of 8
You only
A 2%
To fight
Look
I don't I'm not here to talk
In a weird ultimate battle of Good and Evil right now which I don't think it's how we should
It's just like the percent kind of thing
Like this
I think I
I believe is based on
All the research that I
Andover
Alex's primary
Sources
I really think that all it
Charismatic
Decently bad
Version
He does
In order to
Destroyah
Stuff
No all of it all of the propaganda
Be diffused all the propaganda
To a certain
Amount of yet
Bye
Discussing why the propaganda exist
Where it comes from
What isn't I'm tails
And where the problem is
Right you don't like that
That
Exist
Like that in a world
Where
The inverse
Is there
Amtrak
Push back against
I'm not just saying that because
Can we do
But like
Pushing back
Will help if
This is what I'm saying
We are
Uniquely place
Where in
You and I should run the world
Like always
Which of the following of
We should be doing exactly what we're doing quite frankly
The reason that this works
Is because of that
Prime Minister President dynamic
Breakdown
I think it's the most
Not the most
Incredibly important piece of our modern world that we have to deal with
And
Do whatever
I don't know I think that we've spawn off into like
Conversation is certainly very valid
But at the same time we wouldn't be having it if it weren't for
Lot of feelings that were having
The contact
Very clear like I can't stress enough
If you take the time to go read all the stuff that I've read
Did I try to
Expresses Best Buy
On this podcast without just sitting here to get home
Right
If you go and read it you will only see
See parallels
And Alex Jones
Personally
A hundred percent
And it was
Is World in 2000
Right now I don't know the month
Before this
You know
I don't know the months
Before this what what is rhetoric specific
Ugly was I don't know
I hate Muslims
And be really scared of them
But I do know that
If I had to choose
He's not like this
He is not
Someone who is
Basically
Regurgitate
Peter's brevik
Yeah and in 2018
He f****** it
He is 100 /
So is that guy
Totally
Don't don't kid
Yep
They're just
Praying another Anders Breivik shows up preferably in America
Because it wouldn't
You somehow just
Because they've done the pre
Groundwork
Of
If this happened
With all these other
F****** Terror
Shootings that have happened
A grade so we have one more clip here
This is sort of a
I could probably Alex being a
Disgusting
Terrorist.
Whatever
They are
It's for everybody
So the reason that I am feeling like
Clip for this
See there is a false call for solidarity
If he actually meant he was
Yeah I like that idea of like
East of us it happens to all of us
That that sort of thing
Because we know from his history we know
We know that he does
Really care all that much when it happened
Two other
Group
Always be
It would you even is
Expressing In that clip where you talked about like
You Bubba's
You know you think it's just there for
Are the Browns know it's every
You too but that goes back to why
We reacted so heavily or why especially you react
When you made that realization of
His biggest problem was not all of these atrocities being committed
It said he thought they might eventually be committed
Two white people
So in this situation
When he's living in 2011 when he's living with black president
When he's living with
All of these
These ideas that he
Of course he
He's terrified
Because he thinks
Finally
Going to get traded
And now he's totally fine with this
Depression because he knows
F*** it
White
Even though he's wrong
Even though he's
Utterly and completely wrong
Even though white people are bored
Currently by what he thinks makes sense for white
He still thinks that virtual
Novice
He's going to be fine
Yeah well he's rich
You won't be soon
Let's hope
I don't think he's going to get away from
At least
AOL
I'm that's that
I think that last clip really perfectly sums up
Like what the
The f*****-up
Part of Alex
Jones especially
2011 onward
I don't know where to put the
The beginning point
Is it like
Actually
Yeah like he's good
But it's coded line
You know like it's not
It's not like
Face value
Like this idea of like we hang together or we hang
Like in terms of
All the people who are having
Their rights taken away and all that
If you ask
You would be
Champion
People
Who are white
Who
Are having to write
You would have years ago been talking about the private private prisons
Right where you would have been
These like really
People might wind up in private road
There's a lot of
Different ways
Narrative
That was really
Yeah
Yes
Find out is that
For us guys
If we don't
Push back
Also
At the same time
We care about
The actual
Remind me
Much
Of when I would make a
A cogent argument
That's
My family couldn't
Handle
Regarding
Christianity
And how it's a
Like even what they believe they have
Perversely
Asteroid
Their response was always a biblical
Call passage that said
Even the devil can quote
What scripture
Like when Alex Jones says that
When Alex Jones says what
You
Even the devil can quote scripture man you know like that kind
Describe that
I have
Has been emotional
Very difficult
Wrestling
Brevik
Thank you Sonia until I die
I want
I think I think that I've made my point
My specific points are
Andrews
Manifesto
Very clearly
Exactly
Especially in modern
Panda Express
Goodbye most
Tyranny of the Republic
Yep
I want to because it's been so so much
I want to
Let you
Have the floor
For final word
Call Dan
I'll tell you something
We're retired
No no no no no
I meant do you have any
Any last thoughts about
About that because I
Business sofa
Heavy
Actual source
We've been joking around a bit
I only
Of my preparation
The show I feel like I've been able to get my
Across
If you have any other points
You want to make
It's
I feel like it's stanced
You have one
It's
Pimp you out
You're not you're not
Lime Rock
I a
I am
Professional
Handle my own
As we were as we were talking about
I've gone through such this level of
I have to react
Lizard brain
Enough like
This guy should be
And throughout this whole episode
I'm going back and forth
Yes he should be by all
Concept of objective
This is what he deserves
The only way
Prove that
His worldview is incorrect
Is to treat him humanely
It is to it is to accept that
The reality is
Vengeance only
Creates more vent
Only creates more destruction
Etc
Getting mad at
Perpetuate
What created
Stomach
Dealing with infants
Diffuser
They are in it
It is amazing
It is really amazing
How
The Master's tools
Will never destroy the Masters
Like that is
S*** now I have to
Look up
Absolutely not
I love to look her up
Audre Lorde
Okay
Wrote an essay
Regarding
That is
Simply like
So-so app
Proposed for so many different
Like to a certain extent you can apply
Democracy
The Master's tools are democracy
Or are they the oligarch
Are they
What are those
The Master's tools
Toxic masculinity
And that is always coming down to
Violence solves
Poetry
Fix a let me have the flu
No problem
There's a lot of interest
Used to wrestle with
Pictures of like
When they go low we go high
That lost
Man
We lost
The election
Like in terms of
I don't know we had a mass shooting today
So what
Did Anders Breivik lose
Every day we have every
What
Weekly
Monthly
He didn't lose
How do we how do we make them lose
Is the
Question of our time how do we destroyed
Because we're no longer conversation we had earlier
Yeah
Refusing to propagate
We're no longer in a place where we can
Like with all of the bulshit eulogies about
John McCain
Look my again my initial reaction is.
But with those eulogies
What they are trying to point to
Is a
Pastor hearkening to an emotional appeal
Acts like this idea of there was a time where
Arguments were about policy
And not about reality
The emotional truth is
Them for
Feeling
Is that
Is
I think lowering taxes improves our economy
And you think
Raising taxes on the rich
I think that immigrants are killing everybody
And I think that
And weird Rays from Antarctica
Hurricane
He's not allowed on Alex's show
Hey you lost your tenure at
Uc-davis congratulation is that means
Alex anymore
But you still got a place hamamoto my baby
Call Mija
Such a
I
I want to live in a world where we can have a conversation
Yeah and we don't live in that world and we have to accept that
We met
We may live in that world but that is going to require
Defeat
I'm going to require not
Compromised
Am not coexistence that is going to require
Of the right
This is where we get in
Into
Another half hour of
Conversation
Because I don't think you and I have never done
You're expressing
Is dangerously
We close to
I mean politically
It requires
Nothing out of
In order for us to
Come to a place
Again of mutual respect
Define
Buganda
Because what has happened
To the right
Is a case
Study
In propaganda run-amok
No everyone wants to say because blood
People sell books
Based on this
Russia
Has done that
Or whatever
Irrelevant
I know that's irrelevant
It is a proper
Buganda f
Has happened to the right
Here's what the source of it
There is
Radicalization
That is not
Been seen in my life
Normal
Anyway
But it's
Cambion
Done
Bye
Wrestling with a prophet
Humanistic
I apologize if
That wasn't made clear defeat of the right is like
Defeat of the
I like that concept of like
Defeat of the world that we live in where that is the right
Exactly
Play I don't mean to defeat of these
People I mean a realistic
This is not
Acceptable and we
All agree on
And that is going to require
Like what it is
Wouldn't take for slavery not to be okay
Require
Nothing like does require
Story about the Civil War stuff today
Delray
That's states rights
Verily
Dismiss
As a whole to the point
To this propaganda
Have to except for 30 years until they start building Confederate Monument
In order to make sure that
You know it ain't me it's going to require that
But it also requires
Humility from people
As well
Life but there is a prop
Version of Alexa
Distance to the left like commitment to the status quo
Middle-west
Yeah
Which is really just
Exactly
Again we were tired
Fighter
Anders Breivik
And Alex
Go fuc yourself
Yeah I agree with that but I also
Anyway
We're on Facebook
Which is a great group were a lot of fun
It's really fun regardless of my I still like to
Take a look at the group your nose in that group good
Sonia from
Sonia from Sweden, long way but thank you so much for this suggestion of this episode
Cuz I think there is
There's a lot of edifice
We've been able to get to
The dark
Awful
Sonia I cannot help but
But thank you
And I will resent you until the end of my days
Email to make sure cuz I emailed you a butt
Did you get it believe I got ready got confirmation.
So much for getting
It also
Thank you very much but also
If you have
A
Time travel episode
You want us to do
Forget about any mess
I need a new mattress
Please send me a message
We will do them
I just need
Everything's come back
Because I've lost a couple messages I've
Lost track of him stuff
Please hit me up again I don't mean to
Ignore you
Please just left
It's important
Fulfill everyone's request
I'm just shitted
It's important to remember that for one time travel request
Dan has spent the last
48 Hours fighting sleep
More than that
Just like
Don't there's no ignoring
Of anybody it said
Danny's
F******
Serious about research
Forgotten about
I need a reminder
So please
Please remind me
Call the timeout
The Cavs game
David Blatt
You're like
We need to call a timeout but you didn't have any timeouts left and then LeBron
Overturned you but
Fired a f****** buzzer beater
That was against the rules
And Derrick Rose was still great at the time anyway
Miami book fair
Derrick Rose
But it's there
But while we're talking about monsters
It's only right that I remind you
Probably killed
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color