Alex
Alex Jones
I don't know probably
I don't know
Dumbest thing I've ever done I've got a lot of dumb stuff
Jumped off roof
Before I fall
Yeah where are we playing never have I ever right now
3 hour version of Never Have I Ever
Because I have been all day.
Adjust note
Just about all the dump
Bulshit
What the f*** are you idiots doing
How was your day you didn't even count for like the ice people who are loving all of this s*** they don't realize
But everything is f***** over them
Stupid they're so f****** stupid
I got to get off the internet forever I can't read anymore take
Not as hot as people think they are
Caribou on Alex Jones.
Let school out with that criticism
Etc
Analyze the fun
You are
Effervescent
Turn it up bad headache
Episode.
Effect on me
Incredibly difficult to listen to Alex Jones anymore
It's too hard to recognize little pieces that are very familiar
Much less pain
To listen to Alex Jones
Steak
Viola
It's the same stuff that we were
Recovering before but
There's just a reality
Riggs
Medium
You don't like any of those dude out on comedy
Screaming about things
To take a moment
Far out
Because we're a little over 200 episodes into the podcast
Forgot
Numbering episodes is not really our strong suit or anything like that but I recognize that you know
Radar logo had as our logo on iTunes
And I was great but
Now that we're
About the little over 2
After we got a new logo I want to see you very special thank you to a Catherine for designing
If you want to enjoy it
Fallout 4
This far and take YouTube
For the one we're going to be absolutely.
Wind blowing
I don't know I was going to try and maybe quotes
I dug into my bag of 20 in there I don't know
Maybe I saw could have been in there
You're lucky I even say Walt Whitman
Cuz I was close
Shakespeare
Alex
Jojo
Is very excited
Thank you is special
Dakota
I'm a policy wonk
In a very weird turn of events I think we have multiple people named Dakota donating to the show which I think is great
I don't know the only Dakota I know is
South
Also would like to give a shout out
We really appreciate
I believe that this is a pseudonym becoming a technocrat alphabets
Someone someone sodomizing a poop
Google
I don't want to
Thank you so much alphabet
Chris Martin and Gwyneth Paltrow
Chris Martin
I got together with Jason
You got together with Gwyneth Paltrow
It's something that happens on the weekends
Or it could be
Tim Cook
Get together
With Jason Lee
And his wife
They have
I love baby the alphabet is Google
Pilot inspector it's not
Alphabet flight creating an alphabet soup
Exactly
We're going to be doing
The week was incredibly emotional
Feel up to doing episode so sorry we missed that folks
Explain
What happened
Lights
I looked at the episodes
There's something I want
Anders Breivik
Going to be
I think she weaves into it
Fingers crossed
But it was checking out Jim Bakker
Do it for me
Who's lot going on and Alex Jones is so let's just do it let's do a current one
That's all
Effervesce
I went in
And I checked out
September 3rd
August 30th
Owen Shroyer is hosting as at
Zion
On Thursday
His lawyers had a demotion
Which was denied
Forward
His argument that is just as free speech
I was
So that's that
Look stairs like stare directly designs
Fake laugh at him
That would be
Yeah I'm not sure so enjoy with us today we're recording missing like
You know
The regularly scheduled for next week
Recovered from
Spoiler alert
Lot
Oklahoma City stuff
Finish my research I really don't want to do the turnaround
Monday Monday
Officially ruined everybody's
It's pretty interesting on a number of levels
The upsetting
Now let's start with an avocado
Text Rob from today's office
Undelay undelay undelay undelay
Petco
Set the man on Mark that off his the first impression of
A shower
Yeah I think so
I love the confidence
What is that what is that
Know what does sweetie
What are who am I
You're getting ahead of yourself there might be some esoteria
Episode
Starting today's episode off
Envy
Starts every episode nowadays
She's getting
Real grandiose about them
16 days
Megatel
Most important election in world history
Planet is at a Crossroads
Destination down
We are struggling
Hours of operation
Ladies and gentlemen
So we have the theme that developed the most important election of all time
And then of course the same thing that he has to do all the time
Lister
Is that thing that he
Constantly uses which is like it's basically a tie ballgame
It's basically tybalt's
323 of course even though it is tied we have been destroying them the entire game
Everybody knows
Make perfect
Get more money out of people
When you have this world
That's all pretty sensible
I think that's exactly where he needs
To be from his business model
Broke
Restarting the show
Happens at the 20-minute point of the episode
He's 20 minutes late
For the show
Probably maybe he was in court on that dick.
They just play like report Special Report
Weird techno music with Alex's drops over it talkin about
FedEx
Recalled
The Techno music with us.
20 minutes late
Tells you to the most important election ever
Tie ballgame
How many plays
Tucker Carlson
Tucker's
A former Clinton strata
Who idea of online censorship
Stuff like that
Listening to Tucker Carlson I think you suck
He's a douche I don't care
This is Alex Jones
Specifically not what about Tucker Carlson
Kind of worried about his grasp issues
Okay
The First Amendment
Free speech is an internet right
I can't say anyone
I would say any sleeping in
There already are rules about discluding people based on race or
Trend or anything like that
Do conservatives think they're erase
I think it's absolutely
It's not even
We can't play the game on their turn
Cuz they are describing
Conservatives are getting kicked off
Not just even.
Consequences of their actions
Come home to roost
It's a situation where people who are dangerous ideas out into the world
Violating
It's not
Not conservative
Again
Problem that I keep bringing up his
When you have these rules
Good to have these rules
But you can never enforce them
Appropriate
What's the name of the what's the name of the Underground
The morlocks the morlocks
Make sure that there's a pejorative term
I think they would get a real charge out of
It's enough
Understand anything that's a good point
Tucker doesn't understand what he's bringing up black people on it
Absolutely
Regulation
Libertarian
There was only one
Right
Whenever you regulate anything that then make them
Regulations are important when it's you who feels bad and they're not important
Buddy else feels bad what was the road
To Facebook
I suppose
Is already
Taken care of
No blacks
They couldn't say that
That would not fly
I wouldn't know
No no
It would be tough
Dummy accounts and whatnot
It's not okay
Analogy
Absolutely
Have to do that
To turn
That that like
No no no how dare you say that just because we lie and threaten people with physical
We're not racism to say that you can't harass women
Racist against me
Norwalk
Yeah it's it's
It's a tough rhetorical hurdle
I think you're in a bubble like Fox News or out
The show
Willie easy-to-make like
That sort of
Wiggle
Wiggle like
Know anybody who was
Ridiculous conversation
I don't know
We're outside
My friend
Absolutely the best
In the business
At this
He's pretty good at that too
Demonizing
Humanizing his opponents
Enemies
Which is pretty great.
Here
Sociopathic
Hateful dishonorable
Dishonest
Truly Wicked people
And just viciously
And run your life
Destroy the family
Take everything away from you
Virtual reality with a conceal yourself
They are completely turned over to
What's wrong
It's real
Okay
I can't
No has a real-world core
He thinks are great
No corollaries two things that the people he says are doing these things
Every single f******
Everywhere everywhere
Grind all of the things that they are and buy his own at definition
We should be f****** killing them
Is everybody should murder him
Qualifies as a murder where the offense and
His book then
More importantly
This is what you're responding to
Whether he means to or not this is a lot of projects
This is a lot of
Even throughout the show
Arcade
Destroy you and they're trying to kill your family you know like if they were too I don't know
Remove
You know like maybe they were trying to make it harder to get into colleges only make it more easy to commit sexual assault
Policy directive
His entire cabinet everybody's working towards Iris
But I just
He wouldn't even wrestle with that
Humanizing
You don't making it so it is okay to attack them
This works hand-in-hand with his narrative about
How the media is going to fall flag themselves Democrats
To get pity and sympathy in front of the midterm
Blame It On The Rain
If something bad does happen
Who wanted to throw your family and then eventually
So if one of them were dangerous and one of them
Some sort of
News organization
You know you may be the president
Quotes the president in French
Nobody would listen to the president
Silly
Right
We talked about
Like repeatedly so we don't
I don't think we should spend half an hour
Is Uber
Supertanker
Doing it and we're not doing it to them
We're not demonize ultra-humanite these people
Literally doing everything that he said to make you guys demonize us
Supposed over liberal use of the term Nazi
To describe people
I think we've been through dishes
Calling people who are
Expressing ideas
Calling them not to
Stephen Fry
Declaration
But
You know I'm slowly
You're coming over to my
We'll see about that
You could call Summer
Nazi
Is only getting larger
All the people who shouldn't have called before like
You know what Lindsey Graham is a terrible human being who is trying to kill everybody
I know you're like
Yeah I mean I guess it comes down to that
Kind of the right hand
Seamless
Turn towards
Abuse
Dehumanization
Outdoor unlike yourself
The ratcheting up of the temperature of the water
And instead of getting boiled they're all just
Becoming okay
With us
Very very close to
Fascista Jason
Alex gets into
In a weird way and I think he's in a very strange mood
He might have done mushrooms the night before this episode
He's he's real weird on this episode from this boy.
Not far off start talking about the Comets of proof
It's very scary
Probably going to hit the world you have your finger on the pulse
All right Siri
World government use now here in your face
Mark
Marquez and Marquez and
2000 years later
Coming true no one can deny it
Prophecy is being fulfilled
Cool
It also says the church will fly tonight
Most people will accept the mark of the beast because they'll believe
Because the church is our churches
Federalize
Communion ad
Mark my words
Sure
Also I like how you said
This my friend is what we call a setup
Because of course the production staff Googles
Conveniently there's a very similar headline that uses those words
Did Alex clearly read the headline read the story about this
Something weird blog
And it's just someone who
Can use biometrics
Greece safety
I am the entire article what it's about is the idea of using fingerprints
Kids Safe
Churches
Like in terms of like knowing where they're going
And, make sure it's the right avoiding all members of
The clergy
I don't think
But I don't think that's
I don't know which fingerprinting is going to do to help that situation
Look I would say is
Zurn
Because I'm not a part of it
I don't know
That putting this out as a suggestion of Waze
Kris security
Plantable
Not a slippery slope thing that's going to lead to that
It's a
Safety measure
His idea is that in two years churches are going to
Biomat
Scan
Yep to prove or to tie
You you do that but I was like is there a database of people who are in accordance with communion rules
Believe me
You cannot be in a fight with any member of your family
You must also be right with God there
Proceed
The track is it going
Your finger it'll go
Which of course the man is very interested in catalog
Bring as well to let you know to let them know if you are right with God.
The government is going to implement the system where you fight with your family you must report it
He's got a login no
I know your password is the tetragrammaton
Pronounceable name
Special keyboard
So Alex's
You talk about the church is not being
The real churches and have a gun
We're going to need biometric
Kickstands
Italy
How did enjoy that oh my God
Create the hologram
Overhead
So it looked like he was a hologram
But he was still a lot he was he's still alive but his real body
When you go to do the holiday
Got to get out there
Is that he's talking about like
The idea that in the Bible it says that
Projected into
Giant Holograms
If you don't
Weird
And if you don't submit well you'll be done
You don't do much
She's talking about the idea of the idea of like Chinese social score system
Implemented in the United
Answer
Beginning to hard but then about a black mirror episode
Yep yep
And more and more than very few will have five stars it'll be totally coveted the new Hollywood power
L will have five stars, like people
Worship
Sounds fun
Oh you want that five star don't you
Ali cut off of the entertainment jobs everything
Thousand
Information
World government
Once you all get rid of this is going to start
Cool cool man world government
For now you can still go to infowars.com
Videos
Yeah probably
Alex is not actually talking about the actual text from Ezekiel
You clearly talking about the 1974 book that written by
Joseph Blum rich
Which was inspired by bloomridge reading Erich von daniken
Not the Bible verses that the foundation
Ezekiel Saw aliens
Alex leaves
Alright so let's say
Einstein
I'm saying that but for the sake of argument let's say it's not
What time what if I reference
What time
Cool man
Enjoyed
That's Project Camelot
That's insane
Baker Hughes
At Justice
Exegesis of
The text that you take context clues from other parts in the Bible like
Clear that it's
At least partially metaphorical
And then also
They talking about angel
It's not some sort of spacecraft and the blue helmet part that he's talking about is this awesome thing that people have
Extrapolate
Blue Hound
Crazy nonsense
I love it
Car quotes
Sufficiently Advanced blue hat is indistinguishable from Angel
Dip
Alex believing you
Zuppardo's
Centuries-old prophecy Ezekiel misinterpretations
It's just gorgeous like a good spaghetti sauce
If you're if you're watching
They would describe that as a
B
We're not going to talk about this tonight go off on a
Bucking Ranch
Because I know you have a lot of feelings about it
Alex's
Less than gracious about John McCain
I'm not going to go on
There's no reason
To defy him
Now that he's dead
But at the same time
No reason
I think especially for
Put out
Some sort of negativity in the world be like
Alex tries to play the card of I don't want to talk ill of the dead and I'd like to remind everyone how's the day after David Rock
Rockefeller died
The Rockefellers dad
Keep On Rockin in the Free World
He might've play ding dong the witch is dead
Quite frankly I would not have I don't remember that
So he's like
You know I don't like to speak ill of the dead but this guy with a f****** dick
And then he gets to this
Send
But I think it's very interesting
Longtime listeners of our
Gyros
Very familiar
I know it's last name isn't
Capone
Hit on
I like take everyone back to 2015 when Alex Jones said about
You got a name like Corleone they arrest you
You got a name like Trump they don't
He's a front man for Consortium on the East Coast
Trump not a 4.3 years ago
You got a name like Capone
McClain's about her name
Yeah I know
Sure put so much CO2
At least he's reusing some of his CO2
Except very hard
I've dealt with all of my complex emotions regarding John McCain
And I've decided that the best way
To express them
Is to pretend he's John Glenn
And just
Confuse everyone
Okay I just was amazing
When he
Was the
Went into space for the
Changed my
I realize what was possible
Because that man
Did something that no one else
Average better as you can
Conflate
On the 1st
Spacewalk
Incredible True Grit
I don't know I don't know how to setup Klipsch anymore like because
Because of anything that's wrong with me
Because
This show is so stupid
Like I don't
Not our show put like
When I was real
To some extent we Elevate The Source material attached to the show I can't tell you how
How many times am I
This show sucks
Weirdo started writing your notes
In your own s*** on the wall
I don't understand what his plan is anymore other than
I'll look on the wall and see what I got
We heard him
Using a
Apple stores
To claim things about the Book of Ezekiel
Smart aleck
Call me up
How are you
Continually
Fox News
He knows how things work
I'll leave it at that
What is that I want to be the only one
Oh
Poor guy
Talk to me so smart so is the Pentagon
Just calling
Yeah the actual building
Platonic ideal of the shape is calling out
That is actually like the level of heady
He's going to get in a little bit
You might not be so surprised the other day was really
Close
It's real close
I reached into my pipe Neil glandon I discovered the truth
I would consider most of
They just kind of like we're just sort of
Trading gold
Material
But like
We're having
He does getting to like
Our favorite date of Alex Jones a little bit be just like
What are you talkin about man I think you figure used coat here but you are just freaking out on air
Just so that's what Eric nonsense
It starts on this next
Like its main let's call it the varsity narrative
Has been apologizing Watson put out an article with the headline
Is a massive scam for the midterm
Lower the headliner
We get them to the article about it a little yet
Like the exact same nonsense
Facebook is run by the globalist
Like alright man
You're not evolving
He gets back
He starts the 2nd hour
To get to this
Big news
The entire first hour
He gets the beginning of the second hour
And my man
It's time to get serious
Pulling up Bob
I don't really know how to
Putting her sad
Why do people think virtual reality
Blah blah
Play some outside force
Simulation
Different
Telescopes
You name it
Power source
This universe together
It's just that
He goes into plug-in he's having a boring life
Goodwill
Is he crazy or hair
You don't know
I promise you he doesn't get to the point
The simulation that
What is your point never brings home never ties the bow of these thoughts
What is that
What does it mean it like even the
What the scientists have said it for a long time
This whole there's a greater energy or whatever that's holding the universe together
That 400
But now
Bankers m
Yeah crazy maybe they don't probably
They're all magically field according to Alex
Sunrise radio
Also I just
There's a lot there's a lot going on there and I love the idea of Alex
Movies that are based on Philip K Dick's short stories and pretending they're real
Like I would love it if a week from now he shows up with a little
Secret doors
I mean
I've been to drug
You should diversify
Let's start
Let's just start spamming him with other science fiction writers
Village restaurants
No but you gotta understand like he's only been a few movies
Then you have Waking Life which is also directed by Richard linklater and at the end
Linklater appears in the movie
Vet references
Is the book by Philip
All of Alex's cinematic life
Contingent on Richard linklater
Who's a huge fan
His work
Alex is never leaving the pkp
Foundation
Alright
Amazon just green-lighted the foundation
Series references in here to
3 of May
High castle
YouTube
Like 20 seconds into every Spotify.
Himself
He could exist in that world
I really like that show
I think
Okay
I'm projecting onto the world that no one likes
Yeah that could be
I think most people are like
You know there's a speak
TV shows like I got to choose I got to go
Series that way
Was based on Gillian Flynn's novel Gillian Flynn
Okay
Sapphire
This is boring but then there's a twist ending so you love it
Goosebumps
So yep
Alex is going to get even weirder and here is
Little boys
Highway
Not even close to the depth
Spirit
With what
Broadcast
Hell on Earth
That's what every other culture says
None of them are atheist
Play believe in
Everything she did
Yep
How could you not
What we've seen going on
But 2001 Space Odyssey
Mark of the beast is here World governments here
You proved it in relation but it's not
Short but it's been proven it's all held together
I don't know what that was
Experience consciousness
And free will cuz your God
The one thing you don't have it something separate from you is conscious but its own little universe and it's mine and that's us
University
You got cut off by that break
But hot bulshit throughout most.
Sit-in
First of all is like it's a simulation
Okay you're saying
Gnostic
In terms of theme
God created us cuz he doesn't have any
Projection
I wish you could experience himself from external
More into it because I don't think Alex is ready Gnostic scriptures
Is I think
Scott
Delta frequent
Copy of his 2001
Really
He put out he was known primarily for the
Dilbert
Dog bark
Catbird
No there was a character who worked at
Reevaluate
Wall-E
I think that was a hero to a book in 2001
Yeah
No
The phrasing
What's going on with 2001
So I reckon
When I was
16 or so
I smoked a lot of weed
But the only thing God
Could be interested in
Is experiencing a world without himself
Until God destroy himself
And we are the debris of God's Own destruction
What if he doesn't exist
Interconnect
Through the internet what have you and that's our way of trying to
To bring back
The wholeness of
What
We are
Wrestler the CliffsNotes version of it
Pneumatic connections to what Alex has rambling about
I think he just read got to breathe at 6
Mind-blowing
Do you know synesthesia moment
Listening to that whole thing
Smelled colors
Like a Simone biles floor routine
Broccoli
She's the greatest gymnast
Alex's clip with the surf Rock
Listening to him talk was just him like
Do it all these weird movement
And then
All of those
He said it was already in motion
Hot mess
Bulshit
Looks amazing
It's only the beginning
Only the beginning of how weird
For you this is going to get
This next clip
From everything I understand
What is describing
Almost
Hundreds and hundreds
That's impossible
Whole family peoples
Just goes on
Dairy Queen
God nothing
He's in Waking Life
I'm going to go back really quick
Just because
Little fragments of things and whatever
Later imagine
And then you have another dream within that but what if you dream that your multiples
Two people can dream and if they dream
Lindo's
Two people can have two people's dreams
And all the dreams are happening all at once
You can't f******
What's the
Movie like Alex
I'm super into Transcendence.
You can have through like meditating or lucid dreaming I think there's a lot
In those
In those States
Something
Something to be said for that but I do think it's
It's troubling whenever you're someone
Who's a
I don't know 45 year-old big drunk
This world
I don't I don't know about you anymore man
You did some shrooms man
But then it gets worse listen to this
Crystal Vision
Onelife rock song says
It's Fleetwood Mac
Think about that God is all-powerful God is all-encompassing time with an endless
We are independent creatures
Able to have free will or subvert our free will
The other
Creatures that decided not
Does the hierarchy not to Ash and
The long arduous process
But did you decided to just try to rule their falling
Position
What the f*** 2nd Dimension position
I do kind of know what he's talking
About it it's crazy nonsense
That's from like Illuminati message boards
It's not really all that worth getting into butt
Freewheelers
Where you ascribe is kind of also just to the other side
Boring the idea of like
Yes I am serving at a extraterrestrial entity of some sort but I'm free and doing so
These other people that I don't like her serving another entity
Attract
Like I just stopped
Yeah I think my only reaction
Just like I
Doing right
What do you mean
What is anybody's
Is going on here
Alex
What are you doing right now
I'll tell you what he's doing is probably trying to prepare himself to go back on Rogan's show cuz apparently baby going back on
Rogan show soon
Great
I don't know
Decided there was a post that was put on Facebook
Of course
I didn't do any looking into this
There was an account that was supposedly Alex Jones
Confirm
Plausible
Really good chance Alex Jones
Profile
If you're going back
I'm about to do 3 hours
So that leads to this next
Which is
Man
I am not going to be good on this episode
Because this
Text clip is about 3 1/2 minutes long
It's one of the most bizarre things I've ever heard him say in a long time
Connote
Completely
Blocked man
Who is
To deal with it
While doing a radio show
Interesting
Psychological study
Button
Some places
That are like
This is about you Alex
You're wrestling with
He feels it though he feels it but
His entire life
Suppressing the way he feels about himself and then projecting it on other
Eric like this
Starts to creep out
A little bit
So
Possibly
All the study show
This is hurting you is depressing you
It's destroying your
Sounds like what happened
And they were arrogant and try to spend wish I didn't try to turn it around again
The elected all the rest of them you shut up about the topics Alex Jones covered or we will
Destroy you
We will tell elaborate lies
And frogs about you everyday come after your family
We will destroy you
If you don't submit to us without slavery
Real quick I'm just going to cut into
To say like there's so many people on the internet
Play the exact same stories
Is that Alex does
There's so many people
The cover the exam
He's facing consequences
This is all about him
This is all about
That doesn't
Scared of death so scared
Because in their spirit
And only one small part
Fulfillment but you got
God
You're scared of trump
Coronavirus count
Come deeper
I'm even more scared I know I know but
Costas
Oh my God
Freaking out
Ozone
Come with me come with me to this website where
I give you all the answers about just how bad they are ohmygod now you're here you're even more scared than you are
Terrible
That's exactly what he buried
Twerk
So much worse
Just keep holding on to my hand
Until everything you are
Everything you've ever been is under my control
Give me your consciousness
Give me your creativity
Give me your dreams your heart your soul your fears everything you are
And we have an Easter sale besides leaving Shea is I shall repeat what I am
Replicate
Joint with my Consciousness and support yourself
Everybody please take all of our articles and publish them everywhere
Them out as if they were your own believe no one else
Give you a film
We're winning we're always winning
Technologies that he's going to release
I know you follow me long
Watch
Is there only Power is destroying the will
Consciousness that admitted that you are
And keeping you from exercising your free will
Choose to do that you're shut the field you're like oh my God
How did I not see this earlier
You're depressed because you know you're losing your
Hurt your feelings because you care about them
Gopher being depressed
Demonic smiling jack-o'-lanterns face
You watch them go from being
Depressed people to posting links to Infowars in
Demonizing groups they didn't have an opinion on before
Joker face
I'm just in charge
Their soul was
Consumed
Rewritten
Disease
Destroyed forever
Phone out the airlock
That is a f*****-up clip
Wow
That was a ride
That
Wow I don't believe in Alex's dumb like
They have to tell you what they're doing to you in order to do this kind of thing
You're doing that exact
Unparalleled
Dick
He's getting real close to ASMR Alex
Start
I want to read audiobooks in ASMR that would be
Alex Alex Jones like legitimately
Universally
Possession of
Must be
If he needs ale career change I think he has
All the makings of the happiest
Science fiction writer of all time
I think you could pivot pretty easily into some
No
Broadway
Stop f****** around on those 808
Buckley I know you got another ass
I need you to do some dictation
I put it on her Twitter you should check out Buckley
Is a good DJ
Aspiration
Infowars Studios is
Just watching that right
Hoverboard
No one is stopping
Your empathy would override the show
You got to take you got
Take 5
Yeah we have more special reports we can run you got to get your s*** together
We
Genuinely
Believe the bulshit you're pedaling
And even we can see how bad you're projecting right now and we got
Some help
You're not on YouTube little more free
Just let your freak flag fly
But
This is being recorded
So
Reel it in
Admittedly Alex
Really only damn freezing his list
At least with a critical eye
Feel whatever we want to feel about it
But I will say
Gives a real weird glitch
In 2 hours
Okay
Watch a movie office
You got 600 radio stations I really need you to do this yourself your family
Radio station
You're a congressman
Grover
George Washington George Washington
He called Donald
John Trump
No
Paul Revere
Our problems are basically solved before the money love it
What's our number again Dan
530 neon nip Alex
We are around 89
We know you're here will help you we will
I love the pictures
Just trying to watch like
He would let her watch Moana
Repeat Song of the South
The office
Pretty high
Who is on that number of stations
Hannity
That's it
Handy
Glenn Beck
Rush Limbaugh
Coast to Coast AM someone like a Hugh Hewitt
A couple other
People who like
Fly under our radar quite a bit
People who are on 500 plus
Not on their Facebook post
He ran into a little trouble
Townhome values that is probably
Controlling the universe and that's what God is you know
People are generally scared
Of people who hearken back to a Time
And a place
When women were good-looking
All the men are above average
All the propaganda
Angry
It took me
New Year's Eve
The kid to figure out that Lake Wobegon
Wasn't a real
F****** Everett Apartment A
I wasn't all that smart growing up
Garrison Keillor showed up on
No
Classicos allegation
He almost certainly
Behavior
Come on
No
Saving so
A position of authority that he surrounds himself with women he doesn't
Absolutely sexually harassed them 85% of the time or whatever it is come on
That's crazy
The world we would know
I look forward to Garrison Keillor showing up at The Comedy Cellar
Listen to radio theater Radio Theater
Theater of the Mind
Cody Zeller
Drop it in
F*****-up world religions
Eva
Anymore
Oh well
Stand-up comedy
Everybody knows
We've seen Alex is very weird
He's getting esoteric he's getting up in
To his weird
7th dimensional light beings kind of head
Here is
Hey it's just
Standard radio
Is this
A simulation or not or both or neither who knows all of the above yes hello
Is Total Recall reality maybe I'm not sure
Going on with 2001 A Space Odyssey
You all know
Why do they make the whole ship out of the black box
Words very close to that level of thinking on his part
Much more
Problematic
Weird
This is Haiti
Yeah
Kind of
In fact up
To talk about certain
Sing
In society Lutz
Yes you are
The favorite
You are kind of libertarian
YouTube
Headlines all over the place
Jones has the lgbtq Jones
Special Report
Criticize pedophilia in the Catholic Church
Cephalization kids by any group heterosexual or homosexual
I get called homophobic body Publications and show
Of the lgbtq
Lbgt
Lgbtq
Lesbian
So
You just demonstrated
You at the end
Sure
What question
Examples in the same set
Yeah yeah
Dim themselves
It's so demonstrative
Incredible Hulk like they always doing right now
8 bananas
That you know whenever I criticize
Pedophile whoever they are
I don't get why there's a problem here
Because there's a Venn diagram situation going on
When he talks about
Pedophiles he's not always talking about the LG
Gbt commute
If a woman
He's pretty much always weaving in pedophilia to it tends to
As we've been doing the show there's so many times
Like exactly what
He said that like must
You mean that the community is run bad
You don't like
That is an unnecessary suffering to take
Edit
Conclusion that he's coming to from innocent
Coverage of
It's because every
He's like
He can't resist
The urge to be like
Do you like
If you're just making valid criticisms of the Catholic Church
Are all pretty much there now it's a long time
It took a long time
I don't know all of the church's existence for everybody to kind of be like
And knows about it
You shouldn't
Just figure out where to put the. In the center
Alex
Just wait just figure it out
I'm a Libertarian and I think everybody should be able to do what they want to do
.
And then
Skip the last part
Is you being like
Libertarian
And he doesn't believe any of you like standard liberal
I don't know what else to say other than what we've already said
Like people
Come down on him when he talks about these things
Cuz
I guess he uses
You know all the time
East Orange
Anchor the idea of pedophilia in lgbtq
Yeah he's trying to
Conflate the two things
And that's what he always does
Over and over again
I mean I don't want to say that he hate
Every single gay person in the world but it's hard not to feel that way
I don't care whether you're Christian
Muslim
Jewish or
Are there others
All Muslims are run by murdering pedophiles and I don't get why people think I'm islamophobic
Stop to Cy good workout
So
You show sucks he's a dick
Leading into his very clear
He's trying to use to
To defend himself against allegations of transphobia
Is allegations of transphobia
Hip Hop
He's enjoying
But then even even then like
He could have just stuck with the Transformer your stuff and it said he just wrote everybody in with
Reality
Everyone in the lgbtq community
Identities are there all monsters
Hey you guys didn't tell make me bad enough
Just don't call me whatever you want
Speedrunning real terrible show is really interests
Who will still go on it
Somebody goes on Coulter was just on the other day
Locked up
Because Alex has spent months to talk about how much you suck
Because she was one of the famous conservatives who turned on Trump
I bet Adele
Yeah definitely
And now I guess who's back on trumps
I'll have her back on the show
Sochi
Darrell hamamoto was on the other day my dude
Instead of anybody else it's just Alex and Daryl co-host
You have the time for it
Jarrell hamamoto update
Better new car
Asian studies professor
Researcher on the topic of
Sacralisation
Asian males and
Culture
Started
The New World Order
So
We reported on this show that he
Inspired by
Lucy dacus
Because he is no longer working at UC Davis
I bet he has a
Composition Dan
I think he got forced into retirement
Look at these listed I found their like
2017 2018 retirees
I would say a lot of them
Much longer
They been there many more for 22 years
As a professor
There's no reason why you retire except for like
Dude
It could be
Probably accept
Comfortable.
Retirement
But also
The show
And also a
Viral
He was saying that
There was a
Wave
Irish shop
From Antarctica hurricane
He speculated that
John Kerry visited
Couple years back
He was going to check on those weather weapon
And did not speculate it so much as using
This is
He's so crazy
Weather
Did you see David the last dude
Supposed to
Reviews of the professor
Hey
Here
Explains in class
So if you're not Asian
You're going to be bad time in this place
You know what
Sure
Moto Z Droid
You're the one who did Google Darrell hamamoto before you took his class
Leather cursory Google
It's kind of on you
Yeah so
Two still willing to go and show up
My dude
He is a guy
If you are if you don't remember the guy who does political cartoons that are over labor
Yeah yeah know what I like
Very amateurish hack
My
You know
A lot of acting
Will Sage
I've never actually
They'll say to you acting isn't
Acting is about
Subtlety
Tumi Ben Garrison
Is the
Comic strip
Corollary
That is a man
Who maintains
Subtlety as an art form just transforms and then really even transcend
The Arc in the in the world of speech
Brevity is the soul of wit
Visual
Analog of aphorism
Picture is worth a thousand words
So long as you write a thousand words
World is up to 1000 words
He's slightly misinterpreted that today
Cartoons of generally like
Really good clothes
Beyond that
I would I would say that
Kind of living
Proof that
Because the only reason he's all popular is because of
Freddy reactionary release
F***** up
Becky's drawn
Supporting Trump
His entire career is based on the fact that no one is censoring
People
Agree with
What he says
Cartoon
It doesn't force them to think about it for
Even one
Visual metaphors cartoon to look like the words I say
I want I want to make sure that even if
For even one second I never feel the fear of
Am I going to figure this out have you ever seen the back of a
Cereal boxes and sometimes they ask you to find the
Makes me feel inferior Saint Joseph's for you
Out for me
On the back of a cereal box
So we have a Facebook group called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant ever time to time people post Ben Garrison
Cartoon
And every single time I have to wrestle with usually rest I don't usually have this thought
This is got to be fake
You're like 8
The joke
And I can't tell
He has
Like you know how some people have singular Style
Saguiguit filthy's fit2
To show up on Alex's show
We're not going to listen
None of his.
Traffic is really shaky idea of what
Pre-speech me
Or reality
Playground he just seems to not really understand censorship
Has to do with none of them do not understand
But I'm glad the trees
Speech exist
For one reason and one reason only
And that is this next week
We're Alex Jones.
We've critiqued is Guam
Bernie Sanders
His Dracula Soros impression
He did another one
Yeah yeah try and pull out his
You know the weirdest one was is John Madden
Google high-pitched he wasn't trying to tell me fungus spray
Bad impression
I will say
This doesn't least accurate
Depression
This work centers is offensive to the mentally handicapped
I will sing for that
It's much more than this
This morning
Like
Bernie isn't in the ballpark
Hello mr. Christopher Robin
And saw the
Jokes about
Very important
Hundred Acre Wood
More like a rapist
Kermit the Frog
There is an offensive Chinese being the New Smyrna for sir
Colonel is Winnie-the-Pooh in there
Immediately forgot how Winnie the Pooh actually sound like
In my head
Father
It's not just a light there's a lilt
There's a lilt to it
Slightly it's not a British accent but there's a slight bruise What would
It's like
Scratch
Is that lights
Scratch on it
It's almost like I can hear it in my head now perfectly
I can hear it
Perfectly and I can never recreate
I should say full disclosure fire prevention skit when I was at 7
If I showed up and did that
I would have been
F****** fired from that drop
All Chinese immigrants
Play then I really think they would have been right to fire you
Ensure
I just think anybody would I don't know what she sounds like
Inaccurate
That was Alex just doing
Yeah that was him
Like he might as well have said
He's not Jesse Watters legitimately I think what happened
He said Winnie the Pooh Disney
Imma go for it
Terrible idea
Yoda
How do I
I told you that we're not going to hear much
From
The label everything he says
SoundCloud comments right around
He says I want you to say another word that explains the words
I can't do that but
Can you label
Last year
Andrew Anglin
Most Americans don't see Target
We're going to
We have to protect even unpopular speech
Dollar bills
Just having fun with his you know
Survival stories.
Successfully got rid of these
That's their plan
So the problem that I have here is the understanding of
I think I should draw
Perfect Ben Garrison cartoon
Look
Daily Stormer got kicked off of
You know like PayPal
GoDaddy do you mean a giant
Cumulonimbus cloud with a
The calendar on
Exactly
They didn't have their free speech
Anyway violate
Oh s***
Let's not helped Nazis raise funds to harass Jews
And then the business make a decision we don't want to be a part of that
That's not
Free Speech being infringed upon
No that's
A company being slightly
We better than Ford Motors that I agree with what you saying in principle the ideas like you have to pee
Protect even abhorrent
When
Is saying you can't say those things
That's not when companies are saying
Hey you represent something we are absolutely again
So no we don't want to do business with you understood
This is one this is one situation where I am going to put them all on the stupid
Continuum
As opposed to
Continue
Themselves stupid I think they just don't understand that because that's like the same way
Alex Jones
The First Amendment rules apply in f******
No they think it's some sort of Biblical scripture
And they don't understand what it is like
It kind of like works with that grandiosity
Grandiose delusion
You think that all of the world
Should treat you the same everywhere you go
I agree with you to stomach
It's a calculation on their part
Because they realized
F***
Their behavior got them kicked off of these things that we need in order to make the money
We are probably the next
In the crosshairs because
Let's be clear we've done
Pretty bad
Like not a legal stuff we've done stuff it's obviously
People's sensibilities misrepresent
Like I don't I don't
That's why
The present-day I think it's such a stupid
I'm sure it's because of the stupid f******
Free Speech martyrdom campaign
He's going on
Like it
Not
I knows it
Were someone who likes Alex Jones
To listen to the show
They would probably be like hey why aren't you wrestling
Which is
I don't care I don't I reject that as an idea
If you had history
Taken away by the state
Right like if the state were saying shut down Alex Jones we're actually doing
The president
In fact came out and said that a private company should do this
I ordered something and then turned it into a law
For further
If those companies of Alex good
Like legitimately prove that they were all working
Together against
Like the NFL again
Wait
If you could prove those
A different conversation
Those things
Anyway before
It's a valid argument on Free Speech crown
Right
It's just an a******
Brothers
He's getting what he deserves
It's not interesting to me even as a conversation
And it's just
If you had
You became a millionaire by being a dick
Last forever
Almost all the time
Sometimes
Real cool ride
Eventually they even got
And he was protected
Sprite
Comes for you
He hides behind like his perception of himself as a Libertarian
To do whatever you want
Right
Because he doesn't understand
I think that you just
I don't know
Into the Birch Society when he was younger
John Birch Society
Fell in love with Ron Paul at some point
Quite frankly I think that I'd left to do with politics
I think that because Ron Paul probably identified
To have more libertarian
Libertarian
I don't know how to find
Ever
The believer
You have more than three Libertarians in a room you will have a disagreement
That's my that's my
Is that your taxi immatics
Free on anything except they're not f****** Republicans that's all they agree on
What what is is an identity that's like
Call ourselves
Nothing
Is that Republicans we don't want to call
It's more it's more just like a
How would I put that
It's
There's High School mentality
Needing to Define yourself as something
In opposition to
Right right you are mostly just believe everything
You've got to choose some other things
If you want to feel
Maybe you like pop music
Identifier
They can't find
Identified
Themselves so they have
Negative
They have the negative
Articulate
But
Makes pretty f****** clear but even nowhere near any kind of libertarian
Is the
You can have your terms of service and remove it
But but only for reasons that violate law you can't
Whatever you want
Schewels
Teaching three-year-olds that their difference
Men in Drag
I don't want involved with the kids
What
Facebook
You bullied
Cuz our public figures your children
Because
Lgbtq
You just know
Crossdressers
They're closed their clown they're closed
I don't understand why people would think that is a transphobic thing to say
I'm just saying that every part of what it is you are
Is a clown legitimately when he's trying to defend himself
In his speech of like
Is it crazy to think that I'm some kind of an ant
He is an a****** about it
Delivered
I want them to write a law regulating everybody else's speech to give me
Free rein to do whatever it is you need to unpack
Quite a bit more
Because the other stuff we could Alex
Just checking on your transfer via homophobia
Homophobic
F******
Absolute bigot you're a
It is the same thing as like he's scared to see Muslim women at
The pool shop
Muslim women at home
I think it was the Wall Street Journal
No I don't even know I don't need specifics
I did not read okay
There is this there's this person
Let's let's
Lyft
And wrote this
Usually
Islamophobic piece that was like
And so when I was a kid I went there
And I saw somebody
In Endicott
Terrify
My favorite my favorite
What is the
It was like
And then I saw a sign that said
No alcohol allowed here now
This must be the Muslim
And then you're like
Dude
London allows alcohol everywhere
Except for places
We're assholes
That has nothing to do with any religion and everything to do with
Assholes
Unlike in America
AA most places are like
New Orleans where you can just walk around with beer wherever you want and there's only specific Zone
Where people have
Stupid amazing and that people are just going to believe that s*** is so that's a justification for their islamophobia
Bananas
Lauren Southern
But you posted not to
Longo where she was
People in America
Has like a weather
Arabic restaurant right here but where is there a where is there a British restaurant
Whoops
Because
If anyone who has the in
Information can answer the question
That's generally
Write an op-ed
Cuz there's no or or they just use
Like people
Selectively that they talked
In order to make people afraid of something
And then don't believe the rest of the day
No I can't think of anything like that
Regulation
A little bit more
I really need
Because it's very important
So Alex is anti-regulation
As a rule
Buddy
He wants regulation on the internet as a free speech Act
Order to make it so they could not be any
Hold on hold on
Sorry that's just a fun name for an act
First Amendment act you know
Unlike the first
These people can't have regulator
McGovern
What they will or will not
Except
In terms of Internet
The problem was that
I can see no problem
I mean obviously we apply to anybody would apply to like if you have a Blog
And someone leaves a comment that you don't like
Commit a crime
You just
You just proved you're approved how great thou tactic
Yuki you don't have control over your own
We have knowledge
And a lot of people that left
Realtruck.com
Particularly
And then what I do is I
Take point
Absolutely a billionaire
Suspicious
5 but
This Pacific point
Stupid the globalist propaganda
You know all that s***
Atlantic
And you know what you don't want to
Engaged
Terrebonne
Monster X
Damn,
Or $25 or whatever
Not illegal
Now I can't erase that from the website
I can't clean up our comment section
That's not a crime
For them to advertise in our comments
Or not we need a regulation saying that it is a crime
Fruit advertising in order for you to clean up spam
Comments to come in
You understand the problematic
Territory he's entering into in terms of
No regulations on the internet say whatever you want
Normally
Facetiously
Buck against
Intake
The the wrong side
As a joke
But I
Nah that's dumb dude
Don't worry
A harassment
Sometimes as a key area of whether it's illegal or not
And you should be punished for it
Because
Decorum
Lakers much better arguments than
Hey Alex
Create the free speech
The First Amendment Act
With a caveat
Sunglasses
Or whatever
Especially after today
Just
Just the barrage of
Stupidity
That the internet game
I-i'm just like
You know what I am
Trump
EPA
I want them to
To deregulate all CO2 emissions
I want everything to be in the atmosphere because you know it's really going to happen
Everybody's going to die
Except
Billionaire
They're going to have their their Castle
Closer whatever
Call Dwayne.
Guess what it gets we haven't come into a foot like a hundred of us are going to live in Peter teals f****** Island
Going to eat the Peter deal bones were going to make
I know there's not a lot of calories in it
Lakers first first first
Hat on a goddamn spy
Ana Lorde
Exactly like Lord of Lies better than that
We're better than that
Experiment
That is a fun piece of literature but also doesn't necessarily to pick the once again
As we've stated previously
Most people come together in China
Help each other
So
But
How long is
On this ride
I don't need to bring up again how weird
Esoteric
But he's twice tried to talk about how he
He's not against
People doing so
Has been
Very much
Inflate the ideas of
Queer identities
With pedophilia
He's been very explicit about being against
Sir being against trans
So I
I don't
I don't want to talk about that
Because
Who cares
Anyways at is dismissive
The feelings of people who
Because I do understand that
You could
You know trans identify
People would probably be like
Hey motherfuker
Your rhetoric is so dehumanizing
Sing about
Now you want to use us as the way to get your jollies you know that sort of thing I don't want to take
Away from that I respect that position
That's not an argument I can make that's for them to make and I back them up 100%
The only thing that I care about first of all is that he clearly was looking at p***
At work
Which is very
I think it's
I think
Leet
Profession
I think there's that
It's sexual
Just about every work
We get to the bigger issue
Which brings us to our last
And that is
Because everyone
Doesn't really hurt him all that much
He's going
Use that to his benefit
Trolling operation for Soros text messaging
Story of the world
Call Trina
This is what I
Like another perfect example
Earlier in the show
That Bon Iver song is really fun
I'm glad everyone's having a fun time with
You need to realize how propaganda
We'll use the response
That you give it to them
I don't think Alex is going to follow through with it
That's his way of reclaiming
I got out of that
He claims it is just like always a pop-up
XVideos
The screen that's not
It's not where pop-ups
Mike Sheehan
The store
Go to specific places that'll give you a virus
Or they go to places
AmVet Archer
Covid-19
So but he's trying to use that too
Play mint
Like I'm going to f*** with people even more
Indian places
Piece of Advent maybe I was f****** with them that time
He's a good propaganda
Lil Bit no one really understands the issue
And then
Man you should just not
Like gay issue
Issues at all
Resist making it bad
That's because he is
I think that there are like
The stories that he
Wants to cover
Some of them have
Like Blake
Do a better job like
About the Catholic Church
Again
Pedophilia
Cover that much better because
Does
Thrift
Real big
I hate
I hate this
I really do you were
For not being effervescence
Earlier in the show
Because I just got done
Listening to shopping list
It sucks
I know
Mine is
Samsung music
Infinitely easier
Cypress
God dammit
This
Bigger issue
What is Winnie-the-Pooh
Oh man
I don't want
To keep covering
Present
I know that I keep choosing
There's a sick fascination
It's like
Is that
Schrodinger's podcast
Or whatever you know like
Maybe it's never Oreo other board
Until You observe
And maybe
Hit hit a reset button
From
Like maybe it would have felt like we were copping out by doing a
Jim Bakker
Yeah yeah if we were just going to clown on Summit
2 hours
I don't know
There's a lot of issues that I need
But
Website
What is that website
Call Manufacturing
The moment I'm just
I'm just
Unsure of
Any other ways
Forward
With this episode
All of that stuff
If we were if we weren't our show
If we were just a mainstream news Outlet trying to cover news
All of it I would think
Is just like
There's more
You know like all of this s*** every time
We get a rundown of
Dumbass Trump
Tweetstorm
No
You don't get this
This isn't
You don't win
Giving you attention
So you don't get
Did time you lose
And it's the only way to make you lose
It's just a f***
You were not
Talking about you grow the f******
Every Trump headline on like Google News shouldn't be like
Trump at 6 a.m. tweeted this Butch bullshittin
Trump said some dumb s***
Because everybody f****** knows I get doesn't matter
I disagree
I think
But I think there is probably a hypothetical version
Covering
Leica is dumb
Like in a real version there's a way to do it like I do
For someone to do it
But everyone does it wrong
So we keep coming back to about the Alexa
Natura propaganda and the emotion
The two sides of the sea
What is manifesting
I'm going to troll people like that
No
People like Alex
People like Trump
People like
Most of the
Active participant
In the right
The alt right now
They know
Dino the game
They're trying to elicit the response
That most
People give them
Because it
Advantageous to them
They have no shame
The reason
It's not a big
Bo4 Alex
In his own heart
Tubi
Seeing
With a window of pornography open on his phone
That wasn't history
Open
In his phone as a window
The reason
Not shameful
There's no shame there's no problem
He knows what he
He's doing he's
Crazy
He's just
He is
Talking
Just
Dorsey
Transmuting
Fear
White identity
Chauvinism
Anti-islam feeling
Into
Who's the Pope
Exactly
No I
They don't all have pill operation
Put all of them quick whether it's
Ben Shapiro height
Exact
In an order to run the game
You have to elicit the response out of the other side
That feeds
Now we don't
Elicit that
Response like
We hear him
You're not going to give me
Petulant child screaming that wants attention
Giving him attention
His show
You could interpret it
I think it would be
He would have brought us up and
Parade around
We do is beat
His rhetoric on
Angie
There is a version of that way
With all of
The alt right
Trump included
Just not
What is Mos
That is exactly
How I feel about it
It's
It's that
It's at double-sided you know like
Hey
To Alex Jones
This benefit is to elicit that reaction
The Atlantic benefit
Is to respond to that
Because then they get more click right
They cover that b******* the way that they
It's pretty lit.
That infuriated me I'd like
I don't know what it is I don't know why Atlantic I think it's just
Out of pure heart
Hatred
Feel like I hate Reid
But this one this one thing this guy wrote was like
It turns out children don't trust the mainstream media anymore
And there's no reason that I can think of why you guys are a f****** failure
Why do children need a trust
You're interested
Linda f****** Ellerbe doing what's wrong with you
My lovely daughter babe
It is it is not
It's not that I wanted like
Like maybe it until until then
Like because now the the martyrdom of the mainstream media
Praise because
A goddamn appointment
Until the news media
Until they're willing and capable of
Exam themselves
And how it is that they too
Have enabled all of this s*** to happen
How they too are at fault
They're the enemy of the America
Why did this come about how did this guy come about
Guess what
You are
F****** culpable to be complicit
Never happened
They're just like oh now we're the victims are doing the same
Fit the f****** idiots did
They have spell
I'm serious
No response sorry
Sorry, I'm sorry
You asked me if I had any
I mostly agree with
I think I lost
Couple of the points
I do agree at Large
Doesn't
Because they're not recognizing the game
And I kept trying to interject
I'm sorry for that
The same thing with like
Especially in the WWE
Is that like
Who cares if it's good or bad if it
So your healer your face
He doesn't matter unless you're getting a reaction
The worst thing is getting no reaction
You're the best wrestler in the world
And no one is like
Interested at all
You're dead in the water
We've shifted to a place where
Like legitimately understanding pro wrestling
I think it's going to be
The most important thing moving forward.
Internal
You can understand why they're doing that
He's being a shitheel
You know
Sphero challenging someone to a debate and then
Bailing on the debate when they didn't reach whatever qualifications
The Cowardly heel
Or whatever you know
They're all playing by weird wrestling Playbook
And it's not it's not conducive
Two things going well
And when the media trying to be like
We are just here
Is B
Trick bike
Over and over and over and over
Do you make you make a great point at the same time
End up looking f****** stupid
Because those are the people
Constantly get tricked by the heels exactly responding to the heels doing obviously evil
There's nothing
Things to do other than be I guess
The shity fan who's watching
We are
You just you just
Encapsulated it
Perfectly because I do
Professional
Is
Just as much info
Interested in the
As they are in
Probably do you know what I'm saying
Accurate
I don't disagree but what I know
As far as compared to watch wrestling
In the in the
Sarah versus now
Sorry I caused
Like I'm early 30s
Is your late 20s
I think it's because there's a
Okay because I can play a 26
There is a difference
Between
Knowing
While working Arthur Vines
Regal
You know like wrestling now
Beautiful mind I retract that
Entirely
Without that
Bulshit
Tell that book personal
It is that
Distance of recognizing the Mediterra
As being
You can watch
So is recognizing The Meta narrative
Are our current
Political propaganda
Importance
Like to
Recognized
Even if
The individual reporters
At the New York time
And their boss said no
You got to write a thousand words on block
Somebody at the New York time
Recognize
The matinee
I know
We have to respond
Just because it's going to get us
Traffic
Then if we don't
Bright
There is there are people who recognize that
Who are playing the game
And we're not
Like you and I probably are but like
Most people are not playing that game
Wrestling is real like I don't know I don't know what to tell brother
Back then
The metaphorical version were talking about
Goes over
In the real world it's like
Bombed
Yemen people are giant
The rohingya people are still being
Like Slaughter
Definitely deserve that Nobel
Super sure recognizing similarities
Incredibly important because
You can't allow yourself
Debated
In the way that
People like
Bates and what's so f***** up about it is that sometimes there are things that are
He didn't mean for his phone to show that
Salute
It still provides him an opportunity
Appositive
And you need to
People need to recognize
Message with large Soap Box
People need to recognize that
Recognize the instances of like this is a viable thing to
Like
And things
Yeah like we
Thousand
About
His pornographic in
I've seen 20 tweet
About how he probably murdered ago
That's a good f****** point
0 tweets about that
I've seen zero tweets about anybody talking about a couple trees
Episode
There's
You know it's not
Stop
Is easily
Reclaimed
Control territory
And unique
We all need
We need to do better
But everyone needs to do a lot better
Closer
We should just focus on
Trying
And it seems like everybody else
Promote
Episode
What if we actually did what anyone doesn't like
I haven't even
I don't do s*** not good
Why would we do this
That's the problem you know how you understand the Mediterranean
Game over understand
We are torn episode I put it up next morning like
I hope nobody
I stand by everything all better
Goddamn
Start
Nice I think
You should not be Shameless
GoodLife where you get up in your
Your head
And ghosts
Where they don't exist
Do we have a web.com
Yep telephone
American Express
He won't have anything to say
Club with Sprite
Manilow
I love Woodhouse so much
Bandages
Drones Club
So much fun everyone's throwing rolls made out of
It is so many times that I will go back and reread those
Then just be like
You have no because this is a
What version of the drones Club
Do you know when the last time
You don't know shitt
Years ago
Call the junior Danny
Sure you would absolutely remember off
The top of your head if you re-read at 6
For this and more references to b.g. what has you could not go to our Twitter
Also even in person I won't tell you anything
Sing about peace
I want to talk to you I will talk to you about it
Anyway we're on Twitter or Facebook
Ben Garrison
Lot of references to Daddy shark
Appreciate
Thought it was something
She made up
Click on any of the videos that people vote
I've never heard the actual song
I've only ever heard him sing
I can only guess based on the words
Comeuppance
Closed caption
Daddy shark
Badoo
I think
Mama shark do 2222
I think something along those lines
The original
If you're listening
Hope you are
Don't call
Neon
Squeeze
Please
Liquid number of times
Especially Impreza
Country music
Indicated Maybe
If you can hear me out
Please work
The Adjustment Bureau into your rhetoric somehow
It's the worst f****** movie develop a dick has ever been involved
Drift base on him writing the short story is involved in
But I would love for you to just
Just talking in that you're
Please Stephen King stole all that hat material and all that
Not a good move. John's
One of the most important things that
And that isn't really the focus
Episode
Say what you will
Alex Jones almost killed a guy or
Kill the guy
Alex