Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Knowledge
Spite
Let's
Just liquor way to do it
Introduce each other ourselves
Yeah whatever
Yeah so here we are here
A gentleman who is very interested in Infowars and Alex Jones
Xecular
Jordan
Sit down have a bottle of wine
Like the bougie assholes that we are
Do you buy prophecy wine
At the Pinot Noir out of California
Weirdo with a bindle
I'll look at a gesture with a bindle on the
On the front of it
And he is surrounded by Woodland
Pure
Illuminati symbol
That's what Alex would tell us
Supremacy the show here is that I have gathered
The Jordan is not heard
But and I will just
Discuss
Ramifications of figure that s*** out
Tubidy Tubidy
At least a little bit
At the end of last week
First of all I could not
I could not wait to do this again by the way I was counting you to possibly do this
On a daily basis
Yeah no
Yeah last episode
Podcasting but I was so emotionally drained Jabari home just like
How old is a man
To figure out Alexa
The amount of
Mental
Stress
It must take
To live inside that world
The moment I left
I started reading about because that's the only way that we can look through this
And the term was coined
Not the way we think of it where it's
Like you can hold
Competing ideas
Whenever you get
The one that you prefer that fits your natural narrative
Is the one that you wind up holding
Psychologically
You know
You can't
Compete
With
Insanity
By using facts
Because when you
People just doubled down on there it's in coop
Run to their line of thinking
It's it's
I mean we're witnessing this play out on the national
Scale International scale right now if you listen to the first episode we know the Pakistani
As well
Set this up
Last week at the end of the week Alex
Mr. Jones if you're nasty
Cavs
He reference on the last episode of we did that he was going to take some meetings
But maybe he didn't want to take these meetings
Cuz he can
Warren someone in person
Well well if you get out
Between the lines
Has taken those
And he's out of this
For the last like 4 days for days that he is going to be
Assassinated
Which we learned throughout the course of
Some of the Clemson play today
Are weirdo College
We'll get to that in the mail
The last few days
Has been like guest host
Filling in
And I don't really care to talk about that
I mention this in the last episode
But like no
Respect to Paul Joseph Watson
No disrespect
Pjw sjw
No disrespect to him or orange a little disrespected Owen Shroyer that guy's an a******
Them because
Without them there isn't
Without them it doesn't matter Alex Jones can do this on his own
Without Alex Jones
There is no info
Yeah like he's built a cult of personality
The same way that
There are
Colts little minions
And they are basically the echo a lot of his marriage
So it's not really all that interested
Sing to me to breakdown
With Paul Joseph Watson
Has to say when he
It's mostly just
There's a on and also people are
When Allison
I would never have guessed that
Anti-racist
At a future shop
But I wanted to do this
But we didn't have a show with
So I decided
Let's go ahead and do that Y2K up
So that's why we're here
We're going
Discuss what happened when
Alex Jones
On December 31st
Unfortunately
So you are missing out on him saying we're doing a white
2K episode and me absolute
17 years later
Here we are
What is happened we have not yet been
If you will allow me to use that term
Of the Opera
Is
This story that I
Picked up
That
Power plant
Pennsylvania
Had been taken offline
So I'll let him
Explain the story
Alright let's go ahead and get to this article Associated Press
I just came out at 7:22 a.m. eastern standard time
December 31st 1999 Pennsylvania nuclear plant shut down one of the two nuclear reactors
PECO Energy Co Limerick Generating Station has shut down
How this morning after a piece of equipment
Play Old Company spokesman Neil McDermott
The problem was not Y2K related
It was declared an unusual event the least serious emergency classification of nuclear power plants they got have a serious emergency
Shutdown
Serious emergency
Emergency
To stop the strippers
Wild conjecture
And total b*******
You like okay well the story is that it's nothing serious
Anal at 7
Nearest
Pretty much
Evidence has been worn out
Not Y2K
But the story is
Nothing serious
It's clearly stated I also like
The the audio quality of this clip now because it does have the feel of
Like Dan Rather reporting
Warzone every sound
Dusty box
Clips from
I'm not as able to take everything like
SMS episode
Just because this entire episode
It's not online
Okay there was just a large compilation of clips
Avalon
Trust me
Context
Is 5 the context is like that's all you need to know about the contacts
Apologizing
Not necessarily to apologize
I just feel like
Affair day in court is required
So
Release date
It was declared unusual then
Shutdown occurred when an insulator on the main generator Transformer from Limerick to fail
We have reports yesterday of this
Off the record I would not report it but I had it from a good source
Implant-supported here
And just go ahead and report it
I know I'm not going to record it I have more information I don't really have more information
Get up on your route
I know this is something I think is also really important
And fun to bring up
This is all he does
He says like
I've got this information
Someone
Told me
Credible information
First of all the information is
Never says
Who the people are
In the same breath
Now we have this
Intelligence report that came out about the hacking
The Russian hacker
You read the article
Just some guy said maybe and there's no
Well
Let me be that as it may
His
The unnamed
Officials
Who are giving these things like
But if I don't
That's because I'm pretty
Texting you from the truth when it's because
Steven Yeun
Premier
He's not dumb
Information here
Tomorrow formation that is not this this Transformer that they're talking about they wouldn't just got a plant on over that
Something serious maybe going on there
So turns out it was
Better be end of every
Turned out it was
It was like a broken
Insulator and acquired them
And it does happen from time to time
It's a little bit
Extreme innocence
Nuclear reactor
Nuclear Power Plant
Is nuts
It does get the cool down to Coors and stuff like that
It's a huge process
But it does happen sometimes
Yeah well it's an immensely complicated way of powering anything
Gets cleaner
Isn't it
I don't know
Amazon going to assume it's cleaner because people are afraid of
Energy specialist
Earlier from anonymous
Actually I'm more of a Gobot
Special
Really where I'm or after
Narrative that runs
Throughout the entire episode
Or he just cause
Only brings up to Pennsylvania power play
Annie
Yeah
It just goes on and on but we can take away from that clip is that
He knew about it
Yesterday
It's on the right and there's four or five other ones around the country
Better
Who knows what's going to happen
Since it's a serious emergency
And not just a
Transformer
Anyone at any time
Message
The underlying message is actually trying to get out or what hit the point you're trying to make
Is that
These aren't real serious problem
The plan problem
It's not that
Happening
Is that the globalist
Want you to think Y2K is happy
Well they have there
Surrogate
Terrorist
Go out and caused a little problem
The Narrative that I was not accept
Afraid of
This is a full-on false flag
Okay
Where were cover story for years ago
And the globalist
He's already established
From the jump from the jump Global from whenever he got radicalized in Junior College
Do now
Globalist the problem
I haven't finished it yet but I'm ready
I've read most of the book that he read in college
He cites as
His Awakening
His redpilling is
As they call it now
Conspiracy
And basically all it is about these
Globalist for
That are trying to
Trick people into it
Accepting social
Because socialism is a lie
That leads to Communism
And communism isn't really people sharing thing
It's otter control of the state
Over everything
Principle behind it and that's guided him
Throughout his
Higher broadcast
Supervisor
Questions at the end of the festival in his
Underlying
What is inconsistent and what
And how it plays out in the world
So so here's a
Question that I have
And Friday
Doing the globalist
25 years ago
Does he think
She's winning or there
He now thinks he's winning
With Trump
Because he believes the Trump is the champ
I was going to take them all down
Okay
He can wrap his head around like people like Rex Tillerson
You know Exxon
CEOs being put on the cabinet
Now you know these Goldman Sachs
Bankers
Did you look at their history
They've been fighting the globalist
The whole way
I have
No idea how that's possible
Because you wouldn't want to leave a record of that in case the globalist win
Atleast play Both Sides there so you can survive
The globalist code
But then you've still got the
We're getting too deep into the story in modern day
But
Is anyone
The behind-the-scenes so let's all go back to work
Where were you
We were really afraid
X27 reactors
Across the country
I'm not even
I got the shoes about the Pennsylvania
Early yesterday got it again off air
Confirmed it with someone that is 99% accurate. My dying
You catch that
Off-air with somebody
Who's percent accurate
Like I am
Yeah that's
Broadcast baby
Only deals with 99%
You only hang out with people in your own social class I'll be incorrect all the time
He's not correct all the time he wants to leave that open
Just in case
Trying to report the truth and now I got the Associated Press saying will they shut the whole plant down but
They call it
Usual event the least serious emergency classification Nuclear Power Plant
A plant that
Good luck
Yeah pretty bad for them to power the plant
It has to be more bad than anything that happens where they don't
It's appealing on one level
But it's also not
Borne out by the
I think it's hard for us because we're trying to
Compete
Non-tax with facts
Right
Engage with this on its on its own level
So I would love for you to do that so hard
My whole life
They got to leave that at the door
This is now I'm delving into this world
You are
Concentrated
99.9
Epiphysis
If it is a serious problem
What is going to happen
All those
Going to go off okay so then
I don't know I don't know
I think it's probably the
We all do
Where's the human Community we all should wear libtards
And we care about people in foreign
Yes but
I think that maybe the
So good
Riptides for people who are not in
So I think the next stage of The Narrative of that would be that the grid goes down
Power goes out around the city's control
Tire grid
And there's no backup and once the nuclear power plant goes down
It's utter chaos
Which of the globalist
Trying to put
It's funny you should say that maybe you should
Shakir and they're coming from one of Alex Jones is
Reputable sources
I'm a little bit
Yeah they're they're they're going up on it right now
I called in today I got another confirmation real early this morning and practice support attorneys
Come up
About the power plant situation
A gentleman from Michigan
About the
PowerPlant situation
In Pennsylvania
Michigan
So it wasn't Michigan fact that I wanted to stop here for a second
Compressor
And
Like you just said
What we were talking about yesterday
He was talking about the guy in Michigan
Earlier
He might have talked to Alex
I like
Proud this dude was that got it before
He is he is getting information before even Alex Jones like he's big-time and Alex Jones right that right
Take a nap
It's 2 in the morning
Even if he is
Accent makes
Everything's.
Wrong
We'll also
The pronoun
And I think it's important
Cuz I am I believe
If you spoke to Alex
Hey Alex what we were talking about
The guy in Michigan or is it humid out
I don't think
Heating contract
The meaning of the wrestler
About the power plant situation while we were talking about yesterday in Kentucky
Call me about a power plant
Exactly
And listen here
I'm talkin about
We have confirmation
When given the order they will shut this one down in that article that you were talking about about that
Paper crane in Pennsylvania
Just goes on to say
Exact same thing
So do we use bag
Is him
Michigan
Actually believing that he is part of Alex community
Yeah okay like
Like the way that
The the church would say that as a possibility also
He goes on to say that there's a
Michigan
That it when given the order
They will shut it down which means what
The globalist
Will be sick
Right
That's what it has to mean in his mind
Even though that is literally what would happen is
Your Superior
Put say
You would
Pennsylvania
This is something that comes up over and over again on this episode
The most interesting
Is that because
People keep calling in and saying wild s***
Never challenges
He never died
There is never been
Perhaps a day that we knew in advance
Was going to be f***** up more than
Y2K
I'm going to be careful about things I believe
On this day
Because
Everyone
Kind of full of s***
My I remember this
I was 13
Started
Putting water
In the freezer
Like like
Incase
Yeah and I remember thinking
Or at least
Tell myself I remember that
That's not going to help
Go back
Maybe two days were the water we're going to have to forage sooner or later
Is reading books about 4
As it goes in these disaster scenarios
Most of the time
You only really have to wait out about a Wii
R2 before like
Most people are dead
This is zombie apocalypse
Discussing fear p*** that these weirdos who come on Alex's show talk about all the time
Survival food
And that'll get you through like
You know
Two weeks and that's when all the
The Lawless people would have killed
Each other off and you know if you have the food it's the difference between
Being able to
To sit around at home
With the family or after go out and fight
Now
One thing about the zombie apocalypse narrative that these guys totally share
Which is
Absolutely jerk off to the fantasy that day would be the Lone Survivor
You're basically saying is like
If if she does go down it's a good thing that we have you Alex Jones and the rest of us who can sell
Play our first commercial break
Commercial break of the Y2K show
Potential wife in case
Interruptions of services
Can a whole food Reserve
Yep
So was that the picture
You start to get the picture of what's going on
Spreading fear
And all this idea of like ohmygodyes disaster is happening
Is going down
Triple A
Years
And right up to it
He's been Hawking survival food
Okay
Is he selling the food is that
Company that selling company
Because I like I thought commercial
Another ad later which is even more.
But
So
This meeting is going to keep water from overflowing in a stadium
How you know your words
Power plants later in the Navy get another update on
Something else around the world
Another caller
Also reported local person Karthik on TNN
A power plant has been blown up in Oregon okay we need to get to Iran
Studios at gtmo
Checking out the boy
Printing folded
Now man this is happen
That's set to report that I got and two other people
On local repeaters verified it
Here is a known
Cif-ss
Blackburn Wayside
Turn on the fact that we need to go ahead and report the truth but
Sure warm people are aware
Yeah
Support the troops know what are you say
Set a report
The truth
Something that is him
His hand a little too far
That is if it causes a panic
So be it
Should have warned them earlier
When he is the only person
Who's out there in the man like in the grand scheme of things
Staying all this crazy b******* and letting these
Whack job colors
Dictate what he believes organ explosion
Didn't happen
No
It wasn't reported in any
You know real
Media
Tell him that someone told him that happened
And he doesn't challenge
Are are sharks color screen
They have to be right or is it only his
I don't know actually
Clearly
I have zero
Ever changed
Yeah when they talk about
Global is
Whenever they insinuate things that disagree with him
Very rarely
Righttime he just screams
Because I remember listening to Handy's radio show
My grandfather
Which I remember as
It's just the greatest
Sure
Is he Hannity's kind of
He would often bring those people on
Because then he could really go off on
And that's what was really excited but actually know this
Document
But unconfirmed source.
We have a number of friends
To work
Doing fake calls
The radio show
And like if you listen to DriveTime radio in morning radio almost
People call in and like
Morning DJs are doing bits with them and stuff like that
For the most part
Notion
Didn't know that you just destroyed my whole world like thirty-five $40 a call or some
Like that we have a number of friends I'll tell you off are who they are and what their business
Chemistry
Really really dirty
That's
That's what a lot of radio station
Because no one
Most people don't call in
Are usually crazy wonder about that because I
Image of somebody driving
DriveTime ratings
Somebody's driving and they just like to call this radio show
So they're driving and then pulling all this s***
Out of there
So they make me believe
Give that
The thing with Hannity's
Yeah it's get these callers any
I have never someone who actually knows their ship
Well
Coincidentally
See that's still kind of makes sense to me if you screen your colors like
The man on the street interviews like
They're not
People who know exactly what
People who are like that fit that Narrative of
Isn't everybody
Pinpoint about some of the Alex Jones Show that we missed
This week that I just want to tee off on real quick
So a lot of the episodes end up
Starting with like a man on the street
I wish this
They start with someone on the street and what there was one that was like Mark Dice
And he was going around
If I your girlfriend
Pregnant
And someone comes up and just punch her in the stomach.
Couple times real good
If she aborts
Is that murder
The complicated Quest
No one else has given any of that nuance
Yes
To kick it out of her belly is it not murder
Cuz nobody else was
Is different baby
So she still acting
Upon the baby
As if she were punching herself in
Okay
That is that is an interesting that an interesting argument
It's murder
Necessarily
I think it's
A brutal assault
But it's a brutal assault from the guy onto her
It made her unable to
The carry the baby
It's not that
He's attacking the baby at all
He's attacking
Yeah but
He's punching her in the stomach
Multiple times
Yeah
Where is this guy coming
Crazy Town
No Doubt
So he's punching the baby now I do think you're right in
In saying that it's not murder
Can you murder something that doesn't have
Or or even the the idea of conch
Now that's where it gets complicated
It's outside the scope of the man on the street
A man on the street interview
Aldi's little debate with coffee
Prophecy wine
Shut up
Reactors
All these power plants
We're having trouble
You know all around the country
Did what
Being challenged
So
Incredibly frustrating
Because
You asked why would he
Angers me
Even the question
Because if you are
A journalist
If you are someone who
Do people listen
You have a responsibility not to throw bullshiter
Especially
On a day like Y2K when everyone is on it
Like
People were on it
They shouldn't have been
But they were people were buying into it
People were hoarding stuff
Like it was happening
Broadcaster
You do have a certain responsibility to be like
Well
You know
Even if you say
The very unconfirm reports
Play blown up in Oregon we're looking into it
It's probably not true will get back to you when we have confirmation
I feel like that's as far as you can go
Would you like to be called in saying
I heard it from a guy like there's only one guy who was watching
But like
Friend who heard it from a friend
Perform another
Who are the Oregon
We were playing a game of telephone that started with
Yeah
There we go
From here
Night was not
Jump
Actually no let's let's leave that until we could really crazy
Okay well the night was not just
What about power play
Lance though the night also had
Various flavors Airport
And power plants are still beautiful
Yes
Do plants came up tonight
It just kept coming up but also throughout was
A bunch of other
Weird
Weaving storyline
This introduces
Couple of them
Civilians crap in the city Russian heinzerling shot down tanks are being blown to bits
Sorry I should explain
That is in reference to the warrant
OK Google
Hundreds of thousands
People are dead
There's another clip that
That the
Says it
It says all of that
He's talking about how there's more Wars going on now than ever
Wait here I think
On the day
More Wars going on on December 31st
99 than ever have
No better than ever in the history of the world
I think this is
Cash machine
Who is known as Vladimir the ruthless
And using profanity on national TV You Name It We won't read the profanity here but we've got it
Unbelievable
He is a creature of the IMF and the World Bank and international communism music
Yes
But also
Hillary Clinton
Nosy little girls
Gatorland
It was just
The guy who had the same picture as a
Ghostbusters 2
The person who Alex Jones Now is really getting behind
And supporting Millions on Russia's
Yeah he was on Russian television being loud by Alexander Dugan
One of
Putin great advisors
Very close
Alex Jones was on Russian television
And you look like you was going to cry
There's a translator
He was on Russian television
And this guy Dugan
Explaining to him that like
Because of you our opinions about America have changed
Like it was just a rim job
Of a segment
Alright they can't f****** believe
They're giving him lip service because narcissist
How
It's a very old trick and Spy game
So they're just like
Because
The View I say this
Anti-americanism is over
Looks like he's going to cry
Like he's finally got Daddy's approval
It's insane
So is
Who hog
On the side of Russia
Alex Jones
Is over
Directly because of your intervention
Yes
Okay
Because of you and because of your help you gave to
The Trump you shown us that all Americans
Weaselly dick
I'm paraphrasing a little bit you can find Alex Jones
It's on
The Infowars
I Channel on YouTube
You can find it
Absolute insanity
If
If I were on Russian television they were saying those things about me first of all I'd be panicking
Hope no one sees it
This is like
S***
S*** rush I think I'm awesome
Is the nickname of this podcast so
Like a demon
In Cahoots with the IMs international monetary fund
But he's also
Putting him as one of the heads of the global
So he is
Painting Putin as
Part of this Global cabal that he is again
Hey 1999
Which has now completely
Former KGB head
And this information is vital ladies and gentlemen we are seeing the New World Order
I really come out in full force more Wars that have been the last 50 years are going on right now
Now report 2009
100 100
You make those claims
Which is
It's a lot of people impossible amount of
That's what that was in reference
Get back
My Maybe
But they're not old
4040 South
Sorry that everybody flat ground scorched-earth
People are off of
Okay
In the city Russian Hinds shot down tanks are being blown to bits
Massive agrad unguided rocket attacks are big long, City industry
Air and artillery bombardment as well
Clear plant has been shut down one of the main system transferring the power from its failed
So you went to the commercial with that sort of terrifying
Bellevue place
Random places
Like
Didn't know where they're going to go or they just shooting their water at all different directions
But then we come back from
Commercial
Minneapolis Minnesota to shortwave is basically downloading them
Production of another narrative
The Narrative of
The government
Is trying to take out radio 6
Okay
Throughout the night
Which
Alex Jones
We'll get a little bit love you
In Washington DC has set up a huge 50 million-dollar command bunker hooked into all the female boxers that can pay
Take over
All the shortwave
By Broadcasting
What the f*** is that the central government
Also known
Because we should operate under maritime law
Or whatever
Did they
That day
Also
That's not much for a bunker
Bunker
Set up
Because on
On Y2K
Just bladimir
Shrek
Marshall AM FM stations as well as television broadcast.
Activate tab
Yeah but he's afraid to take out all AM FM stations television as well he goes a little bit
Further into this
Why would they take out all the am and FM
Cuz they don't want Alex jumping on any of those stations
Communicate special
Patriots
Communicating on AM FM radio or just radio
CB Ray
Maybe I mean I don't know I don't know enough about radio waves
But I'm guessing that's one of the
Okay okay
So he is once again
Whatever it is
As we as I refer to it on the last episode
Think I'm going to keep on
Keeping on with it
It's just paranoia scat this coming out in this case Ella Fitzgerald
In this case it's clear that it's not random
These are the Spheres that
The people have
Antojitos
Amplifying them playing into
Like that
Now I will give him
That on
January 1st
A2000
Boris Yeltsin
Yes and that broke
New Year's Eve
So
The idea of being scared about this Putin guy
He's worthless
Although if
If your name is Vladimir you do have to have a after that with whatever like
Vladimir the Impaler
My editor
You know.
Wonderful mycampus editor in college
My wrote for the student paper her middle name was Vladimir
I don't give a s*** about gladimir Vladimir the editor
He was better than what
I think I actually know another Rush
Asian girl who's
Middle name is Vladimir
That's a pretty weird
What is
Vladimir
Tell me their name
Right
And you can't say the name Vladimir without putting us up blank
He's talking about someone who's giving him information
Are you starting this clip off talking about someone who
Is feeding him information that you will see
That he plays his normal game
Feels like does he give
A name to any Source at any point in time
Want to former military Pizza on radio company
Nope nope
But also we learned
We learned that
We also learned a lot of former military people now on radio station
Powerpool Cold War in the North Pole
Origin
A 9.4000 up to nine point
Everywhere right now.
Superpower
Radar systems nuclear systems up and perhaps our military
Is refused
It's now backup from people that actually worked in there
We have a confirm from The Sound where it's coming from from experts
Meme
Well one
Win 4
1999 when did the Cold War end
To him
Never
Okay well no no
This year
M1919
Okay
So we have
Why would they put
Disrupt
Technology
In the North Pole on the northeast
Santa Claus is real
I think he thinks Maybe
There
So let's just let's just work let's just go throughout this whole thing
Yeah cuz there's so many pieces
Because he
Brilliantly
A later one of you one of those things
Is going to hit one purse
Power plant
This is actually going to be
Be out to Pennsylvania
It was really
Let's just keep mischaracterizing power plant
Which Are we more afraid of
Okay
So we got
Powerful cold war-era
Destructor
What does from the Cold War era they didn't even have f****** planes
It's because the short-wave signals
Aren't that sophisticated
So it's good
If this old-time system that can shut down
Am and FM
Shortwave radio
Have you seen a lost
No I haven't seen lost that's another thing that I have not seen
Great show
Okay there's a whole thing
In a season where there's a
Signal disruptor
On the island so they can't get radio off the island
Because this
This lady had
Signal jammer
I think that's what Alex Jones thinks of happen
The signal
Going out of the entire world
So so if it's on the North Pole
He believes that it can then reach the entire world
Yeah you're you know what you're right
We all know that
The South Pole
The North Pole is up
That makes perfect
I don't know what the
The logic
Is there other than
Got to say something
Me some
Internal logic
To that long
Cuz that's just a long list of
Different things for you to be afraid of
None of them are connected
Did to each other in any way other than he
He thinks they're all happening
Orchestrated by the same
People like globalist
Iran Bill Clinton
Disable the Cold War other stuff
But not this
But that's
Call Doris.
Okay
Cold War by first rap album
I think the picture that we start to come up with
And we have
To deal with
Is that maybe scaring people
Maybe it is
Not fun
Inversion of War of the
Basically is what we're bogged down in
What were the world that it was artistic
It was that's true Orson Welles is pretty good dude that was trolling
This is not
This is
And we'll get to again why
I'm a hundred percent
At our next commercial break
Can't get out it's like
This is a whole doctor Strangelove situation
It is like okay
They put their Cold War stuff on the North Pole
There's only one way to fight against
On the bottom
Do you want to be afraid of s'more stuff
Hot ladies
And gentlemen
A police and military are on high alert running around looking for supposed Boogeyman and I would have given anything
For him to stop
With ladies
Ladies
Do this for the ladies
Usher concert
Hot lady
And I believe the military are on high alert running around looking for supposed Boogeyman in
Paris under every Rock
Military are highly visible now
Military equipment moving into Austin
Are two nights ago on Wednesday night the Fox News reported that the airport will be used as a Mastiff
Holding facility for troublemakers for Riders here in Austin that has no history of riots
They need to get that country lockdown so they could save the election
Vladimir Putin
Okay
So the military is
Highly visible
Highly
Highly visible in Austin Texas
Occupied Austin
In case of a riot
Even though there's no history of riots
The airport
Yeah they're older
I don't have the key
Broadcast
All the Blazer the sky gets a call and they like hate
Let's be aware there's other countries we need to be afraid of two
Great Cyclone we're all going to
China exist in Germany pretty weird too
The crazy thing
He's one hundred percent correct about Vladimir Putin
AAA like low-level
Country
I would posit that
He's right big picture
Globalist
Chill and all that is
Not really backed up by anything
But yeah
Be concerned about it
Only Alex Jones
That's not true exactly
So
Let's go
Where did that come from
Where did
Even got to take guitar
San Antonio
I can't play the clip yet but that will be
That's really the only way.
Add to the answer
Is that
So maybe you're wondering
Jordan maybe you're wondering what's going on around
Absolutely wondering where else
Christian report
Excellent
Eco-friendly yesterday saying
Don't want you to leave here in Arkansas my girlfriend work here I don't want you to leave and I want to leave I'll take up more
We just found out now
Text Nepal
Arkansas Highway transportation department vehicle
All over the place
They might have been doing road work
Where the department
I've been seeing them all over the place
Did he
Alright
Mancini's Deli workers Mariano's
Conspiracy to cut some
She wasn't even a pop
Was there a potbelly
And this girl here just does not believe in except Nelson totally
Thor nuts over it
So you dumbass person for a long time and she was a doubting Thomas and now he claims he has personally seen the martial law
Arkansas
Call Sergio
So what's gorgeous about this and what you're about
To hear and I
Spell it out this is
Alex
Not question it
Challenge
Now listen to this pain it's gorgeous
Robert Mueller Airport
Former military officer informed police officer retired gentleman than own
Northeast a company that services for the military for years
So there again is another person who is not playing but like I don't want to say
Logan figure it out is a retired
Former police officer
Former military guy
Retired
What like power plants
Some s***
Some Consulting work for the government
Where I paused the cliff we might end up swallowing it but he says also
But you you see what I'm saying
Crazy bulshit
I meant instead of being like
Well I don't
I appreciate the call but that's not worried about this for now
He says here your brother
Now also
Anybody in Central Texas
Did you just walk up like hey guys looks like you got a great concentration going on
And you were a real Alex Jones who wasn't full of s***
The message we stay the f*** away from there don't go over there it's dangerous
Go look at yourself
But but that's a great way of signaling it exists
You shouldn't actually go there but you could know that it's there because you could walk upright
My listeners
And if you
If you believe what I'm so
You should go there and why
Don't do confirm Define
Basically,
Clips not done
Okay
Standing
Individual
Happy Merry Christmas Manny told me two nights ago that he was out at Fort Hood during the bailing work where I know he is working right
Largest army base
America
Someone would know
If this guy's actually telling Alex
Somebody should know
You should be dead
He's just identified him
To someone
Know-it-all
I think he's making up
A person
If you're if you're going to go like in the Washington Post
They still went just like
Anonymous
Government officials or like intelligence
Power plant
Sing from last night
Official Anonymous intelligence intelligence officials
I've known for many many years
We go golfing every now and then to a herringbone suit wonderful
Wife
Good to kids
Barros
So like the temperature is water
Whenever we are kids
Whenever you lie you tell me what the word
Creative stories
Details
When they're unnecessary
Kind of mean you're lying
Ya know that your girlfriend is having an affair
Except except
Forgot
And they were
Giant crane online to Crane flat cars loaded with a PCS and lav
Armored personnel carriers and light armored vehicle
Somalian pirates
Just get it all over the place
They got flatbed trailers they have
Large cattle trailer types of situations navy blue with black
Or maybe red or maybe grieve their vert look like
Alex that is a producer
Color is
Not super important
Light armored vehicle
That would have been
Do you see all of these lightly armored vehicles
Car with a lot of
Sure that's a lightly armored
And in my 32 years of life
Number on a number of occasions I have seen provide more details 232 I don't
Actually believing in my water
Begin to hurts around a 20
30 but I'm literally
Microsoft tricks
I have seen
Large
Convoys of military machinery
Being moved
It's never been asked
Suspicious thing
Machinery
I like sometimes I do have this
Sometimes you make sure
Anytime you see one of those giants
Windmill
Trucks that carry those those windmill blades that are
Ever a cross
Do have this tendency
T2 like look at it be like
Big f****** plant
I want to give you two
Do you want to go for
Dairy
Or do you want to go to Atkins
Commercial break
Did something scary so we got to go to a
Break
We will go to our next commercial break
His
Alright
Kenny Loggins I'm alright
Don't nobody need a reference
You better believe it's going to be Dane
Week week
So this
This is pretty much all the evidence you need this commercial have shity it is
How expensive it is
The name of the game
Scaring people to say
Okay
Start over
Control yourself
Which is the last commercial
Yeah
But
Ability of having to flee for your lives
NATO is going to war because they're onto US
Yes
Irresponsible
Glad that was trying to sell gold
Might as well get more gold
How they sold iPods in the 90s
God damn it I would have bought so many iPods
You're going to leave
It holds
Company owned by a guy named
Mr. Anderson
Who
Bcn also in the major
This is one of my 309
Scooby-Doo
Alright
Unimportant
Lyon
Literally everything is important
This guy owns
Gcn the Genesis
Communications Network which broadcast Alex Jones
He also owns Midas
Which is the people who sell gold
And also is
Is a part-owner in
In the gold sales
Consortium
Answer
Deceive
Conflict
Beginning of every episode
They don't ever disclose this
Not even when Anderson was on the show
As a guess
He was on and they talked about how great an
Gold one
Even talked about how they're all in a rat king
Like
Financial entanglement it's insane
Yeah but
I feel like now.
What is literally
Play every media
And also I mentioned this on the last step
Bring backup
Midas resources
This is the company that now sells the weird help
You can go to their website
It's Midas resources.com
Creative
Supported
And vouched for by a Veterinary
Veterinarian
Anti weird new AG doctor
I actually did some research into him between episodes
Arizona
Confirm that I wasn't talk
I'm not quite the thing that I also found out that
Is that the guy went to the same College
We're both alumni of University of Missouri
So bad
You never answer
Is he a good veterinarian
You the best
What if he's a really good veterinarian
I'm more likely
To buy bolshit products Veterinary
Super good veterinarian dietary medicine in college
Same brother
Because I just barely graduated
Let's be clear that's better than me I never graduated let's be clear it took me five years and I had to come
The fake major
I got out
Veterinarian
I wish I was
F****** Wallach
Richer than me
He's basically but that's the same shift the Doctor Oz
It's like he's not better than
No but I'm not judging
Remind me
We are now on I
Crazy bulk
Just last episode was just on YouTube but now you can
You subscribe
You can get that episode
Now on iTunes
I don't want to say cuz I would never say this
I don't want to say that we're the only source of information
Information
To you this Focus
Also you can follow us on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight.com
Now it's underscore the pipe
Nope
Who's God
I don't know I did
I didn't look but then also acknowledged
But it's too many
You can only get one number past knowledge
So now it's underscore fight on Twitter
What else
Go to email us you can email us at knowledge fight
Gmail.com
Got all of it
Yeah we got we got some social media
I think this has really came about because
You are you like you were talking about it worth
You know if we get a lot of viewers on the YouTube
You said that
Sweden
But but that's
That's it quickly spiraled out of control for yours like
This has to be if I can
I just love doing it to a lot of positive feedback
Twitter
And
Really enjoyed
Are we are we done
Music
Could you edit in some Saved by the Bell music.
Realized I forgot
So now unfortunately.
Unfortunately I have some bad news.
What's up
Debit
Bright lights in Elizabeth
I hope it's not okay
First of all
If you are going to do a nuclear First Strike if you pick
Austin first
You have no idea where anybody in America
Well if you
Carsmart
Okay you know
First of course
Cuz you're the only one
Is the head of patriot
You understand
He's the bellwether
As goes Alex Jones so goes the nation
Very first words worth
They reserve the right to First Strike
Can you just do that
Mom
Reserve the right like you don't call the restaurant advance
If you
I'm going to
Signal that I'm going to take
The first Reich
Wouldn't you surprise people
Unabomber
What are you talkin about
Oh yeah
Some 2,000
Do you got in a little bit
He's a yeah
Yeah
Missile fan never asked myself out more
Reserve the right for
Strike and then this other voice
And he's like
I hope those five missiles are coming towards
Yeah
He is God
Gorgeous
A little bit later
Okay
The Narrative it takes over and sort of
Of course
Clinton said he would absorb the first
We will
He's not the he's not
Or he's not just some guy jumping on a grenade
This is unconventional but I propose we have a cigarette
Let's do this
Concentrate
So Focus that you were about to light up cigarettes
You know I do hope this conversation
Smoke
A part of it is that
We got a long
Okay
Smoking with you got them
It's my way of family
Smoking
Suggest teenagers
Reynolds and George Soro
This is a little bit of explanation of what he was talking about with those five
Protocol time we appreciate
Who tells us that they're currently missiles being launched
What's going on
Cheyenne Mountain
Five nickels at Willow Lawn
He wouldn't say where they were about that
Nichols at 1
Our general is out in front of our tryan Mountain tell me all this
They were going or whatever coming from
We're going through what kind of meclizine you could I can't give out that information
First of all I want to say this
Some pretty important
Information to give out
Absolutely
I think
Information because I don't
Nowell
I feel like it
If there was a history book that did
Have
I think that is
Probably a mass
An actual news
And we'll get to why I believe
There was a news report
And a bunch of people misinterpreted
But I mean
The reason I wasn't
The reason I wanted to take a pause was because I wanted to give
The co-host
Two props
But I'm going to give him
I don't know who he is I don't know his name
But he
I like that
Galax
I like the idea of him being like
Itsfunneh
Cuz it sounds like he's
Contesting the story
Hey we didn't hear about that
Maybe and then he's like tell us more
Almost invalidating
He's close to it because he's like funny didn't hear about that
But
He got a message
In his ear
Your
Pissing off all
Gcy
Capitulate
We can't trust the American people or that information
Cooperating
I've always felt that way starting back in grade school and I totally forgot to hide underneath the Jeff
Because of our friends over there
So
They they spin out there a little
Cuz they get this
Skip this news
Trump Anonymous caller
First at the shop
Colorado
We're the only guy who has
What is he have that is like
I can
Text
Blacksmith
CNN
Oh okay I thought you talked about the general refused to be named
The end the reporter
And the first
Call Vishal
To tell them
Right so he got
Which as we all know is how radio shows work
That he just pulls up and get the direct line
What's imagine he is
They're actually screwing
Screening calls
And if they are then
Uno
I got missile news
You're getting to the front why
We got we got missile news
We get this call
From another
I got a boy
Verifying with the fellas
Cheyenne Mountain
Colorado Springs
Easy that you can create
Edgar all the time
I love the first of all the co-host
You suck up evolved
Heard something
And I love the idea that
Did I can't visit
Point in Infowars history
Cohoes
F****** bus Alex
I love that
Wonderwall
Is no longer with us
Movie deal
Vladimir the Ripper
So
We got a caller who's in
Camp
Well that's what we start to realize to is that all of these callers Longview colors
Are coming
From
Camps weird
Patriot
Melissa Folk
If you will
They are they are a History Channel special waiting to happen
Once we're out of the woods
He's got a TV
Yeah that he has
ABC
Why not watch the mainstream media even if you don't believe them
Does is this still back when there are only four channels I don't remember 99
Well in a little bit
EVS comes up in a very positive
Finish out this sort of weird
Narrative of the missiles
Switch
We don't know where they're fired from or where they're going.
I love Alex Jones responding to the news
You haven't been this whole time it's time to get serious
You dick
Let's kill a human
Yeah
This is
Another caller
An organization that
Where Duncan Mark Courtney Conifer Michigan
Did have a commander who came up and online for the state command
Specifically talking about
Space command
I got to pull this back a little bit
Bass
Command space command
On the moon right he believes it's on the moon
No no
Space command
NORAD guy
It's like either like yeah
From Galaxy Quest Tony Shalhoub came on the news
The god
Ariel
X-Man
Specifically talking about
Yep Alex Jones is reporting
Lightly armored vehicles
All of the
Meanwhile we can't forget that ATMs are running out of money all over the world without in Austin
How would you know the running out of money all over the world
Because I was
Are there ATMs
There are ATMs all over the world
I feel like that was the most ignorant thing I've ever
I feel like I'm the only existence
Presented as
This is dumb because ATMs don't exist in Europe
Or something like that
That moment was like
Really
There's ATMs in Uganda in 1999 play me not
Pixar widespread release for my brain before I allowed it
Everything
So this is a guy who's in a militia
Space command
Now we're in Star Trek 2
Yep we have insignias
Heat and so just by wearing a patch
Lake Anna look like
Space command is
Very Lacks
Security unworried about terrorism 9/11
What is the name of my second rap album
Kick my own ass
For making album name
That's so happy I'm I apologize
3911 space command
That's a great
Collection of words really what I meant
Easy just like
Borderline
Masturbation so that the militia member Rambles on for a little bit but
The Weeknd
We can blend in
We look just like these
These guys if you were
So he's combining Red Dawn with they live
Yeah
Space command
Pretty tough I want to engage with everything else he said
How did space command come about
Okay
You able to Google space command you're not going to get something
Other than
These North America
Can Aerospace
Defense come
What do they do
I'm looking this up on Wikipedia here
Space command in Colorado Springs
Oh my God or we're not
It's not cold space
What is closer if it was real
It would totally be shortened
If you want it's like the Affordable Care Act
Yeah you know what let's be in
Entirely Fair
Yeah
Silly name but it is what you were we are 100% wrong on this ladies and gentlemen
We're not a hundred
Wrong in making fun of
We're not even wrong
Complete disbelief
Our our head
Was going towards this guy thought it was on the moon like Moonraker
So yeah
But I mean of the North American Aerospace defense
Command is just NORAD
So NORAD
Slang term for that would be
Space command
Okay now 100% right
We're in the middle
If we're if we're going to be anti Alex Jones
When were wrong
And then need to bounce back
Fitbit that we are actually write all the
I'm okay with that
Because history has borne out
And second of all
Placemats didn't take over everything
See there that if you know what
How can we be sure
I guess we can't you know
To see the Arkansas
Transportation on the road and sources are telling us that
These people
Might have signed my girlfriend
Know someone
Still doesn't believe me
Nope she was
Alright
At every point
Not on board
She has a friend who told her about signs
Now she's on board
Anyways every weather
Exactly what this clip is but it's scary
Things up
Here in a second with and
An explanation of
Why you do
Carolyn
Gilton and Jen commands quotes
The dictator of China in there
Are there
Three weeks ago they're ahead of other missile forces
Q Park
Eternity is plunging a dollar in Japanese yen
Market on the
Just all of it it's just
And the America
Gas stations here in Austin have the little
Gloves over the pumps or singer Atif you'll never see this in Austin Texas
Buy here in South Austin I see several stations
We don't know this is just that Y2K that was here
Not sure what that means also was here like at the store
Brimstone
A call
Okay
Alright okay
Bizarre behavior American standing up as Russia threatened to attack us with nuclear weapons
As we were power plants
At least water being shut down
Stop
And the military runs around with the police and the FBI Chang terrorism is eminence
Han
Someone characterized us is dangerous because we report the facts
Absolutely
Out of control
How fuckingawsome is that last
Absolute
Out of
How f****** amazing is it
Just cuz we were poor thing
Facts
Although
Time ago
Yeah okay
China and Russia have reserved the right
First Strike us
With nuclear war
Tricom
Let's leave that as being an insane
Like why would they do that
Does he ever give an explanation for why they would
Why they would do this why do stripers because no
Not be a first strike
If they
Didn't have a reason for it
But their only reason is
Clinton has already said that
The first strike
Okay whatever
Alright p**** communist
Clinton is willing to not destroy the world yet
They now know that they can
REI
So even though even then right
So that the first strike
It's not like
Are you working with
Because I am
Call Matthew Broderick role in your war games
Using I'm red.
Wolverine
I'm shocked that at some point
Cuz this is all straight out of
A lot of it is basically the like
This is what we're doing to other countries ironic like born in the u.s.a.
F****** Jordan
Get your war games
Because of our nature
So much
Understand how they do it
Perfect male virility pills
Have you tried
It's super male Vitality now available
About infowarsstore.com
Alright
So because Clinton
Supposed
And their currency is dropped
Which okay
Pound and the Japanese Yen
But those are neither of the two countries
So-so
They're going to first strike
Maybe a rogue actress point
And they take out
Justice
Does he not understand the mutually assured destruction
Places then we have no capability
I think we thought
You think that we put all of our missiles in d.c. I'm a little bit red wine drunk
And I'm confident that we've always thought
I'm a hundred percent sure pretty sure only only the only New York
Only our largest population Center
Have nuclear
I don't even
Think that they have them
The other places
Do you want to put that
See that's what you're missing
Alright all of China's nuclear weapons are in Beijing
Okay weapons are in Moscow
That is where you build
But then what
You can move them
Station the mother places
Right I mean
Oh
Not occur to me
Or either
OSHA
Somehow
You have outsmarted
I don't know what's going on right now
All right you might be asked
And yourself
A little bit
This is the problem with this app
Episode
At no point does anybody breakdown after the five missiles
No no no you know what they do do
Never
Get to the bottom of
There's never a point where they're like
Is bulshit sorry about that nothing
Move Along
Move on to the next thing to be really afraid of
Being the
Like today in so if there are there saying you know like
The apocalypse is coming because of Y2
Make you afraid of Y2K
Really
It's all
No because
It's all about the globalist
2K bug-eyed
Idea in order to push the
Their agenda
And create false flag
Okay now you might be asking
Can yourself
Would love to be asked
Why
Are we finding all of these
Truths all these
Power plant
All these people dying in Chester
People dying
All of the
The five missiles
The gas being out everywhere
Are the five senses the water being off the shelf
Everywhere
The power grid going down various
Places
The shortwave radio going
The North Pole why doesn't everyone know
I want to know why everybody
Relegated to the Backpage
We worship
Out of control
Not on Fox News I showed the old airport Robert Mueller right the middle of town
Montego Bay airport
Mac Show
Barbed wire fence side of the hangers Michael and Shackles On The Ground concrete
Give me the ground
3000 years ago
Texas in their defense
Slavery
This
Clip is amazing
Because it's basically
But then we got on that
To be the main point
Does seem to be the main
No we got to talk about this airport Hangar again
Also
But only in Austin
Philly flights
See the garbage
Reflect
Better Sun worshippers
That would be
What is that what is that even
Close to a reference to solar power or is that just a dude nothing like Illuminati
Every
Also by the way
If you guys
Want some fun
Look into
Like the real story of Alex Jones breaking
The
Bohemian
It's amazing
He broke into the beach
I do I do know about the Bohemian Grove
The Bohemia
This is how he came into
That's how we got on
He broke into Bohemian Grove and videotape
The Cremation
Pierce Arrow
Which is where they sacrifice a baby
Do the giant Stone owl Mala
Alright
And
Kia
So he caught
On tape Yaya
Yeah there's this documentary about it you can watch
I can't believe it's not in the mainstream
In Austin
Cuz he least like to watch there
Bright
Bohemian Grove
It's weird
But it's not anything that's a damn if you watch the actual video
Bucked up
They're they're like
They're talking to a giant owl
That has one
Walter Cronkite voice coming out of it
Recorded the
Be vocal
Formalogy life science Stone out also recorded the vocals on Young Thug
The great album my name is
You can hear Walter Cronkite on the back of Pop man with Wyclef Jean
That's what Molly
Things to do before we go
The Y2K bug
If I understood correctly
When it happen
The entire thing was that
Our computer system
Didn't
Stan had to go
To the 2,000
Yeah right I was literally everything
Okay
Never ever once fear was that once
I became
Two instead of one
Our computers weren't built to handle that
And because of that all of our systems would crash
Yeah you'd have like Wall Street Computers crash
Everything that ran everything crashed
Aqua deck go out
So that was the big fear
Okay
Everyone everyone Warehouse film
Yeah how is it that we're having Y2K problems
Before
The switchover on the clock
What you mean by that
I mean having all these problems
On all of these
All the planes are in the sky
But it's not
It's like this isn't
Exactly at
Right it's
To figure out
Here's what I would say
If I were Alex Jones
My defense would be
The globalist
Floppy
An hour early
Grateful is a timezone
See that's what I was was my whole life
When Y2K was happen
And everybody was panicked about it
I was like
Guys do you know we're not
Yeah and I think that would be
A real reasonable thirteen-year-old
Meanwhile we had a
30 year old
In Austin
I mean look we've heard
This is about where
We're going to jump off
You guys get
A pretty
Here's my summary
First of all
Looking at as a performer
I have to assume Alex
Really you think so
I have to assume because he had to know that everything he was saying was
Verifiably false
That is not a bad
Fair enough
I'm applying my own standards to measuring a bad set by
The truth that's your measuring the set
Because you retarded you started with the dirt by the audience's reaction
Love you started with the presumption that he was a journalist
I
Do not agree
Ivan Ivan idylis Bill O'Reilly
Entertainer
Yeah he's doing is entertaining
His audience
Nailed it
Yeah probably that was the greatest set of his life
The night Obama was elected
Rockton
Like he could have been a Madison Square Garden with nothing but the militias
An absolutely
Smells like
Sulphur
The clips that we've shown
Come to a bunch more than we played
It's all just repetition
I think that the indications
Instead we should all take away from this
Learn is that
I want to give the benefit
Alex Jones is a terrible
Terrible
Person
Because
He sits on the air when he knows that people are scared
Any help somebody scare
He takes
Unverified reports
From Anonymous callers
And treats them like they're real
Doesn't treat them like they're
From an anonymous caller
From 2008
That's fair enough and we'll do another podcast about them in the future
From this episode
Here's what I
Our first episode we went with
Deck
Whenever we recorded it was that day
This is
17 years
It is the same
Bulshit
Yep
However long we've been doing this
He has come at you with the say he's like an apocalypse help like you remember the those guys in
Super specific
Friend who saw.
Eclipse called that exist
Throughout this
Men when they're wrong
Half of them
Probably kill themselves
But the other half
Just keep
Predicting more apocalypse find new news that change
Angel eggs
We were going through the whole Kabbalah thing the Bible told us git Outta transversive
Variable
My specializations he's a religious studies
Professor specialization
This revelation
Apocalypse
Literature and so whenever there are
These people come out
Resetting the end of the world is next week and also
People who are closeted
Whatever they come out
Whatever these folks
Tell the world that next week everyone's gay
I mixed it all up there but
Happens over and over again and he'll be
Asked to comment about it on like NPR in
He existed because I was
A scared child
During some of that there were apocalypse cares but I was always there to be
You're 10
I can't really explain to you
I'm thanking God because
It comforted me in a way that
If my dad was Alex Jones
He would have
Erik McCoy
Amazing be
Because that's a guy who's
Turn rational like
For my parents
You know they lived during just like that
You do to school and they would show you the
The day after
Scariest movie at the
Set timer
And then we got Nightmare on Elm
And they were told to get
So good delicious as as a concept of like
It doesn't get more pacifying
Little bit of wood
The walls
Garbage
That little desk
F******
Destructive
The other
Piece of it
That was what I was
The other piece of it is
If your
Adult and you really believe that a new could go off tomorrow
Telling kids to get under a desk is the right
Because
There's nothing they can do
And giving them some sort of agency
Make the kids feel like they have control
And that is very helpful to a kid
In terms of parenting that's the right thing to do.
There were better answer
But I mean
Listen
I'm glad that you got this message
Across the idea that
For 17 years
It's pretty much been the same thing
But the variables have changed
The good guy went before he was so terrible
The illusion of him
Growing as
Broadcast
Is that
The boogeyman always
They have to
You feel like
He is also still relevant
Yeah even though he
He's using the
Same exact
Like he might as well have a
Script
With madlib
Send whatever's new a 17 years he's been doing that exact same thing of like
This person told me
Both
Very like a Verbatim to parks
Again
If like I said on the last episode
It's
Amazing Frog
If you look at if you take the morality out of it it's
Gorgeous Broad
Andis Supra
A propaganda
Propagandistic a****** so congratulations on that Alex
With another episode
Soon
Alex should be back in studio I guess
I mean he's not going to be gone until the inauguration that's insane
Well who knows how they might
Recording this
This is going to come out on Monday but I if I get to work
Today on Monday
And there's a f****** guest house
Livid because
Clearly right now
The only thing worse
Then the Alex Jones Show
Is the Alex Jones Show without Alex
A dumpster
Starfire
Anyway
We will eventually do an episode on
Sooner or later
Yeah we do be good to use on all of the
But
This is been the most fun of my
I hope
Your your two
I am already terrible
Be there are plugs in the middle
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work