Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Podcast
Blistery start hazard
I'm Jordan
Discuss Alex Jones
Pictures of Chubby Checker level twist I watch tons of Infowars
I know a lot about Alex Jones
And I don't know God damn
Where we find our fun
But you know realities of life
Happened and we didn't promise you s***
Ale-8
Nobody would have even said
It's a good
We're finally getting an episode instead you like suck you
I think I project
Getting a little bit of anger at myself not because we didn't get
But because I listened to the
Show I listen to Alex Jones
The entire week
For what feels like nothing
It was a very fruitless Quest
That makes me very angry
Play hours of Zelda and did not end up freezing an elephant
It's a great I've heard nothing
Single positive reviews about
I don't have a girlfriend
Breath of the Wild
Record
News about the show
A video game review show
Really quick
Decent man all the sudden
That level of pivot
Get warmed up
So I have a couple of out of
Clips
Alex Jones from the area
Is all of last week
March 6th through 10th
But I reserve the right to go back to that time. More specifically later
Okay because the only reason it's basically Monday through Wednesdays or recovering but we have to go to Friday in order
Interrupting
Man what the heck
Alright
Here's the big enchilada
Butler auto contract drop
I've noticed
Here's the thing I've noticed that
He is now a
Best with the
Expressions the big
Enchilada
So much
I could make a Mastiff
Supercut
Over a couple days
But I just have a second
The Big Kahuna
No it's not even related to each other
They're just both big
Gelato
Motor enchiladas
Kahuna
Spider-Man GTA
What is the
The Big Kahuna is like it's a Hawaiian thing
Super cool dude man
It's not like a an official title
So it's not like
The humuhumunukunukuapua'a
Anyway
He said it was relish
Some clips on March
Fixed that's Monday
If you're nasty
What goes on on this app
Alex is still in a holding pattern at the
He is still like
The oldest bad news is coming out about Russia all of these things
The news hasn't broken at this point
The point
General Flynn has
Turkey as well files
That's great
Papa John's
You side of things
Clippers how he decides to
To start the show off
Very dishonor
Is a good example of victim card playing
When that is
Three weeks ago and general Flynn resigned
He doesn't develop this in this clip the visit
Basically
Hanging right
Priebus out to dry
Not a bad idea
To go to people and tell them that they quit
Edit the president has told them
And then they go in
I think the news is that true
Telfar
And everybody else around him
Guys being
Trump
This is f****** insane don't do this anymore absorbed
Kobor likely story than the story of rain
Priebus sneakily going around
The trick people into resigning
To what end
I think to become the president
President of the 4th president United States
Inaugurated three months
After we've gone through
Somehow we're going to be
Cool with him
How many present
In a row do you impeach before you just like
Now we're done with this whole America
Here's the good news
Easier as they go along
If you get used to it
It's like a it's like committing a burglary
The first one
Incredibly difficult
You got it down
Maybe like
Impeachtrump we get through
Pence in about a week and a half
Buy Congo
Like they just murder him on the floor after Scherzer
Remember Celeste
Just go with
The devil
I'm assuming
The oldest person
No the president pro tempore is the oldest traditional
To the oldest
Remember this
Angel
F******
What's the Strom Thurmond was fourth in line to become president
4 years
Oh that makes sense from Thurman who is wondered why that was
McKay's
Because he was a well-known social
Rainbow snatch
Fun in the park
No he's hating on the
Amen
You got priebus
So then it gets more into like how this exact same thing basically happened
Recession
But didn't
On Saturday was that President Trump was absolutely infuriated
That he had not
Everyday everyday.
It's in the news everyday
If you put it in the newspaper you're just doing dog bites man all over again
Always.
Trump is mad is taken as read across the board
Went over
We can't take weeks off
In future, slightly off and I think we can both feel
Yeah are you getting to the white wine is what
We always drink red wine or champagne
And I think this white wine is f****** us up
Okay
Anyway
Was that
The reason the Trump is really mad
Is because
Sessions
Kim
About resigning
Which is
Not the role of the Attorney General
Like that
Ethically
To the president
It was like hey hey bro
Do you want me to recuse myself
Yeah that's
Incredibly unethical
Of course
So he's mad because you didn't get to consult
Even though the Attorney General's office
Executive branch
The president are
Separate
Close
For now
Declarative
Himself also the Attorney General
Over the weekend
The new
Trump is dictator for life all of these headlines I can
Can believe anything is possible except for Alex telling
Ridiculous
Jeff sessions recuse himself
He's very clear he was at Watkins talking to them at start again
A drug has the headline
When you calling in for the day one
Again we agree that those blocks of water about all of this
I wouldn't told the reports yesterday and especially
You watched it
Sunday show
The Articles from a month ago
Wiretap
Organization
Tracking phone calls out of Trump Tower
General flange and Russian ambassador
What's the
None of them
Call the President Putin
Exactly zero of that happen
Yeah 100
Happened in that was accurate
It's a disgrace to the definite article
The parts of it that are kind of
Accurate
Representative
Wiretap Trump
We already got distracted from
And everybody be like
Tactic
He's he's jingling keys in front of the press and they're like
That's what he's doing everybody
That we all babies up and miss
My God I think I think we're we're getting off track here
Playful
I think is white wine is bringing out any unnecessary playfulness
But it's out of my knowledge fight carrot
I think I think you're just
Really
Struggling to divorce yourself from the Zelda
Are still wandering about like
Oh look that's beautiful I saved an elephant said open is really cool
Everything is Everything is faking what are you saying
He's going to
Make some other false equivalence
Is about this exact same stuff later
But one of the things he doesn't understand is
What you talkin
Which
Blake Alex Jones
Doesn't understand what he's talking about
The movie
The headlock
When was taken
Game calls
The set up meetings for Trump
To talk to them directly about
But the media twist
And said they were talking about sex
The reports from intelligence
Communities
You straight talk about sex even then
The wiretap their talk
Sing about Loosely I think there
Their bases
For this story
Is that there was a server that was connected to
Trump founded
Schenectady
Alfa-bank and that was 80% of its traffic
Just going back and forth
Emailed
Birthday like
Does Snapchat
Yeah it's specifically setup to be secret
Yeah exactly
Private server
Used
Illicit business
What if they have
That we don't have
Who's the president
Three weeks into Trump's goddamn presidency to find this bull
Let's speculate
Have really good spam
That's why you had to set up a separate
Server
What is what's a really good spam email
It's just
Hunziker
Giving him a lot of money and he's
Great deals
Real ass memes
And the other thing is that Alex
Conflate
The wiretap stuff
With
What
Asserted and that is that Obama did
And that is not true at all
Oklahoma
That but that's why I think
Right-thinking people are upset
People think like
Lying about being wiretapped
People were looking into stuff
For good reason
Did I
Instigating him for s***
He says
People
No one really is saying that
Wildly inappropriate that he's like
Obama
That's the part that people are f*****
That's it
The thing about that is that
Obama in
A boogeyman
That now you can basically
Of course
Done
As as human beings they're done
The checked out you can just say Obama did anything
Leaves
And of course Trump with it because that's
What's the type of thing
King Trump has
Has like in Trump's mind if somebody was challenging him for the president
He liked well of course you wiretap them of course
Exactly
I think he believes that
Complete
Because he read it
Yeah well
Is another problem that will come up
But
They were all over the news
Obama
Again again he's applying to the transcript
The night they are
They are not
Last week before all this latest wiretapping bro
New York intelligence
Here he's implying that they gave the in
Information to the media to
Through government agency
She's right classification as well as much as possible
So the fairies
Could share information
Executive orders did Obama sign the information that prove that Trump was
Presidents
Every all just agreed on that yet
Converses
If you want if you want
Step back
In like not say something that inflammatory you can just
The Chinese
Grant
Isn't
Definition
One sentence of
The Constitution
Says
Don't do that it might as well have
Parentheses
Thomas Jeff
Person in the March
By the way we can see the future in this is Donald Trump
Predicting the future
And nobody is f****** all of the second
Amendment bulshit of like
F****** window
Just did our first
Brennan and Clapper and all The Usual Suspects
On TV today
Preposterous
The truck says
His transition team was under surveillance and of course. It was found where do you think President Trump got that
Breitbart
Elizabeth
Bored
Nunez
Nothing they're not even phone calls
Errol Flynn is in there supposedly for the president
Social Security advisor
Winding up his phone calls with world leaders
Oh okay
This is just become unbelievable
So like
This clip looks really bad
A week later
It looks real bad now
Really frustrates me about the whole wire
Bulshit
Is that
Trump
As president
Could you
Declassify the evidence that he was being wiretapped
A hundred percent
If there was ever
That's a total Trump
Is it somebody told him how you can Declassified this these people will be under
Indictment
Tomorrow
And that's something that you should do the globalist
Are we moving again and frankly I would do that if I would drop out
I would support
It's almost like if there was some sort of shadowy agency infiltrating the
We would want to get rid of it
Even if it wasn't from Russia
Question in 10 Spicer's press
Lady asked
So
The proof why is he asking Congress to investigate just provide the
Heather was Noah
Of course not
Scattered is a
Weasel of the Hyatt
Yeah
Clipped
From his
At the end of the week
When he was talking
Jobs report
Dan Howell Trump
Like
That's terrifying
From the Prescott
Because
It's like there in one big room where everybody knows everybody's lying to each other
Anniversary
There's nothing we can do
Like to actually be
It is it is pretty funny
That he's just caught in a bald-faced lie and just double down
Haha like we're f******
Yeah and we're not even bothering to lie about
He's out of
Almost
That's the comic side of right
Performance
Cackle like a witch
Battle B2
Domino's bumbling
Meditite
But
That goes on to cite
About
Attention span
And how everyone in the world is stupid
I am in Tilton more lies about you
Do you think he gets
Distracted
Halfway through the attempt
In Spanish
Movie 3/4
Because he's not like he's not a lemming
It's not at 9
Dumb piece of s*** low-information liberal
All the time
Actually pay attention to those really goes on and government and a note was released
Are so stupid
I don't have a 7 second
Have less than goldfish
Neither of those goldfish
Famously
Have a five-second
Memory span except
That's a lie
They don't
Junk science
The fair in this in this
Okay the study I looked into it
Goldfish
Is what they say
They say it
The truth is
Studies on children
Attention span used to be like 12 seconds and it's gone down to eight
Since the Advent of
Handheld
Phone
You can use the internet on
Made it expands go down
The same study cited that
A byproduct
Also
Is it our ability to both
C task is gone up dramatically
Ratso there is a
Kind of
You have to do when your obvious bulshit all the time
Celebrity culture stuff
Liars from Alex
You have to not
Thanks for very long
Goodyear
Move on to the next thing that grabs your attention
So that is
Kind of just
The neuro flexibility of human
In the meantime
Because we move on from things really quick were able to juggle more balls
I think it's a fair trade-off
In terms of our brain
You know I have no idea whether or not there's a valuable
Conclusion to draw from
From any of that
Certainly not the related to
Whatever
What's going on there
Further
I don't think it would be possible that anyone could have
Plan
Smartphones out
It's going to take
33%
Are 25% off people's attention span
What about somebody
F****** dementia
Did you report it
Demons you're right
They're doing it all simultaneously
I always forget about the dementia
You got to remember
Either TV volume
Hypotenuse
Do not believe or remember that a month ago it was on every TV channel
Every News Channel every newspaper everywhere that they had surveilled Trump and Slimline
Talked about
With the Russian ambassador
Release the transcript
I'm sure you can bring that up with me
Did you decide
Line up a discussion about them absolutely real government
And in-wall they trained everybody who answer exactly as their ass because
They don't want a bunch of obfuscation
Which is why you like sex
Trouble in the first place
He answered
Exactly as he
Wasn't asked
No that's
That's right
Al Franken a question
Anybody have contact
No we've been over this a hundred times
Alex Jones quote
He doesn't understand
It's so f****** frustrating auto quotes
What about even though he just said basically the same thing
INR last clip
Is because
I wanted to illustrate a little bit the repetitiveness
Rats and how
You just says the same things over and over again that part through
To your mind if you're not paying attention
Oh yeah I guess that you know
When did get set up I guess sessions was a state
Lawyer lie Quest
Mayweather
Not
A question he wasn't
And answered it poorly
Cuz he was
Nervous cuz he was
Because
Is a
Colluding
Terrified if I was in front of the Senate
And I was up to some s***
Which again is another reason to respect Hillary all the
Cuz she lied for like twelve straight hours
Versace had that level of a
No way
Stone Cold
Yeah great
It's so great in the same Obama
It's time to just move on from Hillary
We have a lot of Evans
Hey it is someone is like
My schedule
If you're in the NSA email note
Letters to the editor
Text Alex isn't the first
The two instances where
Sorta gets into
Talking to Trump on the phone
He gets into
Again he's inability to understand nuance
And the
Between different kinds of meetings
The politicians
Incredibly embarrassing
Calls
Another new listings
And look up
Where they said that they had all these communications out of Trump Tower
That's really good advice for like the guy in memento
If you don't have a memory
Go back and check the new movie that would be if the internet was around
Holyshit cell phone
Advanced technology helps everybody
Really lucky
Specific time history
Movie though
Like it
There wasn't anything there
It was Sophie
Call Celine
Whatever I forget the number
World leaders and royalty and Business Leaders all day but you're on the list is your Lester's
We're so awesome
For their support this big Windward
I don't know if
True or not
It seems plausible based on what we know and yet it's
The same time
Equally as possible that he just
Decided to make that up
It is possible you're right but then on the other hand we also know that Alex is a liar
Oh no to Alex
Is that just toss the ball up in the air
Is punt on a cold beer made out of happen
It's not as important
Is what Alex
Says his response
To that is
Call me back I want to call you and call and royalty
But I had call you cuz you listeners are awesome
Here is what Alex's response
Nice call
I would say
If it did happen that's a really nice guy
Scott it's misguided as f***
Call
I would have I would have preferred if it were me and I were propaganda I would have preferred a letter with the present
You could put that on
Tell your grandkids about you know what
Swim in the water
Which group is worse
It's probably proof
Oh s***
Oh s*** I have to be exactly
On the phone with Russia everything is recorded
So here's Alex's restore unless you're deleting
Typos and f******
Open Twitter
I want sure they are going to come after you they're never going to stop by now he's going to get both prosperity and
Got to go after you got to get on the offense because they're going to come after you
You wouldn't even say like how are you doing
What shoes are coming for you
Need your bones
What's Superfly Nisbet
Because he's clunky with language
It kind of makes it sound like his listeners are going to come for a pronoun
Iraq
Canada our private conversation
But he doesn't heat the ultra-high
Yes
The president just wants to turn the car back on and that's why hire Road
He doesn't want hurt small businesses the average person so
Beaches
So that's actually just Alex literally verbatim
Dropping
Trump
Like the idea that he could sit back and watch Obamacare and plug
Just want to do that to people
Is directly out of
He did say that
Yeah
Just hit
The weirdest thing
Listen to this
This is that
And it's like
Absolutely
Steps
Towards even
Pretending to make the middle classes life better
None
No no small businesses are improved
Well
Nothing if you are 0 positive
Things that he's done for the very people Alex Jones doesn't exist
Are the only people he cares
If you listen to Alex
He does site
Ad nauseam
That the stock market is
Going up
Middle-class or poor people
Because you don't have
Stop
All those stocks are businesses that are able to
Employee people
The stock market goes up those businesses are doing better
That helps the Common Man
It's duck
I'm sorry every time somebody says trickle-down I just
I have a stroke
Flames
I don't think that's the last time you're going to barking this episode
And he's been dumb
The entire
What they just keep the money and he's like
Shut up boy
You you know that they would because history number one and they already ever ever hear about it
You would do probably
I know I'd wiretap Obama that's for damn sure had a couple times like Bank errors and a
Accidentally given me like 20 extra bucks
Good business is a dick
Okay so the other thing
Is that
He constantly talks about
The small business
Confidence index
And stuff like that people are more optimistic than ever before
Which
I don't know about
I literally don't know about
Little liberal bubbles but
I mean
I'm trying to read all the
Conservative news that I
They are not
Optimistic
PetSmart conservative news
Really Optimus
Super
Breitbart
Yeah they're doing a lot better
Let's get back into this
We're going to get to the point
Right here where we talked about the
He's meeting
He just doesn't understand the difference between like we talked about
People having public and private
Understand that at all
Everything going on
Morning
And
Trump is so good
Sick to my stomach
Again he only uses those ref
Because he has that clip of them
Yeah
Petty
Stupid
Yeah and it's proof that he doesn't have
If he has anything he wouldn't have to keep going back to Maxine Waters saying
Premier
It is one of those thing
Things that by rep
Petition he's created a
It created like a
So we can always go back to
To that area
Yeah
Reenact
All over again and then that kind of like
Pavlovian response
Yeah Liberals are dumb
Have to take forever to rebuild itself
It's that really stupid
Very bad
Effective
Clearly
I would like to see
What's coming up at the end of this episode
We have a return of Eddie Bravo episodes
So get excited for that
We never met with Russian Ambassador and they're just photo after photo of Schumer and Pelosi
Public
Brazil and Mexico are powerful yeah they are there people aren't there
Going on
Yes there are
I don't just
Fat at all
People
What's heads-of-state
In official capacity
Do you think that he
I mean I'm not sure if he understands
Is the difference in a
Purpose
Because to him it seems like
A meetings a meeting
Read whatever on the record off the Record you're doing it's still a meeting so does
Mater yeah
If he were to say you know what I bet other people have had off-the-record meetings with
Before
I would actually be inclined to believe
Surprise me
You know Schumer
Can't say that
F***
I've got to do some investigative journalism
I can't do it
But he was at
Actually prove a point
And if you say that though
Purposefully lying
About not knowing
The different type
He says you know it's Alyssa
The record
That also mean
It's Alyssa that
When did these meetings Austin
That's a really good point to
Not under
Understand
Romantic fascinator
Send it
He has to not understand
The only the only way to be safe
Is being really dumb
S*** parents is
If I'm not
I think that where we go next
Is equipped
Bees v 7
His come out
On wikileak
When this happened
He just becomes a new man
You know how when he lost Google
He became a totally different person
Nna Petty
Money-grubbing
Kind of way
Vault 7
And stuff comes out
Is like
A weight is lifted from his shoulders
And he believes that he's been proven right
About everything
Throughout his entire life
Everything that you set on air is totally true
And that means that everything he's going to say
Is going to be true until the truth
And it gets into this like a cult leader getting the Apocalypse
The look on his face
12 year olds
Dammit
Yeah
There's a little bit of that
But that's a that's a pitch for a TV show
The cult leader whose accidentally always right accidental leader
Yeah
So get this clip Alex tells a little bit
The story of his past
That's why this is an intriguing question
Directions with Nazi police officer
After is about
Him as a broadcaster
And I don't think
I really really really don't
Can't stress enough
Bulshit
All right I think it's time to go
Directions
Also I just realized I think we're technically in his eyes globalist
I could
I'm going to do voice over for that movie
I just
Because we're
Is is anime
Philosophically and ideologically we would obviously
Clearly have to be in the employ of the global
I think that is the only way that's the only conclusion
I'm not
That's the reason that they got me I'm here to watch you
Was minion this keep an eye on
What if you go full-on Apocalypse Now
Oh no
Diesel mechanic
I can assure you that I've I've gone this far down the path
I'm pretty face
I don't think there's any
It's going to happen to miss about thesaurus
Looking
I say hi
Horses
Dysfunctional
You have been undermined for decades and the Patriots inside our government others have been quiet
Absolutely complete
Not your overthrow
But your lips
Because you can't overthrow something
Remote control in all the airplanes for at least 25 years
Remote control your car right off of bridge
Ago
The television set for watching and listening
Your regular smartphone
Whatever one like the only one saying that s***
George Orwell
It granted
He is
A lot of that stuff I think even he surprised that he was right
If you take out all of the stuff
Come true that was
Paranoid bulshit
And only cherry pick
These examples
If you're paranoid about everything you're going to be right a couple times paranoid doesn't mean they're not
Republic
Like a lot of these things were public
It's not that
Describe what things are public people could hack into your computer
Camera
Technology have been aware of and had been warning
Not like Alex Jones cracked the case
Anything like that
And I don't think he would even say that
You did
Maybe
Only thought about looking
Looking for it because he told them
Cuz he had
The globalist information
People were globalism
Woke them
With his knowledge
I read bill.
This stuff is really hard for us
To deal with I believe
Because
It is a point where I know you well enough to know
Hollister
But Technologies pretty scare
It's very a lot of the stuff that they can do with technology is really really scary
Against these things
The ability to
Computers
Philosophical
We shouldn't
Like its
Could be abused
Terribly
Some sort of autocratic president
Slipping grip on Power Inn
That would be really
Fascinating of all the sudden we start
Movies leaks on every politician
Aries with him
There's got to be stuff
Right
The problem
The problem with the you know what Snowden revealed about the wide net
That they're doing where they're just saving
All of these
Is that it doesn't help
To stop terrorism
There's too much noise
You know you can't find the signal
It does help if you are looking
You know you have all this information
Time to go digging through
Preventative
Play so if you want to release them if
Like you could
Is there have a secret
You can put that out there immediately there discredited or whatever
All of the new Wikileaks dump because it's
Yeah
Literally no way Alex could have
By the neck
Day on air
He might be a literate
Yeah there's no way you could skim a couple headline
Here and there would seem to be his motive
But there's no way he can have a nuanced understanding of what's in there what is actually being revealed
And he just
In the time since then
Assessments and Analysis
By people who were in
Like information
And basically
The dump that happened
Is dangerous
Because
Does illustrate a lot of tools that are at the disposal
Of the CIA and other intelligence agency
Does not indicate in any way that these
These things were used
On citizen
Didn't know I mean
No
It doesn't point if there is no smoke
You get you get a chance to play with
You know like even if it's not been used maliciously from a government
CIA dude has seen your naked
Right it has
It doesn't matter
You know it I know it dudes are awful
It happened
It's probable
I have to I'll give you that much
It's likely
But
It's not what Alex
She says
Proved killed Michael Hastings by running
Okay
Which is better
They're going to need a little bit more than
Just short of saying like the Malaysian plane
So f******
Far on this and that everybody's
TV is listening to them
It's like
Like in that book
1954's paranoid fantasies
There's a slight confirmation that these tools in the back doors are available to people in intelligent
Using that in
Information
Is confirmation of his paranoid fan
He's been having for years
And also they haven't had it for as long as
Find me the back doors
They have an iOS
And those
You know those have been around for that
And they will be around for longer at all
Which is the
For all the weird and awful WikiLeaks
They did this time
Like say
Hey we're not going to publish all of the weight
To get into the iOS
Send the Android operating
So they can closes
Oh they did
Oh that's great they haven't done it they are going to
But they're going to wait until Apple and Android closes
Okay
Cuz that would be a data reader is hacker tool
Purposefully found these
And ask
Them to stay in there
And not reveal them
Is the most dangerous
Yeah I guess
If you're in the government
That helps you in a certain way but that also mean
They exist
Yeah and somebody will find them and it's there
Exist for a reason the only reason for that is to bypass your privacy
Insecurities
Is it
The small point
In which we agree without
All the rest of it
Why is it
I don't know
It seems inconsistent I want to know apparently there's my paranoid fantasy at huh
Beating up that like
Trump is already dropped more bombs
An Obama did in a year
Perfect
Play some America
Yep he's already gone golfing more time
That Obama did it in any year Melania cost
Some ridiculous that like Fifty like half a million dollars at goddamn day
Million a week of every single American is paying for her to
Her husband
Well that's bad
That's the part where we get into fantasy narrative
We don't know if it's
Because she hates
Trough
It seems like there's no other
The only other explanation errands got to go to school matter
Blame her for that day I just realized that we still haven't gotten to the point where Alex Telles
All the lying about his
Unpack that Wikileaks thing a little bit and I'm glad without calling Julian Assange a Russian agent
We told you everything
And because Patriots inside the different agencies
Was
Adopt
Not official
As a place to dump information
The
The technical head
What the tech
I don't know if you means
Head of Technology
Like we're going to get into one of them later
Pieczenik
CIA
He was like a psychiatrist psychiatrist Within
I don't know but he's crazy
Yeah
Nut
These people who Alex gets on
Some of them to have
The history of the servicemen what-have-you
But they lost it
Yeah or or they never had it which is
Is even scarier
Equally possible Street Preacher crazy
They've they've got it
Together enough
They can tell a story
Like how did Buzz Aldrin insist that there were people on mars or something like that
Yeah
That's the beginning of
Is
The Milton everything right because the military
Unofficially decided
We know we can trust Alex Jones
To disseminate this information because no one's going to
Conspiracy theory community
Is that he's being trick
Intelligence
They give him one corrected for
Piece of information in for lies
It's basically so they're just playing a game
Is to discredit Alley
Essentially
Has the truth
Okay it's stupid
Stupid
Stupid dumb people are out Dumb and Dumber
What you just described
More or less
But it's
Clay Madsen
We've been absolutely On Target
Never about them
Never ever listen
To him
Just once I wanted to be like
Hey give us some credit this is pretty good
Censored stuff
Cuz we just here every every clip it's like
Look I know we're amazed
It's possibility I know I'm right all the time but I don't want
He's big into the false humility game but then he's also big into the I'm being victimized
Which are very difficult games
Play simultaneous
Cuz if you play victim game it's I'm awesome and someone else is holding me back
Breakpoint
It's very difficult
What is $1
Set an alarm visual groups
In the defense department in defense intelligence
In the CIA in the NSA
And the geospatial group in all of them
This guy's young he's wild but he's done the research and has horses
He's dead on this is the voice of America
Lego shows
He just described Point Break
Is wild
Utah The Voice of America.
Unless maybe go with Lethal Weapon
He's Mel Gibson in Lethal Weapon
The military
Alex Jones
What do you mean
Play football
How much water in Texas
He was an undercover
Golden State Warriors
That's true it's family is here
Cheese's
This isn't it
I miss Mortenson Postino got calls they're like yeah we got ordered
12 years ago
All the fucken what
They got ordered to listen to Alex
It's an order
You think it's been the same thing like SEAL Team Six
The same guys for the past 12 years
You can fly goddamn helicopter like a motherfuker
He always keeps
Feet dry
Bridges important country
Infowars
You don't even listen to Infowars
I do
So there is that
That's right I got my marching orders from himself
Disc
That's what that's what George Soros
Sounds like
His glass still more convinced
Alex Jones
Anyway you still haven't gotten
Come to the death
We resisted we stood up
Infowars Is On Target
Trump
About that
It's amazing I can't believe intelligence Community loves you so much
Set alarm for 20 years
Wow yeah I'm just going to learn about all this
The two thing the intelligence community that trunks hates loves Alex so much
Will trump
Just surprised by
Narrative
Elgin Stadium
Community Bank
Right
The chicken neck sorry
Pencil pushing chicken necks
With their American flag
Absolutely
They do not like
Is a liar
The end is that like
He says that in his phone calls with Trump
I'm just starting to learn about these things
Which undercuts The Narrative that he's been in Americana Sleeper Cell
Since he was 20
Well he's just starting to learn about the real death
Save the globe
Confirm the same
Playbook
But Alex was getting the information straight from the end
You may be right
Trump is just been being the good man you know it
Great man
Information he would be compromised
That's a good point
Also I don't have a clip of this but there's a point where Alex goes into the story about getting
So like classified document
When he was younger
Like The Neverending Story like he goes into a library and find
Magical
The way he says he got there with some guy pulled up in a car and gave it to it
You can get we got to burn these without my dad
Regis Burnham
They're trying to set you up with
What does classified information
You're going to go down
So they burned the dock
Well I see
That's even
Because the only way to really get rid of those.
Is to boil them downright
Silver filling
We all know that how do you get rid of a body
Turn it into filling
Everybody knows
Turn it into non-fluoride toothpaste dentist
That's just his cover
Anyway
You want to know Trump's work ballast right
Mocontrol planes
I know this
Engineers in Austin at work very well
It's a good thing they were very wealthy
Say that way we know we
We love the rich
Thanks for pointing that out
But also the other idea there if you really unpack what he saying is like
Have no proof of it
This should work
It's not journalism
Lucked out
You hit some sort of lottery I don't believe the store
In the realm of a believing the story the story is unbelievable
If it's true just
It's not good good life
College
There's no wind
But it's so delightful
Like
Of kind of boring subdued Alex
This kind of thing is
Is delicious it's just such a nice
Oasis
Bill Clinton ordered people to surveil me he ordered from our Intel people to beat me up
Breaking my house URL
The decision was made
Persecuted me up front and then what the hell are we doing
Real
That we at least 15 16 years
Hardcore
He's got on this is the program
Google read
Books and you go read Bertrand Russell book and you go read a book
170 years old most of a 67 years old 30-40 years old
I just read all the books
WhatsApp
They're not they're trying to act cool
I did it
You are I love how I love how it goes immediately from
Community was
Tell listen to me because I'm
Only one who's the greatest
Broadcaster in history
To tell you how great I am
False humility you guys know
This is
The delusions of grandeur
Within that
Credible
We're getting to like
Talking over that cliff
He doesn't say what
It's all in there
You haven't read these books
What's in the books
Just been reading the globalist book
140 years old
Is he then
Saying that the
Technology
Watch 3
More less the plans
JK Rowling
Where you can just wave your hand with
Yeah
We have also put a really fine point
So
Making the point that he's done the research
You studied these things and he's right about everything
It's by the grace
God that
We've consistently
Shown that he doesn't know
About the
Is basically Alex Jones
Can't read right
I've read all these books
I don't trust your ability to read those books
I don't I don't listen to him
I don't want to read these books
To be honest
So I'm not going to go to review
Take the new running
Think of debugging Alex I got Zelda to play I guarantee it
They wouldn't
Very humbly
Trump
What
And no they can't
The news
Trump's Russian
False flag
What
At the claims and they were fake
Anime world the whole thing up
He's saying that in WikiLeaks
The CIA
Specifically points out that they have the
Tools
False flag Russian operator
Nations against Trump
No
Well no not really
Showed is the
CIA does have like
Russian origin malware
Confiscated or found
Russia has some of our
He then makes the leap to all of this stuff is what was used for the Russian hacking
Which is absolutely not true
There are good
Resources
Don't fully understand
But I understand enough
These malware things that are in the WikiLeaks
Or not.
Specific one
Better the code
Booze found
Proven by these WikiLeaks
Is that not true
The bigger issue
Is the Alex
Having presented himself as someone who talks
The Trump on the phone
This little bit where is a water released this stuff
Which
Why Trump released through Wiki
A little bit
Oh man
Because the globalist won't leave him alone
Now if that's
And we do know that Flynn communicated with guccifer
Rodger Stone
That's right so stop for knowledge for knowledge's
I mean
Because we're using the term sort of loosely I want to make it clear that we don't think WikiLeaks
There's a separation of
They get the information
A very strange
Power structure
The hierarchy there is pretty I just noticed that we were saying WikiLeaks
I want to leave it
They just get it and throw it out there
Soapstone has connections
Knows in advance
Is coming
Yeah there's one connection
There
Because
What was his defense there that it was just like what everybody
Lucifer
And that also was a benign conversation
9 conversation can you have
He went on Alex's or Rogers.
Stone does not have
Have any
No sir
Or talkin
You know he has a tattoo of Nixon space on his back
That's not true I refuse to I don't want to live in this
This world
You just
You just proved that there is no point in
Is any of us
Notorious liar and a republican dirty trickster for like the last
Aboveboard is just
Spreadable Luna
Anybody who is word is
The f****** idiot
But we do know
He has these contacts
Text with Ricky Lee
Guccifer
2.0
It's not
I don't know what it was
It maybe it was just information digging or something like that
But still f***** up phone know what it was
Someone does someone have
Why can't we just get
Everything points
Possible conclusion
Yeah
It's all a weird system of
What happened
Like everybody's
So it's either there's collusion there
Or it's like a drawing-room far swear everybody
Then they come out of a different door and they look at each other like I didn't know you were there and
Is it a 23 company
Basically or it's like murder on the Orient
Express everybody killed
New exactly everybody on this train independently killed this guy
There's multiple endings
Dumb people
Have to have enough information
By this
There's no
Possible way there isn't enough information
To go one way or the other
Rodger Stone might be closed
To getting a real Polonia
Poisoning
I will
Isaac he's in danger
The ambassador's dying
Yeah
A witch even then
We could have just died
Possible they're all connected to the CIA
Circle together this year
What does parole hold most reasonable thing
Somebody knows and we don't
Just f******
To me right now this is
Seems like Chinese water torture where everyday there's just
Just another little drip
Another drip
Like I just want them to blow up the world or leave you just wish that the Band-Aid
Will get pulled off
Nuclear war
We're heading towards.
Disclosure
Reader
Anyway
During this time
In specific Alex Jones has that about Trump
Suggested it
Is there outright said Trump will tell us about aliens
What
Wasn't the first
Where is like
The first thing I would ask is
Where are the air
Galaxy more interested in for very overt about you going to give us immortality
I don't know about that Alex does want to live forever
Speaking of Rogan
It's time for a smile
Strfkr reapportion at the show
Alex's when going into overdrive
In terms of bookings
Who are
Celebrity in nature
Anything's
To distract he has some military faucon who carry in their commitment to
It wasn't just because he
Is president
Felt very weird
He's had
A string of Celebrity Guess
Week he started the week
Peggy had Eddie Bravo in
Studio
Which
And then also at the end of the week
He had you've been teasing this for
The entire week
Jesse James
Motorcycle impresario and former reality TV star
Nazi
I avoid celebrity everything
As much as
I can't believe it he's a Nazi
But it doesn't look good
He was wearing a Nazi hat
Two fingers over his like top lip indicating sort of like a Hitler mustache
That was released
Which is just isn't that I think I do remember that one cuz the internet got
We're going to be mean to him for a day until we ignore him again
That proves anything
Pictures all the time
Especially Rich entitled
Now here's my question
Covid-19
Let's number one
Don't you have enough
Number two
This is my other piece of evidence that I think Jesse James was a Nazi
His business is called West Coast Choppers
Okay and their original logo was very similar to the Nazi Iron Cross
Almost identical
He then
A couple years later his logo
It was basically
It's just that bird
Celery cause that new logo the warbird
Which is like that
It's not proof but man it doesn't look good
Now
It's a coincidence
Another piece of cake
A boy after he got divorced
From Sandra Bullock
He started messing around with this lady named Michelle Bombshell McGee
Who is Abed of a Nazi
Sandra Bullock
Yeah that's crazy I don't know
She divorced him and adopted African American babies
I don't know so this lady Michelle McGee
Right
Has a tattoo
On her her leg
On the back of her
WP
Which is
Notorious
Circles
Has claimed
I mean
I go with either one of those she was quoted as saying Jesse and I had a conversation about it and he says he'll walk
What are his friends have the tattoo
A wet p**** World wipe
Doesn't look good, like my friends have white power tattoos
Then
Another piece of evidence that Michelle Bombshell McGee
Maggie is a Nazi on Facebook
She's listed
Minecraft is her favorite book
Mike
Although that would be
I feel like it's
I've read not the entirety of mine, but I've read a bit of
It's not for the literature
It's not a well-written
Yeah the only thing to take away from it is
Hatred of the Jews
Yeah that's really the only
You know I've been
In the past to read it
And everytime I was like nah
I don't think there's any reason
Much like me going back and reading these globalist
Life Is Life is
Almost over now so glad
Now that I know I only have 5 years left
Husband said that she had child white power
Deez Nuts
Then
Jesse James a Nazi
Was formerly married to
To Janine London Mueller
Who's who's on the cover of the Blink-182 album
They're f****** dumbass title names
Divorce
And then she got remarried to a guy named Jeremy Aikman
Who's a multiple-time felon and
Yep
Jeff angles
Revoke Linden Mueller's custody of
The child
Janine had together
Average 28 minutes evidence of negative environments for children
That's a good
All of these
Look dead to rights
Proven
But if you're hanging around with that many enough
Not good
I don't think I don't think that necessarily Jesse James
Is
Himself
An actual Nazi
He's not not about because it is
Not the 90
He's not so he's not a reasonable person
Because if I were around
Become
Very reasonable while being on Alex Jones
The show and height comparison
Seems like a kind of chill
Comes up pretty decent to
But like
He he does do one thing
Amazing
That is he tells Alex repeat
Deleted stop being a sore winner
Which I think is
Great
And it really disrupt Alex Alex's got
Since we've since we've been around
Because he's Jesse James
Inotorious real man
A celebrity
Al pastor kisses ass
Right because he's a store
So
It really throws off the interview and
By the time
He does
Tell Alex to stop being a sore winner
It just bike
Alex
Get his bearings
And he ends up just what kind of car
Image of gestation in the first place
B v narrative
Show though
Jesse James and then we will get to the real fun
Which is
The Adventures of Eddie Bravo
But this one actually Jessie
Isn't it
It's just
Alex Lyon
Real heart
That didn't happen
Reagan Metro
Trump Poland trumped into younger
There's a picture of them shaking hands
I thought I was meeting the present
Cuz he was such a powerful presence
He never said
No
I did some research on it attracted
Alex is quoting a meme
Oh
Okay for you to say Alex was quoting Alex
Cuz that seems very much
His moves
This before in the past like it is I think he keeps bringing up
That is no basis in reality just showed up in a meme
Except that it's true the same way 3 million undocumented immigrants
Voted
In the last election
I love
You just
Proceed definitive evidence of someone
Making s*** up not doing the research
Not understanding what he's reading
It would take a 20-second Google search
Define the origin of that
It's so easy
The only thing that strange and we'd even surprise you is the Reagan
Yeah like that is weird
Because it's so weird and there's a
Picture of it
That's why
So this clip is a little bit longer but I'm going to cut it off
In the middle
Instead
Make the meme about when
The clintons
Hanging out with Trump
It's like Hillary 20 years ago
Methylpred
Reagan's death
Reagan is dead
So you can lie in Contra but it
Well I mean
In his later years
He can walk
I want to point this out last week Donald Trump
Did tweet
About how Russia has run over America and put run over in quote
This is incredible
Because that's Alex Jones Lang
He talks about powerful people running over
Weaker
That's specifically
Donald Trump
Using Alex Jones Lang
I mean it is it is in the popular consciousness
I don't know
I don't have to say it all the time
So because Trump doesn't know where
Costco
Not at all
Correctly at all
He starts out
This clip really dumb
And then gets really aggressive about protest
Russian Russian hacker Russia hack our election
What
Alex
Fix that like the idea is that
The Russian Hack memes that no one voted
Stupid that's not what anybody thinks
Million reasons
Notably hate Hillary Clinton they have a documented history of him really not liking her
And her being tough on them in terms of section
Election I would if I could hack
I probably would
I know I'd leave a trail I wouldn't
Did I stick of things I'm good at like three elephants from the land of Hyrule
Russian robot
I don't have anything really to come on here to talk to you about it's really.
Special I think
I like to come on here
Just as a voice of The blue-collar Americans
See James American worth a hundred million dollars
Married to Sandra Bullock Award winner
Nazi stripper
Hey
We can't yet prove that Sandra Bullock herself is not enough
T-strap that's a fair point
I don't want
If we broke
Sandra Bullock
The Northeast
Stripper Chicago
Give us information
Anyway
Like I did
I get what you saying about being blue collar
He has these outward
Appearing blue collar
Hundred f****** million dollars
Is probably worth way more than
Really you know why he has all that money West Coast Choppers is incredibly successful
It's a huge motorcycle
And
They don't really get into this on the show
Has NRA branded shirt
And clothing wear
Like Target
And stuff like that
What do you make snow
Billions of dollars selling NRA closed
It was murder weapon
I don't know
Because they're Nazis
Nazis really do know how to do their guns
They also talked about these allegations
Videos of Nazi
At some point in his life
Like everyone says all this ugly s***
That's because there's ugly
Yeah like if you didn't
A Nazi stripper girlfriend
We're banging around
Stripper is
Is a negative part of this at all
Cut the stripper part that makes an interest
I think the stripper and Nazi girlfriend still works
And me being in the media narrative going from Sandra Bullock
To a stripper is
Compelling
I agree we shouldn't Sandra Bullock
She is
Just interesting I feel
I really could be a lateral move
Our investigation
And then like all these other connection
Since the Nazis your iconography being Nazi An Origin like
You can't be mad that
People started drawing
In the same way that like this whole thing that was Trump being investigated you can't be mad about that
German last names
And your grandfather has a lot of Nazi memorabilia
If they're filling
Maybe he's just really fascinated by WWII memorabilia or maybe
And maybe it's worth looking into
Exact
The difference really matter
Hitting your grandfather up on
International Court
Get him into a nerve
Nuremberg trials
People that think that you know because I'm filthy dirty everyday and because I work
Mechanic
They think I'm an idiot
You think about the majority
Modern history
Build your own business
Alex keeps trying to get promos on blah blah
Put it in the
He's very resistant to a to his credit
He's getting he's getting to work and he's going about his business
Why did you yell at everybody all the time Alex
Think that he's an idiot
No
I mean I don't think he's a genius
In the same in the same way and I know this
Is a weird equivalents to make
It's the same way where people think the Kardashians
Tumi
I mean maybe that's
Maybe
But also they turned
Not
Being able to have
Skills
Into the most profitable skill you can have
They did make this whole weird Empire they're not they're not stupid or there
A Machiavellian leader
Like a mom
Could be incredibly smart and everyone's going along for the ride I don't know point is
You can't be an idiot
Create
Something that huge
I mean you can
It's very okay
Play an idiot
So the fact that they present themselves as
Is dumb
Is kind of almost an indication that they're not that dumb
I think you're getting a little bit too far down the rabbit hole
George
The w
You know he could be
This brilliant Mastermind
A dumb idiot with a great
Pedigree
I think he's like Jesse James
He's probably
Diversion of The Middle
You know like I think that the reason the George W bush seems dumb is because we're used to
Smart
Well spoken
Articulate
What are the traits of a smart
4 of a
Right
Positive traits
He looked
I looked dumb and comparison to our image of president but he wasn't that dumb
No I I think
Probably don't
He looks dumb because
Of images we have in our head
He looks
For so many reasons
Not just images we have in our head
He's not.
Don't let him get to you
A decade
For the people
That's not in the
That's not an every single newspaper
Because he is
Thousands on thousands of Articles ethical Point red
My argument doesn't
He's just about assassination
I'm sick of this crap
I'm not pissed about those people I think it's funny I think it's funny that they ourselves up into a big dizzy
Over
Working Class People working
He's working hard for them
Hootie the Blowfish
Yeah I was about to as about 2
Lesbia sore winner
There's nothing worse than a sore winner
I'm just pointing out
That's what these people do
They like
You know
Never got to do the man we have the best
Protection the best Elite and it's
The same thing it's a trunk full of ping pong balls
The only
What's a metaphor
That's not going to add anything to your car hurt your car
It's just nothing
It says that doesn't do anything
People tweeting threats
It's not great
It makes sense to the point he's trying to make
I like his perspective
Doesn't like
These are assholes
People who are threatening to assassinate the president or saying he should die
Shocking
RN positions where they actually could
Yeah
I definitely wouldn't vocalize any of my inner thoughts
Publix podcast
Covid-19
Mascot to a collision in the streets
According to our laws
I'm not saying I agree
Play hang'em industry
To the cons
Institution
And the laws we have
It is well within our legal rights to hang
Disagree but I also don't agree for safety sake
Glitter coming out on Twitter
And saying like they're only doing that to give themselves a little bit of Fame
The little bit of like oh my God
Its meaning
It's it's
It doesn't mean anything
You know what I'm saying
Hundred percent agree
Are the false reality mean
Duran Duran 18 hours
Programming every day on all trumps
Accomplishments
And everything he's done in the first 50 days and all that
Twitter account
Scream of Billy 218
Investigative journalism
I doubt that if you Google something it will appear
But they got the number wrong
He said Billy 328 Maple up to 18
So that
You know what I'm going to give them a path I think we're going to give him an a for effort there they do Google something good
Time Forever
But if they ran because it's not
If you shut your phone off and your computer off so all that stuff
So you just ignore all the trip
I'd like to see I was hyper connected to it
Before the election and now that we won
I can sit back and like I know I have my friend
Working in hot working his ass off in the White House
People like me
And people that think like me and I know it's the first time
Find it really
Cared about the little guy the guy game
I totally agree that statement
I don't know
I don't have to worry about it anymore
Interesting Jesse James
Just stats
You sounded like the most
Brilliant person absolutely
Is rambling
Rage
Like just
Just
Lexus coming out of his mouth
Jesse James
He sounds completely reasonable for the most part
Dog whistle
Like we don't have to worry about it
Stuff
There's there are
We don't have
To worry about something that rhymes
Really long time
It's not
Woodrow Wilson
You're right
There's no indication
Like this
It holds water at all that the president's haven't
Cared about
For people in the middle
No investors
There's like a lot of evidence that
Well I mean maybe the last
Cared about the poor in the middle class
Carrot is a whole different story
That's true
He's an interesting
In case study
Okay
Look up Billy 328
Interesting
Didn't take that long at all
And they were all Twitter eggs
Course
And they were the same thing they have like
No they don't follow anybody and they have
3 followers Max
It is it reminds me of that
There was an article
About how
They're these Russians
Twitter Bots
Yeah even Russian
That are lying dormant
Still kind of mixer
Topix
And put them into the Nash
Consciousness
And those
Works
Suspicious in there
Update
Just exist
Nothing going on there super f***** up there's like
Number but it was a it was a
Chinle high percentage of Twitter's total accounts
Cambridge analytica
Video
Which we don't want to talk about
To get to our main man
Again
Seems like a really good hard dude
Also seems very dumb
But like he comes in
I could not help but smile
Sing Eddie Bravo in the Infowars Studio
It's great you watch the show every day you're on Bravo
The highwomen
But it goes south really fast
Let me start talking about
Accidentally walks backwards
And stumble straight into an addition of
You're busted
So there also exists starts by them talking about that Ted Gunderson
Apparently
FBI guy
May or may not have been
Ted Gunderson
I would poison him. It's like out of the bad
No I poisoned him because that name exists
It's like that it's like a name you'd see in a script
Where do I will come back on
Poison poison three other people
And he was in the FBI for 27 years he was in California
Yes
I am ahead of California
Also I f****** love that like I'm not allowed to talk about this with a poison three more people
Willie got a lot to talk about it's classified information
David three more people just got poison
But do you know what's crazy
That's always
Every
This is a truth
Statistic
Three people at Alex princess
Three more people have been accidental poisoning
Overdoses
Impossible not to
For Alex to say things
Would be
I can't get into the details
But
And then
Say a generalized broad statement
As opposed to
I can't talk about this but I'm saying the exact same thing
That's portfolios of Ted Gunderson former FBI chief
Gigantic pedophile ring is going on
A national origin International
White supremacist
Liquor store you got hit in the head with a gun you got to shoot somebody
Those are rituals
Yeah I'm your boss
Cheerleader
From from The Godfather from
Uno's movies all movies or whatever
The Godfather Mario Puzo
Mafia life at all
So even
Even Alex Jones is fake stores was also lying
Three levels deep on lies
Reporting it as reflecting reality is
Nonesuch
That's enough
To show you feel somebody that got dirt on
You got
Took you got to hurt it
That's going to be another contest
And I'm not just talk about mollusca
Pause levels
Baby blue
Build-A-Bear
Machine
Alex Jones
Pacific engineering
Requirements
Someone's at the door
You're busted
What he's talking about there
Came across
Conspiracy blog
The only way he could have ever come across this information
Yes I'm first in order to get their adrenaline level
You could just do that with
I mean like
Time run
You don't have to terrorize an abuser
Like
We're going to see who can run the fastest
So
Don't know more questions
To some random ass pedophile
Hypothetical Supply wrench
Let's sit down
Rework this whole plan
On the conspiracy boards
Narrative came up to explain pizzagate
Andy's
Organization
Is the
Then kill them and drink their blood
Because the adrenaline
Is it's called adrenochrome
Will it been released in
Made-up nonsense word is that it is a real thing adrenochrome adrenochrome
Molecular formulas 989 no.3
Paul Simon wrote a song about
It's produced by the oxidation of adrenaline
The derivatives and who cares
Wacky and
Information about
Chemistry that we're not going to be able to
Oxidization of adrenaline
Perception by Elvis as a
A product
Decomposition of
Produced many of the symptoms of
Also author Hunter restaurant
Mentions of his book Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas
Being also appears in the novel spill mat
It's reference
Fiction a bit
Hallucinogen
Liars
Journalist
He made shut up
The first thing I want to point out is that this is there any evidence
Done
Adrenochrome
I get to it
The first
Ibanez
There are
Pizzagate researchers
Who just
Throw whatever they can at the wall and see what sticks
And one of the things that came out with was
A completely unsubstantiated
Unverified unsourced Theory
About adrenochrome
Being what
The killing of the kids was all about
It was because
Adrenochrome if you've never done drugs
You might think
Did it creates
Crazy hallucinogenic euphoric state
And it sounds like it might
Cuz if it's something that you could only get by drinking
Can kids blood
Then it seems like a great High
Really good now has a couple problem
Otherwise you can just like
Coke
Sure illegal
Still illegal like you could just do what you don't even have to do a pedophile ring
Anthony wearing your bone
Theories are widely discredited
I can't imagine how people in the pizzagate world
Don't look at this as a salad
First
Because it is
I love
That you hate that
Name for the segment so that's why I'm going to keep it a lot
When Alex was talking about pizzagate on The Joe Rogan show he brought up like vampirism
And stuff like that
Literal vampire vampire
These guys are drinking adrenochrome
Through the Wire
I don't think that there is a machine that allows you to
Alright so
You got
You got the kid
Terrorized
He's alright
Haha you put them on the machine what it what are we
If we're going to entertain this Siri what kind of Machinery talking about
Is it going to look like an MRI machine
I'm picturing you being like that the
Clockwork Orange
OKC I saw it like the Spanish Inquisition
Back right
It creates more surface area
Eliza
And then you
Slowly drained
Blood
You probably would have to do is ask
So now you got all what you would not have gotten unless the kid were terrified
That makes sense
You could just go in and get their f****** adrenal glands
You got to get it from the blood
Or take an Epi shot
Or just watch the movie Pulp Fiction
They have adrenaline and here's the deal
They made it up in the truck
Adrenaline can be synthesized
Otherwise
Is then
Exact same chemical compound
In different ways
Much cheaper do donuts kill kids
So we're reducing the number of children
Jim Kelly
There is a lot of websites
Where people do trip reports
Where they take substances and then they report back on what the experience
Thank God for the
Sure
Are universally
This is not a good Buzz
Not that it's a bad but if you didn't know that
The effects are so mild
Do you not
Really even know that you're
You wouldn't know that you take
Substance
You couldn't be dosed with
So
It's it
So there's really no
If you don't if you couldn't know there was a high if
You didn't
No you are high
Junior highers smoking
Oregano
Basically yeah there's a psychosomatic High to it
I looked at was taking a low dose
You know maybe that's
Maybe he only took a quarter of a kid when you need to take
You need to take
You know it's like with Edibles to make sure you get the dosage right and everyone is different
He's a really hard to scare
Next
Going to really cut into your time
You don't want to get one of these brakes
Get a bad Buzz
So
That you want to get a Really Brave kid cuz that a video game is drinks out of my computer crashed and I lost
The the word document that I had that had all these calculations but I'll redo it
I've just going to be a little bit vague with the numbers
Specific
I found the amount of
Adrenochrome your body can produce
You're at your maximum level that didn't
You can't just
Create
Child
10 year old as sort of a myth
A midline
The amount that a 10 year old child
Create in their body
Is
Like the equivalent of nothing
Basically
All of his blood
I meant take me to drive to crawl out of it
You would need
To kill I think
300 kids
In order to get enough
For that bad Buzz
Did that guy on the trip
No wonder they needed an entire
Pizza restaurants
You got to get
They needed at least two or three Chuck-E-Cheeses operating at the same time in Oregon
Can we just stop it
Think for just one moment how's the real this entire f****** conversation is right now
Thought I would get to a point where somebody told me exactly how much a
Adrenochrome
The weirdest f****** thing and this is how crazy the times are right now I was lifting
Like 10 minutes
Let's see how this goes
We living in a
Same world where that's the least crazy
Crazy thing I've heard today so that's why it's important that we Embrace this craziness and just like
Follow you down the rabbit hole what how much
Blood
Easy to get really horrified and shocked because
If children is a real thing
It's horrible
To be like
This is awful
Looking at
The perspective that I'm coming from
Is
They're not drinking
Visiting app
And all these blogs for pitching this as a rationalization
10-4 it's like no one
Ditl
The very idea
The in order to
To get a week
Mild bad Buzz
You need to kill 300 kid
Make this
This
Stupidest f****** thing
In the world
Alright
Globalist
Have been around according to Alex
They have evolved
Separately from
The human race
In order to process adrenochrome
Arab mud
Efficient
Rate
Sure
Okay great okay
Your body
Is there
Found
Science
If you're speculating had an alien race I think so
He really does believe that
And the idea of it being a metaphorical psychic vampire
Thing he can't he can't fall back on that would be to drink
Contained in one person let alone 300
And no
I can't imagine that that's not a thing I can imagine cuz I don't even know I don't want
Did you drink a glass
Ipecac type quality
If you end up throwing up
The very least it would bum me out real heart
Yep so that is
Uno
Great and Brazeau was able to pull that out of him I really appreciate that
Bravo
Realized
How stupid would Alex Wassabi
Cuz he doesn't call him out
Realizes how stupid what
Yeah
Eddie
Is going to be a
Hero
I love Eddie Bravo as The Accidental Hero of every one of these people
Anytime Eddie Bravo shows up he's like
He's like mr. Magoo
Eddie Bravo is to be like he's blind
I'm stumbling around and just
Just makes it through just fine also a little known fact
We're not allowed to give you this on Facebook
Nazi stripper it's dead you pulled the right you got
Ultima Google
I got bus
We're not allowed to give you this on Facebook
Chop
No because cuz we told you 12 years ago they
Watching
It's because we're on target
He had a couple things on Facebook
I'm not sure
Details of it could be a false flag things getting erased like he did it to himself
I don't know
But
He's using it as like a really harsh example of censorship
I have the details emerge
You know as is
V
Of what he say
They're saying
That they're censoring us because we're Liars end
Fake truth is there's no
Now you get back to how we talk to Trump
Isn't the president United States is called regular people
Nobody takes
To get back to this
He f******
Loses
His train of thought so hard
Why couldn't you just asset the heads of state
That's ridiculous
Don't
Want
To review
Something
I guess
I don't know
It's ridiculous
It's absolutely ridiculous
Not as ridiculous as next clip
Where
Eddie Bravo
Bravo
What are you doing
That's on your cycle
Are we late
Alex wants
To talk about something and Eddie brings up a topic
The clearly Alex
That's a family that have been in
And whatever heard was
Drugs that kill people you don't want to join
But
A Delta Force years ago
They would come in and order them listen info
I'm saying
Confirm
And and and that's just a fact
Pizza Patron
Ociaa
Overthrow government
He said all the next month are going to release you tomorrow the CIA to
Discipline
He's talking about Steve
Pieczenik I brought up earlier you do the guy who comes on Alex's show
Some put some regularity
Wasn't
Director of the CIA
He was the technical hat
Steve pieczenik was a psychologist psychiatrist Within
He's also
Source of the
Counter-coup narrative
About how Rogue CIA agents
Running is silent
Peaceful
Against Hillary Clinton
And then
Now they're trying to run the counter
Yes got that information
Steve pieczenik
This is where are you
Is about to show some
Real Valley
Early settlement
Dr. Steve pieczenik totally legit right
Italian newspapers
On your show
Stead
No
Kids died at Sandy Hook it was a Homeland Security drill that they passed on
Bravo at 8
The thing is that if anybody else were to bring this up
Alex
Because he's a strfkr
He is like
The other
Yes you can
Yelp
But that's that that's the most
Cowardly a conspiracy theorist argument
Where the other
Anderson Cooper
What are the Worcester
Well let me let me
He's talking about recovering
Sandy Hook stop
And it does appear that his
But
Their theory is that it's green screen
Reduce the news
Because his nose is green
I don't know I've done
Some looking into it
Defined
Arguments for why
Anythink
Media space
Everything is fake
I work
Video production
And that could just be
It's called like a p frame rate
Little technical glitches that
It's not evidence
A blue screen
I got so
Stupid and you should not use that as evidence
The kids weren't killed at Sandy Hook
Very lame
You can't you can prove it
When were the other
There's one way to prove it
And listening to people's stories
Boat
Jesus f******
Question about Sandra questions why weren't the
Medevac helicopter call
Operation
Paw Patrol
That's not what we're not at all answering just completely cuz he doesn't want to talk about
Country rock
And he even though
Now he's got a back down on
So many other little things
He's a better strategist that are f****** president
Because that's the same thing that
Happened with Flynn
They got one
Now they're going to go after me
Blood and water
Me to to just avoid instead of
Admit that he's wrong
Anything
Then he can keep on going and what are the things that super interesting
Keep track of and watch is the
The times that I exchanged
Subject
Like that
There is not like
Oh I just realized it Steve pieczenik
Helped overthrow
Right he wants to get off this topic as quickly as possible
And not draw attention
Right
Of course not
Intero Tom Clancy's books
Here's a big secret by the CIA
Man there like for Special Forces
Are there Army Navy Marine Corps
Animation Squad
Locations around the country
Sleeper Cell
And so that's basically what goes on but do they really have a assassins are doctors
The Navy or the army
Cars
We're back to Batman
Yeah we're back
You get
L.ron Hubbard
What is goddamn happen
What kind of
What
Dr. Fortune
Is the basis for Jack Ryan in covert action
Any possibility we don't have time to unpack
It's such a side issue
He's that good I'm already
Forgetting about Sandy Hook
Anyway
Snitching a little bit
He's telling tales about the CIA
They have overthrown at least seven or eight
Before we get out of here I'm just going to talk about one of them
Play the last one
Set up with
It's f****** Pope
Because he claims that the pope said muslim terrorism.
Exist
He goes back to this a lot and I've actually pulled up the the speech that that's from
Actually really great
It's actually beautiful
Full sentimental the pope was make
Here's a quote
The Pope
The other
Reflection that I shared it on most recent World meeting a popular movement
I feel it is important to say again
No people is Criminal
And no religion
Terrorist
Christian terrorism does not exist
Jewish terrorism does not exist
Terrorism
They do not exist
No people is criminal or drug trafficking
Or violence
He was actually saying that the identification
Smart for him to say because then he never has to deal with
Ireland
He goes on to say
The grave danger is to disown our neighbor
When we do so we deny their humanity and our own Humanity without realize
We deny ourselves
And we deny the most important
Commandments of Jesus
Herein lies the danger
The dehumanization
But here we also find an opportunity
That the light of the love of neighbor May illuminate the Earth with its stunning brightness
Like a light
V in the dark
It may wake us up and let true Humanity burst through with authentic resistance
Resilience
Beautiful
Claiming that there isn't
There aren't people who are Muslims who do terrorism
That's not the point
Anyway here's the last clip
This is Bravo
Tell you that
Okay
Along with Eddy's in-studio appearance
They also posted
Hour long video
Of him at dinner
With Owen Shroyer
Annie and Owen Shroyer
At dinner
Do that for an hour
It's just crazy but let's go
Because you're too humble
Go do an hour interview airplane with one of the great reporters ha so we can actually hear any Bravo on shame
Eddie Bravo
Does what they want
And so they do
They go to dinner
I was going to make a Supercut of all of the stupid s*** that they talk about
But I couldn't
They talk about Flat Earth
There's a nice wall
That's
There's something on the other side of this
He know what it is
And we take it over there
Because I have to come over here
F****** retarded
I apologize
Also he says that nuclear weapons aren't real
Dinosaurs are fake
Did you know
The every dinosaur bone at museums
That doesn't mean they're all replicas
I wanted to make a Supercut
Hear that
Stupid blogs
I'm sure
Anyway
This clip that I did pull
Really something
What does underlie all
Research
Cuz I didn't look into it
Yeah so
They're well done Eddie
The entire Alex Jones
Still well you said it
Look into intellectually offenses
Just told f******
The guy who doesn't
Try
Because
If you fail
And you don't try you just know I didn't try
Imogene
My college career
30 problems like
It's probably true
I didn't look into it
All you do is take away any like
Semblance of State personal responsibility whatsoever
Through Alex Jones
Little bit
Episode
Soon I think
Maybe more into
What we do next time ladies and gentlemen
Absolutely you can follow us on Twitter
Knowledge underscore fight you can look at
We appreciate it
Just anybody
Please email us
Knowledge fight at gmail
And we will have a form
Just
Which will say do you like us
Yes or no
Also no interest in these shirts
I think if the interest is implied
If you want
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work