Alexandra Thurston color
Look up a little bit
Dan
What's the what's the deepest
I've been in the Marianas Trench
Chalmette
I got deep like I don't need that I don't need that in my life
Referencing
My favorite part of your electromagnetic
A great album that I loved before I realized
I realized
My favorite part of your references just how relevant
I've been there I kicked the shark once and I wasn't
Swimming around
He's like a little shark.
Call sharks
I kicked it
Steer the ship
Yeah
How do you make a reference
Legacy of blood
What method
Visions
Gandhi was another one
Servants in heaven Kings
Horrible monsters
Late 90s hip-hop was really homophobic
I never grew out of it
Ikon the verbal hologram
It's cool I didn't know that
. I'm not a
Keep up with Odd Future Wolf Gang Kill
I'm telling you are sweatshirt man
I heard that album is good
I saw some
Jordans
To some new folks who joined up in
First
Benjamin
Congratulations
I'm a policy wonk
I'd also like to give us the world
Thank you so much Daniel
I'm a policy wonk
Figured
Every music now is going to be Jedi
Yeah I know I heard it but I needed you to
Direct
Forever
Spread the word about the show enough
So much Heather you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Heather
Satellites to have you onboard although you would have been for a long time
I know
So she's at the very least
For so long
I don't know like now it's like
It's good that you joined the policy was which apparently has an entrance fee
Under the bumper up to a technocrat
Someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean black
Jesus Christ
Three days ago what calling an audible
Samsung
Around 9
Colloquialism
Okay is I don't understand what that means still
There's a lot of expressions
Look there's a lot of Expressions that we don't know why we stay there but we do so
Indira Tyler
It rhymes
One more little bit
It turns out that I
Retired before
Sound effects I can't find it
Everyone is a globalist is now globalist
Someone sodomites
So yes thank you very much Sarah also to everyone who is currently a globalist
Email Dan we will play
A 45-minute long
Repetition of that exact I hope we all do that everybody
The last month was really awesome
Growth
Iowa
Showing dividends
Everyone's help
Shortcomings
Also I'm emotionally unavailable
I watched shows about people eating food all the time
The Bryans dolphin make
Major city I will text you about this I don't understand that you said the words famous maitre d & I
My brain broke
Really good at
I want to be like him
Dallas show
Looks like French
2009 Vette
The present day
I'm covering it
Deandre
So we we got off track
Because we were
Close to me
We could taste it
To getting to the outbreak
I mean literal outbreak
Today we're going over February 25th to March 1st
In 2009
February 27th 2000
Is the date of
The first
Chicago Tea Party
The broke out Across the Nation
Slater
The many of them
Some cities around the country
Formal kickoff
Tea Party
Verystream
Very strange
Especially when you track the the roots of it that were around from the Alexa system for a sound economy
Before
Stuff like that
And I've also been a little bit
Not forthcoming about the
Reality
So on the 27th
There were 40 cities
But
On February 18th
The day after
Homeowners affordability
On the next day
CNBC Business News editor
Kelly criticized
Chicago Market
Tile Exchange
He's at the plans
Promoting bad behavior subsidizing losers mortgage
He suggested holding a tea party
Fur Traders together
Breeders
Together if they're little
To the Chicago River on July 5th
President Obama are you listening
Israel
I was promoted on the truck
So turned on the 19th
Covered that up
To know about this from the sources that we know he looks at
He's not mentioned it
So now as we get closer
To the outbreak of
The Nationwide
Chicago Tea Party
It's
How he
Response
I don't remember everybody dropping
Derivative
Lost the thread
Pretty quickly within that
Also it's funded
Business Channel and said
All that
Recession coming out of
It rewards those losers
You know
The people who were scammed
Money was stolen from them
No thanks
Thanks Trader Joe today on the 25th
Tiger episodes
She's really passionate about
1 star
Some Congress
I guess
K
Congress Critters is some call them
Hardcore criminals
Chairman and others
Like some primitive
Rituals
Disagree with criticism
Whenever the President addresses Congress
You don't stand up for many years
You wouldn't want that
I'm not just least of which but if you're not making some people angry
Exactly
Paulson artificial in
Totally
These things
Obama's doing something wrong by addressing Congress when it's not the state
As if it's only one
Only one man one would ever address numbers on
But the reality is it is a very common practice
February 27th 2001 George W bush
The Joint session of Congress
Sounds right after 9/11
On February 17th 1993 Bill Clinton
February 9th 90
Address The Joint session
For the first time
On February 18th
In 1977 until April 20th
Click until April 20th but it was not
Did 1973
A little busy
On March 19th
5 lb
The joint
The Joint session
The great impression
On May 16th on May 16th 1797 John Adams address
The Joint session
What's the deal
Typically in especially the first time a president Wednesday
Generally not if they get real first time
The General
Election day give a speech to the Joint session of Congress
About a month after being inaugurated
Is a very common practice
Especially in modern American political tradition
Oh and also on February 28th
2017 Donald Trump addressed The Joint session of Congress
It was not the State of the Union just the exact
Same formality speech that so many president
Tyrant Barack Obama
Has given in the past
Very very tough and Alex should know that complaining about it making it seem like
It's on the weird
Means to me he doesn't understand American Civic
Reality
He complains about this probably throughout
A lot of this episode
You comes back to it over and over again
David gave a speech
This is an entire Apple
No it's
He brings it up with his gas
But he has on it
It sort of something that he's really trying to make a make a eagle out of
Alex is going to in a mood
You get the caller that asked him about secession
He addresses the issue of secession
Of the states
And I don't know if he does a great job
I am
Hypocritical
I am not
Secession
Okay
Merged with
Declaring their inherent sovereignty
It was a state
Not real
Let the feds come in here
Is there job
Created the Federal
Government that's why
35 States
Well I think you just
Summed it up appropriately
If you have 35 States you decide to abolish the Federal
Then the federal government has two weeks
To get out it's like
I'm glad you started it by saying let me be clear
Crystal Clear lyrics
Let me be clear
I do but I don't
That would be a last-ditch effort if it's federal government was doing everything is currently doing right now
Exactly
Emergency
In favor of
You don't want
Over the idea that
Also
Principality
Feudal City
Countries with the governor is
Authority in the land
I don't like that vision of the future
Like that vision
The pest
Here we go
Finally
On February 25th
Yeah after
Copious amount of
Looking
Please finally signed
Cool not Alex
Holly Susan Illinois go ahead
Hi Susan
Well I've been awake for about 3 months
Betrayed
And I
But with that I wanted to remind or tell everybody to go to
Nationwide
Chicago Tea Party.com
I don't know if you've heard of it but there is
You know a nationwide tea party happening about 35 cities
People protesting
I'm really encouraged about that
So unfortunately at this point you like what you think
Alex goes off on answering questions
He gets lost in his own world of like
Yeah yeah we still have we still have ratzinger
And so I only know that because someone requested that I go to
To the day that
And David night was hosting
The Pogues
Is no longer
Hope
This is not been
Seems in
Other popes
Enough
Leo zagami
All right. That's that's not a good impression
Roll today
Where to eat
Circle
Question about the Tea Party
And we can see where his head is at but before that
YouTube
He wants you to f*** with your priest a little bit
I keep forgetting
Alex's whole thing is like
The government's trying to can
Trolls he's the preacher is a 501 c 3
I'm very simple solution
Really don't understand why they don't pay tax
Jim Bakker
Except
These weird
Broadcast
Because it's a religious
Yeah you could do that
That's the only thing
Just cuz you believe in something
I really don't think you should be
Tax exempt
I feel like that's what sounds terrible thrust
Unpack I do
Religion isn't real
Don't necessarily want
Texas
Churches to be
Not tax-exempt
Because there are a lot of
Good thing
Getting paid for
In terms of like soup kitchen
Staffing like
Helping the poor
Complicated tax code even more
Look
Ivory religion I'm fine with making their lives harder
The idea of churches being taxed
If you want to preach Patriots stuff or even if you want to
Democratic talking points from the pulpit
Your Scientology
Pay your f****** tax
Simple Solutions
Praise for whatever their Rabbi other Imam
I want to help
Suspicious
Sounds right
Imallexx are you encouraged about the
Tea Party
On Friday
Friday the 27th
You know I heard something about folks having their own protest
Just getting on the streets
Muscles
Is just awesome Susan I appreciate your call
Alex has no idea what's going on
He doesn't know about the Tea Party
Because I I don't I don't believe
I don't think you can play anything close to the vest
If he does know about it
On board at the point already
He be going nonstop he wouldn't be able to fame
Lack of awareness
The sympathetic caller
Talking about these
It seems to be like maybe he's heard about it
Tickets to the plant for sure I'll probably
I think we all know
I've been awake for three months
Legos five
But be that as it may
I wrote down
Okay
You're probably right
Alex probably
Got wrecked
Walk by Alex Jones radio
Maybe I don't know or saw a link
You know or she was paid by every radio station
Give them
Multiple times and website
Like a lot of radio stations have fake collars
Yeah
Using the platform
Get something else out
We seen that a million
Clear dictionary
Suspicious
Little weird mode complain about Obama bunch more but before he does
Astarte's
Think about it
Of course
He's got to talk about
Yeah
Week
Cool and your father
Eat what you want it's what you get
This is what they want
Everybody
This is what
YouTube that I bet you can just like this is what they want this is what they do
Trevor nuclear war
Girlfriend
The Warriors
Wall-E Droid
Apartments
This is
This is what they give you are.
They hate you serve them
Afraid of you
I love that
How do I get to the new address
Springs
Depleted uranium
Whatever
Can you spray it first
Not sure all right
I've looked into Chemtrails enough to know that
But I don't think that's one of the weirdest conspiracy
I don't think it's depleted uranium you know it's crazy though
It's moments like that make me wonder if this show would work
So much better if Alex had a co-host
You know to bounce the movie
The other guy can come into be like where I live
Whatever the f***
The problem is it whenever Alex has anybody
Subordinate
There's no way he could adjust
Free
Existing respect for life
Mike Adams
I think he could
Have the authority
Time travel
We're going to book
We're talking
Major League era Charlie Sheen
Sossaman
He could have used Victory not sure that Charlie would want that
We would never have had Two and a Half Men
Would have had to deal with it
The second one
A lot of other stuff we wouldn't have
My friend Alex
It is a continuation of all of his state senators and state representatives
Is an Oklahoma
I believe might have been a rap by the name of Rick
That's the most Oklahoma state senator named you could ever have.
This guy is not cool
Most of his career is just like Tenth Amendment
Things like that
He was created by the Dare program
What do you mean
Keep kids off drugs
Another agenda
Andre
Big more recent pad
He's shown a bit of his
Is wild
Is Wild Feathers
I'm using the wrong now we're trying to get colloquialisms in here
Call Brock
Call executive director
Gerber Oklahoma
DC Ryan Young Band
Stop be too upsetting except
After Ryan was
Domestic assault and battery in the presence of a minor child
As well as interference with an emergency telephone call
Rajan said Ryan was being quote Drive
Through the mud at those critical of him quote should not be
Casting the first stone
The ironic part of that is Broad
That guy was arrested for dragging his wife through the mud literally
Police reports
Specific
It is
So I also I'll just tell you right now he is really punching up
I will just tell you right now this man here he's
Baseball real hard at a person
Call Leticia
Has the Oklahoma Republican Party
Call disgrace
Party became a little uncomfortable
Puppy party Facebook account
Defeating animals in national parks
Cool
Cool coco coir
During a debate about this
Oklahoma Legislature
Real Racing
Hilarious parody of racism
Using your race so racist
You mean by that
Is the snap program
Do that
Watermelon
So I can confirm this from the site I looked at those
Apologize
Ballsy on both the
I'm on the
You said it
So apologize already support
Reflected on how help Implement legislation
The required
Seeking abortions
Ultrasounds of heart monitors of
In fact tempting to terrorize women into keeping unwanted
He lamented
Not ended abortion in Oklahoma
And repented for his sins unless the pro-life camp
Sing there's a
What do you like to call an abortion
Seeking
So yeah
No women
Which is cool great
Also in April 2018 came out that Randy Brogden was the executive director of a super
Free states
We could at least $24,000 into the gubernatorial campaign
The pastor
Fisher
Fisher is also an abortion abolitionist
Making his first order of business
Outlaw abortion acceptable to women in Oklahoma
Sounds like you probably drag someone
Also feature is known to preach at his church
Which looks exactly it looks exactly
It looks exactly
He's trying to bring back what she calls the black Rogue
Regiment which was a group of creatures in the Revolutionary War era
The British
There's literally nothing exactly that
Just pay your taxes
So you could do that
But no problem
Muster up
$25,000 to give to monsters campaign
Boyd Texas
Given Brockton and Fishers
The fact that Brogden endorse
Fisher
State representative
The fact that their friend
It's unrealistic to think that they didn't coordinate a little very serious FEC vie
Violation
Probably not worth looking into those until we got 7.9% of the vote
Republican primary
What a waste
Never going to never going to get that 20 for Grand back I could use that
24 G
Brockton
Support
Anyway that's a little bit of fun about this I don't want to listen to most of his
Because it's very similar to
Other 10th Amendment
Alex
Complaining more about Obama's speech
Quite quite escaping review
It was probably one of those sophomore
I've ever heard in my life
Parrot
To the Constitution if you compare it
Founders of this great nation
Alright
What are we talk
Grammar
Whatever
This speech is nothing
The founder
Seems like you're setting the bar
You know what I'm going to be honest with you
The Constitution
Benefits news
Siri doesn't bring out the emotion like the Declaration of Independence
Maybe you can toss that in there that would have been a great speech
Come on man
Those amendments are boring or a little dry nothing much going on
No
It's a sophomoric
Just stop
What about
Compared to an Oscar speech
How about that
Another guest
Was the guy named William William
No
Like a little too much
Because you sort of new to our scope
Embarrassed
Who is this guy
Political and economic
Are they
Engelsman published released 2014
What's the foreign propaganda front we encountered a couple episodes
Which is run by the Russian Academy of Sciences
He's published almost exclusively anti US stories than many that followed the exact line the Russia puts out about
Including this headline quotes Soros
Kiev Central Banker
Even wrote an article in 2015 titled quote why I wept at the Russian parade
Here's an excerpt
My tears that's being the silent Marchers and Putin amid them was
Conscious reaction to What on reflection
I realized with my very personal sense of recognition
How remote from Anythink
Comparable in my own country
The United States of America
Such a memorial March
In peace and serenity would be
Oh boy
Pretty indicative of his
Strongly
The government's stuff lot of Ice Age
Muscle pain
Like late. Robert F Kennedy and still be like
He was
Advisory Board of veterans today
Is largely as a propaganda Outpost
Articles from new Eastern Outlook
Partnership representative
Effort
Publication
At least 26
Important works for the center for research on globalization
The canada-based think-tank Run by Miguel
Bosch
Dopeski
In 2017 the center for research on globalization with
Communication
Which is where their information Warfare Special
As a website
Icky accelerant
And helping popularize articles with little basis
In fact
Also happened to fit the narrative being pushed by the
They further described it as quote a link in the
Concerted
Effort to undermine The credibility of mainstream Western media as well as we North American and European Publix
Government Republicans
Rite Aid careers
Just a laundry list
Working a conspiracy Outlets
Russian
In other words
He is a
Very normal Healthcare
Do you think do you think he's like a
Listen
Whittier writer just
So maybe he just answered answered an ad or something like that.
Do you think he's just a jobber do you think if somebody boris's list
Somebody within the American government
What are you just jump over and be like cool America's the best
I don't know no I don't think so
I would assume not cried at a military parade
Like its contact
Early early
Career Test
That's a no
Probably not
It would have to be very difficult to buy a lot of them now because there's too much traffic
A lot of money
And foundational moment
Could use to pay that the writer
You still need to have some sore
Had a little speech by dr. Like right after all
When are we welcome him back with open arms
Do
Here is Alex talking to F William
Stock predictions that did not come to pass
And then
So something hours shooting
Because
New York
In the last 3 years
And corporate lawyers
My 2010
The islands of Caribbean islands
Certain places in certain point there's no place to hide
Affects everybody
We can't live on another planet
Yeah
No I I I read you
I think they realize that they're going to be some very very angry citizens were going to wake up and say wait a minute
How did
The head of Citibank accumulated a billion dollars
President of a bank
He pushed on
People who couldn't even write their own name but we're told they would get a dream house if they just put an x on a piece of paper
Regulation
The other part of
Speed switches that we rise up and murder them and their readouts
Mustafa people
I see much more on the left
Yeah
Except for the fact
Right right
Prediction United States
Months 10 months
But there's a black president
Betfair
From their viewpoint
Like to see like I was probably coloring a lot of their opinion
Episode
Fried Chicken was going to be mandatory
Affordable Care Act
Now that just feel emboldened or empowered
Talk like they're racist all the time like I texted everybody
The birth because you don't hear stories about like
Not like you don't hear anything about state representatives unless you lived in Oklahoma you might have
That's right
Every single Alex Jones
He has all the 10th Amendment
Raps
Come on
Yep
You do that
It's been just as awful
It's the one that's going on now
This reminds me of s*** that my dad my family would say where it's
Okay well
Would you
Vote for this guy
He's clearly an obviously a rapist
They be like now I just wouldn't vote
So is like
Possibly allow him
To be Governor could wash your hands of it as opposed to actually stop it
A knot before being elected there's some sort of corollary there
It's almost like that kind of thinking contributed to the rise of the Nazis
It's almost like there's a
On the right side
Just feel like doing nothing
Crazy
So you don't want to you don't want another Governor but you don't
Want to stop at nothing from being governor
Governor
What's there but what stopped
Florida I'm sure they'll make the right
Sojourn
I don't think he realizes how much
You could be talking to his
Yourself
I believe that
Very precious
About something
This clip made me like
Are absorbed
So enjoy
Just snowed
That's the most important thing
Just been suckered
And you're going to have to experience this mail
This is the bankers having your way with
Direct
Proto at pivot
That the wrong just know you did this to yourself
Alex right now
You did this to yourself that was jarring
You think you're one of the protected
You think Trump is going to stop you from getting kicked off Facebook
Everything you've been suckered in by
Vista Global spring Washington
Propaganda
Over his life about the globalist
And you're complicit
To a certain extent
And repent
Cuz that is what life is all about
I don't think that's
Turn yourself around
I thought it was
Jordan
We need 30 more policy wonks and then we can rent the biggest bounce house
George removing all to the 26th
February
We're going to answer a little bit of an Oklahoma City situation
But
This next clip is one of the things that
Stupid stupid her for another
And I August
Majority of u.s. states joined sovereignty movement amendment rights
495 Oklahoma City
Salute
Absolutely
Eric Holder
Eric Holder did Oklahoma City
You know
No
Like contrary position
And it's up to him to prove it
You're like these specific thing
Narrative
He's overarching things that Alex talks about Oklahoma City or
He'll use like they'll just say I have a false flag
They blew up the building Eric Holder
Is complicit in it he was using Volvo
I can't do anything with
I can only do something with
Pacific Power
Pieces that he's going to bring out
And so
I'm not going to sit here and go through literally every
Piece of information
Could be involved in Alex's
Possible conspiracy theory about Oklahoma I can't do bunk
This nonsense
Did you see that on the Eric Holder was photographed walking out of the Oklahoma City
Rebuilding someone else
Then let's this other bit of evidence
I didn't doesn't necessarily correlate but
Did you see that Eric Holder was walking out of The Book Depository
On 11th.
The problem for me
Sure
The time traveling
Jumping-off
The only reason I bring this is like
Trying to find out what he's talking
Sing about
It leads me on wild goose chase
Because I end up trying to look into what he's talked about and I find like
And then I go down this path
Savannah
And then I end up spending seven hours
Reading bulshit
May or may not be talkin about
So we had that one time we talked about Oklahoma City
The police office
Suicide from Survivor
Grabill
Pacifica
Implying that Eric Holder was involved isn't good enough
Because I'm going down f****** wild-goose chases about his nonsense
I love that I love that rhetorical technique is as well
Guarantee
That the government
That's it it was the government we can prove
And you know who was the librarian at the time
His eyes go to Siri exactly
Anybody who might have been an office is involved
That's WeChat
The other thing I need to bring up
Is it I did a disservice
Restore audio
And I only realized it after going down all these f****** stupid road
So
I mentioned that Alex
DHHS
Report
That they were concerned
This is an unfortunate incident
Where I took Alex
I didn't look into what you was talkin
King about
What else to talk about
Department of Homeland Security
It is a
TSA that they put out or a video that they put out
That has a
Bunch of people
Advising people
There's things afoot
In terms of being eyes and ears
Which I'm slightly uncomfortable with play understand why
Society would be like
Hey
Or I don't know what we do if you see something say something
Sing
They aren't
Alex watch the man
Alex watch the video
And you thought
Huh
Too many white people terrorists in this video
It's not that they
Are you commissioned a report or anything like nobody did a s*** ton of research there's no speak only
He's a video watch where he sought
On his own
Objective basis
So
It made me realize that a lot of these
Timezone Alex's bringing up a colonel
It doesn't exist
It's in his head
It's just his subjects
Give experience of the world is
The ghs
Do you think that
Because of your experience of watching this video
I can't remember specifically
Women wearing these are like 16
Nobody
Sexualizing
Realized
So nobody is insisting that these people are saying that
All whites are terrorists other than Alex
Who's like
Well yeah I mean all whites are terrorists
He's appealing to the authority of his
Watching that
And that's a really troubling thing that I realized
About this world
I can't study
Until he reveals on the show
If so
It's just it's weird
It's really weird to have this year's in
This colonel
Long ago
CID
Resources might be ramping up
Something you thought
Yeah I'm at
Not good
What's even more concerning
Is that the reason that neither of us were even considering looking into it is because we were both immediately like
Oh yeah that's
Yeah even exist
I could see it
Interested in looking into it specifically is that like
Level I kind of
Just assume
I mean even if you do
Consider the idea of like
Rising right-wing
The militia
The Patriot movement
Fooled into that
Environmental
Rat and large
If you include those.
It would make sense
For people who were trying to
Keep an eye out for terrorism
Or paper
What
I'm just
Something like that I don't think
Oh this is
You're misrepresenting Something problems
Yeah it's it's always been so secondary
Two things that
Did I've never saw fit to actually like
Buckledown finds the
Based on his
Rhetoric
Boots Justin
Well the other thing that makes it obvious
They're just more white
A lot of murders in Chicago but statistically that's
Who's most likely to kidnap a child
Simple statistics
Blew up Oklahoma City
I could sit here and give you all the evidence
Of all us he like
Timestamp
Bills
Look up watch a f****** documentary
We're looking
Because everything I could
Re-strengthen
Basically the
Of the Oklahoma City
They're been
Every
Piece of
Stop.
Is flimsy
Everything is circle
There's not much to it until like
Do the f****** text bride to tell you
Here's exactly what happened
Went through the legal system do you know who is Kennedy attorney general at the time
No is Eric Holder
So I can't I can't do s*** with that we'll see if he eventually comes up
Before
To talk about how much you love guns
I have you don't
You are basically
Housefly
Oh man
Great
But vaguely
The United States
Exhaust slave
The slaves got a weapon
I see articles
Woman calls 911
Somebody starts bus into my house
Discharged
That's not good
I'm not sure that Kelly would be
I don't think that you would be
Chill shooting somebody
Exactly
Calmly aim at the center of mass and discharge
F***** up even more f***** up live
Explains what
Open fire
He's doing that voice
Voice that he does
Grabagun
Oh my God people who have gum
Now
That's not good that's a bad way to think about life it's not all of the people who have done
Free consistent within people who love
You know that sort of
Like I want a reason to use my gun to kill a person
That's probably
That give me a reason to kill a human
Like
Like a robot Grabagun
That don't answer the description
Robot
No longer has a thief or other human
Like a good person and definitely not at all like what I imagine a serial killer
Beep bop boop
Boom boom boom
A robot would actually be more
RoboCop
He doesn't aim for Center Mass I'll tell you that right now
Jordan
This next clip
Start literally right after Alex said
Yeah
After he said that he is fine with killing a human being he then says something f***
Connected I don't
It is a play
It's a jarring jump
What
What is that is it look like
No it's totally normal you can't
That's a good idea
Bad trip
Imbalances in an aggression hormones flood
Well
Being
Closed-minded is nonsensical as well
If you're coming in with like
Affects the serotonin
Butter system
The class of
Drugs
CO2 serotonin
Apple invented that right that's Siri
Hooters
The drug
Not a part of
Your brain
Do you think he's just
Grasping at straws trying to
Demonize the idea of cycle
And s*** like that
Really bad
Really smart if you're a person with paranoid schizophrenia medication
Kind of true
If I took care of myself I would not believe in these apparitions I call globalist
Probably true I don't know if
Like an active
He must know
If he advocated wellbeing
For his listeners
And advocated for them speaking
The help they actually knew they would often drift
Better about life they would under
1st and
Guys just try to make me
Scared all the time
That's that's kind of a
Mannequins with our time
Manic demagoguery
Just because we're so
Pro
Medication
I think we should
Not everybody
I don't I don't believe in a world where everyone must be
Diagnosed and put on a
Regimen
But I do
It's probably good idea
Well we do now
We don't do s*** like this where he scares people
With terrible prediction
You're just a lister's of his show
But we only
PetSmart
He already said America's probably not going to exist in 2010 with 10 months
Maybe a year from now we had another big one coming
So
It's usually wrong
Stevia probiotic yogurt
That I'm going to go with a lot of the health benefits to those are over-exaggerated
Love it
Take probiotics
Biotics
I used to drink
Liquid yogurt
This is me
Hello yogurt shot
Terrible that sounds disgusting
So
I just went all-in on Greek yogurt
What happened at my name in it
Tonality I LifeStraw
From textbooks
As I did
In element
High School
But I would like to point out that Alex
Different version
Afterworld
Little bit differently
Three different textbooks
Second Amendment
There's a bunch of textbooks
The government
The song
Time Magazine
Your parents are backwards
What is science fiction nightmare dystopia
The cup is clip for this Alex
Highlights for kids
Goofus and Gallant
What's
Close to reality
Except for the Goofus and Gallant reference now that I think about it there's no way that he's he's on that tip
But I have
Has a plan by the globalist
Change the minds of
Kids
Textbooks and
Time magazine for children I didn't know there was a Time magazine for children
But
That's not the
Cuz they don't give a s***
Child
Is always
Richard
Couldn't come over
That's all you got
Yep
Wait there was a town drunk
Yeah it's Andy Griffith
Sleeping it off in walk-up
And then of course The Lovable Town drug who's always in prison
Call jail I apologize at all
Now there was Aaron
Come down on them
Is the problem
F****** way there's
Population was minuscule
Drunk all the time
Crazy recidivism is a real problem
Wild
What time is part of this route
How much is it
Depiction of drunks
Should be like Winos
And stuff like that where they
It was
Who cares
But the best the best depiction of that time was always the the drunk
Who is on like the the sidewalk
Just holding a brown bag
And then something crazy happens and he turns and looked at it
He looks at me like
Happen all the time
Cuz that was like a classic
Comedy
Houston
Fabolous Rosa Baca
Hold on
Betty White
Haven't you ever seen The Good Wife I don't know why that
That was a weird Paul
Not positive face on the cliff
Time magazine for kids and textbooks are traded
Probably
You know
Politician
And one
Only
Is Ron Paul Wright
Caller calls
Clowning and Duncan on these global
Alex has an interesting
And then I have
What I want to see from
Ron Paul
Next time he has
Bernanke
I mentioned this before
Why can't you just start embarrass
People in automated system
Any reason
Still listening to the globalist
Is because
Globalist
Still have this
We have to call them out
Criminal
There's too much of a gentleman
Gore
No
New
You were not at 1
It's really funny that Alex is alleging the Ron Paul is too much of a gentleman to call out the globalist
We've already discussed this very definitely self author
StoryBots
Even more exciting in the 1980s
Jordan
Story
It's something you've never heard I'm certain
Okay
This is one of the greatest things I think I've ever read
That's not
Alright on April 27th
Nobu Nobu
Who are suspiciously
A bunch of dynamite in a Nazi flag
These men had planned to meet up with a hastily thrown together militia and overthrow the government of the island nation Dominica
In hopes of setting up a white supremacist
What
The guy who created I just a regular old racist website
Yeah
Weird way to look at it but
Broadway
So yeah I had a plan
To perform a coup
You better and take over
Really
Yep the 1981
Is really think highly of themselves again he got arrested surprised by that
I can't stress
It was 90 they were going to
Get on this boat and then meet up with
They were going to beat up with
Perform the coup
So
Originally secured a captain to take them back out in February
Conspirators Klan member Mike Perdue found a new captain operation
You are smart
Who put some countermeasures into action
Put down the phone and then immediately
Install is the new prime minister in Dominica
Patrick
Was erected
In Dominica
Those are
Naturally the ATF blankets and towels crew and arrest everyone
Also naturally wants Mike Perdue got arrested he started squealing on everyone
Start trying to cut it video
Both personally aware of the plan
As was revealed governor of Texas John Connally
What is a catered three men is financiers of the adventure one of them
Kirkpatrick suicide
Before he was due to appear in court
John black as mentioned would go on to create storms
He would also go on to aggressively campaign for Ron Paul anytime he was up for election
Particularly in his Direction
David could also be a very loud supporter of Ron Paul's presidential effort
Decline to subpoena Ron Paul and
Conspirators trial
A pictures about anything that I am absolutely
And may have been involved
There's so many people who were connected to him who were involved
Definitely
Yeah Ron Paul
Other people
You said were involved
One of them killed himself
The other two
Probably were involved subpoena Ron Paul
Really feel like you should have subpoenaed
Governor of Texas
Suspiciously
The conspirators who ended up being found guilty or pleading guilty
3 years in court wonder why really
Really feel like I really feel like
Planning and attempting to commit a cool should get more than 3 years
Well the guy
But that's because
Mikey was here
Yeah
Are you are you telling me
I could Charter a plane
With like let's say what are they got made
Max
60 guys
Just cover it just filled up
And then just fly to a ran and be like we're going to take over this b****
Yeah it's tough
Champaign Illinois with 60 guys
Yeah
Logistics
Guys
This is a
Really bad idea
Call UCF
It's the sort of thing that I think you could make
Oh really good
Dark comedy about
Because the story is hilarious
Hasn't never
He's never made a statement about Italy
He was
It's crazy
What's the wind
You just
You secretly aware involved in helping us to ask a question about how old white supremacist
Ron Paul keeps his hands
You'll have people like John Black
People like he's playing members were involved spreading the word on the low
Anyway that's not provable
He was part of it
Keith back in what's up
Shrek
You can put that rhetoric out in
Publix
Publicly disqualified from ever being an office
DaVita paper trail
Well that's true
He wasn't one of the finance
Okay well
Money orders untraceable money orders and
Like with manafort there's definitely that like
The worst thing that happened to manafort was Trump won because otherwise nobody would have looked into it
Well yeah but they know
Yaks
Ron Paul tried to overthrow Dominica
Ron Paul will be elected president of Dometic
Yes
So
Alex has representative Charles
Keanu
Isaiah
Francis
Scott Key
The guy who wrote
Which is
Yeah that sounds great
Third cousin
Not what
Exactly exactly he is a state representative from Oklahoma
Deep dive on him
The Oklahoma City bombing
This is sort of
Charles
Cheese bread and butter
Oklahoma City
Conspiracy theorists
This is
These problems examples and
Oklahoma City Bombing case has a very good one. Thank God for Jesse credited people like him
What going to keep fighting this thing a dick born where
But there's more than enough evidence for the people to see the
Their government is out of control
So this is where we can go
Because I've heard the name Jesse Trent
You brought up
Some of the wild goose chase
From Alex's
Like let's see what he's talking about
Fun to say
That is fun
Detective Charles Keith bring him up as likes
Somebody who's been doing
So we finally have like a climbing the rock we got ahold
Little X
Super Inn
Because here's
Jessie Trice do is a
Utah-based lawyer whose brother Kenneth was probably murdered by the police in Oklahoma
The official Declaration was that it was a suicide believe that evidence shows
The official version of the story isn't
To get Justice for his brother that is light him to become a
My hero for the militia and Patriot
Without becoming a hero to the militia Community believe that
Crossroads in your life
It very much looks like Jesse trentadue has a good point
That killed his brother.
I think he has a good point unfortunately leads to a really bad
After reviewing the evidence I have very little reason
Dial Jesse
Was murdered by the police
They're massive inconsistent season we all
We're pretty well-versed in the idea of police brutality
It's kind of
The idea that he might have killed himself I recognized a certain possibility to it I would say too much less
It's likely based on the evidence then
He was murdered
Because there were like ligature marks on his on his arm from
The probably wouldn't be there
Struggling
Third wound to his face
Don't
Inconsistent
Hang himself
Cell
Unless there's some sort of
Unreported
In the prison like us
Spiky got into debt
So he was killed in
Oh
Impossible for me to know like based on things that I've looked in
But I would be pretty comfortable
85%
I think that there's a good
Good champ
Now the reason that I think was a shift
And some of those
Wounds were from
Him struggling while he was alive with him
Cops
I have
Lasted after
Could have gotten ft prison and then hung himself
He was a heroin addict
A lifelong Criminal
So like the idea of it possible
This point
Despondent
I think there's a small possibility
Much more likely based on the evidence
He probably did
Which I think is f***** up
The argument that this has something to do with the Oklahoma City bombing
Seems to have something to do with the fact that the government was resistant
Investigate
The County Medical Examiner became frustrated
You couldn't get together to look at the
So you tempted to get the
Oklahoma City
The Peace of their
In reality they didn't want to get involved
I went because it was unrelated
But the perception is
The two crimes were connected
In fact they wouldn't deal with it on that g
Is evidence that they were trying to shut it down
Now I believe
Again it's 8
Very important that I make clear where I agree with this guy and where I jump
There's probably a cover-up
I don't think it's a vault Oklahoma
Back
Crazy
It is this corner
Her know what was it
Was just like
Nobody's paying attention to me
Toss this in with the OKC
That's what I gather that's what I gathered from an interview with the medical examiner
Really feel like you can't just do that
Now if I ever heard one
Resistance
It's exactly what would happen if the cops killed
Exactly
Like
Awful
But it doesn't
Necessarily better than that to prove to me
That this is somehow involved Oklahoma
Same time
It doesn't necessarily mean
But they're connected
I have a bit of empathy
Ford
Even though he's a f****** Criminal
Even though he's someone who got himself back in prison
If that is what happened
I still have some empathy about that
Jessie
Trying to find out the truth
It is
Very much like
There's a Crossroads there's a One path the other path kind of situation
Either I can become a crusader for good
I can believe that it's part of the Oklahoma City bombing
Now
Beyond all the stuff that I've already mention
Du's argument hinges on
Anonymous phone call
Video
He's received told him that his brother's death was involved with the bombing
Including one from Timothy McVeigh
According to
Trentadue
The theory is that the feds
Confused do with Richard Lee Guthrie
The creator of the white supremacist in Neo-Nazi group Republican Army
23isBack
Between 1994 and 1996
In order to thunder terrorist
He was inspired by the Turner Diaries
Just like Timothy McVeigh
Elohim City
Just like 10
Witnesses of Elijah did Guthrie and his members
Republican Army
Use the funds that they stole from those 22 back
To pay for Timothy mcveigh's expenses and putting together his attack
There are unsubstantiated
But alleged
Connections between them
And Associates
Richard Lee Guthrie
Had I been
Placed at like
The Timothy McVeigh was at
Prior to
The attack
I can see why that, a wrote bank robber movie
You know Robin Hood
Bank robber sorry that we always
See over and over again
Bank robber story
I don't think that was going to be famous
Schedule
What is a nugget
What
Most of it hinged on the fact that they
Mostly targeted small-town Midwestern Bank
Security
And didn't
Easy A
It would be close to the highway
Would be
Because you get in
Get on the interstate
And generally speaking
Harder to catch
Like as long as we kept it till like 2 or 3 years ago
So the technology of
Surveillance
Around in order to
That's a good plan related to Kenneth
Two things come up
First
Kenneth allegedly looked a lot like
Shirley Godfrey
2nd Timothy the rap sheet that included
Which is the reason he was in Costco
In the first place
He refused to conform to the terms of his probation
Not that part
He told me he wasn't going to stop drink
King Boos so there was no reason for him to come in for drug screen
Is there anything like that
Right cuz he's going to be
Caught
And so he just stopped going in for piss test
Which weather condition of his parole
He also hit in laws in Mexico
And right before he was wrapped
Country
Sentence probation
Is the argument just were
Drawing of Guthrie out in the world as John Doe number two
Yeah
Handprint to do look a lot like
Then I think you have a theory that makes the
I don't believe it
It's not proven in any way
But there aren't any glaring problem
However
Jesse trying to do his narrative is far more,
He believes that Waco Ruby Ridge in Oklahoma City are all part of the federal government attempt
Disrupt Patriot organizations
It's a part of an operation
Or the Patriot conspiracy
Because he involves this as part of his
San Diego
Because he involves as a part of his argument everything falls apart
If popcorn is real which I'm not sure it is I don't
Then the feds know they were looking for in John Doe number 2
They knew they would be looking for Richard
But probably didn't want the public to know how they lose
Surveillance
Putting out this app
Maybe on a person
They were looking for because of
The Patriot
Conspiracy Network
Putting out to the right and just
After Shield that from public awareness
But if that's the
It follows
That they would know.
What
Given the fact that trying to do
Violation
Beautiful raps
They would know that
If the rest of Jessie
Narrative
Going on this Crusade is true
It always self-contradictory
It doesn't work together
It's impossible
Display
The story is really really sad
And you can't help it at besides of Jessie
Here's a man who had his brother most likely murdered by the police
And always try for years to get some modicum of just
This estate is not allowed enclosure
It becomes even sadder
What do you see how he'd allow the pain and grief
He feels about this tragedy
Be transmuted into a right-wing
Conspiracy
On another level it's really sad to recognize all of the
Non-white families that have to go through this exact same pain every day
Having their family members killed or wrongly incarcerated but don't have enough circumstantial evidence
Core Connections to white supremacist in Neo-Nazi group
Alex Jones to even care about their plight
I watched an hour plus long presentation by Jesse trentadue
Where you laid out all the relevant
Evidence
And I think the connection to the OKC bombing
Profoundly Slim
But it's what he needs in order to keep his brother's death relevant
To make it more important than just another inmate stamps
Murdered by
I would feel a lot of empathy for him
If he didn't say this
Towards the end of his prison
You asked me how long I'm going to fight these sons of b******
Till I'm dead
And what Justice will I ever get out of that
Will they ever prosecute anybody for my brother no
Never will
But I can harm the reputation to Department of Job
I can harm the reputation of the FBI
I can do great damage to them and that's my objective
That's the only Justice my family will ever get
It seems like trying to do primary objective as he clearly says
Is the hurt the FBI in the Department of Justice
If you were doing that by sticking
I would support that whole heart
Unfortunately
He's correctly realize that the way he can hurt them the most
Is the side with the right-wing terrorist
Petal unfounded nonsense
And for that my empathy for his situation
He's greatly
I feel very sad
I wish I could care more but
He's got tricked by the
Please do
All around
Best socks for everybody
Vandeventer
Stocks
I'm bummed there's nothing good about hero everybody
Serial killer
Is the guy who got murdered in prison and we don't even know that
Deserve
That sort of only ones with the town drunk
Grievance
Numbers
Everything sucks
What's
Kenneth Jessie
We're actually twins
Jessie
Was the one who was accidentally mistaken for
And put in prison
Is actually
Kenneth was always a what two prime
Going to prison for 8
Kenneth Branagh
It sucks you're right
All that just sucks I had
No pleasure out of learning about
I'm fascinated by it like
You know
Witness
As I was complaining about earlier
Chase the ghost of Alex's
When you find something that's like there's a specific
Are you look into it and it's something like that
Heated be very literal definition
Sour grapes
Yeah that's like all man look up there on the branch
That's just a tragedy all the way around
Because
Like I said
Almost
You know like it is absolutely
You Muddy Waters
Another piece
Eventually
Payoff
From the government
Yeah
He got a payoff not from
The murder
But from
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
They keep
I don't think that makes it better
I think if there is obviously
The best
Could come out of it
Do you have police reform
Isn't any more satisfying than anything else
That's just like Hey we're going to keep murdering people but you get some money because you wouldn't shut up about it
Cover up
If there if it wasn't
Yeah
Now I don't know if it goes all the way up
I still do
The bombing
But there's a different conversation
Hey
You got to rain in the police forces in this country
But at least
It seems like
With God
Conversation
Trolls
There should be some sort of oversight for any human being that's allowed to have
Regardless of whether or not they are in love
Vets
Now we're out of it and Alex Jones is going to talk about you
Dumb bulshit but how
The rosicrucians
Ron
Yeah we're huge fans of them
Christian
What's truechristian Jesse's trying to
But
He was talking to his death
Nougat
From cutting-edge Ministry
And there are already out there on because
Which is on the dollar bill
I do like the title VI of the
That's not bad Bill represent
The mythical Phoenix and at the globalist are going to take it down and from it
You should also know
That
They haven't
Website
It's one of the lamest
And because they came out before Harry Potter right
Yeah yeah Phoenix is like it's a good thing and they're like no the Phoenix
Yeah that might be some sort of like getting on our turf
Yeah absolutely boring Christian nonsense of life
Yeah I know but I did I ever tell you whenever I was whenever I was like
12 or 30
My church
To read the first Harry Potter book so I could determine whether or not it was
Blasphemous
In case other children Reddit
They asked you
The Sorting Hat exactly you got it
Yep
Slytherin Slytherin
Facebook
These guys are wacky
I wanted to like get some quotes from the website
Stupid b*******
But that does not stop me
From playing
From cutting-edge Ministries.
Probably
The exciting part of this process
Is that this all comes down in it and they are they are aiming for the very thing the Bible says will happen
And that is
That is a yacht
Hey quite figure it out.
Remote control Global religion
I'm pushing for this
Yelp
Whomever he was at the time
Uno
I just
Kept
That long and then
Just rambling
You should really know which pope it is you're talking about if that's part of your conspiracy
Like you should have that information like on hand
Globalist
I think so
I don't know
So that
USA
Oh yeah
Cancel
New season of young Sheldon timeline
Anyway I just picked
I love I love your
Your lifestyle
I love it
Like the good
Define confer
Is it a palindrome is that what it is probable that I think
It lives
I know that it can be a funnel to more Danger
SeaWorld
But it's fun
How do you spell lives in this place
Mostly outside of bigotry
I think
Although probably
It's just more fun
The idea is like a it's like
In 1991 the Illuminati decided that no one will ever find Bigfoot
There was a
There was a time but right no more
Bill Clinton president
Nobody can find Bigfoot
Mexico
She's going to find those hitting squash
I don't know I have not
Absolutely
I think
You know what's interesting
Search cuz I don't know if I've ever heard about it
I'm sold it
Probably
Here's the thing
I'm not interested in
Cryptozoology
For the most part
I'm not sure I've ever heard Carrie talk about
Really I need to look into
Maybe pass and she said that they were some sort of alien race
Something she'd be like
And the Raptors are fighting the reptoids
Steamed up with the Sasquatches
Archives if I can find a spot
I would definitely do it
For sure
Chicago Cubs players
Right
Which means
Now to Dave again
What kind of party
Tea Party
Jexi
He was in Independence Day it was
Write instead of instead of the July Fourth 1776 it was like
Throw these aliens
Because okay
Going on maybe as long as
Or at least it feels that way we are now finally it's a day of the Nationwide
Chicago.
They are not
Weather on Sunday
If you're white
But
Here's how he starts the show
Really f***** up
I guess about six seven eight years I want to be clear
She's married to a lord
Literally
Exactly like
It's not like we got a woman
Who cares
I said who cares because like me
CBS
Learn this when I was a child because my dad
Precious
I mean literally
Their houses are
Yeah
The problem
Married to a lord
Maybe it is I didn't work
I can neither confirm nor deny that he's married to Lori monster
Climate creep
But
Big narrative with her is
Beat the s*** out of her and said you shouldn't make this movie
He's going to repeat that
At least six times during the
Who knows
He's going to repeat that over and over again it's the big selling point of life
This documentary that she
To put out to dangerous she lived it man to her rough
Look if you don't want this to happen again you're going to do I don't know why I'm doing so many voices
I like it though I like it
Okay alright
This, can't go on a yacht
Is that court order
Don't know why
But you some sort of a nautical vampire
Sagami
Here is that his dad was
South Africa has really bad
French South Africa South Africa
It's almost like a long time
Connection Envy's connections
Apartheid South Africa
It seems like
It's almost like a lot of the Proto right-wing in the John Birch Society
Maybe a lot of their funding came
From strip-mining countries
People would never do that we have a long history of not exploiting others
Day of the Dead
Seems like
On the last episode on the 25th
Two days prior
Alex headache
Clearly playing
Call Dempsey
Checkers
Maybe he's going to
Be up on it
Instead what does he talks to his survival food
Today
Steve shank has been the storm for 28 years
And
Didn't have any
I found out there and
And sweet
Attract
Elsa's having his f****** survival food guy on as a guest
To talk about the economy
This weird business model where his
Sponsors have to be guess
Limericks
This isn't the first time
Ushanka
Survival
So it's super weird
You nosey ever say that
For his
What is this
16 Parsons bro
Good place might as well because
I'd like a little boy back
I like I like the attempt
I like where you're going with it but that would never be a slogan because
It would be like an egg
Accu-Chek
You never make your survival food think we blew it
What if
You got to recontextualizing
The Wii and the Wii shanked it is
Society
Now yet
So it's a long walk
7 - 1
Now you recontextualizing I get a plus-one where I give myself a -14
Help you
He's having his food so I can sponsor on to talk about the economy
Am I cramping it's a little early in the show
Now cookbook are Lucy yeah
Yeah that's the difference
He's heading maybe later in the show he'll get his thoughts but ho
Nationwide uprising
He has Bob
And he makes
Darling
He's a white South African
No he's already confessed.
These are the main things in a quart
Unfortunate
The key holders
It is going to an absolute
Nosedive
And
They've just
Stock
We got it was going to go down
At the $38 a share $42 a share somewhere up there
JPMorgan cuz we
Shorted out as well
The same price and that selling for around 20
Citigroup
Is down $0.56 today
It's only for about a buck and a half
It would probably cover that short none of it works by then
And somewhere around a dollar I hope
And the
Will have
Made the difference between
Say $40 in $1
It's an awful lot of money
So what keys
Is it
Predict it
We're going to lose
Valuing
So he's short
Heap
And made a bunch of money off of it
What's Jones primary complaint about George Soros
He has shorted Bank he's the man who broke the bank
Use George Soros of being evil for doing Market
I understand
Which is the problem
Speaker problem
We have the stock market as it exists now
You need people short batting in order to pay
Whoever's wrong pays
And whoever's right makes that money
I feel like gambling with Pension funds probably bad
I don't like
Moral aspects of short
If that's
The system we live in
I would rather
Wow it's there
Rules of the game
Although on the other hand the other
Whatever it is
Those both seem like opposite ends of the same Insider training exploitative insiders Insiders
Breeding exploited
Both of those being an option
. is a very bad thing
Crime in front Elementary
If you have a situation where like you
Great
Going to get worse
Economy should work what
Mercy makeup
No more wrong
Is Tibet
You betting against
It doesn't make it
Right
Petros would just
Eastlake let's say the president of Citigroup shorted Citigroup
You get a lifetime ban from the Hall of Fame
For sure absolutely
The Bankers Hall of Fame is also in Cooperstown
Note the other reason that we've been going back to 2000
Figure out when
In this appearance
I don't have the Clippers
Because it's snowing
Consequential
Bobcat
Bring up George Soros
Oh no
Yeah as a good person doesn't
In reference to
Glenn Beck
Talking about how there's going to be this
Bubba
Absolutely
Glenn Beck and George Soros
Being in concert
No
He's implying that
Towards
Alright
But the only reason is like
2 seconds
Like I do
To play the clip I would have had to playlist
4 minutes
Alex
Completely no selling
Jordan
Broadcast
Not on his radar
Doesn't matter at all
He's like
Flip back socks
So you stole George Soros
Ignore that back might be in concert with George
Well
William
I know about George Soros is that he's not going to be like
Glenn Beck
Some good ideas will see what's up with you
The first time his name
Good impression
Sequential a
In this
At least month of episodes
It's the closest
28 your story
You know
Sign of things to come again
20 years
Yeah yeah
Maybe
Maybe the reveal is
Close
I don't know
But
In the same way that earlier in the episode that caller brought up at
How much that would change his life
He has the same response
Bobcat
Earlier was talking about how his dad is friends with South African
Diamond
Literally
His career
And the apartheid South Africa
White farmers
They're not doing well Loki maybe the worst person
And how he has that like
All Chucky voice the same way Ron Pope
This unassuming character to them
But like
You look into their careers you see like oh no the amount of damage
On the ground
Floor involved
Monstrous
I could say
Did anybody in Rhodesia
Then fled
When
Equity was starting to come around
African gold
Yeah you know on some level
You were
Where you be raping the people
And so that's why I think
Basketball
Just save this
When Alex Jones backup South Africa
Diamond
Absolutely
Is enough
Diamonds in the world
Burien
I mean they ain't they
Intrinsically they have little or no value
And has been created by debeers another
Debeers
Which is controlled
Indirectly by the Royal Family
Who financed all the projects
South Africa
And the other one says
Used to
Madison Ave
Especially during the
After the turn of the
21st century
Just a different commodity
I mean
Didn't even mention which one
Like that
The Danish girl
Yeah yeah yeah
Just a like a South African
Apartheid
Tunis
Another one
Absolutely true as much as
Like artificial scarcity
Prices
If the supplies it actually
Stated
We're all amazing ad campaign that that whole concept of two months salary or whatever
What are traditions in words
5 no
I don't know these are just the diamond commercials I remember from my childhood
The Shining
Vampire vampire Rihanna song
They're really great
Incredible
Should we use them for
I think they do exist
Movie franchises
No that's okay
Too many salt movie
I know there are like
Actual functional use
But in terms of jail
People have those but it's crazy it's crazy
What toothache
The song Grillz
Paul Wall
Nope not going well
This isn't going to happen on that song
The song bling bling
Lil Wayne alright
Mannie Fresh
This one's better this one's better actually the remix better Lil Wayne on it
Better than than your previous
Refreshes
We talked about
Helicopter
I love Minecraft
Brett Brett Brett
He's the best use the best of that
New Orleans
Hip Hop
Frisch's found
Good
Bang
And has like a realist
Symphonic quality
Less than shocked that you know so much about a guy like Mannie Fresh in that
Could not
You know what it is
There's like a like I was
Super into 1
Time my life I learned everything I could about that
And then I started to like like others
And everything I could about that
I'd love every time anybody has played any of his
But I don't give a s*** about cuz I know he's very
It's not something
That doesn't make any sense I don't I don't accept that argument
Like something
The bracket
Refresh
She's going over
Incorrectly
Real big
Patrick Star
First song from a real big fishes
Microwave oven
Well that was before they had the express
Optional most
So you have to push like 1 and then 002
But you can just press one and get a minute
Pac-Man
No I think he's talking about how he in his car
Prices on microwave ovens
That's how I meant at all
IMDb the good work
Fresh production
Alright
What are the great things by Big Tymers
They pretended that all of their albums were sequels to each other
Part 1 event
They have a bracket 11
How do you know if I need this conversation
Alright
Earlier
Alex
Teasing that he's going to have this Janine
Robert
Talk about her diamond
Documentaries
Like we've already talked about the idea that there is artificial scarcity
Does she have at least six teeth made out of
Because she had her teeth
Knocked out
Well
The only logical thing for her to do that would be
I don't know much about jean-robert but I'm guessing that you would cause a cold spot
Penny Candy you know what that mean
Jelly and Bean
Is this show about Alex
Sometimes I wonder
Getting a lot of reaction I don't know why
I don't know why
Young Jeezy
I don't know why I don't know why I don't care to listen to
Too much because I sort of implicitly agree with a lot of the stuff
Did you say
Corrupt
Business
Mostly using Arthur
Rise up
Because diamonds aren't available in a
Every part of the world
Temperature
Very end
Like I said
Over the course of this episode
Beat up
People were beating her up said hey.
And so now he asks her about that in the documentary
Specifically
So is personal insight
Her when she was in the hospital and tried to get her to sign over the rights
To her.
Beating
To the people who came
Company BBC
Okay
That is
Remember when Kim Kardashian got robbed
Know what something like that
I don't know anything about that was a couple years ago
I don't remember all the details.
But like
Nope people
Sure that she's
Lorde
Texting sometimes
Skins break
Metaphor
Okay
Hollywood he's a f****** God I'll tell you that right now.
You like his new ship
My coming-out in
Let's not let's not go crazy
Hey you know what
You can divorce the
Play
Some people still like Roman Polanski film
Pizza
What he says and then what
Most recent
Call the
Recipe
You should recognize
Tricks in order to
Gin up
Popularity
Publicity for
His project
Does like sensational
In order to
Dubai his
Supplements
Like this comment
Talk about it
He does this
Who cares
Freshwater
Never do some
I bet
So we're done
Better
He did
Darius
He's never done anything that even compares to run away
I do like runaway Kanye
I know I'm wrong but
Don't act
Set song
Should I just wait in the other room until you're done with it
Call
I don't know what song it is but it's the best
That's the best Big Time Rush song
One thing that I love about your
Hip-hop fandom
Is how complex interesting the lyrics
Good stuff
Soggy bottoms no no no no
From party
Not one
Seems like if it was in 40 cities Nationwide
0 time is almost like the Main Street
Straight yeah it's almost the same way Alex
Kind of given up
Ignoring
He's even been
He's been brought up on his
Couple days before
Doesn't do any coverage
Doesn't bring it up
But he does
Have someone by the name
Barbara Fisher
On the show
Is a
Very
I mean like in that world
She said she's the heiress to the Fisher-Price
Found a
What is vaccination
She's a very big ant
Vaxxer
You guys got to stop
He's he's always easily
He came out the womb Auntie's ass really don't think that's a good idea
Not good
I mean it
Just a little bit
Cowpox
Can give him cowpox
You're right actually
You didn't know that
I don't care
I don't care to talk about her interview
Evax Non-Stop
Yeah I just want
Because
It's so disqualify
Like the fact that you
Making this argument
She's coming onto Alex's show to talk about
In the fact
It means
Know any
Resume.
It's exactly
There is effective as the company
Said they are
And then
You should have said them back news should have nothing to fear
Unvaccinated
Is it shouldn't be such an issue
About forcing
People to get vaccinated
That doesn't track even the slightest indication that she has no
F****** idea
Talkin about now
To anybody who hasn't heard the times we've broken the 100 times
Like for example
Orb
There there it's not a perfect science
And there's a lot of
People who are at risk
Like there is a very real possibility of bringing polio
Mainstream conversation
If if we leave the world where everybody
Could get vaccinate
Perhaps
That is correct
And that's why it's an appealing argument
Don't understand
Like
Thick if you are
You can't make this
Because you look like a f***
It means
Don't know
Directions
Well if there's one thing I know about virus
It's that they never change or adapt
To any kind of
Viruses from the very beginning
Virus Logan Remember When
Then bring it up
No that's what I was listening to
He spent the entire day that the tea party was happening
For 4 hours
Weird
Freeze dried food
You brings it Bob Chapman to talk about shorting stocks
Get them chapped lips out
Brings in Diamond
Phil Roberts
Lady to talk about
Again
She hasn't find
Madden
Do you know she's married
Lord Diamond Dallas
Goddamn
You should have said Lord
No cuz you started with this Diamond Lake
The recording has no idea what that mean
Yeah but he's doing great
Either
He saved a bunch of wrestlers lives
Yoga
He's also
Actually
Text Ashley great
Buddy just Google.
Going
We have a lot of rest
Fair enough
But if you haven't
Inspired
Google Google
And look up
P yoga
There's a number of
Profound
Inspirational stories
All right headlight
Or they were super
Overweight
Loved
Decided to try yoga
And then they
Lose
He's helping people that's fantastic
That's nice about
Search
DDP Yoga
Also Scott
Nevermind
Is one of the
Pro wrestling
Kevin Nash
He was outside
The two of them were
And then they went over to
The WCW
And in doing so pretended they were
Vaden
Federation has always wanted to do that
The storyline of them coming in as outside
Who came in to Blackreach
Havoc
It became the end of course
Coolest things in red
In the 90s
Steph
Afterward
Much later
Wife. f***
Strung out on a
Brink of death
Yeah you can watch
The matches that
Just was like
Let him
Is brown bags like looked at it and then
Wake up
To die and
Cayman
Got it
Yoga
Like
You was on
Like all his life
Hey now he's
Pretty healthy
It's awesome
I don't know if it's awesome
But the story
AR
Amazing
The only reason
The last night
Bigot
They sold out the Sears
Like no no independent wrestling
Has ever done something
So it's
The only reason ddps involved at all is because he was part of the aunt
Cody Rhodes
He was in a
My match for the NWA championship
Glacier
In the middle of the match
Alright
Great work
Why don't you want on the rolling tanjun you got A plus one this time you get a negative one
Yeah but all in
Anyway.
Even now
Year old man
Anyway
I thought to myself
After listening to
The 20
I thought to myself like well
Maybe Alex didn't
Realize the
And only would know
In hindsight
Right now
That was on Friday maybe Sunday show
Is going to be like
Holyshit
I didn't
Realized people were going to
40 City
I'm going to pretend I was on board
Even though
You on Friday
Coverage of people being
Hiding the fact they were like for guys
I put a camera with a
0 Folk
Guess on the floor guys
I'm so
I got at least check in on the 1st
Boy
I'll tell you what
Alex admits videos
I don't know what to feel about that that works
Reflexively
Yeah
I still don't know
Beyond that Alex back in the day
President
Would leave after 8 years and go back to their
But Obama's
Do that
As we look at it from 2018
He's metaphorically gone back to his farm
Did was Carter
And he didn't even go back to his Peanut Farm want to help other people build their own Farms
Peanut Farm which literally
What's peanuts
Is sort of
You know metaphorically when his term is up
Shower
The metaphor there is real rough
Consider what's wrong
Havasu
There's no way
It's amazing how
Like the only thing he has right now is
Access an influencer
Because everybody's
Cuz everybody hates him like them moments that he doesn't have access
No one is going to give a s*** about
Real debit
He has to stay the president
Anyway
I was like
Dude
You going to talk about
Right
Until he starts taking callers
Who won the college
When you talk to her
Listen to say
Their own documents like you always preach their own documents
Exactly
Is it okay if they going to call those guys like
Some friends you don't f****** believe
You put up
Everything
What's a verb
Labor camp stuff
Now that is real but that's more about the private prison
Just like that one that one
Constitutional Amendment that was like
No slavery was like
No slavery but like every put people ones
Kind of makes music
Brings up the
Which is
Eddie says they already Americans
Further not
Responding to this guy being like
Hey I try and get my friend to love your s***
Even though
You proved everything and
Kernel of Truth
To life
Still no mention of the Tea Party
Steve and Alex Jones video and goes
I have no idea what he's talking
About that is not because he disagrees or is very warlike
It's more like
What
Responsible
No idea what you're talking about
Probably intentional
So we have
One last quit
I looking for it I want to say that Alex
Also on this episode
But in the last year
He's got
Billion
Visits to his website
And 170
Individual
People IP addresses
Coming to his website
What rich
Is
From
IP addresses better
70 unique user ID
Showed up on his website
10 billion *
10 billion hits
On a daily basis
Boy if you
If you do that math in your head I'm going to be impressed
But I also think that all this b*******.
Crazy for like
Really large website
The top hundred websites if you look at them are all
Places that have
Like
Places like IMDb
Or Google
Twitter
Places that have like
Hundreds
Civilian
10 billion hits is
Absurd
Yeah but it would put him
Sepsis
Individual person
Giving something he like 1 billion 100 million hits
No
Oh no no no no
Because that's one do doing a lot of
Click
I've got the population of bar in Chicago
That's my fanbase
10 billion + 70
Play Morissette Map works out a little better
Ludacris
In terms of
You consider the population
Spread out around the world
Half of the population
I say absolutely no way
There's no way
I was like
I need something
Another caller
I thought you were a cuckoo by years ago
You are
Keyboard me over completely
What is the underlying Foundation
How are you
Become sore Droid
Oh yeah
One thing I don't understand why are you so
History
History search
That the more
Thanks
Are doomed to repeat it
I have been when I was about 12 13 14
To start reading history books because they were much more entertaining and science-fiction
Louis L'Amour
You live in Texas you should love Louis L'Amour
He goes on a really long time
So now we just bring it up at all doesn't bring up the Tea Party on this Sunday episode
He's not on board that caller might have had the order reversed
Like
You shouldn't be 100% on a guy's side
Before you ask
How do you know
Why do why do you know all this
Instead of like working back
You're missing your missing
Hero worship
How does
This happen
There wasn't
Why are you so smart
That works too
More less
And Alex is more than happy to oblige
I started
Yeah
Have you ever ready
Episode
Like
I know that this is like
So much
Over and over again
And most of the time
That is what will last
10 billion things he was wrong about
It only 300
65 days
How's like
How
What is wrong
Because every
It becomes a fraction
Bullfrog.
Sojourn this brings us to the end of this investigation 2009
I'm f****** glad we
We finally got through
Because boy I'll tell you what
We put it off a bit
And I feel bad that are listening
But I'm glad that we finally got to
Tea party now the new
We've got to the date of the Tea Party breaking out right now the new adventure becomes
How long does it take him for him to realize the Glenn Beck
Bunch of money
Yeah
I know but I got a I got a usurper
Secondarily
How long does it take him to realize
Bra tops Rose
On this episode
Soon from now
Or all of our narrative that we're trying to
Figure out play
Now
I have no faith that's
You know what
What's what's this
Like going this far back with this relatively nebulous of a
Like we have a concrete
The concrete narrative is when does he jump on the
Investigation
When does
Thesaurus
But that could also be pretty concrete
It could be but we don't know when it's going to be
2009 to 2011 Corvettes
I know you are concerned
Things like that says
Hello campus
Hated
But I didn't go
I was catching I will
I've been out there I know how to throw a stick
I feel like this is a weird level of our
If it takes that long it takes that
Biggest 2009
Roundabout
He's a pretty serious Flashpoint
George Soros
Becoming an enemy of
Wrecked in the same way in 2014 was another
Those are two pretty
Seriously
Demarcated
Soros meddling
By trying to
To give support to
Free speech
Movement right
When he was like you shouldn't kill journalist on your birthday 2014 it revolved largely
Before
Involved
So the theory
Could happen
I think that is zero chance
Happen
Frooties
Yeah you think so
I do I do
Directions by the idea
Because I think Bob is also
Propaganda
Please bring it up please
Downhill to Alex
I would be interested
To know when
Because based on the way that the Tea Party things go
It seems like he's
He's a bandwagoner who insisted he's been there
Big time
Interested to know when the bandwagon
Got on thesaurus
You know what I'm saying
Glenn Beck
Report about
I think it was an early
Okay
I really don't think that he was on it first
We'll see I mean I love that we have Miss
In front of us
We all kind of hope
That we get to the
Happy party day
Actionable results
No interest in it
Cuz I think it might
Because you still at this point trying
Posture as a Libertarian
Right
Libertarian is essentially
Purely Republican
He doesn't know that
Well I think anybody
I think anybody who's
I don't think
Take
I've been wrong a bunch of times
But I think my mind
My prediction on the ground right now
How is that
He starts
Notice that Ron Paul
Party
Okay
Restart
People gaining
Attraction from
He starts to see a lot of his like world
You getting popular is like
I'm not making money on this there's money on the table
I should already be there
How many retcon
He was
Elders of Zion
F****** walk
I tried
Flip Flip
But I will agree with
You even like
That's fine
We'll see what happens but I'm glad we're through
Fun
It's cold
Do we have a Facebook group
Too complicated
Confused by the direction
Bunch of reports
Tripe
Helpful for
I've heard that feedback
And also also in any situation
Not proactive
Towards
Psyqui legit
Yeah
We can't get on
Because they would
Absolutely
Flakka
Are you using
Plays the tracks
Running afoul of
Music
We didn't do it
Yep
Jordan This is been fun going through 2009 with you but
And that is the reason back then
He knows something
Holding
Alex