Alexandra Thurston color
Work around
They are fresh
What started a fire for
Bow drill
First of all I don't know the bow drill is
Shop class
Middle School
Are you talking about one of those things
Around the woods
I definitely tried I am sure I've never succeed
Have you ever
Made a fire with anything other than the lighter
Yeah
Propane
Not a later started I know that I have
But they've never been impressive
Little small fires with
For sure
I think that I've ever been able
Then transition that could build this whole
Cheddar's
Paradigm Central Missouri
Timbre talking about
Flame building if you started the fire with a bar Journal
I've never started a fire.
Hell no
Exactly
To give a shout out
All right that's a weird
That's a weird
But the wind is about our life
One of my best buds
In the world
Inform
Story about Ron Paul possibly being a gopher of Dominica
Remember that
What are we going to do this Simpsons ever exist
So anyway
I've heard that from there already
Yeah come on favorite murder podcast is entirely about
Get that other people have done I think we're fine
Turn off as long as we didn't mrs. long as we didn't
Contributed
Irrelevant
That but
I felt like it was our due diligence
To call that out
Intersex
Took a lot of the stuff
We end up talking about
Oh well
Perfect
Steph
And decided
Sports Chalet
First of all the shout out to
Tiffany congratulations you are now a policy wonk
Negativity
We also
Weston
I'm a policy wonk
Continue to donate you do know my
Hard yes on white genocide
The feeling of maybe aristocracy
That should not be held against
The name Weston
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
We'd like to have a high level
Someone who is
Is very appropriate I would like
To call them this
Even if it works the name they use
Call patreon
Thank you so much
You are now attacking
McWrap
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Find folks
Many others have
Website.com
Appreciate it
We talk a lot
Lot Alex Jones
Cuz I would have not had
Thank you gifts when I was text
Earlier
We're taking a little vacation
Here is an out-of-context drop
From our vacation
No problem
Alright fine
Okay
Going to jail and her been there before
All the sudden now I'm like it's going to turn into one of those episodes where you did a ton of research is like
This guy is killed Because he believes
Space for them.
It almost was
Anybody Google
Talkabouttd
The guy we're going to be covering this guy named Ronald far him
And I was looking at
A dude
Name Ronald Farnham who was arrested
For child pronography that's not good I don't want I don't want that to be
All the fun
Different middle name
Budget different
Weekend laugh because
Is the guy the only time
He's been arrested as far as I can tell
In 2016 on August 3rd
Ronald Augusta Georgia
Augusta Mall property
According to the Richmond County police report
You still even told law enforcement that private property laws part of the people
That is a good reason have a good reason
That's the only rest I can find where my don't know if you had better go to prison for that
The people a larger group or just
The people I'm sure he capitalized
So I already told you this guy
Let's jump
Introduction for him
Everyone I'm sure Cassidy from Project Camelot and very happy to be here tonight
So we've got a fascinating gas
And his name is
Ronald Russell Farnham
And I think his family name is somewhat well-known so I'm going to actually ask him about that but
Can I bring them on the show here just
Diane.
Ronald welcome
Hey Carrie how are you
I don't know how much I can answer about my
My name my phone
He doesn't really
Looking forward to making a lot of Futurama reference
Jordan going to happen
You can't get bog down on him not explaining his name
We have so much
Wouldn't even say
Nothing
I don't know I don't know
Want to know what
He's doing on the show
Especially given that like in the last
Couple months carries guest
To been a janitor who's
Discover the hyperspace Drive
Good Will Hunting
Three interviews with a rapist
Really you can't find a racist anymore
Is this guy
Coming to the table with
How to start this episode
He's owned
Sort of
Bonus
Curriculum vitae okay
I was saying that I'm I can't confirm or deny
But I don't
Let's
I know it's kind of
Changing your background so can we
We start out with your
15 years in Department of Defense
3 mi into the army as a signals intelligence analyst
Any Korean language
And I went through all the training with the
Language School in Monterey
Friends language
In Monterey for a couple years studied Korean
And then I went to signals intelligence School
Korea
Then I went to Fort Gordon
Korea I basically was doing briefing
In Korean
And Technical briefing
And then
Sergeant
Over there in Korea and then I came back to the
3 year and I
Fortunate
Dcct k
Which is
Somebody where we
Monitored
Korean serial
Korean language
For about 3 years
Was
Friday
Number 7
4 days before 9/11
Play Lele Lele re
Are you conducting a cigarette I don't know
He has told us a lot about where he was all the way up until 9:11
Very suspicious
So real dry
Just giving the name
Even find some
Google
Deceased
Gcct
I don't know what that is
Hey that's a great f****** show hometown
Great
No he's not we saw him live
Nothing
So do only reason
I want to play that and another
Describing his resume
Is because
Interesting to gear
His voice
He's talking about this so dispassionately and almost just would have liked
Laying out names of
Places and then like
Years I was there bought that I've got.
Right nothing in there's nothing in it that indicates
He's drawing from memory
It's almost like he's memorized a bunch
He's just kind of reciting
Yeah you know like the way that you memorize your your bio all the time and you say it repeatedly to any
Come to the point where you have it down as a roach
I am dead
Starbucks
You know I was like
Goddamn words episode
Hillbilly
Sing like that
Guess what
Esai Morales
Colors talking about like you know in Russian
And the guy sprayed up does no Russian
Conversation
It was such a good moment
Remember it
Play radio never expect the hillbilly
He'll really demonstrate some sort of talent beyond what a hillbilly should
He busted out some Korean at any place.
You know Korean but
Cannot prove
But from that resume like I said
To be a memorization
Part of the brain
Does feel that way from the way
I meant beyond that
From what
Describing I could just a like
Maybe you were a trans
Insulators
4 something
And then you're putting on a bunch
These departments that he's describing
Department of Defense is never going to be like
This guy is lying about working here
Because then every time some
I'm out and said that they work there that after
Either deny it or that would prove
That they did work exactly
Game that they never get into that blows
Any kind of seek
His
Entirety
The Department of Defense
Yeah yeah yeah
I mean it sounds more like you just worked
Translator
I mean but it sounds more like
He was translating briefing
There's a good chance about that and that would probably necessitates some level of clearance
Shirts
There's an outside possibility he had to
Some sort of low-level clearance
He's turned it into
Something else years of service
And then he left
Right before 9/11 but
Because after 9/11
911 brodbeck
Contractor
War right after 9/11 and wash
DC working on
Road map
I was working for a company called Grayhawk
I looked into it I can only find a construction advising company on the
Coast called Grayhawk
I don't know what you're talkin about
But any called critical node mapping
That actually sounds like something
Construction Company would be
Did knowing
What you want to know where nodes are before you start building
I don't know
They were basically working for CIA at 4
2 map of the United States of America
They're making a huge spreadsheet on all the areas
Anion and protected from terrorist
The note
Mexico
America
And then in South America
My timer
Southern
The man
Northern command
Stood up
Is he setting up a northern command in southern command
I don't know what's coming man we're just
Alright because
I feel like what I'm hearing in our future is a command Civil War of some sort
I assume Northern command where's the blue
Sure Southern command which put him in charge of counterintelligence
South America and Mexico and the surrounding area
Korean
What
Aries nose at 2
Give me some note information can't know they're too critical to be public information
So I mean look theater
He's just following basically online
Conspiracy world
Narrative
Grayslake North cam was created in 2000
They stood up
Is what like
A lot of the people
Like the Alex Jones
News of the World
SeaWorld
Of like they were that part of a takeover
Which you'll get to
Next quit the South will rise again
So you know the language they stood up
Yeah is what I'm interested
Rebuttal question
About that very thing
The fuc
Manhattan area of responsibility
Free 2000-2002
Fair when they stood up
Canada United States
Mexico
Just want to ask you a question
Northern command
You really been open for business yet and they were taking on their area of responsibility
So round to end of 2002
When Northern command open up for business again
United States of America officially physically invaded
The United States
With Northern man
So
They open up for business is like with a storefront operation did they start small and then
I don't want to work
Neighborhood
The United States basically invaded the United States through northcom
Yes in the United States
Previously in 90
Started
I don't f****** know
This is just
Very Baseline pay
How do you say
He doesn't sound like he's old enough 49
Is 49
He says he's bored
We're getting a bit into the weeds
Resume which I think is really unimportant
Yeah
Laying this out
Because
Most of this is
Completely on
Falsifiable
No one's got no one from North Commons
Going to be like f*** you
Have a long-standing rival is like isn't the every year there was a play the North
South County football game
You would think blue and gray somehow
You're welcome has great
You think
My friend
Supposedly a contract
Doing high-level terrorism analysis
Score
Speak Korean for Central Command
The north northern
She was he says he's around 1 that was happy
Nose
Picture of it
We are
Invaded by the Department of Defense
Skier in the United
Who does who did you all report to
Northern command
Northern command is headquartered in
Join cheese
Are we talkin joint cheese
Work together
One of them
When you were there under
I don't know who the Northeast man top guy was
General
General guy who was in charge of sex
Around that but he was also like
Is directly involved overseas around if he was reporting directly to General
He is someone who would have gone before conch
General had to test
Pacifier in front of Congress
The justification
Before the Iraq War at stuff like that
I don't know I did my research
Big dude
Military circles
Use my direct
Supervisor or is my general
I think you probably f****** nose
Dude
Quick
And then just hung up and she's but she's doing everything she can to be like
President was
When this happen
Real talk
When I was five
15/16
I knew who this
The district manager was
Over our company
Even though they didn't have any like influence in my life at all
Yeah absolutely
I don't remember the district manager's name now but the CEOs
Bob
Cuz you want to drive over
And he showed up one time
He was a lunatic
I think I'd also probably helps you out
Even before you ever showed up at our
Me working there
My point is that if you are higher up in centcom
And
Absorbed or taken over by northcom
You get a f****** know who the guy in charge of North ComEd
Especially if you think that that's what happened if you already definitely resent the organization
You're probably
Figurehead up over it
So I don't believe a lot of this story
Nathaniel Taylor
Hillary took over northcom
Why doesn't anybody just ask
Might as well
I do want to say that I don't believe any of Ronald fart
Story so far
But
Credit credit
In this next clip
He blows 9/11 alright
I started diving into that
Information and I found that
All the information from September 8th
This is him talking about when he come back
Is a contractor
He's looking a top-secret material that he has no business looking
A felon
On this show
Human gestation
Information
Project pretty sure it's a hard felony
There was nothing in there I could find about
What was going on
Few days before and a few days after.
So
Reclassified it but
Yeah
My theory would be you that's on a very strict need-to-know basis
Solo level contractor can't get access to that information until Kerry Cassidy
Pretty wise of the devil address hold on
Let's put that in another box you don't get the
You know you have a couple of days
To think about it you're like
I bet if we give every Yahoo
Access to this information
Where to get a lot of conspiracy
Right there
And you can't hide that forever
You can classify all the documents you want
But those
Especially
Yeah
Especially 17
Years later
One of the smartest
Detectives ever
Shows up on
Project Camelot
Organise that for sure
What I discovered in looking at that even up to the you know September 7th
What is that
Everybody who was involved in the
Terrorist
Terrorist you
Everybody was under surveillance
Classmates with two of the people two of the Olympia hijackers
University
MacDill Air Force Base
Leo University campus there
I would go to class at 9
Want to finish my bachelor's degree
Around 2000 I finished it up
Second
Believe
Level top secret clearance
And was a high-level Korean translator and got hired as a contractor
Do counterintelligence work at all this stuff
He didn't have a Bachelors
Which I know it's not impossible but I find
Very unlikely
This is
Look
Street smarts
Stroop
Does he
They were used in the reporting
Going to get married
Making Communications
We're using the code
Getting married recurring 20 we're off to get married everybody's leaving to get married
Mazel tov
Around the same time we would stand outside class weights for going to our next class we have a break and we would talk
And they were telling me how they were going to get married but they wouldn't give me any details
It was farthest thing from my mind for the 9/11 operation
I like the proper offer a second
Where they getting married
There's a very high likelihood
These were not
911 or anything like that
He just was in
It was weird
I'm guessing
Is as likely as
But who knows
I started thinking about it
10 years later
Even
What do you mean your conversations you had 10 years ago
With random strangers
Talking about dude
Week
You shouldn't you should have been like
Do I have a photographic memory so I can do this this whole thing
I can pull it right away
Otherwise unreliable narrator
You can call all this back that would
A bit of a brat
Well there is one thing we know about it
I am so far
It's a very modern
He explains why his time as a contractor ended
I don't
If there's ever been a fish story
The National Security Agency emailed me
Depuy other analyst
Specific
Problem
Be back or solution or what my thoughts were
So I put together a point-by-point plan on a house too
Stop terrorist activity
Any more terrorist activity
.
Very simple solution
And then demolished
Security agencies the next day I got my Commander's office
Email out
You know they wanted information they wanted a solution
And then the next track
So I talked to Maya
My manager my contract
Resign
Guy just solve worldwide terrorism
They got a fire in forest
That's rough now it's Tanner of that conversation
Go back and look at the
Which I do have access to
And I have a photographic memory
Sorry
Can't wait to go to the guy says
Did you write this
Email and send it to
To the National Security
Agency
He said
You know
Can't run the world
Well.
Hold'em
You know that my aunt read created
That's crazy I don't know why
You know what else is crazy he wants
Anytime would be great
Not like because you came up with the idea and sent it to the NSA
Just f****** come on
Actually I think I am
Is Alex Jones
Reverse
Tell you what
Possibly is how he would end worldwide terrorist
This is a very simple solution
If I don't want him to kill all the
So
He has missed
Supposition I guess the Deacon and worldwide terrorism
Which carries like a man
You know
Terrorism intentionally
That's what's up
Which leads today
They wanted me
So I told them I go fine
I'm going to resign
To stop
If you're not going to implement this solution
I just know that you don't really want to and I can tell by the way they were behaving that they don't really want to stop terrorist activity
You probably know as well as I do that it's
It's an operation it's a money-making
Well it's also at you know it's it's the state
Arm of the state
Trying to put fear into the People by creating false Flags actually it wasn't supposed to say that on my YouTube
YouTube channel so
Creative
No creativity can't say it
Supreme BFF
Because she got the
Oh she's not even not allowed
She got in trouble because she had people on
Berkeley calling
People crisis actors
About
Particularly Parkland
Shooting tragedy
Sushi
Contextualize
And turned it into
I'm not allowed to say false flag on the show anymore
Which I would say
Even if you literally weren't allowed to say false flag on there anybody was paying attention to be like
Oh you can't say FF
Abbreviated
No no don't
You scare the public by
Follow Friday
Oh no I would never call them prices ha
But they are CA
You know what I'm saying they've got a good talent agent you know what I mean the government was trying
Terrorize
Putting out the fire
Fantastic Four movie
That is not that's not wrong
Visiting King on for my neck
Why can't I finish a f****** book if this a****** cat
Before we go
Terry wants to know like
You were a contractor with top
Top secret access you were clearly going through in like trying to find
Information
Definitely
Outside
Cuz of your job
Why the f*** are you snowed in
Sing like that you had access to all the information
You didn't become Snowden so how did that knockout
I started investigating
What's 14 Terry by the way
Find out
Who killed JFK and I started looking through the top secret messages that I can
Find
Where I was working
And this is why I was in Korea
So this was 90
I'm sorry to hear that
Start to sit through some of the Intel
Find out about the story for JFK
Cover story about what happened and who was blamed and it was basically
Play pretty-much
The same cover story
So
I wasn't going to get the true answers
Because
In the military
Information
Compartmentalize
So
He didn't become
No because
Top secret files
Anyway
Well I was in Korea
And I had access to top-secret information
I was bored
You know like most people
So I just started looking into whether or not the government killed JFK
Go through all their top secret files and for some reason
Even the government's top-secret file
Say what the cover story
There's some sort of narrative consistency they're even in their top-secret files
Tell you the true story that's something of the implication of it
You're not doing a beta dump
Everything I found wasn't much anyway which
He's making this up
He didn't have access but he's pretending
Strong theory about that
Now
That no matter what you say
Even if you have access
To the top-secret documents themselves
Conspiracy theorist going to
Crispy rice
There's no convincing somebody like this dude
That's what's going to happen
What's going to happen right now
Is that everything
You're going to go very wrong
Everything
So insane up till now what are we like 36 37 minutes
Just being like
I don't believe your credentials
And that's not good enough for a Project Camelot episode
I need rafters
Or I need something of that level
I believe it or not Ronald far him
Delivers
When I resigned I immediately started writing
My first book
Second coming of the Messiah
Which way is
Autobiographical
Reach that Tipping Point
Say wait a second this is wrong
Something is wrong
I'm not going to take this anymore I'm just going to start doing something about it and I'm not going to be part of this anymore
And so
Emotion that I went through with that transition in
The story witch
In the second coming of Messiah
The story about
This person who decides
Save the world and come up with a solution
Modell's
End to where we are now
Illuminati in the powers-that-be
I really think
Duration of
You're the one thing
Israel
Now
Cover story but I think the bloodlines
Thousands and millions of years
Is Illuminati
Black Power
Steven
Pretend
Information information
I hate
Because he's never going to
To say I am
The new Messiah
Oh yes
He's described his book as the sequel to The Bible
Messiah
For fucksake
So is it is autobiography
He does describe it as autobiographical
Spell and the first part is everything leading up
To him finding out
The movie visit
Even if it was free you couldn't afford it
Be the case in the book as well I didn't read
Read the book
I think that he puts himself in character in the book but it
It's supposed to be here
Female character who goes to Hollywood
Two balls the new Bible
Or something
It's
Wild
Clearly on at least
Some
Very real level
Thinks he's the Messiah
No
There's a possibility
He's the son of God to per se
I think that you might
Using the term Messiah
To be like
I'm going to save the world
Servexpress
Which I fixed
Feeds into her
Solution for worldwide terrorism
Everybody do what he says
Which again will get you in a little bit
Not to be
Badland
So why
If he is right White
Can you be more into
This isn't that was the most boring I've ever heard a person talk
Spoiler alert
Twitter
We won like
Over
Amanda
Manny
April 21st
One light
With that low of a social media presence
I feel bad about how traction weekend I feel great
The Messiah
So knowledge fight
Rick and Morty
That's his first book that he started writing 2016
But Carrie brings up here because
He's got a new book
He's working out
You're actually aren't you writing a book on a Bloodlines that right now another book
What I'm writing the screenplay and in developing it right now
All the lines of Destiny
It's about
These 13 major bloodlines
You're controlling the physical domain
We're also being controlled by the archons to work
Rolling them vibrationally
Demonology Satanism sacrifices ceremonies energy
The laundromat I want
He's not done isn't chocolate more about this book
His work
Specifically non-fiction to her
Busy
Real to him
He's like I came up with
The greatest
Bloodlines that are psychic
Controlling the world chat like that so
Physical world of course being controlled by the demonology
The Satanist what are the Angelic being
But they're probably
David Icke talks about the archon
I think they have come up on another Project Camelot episode
We've done
Feel like there's probably a
Vibration
Cancel this group of bloodline members who are
Assassins
For the different bloodlines
Decide to make a break from all of them is that
Concern is giving information to the different bloodlines
Uncertain timelines to manifest
Skorts
Different
No assassins in their bloodline to go kill
Baking shipping to the timeline that they want and it's causing a lot of different Mandela effect
The story
So
That sounds like a cool
Story
I thought I thought the Google that we got from the earlier was going to be
That we're getting into her pool on bed lights
You're full of s*** dude
He is not having a good time
Refuse therapy at
Do not understand the Mandela effect
No no I just don't understand how he thinks that makes any sense
No I mean if they can if they can move
Zurn so why do you need certain to Divine
Which
Timelines are best for you if you can move between all timeline
Whenever you want because and all timelines are simultaneously occurring
There is a big spooky machine that exists in the real world and a dumb people are afraid of it
It lends you like a little bit of you know like
Magical Realty
Magical realism
Concerta hidebehind like
Causing people
Assassins to go create Mandela effect all over the place
Steam Bears I'm not sure what the
No don't worry about it
I'm worried because you're worried about
I'm not really that worried about
Berenstain Bears
Actually spelled
Maybe that's why they had that
Yours beginning of that clip my dude
Because he wants to
Inject some sort of like
Real Steel
Into movies
Is the other Mandela effect
What was it Sinbad was in
Cuz I can
Second
There's a bunch of kind of fun
Cuz they're like they do take a little party O'Brien
Kind of remember though I don't
Get it
At this point
Carrie is like
I know you are not
Fight
Need to know
If you actually
Show Business
Because he's presenting himself as like I've made
He doesn't write books you write screenplays
Cuz if you wrote the book
App for the best original screenplay Oscar
Andy Gibbs
I would say the worst answer I've ever heard from
Can you elaborate on how you kind of
Are you in the business seriously or you are you aside liner
Where are you at
So I moved to LA in 2011
I started doing
Extra work
Movies and TV shows
Enjoying the Screen Actors Guild
Member of The Screen Actors
Who keep calling here with his story but I want to
To point out the differences
Compelling story
Any story about the time he spent
Top-secret work
Do you think Gage been this story
He's remembering
$3,000 to get my
Do the hundreds
That's his brain the part of his memory that actually has emotional
Intuit coming out and bring an X
Information cuz that's how human brains work
The rest of it
Is memorization
Gibson
Credibility
To the other parts
I just want to point that out very clearly
Play
Doing commercials are getting paid
Voice overs
And I was here in this floor
So I moved to LA
Wanted to take it to the next
And then I realized that
I just had this
Produce and direct and right
File the paperwork
So that's what I did
Heard that
You don't want to try if you're going to write something you're writing for
You don't want to try it
Your opinion
Do you want to just have some kind of a strong voice
I'm going to waste all of my spend all of my time
Grossing movies of all time
That's a very
Appreciate movie
I want to be able to retain my voice
So
I decided
Hollywood and Vine
Woman who wants
Take down the global military industrial complex
Hollywood
The sequel to The Bible
Second coming of the Messiah
So
His book
Is in the movie
Sprung
Goes to Hollywood
Hey babe
Thor games
The sequel to the Bible is just the second
It suffered from the sophomore slump
The new part
If you got the gold the golden tablets
Forgotten books
Lord of the Rings The Return of the King
You do
He got
Within you got the prequels of course
You have other
Just text
Yeah I forgot you got sumare
So this guy
A little bit late is a little bit behind
Clowning on him for like being an extra
I'm a little bit
I'm being extra if you like
Just want to do it to have fun or
You know if you want to try and see what it's like to be on a movie set that sort of thing
I think there's very valid reason
Think it's something
I think that is something that most
People in it
Don't be as a viable path
Towards beginning
Further entertainment
Maybe just a little something you do as like the way I smell blood
I don't think that's going to make me a phlebotomist
I have a
He's expressing
Sort of
Until he decided I
Start out like
And then from there
What is filmography
Hey did you even IMDb
I just use on Imo
Maybe I'll pull it up
I think it's
This movie
Live TV on America's Got Talent
Guinness World Records on Wild
Drummer is that right
Summarize the drummer in some bands when I was earlier in the military when I was in high school but
I actually was just
Cruising Craigslist one night when I saw this ad for a talent casting director
Wanted to know if you could do any of these different thing
Can I play college baseball and I still play baseball
A picture
Send it to them
If I could break the
Record the world record for hitting the most number of people in 1 minute
You look like you have
Something on your tongue
It's come out the mouth
He's there plunger the people because he picked baseball score
Logical
Magical uses a challenge
Arranged
Locomotion of throwing a baseball
Not the same
Do you throw a curveball you throw good punter that's an old thing
It's the same as
Semillas you got to go over-the-top then you got to make sure that your brother
Did somebody
Testicular back
I would say that it better
Credibility as a
Or something like that
Seems like that would apply across a wide range
So he was on America's Got Talent
Who is the world from thousand years of Torment that we have existed
The next ten thousand
He was on
Even Jesus blew it if you'd
Kill that kid
This guy's a mere babe in the eyes of the Lord it was weird
Jesus through a plunger through a kids back
He's trying to break the record at the time was Zero could Plunge
Guinness World Records
In America's Got Talent
Do that on America's Got Talent
The book with
Someone who hired me to write a book and
Howard Stern
Howard Stern that would be help us get financed to get on his radio show so
Another
My friend from Pennsylvania we were on America's Got Talent
I gave Howard Stern a copy of my book or our book
Crazy Journey
Okay but
That's the right response
Had you
Department of Defense
I guess JFK I would say 9/11 was your butt
And you throw plungers now I would say
Larger part of the show
Very little to do with him
Specifically
You trying to get funding for his f****** movie oh that's his goal
Farnsworth
PT Barnum
Ronald
This dude
I don't know how to talk about this
Because I ate
Tubi
Groupon necessary
They go on about tractors
The tangent about how he was homeless
For a bit
Because we're making fun of
It might lead us down a road where we're making
In front of homeless
People unnecessarily
Sensitive
And not mock him for
For being homeless
If he were homeless
Insisting that he was there I would have far more for him than I do now that I know he is not home
And the other thing is that you
You have to listen
Entire long jump
Make the point
There is no point does he actually described being
About living in a friend
Kitchen for a little while which is not ideal Circa
Struggling actor
Write my point is
That
I do want to make fun of him for being homeless
But I do want to make fun of him for what he says
I was shooting on some TV shows on the TV show
Catering for my stuff my movie
Let me move into his garage for like 450 a month
The welcome in East LA
Everyone just happened there
He's a racist
Traditional
I would like a better what's up
So that's when he tried to do the caption you get it wrong the first time you just reshuffle man give it another go
I didn't want to live in East LA
Become
Project Camelot
Right
Expressed discomfort with minorities
So in this
Jordan
Troy
We've already reached
We Everett
Okay cool
Clip
After the races part though now I feel like he's going to call it the final solution and I have problems
This clip starts with him saying
Was looking into the solution
Got it
There's not much before it that helps make it makes
9/11 not involved
B like
He's the Messiah and that he was a extra an autobiographical
Movie Bessemer
Bible
Vape juice
Be enough
For me to do this episode
Gets to the solution
Okay
Man-o-man
This is bad
Wednesday
Scary monsters
I think this is
Dumb
One of the things that's a part of it is the promissory note
Video about the promissory note I started looking at houses
Except for value bills
Doing research
Our
It's really our vessel that carries our soul around
Everybody into a bonded moditi
And we have an account that we can use and we can accept
For value
So I was looking at trying to bring down the government and say we need to get rid of the Federal Reserve
He's a sovereign citizen
Hold on hold on it gets so much
My reality show
Things like that
Concept of the promissory note
Making his own promissory note
I'm doing the research based on on that video
Was that the Federal Reserve
Is it Corporation
United States of America corporation
United States
Which is not the United States of America that the United States
Series of countries
That we all call States
United States of America corporation
How to deal with the Federal Reserve operation
Two forces to use the Federal Reserve Corporation
Promissory note
Whatever whatever
Search
Operation operation
Unless you remove yourself from that whole situation
Uncapitalized
Facebook
Write your own promissory note
You want to autograph it
For value
Except for they're committing the felony of MS
Honda
Public office
That sounds right
So you make an offer
Honorable in court
They're answering
Accepting accepting
Your offers
Shortboard
Promissory notes
That I had credit with orange
I even started creating
Dexter
Promissory note
I want to be real quick
It's not Space Ghost
Hey
Kentucky shark has always been their dad a shark on Whiskey is mighty risky
It's still.
I look this up
Credit Union
Is clearly who he is
Wikipedia
Because it's the pollution
You got to see how it plays out at work
Deposit
And this was something that was punishable that I was doing it was fraudulent
Then they would come knocking on my door and then I would say
Credit Union
My account
Did she Financial Officer resigned probably coincidence
Donald Trump
Space Coast Credit Union
How many misconduct in public office
My promissory note they shut my account down at Financial Officer resign
How'd that go
Get out tender our promissory note to the bank deposit feed numbers into our account
Somebody would have come to my door and said hey you know you're under arrest
Broad
Sir
That's the solution
Everybody right $2000000 promissory note
Autograph them do cellular numbers in your
Solution is still we get Federal Reserve
I think this is the first time that we've legitimately had Carrie bring somebody on her show
So she could laugh at how stupid they are
I think she's having a good time
Junk on this idiot
Duncan Bridge
Silence
It speaks volumes
I didn't get that two million right now
That's
Went to the CEO
Promissory notes are real
Pam Bondi
Promissory note
Crime
Is because there's nothing being done
You know like if you
He was trying to do this with that like
The crime that will end up catching up with him
The money he still owes
Yeah usually that comes back
The bank I've written a fake check
They can just throw them in the trash
It is a crime and then you start to use that money which is
Dumb witch
Kind of brings us to our next
Quit
Because that's what Sean David Morton did to the
We talked about it on the recent episode Sean David Morton
Frequent Project Camelot gas
Supported his income and
I bet
Deductions
Order to get millions of dollars from the government
Because until they look over it
Through the cracks you could fill out a complete
Reedley fraudulent
Text return
And there's a decent
It might go through and you met
Might get a giant check
Yeah we're like maybe 35 years and they just
Depleted the irs's staff so you might get away with it for a long time
Everybody listening is defraud the government
Audits are scary because
Because some people
We'll miss
Report stuff
You report accurately because
When did
If they find something like that
You are
F***
They're going to be mad because
Tavares
Especially when they're four large
I'm not accident
They're intentional defrauding
The government which is what Sean David Morton is now in prison for
Now interesting later Let It Go prisoner Dan they don't have the authority to do that
Broad and Ronald
Is not fraud
Is because
Get me money from
But only because of the bank
Not going along with it the attempt is there
But
Malicious repeated attempts
Surprised they can come out
Maybe
$200 anybody good laugh
Houston property
But
Is really important
Jamaica because now Carrie is going to be like I need to tell you
You should be careful with that because Sean David Morton to prison
Financial advisor
Dave something would like 30 grand herself
She's not against
Plan
She just passing issue
Doing it opens you up to
To the government
Very much misrepresents mashonda
You're doing this
You filed these
Whatever you want to call it promissory note
And he literally got thrown in jail for
Kind of a similar thing in a way
What is the chargemaster IRAs and what a sham that is in gyro tab
Get all done his value or whatever it is
I don't quite get it but you know a certain amount of money
And they accepted it believe it or not
Payment for his taxes
And then they turned around and said he
Literally
For money they owed him or some
Something and they
Paid him
And then they turned around and said no they made a mistake and he was responsible for their mistake and stuff
They put certain counts against him
No no no it does not take a twitching of logic
For you to be like
Oh yeah you like that money isn't real and then you took so
It's not a we made a mistake on our end it's that the mistake was you were allowed to do that
Ever
Transaction
You committed fraud we didn't look
Hey
12 million dollars back
Something like that I don't know
Defraud the government
Even the government like
We're fine with it if it's like a little bit
I would imagine
I mean
You got to think about real resource allocation
The guy isn't making another movie
Ronald
Just making another movie
Yep and we didn't babe
So Gary wants to know what his new movie is about the in revealing the plot of the movie we find out
He might be another category a cat
Genius
In terms of your
Making this movie
Ready now
Horoscope
And there's a message behind that
In the one I'm doing now that I'm writing lines of Destiny
Remembers
Attempt to escape
The Antarctic Ice wall
To get out of the Earth
Stacy archons
Enter find out who this
The architect
Alright well
Interesting concept it in his self
Swery Carey come out
Arctic Ice Rink
You're talkin flat-earth baby that's fun
We know from our last epoch
Plenty of them
He better predict
I would say that
Right up there with them
We are headed
For the
What Albert Pike
Putting his
Surono
Don't do that
And it's going to
Tire world
Hopeless
Stricken
Samurai
Fearful
Not in the position where they even
41 Albert Pike Road
Is turn toward the luciferian.
Bring me to Messiah for him
Preparing icing for a fake alien invasion
I don't know if they're going to have
Global war on terror
Blow up so much that it turns into a
Small nuclear war
Sure
Georgia guidestone
Are out there
The first commandment
Is to maintain a population under 500 million
The Georgia Guidestones are out there
This guy
Out there
Is really drawn from the hole
If anybody is ready to write a sequel to The Bible filled with as much b******* as you can cram into one
This is the problem with people having
Free access to the real
Let me Google weather
Memorize that generals
Databank in general
The thing is I want to unpack the idea of this fake
Alien invasion
Suggested that possibility
Together in a new one world government we have to unify against
Does alien menace the only way human beings really your night is whenever there's a
Common enemy well now him bring a good sup on Project Camelot
Kind of problematic
Because Carrie believe
Well that's what he would have to be a fake alien invasion
But see here
And I would say that in terms of the alien invasion well it's going to be a little difficult
Because you know I would say
That is
It's kind of hard to conduct
Alien
Invasion when you got a real one going
Stop
Booyah
Saudia.
Like a trio of
Close to dump
The first one
Do you know my whole thing is about that there's aliens already may be eating people for chocolate
All the time like
Maybe the Parkland shooting was really just covering up people on Carolina
Yeah
That's going to be tough
Right now
Quick thinking on my feet Jordan
I'm saying
That's why it's so easy to
Invasion
Even though the living amongst
To safely unsafely
We need
Fake invasion
ShopRite
Epic point
Ronald
I assume he doesn't come back with that
That sort of his AI
Empath
I asked you that question
Bad baseball players
Del Sol
Because that's what it was now Ronald's going to get back to
Slam his solution
Yeah which is just Auburn citizen
I can get unlimited money
Promissory note
And so he has a
Everybody we're going to be free
The evil central banks
No no no
The promissory note is accepted for value
Then there's no reason for most of the crimes that people are incarcerated for
I want to also say really quick to visit a good argument for Universal basic
Muddy the waters with that sort of
Reasonable thinking
Nobody's going to go out
Because they don't have to because they are they have their wealth
You're not going to have to go sell themselves or sell drugs
Make sure that
Something like this never happens
Obviously
The numbers
Okay
You know whatever
God I Am Legend
It's still not great
So
We have spent so much time
With the most
Credible women
In the world
To hear her credible
Credulous
Hear this level of
I know you're dumb
And I don't think you know your
From her
That's fantastic
So Road
And so
He wants to get funding for his movie
GoFundMe
Page
On the show
And now is the time
In the episode where I would like
Jordan
To guess
How much
Making
On
How much is he asking
He's been on Project
Week ago
And
The GoFundMe page
Was created on August
It's been about a month $100,000
The Messiah
Making a new movie
With the help
Of someone who gets it
Easter in the tens of thousands
The views
On all of her videos
How much do you think that he is made on this GoFundMe page that I am looking at right now
$65
Info wagon
I don't know
He's doing well.
Struggling
So
He is offering
Yeah
This promissory note template
Please show it to your lawyer
Show it to your Banker
Don't do it
Can't find any problems with a can and will
You know if you know that store to Gold salesman
But
Do not only offering the promissory note
He's offering you the
Oh okay that's good
Promissory note to Freedom
Which is a document
From the sovereignty education defense Ministry
OK Google
Will you can remove yourself from the jurisdiction of the
Estate sale
You don't have to have a driver's license
You don't have to have it
Security number
You do that
Can I ask you if you know how are you going to raise money for a film and not have any of those things
Introspective
Get people to withdraw from the government and we all start working together and Mast and yes I won't have to live
Federal Reserve Note
Right now
So I have no choice I mean
I don't feel hypocritical
I have to do what I have to do
And I'm not afraid to be uncomfortable
If you're preaching ever won a divorce themselves from the government and I'll set you free
And you haven't done it
I got to give you a pass
Yeah
You are
Facing your own advice to take it
And you've already done the promissory note doesn't work
I love them to carry is like
She does bring that point
Nice
So
Episode
Carrie do something
She does quite a bit
She tries to go to the audience
Because she's live stream
Do the people in the chat
Question
Does not go well
Lot of nonsense
You think
It's a good idea to raise your vibration
Hypocrisy
Kerry Cassidy
And also
Reinforce
Carrie
All right so there's a lot of nonsense going on in the Chatham sad today and so I'm
Basically being a bunch of people so acting like an a******
So I don't.
Okay
We don't want you and
Go elsewhere and that. Goes for the CIA trolls the pay troll
And the moon is out there that stupid s***
Is there
Alright so
Hey Carrie
Why you Banning people for speech you don't agree with
Carry all these people
It seems
Like
There's
Some sort of
I want to say like something like
That that she just did
With no compunctions or guilt or self-reflection whatsoever
May have occurred like
To her
Recently
Let's create a habit
You know it's kind of like
You set up rules
Kick them out watch like businesses
To do I don't understand
I don't know
Follow them
First Amendment
Dumb people CIA Shield
Jim Carrey
Cancel anyway
Bring up to the end of our journey with
Messiah
Album
Followed up Surfing With the Alien
Time with him
Jazzy doing
Joe Satriani
You doing all right
Haven't gotten any donations does GoFundMe
It's probably
Problem with his
Unable to give a promissory note
And have them then put
Maritime law
Call Manny
Feel like the odds aren't great is there not good so far
We are now at the end of the journey
He got killed for 40 Silver pieces
You could have just written Judas a f****** promissory note
You know the thing to is
Saviors
Pastors not been soaking
Concerned
Who is God
Earthly goods and s***
Overturning things
Temples
Give to Caesar what
About money
Sparks Auto Care
You check that out could you follow us on Twitter
Are we do we have like a group for people to go to where they postponed
Call Diego home tell your mother you're really where most of the action is social media
And you want to take one of us is completely off social media
Listeners I'm on there a little bit please
And if you want
To listen
Search
Find us the
Jordans
Next episode to Alex Jones
It's really important that everybody out there remember that Alex Jones
Probably killed.
Alex