Alex
Alex Jones
What's up
What did you do
Sunday
Where were you on the day of
No idea
No idea zero idea
What are you getting at
Questions are really starting to fall apart.
Opening one for a long time that was terrible now I'm searching
For the questions
Yeah I know that's why you kind of have to ask question
I don't know what I was doing
Sorry
Drinking a little bit different of a
What is OSHA
Boy popping corks
Which I don't mind I'm not mad at you
Bubly water
Whatever will be for them picture
Not from the Champagne region
But that is fine so
As everyone now knows I was Jones and Infowars account itself have been permanently banned
Trump Twitter
Twitter presence
NFL
This week Alex Jones
Washington d.c.
Go harass people during the Senate intelligence hearing about
Social
Well I don't know if that's really what the hearings were about
Want to talk about this is interesting episode breakdown
Random feelings about
New donors
Signed up to support the show first of all
Thank you so much you are now a policy
Also would like to give a big shout-out to thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Chase Bank $40 goddamnit
By the way going
It's so frustrating cuz they know they're going to give me the money they're just inconvenience
Bag of apples
You're making like 3 or 4 cents off of you got to do the scam
You are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Like I told you before
We have so many Dakota different Dakota R1 Dakota just make
Making a different account
In order to maintain policy wonk status
Without ever getting the globalist
Discount to no possibilities as being the case
The world we appreciate
Your website, click that button
Dollar Tree on to be like an automatic message
Two people when they donated gave them the password to our bonus section on the website
I think it might end up in some people spam filter
There are some bonus episode podcast
Exactly and I know a lot of people on Facebook
Hey so just as a broad message
If you did not get the password to that and you would like it please send me a message I will send it right to you
I don't like to withhold
It's from people just because
I want money
Or something
Yeah I don't think I don't think it'll shity
What's the what's the Vodka Schmidt
This the standard for like vodka
Congress
Congress vodka was the
The cheapest how much was that
2 bucks for a pint maybe in Missouri
What will go get some Fresca
Wolfman
One time I drank
An entire pint
Congress vodka in one talk
Me and my buddies were going to go bowling
And I'm the only way to deal with the
Before You Go-Go
One of my other friends are busy go f****** tag along with you
Answer me and my ex Josh
What's the pints of vodka before we go
So we just got booked.
The whole thing today
Very drunk
Very bad or was the night bad
We just got drink
Jordan how do you feel about the question up atop that would have led to that story as opposed to some dumb s***
What about Sunday
See if I can be edited
I sat down to get this episode together and because of the events of the last two days Alex Washington out
Getting banned from
Twitter I knew that we would have to do is do a present-day episode
As much as
My heart and soul
You got to do what you got to do
Okay well I know Owen Shroyer was hosting on Wednesday
So I
So I thought for sure Thursday show would also be Owen Shroyer
So let's go check out
Around
Before all of this from that
Now
Through that I realized
Based on
Interaction
How much is in studio here on Thursday
He went to DC for a day
Just to do that
The show on Thursday
So
I suppose so
I have a few clips that I want to play
And then most of this episode will be going over Thursday show
Being f***** with Marco Rubio
So
And it's kind of fun because we all know that a couple hours later to get picked up with her and he doesn't know it at all
Bear
But
Here is an out-of-context drop
Today
My favorite DJ call
There should be a police for specifically for that
On the Wheels of Steel
So great
So we'll start here on Tuesday which is the
Mistaken
Most of the show is about Alex being mad that everyone is saying that he doesn't have a lot of fat
Right it's really petulant
It's really Petty
And it takes up
A very large portion of the episode malignant narcissist
So he's rambling about how the media is weaponized trying to
To destroy your will
Trying to break your back
But Alex uses this as his example of how the media is
Demoralize you just military
Let's find out
Text Alex Jones
Anymore
Lawyers
What we're talking about
Full shots
This is what we're talking about
They know this
So is that it
What are you talkin about
This is highest traffic ever
So what
Fair
But he's just not telling the whole story
Alexa
Like
You had a massive spike in traffic
Drop off
Immediate drop-off back before or roundabout
Telling the truth but he's just using a sort of
Cheating
Great I mean
The New York Times
Whatever they're talking about this time talking about what happened
After
He's got kicked off stuff
He's using the immediate thing as like
Forever
Then the same way that whenever he got kicked off everything his app
Shot up the rank
Town after that immediate push
Because there is like that
Oh where we going to get this from let's all migrate
And then you see diminishing returns
You're not getting penetrate
Well not least of which nobody has any f****** attention
Celeb becomes non-existent two days later everywhere
When everybody you
We spent a good couple of days tweeting about it
And then it was
Talking about this he wants to tell you more about how is traffic
Check is better than everyone says
Surprises
First culinary wisdom
Your buddy Milo Hunter
Thanks buddy.
Milo is a member with
Have defeated you
Video
Victuals
It's on real Alex Jones right now
This is off Twitter
Visitors in the month of August
Aber
Relic they want to take you just talkin about his own
Traffic
He's the boy
Award Woods
I feel like he has done something superlative
Maybe it was a good soccer player gets a trophy
Player of the year
I don't know if I ever read any of his like biography
Know about his
Extracurricular skills
You know there's a relative
Actually not even in the realm of cannibals he's really not in the top 10
The Fine Young Cannibals
Play ever actually
It's driving me crazy all right all right
I'm so it is next one
No you get half-life alyx
Continues with the theme
What's wrong
Tubalcain
Demoralize you
What
Doggy style
News flash
Rick Moore
About that
That hurt
What rtj1
AutoZone rtj2
No idea what he's talking about that
Most of what we would have ended up
Talking about is traffic
How everyone says it's worse than it is
Just because
You know
It's fairly it's relevant
I listen to it
Still give you the insinuation that he needs more money is in
But they're also causing record expenses and
Or else the game is up master of physical Judah
We're winning the no one is motivated needlessly give him
If it's a
If it's also a tie
It'll be like we're destroying them
You have to walk the fine line with both of them or else his business
And rhetoric model don't match
I don't work
Until
Just about
Talking about
Disruptive
I can't imagine you don't know what happened
The only one who doesn't know what happened I'm the only one who doesn't have any
Avoid hearing and Marco Rubio
Really stupid okay well I'll just give you a little bit of a breakdown thank you
Alright good work
Cassandra Fairbanks
And of course Charles notable recent
Trying to push those fake
I doctored documents
About Chuck Schumer having sexually harassed
Along with Mike cernovich
I don't know if
Or disproven
That they may have made those fake documents
So they were trying to work in a propaganda campaign
Suicide Squad
He has tweeted while all this is going down
Gotten out of public life and life
Beast
This is a f****** kind of like I'm glad I'm not there
Hey you guys you guys do that work right now
Disrupting screen but house
Yeah I heard about that kicked out
Don't make a scene in the actual courtroom during room
He knows that he would also.
Has he waited in the hall
Marco Rubio is getting interviewed Quest
James Adam
General strategy
Conspiracy theorist yell at you and then expect
Respond to all of them or one of them
If you respond to the other 29
You respond to none of them
You can't handle my question
Set a trap for Marco Rubio
As much as I hate
He could then there's nothing you can do in that situation
The hours for coming in to try and initiate a situation where he gets to make a video that you look
Or Alex looks like a big man
Who are you
Time to do in that situation
Tweet something in support of
Conservatives being censored immediately after Alex Jones was kicked off Facebook
I don't I don't know
Like
Aren't you recognizing with the beard
That's possible
Like there's 100 possibilities
Is this a walking version of that weird magnet game where you have little
Beard on a little plastic
Alex
Juvly Pat's Marco Rubio on the shoulder
Which is inappropriate
You shouldn't touch
B-ball
Senators
Well it's because they are no better than the rest
Probably an issue that we should talk about
Class that is more likely to be attacked
Then a normal citizen
Generally
Like a remora
Politician
You consider that the sultan murders
Humans don't
Unless they want to be totally across the Spectrum
Always
Zpacks Alex on the patio on the shoulder and said don't touch me
Like. Like not like
Memes
Alex Alex
Rubio's
Take care of myself
Oh you're going to take care of me
Graphite is another trap
He touched him intentionally or some sort of
Thing like that where they
Get into a macho apostrophe
So he does that propaganda piece good on him
People that like the sequel to Lilith Fair the Macho Foster Fest
Not really relevant
So you don't that it works
Congratulations on your
You know publicity stunt
There were no consequences whatsoever
Reporter for CNN in the hall
How the camera on his face
I told him that he had evil eyes
He was a monster
Destroyer
History would remember him as a horrible monster
Understand
He was one of the people who was pointing out winter came out and said that Alex would be kicked off
He did the things that you've done in the past in the present
Yeah
Violated
I believe he was pushing
The listless
So Alex is like telling him that looks like a possum that came out of a cow's ass
He calls them boys you should know I know I know
Really funny cuz I kind of like
Alex
I got his camera off taking him to
What else more exasperated
I think this probably was the bigger problem
Read this and then also straight-up just yelling at those are real
Marco Rubio
Racially tinged
Targeted harassment
No other purpose
To have been there for 9 minutes yelling
With not getting anything back not having a debate
Not having an interview of any kind
It it just harassed
It's like a it's like a
Is that like a
There's some sort of crime
It was like
Your contention is that Jeff was on the up-and-up when he said that the reason that got kicked off with
But I don't put those words in my mouth
Apologize
That's that my interpretation
I don't think that
Alex
Harassing
Jack Dorsey in public
I don't think
Would be like
Oh my God he's
Come close to my face or something like that and then been like
Yeah I do believe
Based on the statement the Twitter put out it does make sense to me that the nine minutes of him straight up
Harassing
Individual
Who didn't deserve any of that kind of treatment
And broadcasting it over Twitter's service Periscope right
That's the sort of thing
Yeah you have the idea that
He's using this platform the twitter-owned
In order to broadcast that harassment in the people listening
Turn around and send me messages to Oliver
You have a situation where it's like
Okay this is absolute abuse
I don't say I'm not here
Trust his motives at all
They
Save
And I'm willing to accept that as a reasoning
With the caveat that he should have been thrown off long ago and we can just order
My personal reaction to a space on the report
Jack
Personally intervening to make sure that Alex stays on the platform
I am going to leave after
Personally
That's right that's my opinion
Absolutely recognize yours
It's it's 22 oz
I guess they didn't if he hadn't have confronted Jack
And he still did that I would probably be
Far more likely to agree with you
Feeling is my sleeping on it is that I would assume
That there was a robust conversation going on with Twitter
World
Yeah I am back was he like he was being like well
You know let's not kick him off you know he was personally
Vetoing Alex interaction with
I would not be surprised if it was enough to be like
Alright you guys alright f*** this
Let's just do it if you want hundred percent
And no matter what reality is Alex
Blue wall
Spectrum
Silence
Conservatives or anything like that
Action
Now be back for the problem that I bring up every time
Something like this happen
Twitter's entered dangerous territory
Do is you have to
Enforce these sorts of
Rules uniformly
And you can't do that. The world's pretty all right
The people at the hangers on the lingerers of the
You're opening up
An opportunity for them to cry
Every time
Someone does something
Similar
Pretty much that's exactly
Kicked off of Twitter campaign where everyone is posting
Racist harassment
Pledging my love
If Milos case study is any indication
It doesn't matter
Anymore now we have this President's Day
That is almost certainly going to be racist
Stop Twitter I believe in wholeheartedly with a world
Wheels
Did the other the other thing
I lost my train of thought
Mdcu analysis
They're obviously
No extraneous
Being a jackass
With his cameraman
I do remember the
Yeah it's just like
Nothing wrong
Kick you out of places
For doing
Things that are
Appropriate there
Fight
Restart the narrative is by comparing himself to the people who are protesting
Cavanaugh's
Confirmation
I also
By the way
If a lot of
Distract
The Kavanaugh
Also
This
Look
Let's hear it
This is exactly the outcome Alex
The reason Alec behaved the way he did in DC was
To either push the limit
To show that I can show up wherever I want do whatever the f*** I want
Or get kicked off
To further his person
Narrative
Preferred cuz the other ones no fun
Cuz then you push the envelope to an extent where
All of your cries of like censorship
I'm being
Forced out
They don't
Doesn't hold water that's true
So did he got exactly what he wanted out of this whole thing
I agree with you I agree with you I would normally not agree with you if we were talking about any rational human being
I would not agree with you because
Twitter's ability to spread his message
Absolutely Central to his ability
He's got to do that because he has
NFL on Twitter
Twitter accounts dummy account
Who actually give me they get lots of
Traffic is artificially on Twitter
False account
So I don't think that is reach will necessarily be all that diminish
By him and not being there
Hilda said martyr status to him
People still talk about stuff that Milo does on
To Twitter through other people using
Lester and the differences in also then put out
4 hours of radio.
So she has an operation in place
That will feed the content all these other accounts on Twitter will then push
Disagree with you on anyone
The timing of it is very suspicious
Considering
That
Kavanaugh is
Confirm
That's coming out about it
And stuff like that
To the point where we pretty much proved into things
That he has stolen documents
That he is going to overturn Roe v Wade
Opportunity
Types of braces
The only reason
That he was appointed
The only reason that he is the choice as we talked about
Earlier today
Is because he will do everything in his power to
To keep Trump from being indicted we believe that aurox presidential
What was the quote we should not bother the presidency with
Frivolous
All of that.
Frivolous of course
Why he was
Respect
And of course he knows that's why he was pick
So that's
Troubling
And that's the only reason that I have you
Conspiracy theory about this like I can't prove it and I'm not
Him becoming
Supreme Court Supreme Court Justice
What's the most important things to
Surviving
By extension Alex survive in a lot of stuff Rodger Stone surviving all of this stuff
So it makes the outlet
Completely buckled into Donald Trump
And having Mutual spiteful interest
Yeah
In order to get a ton of media attention
The hearings are going
So I don't know if that's the case but from a strategic Viewpoint I could see it kinda
Being
I mean
It does make sense
But it doesn't make sense because
Doesn't get
Trump is not going to help him
I think he does
You think so
Legal fees
Doesn't get hurt
I said Cookie doesn't give a f***
I think they still see that as
Last Hope for status quo
Bi-Rite field end the Mueller
Rogers can
And stuff like that is going to go away to
Rodger
How dare you insinuate that this
Gentleman
Rodger believe in trouble
The truth is that if the investigation goes away the possibility of them going to prison
Spaghetti
For Rodger Owens up the door
To Infowars business model Everlast
So will the whole plan is 1 sessions is gone Trump is going to
Find somebody who's going to end the molar
Almost
There's no other way
You can't get in trouble for that exactly
Sweet
Anyways
Guys it was nice having a republic that was good stuff for awhile like Crisco
Doing that election studies
You have every reason to go trying
Really cheat
Refuse to recuse himself from his own recounted that weird that that guy
Would want
Indications of really undemocratic Behavior going on
Very responsible of us
This is what's happening but you got bored of real possible
Well unlike
Do not believe it is
I believe that the Nazis are on the cusp of America
And it's really probably going to happen like this
And we need money and we don't talk about it
Pieology
We're just we're just fatalist
We're going to lose we're going to lose
Southern Glazer's being depressed
And he Compares himself to the people who were protesting
The Kavanaugh hearing
Have a kernel of something
Conspiracy
But I can explain it
The First Amendment
Disruptive
George Soros group
Alright
In the parking lot
And then video and photos of the disruptors
Smoking Gun
Caught a leftist Soros Bloomberg
Huh
You didn't know about him 17 years ago we know that's what Ali says alive
I looked into this
Do you have pictures of
The people who were protest
From someone
Bite proof
The issue is the connections are super 10
People who had money
Because they knew
Network type
Able to help you take care of
The fees that you're incurring by your civil disobedience
It's not a thing where they were getting thousand
A protester types
Now the guy is connected to some guy who works
For an organization that
We got some fun
Sure
You can just you can just dance on that Ballroom floor all day long
But the colonel truth is there's someone was getting money but
I think that's the dura Gore
I think that's pretty normal in terms of like
Co-op
Take the ideas like people helping out with Eva's legal fees
Very very normal
Yeah that's one of those big things that the Civil Rights Movement water
GoFundMe for his legal please he's trying to get paid for doing a wedding
Liquor store
Never never have ever had
What kind of crazy person would say that
So
Weber
Sleeper Patriots
For sure
Not asking question
Journalists don't do that
Alex looked
Just run
Well for Alex
Trophy
Well he was playing in the US Open
But I just don't they just don't buildings Arthur Ashe
Serena Williams
This Mexico if I'm going to say I give
I think it's bulshit but at the same time I think there's a kernel of Alex having a sign
So I'll give
Preemptive
Show up
In the front of the USA
Concerning
You called something new baby
Quotes quotes
Obviously
I love next
Everywhere the snakes
These motherfuking snakes
Awesome lighthouse
Set the point that I think is fair is that Alex
Like it's weird that I was there
I do think that's kind of fairs ever criticism
He would go
Domino's
Unbecoming of an adult
I do get like a they're talkin about stuff that I yell about all the time
I'm going to go just like him at the inauguration
Really pay attention to when this hearing was
Would Alex be there be like
Absolutely
WhatsApp
I thought maybe after Laura Loomer scream
Court
I think it was
It was really interesting
For me to listen to those hearings and have them be like
All the Republicans after you explained
Algorithms
And then somehow more like hey
You know how people are harassing women
What are you guys doing
Extra
Come on man you better
So a little bit of
A portion of the show
Where Alex
Is a b
Super weird
Groundwork for the narrative blossom
Wonderful
McDon
Okay
You never really never get
Exactly he wants to say
He's going to tease the throughout most
To the show
Need to sort of falls off in
The train goes off
The big takeaway
What's the big tackle
Level
Planning
Then being able
You don't know it's Dominic
Hammers about to fall my friend
Interesting Godzilla because
Godzilla Richmond retail
Result of overuse of nuclear weapons
Resulting destruction of
Japan that is altered and changed every part of
Japanese pop culture Everson
I'm further just settling the metaphor for the parts of America
Disaster that happens to the rest of the world when America is left
Nuclear fallout of
Create a monster that we have no control over
Rampantly destroys everything
We meet
Go back to a time like I'm not
I'm not saying shut down
We just
I have no time
Four arguments that we've already had in the past
And besides he has decided or distasteful
We have to
Get to the point where it's not
Like
We need to I hate to say this because I'm a guy
Who
Has a dirty f****** room
Until we do this like
Alex is Godzilla and he's right
Well and caused a huge
What
That's what I've been saying is that I think part of the
Investigation
Whenever the Koch brothers
Created the tea party going to be able to control this movement and then
Whatever they were able to get Greg ulation and everything and all of a sudden
It's gone wild and the Koch brothers still don't even understand that it is their fault that Trump is there
And now they're probably
Public
Alex
I'm living in a spy movie what happened
I f***** an assassin
Heed
He does sort of spell out what happened but he doesn't get into
Specifically
Threatening
Being Russian agent
But that's not that's not boring
That's a narrative
And we have a clip
I don't get it I got a Russian come on guys
It's a fuking idiot Alex comes back
From break and he does what I would describe as a
But not good
Pro wrestling promo
GameStop
It's a great song actually really interesting further wrinkled
His roots and forth back his hat when he was on on radio
What's called the final Edition
Because this might be the last time they allow me on it
For him like two or three times every episode
I'm not going to lie to you when I was in when I was in high school I was a drummer in the
To The Final Countdown I used to play that like a goddamn
Like to listen to the drums on that track you haven't listened to me
I don't even I don't even know if anybody else was
While
Because
Specific instance
This is the final
We went over the last time he was broadcast on kjfk
Kalb
Klbk
Jeff
Perfect
The last time ever broadcast
So
It is fun this is The Final Countdown Alex you're finally appropriate in playing this song
61 days
Robert Mueller dishonorable evil Wicked people with so many crimes somebody
Music
What is morals the North Star
All these lies and propaganda to try to turn you against
Has a push for the 25th Amendment to remove
And they're now him
That Red Wave is going to be woman's Blood on the streets who died trying to get illegal abortions
Will wind up getting women killed
Feather crazy
To just go down the line of conservative policies and think
Holy cow every single one of these will get more women kill
That would be ridiculous
Can't be based entirely upon
Envisioning
Take me to get you charged Final Countdown
Where I switched this is when you use the Bell on the ride cymbal
And a little bit of a drumroll on your left hand
Great
Produced by Mannie Fresh
I love it
Mariah
Help me get a job
I heard he got a job at Staying Alive
Young Jeezy better than
You know
There's a there's a weird sort of wrestling metaphor
All of those
Kingsbury said
It might last
Minute-long
Where all the things
He's built
Throughout the last
You know year
6 months
Certainly ramping a lot of some of the
Particular things up
For the last couple months
Would you eat what he's doing
Building towards the mid-term which is essentially his paper
You know this or like this
Between between wrestlers
Dead people voting
But he's built yet and the payoff is going to be whenever
Claims that
Enough Republican politician
So
Steelers Criminal
Grimes
Got some crimes up there I don't want to not have that conversation but I'd like to have it on better terms
Alex
This about
That bad
New York
A good
No these are connected
To Russian authorities
On the request of both governments
It was uranium that was
Confiscated from people who got caught with it
Would you call it a mutual investigation
On the Russian intelligence
United States
Intelligence
Agreement
In a very serious
International investigation
Uranium one thing we talked about at nauseam
Mikey went there with you on the tarmac for Clinton
Uranium to the Russians
This isn't those are you got to separate
Call The Offspring
Kim separate sorry
You have to do better even if your propaganda
Good enough
In literally every uranium narratives that he's got and say that it was all done
Like if you Jello cake
Yeah if you just if you just start saying that he was Merv uranium one time so now everything that I've
Whatever said about being near uranium is involving him you're undercutting your own conspiracy theory in a way that
Other conspiracy theorists Ruby like
Dude
You're making us look bad
It's clunky
Real real funky
I don't know I just think that
Uranium 911
That's who did it
And who also worked in the government
You know what I learned the other day
I learned that Jim Comey
Was the prophet
Secutor in the case against Martha Stewart
I don't know if that's true
Possibly he's never worked as a lawyer
For New York
It wasn't I mean if it's
Not true
I read it so I found bobcat
I found Bob Chapman
Newsletter
Everybody who's not I'll tell you that it is true
It is true it is true James Comey prosecuted Martha Stewart
Prosecutor is the lead prosecutor in welding
Leave her alone
He also
We predict that she's going to get off
And then like couple months later obstruction of justice
I know that Jim Comey was very wild
A whenever our history books are burned and then in 100 years whenever the fish
People rewrite our history
It's going to be a nice little factoids the guy who
Legitimately
Obstructed Justice with brave
Here's the main story and then there's that tiny little boxes like
That's fun
Also fun in that
It's very weird.
Very current
Players in
Context
How is How is
Is the white race
I tilted my cards a little bit too early cuz I forgot
That I know of always finding new
A Russian agent
Yep
Out of context which that on understanding.
What are they going to do
Pick you up Twitter
Couldn't
The folks
Oh yeah
Twitter
You better believe you got one
Somehow I know I know it's not
Free calling and Pollux
Pollock
Some good invention
Those polish tree
I'm looking I'm looking this up here
Pollux
You don't know what a pole
It's a it's a very long as it's
Oh
It just means
Yep that is at
I kind of thought that it might be some sort of like archaic language for like I was flummoxed
Flummoxed is to Experian
Flomax
Absolutely
I thought Parallax came into my mind
Not connected
Could be some sort of old-time word that no one uses anymore
No one else
Bull crap you
Not true
Disagree
Anyway
I would say that
This idea
Let loose
I don't think that's a big story
He's going to let loose with an Eldritch Polack
I don't think it doesn't like I don't first of all I don't believe
Is telling a bit
Inversion of like
I'm going to reveal something about someone accusing me of being
Because he's already read about that all the time
About that
Forever people accuse me of being a Russian agent all the time
Narrative so
Could you could you reveal about somebody
The interview where he got tricked into talking to Russian intelligence I mean about a person
I'm serious like black
Remind
Yeah
He's so narcissistic
You make any kind of bread again
Married to my wife pregnant
Don't know we have an understanding
Aldi
IWatch
That's what I do
He is
So
Small drink right about when you
Capabilities
I already already mentioned it's my position
I watched the entire video of his
Which is what it must be classified
It was very hard to watch
Just further
I'm in second because he had nowhere to go with it so we just kept
Consulting is a.
Kept being
Like a little baby
Call Cupcake
No he's not a woman
So
It was tough and I do believe that's one of the reasons
In trouble now
Now
I don't think
Text wife is going to make things better cuz this is the next day
Home of Austin
Dishonest eyes the biggest betrayal at weakness
Is it
To deception
I never said take you off no one ever took you
Just at that enjoyment
You might be insane
Have you considered that
You responded
Almost
Entirely accurate
And the reason that you should have that response is
When he talks about his interaction with Marco Rubio
To talk about is how like
He said he didn't know who I am pretend I don't exist
Manifesting
World
Where is like
I think
Marco Rubio probably doesn't know who Alex Jones
Might not have recognized
Deserved it
That's absolutely a deserve it respond
Al Jones interpreted as
Personal himself
Like I don't exist
You you think that you can just make me not exist by not knowing who I am well if no Alex
You're misinterpreting
I believe him
Because I believe
That he believes that those guys said those things
Yeah I believe they can hear he heard those things in what they said
Even though they didn't say it like
No I don't think it's that
He has no ability to
Subjective and
Subjective
Do you know Alexis
I had to wrestle with
Does a whole bunch
Didn't like me
Because they didn't treat me the way I would like people to
This world for me to recognize like
Bearded exactly how they should
Right
Booked
Hang out with them
It makes total sense
Experience
And pretending it's an objective
Has this running with Marco Rubio
His objective
Experience of it is
He's trying to
And the reality
Experience
Marcos
Just trying to do is interview
Alex is trying to make it about himself
And Marco Rubio
Treat it like
A heckler
And he's not good at dealing with hecklers
So he left Alex Jones kind of
Yeah
Steve hofstetter
Looks like my dad
Oh my God
Comedian 42nd
Management great
I mean the first
I'm a very strong
Support
Like
You need is Alex Jones comes in Fox
Let's say we ever have a live show or anything
Sing like that
Because that's the worst
Impossible
Handle the idea people actually accept
Yeah especially people who he wants to
So you accept him
You just like
That's your first ride
I got to do something
View
Maybe don't know about any of that
Tell me more about that
Get him to talk more about
The headlines
Eventually
Lotaburger
Thirdly that doesn't work
Go to the
Ways to
They're very
There's a ton of things that we found
Over the course of doing
Podcast
I wish everyone knew about
Things like
Did your mom throw you off
Can you talk more about that
That would be that would be more fun version of Thoroughly research everyone who heckled
If you would have no idea how to deal with that
You Alex
Do you feel
Comfortable with your life
Right
I don't know why I don't know where we jumped off on
This road but
I guess
I've never been a fan of the comedian destroys Heckler videos like by my dream has always been to
Comedian comes to terms with Heckler and they both leave his friends
That was always my strategy
Like to the point where I even like
No one should
Like
I don't know how to tell the story without you
Call the store
Okay I'll try
Okay
Featuring Anza
I was great
You are considered
Comedic Force
I was I was one of those
Kind of
Right
So I brought on stage
So great
I get on stage and
This guy just says
Prozac
You're an ass
The gatesworth
I am said
Right on stage
Good start I just got on
So now I'm
Interested
Ariel lead singer of Master
Weirdly specific
I'm not but I
If you want to hear up
Everything's over
I got it I got it
Oh yeah there's no
You guys like
You're an ass
You want to see my dick
Would love to see your dick
Yeah yeah
Starts doing the helicopter with
I give you dick ass Steve
Not
Superbird
I meant everything.
Because the bartender came out
Like sort of grabbed
Cancel
Show me where do I go
No
Removing
So that's what I wish Marco Rubio
Alex
You know that that is
Bestway
Goodwill
Because like have been a more fun headline Marco Rubio wants to see Allie
Alex Jones
Is the metaphorical guy
Kind
The floor
With it from there
The idea of like
Who are you
Is is fine
Right you don't have to
But I dropped you off anywhere you want to go
Listening to this
Don't take her advice
Destroys Heckler video.
So NSX
You crazy
Send a text.
Write something
Absolutely
I let him f*** my wife in front of me
It's all right with President Trump
Gross disgusting
Is all of those things
Call
Complete
Garbage
I mean the southerners Bard is just based on that book The
It's coming out
We talk credible
Probably
Lisa little
He's one of those people doesn't really destroyed their own reputation like
Alex seems to love him
Suggest that he should be given a gold star for credibility
Is reporting are actually true I have no f****** idea
The guy I know
And all that other stuff
Do that other stuff like that he's dumb and a racist
We can prove that
It is very very
Or like the criminal
Case against him
Obstructing justice
Should just be like
Cardboard cutout of his tweets
Oh yeah I know he did that
Going to lie to you
I will give him credit for stamina I don't care
Anybody who can wake up at 4 a.m.
Go to bed at like 1
Schedule
Weird circadian rhythm
Diseases that are f*** directly
Space by a biker but that's fine
BB thing is like when you are coming up with like
This guy stamina is off the charts
He's a good guy
Good guy
Let me tell you something
One the boss
Marathon
I'm really did
He's really nice he's such a good guy
Digging so deep feeling
That's what I want a president
Ability to stay on a treadmill for a while.
I need the I need a ball dance
Alex explains why he's the target
And I mean
Yeah
Hollywood
Cam
Great
There's a leftist global plan once they collapsed
Sure
Do you like
First round two or three billion people
Navigate to the round of 16
At the semi-finals
Got to have
Automated
Military forces and brown forces
Depression and mop UPS
For some computer models they've got
Human directed forces
Basically understand
The real reason I'm provoked
It's because there was a plan operation prepared
Reduce world population
Percent
I know I know you're real comfortable on the couch but
Man
Feels a lot like
Bad conversations I really don't know what the f*** he's talking about
Mean in the context
Countervailing
What
Countervailing Force
Push back
Sure that's what that's
All of it all of it
That's where we eat that's where I'm at
James Cameron leads to ninety-nine percent of the world's population
What's that what's that leave
7 million / 77
Enough for like
A world to work
You're insane
Every
Yap who survived
A pilot
Yeah that every pilot themselves
They all have to be pilot
Also they need
Food
You know that you're the real issues
The globalist
Is so worse
For the globalist
Then the current state
Pretty much
For the globalist in that scenario right
Is there to fill the hole
Google garbage
Do we live in now let gif
Bizos gained 150 billion dollar whatever f****** about
Whatever unreal about of money he has
Why would you want the world to be different
That's insane
What can you do
Climate change is going to do to humanity
He's literally just his version of what the globalist want to do is actually what the global
That is going to happen because
20 signor in the reality of climate
Where
If it actually address
Better.
Look and if it got even if it came to it
If Trump
Completely took over the United States and turn it into a fascist
Boiled eggs at least 100 years from now
We will be able to solve any remembered as a weird ass f****** monster
Hero
Baby crazy
He's only he's only going to 60
Destroys all of the world population out of their goddamn home
Creating an even larger Refugee crisis
Which will then of course we do more f****** Nazi fascists
I kind of look at it the opposite way glass-half-full kind of
Do you know do you know me
Wait
I'm good I'm good
Both both
Positive like probably inevitable
But I honestly
People are going to die definitely that's not good
But we're not going to go
Around the world and national stick
Real awful
Fine
But a lot of that stuff I think
Will be nipped in the bud visy Global emerging
From
What climate
There's a decent possibility
They used to get as like that will exacerbate
VI
The Troubles of
The
I think there's a decent chance of humanity
Just take a stand up and say like
Enough is enough
People are struggling
Get the business
And I'm wrong manufactured Alien Invasion is going to
To bring Humanity together of climate
Acceptance
No I know I know I'm just saying we talked about
How people ultimately help each other
Crisis makes a lot of sense
Seeing large population
We all go f******
A******
Of course
Yeah but they didn't just perform a coup and control all three facets of American government
Right
How was we not f****** just started
Leech
Is that
I don't know what you're trying to express
What are the ways to solve the disease
Maybe get a little better.
You're dangerously close
To territory we can't abide by
Political
Climate change is probably wrong
You know what it is maybe anytime
I am not everybody
Guides on my
I know but I just feel like empathy is what
Makes us lose
Yep
This is a clip that I considered sending to Alex
Because in the middle of the show Iran this Thursday
Gaunt
We should send it to Martha Stewart f*****-up about how we interact with
Oh no that's not
I don't
You know
It's not my business
I'm not going to send it to her
Who wants to let her know you know you know how
Wonderful beautiful listeners would never
She deserves to know this
I got but you probably already
Disappointment schools morning
Okay.
You going to pick me up at 3:30
You know
Even more because we're facing
Unadulterated.
Terrorizing
School in like
Insinuating that he's going to
Todai
Listen I hope you have a good day at school I know your math teacher has been riding you pretty hard lately
But that's really immaterial compared to the fact that you're about to lose your father
Is going
Murder
Murder my dad
She probably get you a path
It's not the plot of a book
That's
Really really
As you saying it on air
As if it's somehow gives him a boost of
Real
Don't I tell my kids that I'm going to die everyday at least heavily appliances
Kids turned out alright
Don't think
So earlier Alex called trump super glad that he's hanging out with him
Boston the group that
Sylvia Plath kids
Amazingly
Bright 100.3 Martha
Tell me another one
Baby
Great feedback
So here Alex.
Please withdraw
You didn't
It took you forever
It took you months
Frontman for Consortium on the East Coast you dumb prick
What are you talkin about
I'm going on the Train to Georgia
Before that killing
I can give him something to make him you'll have a heart attack too I just pray for President Trump
Rodger Stone
Okay Trump
A person
I mean this isn't new
Before
It's so stupid
We're going to do Kim
Also
How do you nuke
Involved not just him
What is are there any Target
That only have
The capability to kill
Are you sure
Okay nuclear material
Alex is 14 Stone
So I mean that's not new Palladium
Yeah anyway speaking of the devil
Ricky devil Rodger Stone
You can't be here
They're talking about that it was published
I'm inside the campaign
No time for that
Kind of
I understand why the New York Times
Publish it but not interested
Got to love New York Times
Do anything are you providing any sucking value know you're just providing a f****** b****
I don't even care 100% true that's a self-serving
Piece of s*** trying to assuage of conference is conscious in a way that you should not allow it
I should have received that in been like
F*** you come on this or go home and cry like a little bit
Oh you're trying to save the country well at the same time you're letting everyone f****** died
No time for it anyways
I just want Rodger Stone shows up
If this
New York Times editorial
I did it was written by
Read Chinese
Longest serving member of The George W bush cabinet
Why you would appoint such a person is an odd question or
Russia
No I think
Is Donald Trump
I say God I wish
God I wish
My my bigger issue is like
You don't know shitt Rodger YouTube
Talkingshit
This is just nonsense
So it's not be cool
Cast a little bit of Suspicion
Alex's
His narrative
But his version of it
A professional writer for the New York Times
Okay using a
Composite
Leekers
I don't like
McMasters
I like all the old Lakers
I would actually buy that more than
If I wanted to do that
Fiction writer
Essentially the same
Between fiction reality
The New York Times
Knows who that person
Well then what the f*** are they doing you don't betray our entire f****** country by doing
Holding up journalist
Has a journalistic
You protect
Published
If you don't know who the person
You do know who the person is and they refused to put their name on it I'm not going
They can't tell you who it is
I stand by that
This is Livin a journalism
Journalism doesn't work
Now
No
That the New York Times knows who
Yeah
It's Anonymous to the
Public it's not anonymous
So now
The only reason I got up
Is because Rodger Stone
Likes to play with the idea of anonymity
And he does so in this
So now we have the
New York Times anonymous
But it's official
Hillary
Tell the women down Wild Bill Draper
Cool man
That's actually pretty funny that's a salad move on his
Credit for that
Anonymous
Ever said is true is true
Anonymously
Whatever works
Now he's abusing
Feel that way
He's abusing that mentality
Did Morrill Surak
Conversation
That's the reason why it's important
For journalism Outlets
Who hold themselves
Post-Standard
To follow
Because people don't
Like Rodger Stone
He's just he's just talking
He doesn't have some sort of
Alex
Right
Who comes on
I really don't I don't know if I
Concur with your evaluation
Bye
Stan
Anton that was
F*** whoever wrote that Anonymous op-ed
And then
Published
I don't understand what it is you think that I would say
It's in the equal and opposite reaction being that me saying that we should do what
Doing there
Timeout
You just said
And then you elaborated
F*** the person who wrote and published
I agree with the first part I don't agree with the second
And that's what I
Text to IKEA
3 Maiden
The other option is don't
Event don't print
Also beef
But they've chosen
No
Because it got them
And it got a ton of
What position wasn't made clear
The double-crosser
Is writing an anonymous op-ed
The
By Ed
It is not like
We should make up bullshiter or anything like that it is that if you are working with a known
Bad face operator
Then and he says
As long as you print it anonymous
Double-crosser double-cross the s*** out of him
He's writing it bad faith since you acting bad faith
You don't know that
I don't care
Fine
You'll never be a journalist
I'm just doing this
I'm just a piece of s***
I get the emotional part of it and I agree with that but
But yes absolutely
F*** the person who wrote it
Double-crossed them
Absolutely
No
Oh absolutely
Reparable damage
Do yourself
As
Could you now on
And that source is in the Trump Administration who gives a f***
I would say is that
You're going to draw the line of like
Deserves
To disrespect
Where are you going to draw that line
Right
No I completely accept
The whole
However
Right in the White House
You revealed that you have no compunction
This m***********
So then now Pence's gone
What are you going to give the f*** right now your argument
Your argument then is now
Sources within the White House can no longer trust the New York
No argument is that sources in the future from other places
Could be concerned
With whether or not the New York Times going to burn them based upon a moral decision that
They make
And that
Bulshit cuz it's the New York Times
What are they going to do
What do you say
I'm saying that water what are you what are you talkin about
The New York Times
Of this level
And then people in the future going to not talk to the New York Times
Maybe not
What
What hundred year history of not doing exactly what it is we're talking about
Music matters so much more
Means it is real real face means that it is not a cup
Frisch's acted is not aged an activity
Hypocritical of you
Drawing this line
For someone who loves whistleblowers
Like this is
Freezing
Institutions should be able to
Go back on agreement
Protect their anonymity
Baseline
Of Journalism
Against the Baseline
Of Honor
If you're not
If you're not willing if you're not willing to accept that there's a difference
Between an Edward Snowden and a reality winner
Compared to a
Hypothetical
Mike Pence
As a whistleblower
It's Mike Pence
The reason is the writer uses a word that
Didn't speeches whatever
If you don't accept that there's a difference in a whistleblower who needs to be
And a whistleblower who is pretending that they're doing the right thing
The same time
Facilitating
The very thing that they're pretending to be against
I don't see how that makes
I don't see how that's hypocritical
Because I don't think
Journalism
The principles of
Protection
Have to do with whether you think the person's an a****** or not
An apple
You have no idea who this person is
All your complaints are that they are in a
That's all it boils down what are you talkin about
Blame for this
Exactly. a****** that's all you're saying no I'm saying that they're what they're the ones who are saying weird
Taking the bills that were keeping him from
The trade agreement with South Korea
We're not from his immigration policy avoiding war with Iran
We're not stopping him from
We are the ones who are doing all of this s*** but we're not stopping
Actual harm that he's really doing
Apocalyptic
Maybe he should be made
But I am saying that outing that person doesn't help at all
What do you mean
You take one of those
That's that's a ferret counter-argument however
Imagine impact
Imagine the difference in Impact between
Anonymous
Op-ed written by a nebulous
Trump
Administration
Versus an actual
Op-ed
Naming
A person in the administration
Who is admitting
B a r a
Sibley sabotaging the Democratic process
Alright now let's
Field day that the already violently
Threatening to murder journalist
Alright Alex Jones
Pacific Mike cernovich world
Of propaganda imagine the field days they would have
When the New York Times doesn't honor their agreement to keep
How different is it from what they're doing now
It would be
They would be right
Oh so they kill a guy
How are they know how is your foot doing
Letty's outside of their Epic
But their argument argument is always that the media is doing something outside of their
You can't let them know what is that what is the difference between them saying that they're doing something
And then actually doing something
Alright that's a fair argument
I'm not I'm not just guide
Hey let's let everything burn while we stand by we did everything right
I'm not yet
Let's uphold all of our norms and yeah yeah
I'm not on that
But I do think that there are
Like pieces of
Just
Integrity
And the way things are John correct
That cannot be
Impune
All you do
Is allow people
Who has bad faith
Hey bad will
To win
In that circumstance
Is that date was anonymous
All you would do
Is verify every single narrative
The New York Times
Tricom globalist
Weapons Systems against the American people
The enemy of the people
Look at them not allowed
They went back on their deal this
Is dishonorable
Right now so much of that stuff
So that's a negative
You don't
To continue to do the work
The Way You Lie
So
I really do really all you said
You game
Is one of them is dead
Changes the game
I really do
How because
Once you show
Look if you have somebody
If you name this song
We don't give a f*** about the agreements that we've
Offered
Anytime
Future
Yeah
I get that that's not
No I mean the benefit of people not being able to escape
But that doesn't
I feel like you changed
The conversation on Main
I don't like
I'm following the thread
You're making it
Defend my
Maybe
Position
But
Let me let me try and start back from where we from from where I
Felt like you skipped off I will okay
You just a really quick
Vicky
Getaway
He's not
Ago you would have
I'm sorry I reacted to quick that's not the point
That I was looking
Warehouse
Your contention
We can't let the alt-right be right
About
Journalist
Journalistic integrity
Right small point
We don't exist in the world for that matter
Because to the people who are alt-right
They are
Regardless
The people who are right are alt-right
Already believe that they're right
It doesn't matter if they actually are or not
Because you have now allowed the
People like Mike cernovich
Text realize the word
You've allowed them to Define
Because you're there right
May I feel like you're cutting me off and on
Maybe truth
People who follows
I'm not talk about perception
Where the people are f****** killing us
I'm talking about the reality
The Catwoman their reality
Perception of stuff will always be
Asians are evil and they do evil stuff
Is not true but it is true
Follows
When you behave the way they accuse
Behaving
You validate
Other argument
I don't track
Best Bets when they go low we go high
It's not
Not bad at all
How so
How does that not
Track
I don't know I don't know if we're even talking about our showing
I feel like we're getting into a little bit of a person
We're not
Go back to your main point
When
The New York Times
Takes a real stand
Like this
Where they say
This is a guy who is saying
Exactly what we all kind of knew was going on
And he wanted to say it enough
I apologize
What stop one second
How many species are in the
F*** yeah exactly
Makes it even more likely that it is a she
Will kill her
Politically
If they were to finally take an actual
That is a more than it is a
Moment of their entire track record
It is a
Point of staying
Enough is enough
We're going to finally do this
That does not mean that they're going to burn
Every Source going
Resource
Concerned
Doesn't
It gives every source
Every single source
Like there
Confidentiality before
This one time where and administration
Is f******
Performing what is essentially a right-wing coup
Formerly Republic Nation
And they are they're finally burning a source
That is going to invalidate every single thing going
Maybe it's fine until you're a Nazi
Talk all this
Yeah I don't know it's not the path
It's not the right path I know
It doesn't Chiva thing
I don't really disagree with it.
I don't disagree with you
Their process
Confirm
Vague
It's not
I'm sorry like
I don't I'm not mad at you
And I don't think that you're dumb
Or anything like that
I think it just lying
Not it's not
Productive
It's not
It doesn't help
There are other things
Certainly
The can be broken
Helpful
But this one
It's important
Which they clearly
Of course
I mean like if someone just sent
Request that this is off the Record
Yeah we already
BuzzFeed
Elon Musk
But the fact that
Crossword
So
You can't
It's not worth it
You don't
I get
I get the
The outcome
And like I said
Kind of agree with it
But it would be better if you were worried
That would be great
B
The real outcome
Is that
People like Alex
They're confirm
They're reinforced
Think that's worth
Knowing who wrote it
I'm going to fundamentally do
Disagree with you
I'm going to accept that
That is not a
Free on this
Jordan
God I love our Joe Dan
It's so good
I totally disagree all the time
And I love you
I love you too
Discount your opinion
Find some middle ground but if we can't
There's a lot of times call for violence
Incorrect
Three assholes
Kill your hotheaded a milquetoast
Anybody could do
You're right
I mean I'm emotionally right
Intellectually you are f******
Emotionally I make
I feel good
Journalistic
Rodger Stone
Here on out
The day after
Right
Rodger hazard
About how Marco Rubio
Himself
Is Marco Rubio
URL
Rodger saying there but I
Kind of joking
Kind of despondent about the idea
No we was
What's going on with Chief
Marco Rubio Rubio is allegedly
Easter
Maybe censoring
Is actually
In Congress and doing the work
But he doesn't know who you are
You're f****** pissed
Yeah
Jordan
I told you earlier
Did Alex keeps playing
Final count
Right
Which
I've speculated it
Harkening back to
In the same way that we heard him sing along
Azteca
Couple weeks again
Coming back and I think of is next
To hear another
Much more very legitimate returning to his roots
We get to hear The Offspring cover of the final
In terms of Alex Jones his future to Jeffrey Idaho
Erode
And this one still describes the more preferable
Nipsey Hussle album
Had they kick ass off cyberspace
We want
Rodger
GoFundMe
2BR with voices
Alex is going back to his bullhorn route
Tyranny Crushers 3 through 405
Like legitimately at this point
Kicked off of Twitter
He now has like gab and Mike
Mike Adams has his
Real.
Video where some
Watch the video
Thousand
Yeah there's no like Market
Penetration there's no encroachment or anything
Violent
Coming to God MoMA
Like him realizing
I've been holding back
I'm just going to start throwing and words around
She's not
Already
Just diminishing what
Forever like
Like it's just going to be
No
He always does
And how many how many viewers does Stormfront have or whatever
Well yeah then why not just
Migrate to that after he's been kicked off everything else
That's true there
But
White supremacist are genetically Superior they don't need Super male vitality
What time does no
Great Lake
Lose the song
Right like Edison
He has enough of an audience
Milk them
For money
Yeah do a
Small-scale version
But the unfortunate thing about that
Become basically what you
You were into
So fun
Is your boss
More down
Ladder
Little bit further
You're back on the
The bullhorn
Fun situation
It's the most natural course
For his career to have gone
He flew too close to the Sun
He behaved in such an appropriate ways
He blew all
The things
Yeah
Creating
That but
He was
Part of
Creative
Talked it all up
Midday
Trump
I would love
Come back to
Because
He couldn't afford his mortgage
Yeah probably not right now is
Alex has so much more fun being the underdog who does
Don't have anybody
Scrambling with with gold as in with racist as Bob Chapman throwing everything around
Sure
Got a mortgage.
It's different for us
This position where we like
Yeah come back baby come back to this low roof for someone to
You have tasted gold
You know like
Truffles
Oh man
My bullshittin live
MSNBC
I don't know if we be super cool going back into this apartment
Throwing microphones crossword
Bill O'Reilly Twitter horseshoer
I don't ever be a lot of Tears on our TV show
God
Big difference
Between like
Being cool with the
Falling
Yeah yeah
You have my
Be better
Still preferable to me then him
Unleashing the demon that's within him
Nationalism
Outright
Horrible
Is there
But I don't want it
Become like
I centered myself cuz I was on all these
And if you kill yourself
If you f****** killed yourself for a second
And think that Genesis communication
Will kick him off
If he starts throwing words around
Or it
Becomes an outright White
Anderson
Years released
About International
Nice little excerpt from 105
Journals
Express
And I'm going to go out
White nationalist
Viewpoint
This is from the August 2000
Reissue you put that like four issues
This is
This is one of these
To be clear
You guys are not heard the ships
Buy steel and gold
Apartheid South Africa
And like a good guy started falling apart
He fled the country
You know like a good guy
South Africa
The entire social system is
Like
So in this issue of his
His journal
Advises people
Against South
African gold
The remaining
Starting to eat there
Destroy labor National Mine Workers Union
Only another way of saying
Communist takeover
Yeah
That sounds right
You know how
Three put outside
A journalist
You talk about immigrants
Unfortunately mr. Bush's return
Paralegal next
The guys of
Controlling a regulating illegal immigration
Arizona representative Jim Kolbe
Residence residence
Status over a period of years to illegal aliens already in
86 all over again only this time we're looking at
Most illegals have a third grade education and don't speak English
We are told by sources in Washington
This is Pastor Republican
Speargun
So also
Bob Motz talk about
We know that you lived in apartheid South Africa
Became a Zimbabwe
About a gross pay
Be cool
A few years ago is 8
You can accomplish this when you have a dictatorial Marxist
Tribal government
You may choose to disagree
We see America heading in
Direction
Yeah
Really don't think he meant like
Governed by
Tribes
Now you're talkin about a flag for like a
You know what I'll stop right there
I can't presume to judge somebody else based on their work
I mean
I would say that
Rhodesian government
Dictatorial doesn't matter
Distance
It doesn't matter
Alex could
Just start expressing
The most overt
Frederick in the world
He's totally fine
All of this
Where all this world is
Totally fine
They just want
Yep
Exact
It's like they own NFL
All right of course
Actually you know what
Of course it does
I brought up the connection
Why would ice be silly enough to think that that's beyond the pale
Anyway
Alex is in trouble basically because of his
Harassing of
What you've already talked
Yep Transit Rogers
Crawdaddy really is
Mr. Jones Goes to Washington moment
And confront that
Rodger is right on
In trouble
Weird
Cold
Oliver Darcy
A possum
I believe that's how we free
I haven't
But Alex has
He has like a possum
But just climbed out the carcass of a dead cow
You already said that
What you look like
I love you also answer
Exactly the thing is probably the most
The most dog Wesley of it all
You know what
Rake
What I can't let go is that he seen a possum climb out of a dead cows ass before
Not explained by back always know they've done something wrong
No one. He's like
Just finish it
You've not heard of the video of Alex
Confronting
Darcy
So now we're going to listen to a tiny clip
Small taste of obligated not to
I understand that that's 45
Five seconds of
Is there interaction foot 8 indicative of the entire 9 minutes
It's Alex harangue
I don't like
How's the wife
Microaggression
Although is a leftist
Got offended by that
Call them triggers
Took that I just want to play
Give some sort of an idea
That's the vibe of that
Tire thing
This is a guy being
Yeah right
It's not it's not like
Haha
Are you staying there silently
Yelling
Children in
Have you ever taken a red-eye flight
Teleological
Jet lag
Do you want book
How many hours I'm
Am I in the doctor brought small log
Why can't I get on red eye on malaria
Can I get
Oh my God
Let's just the time to shows up
And then
I think I want to do
What you've never done on the show before
It's kind of in forwards roulette
Okay
I have the video of Alex's response to him
9 minute video
That we are going to watch a
These last two
Yeah probably
Guarantee it'll be like
We're still on Thursday
Like
I can't stress
I don't have any clips
Because it's
Embed
Really boring long
Alex
Does Express
Couple time
Admiration
He expresses his ideas at like
He's not as bad as Facebook isn't kicked
He doesn't realize it
A couple hours for then he's cooked
Copper
It's only interesting
To be in as much as like
You would later probably say like we knew it
Blindsided by this like crazy
Earlier
Episode
For the episode
Ticked off
Eventually
I know that
Skating on
What do you think
Because he is
Keeps testing
Break
Hey I know you hit the wrong patch
F****** straight through
He's not interested
Reason
Verizon
Because
Most of the show
Husband
Basically a Victory lap
I'm talking about like
People suck Seahawks Miller on Godzilla
Sirius bankrupt
Godzilla
Marco Rubio sucks
Bear f*** what they're saying I'm saying this
Dorothy
Socks
A clown them I made him look like a cock
Taking risks
Listen to this
This going to make you really mad
I think that like first of all this this is
Wild
He's
Then second it's also fun to see him
Consistently Miss Rippers
Mispronounce
Brand
Something that's really
Central
Dish.com
Infowars.com
Who cares drop
Generation Z
Add camp
Why is this the key to everything
Because
The last year
Hollywood
Racine
Real quick
Depart
The park
Department that is true in terms of like
Diminishing
Because of like a different ways to find
Do you want to watch
It's just a
Modern technology
Issue in the same way album sales
Tamarac
Didn't want music anymore
Joey f*** cable and all that s***
So
Your arguments Pogo
25%
Year after year
For a few shows on MSNBC and fox
General a v
Declined mashup
Drop 34%
Why is that so important
7 million-dollar
Through Time
He become scared
He had become
Call
A little b****
No
Anymore so he got basically hired by Soros and others to be this PR person
Strife and Division
What is your first amendment
Give you're not on the team
You can pick up your bike again
I want this is an audio broadcast Jordan just stood up for most of that and was
Curious
Chakras
Pittsburgh
F****** come on
I want Kaepernick destroy the Bears
Roy's
Like it was even a f******
Colin Kaepernick is one of the more talented but not after that
You still be better than f******
Whoever you want to talk in there
Colin Kaepernick was
Good
He's actually good at what he does
Beetle
Cubs
There's evidence
Yep
F****** God
Here's the is original
Compliant
His original
Speech was about
She's very
And somehow
That's the point
Somehow we support the troops or any b******* like that Colin Kaepernick was literally
Kneeling
As he stated
Because police were it's very interesting
I agree
Ivory
Call Yuri
You've touched on already
It is
It is a protest at
Start
Very quickly became
Like if it has all of that wrapped up inside
I hate this
I hate the idea of the right
Work
Let me know that I hate the idea of power over their bosses
And then I also f****** hate the idea that
Uppity dude
Is that
In his position
Weird question
How many NFL owners
I don't know I would assume not many but I don't know
I would be surprised if I don't know
Who is the Kool-Aid Man
Through the wall with Colin Kaepernick
I don't I don't know that that that stuff
Cuz it's not like
Familiar world
He's very black
Imagine he owned every NFL team
ECW Champion awarded durag
This is closest
You were do right
What
Durag
I'm not okay with
Dark time
Of his
Company's history
I'm sure he's been good with labor
Because it's clearly a union company
And it's really about your contact take care of your
You wouldn't have a show
I was playing the game
So you want to make sure that they're taking
Terabrite you want to make sure that if they get an injury their careers are over and all their money
Travel between shows
Look
Play food
Everyone
Everytime I try and bring it up at the office
Come on guys
Unionize
Frustrated
I think it's frustrating that I work in an office because
Are scab labor would destroy us
Yeah cuz nobody knows what
Nordstrom
And tires
Here's what I want to say
Earlier in the show Alex is talking about how
He got a cost
Goodbye somebody
Expelled it out later that
You're all that stuff
And here is why
Him being kicked off
Twitter the next day
King Soopers
I don't think it's
You need to do it you should have done it earlier
But the timing is
Really f***** up
Because Anna's on his show today
This one
Validate
For the next
Tomorrow at least 6 months
Tuesday
Wednesday
We're going to have some big news
Big news
Zbigniew Brzezinski
I just gave you the facts
Come hell or high water
Release the information on air
Do it
But
They're making their move on this country
No doubt now
Oh yeah
Stop that
Trump has to remove that special office that the clintons Left Behind with Obama
Department
Whatever
But it doesn't matter
This is just what he does all the time we can look back to our
Podcast history
Jerome corsi is going to be killed for the information that he has
He does going to be honest I've never listen
He does this all the time that sort of like weird T's of like
I'm going to do this afternoon we're going to but unfortunately
We stopped the global
Right yeah
Because it unfortunate
Tomorrow I'm going to f****** do this
As if he had done that a hundred times
Because you said it on this
I think that he's going
But Alex is going to be
I was right
That's why they kick
Ticks me off
Which is
But it's like it's like if all of the time
Terrorist attack is going to happen in the next 3 months
It happens like
Unfortunately
Coincidentally
Because
Will it happen
That is going to happen
His prediction was
Cuz they're going
Take me off of
Twitter
Then he would have been accidentally right
Be like
Tomorrow we're going to have to do an emergency
But for now
Jordan the exclusive!
Alex Jones responds to Twitter
Video in front of me
I do
I'll give you a
But
Nathan's iodine
So what we've learned what was learned
I'm watching this unreal. Video Mike Adams
Real.
Real also selling Mason
Oh
Crazy here we go
I have to tell you
I'm actually getting probably the best exclusive in the world
And his own officially
Terminated
Terminator Terminator
F****** suck it up and say
A bit of
He's growing sympathy
He's growing a sympathy but he also has a big
Yeah
You know what
React started growing my beard I feel like I need to shave it off
Fashion he had to go live
On one of the mainstream social media networks Alex
She's now been banned
So what you goddamn right
Why do you think you got banned
What is this mean for free speech in America
It sure it still
Interviewing his boss
Oh
What does it mean for your future
If he actually knows
If she has the sense of
Hey Alex
I'm interviewing you
Cuz you are going to be
Alex
Do you think I could be hired on at another
Pipefitters what is beer doesn't
Look terrible
Fair enough
Tell the truth
And because we were popped
And because we dared go to that Committee hearing
Stand-up the Rubio it's tantalize the mainstream media
The secret police captain
Who admits he goes around and gets people I can forward taking off other
That monster
That is abused
Because of that because
Your mother married a brother
Monkeys as well
And because I
That happened
Yelling and screaming up and down the Halls taking over to lot of that
Bullying the Press
I showed up and all the cameras wrong baby because I was a big dude
Pressuring
Soros's pressuring
Stock
Today
Shorting a stock report
Suck it up
Oliver North
Stop story
Bigger than that
Darken a major
How's the wife
Now he got last week ago Facebook
Twitter
They're banning
Everyone
And they use me as a cover story
Who I am
Thank God drudgereport.com has been so
A colon this drug is the only planet right now
More traffic
New site in the world number to website
.
Thank God really Prescott
Wards.com
A lot of us on Twitter laudamus from other servers
Website
Thank you
Support free speech
As you said when I was
Get your battle rifles ready for
I said
Members of Congress members
Get ready with
Your
About rifle shoe protector
Yourself there so
Doesn't it seem like he just admitted he said he said he didn't
Run Whatsapp account
Well when you said
I didn't say get your battle rifles
Who's ready I said
No no
I believe we talked about this already like that
Alex is right about that
I mean he always calls for
Couches it
And just like that
He's he said much more things that were like
These are demons
If you talked about have your battle rifles ready by your bed cuz
Cuz they're coming
Yeah
Do you need
Kill them when they come in your house
But it's still in your house
It's one of the rare things that I'll defend
I'm not going to say that like
He was trying to f*** with
Call to respond
Course
I'm done with this response
This response is stupid really sucks
It's Bora bummed out cuz I have the video in front of
I hate looking
Beard is okay
What is a duck boat
Here here
Jordan
The final point that I want to make
Alex Jones
And the people who are against Alex Jones
Quote unquote
Yeah
More than the other side
Exist
Only because of cintra
They only exist and they're only able to
You being what
Because
Forward
But they don't realize that the moving forward
Just a tornado
And they're counterbalance
The other person
So
The other side
Yeah yeah
And the force
Create
Forward keep
Watched
Together right
And that's how Lux
Skywalker
Created a force ghost
To fight against
What I feel like you're goofing on what I
I think was a
Decent know it was that easy
I'm sick of this s*** I don't think it's okay
I think it's nonsense
I think that
His
His response
Twitter is
Exactly the same as
He has nothing else left
To rebound
Like he has no
Person
You know
You got
Yeah he's absolutely
There is no Jack Dorsey
Telling him
Hey you can't do xyr
Now he is
Is just his own
Media operation
Infowars.com
They have their ability to stretch
Newswars
Newswars.com
Now he can beat
Purest Alex
I will guarantee you that's not going to be
So
Here's my point
F*** him
Jackson done it long ago
Ivan nope
Trying so hard to
And I just don't it's been a
It's been a struggle I just don't I don't care
He did things that he
He should not have done
Not honor like
On a human level
He has four
He was not punished for it
Now he is
Didn't
Great
So now
Do you know where you can
Can't find
Alex
I'll tell you the numbers
Or website
You can't find it at our website
No you can't acknowledge underscore fight
Where else could you find a stand
Could you find Alex on ice
No
Prssv
Can you find Pokemon my
Shut this down
Fun
You know what
It's been very fun but I just don't give a s*** about this
Modern stuff
Goal of this
This is
Diminishment
Of Alex
A force
Which
I do fight all that interest
Him becoming in
Outright
Avatar of neo-nazism in white supremacy
Not like I was an amazing Avatar
Wait what
I was not here with corocoro was it amazing avatars
Oh my God
Trouble
Brian Kinney ask you let's get this s*** solved right now can you have a race Bender that's not okay
How dare you
Great jokes over what was it
Amazing joke I apologize if you wanted the three of us
Absolutely f****** supplicating
I don't find any of this
Did the end result
And the other
Be scared of that
But we'll keep an eye on
We'll see what happens
Future
Hope it's not
Probably will bake
Cuz it's worth more money is probably really doesn't matter
Because we need
Remember specific about Alex Jones
That maybe we should always have in our consciousness
Alexandra Thurston color