Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
What was the last time you lost
I don't know if I've ever actually play 10 recreationally
Just f****** around with friends
Play play
I've never played that actually kept score
My buddy James desolation Williams
High School
Is really funny
CVS
Williams AZ
Really funny
I don't even know what that means
So when we're in a little glass enclosure
Hazmat
Look my name is just a box
Rich people have business meetings while they sweat
Losing record
Alright
The best players in the world
You at tennis and I know nothing
Bright
Before we get to that I thought
Just to talk about our last episode
Shity veneer
No I don't think so
People who listen to it because of an argument about whether or not the New York Times
When should burn their source
Yep
Criticism that came back
Instead of like a
Journalistic
Different there
I still stand by my position
That you do much more damage
Zen good
Ibotta
Like calming down like that was a rough
As far as being alive is
A little bit out of sorts.
Yeah so I just
F***** up
I respect your ability to
I don't think any less of you for
I think people
The reason that I ended up leaving it in even though I don't feel good about it is that
I think
There's a value
For people to see that we don't agree about every
You and I
I meant later whenever Ivan
Right right
But even beyond that people
Disagreeing
Weather
Gifts anywhere or not
Being able to discuss
Whether or not it's
A bit of podcasting we've ever done I'll say no probably not
Hey man there's another further value in this
Psychological
And that is
Feel great
Anxiety when I put out a product that I don't think it's very great
And I don't
Feel that very often
I feel really good about
To be said for like put it out I don't feel great about it and I didn't either
Great deal
Sorry about that
Greener pastures anyways
In theory that's that's my
Speaking of grapes
True Value Hardware
The new donors very about
Thank you so much
Do you want
That almost sounded like a question
Michael Cera
I don't think you so much there we appreciate it very much
You're not a person who has joined up with
I can be but thank you very much
Show button
Are we would appreciate it
Indeed you can
Yeah
Sojourn today we are
In 2009
The Tea Party
He has gone
Nationwide
National
Tea party right
Whenever
People of all shades of white
Got together to really
I talked about were they mad at Texas
Sounds more like a black guy
We've got some real interesting
Stuff to talk about today
Stuff
I got some stuff I'm very excited
Good to get into
Start where we left off on March 2nd
Through about March 4th
I'll be honest
The halfway through March
We're going halfway through the show and walked away from it
It's not that it's bad I was just like there's a point
The show gets too at some point
Okay
I just kind of like I felt High
A little bit
Biggest show me so little sense
Later I'll go back and listen to rest of the
Before anything else
Amend
Addendum I will do that
For now
March 2nd
Through
Half Price Books
But it was the equivalent of a listening to
Somewhat
Start
Martial law
Alright
Conditional statement
Should we defeat the New World Order
Never we will never
Far enough
He's going to drop some little brown baby
What is it is this like every 10 yards brown baby is this like a football match
Football match
Very weird
I will say that was apart of where I am
Turn it off
I believe that entirely
I will start here on the 2nd
I believe the last time we were in 2009
I mentioned it Bob Chapman
Yeah and Bob Chapman mentor
George Soros
And I predict
Hey I bet
Start talking about
George Soros
Shockingly
Here on March 2nd
Play
It's for George Soros Club
George Soros admits
Elite plunging oil to bankrupt Middle East
Email is missing
So is it a couple of verisign points
But I think are appropriate
To make here the first is that
This is still not
His normal George soros's run
He still isn't like on the George
Zoroaster
I'm not satisfied
Because in this time that we've been covering
You know some 2000
Do before
IR coverage
Of this began
He's not talk about Soros at all this isn't the first time that he's brought him up as some sort of
Evil nefarious
Familiar with sorrow saddle
Listen to the tone of his voice there it's like
This guy Soros
He's a headache
Soros Soros
Anybody anybody
Who Coronavirus
But I did find
Stuff about surisan oil in the end of
Are you sure you didn't did you
Infowars site for like
With a bunch of exclamation points cuz I think that would have found
Find
That you didn't find that no but what I find it
Peace in the New York Review of Books
That goes over
Soros
Us
Committee oversight
Give
Slightly amended version
To the house oversight
Is that
You look at the
Price of oil
How is
It's gone up
Dramatic
Increase interest
Doofy
An average price
50 a gallon at the pump go up to over
Over $4 a gallon
He's discussing about how this
Probably is representative of a bubble
It is a piece of like
Overspeculation
Can people over Trading
In commodities
Is what's causing
Nothing
Or any of the other piece
Places that I've been able to find
From around
The elites are going to plunge this s*** right against the idea that people are
Amateur
Getting an
Piper Inn
Inflating the prices
And has nothing to do with the actual supply and demand of what a market would do
What kind of genius could possibly predict that
Phineas
Like if somebody were like looking at
And I'm just going to choose something from
Just at random
Like if somebody were looking at Bitcoin and seeing that price keep raising will keep going higher
And then buy their own Bitcoins there's no way enough people would be able to do that too
The bubble
Anytime a massive bubble is created it is probably going to be a crash
Too smart he has to be connected
To the elites
Well I mean there's some religious income housing
That would never happen
Interesting
Address
For the
Oversight
Alex
Prima facie case
Against
Nutritional invest
Commodity
It's intellectually on sound potential
Destabilizing
A particularly harmful as economic
When it comes to taking any regulatory measure
However the cases left
Regulations may have unintended
Adverse
Brinston push investor
Further into unregulated markets
Shiploads of oil which are less
Turn off Earl expert
He's making an argument but it's
You know these are the consequences
You see when people get it
Irresponsible
Commodity index
Trading
These are
It's bad B
What you also
Have is
Possibility
So even I mean all of this
Should be okay with
Speech was essentially
I know this is going to go wrong
But I don't know how to
No no not at all actually
Know how to sex
Eerily reminiscent
Vestibular craze for portfolio insurance
Stock market crash
Institutional investors
The piling in on one side of the market
Efficient way to on
If the trend reversed in in
Institutions as a group
There would be
Index buying and speculation
Fallas
Reinforced
The prevailing directions
Enterprises
Equalizing effect by aggravating to prospect
The effect will be reversed
Only when the recession begins
To take hold
Samantha Klein
But it would be desirable to rain in index buying and speculation
Wow they're still in
Bubble
Is right there is advice
Queer
Buying and speculation
Yeah but he also said that he doesn't know of Regulation
Is the way to do but he's not even in that
Advocating
For regulation of their own accord
Invest
I'm still not okay
Time for regular
I understand and I think that maybe there is some
Could have
This is also very
George Soros
Supply
Oil at all
I'm being very concerned about the
Prices
Annoying
The late
Part of 2008
Advise
Call Moorhead
Find a better way.
Yeah and he didn't even know what
Terminator had the rise of the
Had a chance now
You may think you may have Alex actually knows what
From bad to worse
Ladies and gentlemen
They are going to destroy the economy and then right at the point of peaceful Revolution
Joshua
Literally thousands of different
Police detective
And sleeping something
You get a very scary
Power of
Predictions didn't
Happened none of that happened United States are is real
Got better from this point forward
Going to destroy everything
Dissolve the Union as he's
Masturbating thinking about it
Mid nose is very off
But that's the Memphis that s*** that's why
1990s
Nobody knows who committed any crime before
We got computers in forensic evidence
That's very
Until DNA
Sports
Perception
Actually I'm going to leave
Ever
Ever. What
Back on every every haunt you ever had
Bulshit
Oh yeah
Well if Alex
Hurrah reopen every Cold Case
Warranty
Split everybody got it
It's called a warm case when it's solved
No it's not
It's
It's done
It's gone cold
It's got to be a middle ground
Cases
In purgatory Olympics
Hot
All right what you got text clip
Alex Express is semitism
About geopolitics
Your thoughts on Iran versus Russia is this all just WWF fake wrestling grandstanding or is there really a threat there
Yes
You think that's a possibility I appreciate your call
In Iran's mountainous North before
Technology consultant
Iran and starting World War 3
Okay
Clearly Russia and Iran cool Israel
Yeah probably
Yeah
He wasn't here
Because
Mechanic at the time
I still think of the text message wrong just because
I do agree that he's much closer
Ron's capabilities warrant
Defensive they were
Nuclear program
I think is wrong about Russia
Is more accurate about Iran and Israel
There's that but the only thing I find really all that
Thing is denoting
That hasn't changed
He also expressed
Neutrality
Everything is Everything is
We're still waiting on
As long as it's
For it
The moment
Fro
Stupid
Calls
Call from a guy
You should not need to be remind
The clowns are welcome George
Yeah just reminder listeners day is Texas Independence Day
Victory or death
Yes you know I was sitting there reading about the Alamo and I can tell you one thing I was on fire because
Even though they were outnumbered by the Mexican Army days they stood their ground and they
You know they all died they would not
Nada
Dictator
And that's something that flickers and
What
Chicken nearby
Anil amount of media propaganda
And thanks for reminding me
That should be his birthday
Texas Independence Day he's more of a only goes to church on Easter
Easter Christmas
In Texas booking Independence Day
The Texas Independence tattooed on his arm
Quite frankly
I don't remember
Well Arbor
Fair
But you don't make your whole life about like what are bird
Myself as an oak
3 million time
No but you have called yourself The Lorax more times than I'm comfortable
I speak for the trees
Guest on the show Mostly on notable
Boring inter
Interview with the guy named for
About from Mexico
Anti-immigrant
He's more concerned about the idea that Mexico is going to
And that is going to
Weed to everyone spilling over
Into America
From
Globalist
Plans collapse
Never heard anybody
Or even
Demonized
Entire country just
Immigrants come over that's
Crazy it's still so
Then the current day version
Murder them at the border
But it's still so much
Generally other
Still very different
From like places
Individual a f*** you immigrant person
So as far as I can tell George Grayson doesn't
Seem like he's crazy
I looked interesting professor in
He's written extensively on
Bartell's
Answer
What I would say probably is
Is the big
Question
And you might not get
Let me throw this question out at you
Homeland security has shut in Texas both state and federal I've had
Quietly
Beers on wood highest alerts
Turn on air
They claim
Chance Mexico completely collapse
No Mexico's not going to
Collapse
Really really invalidating your knowledge
Pitstop I mean that's right up there with that volcano
No
Building a real life
Version of Rainbow Brite brought into this world from a text
Cuz University
Can you respond to that
If you read it
Okay
They were having a perfectly amicable interview
You going to say
You bet
They were on they were on
Similar wavelength about cartels taking over
Patches of
Right
You can have a
Conversation
It's just when Alex
Start getting it
Any academic
Hold on now
I don't know about
It's just like you and me whenever we're having
Conversation
We were having a conversation
Sometimes I'm not
Holy prepared to deal with it
Do you just keep going I have a heart problem
You shouldn't have asked
Bubble a lot harder to make
His information War bubble
Moana
Confronted with
Who's not playing ball
Yeah. Had a reason person on there
Yours
I think the last time
Might have been like
Was it one of our 2,000
Was it like a time travel episode
My2030
30 min with that whenever
The way back
Nevermind
I'll call him
Austin
That was just
We got to get Bill
The other thing
Like I said d
You know we're just sort of
Tracy
A little bit
You have
Alex
Being pro around
Anti-israel
As I mentioned
Do a bit against the military
The military
People of Arabic
It is very weird
I mean Alex it is it's ridiculous the way I see people allowed people say well hey
You know you're guilty and
And it's okay to use you should be there
A patriot and let the police come in and
Style Encore
Military recalled hodgie's
Straight
They're going to be
Government run by people
You are 100% right Alex
America's Best
Understand the Mastermind setup of this
Bank of America
Right that's that's what I guess he's saying is 2016
Damn that way they can't do it
Black president all the sudden they're going to mistreat Muslims and then they might mistreat you
Can you get a wife president mystery Muslims
I'm confused by that line of thinking but not so much confused
Hear it
Vitastik
Step back like all right
So
He's saying that the CIA put out all the information about Abu ghraib
To make us look bad in the world
What's going on
What are you going to do
I don't want them to not
Tell the world about that
A very serious issue that abuse
The prisoners in torturing
Like that
Unique unique
You have to take your lumps
Good
They had nothing to lose cuz everybody already knew it
Like the CIA can release all the Abu ghraib stuff they want and
2009 everybody in the world
Looks like you guys are f****** torturing people 3000
For I still don't understand
Questions you would like
America look
Looking good I would like for the
But it doesn't seem like that's what he wants either
I would like for them to have not
That's what I would like
Yeah kind of flies counter
Whole thing
I don't know it's very confusing for Alex to be like the government
Publix
All that tracks from
What do you think
Especially hearing like all this
Pretty soon you're going to be talking about how the military
Some stuff like that
I don't I don't get where
I have my key
He said that before 2009
He's like
Symbol of authority in 2009 is
Associated with a government that the out-of-control
Where is now we have a government that is
Before that he started to get the narrative that there is a counter-coup
Beneath the surface
Globalist
The military
You know we talked we talked a bit about like why it's important to cover Alex Jones
Ford Focus
One of the reasons is because I
A lot of rain
Conduit into much darker
Now on another level
More mainstream things that Alec
Save Fox News.
Service conduit
Which then lead people further down the hole
Into like
White supremacy
It's like when you get lost on Wikipedia
You never know what you're going to learn
This is
This is something I would like to
Is because
Towards the mid end of this episode
Alex get the call who actually
Expresses
Exactly that
But as a
Appositive
Interesting
Hey how you doing
Good sir
Hey I just wanted to thank you
First and foremost
Or what you're doing
For the country
I believe that
Your Patriots
Thank you
I'm sorry
Commission
Thank you sir
I just wanted to stay like that I'm new to all of this on YouTube politics
It's been quite an
Buy opener
Selection is what got me into it
My mom got me a Fox News up first
Let's do another eventually
Found your show
And I
You've opened my eyes
Quite a few things
I listen to a lot of the
My radio shows out there just about all of them
And I think your
Your
Truth daughter guide the Great
But it's like there
Dared to
Talk about what really needs to
Just because it's fun Alex
Blame
Literally all the time by Glenn Beck
At this point in his career
Michael Savage calls him Michael weiner all the time
That's all
But if you see there that's
Callers talking about
Okay so my mom got me watching
Fox News
When I found you
And then once I found you which is mostly like
Hardcore drugs the other stuff wasn't good enough anymore
Because you've convinced me that you are actually the one giving birth
They're full of s*** because they're full of
This is how indoctrination work
This caller is Express
Exactly
How the path downward work
That's a bummer
I don't I don't like
Politics
Did you all right fine
Winter
What
Alex Jones f*** man you know
People who
We aren't that smart
Things filter.
Really entertaining
Aristotle
I'll give you that
So dark.
Remember that terrible idea
Balance
When are you staying at least made the effort to pretend
What you got a tip the cab to a little bit
Or not do you know
You do need to tip the cap to this
Nice transition
We listen to a lot of Alex
Joey sings along
With a lot of music
But we've never seen him become self aware
Alright
From now on The Highwaymen and then dropping just like
More fun my way
Studio
Jason bermas
Midnight Show Network
I don't know how
The castle that was I don't
To find out
Jason bermas
Who is Jason
Timberlands
Refresh my memory.
Like he's the guy who's made some 911documentary
Who do Molly much
Character
There's nothing really about the Tea Party
Really about
Except for that first week
Yeah it's boring
This is an omen
Kind of hope
Find something
At least
Now so now we're in a holding pen
And we get to Alex talking about
Sears
That
Metastasize
Becomes
On the road
Walmart managers
And 2000's Walmart distribution centers in Walmart
Under martial law
Walmart
Was helping during emergency
Vaccination drill
Walmart emergency preparedness drill
You shots
Then have drills
Free flu shots
Bob
Walmart employees
All this is really just misrepresenting
The fact that they give that back
Walmart
How can we effectively serve the population
Huge ass building is it's a Walmart to Walmart
To consider how many Walmarts are in America and how many Walmarts are in
Towns that have no other Central meeting play
Like
If you didn't grow up in
Small town
You don't understand
You live in the town where Walmart is
Town Square
Where are you hung out with my small boat
Has grown up the Columbia so close to a lot of small town
I'm hanging out with people who grew up in Mexico Missouri of Oz
Yeah I like those titties words like there's nothing
Do except go to the f******
Super Walmart
Go on Friday night kids at all go hang out at Walmart
Just nowhere else to hang out
So now there's no more
Tavares
T.j. marks for Public Health
Work with Walmart
People sexing
But also
As opposed to the local Pentecost
So now you have to scroll. Every town has one of those Walmart
Mad baby.
Because
Sacred
They don't need back
The snake
But
The important thing
Brand of fear
Is exactly what motivated
This is exactly what was behind
Jade helm
Spear of a government takeover there all these Walmart
Close down
And people were like oh my God that's where they're going to have that
When they take over
So Alex
The present
It's been like I didn't get on the helmet
6 years before
If you are giving the Proto narrative that led to the Jade helm
So maybe I don't know we'd still have to go through that fear to time
Find out exactly what happened
We going on our next investigation is out
Investigation
Laying the groundwork for the
People who did make
The weather or not
He's a g
So that's fun
Anyway I mean a look
If I was going to put a lot of detail
I would rather surround them with a pit of snakes
Indiana Joe
Vaccines that way
You know how easy it is
To keep people docile in a Walmart
You never see people freaking out at a Walmart even at the checkout aisle because everybody has that
Easy to contain people there
Use lock the doors and no one would notice
I don't know if that's true
Readers would have a very different job they be on the other side
Peanut butter cups able to walk away from the exit
Peanut butter
Free peanut butter cups
Like I said I don't know
You're working late last night and I went and picked up
Credit
But
Can I have another guy
That's because right now I never before
Messianic Messiah
None of these people
But
Go to work
Continue a lot of those negative programs
It's a bummer
Conversation
How big was this hot dogs
There were that many people
Hub of social
Not a lot
Going on
Alex plugin
Cuz I remember that clip
Spiraling into
The Obama Deception is going to be Mike Rivero on the show and visits only
Because
As We Know
Some point after this bike Rivera's going to
To call Alex
But she'll for Israel
Anymore
They're falling out having
I know who else is Richards
Cook
It's not important
He's just a guy
No he's
He's someone who I
You wrote about the Challenger explosion
Got to the bottom of
Some of that
The fire about it
Vetericyn incredibly fascinating tree that's awesome
Goodbye
Experience
Economy
He's fairly knowledgeable
He tries to
Push a lot of
Do you like they're going to
Collapsing
Language
Cookies
Maybe a little bit more polite and generous
Conversation
Everything in order to
Have everything
Be super cheap snake
I can buy up everything after it's all over
And that's the only way we're going to rebuild the channel
Richard cook comes in he's talking about how like
Historically when things have fallen apart
People are
Much diminish
Price
Puerto Rico
The fact
That you can
Things Fall Apart
Does not
People do that
Intentionally
He's so they can later
They're just predators
In order to
Not necessarily always
Force for good
Go with the large majority
Like literal carpet
You work things
Collapse
In order to buy things up on the other side
In order for you to get me to
That that was a larger plan by some sort of
Coordinated group
You need to do a lot more in terms of evidence
Yeah and when Alex brings up like
Soros
It was he doesn't at this point
Conversation
Hadn't happened years later
He f****** what
Also
The Rothschilds at Waterloo
That whole thing
That's not true
So like when your
Arguments about the idea of like causing a collapse in order to buy things up on the other end
Hearken back to vet
I don't I don't care
I don't got I don't I'm not coming alone with you for that right
Ratso
You need to do better than
And I am courage
If you want to I'll listen
I'll review the evidence but up till now
There's not any actual example
Venezuela
Nimeni nacar f****** Hawaii
Like name any number of these things where I Collapse is created in order to
You purchase all of this
Are you going to prove to me
Collapses were
I created
Whether or not it was exam
And then
Like you say predatory forces at call the banana
Like that
Right right
Like
Conspiracy orchestrated
Collapse a government
Then take it over
You know like that's a thing
It's
The problem is he's using a numb thing to describe a thing that's a thing
You see what I'm saying
Somewhat probably
Summation of Alex Jones
Intellectual
Strategy
Describe a non Thing by ignoring a thing
Talk about the fake version of the
Which is fun
This is the only thing that really was like
This is going to be fun
So that this is
First of all there's a lot of excitement
This is the first time I've heard Rob do on the show back in 2009
I love the professionalism of this just shows up after a commercial break and how
Alex is like
Private conversation
Right
Does weird
Kind of brings up the
Pity party he talks about
Chores
Yeah I'll tell the people that interested
Tax protesting is boring
No
No it's not like no it's not like to Alex
He has a very specific group of people
That he thinks are legitimate
I swear to God I would have ignored this entire clip if these names
Really funny
I bet I looked into them
Let's go ahead
Let's go and get all The Usual Suspects
The 15th is the middle of the week so
Transparency
What's Iran
What's good job
Who else should I get on here
Skip larousse
These are all legitimate researchers and activists in prison
There's a lot of Patriots apology
Appreciate that
So I
First of all I love
Hello the name
Red Beckman and crafts crafts
And then the idea that you saying that like there's Patriot mythology out there
I wouldn't I wouldn't do wrong by bringing in a crazy person
I like
Irwin Schiff isn't on your list of names
Leadership isn't on his list
The attack
I'm stopped so I had to
I had to look into it
I had to be like
Who are these f******
People what are they all about
Cuz I don't
Bring a little bit of a bell
But most of those names I was just like
That could be
Larry becraft
Do you know what my favorite Patriot mythology
George washy
Season that's why we have
The seasons
His mom got sad
I'm going to tell you all about
Okay my research took
Legitimate taxpro to hear about first
Earthquake
Unfortunately
Baby crab
He's a solid be crap
Text generally working in the world of Defense
In court mean that he himself is a sovereign citizen
You're making money off defendants.
But I'll tell you what he's rich as fuk 1985 becraft
Defend one client
16th Amendment
Which allowed the federal income tax was
Before ratifying
The judge was not impressed
Beecroft is now
Was the judge
Nonplussed by his argument
Pressed
Impressive to go all the way to the 16th Amendment
Possibly because of his willingness to be flexible and try anything
He's one of the only text protester attorney who's ever managed to win a case against
The government
Memphis legendary ship
On October 15th 1993 Lloyd long under-representation from Larry becraft
Represented by Larry name
Is found not guilty in a criminal court on charges that he evaded paying tax
Use that case
Is there Smoking Gun
Swallowed long approve it to
The only problem with their argument is that long only one is criminal trial
For which the burden of proof
Involve the government
He knew he had to file taxes
And the jury found that he sincerely
We did not believe that he needed to do so not guilty by reason of stupid
Not rule that need Wheeling Nevada Texas
Beechcraft even make sure of his defense in his opening statement
I found an entire transcript before you read it
I'm already trained pre-summit it
Alright
Texting you too f****** stupid
Hurt his sort of stature in the text protester world
The question is did
Meeting with a
The Criminal Mind
Or
Belief
A reason that he's done what he's done
Now that's the bottom line issue
No it's not
So he's even trying to frame it as like he was really trying to commit a crime here
Forgotten is like he's too dumb or he is
Thoroughly convinced of this
Not going to
So also in Civil Trial
Found guilty
Backpacks
Who Among Us can say that we haven't murdered somebody because we sincerely believe them to be a dragon
Haha
Crazy
Do you really think this man committed murder
No
He farted
Dragon
Like a hero
Well I mean
Don't ever really talk about that
Criminal
It's like he got off with it because Larry be crafted coming in
Work in Texas
I read so much
He's not really been too big a player the tax protest
Yesterworld
Also as of this recording the only post on his blog is just him saying contact him to be your lawyer along
With a picture of himself escorting his daughter across the football field when she was
I'm not sure that that's customer
UPS Coronavirus
What water is right to escort the homecoming queen
Auto
Billable hours
Gonna guess that that was
Like his idea
I don't know
Involved with family stuff but it seems like he was like
You're the homecoming queen
I'm motherfuking escort you yet
No
Alright so now I guess
I guess we can go next Tom Cryer
Town crier
Tom Cryer
He is yet another guy who decided not to pay his tax
Got in trouble for it
Pleated quote
Need to do that using that as a defense in order to get out of criminal
His story is the absolute run-of-the-mill for
Idiotic tax
Protesters
In that world
You got a bad sat argument
You rely on technicality to stay out of prison
Civil court
Pay your back taxes
You pretended civil case net
Never happened
Tons of money in the tax protest circuit preaching the people to do the exact same thing that you got in trouble for in the first
You don't have to go to jail but you still owe us this money please pay it
All hide behind that
Sincerely believe this stuff
Right so you don't have to go to
Prison
Pay everything back
Regular
From all the stuff that I looked into it had people wiggling their prison
For the crimes
Super super rare
Because he was like
I'm not going to beg.
Just haven't beat being forced to pay their back taxes
The publicity that game
Ship the perception
Going to make it like
I stood up
To the man
I meant just not talk about this
He decided to
Agree that he owed back taxes news
Any further thought that he shouldn't have to pay any penalties for wasting everyone's time and court with long debunked
Discreditable
The RS of the Odin that north of what
Where is believed that the number should be
Nice round number let's say
Bring up the
Dollar bill into everybody
Joe Bannister hot name
You know what I don't
If you are making like a car
Pretty good life
But interested because jobadder is a former IRS agent
You turned into a text protest
And as if by some sort of magic
He slid down
He probably had some of these ideas in the IRS which is wild
To be in the IRS file taxes
2002-2006
Trouble
Banisters first real run-in with the laws regarding 1004
Easter was charged
Conspiracy to defraud the United States as well as
Three counts of aiding in
Assisting
The filing of.
1997 + 19
T98 tax
Cher now
No that was just how I pulled the quote Adams
You had to do with a client advisor
A luggage
Manufacturing
Possibly due to banisters
Incoming employment taxes
And also stop filing necessary paperwork for the employees to be able to pay their taxes
Correct
Shrek
Ddlc leave riddles and said that he just sent the baseball arrest
These questions
Free from that press release from the
The indictment further alleges that there was a second meeting on October 11th
Thompson and Bannister
Cencal employees
The compensation which they received was not
They were not required to pay individual income tax on those wages
Hold on
Bannister sure the employees of cencal that Thompson would not like
Regarding tax
I'm sorry what
To do with this idea that like
Vortex
Protesters believe that the only people who
The federal employees are the only people who actually pay taxes
And the money you're paying
Classified as income
It's all a mess
All right we could be here for another 6 hours
There's got to be a little bit of that on you if I went to an employer they were like
Don't worry about it
What a penny with an income I be like you guys I don't think I should work
Someone who
Authority implicitly
You could really they could really you have screwed some people over with like
Remind me that guy works for the IRS
Except the
Supposed to pay taxes on this look at that f****** guy
Take another step
No matter what these employees believe or disbelieve
Maybe because he believed with ancestors
Stop pandering pointment taxes
That's not good stops filing these quarterly reports
Need to be filed in order for
Employees to file their taxes
Paperwork is hard
Administrative leave f****** these people over
Whether or not it's all because of
Of course the issue
Never just
These people don't pay tax
If you take the money
Absolutely believe it always end up getting
An amended tax return filed they were trying to make
The tax liability for the business
$0
And reflect that they were entitled to refund
$65,000 for both 1996
130 thousand dollars from the governor
Quit it because he's a member of
The promoters
Of a false and criminal ideology
Tubalcain
Jake Atkinson attacks lawyer who studies textbook New York Times
It's hard to convince
Promoters
Promoters make a lot of money off their marks
Watch their marks go to
And then take advantage of the loophole that lets them prepare bogus
Did they characterize as protest
Return prepared at the direction of
The client
What
So
He can get away
As an advisor to the person
Who is Doctor
Taxes doing this disorder
Ask a question of the IRA
Somebody should have stopped at by now or whatever and I just doing this
Direction of
That the client really don't think
At his Direction
You get Santa
Slither away
People like banister could profit profit off this way
Week shift and he knows the when everything falls apart
He can hide behind even week or arguments
Either
Doing something
Not intentionally Criminal
Set the timer at the direction of his
The 2800 fraudulently filed
And ODI rs.10,000
Dollars
Appeals court
He tried to take the matter to
Supreme Court
But they recently said
No thank you
Buy your own bulshit
You can't do it if you can't
Game yourself so now we're three-for-three on Larry becraft I'm not entirely
243 people who actually do like
I meant
Howard Lee head wrap
Bob Shelton
Surprise
Perhaps only because
The perfect example of how these
Deep down even though even more than they're driven by Prince
Bombshells started and ran the weed the people Foundation
For constitutional education
He was the president
Vice president 53 much every other important role in hives
This house like all reputable tax protest
Because he groups who have been given
Status
He's been exempt status
Over the years Bob used by we the people to put out his anti-tax using
A lot of people down the wrong path
Making a lot of money out there
Eventually once Obama was in office
Cuz we the people do different being solely text-based group
Conspiracy theories about how Obama wasn't a citizen
Short fuse wtp money to buy
In the Chicago Tribune
On December 1st and 3rd 2018
And is that
Wood cabin
Thought you know
He would have been fine really speaker
Keep your head down
Just keep your head down and don't attract attention
Into yourself
Stop would not have gotten in trouble for any of
He would be happy as a clam make a nonsense accusation
If you just paid
It taxes
His personal taxes
Oh no we the people was the perfect place for him to hide his money
Court documents reveal that he had made personal
Unsecured loans to WT
BP of over $100,000
Do you practice the entire organization operated
It short the court found that Bob Schultz
Was using attack protesting tax-exempt organization as a quote
Abusive tax shelter
On July 12th 2018 for tax evasion
WTF
The front
I was rejected
In all likelihood end up being in prison
Before too long
Your mother
You just put it in some sort of offshore Bank
Tickets
More fun when you have a
Organization your ass in front of the
Create the tax-exempt business
And then put all of my money in there and that's kind of like a big middle finger to the government
Seat lookup
Smarted your Sixteenth Amendment or whatever or amendments are going to have
We should have stopped at 9
That they're big on the temp on earlier
So now we come to read back managing before the 13th for these
I think that should be the rallying cry for these white instead of blood
Soil and all that stuff
Just be like the amendment before the 13th
Identify doodoo
So
Martin V the headliner of Murderers Row
Martin
Redback
Instagram
Text
He's nineteen eighty-five book the law that never was
The fraud of the 16th Amendment
Is one of the primary drivers behind
And the tax protest movement
Despite the fact the claims made in the book it been repeatedly.
Fraudulent by Court
Novitex protest removal
Existed since before the law.
Never was this book led to Renaissance of idiots
They know something about
Beckman and his co-author William bent
Represent the argument there book
16th Amendment
It was never ratified
And therefore people don't have to pay tax
The courts of review
To be so baseless illegally classified the argument as frivolous
YouTube YouTube
You can hit with a penalty for just trying to make this argument in court
That's like what's your f****** friends like she's legally a fascist
This is legally frivolous
What do you mean you can't just argue that a lot of amendments
Was it actually ratified what's that well
Benson's
Clamdy did a bunch of research
Sound like
The versions that were ratified had punctuation
Places
Katana claims about like
Has looked into all of the claims
No that's good
Originally when his argument started to be used
The same people who got arrested for not paying their taxes
They did review that evidence
Found it
To be lacking
So naturally William Benson was arrested
For not paying your taxes on over 104 years in prison
He tried to appeal in the process insisted that he should
Allowed to have a hearing on whether or not to
Sixteenth Amendment ratified
Icracked
In their decision
Benson is wrong
Thomas which is a previous court case about this
We specifically exam of the arguments made in the law that never was
Concluded that Benson
Did not discover anything
Your honor I would like to challenge the 16th Amendment on the basis of
Existence and everyone had to transcribe it themselves
In 2007 the United States district court for the northern district of Illinois
In his six
16th Amendment
Reliance program
Selling in order to
This is how you get out of paying
They found that selling the 16th Amendment for Life program constituted commercial fraud
He was profiting off giving people
Specifically fraudulent
Advice
Because that was covered by the First Amendment
But that he had to stop selling packages
Some of which cost up to
$100
All red
Play William Benson
Where's all been about William
It's been about Benson
Because he's easier one of these two to get in
William Benson is a fan
Protesting idiot
Red Beckman
Is a monster
Human disguise
So we have our Rodger stone versus our Alex Jones
Call the church.
It was judgement not Holocaust
The Troon almighty God use the people Nazi government religion
Of those with crucified the bride
Bad they talked about the terrible Holocaust of Hitler's Nazi Germany
They are still with us today still worshiping their God Satan
And they're still stealing from the people
Rural fire to create a Federal Reserve banking system
Huh
Call to the Federal reserve's
There is is evil because the thing that the Jews conspire to create it but it's like
Implies in his unwilling to correct
The Jews created the Federal
I think that a lot of people
Side on Alex's side of things
Do you think
Gmail
It's the same thing as a s*** you know what look you want to say bulshit like
The Jews killed our Saviour whatever at least there's some kind of like
Words
Not just like
Do you know what
The Jews killed all the Unicorn
That is true
I don't know why why do we stop yelling at me
Stop it
Also
He has a long history which is
Phraseology
Apology
There's a long history of speaking at whites
Supremacist Gathering
Alex
Should know that
Is every reason to know that in 2009
When he's talking about having him on as a legitimate
294 red suit a whole bunch of people
Including Alan Greenspan
In the US District Court of Montana because back in 1970s
In 1970
7 because he didn't pay his taxes there was a lien placed on it
He just decided f*** it I'm still going to stay here
Even though they're trying to take away
Got everything they're Tangled Up in Westerly
Tying up the courts with frivolous suits to dry in a phone
Come to a head
People seem to have a little bit of
Go great
Read document largely boiled down to Sovereign citizen lines about him not being a person
Like that freeman-on-the-land
And kind of stuff I'm allergic to bees and therefore I am exempt
From taxes
He ended up being evicted from his land
Pita Pit
When he was not going to
Supremacist
Not good no more Waco
When asked about piggies
When asked about things you told them this eviction isn't going to go the way they law enforcement playing
There's going to be enough guns to make sure of that
The law enforcement plant
Kicked off then doubt a burn down
Okay I'm not going to I'm not going to know
Long after long after he gets vacated the premises
Pictures that you put those in the same setting
Together I understand what kind of confusing
Exactly plan Weber.
Loud later
Later
The dude Bob Schultz Tom Cryer red Beckman
Do Alex says are legitimate tax researchers
I think we've shown
They are not
Yeah
Who has failed over and over again to make argument
Courts that they shouldn't have to pay taxes
Is largely gotten in big trouble because of it
You can't preach the things you're preaching because it illegally fraud
So
Okay
Come on
Hannibal
Backpack
Oh okay alright
Piecraft
He's the only one who successfully do you know that you're right
My brother
We don't need to worry about that
Like I said bring them to the end of March
First of all if you robbed
Like people who are less reputable than these five
We refused at a barbershop
Goodwin the beat
You can never goofy or troop than these after
They're all crazy
Very wrong
Search and they are a ragtag band of Heroes
Infiltrate
Turn up
Don't like I said we're going on a little bit of
The 4th gear just because
I didn't want to end on that like laundry list of tax protesters
The 4th
Alex is like he's mad at Glenn Beck
Brewing Shore a little bit
I'm starting to get
Much more frustrated with Glenn Beck
Doesn't really go anywhere
You kind of mad about the idea that
Glenn Beck
Talkin about
FEMA camps
I'm being like I do I got to research this I don't know if I can
I was like that's my bread-and-butter grind
I'm going to
Half hour
Finger finger
Whenever I try and do that
I just have too much of it
You're all the time for people with all the evidence
I'm so unlike
Weird
About abortion
And talking about how like
If you're sorry you can repent
And all this stuff not mentioning his own history with abortion
It's really weird
Dimensions of stories doesn't
From the Miami Herald about an abortion
Doctor Who Threw baby up against the wall and then threw it in the garbage and ate it for a couple days while the baby was still alive
None of that is in there
It's the wall like the baby Odin money
Yeah
Start a Shakedown this penis
Stories
About is absolute
They happened
They were doing with malpractice
And they do deserve
Cast of all the rest
Eating a baby
Who's alive in a trash can for days really don't think I could do that
Possible
And not in the article
Can't find that anywhere except Alex's
Weird brains
But it's down
Crazy
He ends up
Like he said he was going to get
Get into the FEMA camps
20 minutes
Well the rest is greater than the guy who covers the rat eating babies
Might be
But it's
Glory will come when we defeat
Globalist that's when you have the Clipper he's talking about
Didn't have time
This is 20 minutes
Alright
I can't
They makes no sense
If you want to prove it prove it
Clearly is motivated by
Papa Keno's
He feels guilt about but doesn't want a process that guilt now so does this
Rambling diatribe
About nothing
Now it's like you know how when you studied really hard for
And you know everything about that
But
You have a little bit of
So the night before
No you don't really sleep and then the next morning
You can't stop thinking about drawing
Incredible
Metallica's most recent album
That is the only thing that happens to everybody so sometimes
You're going to prove that the government is destroying everybody's lives with FEMA
Start talking about rats eating a fetus and then from there other than
I'm the greatest there ever was
Boba
One Clip that I wanted to play from this episode of the part that I watch
Because I think it's
I think it's indicative of a couple of inter
Trusting thing
They were still tracking
And Alex is at 3
Like we be here all day
If we were
7:40
Metaphorically
Go down that route
I would probably
It was just
Whoopi Sher
So you
In terms of us following
A coherent
Because I'm controlled it's conspiracy theory
Next
Russia
Flash
It's just incredible propaganda
But Alex
Describing the sort of Russo Georgia
Is very clearly indicative that I just
He is
Hook Line & Sinker believe in the Russian lion
Because what happened
It's not at all the way you've described they were separate
Ndi application region in South Australia
They started attacking ethnic Georgian villages
It started ethnically cleansing Georgians
Out of those areas
Georgia
Sovereign territory
Was George
Started fighting back
Against those.
Separatist
Who believe themselves to be
Closer live with Russia Russia started
Eventually
The conflict Georgia was more complicated than
Giving a service
It's not
Is very clear indications that the Southpaw sessions
Were actually
On in Russian
In order to Annex
Parts of Georgia
To the Soviet Union
When was the last
Russia was the
Goodguys in any kind of action towards
Consolidating the old Soviet Union back
And also they have occupied
Seems like another insta
Russian incursion
Galaxy
You know taking the Russian line on
Which onion is fine
Be more upfront about what
Truth
We want to believe the truth is
Who's going to save us
From the New World Order
Jesus believed that since 2000
Something worthwhile
To bring into our
Fear
This investigation
Because
It's not a part of whatever change
You don't say
Like all the other stuff is still different
Yeah military stuff the pro net neutrality
The anti-israel pro
Business
That's very different than where he will end up being
But the brushes stuff is always been
It's always been there
Is that what it really is
I mean in 2015 when he was talking all that stuff about I like Putin May save the world
When you talk about that talks about it being like a masculine
In state
What is like a testosterone to
Murdered
Close to a Christian
I think he believes that which is crazy
Any like if he looks into Russian Orthodox Church
It would be like oh no nevermind
I think he believes those store
Things on a baseline level
Russian media
Being very
Accommodating to his anti-west
There's different
There's different reasons
I know that Alex
Alex is anti New World Order
Yeah
And
Putin and his Circle
Or anti
Atlantis ism
The western western Europe
The United States any kind of
Allow
Them two
Encroach on their neighbors and what have you
Alex peas
Russia
To have him on
As an expert
And sing
He sees Russian M staying very similar
He doesn't understand that the reason for that is very interested
By weakening
The alliance
States in Europe
He thinks like I know about the globalist they're on the same team
Flattery I just I just have a heart
I think it's partially flattery partially like
Twisted familiarity
Perhaps but he sees a lot of his worldview mirrored not realizing the reason that it's mirror
Is because both
Destructive to
Status quo
Maybe
Fruit for the amount of water
That just doesn't
Enough you know what I don't know if he's doing that much
Carrying now I think it might be the sort of thing
Grows over time
Goodbye
I think that's probably
Probably the
I don't know it's weird
Navarre
A little a little
It's kind of like
Satisfying in terms of like what we're looking for
But it is what it is I like the idea that we got to learn about these weirdo
American speed like these trends
Bloons TD Transit
I've already been established
Early 2000
Racino pivot we
Alex not be interested at all
Almost a week now after the Tea Party
Disapproval of Glenda
Yeah I think is Glenn Beck star starts
And of course
Michael weiner
Michael wieners.
She's one of the first people I was saying these things what do you do
He's a wiener
What we see what happens in the near future
For now
I'm not super interested in
Alex's
Present
Situation
Twitter and I've kicked off
Apple
ITunes app
Yep kicked-off yep
I mean we're just going to see
Google see what happens
It's not all that
Too much into the world
Go to schottenfreude
His painting
I know it's easy to feel that it's fun
Productive
I think I think it's going to let him wash down the drain and then
Become whatever you become
And in the meantime I think
Interesting to see what
Let him slide down the banister
Check out our website knowledge fight.com
Knowledge underscore forever
Can talk about Alex Jones
Cause
Very serious harm
Two people and privacy
Slander Folk
Which we try not to do and if you would like to hear us not do that
The sporting a show really appreciate it
Have I got
Word or the
One of the problems might be the we don't have
Goals
Up on the patreon
We had two goals up and the two of them were roles that we just went ahead and fulfilled before
Or even hit the one with the live show of now
The other was breakdown one of the documentary
Right and I realize like I didn't know what to
To do with any other goals
But it
Inspired by it or whatever
That's why I've stuck to new goals
Yeah on the on the patreon
Which were working towards one of them will do another
Okay
Probably not The Obama Deception
I'm not sure we'll figure it out but we'll do another documentary if we reach that other goal
I'm calling my magnum opus
People have asked me to put out a book
A book
Don't want
So I've come up with another form
To put out the information I would put in a book
I'll start releasing it
If we hit that goal
Probably serve releasing it at some point anyway but if we get it I will feel guilty if we haven't started
I'll put it that way
Alright appreciate it
If you have if you don't and you want to help us work towards
Anyway
Has been fun
But
What did Alex Jones
That is
You probably killed a dude
Alexandra Thurston color