Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Work
Yes sir
First video game
Justin Lee My grandma likes play video game
Little bit of a
What you do is she would get the video game stats
Play it's all the game she wanted to play and then
Some came out
He would give us the old
So I got an Intel like that
At least that was the story
She bought us a Nintendo and that was sort of like what she
Send it
Remind me original
A lot of Mario Super Mario Brothers 3
My parents
They hated television
Video game
I'm so me and my brother were allowed
Play half an hour of video games
Or an hour if you play together so we would generally try and find ways to play together
What is kind of difficult
Single player
You got to keep doing it over and over
That's why I was such a revolution Nintendo came out
Donkey Kong Country
It was on
Because that was a super fun cartoony game like my parents wouldn't allow it
Yeah we had the super cartoony fun platform game
With two players
And I'd like
But of course my brother
Maybe daddy
Whatever
Call families R Us
One of the reasons why I was like I have
Play every Donkey Kong Country
Comes out
Nostalgia
And like warm
Is because all of those times that I spent playing with my brother
That's super we boy
It was of the devil
Destroying
Revolution
No it's not yourself
That's a good thank you that's a good transition
Donors
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Also
Is
The guy who kills
The Galaxy
Life the universe and everything
We find out that
Now I can't remember
Who cares what I think you might also that might also be the name of one of the characters
Two of The Wire
Greek himself
Someone who has
Was policy wonk bumped it up we really appreciate it
Thank you so much Williams
I'm a policy wonk until your brilliant someone someone sodomites
Jordan we got an episode to do today
The time for Wacky Wednesday
As we're calling it
Consulted on that
It's not alright alright
Talk about project
Camelot have a ton of new listeners who
And some people may be slightly
Confused by why we cover Project Camelot which is
About the secret space program a crazy weirdo
Who show up the carry
Just believes every
Some people might not understand
Connection to Alec
What's Jones
These worlds Baker is also some
That we talked about
And I think today is
Episode is going to do an amazing job
Verbally
Laying out
Why we do this
Why are these worlds
I think you'll see as this goes along
Exactly
Psychiatric
No no no I mean
Alright
Play this the end of the last episode
Turn it off once
We have some new goals
On our patreon page
Level
So if you are someone who
It was thinking about donating to the show thinking about supporting what we do and you were like
Well I really just want to hold back until there's something
Concrete
Now there is
What's the point close to Jim Bakker with the alayka I know someone out there is a good time right now
Photobucket
Just didn't like
Goals
Dot-com click
Check that
Anyway sorry I didn't mean to interrupt
To the actual
Episode
For that that salesmanship
Gets on your plate
Jordan
In the last
Little bit sport of interviewing Eddie page
Getting interviewed on Kerry Cassidy show
On a weekly basis
Use on again
Recently
Yep and so I was like hold on I think he realized
MainSource
Is in prison
If you can't talk to him as much as
There's an opening for someone else to come in
MP her
Varsity player
Substitute teacher
Yeah
Correctly suck that out
He's trying to step into that hole
Do to get a recurring spot on Friday
Camelot
And then she's like what
You have no Backbone in your old willing to let Terry sort of guide
Narrative
Pretty f****** races
The idea that Kerry Cassidy has not come back up on the
This episode
About a lot more like tell me about honestly I might not
Like
Check this out
In bed like
But it was Draco information
Owl
If we don't, it's not going to get out into the mainstream news death
To our listeners
So every page is a Canadian whistleblower and I should be around
My fourth or fifth interview with him
To try to Project Camelot YouTube channel
D d i e and you should find all the interviews
So after you watch this
Highly recommend that you go and find the other interviews because we covered quite a lot of ground
Interview
Your shirt
All you need to do is go to the YouTube search
And then typing Eddie page and that's
DIA
And then you're going to want to watch those videos now the only way
Is if you move your mouse
Cursor
Click with one click not your right click
Click on the left side
People who are 85 years old
Iprep
Eddie
How many is birth name is Tommy Coleman Jr
But also let's not worry about theirs might be alright
Absolutely almost
Will my birthday
What the truth is
Behind whether or not they're lying about being
Military
Anyway
Next clip
You like
The f*** are you doing back bro
I know the Draco invasion is in the title
But I need to know more
I need to let you lay out
What's going on
I opened up the discourse
It disappointed
Nauru
Planet X
At 9 is NASA now has admitted they know of
For a long time
Force
How long has Burstein our galaxy is been noted by ancient culture
And when
The Ancients called it the Flying Dragon the dark dragon the red dragon the Dark Star the Death Star
Biblical teachings color wormwood
Bruce Willis called at the fifth
All planetary systems in this galaxy
He is coming in
Tutela
Nibiru is coming back
Nibiru wormwood all these names referred zecharia sitchin called
The 12th Planet
Explain it to
Zecharia sitchin wrote that book it was the 12th
Planet because he had also
Just added an extra couple if you don't know what team
Kitchen believes that there was another planet Nibiru
Time
Cricket
The moon as I understand the asteroid
Mostly from Miss translating and
Just making stuff
Trickshot
Yeah
Long way to go
Who created over billions of years from space
Also
Be the home of the
The fabled Anunnaki
The Ancient Aliens
Okay
But there's so much to do
The idea that Planet X was coming back into orbit near Earth was one of
The primary preoccupation
The people who said that the world is going to end
December 21st 2012
As they related
The elongated
Baktun Long Count cycle
Calendar
To the very long orbit the de imagen de Peru would have to have
To escape notice
For all of these astronomers have been able to witness
Okay
So you could say that
Most people thought that
Nibiru
Was going to come
I'm through December 12th
21st 2012
It's hard because of the
I'm sorry
We Are The Sugarhill Gang no need to show off your skills
Diculous
In order for it to
Of people's ability to
So they come up with ideas but it
Goodyear
The orbit
Supposed to
Why not it's not
That's the part that NASA does it make
Possibly true
Is it there's a theoretical possibility that there's a bunch
Like a large planet
That is outside of our ability to observe it
They don't know that it exists
They don't say it does
But there are wobbles in orbit that would be explained by a giant
A giant a giant planet like
The out there
Create that slight wobble
Probably isn't
Necessarily true
And also based on how far I would have to be out it would have been thrown out
Of the orbit
So if there were something
Close to what
People who believe in
That's probably impossible
But
Believe in
The Planet X
They suggest
Set the calendar that the Mayans
It was actually
Itself used to track the time
We're here
From Planet X
So the Anunnaki made the mind
So they were running out hours
Here's the thing
The population of the world because they
Nothing like that
Destroyed
Somehow this makeup and
Fix the
So run out of conductors
There was a bit of a miscommunication between the print Princesa and
Belittling of the Anunnaki people
For the last time
Well if you're talking to
It brings in all of his mistranslation to Samaria a little bit of
The fight I don't remember the rest
Those books
Pappadeaux's bacterol very super
But the thing is the idea of this planet didn't start
2012 Syria
Or 12 or 9
Whatever it was first put out by a woman
Who believed yourself you been chosen by aliens
From Zeta reticuli who communicate with her through a chip
Put in her brain
He was chosen as a Paul Revere type toward mankind of the imminent coming of Planet X
Sitting back in 1995 at which point she assured everyone that this was going to happen in May 2003
She was wrong
She claimed that the alien specified that dated a white lie
Meant to guarantee that the establishment on Earth did not interfere with the alien
Very unspecific plan
So after they destroy the Earth
Her contention was that this information is important for both enemies
Exactly
You're going to come up with something that's a little bit more interesting than saying like I f***** up a digit somewhere
Now unfortunately a week before the supposed date of the arrival of Planet X
Most popular radio station K-Rock
And advised listeners to euthanize their pets so they wouldn't have to suffer when Planet X arrive
But she may be responsible for more dead dogs than Alex Jones
Because
K-Rock is a
Huge radio.
And
Some people took her at her word
Hate to do it
Put my dog down
Whatever religion
Destroys every $20
The moment that it was supposed to happen
Hysteria is real
From that point on the idea of Lakers
Nancy L
Planet X
Zecharia sitchin
Most people don't really even know the difference
Nancy's all about that
Connection of credibility because most people don't know
Takes a crisis
Turn on the other half
Who's responsible for somebody dead.
In 2017 a completely insane Christian numerology
Just named David Mead started propagating
Theory that Nibiru was inbound to go to
MSY Perth
In September twenty
He based his theory on misreading scripture tying and tons of unrelated and false conspiracy theories
A little bit about astronomy
I'm at date came naturally said he had
If your numbers wrong
He's not as creative as Nancy
Eclipse the Sun and North Korea China and Russia would launch a nuclear attack on the United States
Earth would be devastated by a series of earthquakes
Lordship by 30°
United States and Barack Obama would be elected president for an unconstitutional third term
Let him stay in there until we get that s*** worked out
B12 because you got a you got to remember that that was theirs
Popular fear
You're back then
They're always so sad that dumb pets
Credible
Who is going to make sure barakett the Third
Stick with the red dragon exploding or whatever the f*** you're talking about
I'm having a difficult time because
Would have already been elected
I don't understand how he saying that Obama would be Alexa
Good for a third
I just made
Killed in the
Android
You're right I apologize I forgot
Search for 25 years now.
Not so talented planet
A heading for earth that's full of malevolent to alien
If use that to sell book
Videos go viral
Does a real-life Messenger on Earth from another world
Every time
David wrong
And shown to be liar
So
Is coming on
To bring that into the world.
We did this 6 years ago rehashing 2012 stuff that was a big
Embarrassment for my community
But he's doing the same thing I know it's time for the same
Are we need a remake of Spider-Man one more time ever again Spider-Man
We now
What are you talkin about that
Yeah that's
What do you talk
Sing about
He's literally talk about the same thing
This is not new
You know
Anunnaki
Because of this
Friends
What we started the ancient Sumerian
Darkstar
The dark
Prepared
Cannibalistic events
Soon follow
So he's friends with
Did he say
Chronicle Expedition got really high with him
Earth Chronicle
Aromatherapy degree
Fresh lavender
I would be like yeah I bet you did
7 friends
First of all
He's dead you can do whatever you want
It seems like
Who's crazy
No compunction about life
So
Or just believe in bulshit
You think if he was friends with an alien
Why wasn't
They can't allow him on Ancient Aliens
They would have to have they would have to come down with the concrete
Because he'll we got one of them
Right
The season finale though right
Surprise
We got
And then
Really like
I felt so
Worried
That like
All the episodes
Alien
He was on it I've seen nothing come up
Because he wasn't talking
This b******* back on there
Self
It's a big problem whenever anyone is relying on snitching to make their argument because the
Reasons are to plenty
I know that I was Joan says that sort of thing like
I want to prove this to you but I can't cuz I've so much
But in this case that is
Kind of true
We're just going to do a great
I'm not even going to do that but I'ma tell everyone where they can
Can go
You should be very skeptical
Because
Claims to be a linguistic
$6
His work shows that he has absolutely no idea how to translate Sumerian or Aramaic
How did he claimed
Upon which this whole argument is based
His translation is what
He's basing all of this on
Experts
Who have studied gorgeous day like
No
It's not
Vacations
He also doesn't know anything about
Hebrew and in fact
From his works like
Stairway to Heaven
To not know the difference
Hebrew and Aramaic
Which is a big problem
That seems in Port
Just because the latter is look similar than a lot of cases
Does not mean that they're the same language
He's running the East room
The old kind of goes into a small village
And then surprise
The only one who can communicate with this person he might as well be
Just make stuff up
The matches predetermined meaning
As is the case with his translation of nephelym
The possibly mean quote
People of the fiery rocket
There's literally nothing in any language that he's coming from
That is close to
Mentor people of the fiery rocket
Citron scholarship is
Complete ship
If you want to learn more about this
Go to
Ww.w
This is a site run by dr. Michael S Heiser
With a PhD
Hebrew and somatic studies and was
Biblical literature Regional
For the Pacific Northwest
Very academic minut details
Exactly what
Kitchen Miss Translate
Why it matters
I would love to get into it like
The reason that I'm just saying go to that website
If you want to learn more about all of it is because
I can't sit here
And like
I don't know
Credibly explain to you why it matters
If there's a yellow.
In the middle of the word in
Kitchen just ignores it
Write in words
Assuming
Come from one root
When in reality
Because the morphology of the word
It's clear it means some
Okay so there's just like there's
I understand
When I read it but
Explain it to you
You can visit my website
Www.is ditching wrong.
And when you go to that page there's a
Just a big banner that says yes and it's a link to
Also this guy Michael Heiser
Michael Heiser
Has repeatedly
Offered
Debate
And he is never X
Even like I used to
He has on his
Coast to Coast AM
Multiple
Is offered
Do you like to debate
An antigen
Not do it
Which kind of
Could be
The circuit
Lived in
You can just make sure it up
You just makes it up that people know about
But because nobody knows about Sumerian but like five people especially
Awareness
Of the language
And it's really easy to pull a con on because it's
To most of
What is taught in history class
Really easy to
Trick people with
Video
The veneer of it
Exotic
Yeah
Sumerian
Like stuff I know a little bit enough to be
Idiot about it I mean
It's just like a unrelated
Like it's not it doesn't have a an aunt
Decedent
Forms of language I can't speak to that fall out of credibility
Disabled
You know what I have a theory that I'm working
I think it has a pretty solid grounding in reality
I think that Eddie page just read zecharia sitchin book
He's kind of repeat
Feeding them
I think that might be a whole lot
Of his sort of
Worldview
Yeah maybe a lot of it is
Just here
He's just
Reciting
And stuff from searching
When we understand who the Fallen one
The Watcher angels
They were warriors
And they were giants
So now
Piper Warrior
We're here to protect
The first creation the Atom Man
Is mentioned in the Book of Enoch the Watchers
And you know again you haven't you have a garden here
Separate the flowers from the weed
Specifically
Translation
Got that idea of the Watchers
Is the Nephilim being the Fallen one
Stuff like that
Heiser's
One of these
Going to the explanation
That he provides
Is about the idea of
Nephilim
Fallen
And that is a mist
That's describing the root word being the verb
The fall
Approved
Very very
Easy-to-follow explanation
Open explanation is
You can have with ebru
If you don't speak
A very thorough explanation
Otherwise I can't
Abita root word
Cancellation
Leads me to believe
But he is just red
Zecharia sitchin
Kim's work
It doesn't even look like it's more like they were the Three Stooges
They were the fallen ones they were the ones
To fall regularly and
Yeah
Three Stooges
Harbingers of chocolate
They were giants
Metaphorical but they were giants
Industry
TV
The Vaudeville
So I don't believe a lot but that already
Southbay pulling up
Nephilim the barouche it
He's a no
This guy's got some
F****** academic
Background
You don't know that about it
Yeah man
What with a voice like that
Master's degree and Jill set
Very proud of my education
Money goodbye
Thankfully the government pay for that education
Anyone feel but I do know what's going on
So
Geophysics
Buford
Y'all make your own conclusion
So now this is where it becomes difficult is the fact is that his birth name is Tommy Coleman Jr
Going by Eddie page when you talk about all this alien stuff
Facebook
Zoeva 3rd Michael Wolff Michael Wolff
Do you write that book Wolfe
Not with you at
Alright
So now we have Tommy call him Junior Michael Wolff
Form of his actual name
I don't f****** know I can't
None of this makes sense
But who cares
Probably not
Because of the like murkiness of the
Guaranteed you're going to spend a week your f****** life trying to get to the bottom of it and maybe you won't
Why I'm going to go
You can skip all that
Because he just said the government paid for his education
Along with his brothers and sisters
Would kind of implies to me that what he is
Over and over and protecting him all the time
They then paid for his education
I don't believe that you're getting the Palladium scholarship
No true true
But he would say is that he was in Vietnam
Days or whatever but it's
Didn't pass in real time when he was shot or whatever and then the aliens put them back together and then
We came back and he was in the CIA or whatever
So that would have been the time when he was getting his master's degrees like when he's
Although he said he was like
Overseas
Whatever for
The timeline doesn't work out at all and it's going to get even worse as we go through this episode
Literally impossible
To be true
I don't know
ATMs to go to college
If it were a part of
GI Bill
I don't think the GI Bill covers
I'm not entirely sure
I didn't look into that
I can't say but he's argument
Alien
The government then
Pay for him
His buddies to go to college
That
Just to see if they could do it you got to do what you got to do experiments on them
So let's do our first experiment
Can you guys
Ticketmaster
I want a couple more clips
Is there before we do
Blown wide open
First
Here's some good news
Tiamat got hit by nav
America
The Earth
Not going to
You search music at their your conspiracy
Shield around it
It will pass within
When I say
Asteroid
Minority
We're in person
Dark Day
I'm just trying to read through his subjects
A lot of is worldview
Especially when he starts talking about the dracos
Dangerous
Expression of his
Yeah that sounds right
Isaac
Drake
Going to get that done
Closer to
Massive planet
2 million miles
Wouldn't it
Just by being
Like I'm pretty sure that that is
Really f****** close as far as Giant
How far away is the Moon
You know what else dude also fuckis up
Way before it was
All sorts of effects happening
Comical about the people who are like if you looks
Like pretty much right at the Sun
Right off to the side of it that's In The Boro
The fuk up
You could get a pill
It's coming it
It's from that direction and that's why telescopes camp
Coming from behind the Sun
Right
Because her access is even tilted
No it can't just hide
But that was one of the arguments of why I like that's what a lot of people
You know how bad the arguments
Level of thinking but
The only reason I bring that up is because
Advocate
That f****** planet
It's going to be affecting us in a very serious way
I'm not sure how big it is
Bigger than Jupiter
Like I don't think
Carbon-based
Planets
You're f****** really don't think you're out
Your daps
As a master's degree in jio
It doesn't make any
Of course I really don't think
Has superpowers
He basically said it was supposed to be seen in 2017
You could say there been some sightings of it
And I'm also wondering if it has the ability to do what I call interdimensional
Like any
Probably music
A rapid speed
Because I believe it can appear and reappear
Depending on where you
It is
What what do you think
Very credible
You're watching this my hat's off to you brother I'm praying for you
He's known me for a long time and I just wish I could talk with him or
What is happening right now
Hyperdimensional
It is also a
It is under intelligent control
Okay
Dealing with a planet that can create
Rosen Bridge reality whatever it likes
Intelligent
Traversing the universe
It was simultaneously here and not here always
Look this is.
This is
Ridiculously
What do you even do with it
It's a f****** big that star out there real hard-hitting research
You got it
We need to interview
Stitching is wrong
Right
Otherwise how will we ever know
New school reading sites
Plenty of examples of
Into the idea that it is a hyperdimensional
Planetary size
Spaceship
Ludacris
I think that's all we need to say about that because I want
To get to this
Is where the timeline
I can't even
Okay
Labor working Theory
First
You just read zecharia sitchin stuff and he
He's co-opting it
Fit
Is Kerry Cassidy
Larry nickel
Almost certainly wasn't associated with polarity
So are you ready page
Are you ready for the timeline
Busted
And I don't know I mean I know you've been tested I when you work for the military cetera as a psychic
And I know you would do that
Is there anything else in the public domain if you can talk about where you can improve
That what you said was
What's true in that case
Came out later in other words have you done any other predictions that
People might recognize
I don't have all the documents here in front of me and
Talk about it that you can send documents to me later and I can post
And I will talk about it
United States President Ronald Reagan
Great Britain
Eddie was at
David and 86
Yep
Alright
No no.
Don't worry about that for now
Why didn't you bring this up
Well he was but he was the one I would assume
I would like to ask him about that
I mean like this
Your first time on the f****** show I would assume he be like
Give you a lot of credibility brought up in
It's such nonsense but
You talk about a lot of great friends to call Bart Ronald Reagan
Great friend
I'm the guitar up and having they like any we could use you on base
I'll be up there later boys
Actually was friends with all of this
Dead Prez
Not friends with any of the living presidents
Is George h.w.
Now hear me out on this
Cuz I was friends with him
He sort of calls out h.w. bush
More concerned about
Assassination attempt
Play mr. president
Especially
Yep
Sounds right
In what
Looking for my brother
You talking about the Bible guys
Is funny is I received from President Reagan and George Bush
Why aren't you talk about this with the president
Ronald Reagan would look me Square in the eye and he says what is
We will see the rising temperature will see strange weather pattern
The big dragon
Is sitting
In our living room
And we will see multiple multiple
Destructive
Before this planet arrive
The Earth's center will
Eric Bullock
This is my favorite and perhaps most creative way to be a climber
Pretty impressive
If Yellowstone
No no no planet is making a burger coming
Inside
So George h.w. Bush
Did not enjoy the present
He was trying to help Ronald Reagan figure out
What you was going
To do about this
I have a lot more respect for HW now that I know that
Stair 48 hours straight
That's in any kind of no contest
That was a 2-minute long clip where you explain the interaction
With Reagan and Bush
Raise already said that he's good friends
One play this one more time another clip work
Reconfirm
But he talked about aliens with
You're talking about
How you were you're dealing with Reagan so you're saying that you were talking about this back in the days when Reagan was
Absolutely
Now
Here's where that is problematic for
That sounds like a Robert Evans
About aliens
Was Ronald Reagan
George h.w.
And this is after he showed us
The video of him
Bob Chapman was there
Advise President Reagan Vice President Bush in 1986
The Draco aliens
Nibiru
Is a slight problem
Because you didn't know anything about
On February 10th 1991
No no no
He didn't know anything about being a Pleiades
Nope
It doesn't work it just doesn't work
It doesn't work
Absolutely doesn't work there's no way for this all to I mean
You know with me would be like
Fractured logic of people
Spinning yarn
Obviously it would be something along
Story workout right right
I remote
View into the past of my own brain
The stops that his narrative comes from
Happened because
Regression
Videotape
These these exist
Of him
Coming to his
His awareness
Inter 1991 repressed his memories
Advising Reagan about
He knows about aliens
That should be like
Lake Michigan Beach any shocking to him
To learn all this stuff
It's nonsense when you be shocked
You just found out that years ago you would hung out with the president
Shocking if you found out that
Pictures of badass
Yeah kind of pretty as that O'Shucks any kind of avoid
Carrie is Charmed by this somehow I don't understand it
At all
Like that
But that like those
On par with the documents
He flashes up on camera
Weather
Fuchsia
Later this episode
Question from the chat room that is accusing of being a temp
He pulls out from
I don't know some f******
It's like it's literally like if he was
Being on a Wheaties box
This is a this is a picture of today's newspaper in 1986
There is no
The Templars the Tif
It looks like just something
Turn it off and look at it like a
Like a bad printer
Frames do and then he always
Flash up on screen to stuff
Just like fire
Horlick even on the other episode
She was talking to him about all the metals you received from the Army
Like all of us
Titles
Represent the real metal
Sure guy
Call Eddie
Do better the only thing that I would accept as if somebody called him a cowboy
You're goddamn right
Surprised at this point to learn that not only
Is Eddie into a lot of horseshit
He's also into
Ostradamus
What
Sumerian
Oh yeah real quick because you was taught by zecharia sitchin which I would say even if that's true
That means you don't know how to repost
This was mine
Historical
With a master's in journalism
I did my job good thoroughly well
Understanding the theology
History
I forgot that Nostradamus his name was Mikhail G Nostradamus I thought it was just a guy named Michael
Nostradamus
I'll recite it to learn about
Man
You know what
WhatsApp
His other name
Notarized
Can't do it
Can come up with
Fear of a
But not everywhere
She's going to go somewhere
It takes a nation of millions to hold us back
I don't think I've done perfect job of selling us out just yet
I made the claim that I believe that on this episode we
Receive much more of a
Link
Between the worlds Project Camelot and Alex Jones
They should make clear why this is still a relative
Use of our sphere even though it's
Ludacris
Wacky dude
Lying about space
In their cunning form
They will return
I do believe that will be the return
Okay
I don't know nothing
Should I carry
Very good
Mister
Brock
Loan
Fisher
Is there a Brock Lesnar
Okay Mr Brock if you're watching answer you got some of your flunkies watching
Anticipating your reply
Putting on the spot
I wouldn't hold your breath
I won't either
I don't believe
Brock long has years from now
Making stuff up
I know Maria I got a flood of that up pretty hard
But
Want to tell me something about
Future
Is going to happen
Break because FEMA director has told
Yeah
So
That's stupid
Is he even going to be the FEMA director
Orbitz
To go conspiracy
Yeah if you know what's going
Be happening
December 20th 2020
Getting ready for the election
Finally when we were going to redo 90210 September 20th
Does Trump knows he's going to lose
They're going to fake an Uber ride
You know
How many people work
Lighter to the ground
How many people do
Look
It doesn't matter cuz I one person
Works there Brock long
Don't believe
Whatever
This is just more s*** that like
Verify his school history
It doesn't say where you went to school
The same thing here it's just okay Brock long told me this s***
Google who's the head of FEMA
Play me talk to you he's never going to address it
This guy's lying
Things to worry about
Also I think
Said something along the lines of
Broccoli
Put on the Cowboys
Metaphorically put on the cowboy hat
I said that this is very similar to
Alex's work because
And now in this next clip
It becomes far more
I've been told by whistleblowers that there is a
Storage shelf life.
Things that need repair on the planet
Likey no railroads and infrastructure
Airport
And that there is a great deal of things right now that are in need of repair that they're not bothering
And that they're also trying to move populations as she says there's evidence growing evidence and I'ma
This as well
Through my own intuition I dreams
So on of a movement that people away from the coast
And also to get them away from
Being out in the
Outlying areas so they won't
Have lands they won't be able to have their own well
They won't have their own water they'll have to allpak into FEMA camps and all this time thing
So that when anything's strikes regardless of what it is people will be
Vulnerable
Before you
False Flags
Entirely
Exactly the same as what
You into FEMA camps
In order to take away your autonomy
You're not fixing the roads and f******
What are we doing
It's not it's not like there aren't people who are pushing
Ford
It is because people allocate money in the wrong place
Any generally allocated towards
Rich people
In the same way that like
Eddy's using like this idea that Nibiru is coming
Explain away the effects of climate change
Carrie is using this
Conspiracy of trying to
The Forsyth
Explain why Rich oligarchs don't want to pay for public goods
Republic
Why are libraries
Deteriorating and no one cares about them
Probably if
I do not like
It's like all of these people
Smart enough to know
What problems
The problems are supposed to like your your right-wing where they're just like climate change has even happened shut up
Oligarchs are destroying our
I'm still racist so I can't be on the liberal side
So maybe it's just a lie
People who are all of them
Deal with the solution because it's associated with the people that they don't like
Definitely not racist reason
So if you recognize the problem
Then make up a different problem and call that when the solution
Climate change
You know there are problems
You're talking about
Did they have
Answer
The problem
Jiggle around with the answer
Is because they're trying to sell something
Denial
Whole cloth
The reality that people see in front of them
They have to just come up with a different
Explanation that serves there
Weird
Yeah cuz cuz
Rich people
You can't pull the same like just deny it
Right right operating the margins like a Little Lamb
Basically
Here's another clip
Pretty Infowars adjacent
Now I would I would like to do however is
Talk about
What you think is the motivation
For keeping the
The return of Planet X Nibiru wormwood whatever they want to call it
From the people in other words
Are you of the opinion that they are going to basically try to
Put people in FEMA camps that you've seen maybe the coffins and things they've showed
Is this is this your understanding
I will tell you this
Again
Nothing hidden by any
Government
Good luck
Organ harvesting
Get rid of the dead body
Easier ways to get organs outside
Are they cut
Are they cut your head off and then get
The Morgans are they like
Jordans out to preserve the organs
Look at the dump what's a great explanation for why the government would be hiding
Cuz we're not worried about
I would probably a reason
Brielle why they would talk about it
Directions 84th Street
Specifically
Created by right-wingers in order to try and lock up
Sprite with an ox
Something
Continue playing
It was not something
Has
Talk about all the FEMA
Camp s*** in relation to Alex
Sawbuck
Is really disgraceful
People's arguments
There are
Preparation
The Federal Emergency Management
Is making
Shoot
Catastrophic
If they didn't
80-page
Alex Jones Kerry Cassidy
Will be the first people standing up and being like
Government
They would be the people who were victimized
Preparation
They're not coming from an honest
Place
If they were they would actually look at the reality
Of these programs
And what is
Made up and what is real and they like
For Global
Fetty WAP
Who would be angry like at anybody
Preparing for anything they're like
Oh you're preparing for us
Do you know what that mean
You don't know what's going to happen
You can't see into the future so you're going to make it
The magical thinking of people who believe that
Planet-sized
Spaceship out there that
Enphase in and out of existence
Oregon
I don't have a club
Eddie
But
God is an idea created by
Project Camelot
Auto
Carrie and all of them believe in angels
It like that no doubt
Damn
Geophysics
Yeezys all kinds
Title would not become have
Is a word
He has an exit strategy
There is ships out there waiting too well
Not the rapture
It is an extraction
Because the final battle
Right here on terra firma
All right so what
Interesting that you're being so specific about it and I do appreciate that so people
Will certainly
Vibrant
I appreciate it
I like
I like what she
She just did
Some Judo right
How do you mean I mean when she said like
I'm glad you're being so specific you're being so specific about it which I appreciate
He was really saying like
Don't be specific about it you're saying this dumb s*** on my shows as disprovable I don't I don't want
This to be I don't want to look like an idiot for having you on don't state-specific s*** this is
Do you want to continue to be a guest for those years leading up
To the date of your prediction
Eventually want to write a book I'll help you sell
You better not
Can say something
So
You know
I think he's full of s***
But
Man we've got this
Everything is leading towards
FEMA camps
Similarity with the world
And do we get another one
Huge but
I mean there's overlap
Underneath the Vatican City
That he's referring to another guest of Project Camelot that he is not a fan
Believe misled Carey
Who cares
You're talkin about a layer
Draconian in influence
Ask yourself this
Why did the St Peter's Basilica have a throne
The Throne of Lucifer
Admiring
Talking about what
And I can tell you that actually ledwith
I asked him about that
So are at least acknowledge
We have a whistleblower called Leo zagami
Did I try to take him over
The last-minute whatnot
Anyway he did a famous interview with us many years ago in which he a great deal
To his credit
About what was under the Vatican
And the black cloak
And a lot of other things going on there
Live.me is a pretty regular guest on Alex Jones another Infowars program talks about
Insider stuff about the vodka
Wendy's on Alex Jones Show with mind-controlled
Parking lot
You gotta know you're already
Depending on who you're trying to
Convince
Drive-thru
Control mix
Very strong antihero
So I mean what are you going to do
Another overlap though
Someone who's a guest
On both of their programs and for some reason
Noah's Leo zagami
He knows everybody in this every single name that anybody out there
Ronald Reagan
Bush
Close friends
Absolute
I wish I talked about Liam or Leo
So there's a drink
I thought it was
Just whipped cream
Nope
Wish
It was whispering
Unfortunately
It is not worth creating all right
B well that's what how do we get rid of them
For a lot of whipped cream
Now
Visionworks
What's that
Chicken
Worst news
There's more Draco basis
John Kerry
Do you know him
A base there
Otterbase down there for
Long time
In Antarctica
We can go about the the
The battle that took place in
He f****** just does every conspiracy
There was a battle between
I don't want to get into this
Like if this is all based on
Sadly mental
Who ended up committing suicide
Who created this elaborate hoax
About being at the door
Sea Battle
Yeah
Because I'm over Bama's
The fuckout
But there is an episode that me and Marty DeRosa did about the Dulce
Episode where I got into where all of that comes from and all that
Also another similarity
Carrie went down to Aunt
For some sort of Nefarious reason
Dr. hamamoto and Owen Shroyer
Suggested it's for weather weapon
Certainly not mutually exclusive
Why wouldn't you
Nose
Just lunch
You know
He's running down the gamut of all
Hitting all this
On the
SeaWorld
I apologize
Gobekli Tepe absolutely
Is there when it was first activated by the archaeologist
Free skeletons there
Uber 18 ft tall
This is a hoax
Won't you
Yes I know quite a bit about Gobekli Tepe
It's one of the things that I know that this is a place
Sacrifice
Supposedly also genetically engineering humans
And I'm not surprised that is that what you're saying because there are
And he work with them
Another guy Jim and I forgot his last name
They've been touring of the the world
Documenting the spines of giant skeleton
Over the world
And they found
Unbelievable numbers
Specifically North America have been a tremendous number of giant skeletons
Most have been in Egypt
Giant skeleton
Is that the British Museum of
If surgery or something like that I haven't visited when I was in Britain
Ashley has a giant skeleton
Standing right next to a human
Real skeleton
It's not caused by some kind of a genetic anomaly
Just like you just like me
We've already been over this for like what if it was though
Performer
To the point of this is not
It's some sort of like
Annunaki skeleton
They know who he is and then
Bones released from The West Wing
Skeleton
Also the person
4th Prospect
Much like in a circus show you would have be very very large guy next to the very very small guy
Kind of old hats
Sort of archaeological
Because it does represent a very early
That goes back
Years ago
Somewhere in that range
Skeletons found there is it true that was a hoax
That he is just repeating as if it were
Right
Please happy is really much more interesting
Conspiracies
Would lead you to
Uno
Now they found last year
Occasions that it is
Possibly one of the first
Sculpt
In history
Yeah yeah yeah
So
Newsweek
Gobekli Tepe
Extremely important archaeological site
First discovered in the 1960
Prices of
Stone slabs
A little like you
UK is Stonehenge
Far older
The site is thought to have been used
First four ritual a religion
Purposes rather than domestic
Meaning it's widely considered the world's first
Explain skulls for
Neolithic.
Discount Tobacco
Represent the earliest evidence
This potentially means that it's
It's the first Neolithic skull
Civilization
Insecurities. Ritual mod
Applications to skulls
So they got baby found
Discovered
Southeastern
Versace
Drilled into
The Deep incision have been made along the way
Black Cadillacs
Running vertically from the forehead
To the back of the skull
One of those also had a hole drilled into it from the top left
Cranium
Which they
Determined to have been done
Death is assertive
Ritual thing done with gold
Those are weird
Cremation
I really I should have noticed this way before now
All of this sounds like
They're gossiping
Everything is like
What did you know that they're there were these Giants
Well did you hear what to do if you know there
The conversation is
In reality
So
Now we've already I believe done a decent
Service
Connecting this to the world
Through the FEMA camps.
There's similar faces like Leo zagami popping up in both places
Among other people like Robert David
Steelers Ben
On both
David Icke
But you'd expect
But now we find a very inter
Similarity David Icke has rare crossover app
He does
Now
An interesting crossover
Narratives that are being sold
On Project a lot
And there it is that are being sold
Jim Baker's were
The story of Raven Valley
Why were they living
Dracko
There was a blue Kachina star
Blue Kachina star
Star
It brought death and destruction
Is hiding on the other side of the Sun
The evidence from Raven Rock
Intex eco
Where the Anasazi Indians
They were Nazis
Warlord
Thirsty
It was people in large saucer ciliary Pratt
A showed
People peeing
Is exactly the narratives it was being pitched by that Gaston Jim Bakker Show that we covered Wild
Exactly the same.
Also
Counterpoint
Do your
You shouldn't call them Anasazi because that is
Is the correct term
And you know why because Anasazi means ancient
Enemies
So
If you're trying to say that they were there
Hollywood's perceptions of native people
Is accurate
Yeah
Website
But the idea that like everyone lived in
Harmony also is
Equally inaccurate
Just based on their names you're misusing
Dump
No yourselves
Ancient
Yeah things to do
It's almost like
Self-contradictory
What should we what are we
I hate everybody here where the bad boys
Continent
So I got there the sharks
Next clip
Earlier made
McKay's
Possibly
Betty Page
Expressing some of his deep-seated feelings about other races
Through this Draco
Free ATM division
To the world
Mike down for this next clip
Because there's some subtleties things he's saying that I want to make
You catch all up
The ones that are left here
Like
The real quick he's talking about when those spaceships that he mention
Earlier pickup
The people who are cool
Make sure that they don't get caught
Knee wraps
They will feel the fire they will feel
The final solution
Blackbird
Our program
Vinyl
Greenlight as I like to say
And I will be
Total Destruction on
Including
Their main mission
Draconian
Extermination
You don't have to call Terminix
We already had this under control
So within a minute
He references something called the final solution and talks about Exterminating
Demonic
That he is at
Its tendrils all over the place they have a base under the Vatican
That's certainly not something that anti-semites
Hinted at the idea that the papacy is under the control of
Nebulous
Jewish
Cabal that is taking over
Now I'm not saying that attracts 100%
Ideas in the language
Deeply reminiscent
Of anti-Semitic canards throughout history
It's a plausible explanation
Some of it
He's putting out there in
Uncomfortable about it
Pass on this language
And stuff like that
Maybe it's
Just overly dramatic ways that he's expressing himself
But I can't
Because the last time we looked at him and listen to him
He was saying
Hey it sucks but you want to hear the racism's write a bunch of the time
Deeply racist person that I'm not wrong to feel that way
You kind of have to hear these words
Through that prism
And when you have such a poorly defined
Groups as
Free ATMs
Draconians
Kinda have to
To think that maybe your
Saucony
Might be
You think you think that was bad
This coming
Great good work dude
So
At this point
Carrie brings up
Something that I know Mark Richards told her
And that is that idea that we talked about the
Satellites up there
That are low top
So actually I
80 Pages responses to life on her pay
Dumb
Not worth listening to that necessarily
Because what comes after it
Eddie
You don't get the Laughing anybody
You don't get to laugh at anybody
This Alters the monster
The fact that I
Carrie doesn't bring up
It was Mark Richards
Forgotten
The Narrative came from
Tertiary
She cares about
It's Eddy page
Alexa
Haha I can laugh
You think it's true
I've become so insinuated in your world
Is my 5th time on in like 3 months
Brett I am taking over
To some extent
It gets good
The power
But he has on the show
Come to this
A f*****-up
Realized
Outside lights
Around the globe went down
You know I have been hearing that periodically
Well
Real
Let's see something
Communications right now for your alphabet agency
And we'll just not take it in America
Well
I'll be the first
We shut down several military Hi-Tech communication satellite
The Chinese are scratching their head
What just happened
Vladimir Putin saying
American
Summit Facebook
We could be in a bad mood
Just taking responsibility for satellites
Absolutely I just saw it in your face
You noticed
Quirk of his language
Where he said the Chinese were scratching their heads what happened
Vladimir Putin said I told you so
Now that's interesting because he's saying
Or at least Woody's
Pretending
Is that his plea alien Brothers
Is that the force that he's on the side of
They were the ones who took down the satellite
Interesting because just recording
On September 10th 2018 an article came out in Popular Mechanics
About how the French were accusing Russia of meddling with their satellite
Quote Frances charge the Russian government with one of the biggest ever cases of
Space espionage
France's minister
France's minister of event
Defense defense
I complained that a Russian
Maneuver
Eavesdropping
Advanced music
Accusations flying
Approved
Anomalous
Movement
Patterns
Among Russian satellite
That are
Indicating there
Engaging
That would be one thing
But also
There's an article that came out in July on
Electronic warfare
How to turn off
Install.
School bell
Yourself
Just like Alex
And the rest of the Patriot world
Eddie
Lowe's
Vladimir Putin
What is wrong with it
The type of a team that he
Yeah
We
He said
Roland
From all other reputable media
So that's
Drawing
Just another concrete
Alex Jones
That's interesting
Opens it up
2 questions
From the audience
Elitist
Interesting thing
Where are
Possibly.
Here's the first
Now
Someone is asking you if you know anything about
Qanon
Qanon 1989
Actually it's Reagan
Can fake his death in order to become qanon
That sounds like something they might as well
The first one
And then the next one
That's why it's where we're going to end
That is scary
Question
Alien races
She talked about about
Completely
Eversource
Okay well what about the mantle
Long pause.
Praying mantis from Gobekli Tepe
That that week we came across
Time they supposedly
Are trying to cross over to the light side
That's the latest
Information we have
Simon parkes is The Whistleblower who talked about that quite a bit
Cool
I miss Simon parkes he was really fun I want to threaten facts
Long pause
You can't make this stuff up
A regretful
Remember what I've made up in the
My mind goes
Can't make this stuff up
The sequence where he's telling what's going to happen to the people
People who get taken up in
Right
I will teach you new ways of energy
So all will
Arianism
Nevermind
Cuz the powers-that-be that are in charge are out not let you
Adopted
Weather being
Justin Jesse if you can do all that just like do a hard pass on those leaders
It's convoluted but it makes sense
If you already
Primary primer
Hot loading on
Where we going
A lot
I guess
It was a barrage
So it's like a collage
Like it was just put all kinds
Things he's cock piecemeal from
Some conspiracy theories that already exist
What we learned is that Eddie page is absolutely read Zechariah kitchens working is just decided
Sounds good girl talk conspiracy
He's just mixing and matching
Just he's just remix
But buried Within
Similarities
To Alex Jones
This world should make it much more clear why these worlds are connected
Though what they choose
Different
Hey what they decided
Is becoming conduct
Might be a little different
But their worlds are fun to my
Jordan
Where website
We do have a web
That you do
You can also search
Knowledge and fight
You can do that
Yeah
Whenever she overexplained looking great
Go to ww.w.
Sorry I'm late for the game so quick
And then there's foreknowledge underscore there we are
Twitter is a microblogging
Platform
We are theirs group called go home and tell your mother everybody's having a lot of fun
Recently people posted pictures
Water fun
Free second grade and Sonia super sorry about what's going on in Sweden
Right now that's a bummer
But also going to Rebrand
Go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Place where good people hang out
Absolutely
Places where you can
Cher
We're not going to do it ourselves
You want to stay away from
Rigidly anyone follow those rules
Alex Jones at all
Episode except for the similarities
Project Camelot
Remember that he probably killed to do
Alexandra Thurston color