Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
McDonald's beverages
That that boy Alex Jones
Dan
Oh boy
Lest I tell you what never
Original Gameboy red or blue
Never never really had a game for you to speak of
But it's a trend
Two times it went to the torch red
Pokemon go
Bernards I thought about getting
The Pokemon go
For one second
Came out in
Dude
I'd rather read on the bus
It's Ultraman love polka
That's fine I'm level 35 Dan
Can be how many feet
Do you have to catch them all okay what about the pressure
Hell yeah I started with a Charmander
In 1990
I didn't mean to set you off
I only know about
DiGiorno's a lot about Pokemon and think about Pokemon
Bulbasaur
That is correct
The Jordan before we started
Probably one of my favorite episodes of Alex's show that I've ever heard
You listen to and then collectively
Over 200 episodes of our Show episodes
Alex's show
I would I would absolutely
Cuz of all the ones that
We haven't talked
Consider all the times all the times that you listen to 3 episode 78
Conservative States
Listen to
Before we ever started the show
I was aware of him there's wasn't paying it
White supremacist clown
That's true
We will see
Do the expectation
I think it will but
No matter what
You know what does live up to
I don't know
Pandora listeners
Oh so very
Look
What working for today
People help
Support the content that they like being put out into the world may enjoy
That's the business model that we have
Is ever probably going to sponsor our Shelf
Very generous
To sporting us
And we appreciate it
Shout out to
Folks
Joined up
Alexei first of all time
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much thank you so much
I also
YouTube
Just joined up
Decided
Sports
We thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Vinyl
Find
And bumped it up a bit
Thank you very much Mulan for helping us get down to business
Appreciate
Visible on reference
Let's get down to business rather go with
Barry Manilow
Lexus
I'm just wondering when will my reflection
Joe
Portuguese
Perfect
Someone who I believe has
Pictures of I have not heard her say
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomized
Thank you so much
Call Shannon
To Port sure we would appreciate the stirring in your loins
Go for it
I don't know
Joint
We forget about the live-action Mulan
I'll do it I know you will
This is this is not an idle threat
Jordan
Friday
You know
What we do
Sometime
On Friday
We check-in what the f*** is going on with Alex
In 2018
He's been kicked off everything
Pretty much
Apple
Apple's app
Will you aren't
The iTunes Store
Kicked off a Twitter
I think the last time we checked in was just at
He went to Washington
Kind of assumed this is
Just going to be diminishing returns
Situation
Paint himself as a
Any Bruce type
Free Speech Warrior
Whatever
I'd probably lose his mind as his qualities
I felt like
He's barnone
The best
Proof
That he is f****** done
Like I do he's going to keep going
But like
He is
Straight
Horse f******
Himself
Goodworks
Because what he's doing
I don't mind
I don't mind taking pleasure in this
Level of
Awful
We're going to hurt other
People by doing what
Episode
Understand fully what I'm talkin about
You'll laugh to this is a lot like it's on fire right now
Maybe
Yeah I might
I don't know.
Somebody
Something like a Charmander over there
A show
Freakishly large
Okay
Evaluate himself appropriate
Good unrelated to widen
This is one of my favorite episode
There's a stretch of this
Sure where Alex is trying to work out somebody images
Bucked up
Where is Alex start
Which hey guys guess what now that I like
Most
Had to worry about before
Turns out
You takes a real hard trip back into blood libel territory
The stress level you can cut with a knife right now
Almost
Because of
The magnitude of espresso just how serious things are for me
How's it official
Beneficial
Of all the
As
Big case
Almost as much as
Every woman on Twitter saying things
But he should
He should up his
Up his claim here like I'm attack
GameStop
Position
Coward we haven't gone to the bloodline
Because the globalists are evil and they're taking our country and our world over it's the only chance we've got
Music
50 100
Yards
Wake up by themselves trying to not be a Slave
That's a spoiler for later but you would try and be a part of it
All about adopting I'm all about things are better
Are really nasty
Devil worshipping
You see that all of it
It's in the medical literature
That's why they hate me
Has got our number
Oh yeah
I don't know what the retail or wholesale price
MSRP
The Fad among rich people of like blood
Younger people real
But it's like people who go to oxygen bars
It's just some sort of thing
Weird
It's just it's just proof that there's no reason that these people are richer than us up
Confluence of luck and events
Really stupid people
There isn't any other Walk of Life
Is with on
Unlike
Will you call it
Listen to some of them talk
Review like all you don't know all that much
Unabridged
You know when you're rich
Some like really
Comes along
How many rich people do
You think
Thousand-dollar
Krystal's
You know like it got Pruitt
Nothing like when you're really
You run
To spend your money on that you actually mean
Are you start investigating right
Hello
Cumin
You might say well I'm never going to be able to
Spend all of this money I have
$10,000
Crystal I could just give it away
Starting to the pledge
Children's Place
Literally
Mystery
Direct
Using historical anti-semitism
Shoe paint
The globalist
Demonic
Pedophiles
Who drink children's blood
Which
We don't need to get into it again
It's just
That's over
There's no other way to describe that
Because that's not what they're doing
Knowing the drinking blood
Transfusion
Stupid novel
Multi pochette for
A drink
Only my own
You know like if I had caught it would be something that's easy to get through
No no
I don't I wouldn't I would want to take a
Tomatoes
Probably less delicious tomato soup
What other red liquid people.
Cranberries
Have you ever had
Corrupt
That might be the Pokemon of
It may not have got that one yet
I don't think I've had beaches
Now we've got a real sponsorship right there anybody who sells beet juice
The new slogan
The Pokemon of Judas
The victory
Of them winning me over you know just like I never had
Advertise a product that we don't believe in
I'm guaranteeing if we get a beet juice
Then we got it done right
This is not Alex's Maine
Rambling about bulshit
Almost immediately after
He does get into
Varsity narrative
For this episode
There's a hurricane
Camouflage coming across the u.s.
Oh boy I don't mean to
Is right away
Cuz I'm sure there's more to it
I'm just saying
That maybe
If you're riding on horseback
Camouflage
Sure
Silver Stallion
The Highwaymen
Filthy hide
Sure
Look we're going to get into what he's talking about
Thousands of
Rush to break
Very dramatically
Across America
I've no way to deal with the threat of this thing about this because it's
So stupid
Why
But like legitimately if that's what he's selling to his audience
We only
Right I mean like this is an infection
Everything eventually
All of his rhetoric would lead to the
Being
Find me
Kill them now you don't need to kill them
Because as I imagined is Alex's screamed over and over again we will give them no quarter
Pretty easy to capture a lot of dudes on Horseback what with the whole modern world we live in
Like I imagined one battalion
Go back in time when everyone
Oakwood Guns
Shoot the horses legs and make them dance
Compete with that
Are they using ropes
What
I like these men on Horseback they're not using roads where they're going
Dago
Exactly what you talkin about I believe
In a couple of cliff
But Alex's got to percolate on me
Unless he's got a really ruminate
About how why
This is
Just like the movie The Road Warrior
Amex
Busy talking about people coming across
Spoiler alert
Even in the movie The Road
Spiritually
Describing them as literally coming over on horse
Part is literal
Okay
Stroke
Videos
Is reporting on
To show people crossing the border
From X
Mexico and there were a couple of hours
Horses in the video
Express1040
Mentioned in that took going out to break that it
If people coming across the border
They're coming across America
I realize that it's only fair that I
Back to the Road Warriors
Thousands of illegal immigrants inside of horses and walking across the border
Easiest way to do it
Here's where we get to the road warrior metaphor
Gets bad before it get
Get better
Literally
Mexico
Okay
Shooting at each other attacking blowing up running over people
50 cal machine gun
And surely thoroughness at the Mexican cartel
Warrior
Humongous going live
Punk rock
Is Mexican with huge satanic tattoos that worship Satan
Sleeper children
That's also free blood libel adjacent
Really bad
We're pretty much the most racist thing you can do
And their demonic Mexico
Punk rockers no
They're really lost
Kind of credibility when he called people demonic
Just kind of like a
Still in
Insult
That here you can use
Misaligned
They do listen to a lot of Morris
In this next clip
Because he gets back to the road warrior thing a little bit later and he also combined with another movie reference
That is
Visual caught on camera
Arizona Ranch
Illegal alien
Yeah
Sure
Road Warrior
Horseback
Nice save
Alex
So
It's like this
Subspecies of apes
And it's not that I'm
Species
So I found this video is a 25-minute video
This is from like
Eclipse
This guy is
Had hidden cameras up at his house then
So it's the course of what could be 22 years and 9 months now
Thousand
Poor wandering around in the
There's no timestamps on any of this stuff
Caucasian
Very imprecise stuff going on
You know what
Fair enough to watch this entire video account literally every person
Baywatch to the 10-minute Mark before I saw
Good footage
And also if you watch it it's like
Visa
And you see the same people from different cameras
Like it's the same group of me
People at different
Point
Along the way
No s*** but in all of these videos
Are unique person
Within 10 minutes
I counted
Before people
So
Extrapolate that out
Multiply that by two and a half
You got what
Maybe
People
There's a repeated peep
It's nonsense
This is all bulshit
Gun
But the vast majority
You know I'm saying
Just have big packs on
They're back and like Alex is saying that's all drugs
But it's equally likely that its rations
Is equally likely that the lot of these people haven't
Supplies in order to get
Through this journey through Central America
Map to the United States
There's nothing
These videos
Really leads me to believe that first of all this is
Is an invading Army on horseback
Like maybe three or four horse
Well
You can try
Fair enough
Hutches good tax
Text answers incredible
There's incredible exaggeration going on here
Incredible
Clearness of what the video even is capturing
It's very irresponsible the way Alex's
Because
Like I said in that first clip
The only reasonable conclusion
Kill these people
Third invading Army on horseback
Mrs. white supremacist propaganda
Tucker Carlson
I'm not sure if I caught.
It's just some guys house
Some Rancher
Hidden cameras around
So he sends in the raw footage
Probably
Maybe
I was a little bit confused cuz I I was just imagining
This dude who has a bunch of hay
Hidden cameras for editing this footage
And that's just a guy who's filled with so much hate but
We can't even get past
The fact that
It's not a big deal
And his own
Well
You're the fifth
50000 square acre
Ranch I believe Brett
Around that
Over the course of almost
3 years
Maybe
800 people
Assuming that they aren't the same people at different locations
That's not impressive to me week
If some of them have guns
Yeah but again
Rancho
You don't have proof that these people are illegal undocumented immigrants
Oh you have his video of people walking around
It's so they do have gun
Better to prove
What you're saying is the reality
Before I'm going to get mad about a couple of them having guns
If he just said you know what I think there might be some people hunting on my land
Carry gun through this
Florida
You want to file a complaint about
To the other issues
Camouflage
Give a s*** about that
Like
Iran army
Or something like that
Florida bulshit
And moving very very slowly like if all of this hidden camera footage showed
Was like a
Whole bunch of hay bales
Just slow over the course I would
Perfect
I could get behind and publicized help you with that
And that's his sort of Varsity narratives Ramos.
The show
It leads to this
Next clip
Relics
Conspiracy about what
Going on with immigration
Do you make
Very bold
Very bold claim
And the UN
Guatemala
Alright we're a good start
Migrant centers
The world
Thousand dollars a piece
Food and other necessities
With the Democratic group
Quiet
Bacon Lover's
Completely forgot that I left and right click with the commercial
Perfect jarring
Lovers Unite
First
I got a guy who can hook you up
Put some buckets you don't need both of them
All over
Display Absol
Hell yeah
People are helping immigrants
Ants on their way up
Through
America or anything like that
The ideas it without
What Christianity
Anything like that
You're not going to stop
I'm trying to see
Refuge
In America you're not going
Do America that's just true but you
Your long as
The world operates
It's in the way that it does
You're never going to be able to stop him
To try and come
Come to America
And if you
Crackdown you're like your evil for giving the water along the way
All you're going to do is make sure the more of them die
You weren't going to stop the Imp
Just to come
To America
You're not going to be cruel to the people
Who are desperate in
Leaving about 2
Situation
Everybody knows that when you ban abortion
No babies ever get the perfect analog you get rid of legal abortion
In all you do is kill with
Just as Jesus said the way you treat
The least of these is f****** dope
Keep on doing it sir
Dealership bacon
The Jews could not be having somebody
Shipping free bacon I'm into this conspiracy analysis version of stupid
I just want Democratic voters
No white nationalist rhetoric
Democrats
Anyway
Jordan
Sears
Alex's
Has been
Back in the day
Maybe I might be a little bit wrong about
From listening to
A lot of stuff
2008/2009
How to pretty against
Profile
Because at least
Baseline level he understands
Ability
Not
A way to proceed with
You is Hope
Night I believe that
Do I don't know if
Day is perfect
Systems in that fact
I get a strong sense from him that like
You don't you don't come into composition
Group is represented
Individual
Unfortunately in 2018
Islamic extremists.
Problem-solve
Your partner
You're but you're going to get pulled
You're going to get extra screen
What you do
I don't think first of all I don't trust Alex's assessment of what constitutes a radical Islamic group
Conversation
Shuffle Murphy
The awful quick
Just like if you were too I don't know
Say that everybody who looks like a member of a radical militants white supremacist group
Should be profiled problems radical White
Logic
Prove it it's stupid
Disgraceful
Today feel like
Terrible
For Alex
Cuz I mean
He's not but there was a time
I think
Advocate
4 out
Out
Racial profiling
Because he's afraid of Muslim
Is just pathetic
For someone who wants to act like you have principles
Standing up
For America and what it stands for
To hear this kind of
Dribble come out of his mouth
Is just like
Just go home man
Yeah
Your usefulness even to
Your world
And that's bad
Peoples
Old assholes
Jerome corsi
I'm saying
Anywhere
Certainly
Anyway
I suppose I suppose he does have a he does have one point
Wichita Airport
Immigrants from
Escaping their terrible situation
To come to America
It's to turn America into a s******* they don't want to come to
I think what you're doing pretty great
Right now
Just like that make it illegal to
Different
The difference in heavy quotes
Nobody hates America more than people who call themselves
So I might be a little bit wrong
You're giving Alex
It's the sort of pasta
Credibility
Past selves
Profile
But this next clip
Is absolutely
Anathema
To what he would have
Ever
Believed in
Trump
Is a dereliction of Duty
2 years
Military
1 billion percenter
In the past
Alex has called for the National Guard
Lisa border
No
He's not
Because that is something that can be done under
Direction to the governor of
Texas National Guard
It would not be again
Alex's
Him saying that the federal f****** government
To do it
Very much against Mexico
Would be operating within the state
About when we're looking at
10th Amendment resolution
Like that
All of them
Completely counter to it
He doesn't even bring up the governor's support
Federalization it's an argument for tyranny don't you remember how much you loved
Loved
Don't you remember how many times the federal government has mobilized troops to do something very innocuous exercise
Compulsion
Bring federal troops into my state says Alex Jones
I don't know all the governorship Salonga
Border
Mario wearing one of them is
Democrat
Bring in the Federal
Then what you have is a
Should be on the side of the governor's but now will not be absolutely will face
This is
Is where people should be calling him at 8
Like before
There were articles in
The publication
Right wing watch
I was just calling for the National Guard to come in to stop that
Train of immigrants that were coming up even though that trained of immigrants
Something that happens every year at the symbolic
Sort of protest
Thing that not even
Threatening
Group of immigrants coming up from Central America
But they wrote about how Alex was saying bring a
If they understood with Alex.
They would know.
Problem for him
This f****** you
It bothers me
Talk about it well the only other way that could make sense
For his prints
As if he wants
The federal army on the other side of the Border
Which would be declaring war on Mexico
Interventionist
Paul Boehner would be
It would be quelled by that idea
It is fine if you are on horseback
That is true
In a video that's on The Daily Caller
Very
Reasonable to go to war absolutely
We know
Looking back at
2002a
9 that Alex
Did not know who George Soros
Ray's globalist
Said he would talk about where the Rockefellers
Sportsound
Child
Absolutely they were in play back then
People that were his big enemies
Most recent
Netflix episodes
George Soros be brought up
Almost confused
Spy it is not
Play
Makes
Is b*******
Did you
What's George Soros
Dogs
My mom always had PBS on cooking dinner
She was always there at 56 for like an hour and a half cooking
Gourmet food
My girlfriend
Add
It was always on PBS
George Soros
The overthrow countries
Keys for sweet little Nazi Collaborators you almost catches award covered booty
Anything about that
I said no ideas
In the world
Until at least
Sometime in 2009
And I don't believe
PBS
Remember When.
I remember when he was subject of Investigation on
CVS
Where where did you lose your way you were once the Vanguard I guess
Man I believe this bro
Doris was supported by viewers like
The letter L
Should have chose a different letter
Anyway he's going on a bit of a rant and how they're evil
Like to kill gays
Yeah that's way different
I only keep raw
I only keep Republicans
I only keep this
I think Alex
Is relishing
Talkin about this a little too much
I'm having a little bit of a breakdown later
They got caught
Mariah
And they took them out and they blew their brains all over the walls
It's so liberal
They got shake that ass
I got the evil that is
Look
I want to say about that
That voices
And what he's expressing is disgusting
Because cover
Ad nauseam
He's very much
Whether or not
Viscerally angry angry at the LG
Enzymes pedophiles
That's cuz they don't like
And there's no reason that they wouldn't like him
Other than if they were
Shooting their brains on the wall
Broke
And it leads to this
Sexualizing kid.
About Russia
Cat Day murder game
Yeah you should because you're a little web of your own lack of ability to wiggle around it
Stop yeah
You're screaming what about Russia absolutely f****** talk about that
You dumped if you hate it whenever government
If people
Gay people boy
You got a lot of options there dude
You know what is the right-wing really does become ascendant
You know that that sort of religious can
Conservative
They wanted to happen
Absolutely
And the things the policies
Lgbtq youth
Feel border weird conversion therapy becoming more recommended
That's the end result
Stickley homophobic
Accepted
That it's not okay to just murder date
Yeah
They like
With abortion
They will do everything possible to make sure they die
Yeah
Hey hey we're not killing people
Creating
All of the circumstances necessary
For gay people it's not like we're doing it
Determination
We determined that you should
So he is next
Cool guy prop
And they're not able to get ahold of him
The vamp
So funny
It's very important
Gaston
Fattest fish
Just like our information here on are World change
Words words words words words
I'm saying words
Information
Stretch
Stretch it out
Stretch it we're having technical issues
Stretch
Our products
Good work
Until you
Keep going we still got issues
Keep it rolling
Stuff tomorrow nearby pharmacy
Just like our information
Stretching a little bit longer
Don't have oxygen
Water is 3 days have
You finally got there
Are about a real joke
We are
Oh boy
What's that hold on I'm hearing something they're good
Fun
Not fun
For him to talk about like you need oxygen
Two lives you need water
His boy Trump just said that
Maria in Puerto Rico
There was no electricity and a lot of people
People died cuz they
Didn't have water
Understand
Denying the death toll
We've not enough to get you removed from office
You should go to The Hague
President
That's all you need the president doesn't believe in reality we have to let him go
Trump
You're cool
You got to go
Road Rules challenge
Wake-up wake-up CT
Sorry man
The real world Road Rules challenge
Like it a stupor in his bed
Vicky punch Davis
Got to go
Who's that
Monroe's greatest
Crazy
Wow
Our people watch power
Anyway
Difficulties worked out after Alex pants for what seems like
Political
Coach that he
The song
And I don't want to listen to this guy too much
I don't even started that hashtag walk away
He's a Democrat
Walkaway
Democratic Party
They don't they don't represent him
Depending on his Reasons I'm willing to entertain that notion
He has a
Nefarious
If you want
Salon article about how
They did
The accounts
We're promoting that hashtag
After it would put out
And there is a
Fairy
Very high incidence of Russian Bots
We're promoting that walkaway campaign
Probably coincidence
It's almost like somebody
Not even a government arm and more like a for-hire service that if you have billions of dollars I want to spread and ID
You can just hire them?
Put on Facebook
He was going
Tea2go on Alex Jones
Effects of patriot
I'm going on
I'm not
If you if you say Patriot
I'm kind of out so after that
Is Facebook
Fan
He was
Understandably mad about it
Send it
Email or whatever
The powers-that-be at Facebook
Here is your account.
This all happened
Before
Thursday
This is the Thursday
Is the Thursday September 13th
By the morning of Thursday
He's had his account back open
Tonight
Before Wednesday night whenever
He got all of his ex
Yeah cuz it Works customer service
Unfortunately
It's still going around everywhere
Showing up on Alex's show on Thursday
Trying to pitch the idea that
You just said it
And he got banned for 30 days
When in reality by this point
He has his account back
They apologized for them
Mistake they made
Everything
Should be fine
Because Alex wants
But if you say Infowars
Your bam
He's having them on and let him start his b*******
Which is really about him trying
Raise money
Free walk away March
He's trying to run
Always looking for
What's my people
Bok
I might as well I might as well give up because
You should email get your f****** account
This is such b*******
Oh I've been because I have
Enterprising
McDavid versus
Goliath I found a workaround to get my account
Be able to access
Talk to people when techno
Facebook recognize that they made a mistake
Whatever it was whether it's dump capricious
Employee who put his account on a suspension
Some sort of automated today. Caught somehow
F***** up here is your cats are locked
And he's
People
No you're not
Stop it
I do like the I do like anytime anytime somebody uses workaround
Like
You're going to need to give me specifics on your quote-unquote work around cuz it makes it seem like
We outsmarted them
That's not what a workaround
Yeah he's acting like
Is a hacker
No
Like in the movie Swordfish
Nope
Facebook said Mia culpa
Appropriately
So
He's talking about cuz it's not
Quite frankly
Read me we got a bit
Of the best
Alex
About what's going to happen
Video
From
You are going to have oceanfront property in Arizona.
What's going on
And they said we're ready
Add just Unity right
Operation
In March
Man on Horseback with drug package
Divorce.com
Whoopi Sher
Call confirm
The game
He's like saying the first of all
Recognizes that Steve pieczenik has been burned
So then he comes
In March
Kill Trump
Bye
Everything can change
They can change their China's behind just know that I said
Things can change
I think he was trying to evoke The Ides of March
Because in the past he has
Refer to Trump as our Caesar
He has he has
Used either as a analog
Really bad thing
You think
Because Alex has big book that he basically said that the government military across
What's our goddamn Nation
I think there might be some sort of
I don't know
But I don't care about that
None dare call it
The book that Alex Jones
Ron
Beaver is
Used as an example
Of what
Happens when a psychopath
Is born
Super rich
In the book Gary Allan is
Describing the ideas
Hey
There are these people who go out and murder
You know cuz David Dearborn crazy
There's just
Vicious Psychopaths out there
They are only
Like one or two three four five
Because they were born
Humble circumstances
But what happened
Psychopath
Lap of luxury
Either I can't imagine
The one Alex
Trump
Well it's a good thing either she hasn't read the book that he's basing his life on
Completely lost
Track of any
It's a good thing that this is purely a hypothetical
That we have no real-world concrete examples
Of psychopaths
A laughable situation Dan bring it up to me
I understand
Gary Allan
It is a little bit
Baseline
Real surf
But
Sometimes
What you end up with
Sublimated
Into like
Getting their jollies off of crush
Competition
Do actually murdering
Isn't
Accessible to
If you're William Randolph Hearst
Sure
But be there
Stupid
Even going to be killed
But Alex already knows
Is also a good time to say
Now because then you got a long wait
And people will forget that mug
Forget you even bring it up
Then you can at least 3 months
Pretending it's going to happen
4 months of time
Exact
Money with a panic
The summer of Rage
Let's talk about the immigrants that are in Europe
As opposed to the immigrants
Hatesphere
80 + percent
Islamic
Middle Eastern North African
Invaders brought in Last 5 Years in Europe
What percent never get a job if you know they deport
Convert to Christianity
What's in the news
Get the job
I don't like that believe that all that is actually slightly better
You are
Alright
This is the most
I've heard from from
Like we were covered a lot of
Heavy
Spectrum oh yeah after Mexicans get out of their North African food
He's going to think that our prediction of like
He's going to have no reason to hold back anymore like it's fairly Act
Call immigrant Invaders
I mean does that anyway that's right
But he seems to be relishing it a lot more to enjoy his
New lb
Yap
Yeah.
Here in this
Text Cliff about what happened
That you are against
And it's
Someone who's against
Infowars
Has been putting out
Long podcast
Very thing every week
For two years
I will say
When you are against Infowars
Not true
Are you sure not true
Well I will withhold judgment
Because I am also against it but I don't know what he's about to say so maybe he's right
Realized
No one is pushing out
We all go down the rabbit hole we all go together this talk
This whole situation
Alex's all the time we hang together or we hang Zephyr
How is that
Anyway difference
Qanon
Now beyond that this is so f****** funny to me
Because he's been vaguely anti qanon for the entire time
More important to be the one that goes viral
About that
But at the same time
Jerome corsi has been on his payroll
Jerome corsi was writing
Goddamn
Book about decoding the truths of Cuba
I'm not going to lie to you very simple explanation Alex
Here's why qanon
Is more popular
It's a non
And your dude is named exact
Fairy
He was on Saved by the Bell man
Nobody's going to 4th wall break this b******* and also
It appealed to people about qanon
The idea that you have to put
Pieces together yourself. There is an element of like
Circle mystery I think you said it on a reason episode
Make make me
Me feel like I'm smart for
Figuring this out
Desire to
To pretend they're detect
And I figure out what is this cryptic nonsense
Announce doesn't provide them
He's just like
Two specific to specific Becca
Harper
Game changer
You don't have any subject mystery to figure out
And that's why whenever we go back in
Episodes to train train
Pathan
It's not that hard
It takes a long time
Because you have to listen to the episodes you have to digest what he saying
The only people who listen to maybe but I don't think
The only thing you really have to
Do is be able to stop us out when he's telling me
Flying in Brighton
Like that
I think if you listen to
Enough
Kind of get the
His voice
There's there's
I feel like even without any of your research
I would be able to just bite your be like
Do you know it sounds like it might be possible but guess what
I heard that I heard the lilt
Alkali
Wellsbrooke
Morlock
F*** off
So I'm going to skip this next book
It's not really all that important it's just Alex
The Border Patrol
Nice smile
Are they
I don't think he said to now
Oh are they
Are there more children in detention now than there were just a few short weeks ago
Whenever whenever the justice system
The children who are being held
It's good that they are
ACLU
I don't care
But I give a s*** about the people who
You know mistreated
Stuff like that but I don't really care
Really
But at this point
Why is Owen Shroyer there because
And he needs to sit down with Owen Shroyer and get to the bottom up
This
Jordan
This is the bike down for it
No no
To cover a little bit and then we will have
DeGraw
This made me laugh
F****** hard whenever
Nothing like some Good Ole Country on the open road huh
Like an alpha male
How does a person with gout
Alphabet
Power
Freakishly large
And my chest is freakishly large
Is it high school
Wizard
Everybody was looking at me
Is a factor attack
Because I was
Try to make me ashamed of myself
Now because they're doing that
Columbus.gov
As the wheel has the spirit has the future
We are reserved because
Could you please play the first
I don't know 30 seconds
Nothing like some good old country on the open road
Around
The alpha male
I was the person that was child
Okay now you can stop right there
Stressed out
Annoying
Looking annoying
Funplex
Have you ever heard the second f****** half of that cup
And ladies, Ramen
You
I'd like to remind you feel like one of them
I've ever heard earlier in the episode Alex said that there's an invading Army coming from Mexico
Be hit by a hurricane
Cuz Owen represent
It's what he's lost
Cohen representative
Why would he know the exact price of a quart
Other child but if not
Five children
Seems like it might having a
The market
Really I think I touched on some
Something there hear up
Presents that thing that Alex
Cannot get back
I think you
The two of them have this weird
Turn off
Child relationship.
Alex
And Alex really wants
Impressive
Like you're either
It's not employee-employer relationship
I don't have a clip of it but there's a point where Alex Alex
Alex you are a
Just like reassuring
No
You are a bad as your son was the best boy you are
Play the reason to do and supposed to be on
Is because that video that was on The Daily Caller
And Owen went to a I guess
Liberal
I don't know
Speaker about it about the like what about all these armed men coming across the border and also
What about abortion
Looks like Infowars is here
What's really funny is that after that Owen is like I've got a stack of news here
He's literally use that he has never been prouder
Expressions
Also the other thing that I thought was
Locked up
Wheel locks
Owen
Says
If you kick us off Facebook
Will come into
3D reality where God is in charge
Usurp
What would you
Man now I really want to find out more about Owen Shroyer
Very clear.
I would say if there's something going on
Drift on the wrong side of the Goldwater rule
I do know that the hero wears
It's going to be it's going to be
Shroyer is cruising for like the worst
Decade of his life and have a
Albert
Can't remember the name of the movie
No we're not supposed to talk about
It's the one where you goes on the ship
Seven Years in Tibet is the other one
He's on the ship he was smoking opium and grew his hair real long and his wife was a native
American Freight
Okay you're right that was
Alex
Just having a bull session
This is like they both
Really need to talk to
Somebody about their body
Unfortunately it on are to each other
This is
You should probably talk to a therapist
Dysmorphia
I don't want to judge them for
Immigrants are Invaders
Like that right
Go f*** off you don't really get
Because there's this whole Trend right now happening about body shaming
And so it's like if you're overweight and obese women
Wearing like yoga pants now that illegal
Probably something like that
It's like
If you walk
Instead of walking and stuff like that like
Real quick
You think Auntie for meeting
But that's the exact same thing he claimed about when he would protest abortion rally
He's just
This is hacking
This is like
This is what if there was a sketch
Where
Woody Allen
Warren Arnold
Schwarzenegger stay
Like this is exactly the kind of neuroses that would come out here
It's super weird
HuHot people hate
About
Is dumb that it's dumb now you're not getting any smarter why are you
Why are you coming we're all of these people are the bench
Shapiro's of the world the Jordan Peterson
Harrison
The Stefano molyneux's
Dark web
All of their stock-in-trade is really
Rephrasing
Conversations we've already had it out of here
What if
Masculinity
I'd like it was smart
Stupid
Qualitative differences between
What is
You know like really whoever wanted his judging is people who
Too hot
They the real victims here damn real victims
People's physical appearance
The next thing you know we're going to be in Harrison Bergeron. Going to have to wear glasses to make me blind because my vision good
Baby
You know what
I feel so bad
That we should outlaw
People wearing tights
Close
And actually it.
Semi political
Beto O'Rourke name
Concert with Willie Nelson Willie Nelson is now
Which is bad
Tony Democrat
You can't
Excuse
I know you got a inflated view of yourself
Still not going to
Now
I will say that
Absent any other information
Is that her real name I don't know he's an expression of rape
Absolutely
Cuz you're not
You know what is very easy
Need to find out if something
Someone's real name
You look that up
You can't
Especially public figures
Name one way
Google it so you can do that
I don't care I'm going to look into that purse
I believe that's
Any less Owens going to present me with some sort of evidence that it's not
I just see that as an expression
Quest
Somebody is a minority
Beto O'Rourke
Because his real name
His birth name is Robert Francis O'Rourke
You started going by Beto and its primary school days
It's because Beto is
Spanish
Robert
Probably had something
Going to do with the fact that he grew up in El Paso
Which I'm not sure if you know this
Is literally on the border of Mexico and 80.7
The population of El Paso had some sort of Hispanic
He went to Carlos Rivera Elementary School in El Paso Heights
That's cool by the way El Paso High School
Is it
Houston High School at 9
Great good guys
Has grown up surrounded by an immersed in latinx
And the idea that most of his friends
Grown-up or probably
Hispanic
End up with the Spanish
Inspired
Beto's
I don't think there's anything wrong with that
I'm a little bit know he's great
I would support a second potatoes on the ballot again
Ted Cruz Beto
The bassist in a band
Oh yeah
Bixler-zavala from at the drive-in
Drive-In
That's not so
President
Actually
Scratch that
At the drive-in
As a concept president-for-life
I don't know about that
Anyway
Amen
What's the name of it
Rats in the Sanitarium
That sounds great
Later album
Little self-indulgence
From the jump a little Philadelphia earlier but
Great drummer
Anyway
Can't get too bogged down in the world of of old old timey
Iraq
I don't know what's going on
By the way that's not my genre at all but my friend
At the drive-in
I'm glad they worked
I'm always going to go with it
Whether they're good or not
Jordan
Yes daddy
Until we come to it
You come to the point
Where
Your life
No
Not my life became
We have
Definitely
Strongest indication that Alex Jones is
Not
Giggle because
This start
With what I would describe
An absolute
But he listens to our show
Okay by the end of this clip
We see
Where the future of Infowars live
And my friend
Alex if you want to donate
Sprouts.com
Karaoke
What about the bridge in the world
Conspiracy
Cam
Infowars yeah infowars.com
Tell you what this is
Is Justin
I just know
It's bad news
Merle Haggard
Does anybody know who owns Infowars note
I think maybe his ex-wife bought
Kelly made about a workout
Widgets
That's pretty funny
Do not like I mean he didn't own infowars.com
But he started it
Write like someone else was sitting on that for a really long time so that he wouldn't cover his base
I mean if it was me and I was going to come up with knowledge fight yes.com we would also
Possibly
Knowledge fight in determined
It's just good planning
So
Manny
The college
Spirits
Conrad Padilla
To talk about
I had a really tough time
Figuring out who Conrad
Videos because there's also an MMA fighter
It's not him
Obviously this is something good to get it on the ground
Infowars.com
Europe
Melissa
The British Invasion
Stop right there
College conspiracy
So this world leaders involved with f****** talking about
Garage
The big news about the Beatles is the John Lennon
Nigel farage
Did a little bit unusual masturbate
You know I don't know
Literally everybody there is at sex is to
Next
I don't find
Anything wrong
With that I don't even text
The fun story I don't think
All the puns
People working out
Billy I really didn't know that that was an Is that real
Really came out David Bowie and Mick Jagger
Did you not see the billion
Cuz I'm Twitter on come together
Of course of course that's the simplest way to go
That's fun for them just like I'm happy for David Bowie and Mick Jagger
Search Richard Procter MD
WhatsApp
I don't know.
No
Russo actor
Free Bogart
What Humphrey Bogart alright
Then I hate to break it to you but Humphrey Bogart to is
I was Marlon Brando
That sounds right
Quincy Jones
Everybody's kids don't understand music
Richard Pryor I don't know whatever
Hey
People using
Youngblood
As a novelty
Sometimes
If you're not gay
You still got to
Are you rich you're famous
Going to go get swing a little bit
F*** one night
Experiment
The college conspiracy
Going to do with student loans
I think it has something to
To do with
People not being necessarily
Prepared for the world outside
By the
Regional system as it is
And that second one is kind of close to what Padilla wants talk about but
I'll let him play outside
His version
All right here we go
And somehow you're going to go out there and get this this job
Right now who have master's degree mail
Highway Starbucks
Has great benefits
Right now
.
I'm not getting it back
No
Entrepreneurship
The office
No he's not
Beneficiary of nepotism on a grand scale and the amount top of that f****** white man
A product
You orally of white nationalism
This is a man born
Who is an elected to office
Purely bait
On how race is he was
Baptism
Trump is emblematic of white supremacy
Trump is the dumbest
Lee
F****** on the goddamn planet
God damn bulshit world that we live in that is f****** on
Settling to describe him as an aunt
Jordan
Look I agree
You said you wanted to get out of here before
That dude just listening to that bad
Hear him laying it out
Witches you know I mean
I don't think that's necessarily the main problem
I would be
With someone if they were
You know like that to me isn't
Isn't like
Or anything like that
Position to be
Do they have language
I mean I think you could make an argument that
You know you got to have
Biology
Credit inmost
Undergraduate degree
Chemistry
Free credit in most
Universities
College I didn't need to have a
Argument being made that like
Preparing People
For the life outside of her
Outside of college party outside
Beneficial
For them to prepare
And have some sort of an understand
I really feel like that's high school s*** like you should freshman year you should have
Credit cards work
Tonight's her to stop or like Civic
Six classes in
High School
Required
And they'll do a good job
The buck back further
Wherever you do with people should be for
Prepared in some way
High School
College
I'm listening both sides
I'm fine again with that conversation
Here we go
Surprise
Now what he perhaps have stumped
I would like Jordan Jordan's for together
Colleges aren't doing
There's an opening
For someone to step
To teach entrepreneurship
Lost is considered selling a VHS tape
You're not far off
Corso there's a pamphlet you can buy for $25 on red potato was like a train
Unhappy with his life
And that
Is where
Next clip
This is Mike down
Cuz this is where everything
Remember he brought up
Infowars yes
We're going to find out a little bit about it
We're going to Allstate
Infowars
No
So
This profession came around network marketing
Actually now that it's been around for over 100 years
This profession
Is so proven around the world that's helped millions of people out the world
Be able to go into entrepreneurship
But it's a model built around good product if I've been offered
Successful
Under them also outselling
Brite products
Distributor
The biggest the owners of the successful business
So if you are not putting
Together
So Alex
Has become a mid-level multi-level marketing scam guy
Ford jeunesse
You betcha he's not even running his own MLM anymore
He is just a contractor for a multi-level mark
And that's what
It's a funnel to get people to sign up to
To be Distributors for
Can't be real that's the saddest thing I've ever heard it's pretty remarkable
Thing I've ever heard I mean at the bottom
Infowars
Yespage
But if you go to info
Forwards yes.com you scroll all the way to the bottom there's a
Quotes
Independent janeski
Distribute
In other words
Distributor
That's not all that's going on
People to sell jeunesse products
What the s*** you know what
Generative formative experiences
Alright alright
When my when I was like
My dad bought a timeshare
Somehow even then when he was explaining it to me I was like
Is a bad idea
It's not valuable
And then again when I was like 22
My dad started telling me about this
Okay so
Right is that
Thank you a membership
And it would through this membership you get discount
You know tell other people about this
Membership and they get this
Membership do I have to pay a small fee
But the more people you tell the better discount to get Edmund actually you get like a kickback
For every person who signs up
Using your information I can't imagine how your dad ended up in a cult
Weird how
When I was 18 years old Cutco
I remember I was working at a movie theater
6515 an hour
Movie theater popcorn
Rat working the concession
And what have you
I would like
Hero of the Forum
Selling knives Albans all the way
My car and someone had put a flyer
A Cutco in there
Maybe I'll go check out this seminar or whatever
Now with the same time
Reality show about my life
Because I was completely out of control
Bad little digital camera
Will be fun if I got
Drunk
And went to this Cutco
Because the cattle call it's just
That was going to be
Wasted
And then we went
Pedro
We were saying we brought a video camera
You cannot video
Rotate
And there's always the guy who
Who's like now
You might
You might say to yourself
There's no way this is too-good-to-be-true I'm going to bring up
Mr.and.mrs Derrickson
They are going to tell you exactly how
From having some sort of regular real estate real estate
To making $38,000 per month
There wasn't
Anyone like that but the guy was running
That was his story
It's me myself
There was obviously one person
In the audience
Stuff like that
I can't make eye contact with the guy or anything I'm like
Probably had like
13 beer
Job
Yeah but like what
There might have been closer cat might have been around 78
Like that
Sarah Sanders before 8 today off from the theater and I will
I am not
I am drunk in my chair and my probably
Tibet
Absolutely
Sitting there thinking like
I got it this is
His goddamn
I got to get out of here
It went on for like an hour
Happy hour
What are you doing
He was the one who put the Flyers around
You trying to recruit more people
Does
He brought everyone into his office
Two at a time
And he gave the speech that he obviously gave
Every single group of to bring you guys in here
Because you
Are. You're not like
You have it
And like clearly
Kind of Interest
She was a go-getter
It's like
Pointing at Herzig
You seem to have to go get her spirit at
Good future in this
Are you looking for
He was like
You
You make great eye contact
I can't say for sure whether or not I left it between what am I
I'm drunk
1 pictures Auto both positions
Of course if you are
Sitting where it's like
You know you have to
Pay a bunch of money to get you
Your set of knives
So you can then walk around crazy how you have to apply the knives
Spurs
It said standard setup
They tried to get me
Constant
Set up list
Together and this is before
Spam filter
In your email
Calling me
Maybe a year later
Is living with another guy
Kind of
Belittle impressionable
Oh that poor kid
Working hard
It's all about you
Until I told him I was like man
I went to one of those meetings
Con artist
Scamp
They made a ton of money
I like but also
Consider how alienated they are from everybody
Either friends
Because I do
To go down
Piss off your family
You might get some
Petey purchases
And then you're going to get
With all of these
Use expensive knives
He ended up
Thousand
Thousand dollars
So now this is what Alex's
Well I don't like
Teasing pyramids
Pyramid scheme has a really negative
I prefer
Multi-level marketing
Define
Pyramid
Is that like
Attracted
The founders of it
Came in with such the
Success in business
You know like they were very
People people
Now Jordan
Is a multi-level marketing
Team started by Wendy Lewis and Randy Ray
Starting to
Scam company
Operated mother multi-level marketing
Called fuel Freedom International
Where they sold the product called
Which allegedly helped your Gotta Have It
Ultimate
Bulshit
Truth in advertising 2009 record
CEO and co-owner of this fuel
Freedom
Voluntary
Compliance with
Florida's office
Attorney General
Thousand dollars promised
For making false
Claims and thereby
Send pic a no longer legally make false claims of full fuel freedom
They close down shop
And started jeunesse
Because regulation of the supplement industry is nearly non-existent
You can just start selling b******* and call it something that's got health benefits because there are
Billion-dollar companies that have lobbied Congress to ensure that they're not covered by the FDA
So these people Wendy Lewis and Randy Ray who started a multi-level marketing
Company
The fraudulent product
Got them $100,000
Find by the Attorney General of Florida
These operations
Because the jig was
Did you next
I'm going to give them credit for that.
Here's the problem
Nobody gets scammed quite like a scammer
What was happening right now
So hard doesn't even know
You can even imagine
Like right now
This show Infowars
At this point
On this episode
Turns into a Janessa
No
Sponsored
What comes up to the info
Real quick all the product
Infowars store now on harsh disc
And some of that is pretty normal to Easter sale might still be in effect from 6
Marked down a lot of stuff
And Alex earlier this
Got on there and said that
The situation with his
The iodine
August 6th
The survival Shield
Sure
The crystal iodine
Earth Earth iodine
No s***
Say that before
Multi-level marketing
You think this is going
To fund the operation
I think that he's not working with Doctor group any
I think the probably a lot of the old product
Well I would if I were him his our yeah I know you would absolutely finishing like crazy
Toxic brand
So Alex probably minutes
Doctor group was very happy to be in this
Where he would rename product
And let Alex
So Gone
It's on YouTube is not able to promote
Product
On Facebook and Twitter and all these places
Private label all this stuff and I will have to be able to sell
When was the last time dr. group
I have no idea
I wonder if whoever comes back
But this is just a
Of my I have nothing to back this up
This is the last X2 thing
Yeah he's not doing that in some way
In the past we've heard him say that
He's not
Like that on this
And you'll get it if you want it
We got some in the warehouse
Where to move it cuz we got to get that juice
Taking up space
So I'm
And he was already running ended monthly multi-layer with
Is operation
You never really sells at all that hard
But you just mentioned
Get discounts
If you
But he wouldn't he wouldn't be like
I would be great if you
Getting people on auto-ship
Cancel auto-ship
For now
Anyway
Is a powerful Ally for us
Another
Bad
Hydrocele
ICare
Okay
70% of Americans
We live in a society right now who doesn't have it
Nala Gianna, I mean literally all day long I mean
All over the place right
The might be helpful
Alex
You should not be making all those decisions
There's two big decisions
What a pile of s***
Ridiculous
Is heartbreak
Yeah really hard phrases to print
Just just go look you lost
Kill his legacy
Yeah overall of his listeners along with this day are going to blame him for
No quit just just right off to the side not the action of somebody who intends to be
Around 4.
Prudently and this will catch up
Absolutely
Customers is listeners will sign up
And you will end up losing a bunch
Money or making none and losing it because they've had to pay into
Yep and then they're going to blame Alex and then go be why did you
Misdirection
You son of a b****
This is this is a really bad thing
But
You know like
This the right one of Hickory
But I think you stop
Which actor group or intends to
Is that list of product
They're all dupla
The product yourself
Solutions that Alex already offers with the global
Center products
Betty cell
So I don't see a reason to
Duplicate
But they're only
Cannibalize each other
If you want to sell
Something
They will help with sleep
You sell p.m.
Knockout
Now a little bit later in this infomercial Alex talks about
PM is better than
Really
That leads me to believe
For sure
Newzjunky
Which is probably a SmartThings
Do because you don't need the rmd
You don't need the production
Capabilities
You can cut costs on that end
Whatever
Chipping into doctor group
Develop the product
Whatever
Paying him
Branding and license
Like that
Maybe some of that goes away
I don't know
I don't know what kind of deal he's worked out with
Do not but probably a sweetheart deal
But also
Genesis the only kind
The company that will probably get in bed without
Yeah
Volumes about both
So all this is bad
Not a multi-level
Products
Fortunately with
A minute
The same clip
Then explain
Multi-level marketing
He contradicts himself within the course
Blisters to know
I think people
Lifestyle
To dominate in the United States
Western
About to get novice
We know what's going on
Business model
Person
Where where
Right off into the sunset
Also the business model is really the big product
The big product is
The business the business
Now I want to talk to you
So we already talked about how the owners
Founders of Jeanette
I also got in trouble for running
Fraudulent
Before this
But also according to truth-in-advertising
Quotes close to
Complaints have been filed with
Florida Attorney General's office
Regarding jeunesse
The vast majority of complaints
Concern problems
Refunds
Enclaves at Janessa's a pyramid
Endorphins
Jeanette is or has been involved in at least six
Lawsuits
Conception
Class action lawsuit
It alleges the company is operating
Pyramid scheme
Aging and racketeering
This
Tobias
Is very
Very clearly setup
Quote new genesse Distributors are required to
Battery starter
For 4995
Next are encouraged in the strongest possible way to jump-start there
Business by purchasing
The product pack
Which ranges in price from about $200
To 1800
Flag
Not surprisingly many Distributors are encouraged to buy the most expensive $1,800
Successful
Operators
Explains it's a no-brainer
Because it's
Catapults for levels up
Compensation structure of Fire
Steven Universe in addition to this there's a 1995
Flag was a minimum $85 a month
Distributor discount
$1,000 a year not including the introductory package
But you have to pay for the privilege of annoying your friend
And here's the issue
I just pretty much always the case with business
Is there setup is multi-level marketing
Their products are very
So buying them yourself doesn't really make sense
But it starts
Look more appealing when you consider the discount you be making
If you were distributor
Agreed to sell the product to your friends and family makes a product that we're want
Come within your price range
This is a very intentional strategy
Because businesses
Like jeunesse are not looking for customers to buy their product
They're looking for people to
Become distributors
Because weather
Succeed or fail is
Distributors
As that Tavares
Successful
Business owner through jeunesse Kim
It's not about one person selling all the
Cuz that's littering
Trading time for money
But this business model
She even use the word linear
Somebody doing something he's in a straight line
However
If you have somebody at the top
With multiple lines going down
Almost some sort of triangle or
Dimensional
What would you describe
I don't know if I could legally
But
Also trading time for money
This business model is about building distribution in about creating well
And then the third thing to do is to
People how to teach other p
And so
Probably called you they don't have the quote from her
Now another
You know we is distributor
You know we is
Distributors we get product at wholesale and then they buy it
So
We get a little retail Commission
Now that will be the smallest are you ever get okay
I forgot about retail commissions for me
I'm not in this to sell product I'm here to build a global distribution
Search very clear what the business is about
Pep talk elections
In 2014
19.6
Distributors
Income of $0
Earned under $1,000 an average of
Dollars in 92
Only 1.1% of all Distributors made more than
$5,000
And when you consider that 85
Dollar
Monthly minimum that you have to buy
Keep on board which is almost $1,000 a year
66% who earned under $1,000 a year
Physically breaking even or still losing money
6% of people
Who have an income of 0 from there are several thousand dollars
Most likely
You know it's sad
That is
Maybe the eggs
Exact income structure of
In 2017 they disclose their Commission in
Information from
Other information
2014 is
Publicly available
It's not a good sign
From Canada in 2017
Do we find it
3% of
Distributors made under $1,000
45%
Nothing
Navigate none of those figures.
To get the product
Yeah of course
Depending on what
Excel the recruit
If the new work
The distributor
$25
If they buy the
$500
Package
Get 100.
If they buy the
$50 Ambassador package
You get 200
If you think about that for
You'll realize
That you would always
Please want to get your recruits
Sign up for the big packet
Makes the most sense
Even possibly using manipulative disa honest
Because you have an agenda
You have a benefit
From
Them buying the package
Whoever recruited you into becoming
Distributor
Had that exact same as
Strained and now
Alex.
Unreal
You know I'd for the longest time I used to have a better chance
The nice people who absolutely
Or I mean the other side of it is
I got a lot of these f****** products are over $140
For some sort of like skin care cream
Or something like that you could get something
As good
For almost
Nothing comparatively just go to
Walgreens
Yep
Or even go buy a boutique one for like 40 bucks
Go to town
Yeah this is
It's very discreet
I got hate Alex
2 years of my life talking about how are you
Nick. Pity it's not.
In the neighborhood of
Disgust
Like I know I've always been disgusted by his racial rhetoric
Stuff like that
Charmed
But he seems like a rap
Stallion in many ways
With his leg
But we laugh at all the time
Like it's embarrassing
Desperate but there's kind of a tart
The Griff
The Grinch
Pyramid scheme
No
Yeah yeah yeah
Really I'm willing to sell out all of my friends and fam
Family
Makes more money
And then the guy that told him
Giving up everything
Payless
For Alex it's not your friends and family
It's your audience
His wife's Tupperware party friends
By the way
We are about to launch our new knowledge by Tupperware
Open up one side of it you burp it and then
But I don't know how Toepperwein
I'm very distracted cuz one of them
Half of one of my eyes is going swimming
I'm not sure why that is
Talking about Tupperware I'll do that to a lot of
Perhaps
We also have a line of makeup
Drive around in a pink Corvettes sell makeup dismount on this here in a little bit
Before we do we have to
Two more clips
Are just
A bummer
Disheartening
Plexiglass
This one isn't this one is Alex revealing a little bit too much
Raise is a bunch
Very serious
Sponsorship drumming
Guaranteed
Everything
Literally defeated
Be sure
We're going to get a good Prada
Pono
These I know we're good
Become a distributor
I feel good at a gut level
God dammit
Compressed multi-level marketing scheme
That's crazy
I don't know if I've ever heard of a like a radio
You've never heard of radio host who's personally selling
Avon
This is banana it's pretty wild
This is a guy who's literally at the lowest he could possibly be in 2009 was not make
Working anywhere near as much
Even that Alex
Real
Pyramid scheme there's got to be a better way you want me to jump into pyramid scheme
I'm selling jeans that might be the right size I'm fine with that
I'm fine with that.
It could be the right side
Pyramids
Let me go probably veto that
This is weird this is actually not both of
Very concerned
I might be going blind you are
O'Reilly's
Definitely
You're missing one of the big points
The millions of dollars
To promote
But also
Who
Who's offering you that money Alex
And you're he's even recognizing in there that I got out of the lot of these
Pump-and-dump
Yes
Yes Alex
And you know
Who's running them based on
Who was trying to get you to promote them because Alex Jones promoting it would be part of the pump
If Alex work to promote those
He would be the one who would
No
Would be letting on Wednesday
Do you think you would I think that's why he's
I think that's why he's more susceptible to the 36th Street
Of the scam the scam being scammed on this
Can actually understand
Bitcoin cryptocurrency
He wasn't willing to jump in on the ground floor the scam
But this scam
Is supplement
He's like this is my skin
Braintrace giving me a new way to scare mice
Are you the one who's being scammed
Where is multi-level
Different degrees
Yeah that's folks must be like
Jerking off over the fact that they
Look we're going to Warehouse
We can talk about the present-day much anymore I think
Maybe too much of a bummer and Alex
Pathetic shell of a man
Yeah
Federal troops at the border
Flagrant racism there throughout this episode is brutal marketing
Sign up all this stuff
Really is the
The evolution of him as a poke
Digimon if you will into
His
Is True Form now into a Venusaur
This Cliff represent
Alex Jones
Literally
Selling his audio
This is the other Trump supporters
Call Joseph
These are high rated
Cosmetics and supplement
Smartwatch and then
There's a new Apple phone coming out
Okay so
We live in a society
Are clouds
You get 25% off of sorry
If you want to get up to 40% off
Can you pay a one-time membership
And you can get all the products 40% off
Most people are out there they wanted
Walmart
My God
Who in the world
Alex I think send it to
Oh my God
Goodbye Alex
Heartbreak
This is really heartbreaking
The river basically like what you have
Like I said already it in the episode his audience is going
Going to Fair exactly as well as
Is the average Junior
Distributor does
Fairway worst
Caswell because
Terrible average already
Let's
They're going to blame Alex
And he deserves it
Because he just sold them
To do not blame
Did is transmute
All of his audience
Is attention that he has left
Whatever haven't shipped
He just took that
And said jeunesse will you buy this
Will You by The credibility that I have left
With my audience
Yeah in order to get them to
Try it maybe sign up for your thing through website that is
Call Infowars yes
You still thinking has the Alex Jones credibility
And once you do that
I don't know I don't know how you can get it back once it goes bad for so many people
Cuz it's going
Like I don't know you can do you know what this is the end for Alex Wright
I can see this going down a direction where he
Recover from that but this is what I think is fascinating about the multi-level marketing
Scheme being applied to Alex
Is that
For the first time that I again I don't know of radio host are like
Tucker Carlson isn't f****** part of a Avon or whatever it is right
I've never seen this before where in
The blank can be shifted
So
Easily
To the f****** glue
To the f****** globalist or whatever
See I don't see that
I don't see it I don't see it being possible either but his listeners
Stupid
Start losing
Scant amount of money that they owe
Did they put into this I don't see you
Hey Alex
Why did you
Start researching
Into other reviews of the company
If you're Alex Jones listener you're not researching a goddamn
Generally not but if some company
You lose a bunch of money to realize you got caught up in a base
Exploit
Business relationship I think you might look at
Did this happen to a bunch of other people and then when you see that yes
It does
Announces every read
The exact
Percentages that I read
That are real that are from disclosures from jeunesse themselves
Alex
And the fact that he's still
Trying to get
His customers
His listeners
You are custom
Yeah
To get them on board with it means
He's fine with the idea that 80
We're going to get fuc
I've never seen a pyramid
Scheme applied to a
That's the fascinating thing about this
It's never like
If you don't buy these knives then the globalist win
Like I've never heard
Because that's real pictures
Work on Alex's audience
And it's not going to work the next step
Which is the audience
Trying to sell it to other
Of course not
Get their friends
Family to listen to Alex
He's right there's no way they're going to be able to you
Use Alex's rhetoric to sell them product they don't need
It's going to be a disaster
But that's
Who gives a s*** about them having obviously obviously
Eventually was going to be
There's going to eventually
But that's the insulation that Alex has that other pyramid schemes don't have is that
The blowback has to go towards someone else it doesn't go back to
Infowars it goes back to the globalist it goes back to
Spelling of Dan
I think because of the economic
To come to his listeners
They're going to try
Differently
Then the Ops
Can do in general
I don't think that he's going to be able to weasel out of this
I don't know dear Republicans consistently root weasel out of age
For the rich
I understand that and I don't know my predictions are
Generally officer
Who f****** nose
Who f****** nose when is my eyes really
Starting to freak me out
Because I
Think I'm going blind
Call Chacha.
For now but will see you when I wake up tomorrow tomorrow
I don't know what I mean
Yeah but
But it's f****** really weird right now you had a lot of caffeine
You just drank a kick-start
Are you a hundred percent believe that's what started it still f****** with my hair
Brilliant that's where you should go really it's really great I I jump in and out of the group
They're like
The most amazing thing
To me is whatever somebody to
Shows up in his eye
I just found the show
I'm a part of the group
Who sign up for the
Hi membership package
Then
You don't have to pay the normal fees that are
Subscribe on iTunes
15 other subscribers
Write a discount on your own
I think my eyes
Getting better
It's starting to wear off
Add somebody who is my God
I do 36 years old
I work glasses for having like
A little bit of blurry vision in all you do
You don't know what this was it look like a dragon
In the corner of my eye
It was still there because like
Coronavirus
Red Dragon
No
Sort of
This is really troubling I shouldn't have brought it up
Yeah I know but it's it's a bit more severe than General
I'm sorry
ITunes
Alex
Is there something important we should know about this pyramid scheme loving motherfuker I almost feel like this is worse
But something else that he's done that might not be as bad as selling out his audiences
I would probably kill today
Alexandra Thurston color