Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
About that boy Alex Jones
Alright
I feel like it's a wrap reference but I'm not sure what to do
I don't think it is
You like or it's just a general reference
I really feel like it's a rap song I'm unaware of
Who's the first time
I actually remember this I believe
Cambridge Massachusetts
We moved from
There when I was about
So before that we went to a pool
And I remember I was able to
First time I was able to jump my head under water
His only notable because
My parents were proud
Is pizza afterwards as a little bit of a reward program
Situation where you got into a pool and you put your head underwater grandparents
I don't know how much before 7
Most of my life is
Kind of a blur except for like
Weird specific memories like that one I mostly only remember that
Because my parents had a mess
Pizza Magna
On our fridge
Years and years after that
And that memory was associate
That story about that
But otherwise I have
Almost choked to death
Hot dog
Tried to get my friend Matt to recognize that I was choking
Threw myself on a chair it really is more than you know
I nearly drowned
Champaign Illinois and I didn't know how
How to swim
Slipped into the deep end
And I was drowning
Climbed on top of them like Sylvester
Stallone in over the top
Congratulations
Where did I know about Alex Jones
Everybody for
We got from my last epoch
We were in 2018 we learned that Alex Jones is starting
It's new career as a mid-level of multi-level marketing scheme
Call Jeanette
Great start
How much I really want to be in
In the present
Look at that
We have just as important of an episode
From 2009 we are back
Very excited about what we're going to be going over today
We have to acknowledge that
This is like the third time that episode that I have tried to figure out what the name of Legends of the Fall
Is it right I think it was like
That's just our Rhythm that feels very familiar where I don't want to talk about whatever we can get
So I texted the wrong movie Fight Club
But it is possible
It's possible
Female show
Give a shout out to a couple of new donors
The idea of us having goals
Everybody who
And almost 85% of the way to heaven to do another documentary
Oh no
Sooner than we expect
I'd rather not do the Obama Deception but any of the police documentaries are up for grabs
9 hour day is going to be a rough one
What is not rough
Is
Stoners
Thank you very much Paul been around
Booster of the show for quite a while
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Everyone who is
Pokemon go
I would like to give a shout out and thank you to someone who took their donation
A globulin
Don't get mad and tell her you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
YouTube
And today
Hey look
Perfectly clear investigations episode
Hey I got sick and tired of listening
March 4th
I will be the first to admit that
Last acknowledged time I've ever done that
I live in the beginning will get back to it
That was the first time I did that
How do I have not gone back and listen to the rest of the episode we would have missed something massive
Let's
The few times you've done it before now you just been like
We've never gone back
I was right.
Chop It Off
This is the first time you've been wrong
Once every twice a day but I am
Getting back
March 4th
And getting into what happened at the end
Then the rest of the episode will be about March
Where Alex
Does something
Fun forever
Except for his listener
Super fun for Nick Cannon
Width of the
March 4th
Alex at the beginning of this episode
He had a quip of George Soros admitting that
Mickey head
Crash the price of oil intention
I was like
I looked in
George soros's
Comments about oil around this time disgusting
Who's created with large
Due to over
Speculation about the price of oil
And was advised
People to
Work towards
That bubble not bursting
Nothing to do with like intent
Internally crashing the price of oil
So that was just going to be
I have this clip
I didn't realize at the end of the episode
So he would actually
Play the clip
What now
Did he doesn't do that it doesn't
And wouldn't you know that this is the exact same thing
Eclipse
Jose is George Soros admitting
But he crashed the price of oil
See if you can
Get that
From this clip
More importantly
Figure out what actually is make
Alex Mack
Ibank efforts going on in United States for there's so much else to be discussed here because this is after all the world economic Forum looks
About the price of oil
What are the implications of $40 oil in your mind
Fortunes
For the oil producing countries
Gulf States
You have a
Quite a few
Bopping
And a smile
Adversity
However
It's not because
Heavy
Ulta prevailing valtorta Venezuela urine
Russia
And
It's not so easy to finance
Boulevardia Revolution
Is Chavez
Probably his days are numbered
Andrea Robin
And he's
He's up for election 09
And an end unless
He can provoke some
Incidental
I think that's his life
To also
Ptcgo
More reasonable regime
It's more
Dumpling
Cause
Booting
Has been using all
For the number of users to June
Re-establish
Palacios geopolitical influence
Average
To maintain themselves in power
And the rulers of the neighboring countries
Game controller
Obsessed
And and
Now
Sunday
Financial collapse
Inflation
Ruble falling
Leaving Standish
And
Danger
Adventurous trying to
Have some fun
Adventure
Ukraine whatever
I'm afraid we have to end it there
The clip most Lionel
You could characterize that as economic and political analysis
Is based on what the price of oil is
The food was able to
Game the system places that are outside of the sphere of
George Soros recalled the world order
Scares Alex
Because oil has
Rich
Relying on the oil speculation driving up the cost of oil
L x light
Stu
People like they're doing a good job
Which is also something that we've already seen 2019
Russia
Like that
What is analysis
I don't
I don't particularly care to get into whether he's right or wrong or anything like that that's not my
Later
Yeah
Not too much longer but not soon enough for nothing the time frame
And then Rush
Some exploratory Adventures
Nowhere in the Clippers
Anyways
I crashed the price of oil
He's saying that there are benefits
Do it come from
These regimes not being able to use
The price of oil today
But that does not imply in any way they like
I did that s***
We did not
Let's remember
Along with Putin
Venezuela
Arawn
Alex's dad lost a lot of money
So you might have something
Give you please like live any
A little bit later and let's see what his analysis focuses on
Does it focus on a rock does it
Months before they married in Georgia
Sincerely nineties
Because I wanted to
Everything you were saying
Understand I'm just an ordinary everyday guy like every other man every morning
Years ago
I had the privilege of living with the elite of the world for three years as a result I've kept in touch with some of them and
Hey have kept in touch with me sometimes over these past 35 years
They knew in advance Alex
I plead with you everybody out in the audience today I think of you please
Listen and believe every word Alex Jones is saying he has tried to tell you for you
Williams
Presenting this idea that because he was a chaplain
We went over him
Because also In that clip clearly he has no idea what anybody was and he was just
Rambling on just like
Well you know I was around those people and all I can tell you is to listen to what Alex
Believe
With a guest
Power butter Alex
Really flattering
So you knows that part of the game and God bless
Time for it
But
Strategically
Referred someone
No I'm for that so Alex
Main analysis seems to be about Russia
It seems to be about how
The the Southwest
Occasion
Attack you
He's using
That was a sneak attack against Russia
Territory
Ethnic cleansing
Used to be part
The Soviet
Right right
Technically it's always will be
How much like Texas is a part of Mexico
Absolutely
Cirrhosis
He did this
He crashed the price of oil cuz that's nowhere in the clip
You getting defensive about the idea that Soros is against Russia
Holyshit exactly what we predicted I still don't know
If this is enough
With the investigation of window
Does he start talking about
Like that
Clear-cut case of this is that
Figure out like that
Cuz he still not saying George Soros is a demon who runs ever
Germination of a thought
Did the Russians very clearly
Deanza
And the fact that we know Russia is
Communicated with Alex Jones
Not to the level that
Has been an artist
Somebody is able to
And perhaps
If you were to out-of-the-blue
Start criticizing
George Soros
We like it when you criticize George
That was good stuff
To speculate
Plywood
It has a certain narrative reality to it
But we can't cancel
For sure although it is
Just fascinating
Where where's thing
To him being about George Soros as a demon
And stuff like that
We move on now
Really bored that I need to really
Put a button on this
Did they had anything to do with the price of oil
Absolutely
Doesn't say that at all
This country that was previously flush was with cash is now in a depression so the leaders
Presumably are no longer popular
Might be kicked out they're going to have more difficult time getting away with the things that they have been getting away with now
Oil revenues
They came from a hyper-inflated
Price point
But it's not exactly like
Mind-blowing analysis
Is the price of oil coming down
For people to buy gas for their cars
Why is Alex so invested in the price of oil being super
We're high and therefore more expensive for lunch pail
I know he cares about the little man
Middle class
We move onto the fifth
Alex
Coming in
Hot
On the 5th
Oh s***
This is going
Point where Alex
Brings
Existing 10th Amendment narrative
But he's been
Spreading to the last month
He's going to have this
It's going to sort of mutated
Something
Combine
The tea party is going on already there
Do you know if there's a lot of weirdos
Who are starting to come on Fox News Glenn Beck is becoming a little bit more ascend
Within that right-wing Community I thought like oh I think he's going to
Okay
This is going to start
And so when he says this maybe not
The beginning of the show
I think that's where it's going
Usually every 5-6 months or so
Prepare yourselves
For this information
This information I'm covering to be lost in the overall chatter
Pantheon or the Panacea
Nope none of those
Laurel
And still somehow incorrect on all the stores
Normally it is every six months to a year that I
The song control
And 8 days ago
He had the
Did FEMA camps are being created
Stop got all crazy
Because he's talking about the birth
Pains and things are accelerating and stuff
That's the same language
Later with Trump like about the idea of the time is accelerating things
Coming closer together
Patriots
Uses a language
Compartmentalizing
Some part of his brain that is only for paperie resurgences like make
Maybe This Is It
White supremacist research
It's got to be right
So
At this point
Egoi moves along
And he talks about his own FEMA
Camp story
In favor of promoting this story
For today
A month ago
Nothing
This story is nothing
Chris
Agree
Nothing compared
The story last night
Upset my stomach
First of all I was afraid that I am so mad
I do not have an upset instead I am upset with the failures of my body
How much acid was produced
Because anthropomorphize every spot you can have
Because I'm stupid
My Palms were sweating I had sweat and my house was cold air conditioner on
It sounds like you had a cold man
I mean
The flu
It sounds like you got a bug or food poisoning any of those exquisite
All of those sounds like a slight bug
Sleep
Is that out yet
Maybe I misinterpreted
It's cute
And Alex
Book the FEMA camp where you were going to be forever forever
When the government comes at you in the FEMA camp
Nothing right again
More important than you spending the rest of your life
In a camp
Well the first thing is
Sleep last night I think he needs a nap
Kind of teasing
What this is about
I'll give you a hint
Operation
Even the target month before
I mean Lisa's right around when BioShock 2
Might have been
In terms of him taking 911
Like it was a regular
So much mileage out of like the fact that he said
They know they're going to attack the Twin Towers it's going to be that long
He wasn't nearly the only person who said that that was a very popular prediction
I believe the biggest person who said that was
What's the time
It's one of those things like
I can't take away from Alex that he
Did say that in advance
But I can't take away that it means anything
Or that he has some kind of secret information
So I don't
I don't give him a lot of credit for that
And I'm going to give him a lot less credit as we
We get into this bio attack
Biotech
I don't like to do
Alex takes
F****** ever to get to the story
That I want to recreate that
Experience for our listeners
I want them to
Feel
The frustration with Alex
That like
If you're listening to show we're already you know a couple commercial breaks. This is big news
Got s*** on this
And then is going out to break
But you think
Eli car right
Talking about
Cuz you know what we love to do on our show is make our listeners breast
Put Pitino that we will get to it eventually or is he don't know it's Alex
Point that's true in Open Water
But I'll tell you right now that the news I've gotten
Because he doesn't respect information
He'll respect
To just
Move on
Focus on something
Over 100 equals
Stretch we don't have a PowerPoint out yet
Arrow
Just the asinine over-the-top macevil
Nautical Surplus
Grocery
On the website and podcast
They just keep calling and there's no
There's no New World Order none of this is happening everything's fine
Anymore
Very very sick Society
What sectors of our economy and Society
Are just really sick evil people
So should they are engaged
Tell the story of this magnitude
People don't respect
Very short
People are
Spiritually what the f***
A gift cuz he's got to get to this news
It does it does disrespect
Preemptively defend against your dude
Take me to
The f****** news already
4 hours of
Come on
In 4 hours
Most of you listening right now this show us around
Did your dad
Our children are probably going to die
Parents
The vaccine
And the first bio-weapon they were
Bioweapon
Cyclone
Stunning
Around me
Again I didn't get the flu I think you got a bug Alex another symptom
This is what this is like what he said
Forever
Tell you what
This buck with information
So
No real
Details about what their story is but thankfully
You promised he's going to read it on the other side of the
Commercial break
Break
And it comes back
He still rambling a bit before he goes
T.i. get caught
My heart out
Commercial
This is
The most important
Story
I have ever
Covered on this radio show
Important
This Dwarfs
911 for the police
In preparation
Bioweapon
Got to go break
So this is the most important story of his career
What
Listen to 1011
Probably yeah
Global 911
To like it's a 12-mile weapons
Going to kill billions
Mega Million Friday night
Right right right right right
Killed 0
But
Bingo
Bird flu
This is wonder what would happen
He got a flu
What's a bio-weapon
Well it's poor he was inspired by having the flu to be like obviously that's how they're going to kill every
I had the flu I could have
I don't have medical records on Alex
Description of symptoms
They possibly eat suffering from a bug
The issue is that there was also a new story that
Come out a couple
Before this
That sort of feeds into
Alex's
He's going to make
Disgraceful propaganda
I will be able to over the course of this
He's getting all of this in
Asian from
It's not the place
Susie says it's gone
Coming from
This is this
He's so bad
I can visit Alex at his
We've already seen him build this up
This is the most important story I have
Have ever
Come on Aaron told you about
And
When we get to
Let me get to the bottom of it
It will be
Terrible embarrass
It's important
But he comes back
Brake and he finally gets to
To the story
And it's interesting
Where he's reading
Okay what I'm going to do is I'm just going to read this news article
And why is she so serious
And connect to other
Crystal clear
This morning accidental contamination of vaccines live avian flu virus virtually impossible
Vaccine scientist
Well certainly there's that issue
Put that aside for a second
Because the big news
He's reading these reading this article this news article
That was written by Paul Joseph Watson
And Alex told him to
The nature of
Big story
You're reporting on your own ship
This is not good
Number one
What Paul Joseph is reporting on
In a little bit
But suffice it to say
It's not
Anyway
Little claims that Alex
The real
Really trouble
So much
Every time
Story with
Paul Joseph Watson
And wrote an article about it
Christ why are we doing this
Yeah yeah
I don't even want to
Tertiary
Paul Joseph Watson
So I guess I guess what I should do up top
It kind of gives you
The reality of the story
He's telling
There was an issue of described as gross mismanagement
Where a company called Baxter Pharmaceuticals Baxter
The flu vaccine
And a bunch of chicks
Pigeons
Showed up
Save
Knocked all the vials of flu on the floor
Got the flu and that's where bird flu came
Company called biotin
Was also involved
H 5 n 1
It appears they're responsible for a mix-up that happened at this check
Not Baxter internet
To clean flu virus
To the check company Biotest
For research
I was replaced by a bird flu virus
Replacement of the test material
Does Baxter's wickard Kichler
But
The problem is slightly more complicated
The origination
Contamination wasn't even necessary
Bald-headed
Call Daisy IR
Green Hills
Who'd hired out a bio test lab
Is only occurred during the process for witches
Particular research project
For a vir
Green Hills
In Baxter's Laboratory
And this specific process will not be
So they rented it out for like a
Staff birthday
Sure if you want to go
That far with it
Yeah whatever
This is kind of complicated so I'm a little up in my head about laying outside
There was a vir Greenhills
I was running attack
Involved
Bird flu
This facility that was over
Christine by biotech
Biotest
International national
Flu vaccine
This Biotest labs
We're avir Greenhills
Was also doing
Search on
The bird flu
They have some sort of
Miss handling
Mix up
Of some sort
Unclear exactly what happened
Working Theory as I understand there were some
The influence five-in-one that were unlabeled
And ended up
Commingling
The other stuff
That was
Plot of every 50s movie where something
Turns
Yeah it's the plot of every 50s movie where is like the giant woman it was there they went to
It has great potential to have gone
Fortunately there's some protocols in place
End up catching things
Ended up being painted
They were
Testimony
Obviously
And they're supposed to not have
Terrible
That is
It's not
They have a terrible reaction to the alarm
Ferret showed negative reaction
Kill the ferrets
Because
Had already been shipped out to
Couple location
From this check
Until the end up finding it
No one ended up getting sick
Sick from it
The employees of the labs
Gotcha
Inoculation
What's fine
Got resolved
Less destructive then when like
Grocery store has turkey
Recalled lettuce
Yeah
But it has such scary pretend
Yeah because the idea that
Behavior and flu which is not really all that harmful
People largely because
I understand
Copper
DiNozzo
Of the human is too cold
Generally speaking it dies before
Your system
Just think that's from an article I read in some scientific journal
No entire Lake
Humans for the most part are not susceptible to
And it's not airborne
Saudia
Mingle and mute
With the normal flu
Flu is much more dangerous
4 people as much
Higher mortality
Mingle with a regular flu virus survive
Incubate Within
The person in order for that
Trade on the feet
Peers
But that idea causes but he's not dealing with the reality of
Actually happened
I've done
You too and it's very,
All of this
Good luck because it will firmly demonstrate what a propagate
Continue with jokes the whole time
Fair enough
To the actual story
Just yet
Now this is a
The 90%
Not true
That is not true
Cuz we would you get that well because there till 6
Percent of the people that get it
But you can come in contact with it and not get it
Quite easily
Trying to mix the idea of
Being exposed to it
And
Having it
Invader
Think you might have birth
I don't but I do know someone who had
They survive
Get it
Come in contact with it and not get it
Alex is trying to muddy the waters
Bird flu is
Not great
So now yours is next
They gave it to ferrets
Hammer
That's not true
They killed the pharaoh
Yeah they ended up killing the Pirates when they founded
Influence
The flu itself
Did not kill
Would it have
Yeah a lot of cuz we saw that they had
The symptoms
We know that they got the bird flu and because the bird flu has a 6290 /
Percent
Spray tan
On the
Thanks
They decided to euthanize all of them not what not least of which two
Keep them from Justice
Physical situation
Precaution and all that
I'm trying to make it less awful that's awful
Testing it on face
Life is cheap
The reality of what's going on here is
An expression of
A very
Lacking
Guidelines
There's hope there's a very serious lack
Czech Republic
Rules
Strict guidelines with which these materials
That is why that is why this situation happened
It's not because
Nefarious
Create a supervisor
Or anything like that
It is a lack of oversight
Regulation
Because this
And I know that
Set at the comedy of errors
So
This is a story that broke
At the end of February
We're now on March 5th
Alex is going to say how important
Very mad
The most important article
And I've never said this before this is the most important piece of the puzzle the Tumblers
This story itself
Many articles
Impossible
Frozen quotes
And that's the name of Paul Joseph Watson
Salty's
You're not pronouncing the quote
British it's in German
Kitchen Chinese
English papers as well
This story has been out for more than 24 hours I learned of it last night and nothing
Play more than 24 hours and there was an article on February 24th about it in Bloomberg
Soylent
There's nothing about it in America
Bloomberg I read the
Find it so
Recovering things they're not operating on
Information
He starts trying to read the actual article
He doesn't make it far before
Restart literally make
Like anytime we
He's just making s*** up at the end
Accidental contamination of virtually impossible
Subcontractor
Ferrets
Supposed to do
Guess what
It killed the ferrets
Vile
Biola
Vaccines don't need to be irradiated necessarily that is one method of
Handling I'm butt
It's not it's not some sort of like you can refrigerate dryers up
Are you can eat them
Usable
Has a vaccine
Do involve radiation
Absolutely it's not the only one
I don't see any
From the
Primary sources that out
Nation from the lab
Specifically use the radio
I don't know about that
And the fact that he saying that he killed all the ferrets
Lead me to believe that
He doesn't have a handle on the X
Suzuki
Keeps going back to that one
Information
Definitely
Freeze-dry the
A couple of weeks
It's just like chick
Sure you don't want to leave it in
In the fridge for a couple of weeks
It's going to go bad
See you later you put it in the freezer that's my advice
Irradiated
I don't know if I
He's getting his information
I'm from and this is deeply deeply Bravo
Weather
Baxter vaccine
National papers in Czech Republic
Infowars.com prisonplanet.com
It sounds like I wrote them they're saying there's no way this is on purpose what on Earth is going on
To mainstream news
Is saying
And it sounds like Alex Road
Yeah
I found all of the check
News sources
The way I was able to find them
Is by reading Paul Joseph Watson article
And finding where
Qlink
To the check mainstream news source
Okay
Keep doesn't
That seems odd for him to not link
He claims to
He cites his sources
He does fight the sources of these mainstream check news
Places
Now the link that he uses
Takes you to a blog post on a website called 911 blogger
Put on 911 blogger
Purport
You have excerpt of the translation
From the check news articles
The source
And they don't say what he say
I got these articles translated
I got a pretty good handle on what they're saying
Edit 911 blogger is
Could have been written by Alec
More life
All of Alex Jones
Is there are these check news
They're being interpreted by 9/11 blogger
Right
Write these articles say
If he's not at 11 blogger
Bless you
He's coming with some truth into your twin towers of it
Translate
Please check articles
Crazy Paul Joseph Watson
Based on 9/11 bloggers in
Haitian
It also doesn't make
Make clear
You quoting
The editorializing of 911 blogger
And when he's talking about the purported translation from the check
Now
Further third step
Is Alex Jones editorializing about Paul Joseph
Interpretation of the editorializing 2911 blogger date
This is a crazy game of telephone
Telephone play the game of telephone
Right
Is boring because everybody always here
It's never funny at the end
To the check news sources
What I found
What I laid out at the beginning
Biotest
The company that is most response
Before this fuk up
Of running this lab
Pills
Anne Baxter International
Had interest
Biotest lab
Nav is green
Hill's is also
Doing research
At this lab
And somehow
Biotest
Is mostly responsible for
Now I've
If you read
911 blogger.com
It's very clear
That
I'm guessing it's a
They are saying
It doesn't jibe with that
Here's the first block problem
911 blogger states that quote the check company biotech near
Comprar got from Austria testing batch
The new flu vaccine
From an American company
Baxter
In February
You found the vaccine
Was contaminated by the 85
Navy
This is not what primary sources say
Austrian company
Avis
Sales is running tests on
Who are also contracted by Baxter
Is loggers trying to
Comply with the vaccine
Coming from Baxter
Work intimidated from the beginning
Who did not proven
That's number one
Number to Bravo
911 block of states
Quotes
Problem of the Baxter Vic
Contamination
H501
Was found in the Laboratories
Lavenia Austria and Germany
Which confirms that the source of
In fact the Baxter
This is also not true based on
Some primary sources
The Articles Clearly say that the samples that ended up
Slovenia Austria and Germany
All originated from that Biotest lab
Where the Avis Greenhills were running their test
Underway to lakhs of standards and regulations
You take a note
So you going to jump in
Number three
911 first the company Baxter was he's open to trades
Bh5 N1 virus
The vaccine
But then when it was already clear that the source of the Contagion
The representative for
That's a contaminated virus
Produced by Baxter Laboratories for the company abreviar Greenhills
While it is true that Baxter said that they cannot comment on how things had happened without giving up Ray.
About their process
There.
It was a procedural error that took place at our branch
I cannot tell you the details
I cannot reveal our business.
Action to prevent such a
Mistake
They were not forced
In commenting because it's clear
That they were the source of the
The contamination
Complete editorialize
And misrepresentation
It is been being weird and parotid by Paul Joseph Watson
Did somebody
Yahoo
Spread this time
The problem number for Ati AR
Biotest
Is the source of the Misunderstood
I thought here's what
I'm trying to understand
To keep everything
From what I understand the timeline event
Baxter and Avi are
Yes dir is working on
Is working on the vaccine
Avian flu
Because of the Lacs
And Avi are
Baxter's vaccine
Is contaminated flu vaccine
Baxter
Is then sending this vaccine out to these other places from Biotest
Vax if it were contaminated that would be the correct process
Yeah so it's call Jim it's all just they were sharing the same lab nobody is really doing
A good job with paying
Yes
Governmental regulations
But the other thing that's important
Before
Became a public
Health crisis at all
Those safeguards with the ferret testing
Stuff like that
And everything was able
Go to be lockdown
Which is
This biotech
Which is not
To make the Misunderstood
They were stubborn
Contracting work for back
That it's not
It's important to Mancos to pay
Won't do it for you
There was still a Fail-Safe of like
Hey are we murdering
Phone number for
911 blogger says quote check authorities now will hopefully proceed
With the prosecution
He's involved in a course
The suit for criminal negligence in public menace
Baxter is still on the
This is not found anywhere
The primary sources
What they do say is that Dana drove over
Quotes will be getting ministrator proceedings in the coming days
Against Biotech
Define culpability
They could face a fine of 25 million crowns
Approximately
$28,000
This again
It's an important distinction
Because that's not the same company as Baxter
Can you sing the Baxters
Prosecution
It's not Biotest
The problem number five
The middleman
It's like a it's like a
Place that just has a lap
It's just like a we got a lab
Clearance
To do test online
Attractive place for Avis Greenhills
Space where you can rent an office for a day
With
What you would do need far greater
Controls
We can do it serves again
Inasmuch as you have this company that
It needs a place
To do work out of you
Have a place
Workout abs
You come together and
Everybody makes
To have your own Laboratory
Because you're not using it
Or your own laboratory but it's not
Cleared to do tasks
Breakfast particular exactly
Raise all of your standards up
Do what you need eggs act as we know all too well most people don't follow the standard
Until they're caught
A lot of people are humans
Are you suggest the capitalism has a has an inherent
Work at those places are still cute
Invicta
Everyone Cuts Corners at the work
Especially after a while you work there
Are you f****** stick to all the rules
Ears
Eventually find out what
Hey what's going to get me caught what's not
Yeah
Flu vaccine
What happens if you know what you're you're just lazing around your
Google and share
Instead of doing your work
That's just like anybody who's had a job knows that
Kind of the patio you don't like
Imagine if that happens in official places
It just might
It's a gig for these people you know
Speaking of gigs 911 bloggers got one
Make a note he is a vocation
He has a calling
And that is about 9/11
Aegis of a 911
Problem number five
With
Coverages that
Are they close by
But was this just a criminal negligence or wasn't an attempt
Provoke pandemic
Being against flute
Spread the disease
I've been cash in for the vaccines Against h5n One
Which Baxter developed
This is super irresponsible conjecture
Post on
He would know that that's
Not at all what's being reported
He further goes on to ask quote don't they follow Eva
Basic precautions
The American Pharma companies
American Farmer
Subcontract
Check web
It also turns out
No they don't have the regulations
Someplace before
Strict implies
Precaution it is not an American Farmer
Company
You know what is this
Is the plot of the BBC
T-Series
But it's a British series
Utopia
It's great if you haven't seen it I recommend it
He's alive but otherwise
Absolute
That series may be great
But
Is f****** your responsible
Now Paul Joseph Watson gets even more irresponsible as the edges on layer
He answers only our propaganda to reporting a 911 blogger post and pretends that he's reporting on stories
Check media quote from Paul Joseph
According to compiled translation
Check Paper Store
The media over there is asking tough questions about whether the contamination with part of the deliberate
Start a pandemic
Was this just a criminal negligence or was it an attempt to provoke
Medium
H5 and one which Baxter develop
How could on on Earth
H5 ordinary flu vaccine
Don't even basic precautions the American Pharma companies
States
Translation
He's using the lab
Paragraph where 911 blogger
Is editorializing
Purported translation
The Paul Joseph Watson
Planet article
Something that comes from
From the translation
Check media
Presented the idea
That the media is
What does Criminal negligence or the temp to cause a pandemic
Precautions in American Pharma companies
He's saying that that comes from a translation of check news sources
It does not
It comes from a 911 blogger
911 editorializing about his quotes
From the translation of Portage
Make a platform
Is there a zz completely unrelated
Parallel lines
Better connected
Paul Joseph Watson
9/11 misreporting of the check newspaper
To draw conclusions like quotes
The fact that Baxter mixed the deadly H5 N1 virus with a mix of h3n
Seasonal flu viruses is the Smoking Gun
The quotes there can be little doubt therefore this was a deliberate attempt to weaponize H5 N1 virus
Extreme
Sexy
To the population who would others
To a devastating degree of the disease when terrible
That sounds right pjw editorialize like crazy and just throws out his own opinions masquerading as facts
However to reiterate
The key aspect of the story that it's
It's virtually impossible for live avian flu virus
Find its way into effect
Biaxin
Which I would respond to buy
A proper protocol
For handling a
This materials
Sample could be unlabeled to get mixed up
Surfaces are containers could be on properly Santa
There's hundreds of different little ways
Would happen
Find it almost harder to imagine that it could happen
Purpose
It been on accident it's a much more
Purpose someone work
Everyone about that whereas the only thing that makes sense
Transfer it to of gotten
So far
Is that it was
You look into
Check
Corn
That they
Conclusion they came away with his
It's way too easy
Something like this to happen
Governmental
Regulations
Just like the way we treat our nuclear stockpile
Fall Apart
Larry's got that under
Don't worry about it
From here
Paul Joseph Watson
Fills out his article with a template for an Infowars
Assertions that the vaccine companies are trying to cause a
Pandemics
Can sell more vaccine
Applying the rich globalist stand to gain a lot of money they sell more vaccine
And of course the long tube unclaimed at the globalist want to kill 80% of the population
It's a very standard
Infowars
A very valuable opportunity
To trace the route
From a check story
Getting misrepresented by a conspiracy blogger
Who is represented by Paul Joseph Watson
Whose story Alex then reports on
On his show
As if it were actually based on any reality
Is a perfect encapsulation of Infowars lack
Journalistic
Looks like
It's crazy to look at this
Oh here's the original story
Here's the first
Here's the second life
And here's Alex reporting on the second lie as if it were the
Mainstream news
Is about realizing on the 2nd
F****** crazy
He's stage 3
It's not
Things get really interesting
I told you that
Bloomberg had reported on
The story on February 24th
They wrote that article and check
A good week before Alex is reporting on it and saying that there's nothing in the American Media about
Bloomberg has put out an article about this
It's interesting to
Because in this Bloomberg article that claimed that Baxter was to blame
For the contamination
There's a couple problems that I found
The first is that at no point in the store citations do Alex Paul Joseph Watson or 911 blogger
They don't bring that up at all
So if they
But Bloomberg is saying what's in line with
Conjecture
So I'm confused why they don't bring that
It's very confusing cuz it actually wouldn't have
Kind of back up there bulshit
Problem is that I could only find that story by searching to the way back
Archive
And I think it's
Entirely possible that articles based on bad reporting
Which they issued a retraction
10-4 then took down to pay
Right I can't find the retractor
Cancel the story
Really strong reason to believe
That the Bloomberg story represents bad reporting
What's my feelings
Well Jordan I was able to find a presentation that was put together by Carol Hebert
Of the State office for nuclear safety in the Czech Republic
Reflecting the results of their investigation into the incident of quote
Potential human bird flu outbreak
So
Presentation mix
Abundantly clear what happened
Blame
They review communication record
Lab documents conducted interviews with everyone who is involved and the police
And it reflected that
Several paragraphs of the biological weapons prohibition
Including illegal handling of GMO with evidence
Freely given to inspect
The presentation reflect
The company at fault in this case not Baxter and even concludes by saying quote
Officially nothing serious happened
I called to change a result of quote a chain of regrettable blunders
Which could be remedied with better Communications
Enhanced cooperation between National agencies
It possibly added legislate
And of course firing the three
They further reflected in this report
The quote Biotest was under hard pressure
From avir Greenhill to break National legislation
Speed up test
The vaccine February 2009
I think there we found our biggest issue right there
Just like an Austrian company that is
Is doing this research
Under the laws
Complacent their own country
Not in America
Even so what you see is
Buck up is caused by
Through this at a Breakneck
Speed
Getting mixed up
With
Staples
Come from Baxter's at work Lane
People f****** up
They don't have
Adequate regulation
That now
Do austrians hate the
I don't know
I don't I don't know about that level of European it's entirely possible but I don't know
We have here is a very clear case
When I read stories
They completely are aligned with the results of the investigation
Betty check Office of the State Office of nuclear safety
Doll that matches up
The things that don't match up
Are the misinterpretations made by 911 blogger that Alex Jones reporting on
And this Bloomberg story that they aren't even talking about that has been taken off the internet
So I'm left with the conclusion
Set the check primary sources
And their investigation that they did
Are correct
And that Baxter was found not to be at fault
Now the reason is Alex's
Going to make them at Falls
Is there a vaccine
No
So he's going to use this
Goddamnit that's was primarily motivated
Like Baxter is
They have been involved in a lot of mess ups in the past in the story.
We not 911 to work
Perfectly legitimate journalist
Every time I'm not going to believe anybody who's in 911 hurdle for you to get over incredibility
It's so it it's so important
We do make it clear that backs
Can go f*** himself to
But in this case they weren't in the wrong
Pressure
Being applied on the
Aaviri
Blackwater dozen
Fuk up once
Timer
Bi-Rite
Observation
Which one
911 log
Call Joseph
This is a disaster
Embarrassing
Propaganda effort
And it's really difficult to see
How much Alex
Cuz even aware
You know like I don't know when he's aware of
Does he know that 911 is totally wrong
Does he know that Paul Joseph Watson
Is reporting editor
Toriel state
Buy 911 blogger
You might be getting tricked by the propaganda maybe maybe here's my healing of his complicity
He was like hey
I'm not going to get the flu vaccine
Flu vaccine thing
Paul Joseph Watson
Grabs on any stories
Search clothing and then Alex of course because he's an idiot
Just start quoting
Anything is possible I can't say for sure but
Details the fact
Let's enjoy Alex
Try and tell this story on air
Notice all of the points
Where he's just quoting a 911 blogger as if it's
Confirm Friday
Five-in-one avian flu viruses
Canadian press
Toronto Sun online
Baxter flu vaccines
Biological weapons on Earth
Czech Republic
All extra quoting from
You know I will say this
The best life
Going to have for almost all the rest of these clips
He's quoting 911 blogger as if it's the news that's not good
Shut up
This was see me when you can
Then hide the fact that the accidental contamination vaccine
Criminal negligence
Arita check
Don't just read the checks
That is Corollary
Implied warranty
What is the road
Exact
Preparation
To create a new
1918 Spanish flu
Is it
It was combined
Between
Normal extremely Airborne extremely contagious
Strain of flu
Where's the bird flu highly airborne and highly contagious
How could you tell if you hear what I'm telling
They don't involve like none of these stories involve instructions to combine these things in order to create
He's just making that up that's not even in the 9/11 blogger stuff
The same time
Yes
F*** it f*** if I know just makes him like an old man
No because the issue is
I think they did a story
It's impossible but like
Okay
The issue of
Like instructions
Is just made
That's not
At all
Issue
You got it
So did we have
Here is the
That
Refer
Lemon zest
That's really going to bring out
This Toronto Sun article is where Alex's
They're disgusting
From the Toronto Sun
Accidental release of a mixture of live h5xhs
Could have resulted in dire consequence
H5 in one doesn't easily affect
Infect people H3
Viruses
If someone exposed to a mixture of the
Bowstring
He or she could have served as a
Bayer for a hybrid virus
Easily to and among people
That makes him
Is one of two ways pandemic virus
Create it
There's no suggestion that happened
So Alex
Taking this
Possibility that they
The implication
He's taking that as some sort of like
Read the next line is there's no snow
That happened because of this
Because it did
Because it was never injected into a person
With both of those viruses
In order to incubate
Mutant virus
And even then
Really
You would
No how would you take unless you had done this
Before
Right
Possibly predict that it would just mutate the way that you
That you couldn't just predict
Mutate
Like you just put one in there in the other one in there and then comes out
I think I think even sodas
A little bit of unpredictability and randomness
If you know what you're doing. It's not like bacon
Ingredients
Continue Cyrus's don't
Like
Just do what you tell them to to
I don't think they do again I'm not a scientist but I'm not entirely sure but I can read
So I can tell you that Alex is just full of s***
I'm making stuff up to
The Narrative that he wants to
Because he wants to scare you
Tie-dye dye
So they're putting you into
Airborne until the world population
So he's trying to scare you bring his other narratives in order to reinforce all of them
The coffin
Remedy brings in out member end
Archived
Play Phil
Bianca who was in
Harshly mischaracterized
His
Dentist
Humans dying out would be great for the natural world
Which is not an extreme
We are doing a lot then after work
And if you are someone who believes
Natural world has more
Gordon's been human
We should die
Or if you watched
The Matrix
Virus
No Remnant like Alex
Thinking is so dim
So childish
He can't understand what are Pianka saying
He's not
Forever
You think it would be good
Screams about feet
FEMA camps
And FEMA like
Teaching their agents
Vector
And if you look at the video that he post
To make that Arkham
Guy blinking really
They say that they were terrorists
Now just
You on their side doesn't make them any less
Ripped
Activities
Yeah it kind of
Is almost like they
Because they could
Attack them directly
That was their recourse
Huh
The only reason I
Bring that up is it so windy
Negative is like this inability to wrestle with ideas
Black and white
Legitimately
Express dislike
Really low grade reason
It's something
Most people
In terms of cognitive
Development you grow out of it
You would help like it
If someone were to tell me
Let's say I was really into America and I loved it
Find somewhere to tell me
If someone is saying that the founding fathers were terrorists
I would say
And I would
Hero Yaya cording to the British crown
They were
No reason to be worried about that
But Alex doesn't have to what do you mean by that
What is the actual thing that's being communicated
He wrestles with
Concrete literal
Beer
And just
Extreme
At what
Ridgewood children
You absolutely
Cannot get into the mind
The exact person that
You describe because the answer to that is
No they would be exactly as angry as Alex
Uba
Reasonable insane patriotic page
Alex
But he's wrong
Mainstream news articles
This is just for
Understand what I just covered
No
7:40 compiled
Translation from Czech
Lennar media to control
Bloomberg had an article about already this and then
Also Main Street
American mainstream news
In the region
Alex just going to find things however he wants whenever he wants
Globalist control
Before he even touches this story
That's out the window and then what
Reading from that article V like
The media is a hard-hitting question
They're all that
He's just reading Paul Joseph
Watson's article quoting loggers
Editorializing
As if it were from actual checking
I know I keep repeating that
I'm sorry to sound like a broken record
But it is so important
Baby so important to understand how propaganda
This is a
Tricom nesting dolls
People and most people listening to Alex
Would never know what is in the middle of that nesting doll they would just be outermost layer
It is
The best
That's good chocolate propaganda that the Belgian
Seems like the best chocolate
Except
It is important
You at you have to open up the doll
And see what's behind
It's prisonplanet.com
The 9/11
8 check news sources that say the opposite of what you're reporting
Alright
You're a liar
You are bad at your job
And most people will never know most people listen to never know
This is really sad
Most people. Would never
Nobody's doing the same amount
Talking about third removed
Sources
Most people are not
Can I go that far you know nobody
Prison Planet
And then
Percentage of people who are going
To read even 911 blogger the guy that he
He's quoting
Very low
The percentage of people who are going to rebirth 911 blogger and then
Insane Translate
Check articles
Text
In the in the same way that the human error is reasonable thing to a
Spectrum
Bulshit place like Biotest
In the same way it's reasonable to expect that
A human error would not
Triple-check
New source
Farbest early every time like every time
Much easier to be like
Turns out the little people but
I can smell and I know this is going to be a big narrative
Discovered
Weaker so we're almost certainly going to continue without
Don't ever take vaccine
Because
That's the way that they're going to
Create the global panda
Bird flu is
Will just be able to
This is one of
I believe so
Again as I've already said that
Templates
At least
Alex
You got the scoop
And we're trying to track down where all went whether it's been shipped out where do I continue to track this as it develops
In fact guys
Action printing the Articles just
Bird flu contamination
Google app
New mainstream news stories coming out every hour Refresh on the page
The only places that I could imagine we're actually covering this
In the same way as Alex were
11912 loggers
Is how we felt
Before 911
Which was bird flu 666. Blogspot.com
I decided there wasn't much I was going to be able to get out of that
What's become the flu
Turn off
Jordans at this point is coverage of the story's pretty much
And what he does is he had Paul Joseph
You still not an on-air Talent
Paul Craig Roberts on
Talk about how Obama suck
Diversion from your story about a pandemic coming
And just talk s*** on Obama for a bit
Express giving him a chance and yet
22 months later it's a worse human being that ever lived
And Paul Craig Roberts is Big claim to fame is like
We got a vote for Obama because we went to repudiate George W bush
And a week later like
Xavier also it Bears noting
We talked about this
It's a bit but Craig Roberts
Has a
JC
Dicey Reza
He's written for Sputnik
4 years right
Is also listed as a
On the editorial board
Thought since at least 2,000
Turn organization publication called
There is named after Virginia Dare
First White child born in
Colonial America
911 colonial America
Cross burning
Specifically done to threaten black people
There's no they consistently make the argument that diversity and freedom are inherently contradictory
And also the inordinate amount of time defending people who deny the Holocaust
It's a real dicey Outlet
Any defense of a burning cross
I mean if it's cold and you're going to die
Great defense
You can't defend the message
There's no good message
Happy birthday Paul Craig Roberts is also listed as a contributing writer for
4 years for the publication
The magazine of American culture
Chronicles of the publication with very close ties
I legitimately neo-confederate and whites
Division
Not good
The contributor to American
Free Press publication
Amanda
Leave the John Birch Society
Just crazy
Cymatics organization American Free Press is the new name of paper that you
Be called the spotlight
The spotlight organization
Stop by Willis
Do use revisionist history
That was literally it stated objective
You can't get much more anti-semitic than this quote
From Willis carto
Hitler's defeat was the
The defeat of Europe
America
The international Jews with all his superhuman genius and diabolical Ingenuity of income
I tried to create a permanent disintegration
Forsyth
He could have done no better than to invent
The Jews
Wow
He created this paper the spotlight which became American
Paul Craig Roberts
Eagles
Hey
It's a trend
Friend doesn't make any money
Publication
Your car you might as well go to
I understand I understand you like to have a lot of fun here but
So Alex
No.
Coolpad
Coronavirus
Wonder
Mysterious
Probably also
Russian
Fluent
Writing
So Alex does that
For a bit
On the show
We get
To the end
Or towards the
The show
Promise
To do that
Virtually impossible
Paul Joseph Watson articles
Where in early 2009 I was like
Please begin Adele
Please
I think he's a persona non grata
Quite a while
Butter Alex
Songs like who could this be
He's getting a doctor
A real Medical.
Rap
Medical journalist
A doctor who gives a s***
Azure catalog
Mike Adams
Rangers protect kind of a doctor
Who is this
Don't know
Going to be
So I could not have been more so
Surprise
It's the end of the show
And this is what
This is mainstream news
Carly
Rebecca
Basically they're trying to cause the pandemic
We have already stockpiled at least 250 million doses of the bird flu vaccine
You know the
The shelf life of That vaccine has a certain amount of time
If I would still have to throw the garbage
So they have to start the pandemic so that they can give the vaccine
Belittle conspiratorial perhaps
Rebecca Carley
ICarly
Would you
ICarly have a medical doctor on to talk about this
Would you be surprised to learn that Rebecca Carly is not a doctor
It turns out there
The New York board for professional medical conduct found Rebecca
Carly
Practicing while impaired by a mental disability
On the condition that
To seek psychiatric
Help
He did not protecting the public that she not be allowed to regain her medical license
Really hard
Oh but they did
Deserving of that are never
Wait till you hear this
Psychiatrist
He found a delusional disorder with the
Narcissistic and borderline personality
That's not good.
It's not a lot of really good work and everything is sighted
Everything is as the proper citation
It's very professionally done
Do the title
It's watching quick
What you going to do
It's not it's not like 911 blogger at all
Fair enough
Question
Quotes
Dr. Levens also testified that the respondent believes that her husband's son
Because she does not vaccinate
Because she has children with autism
Dr. leben's David responded believes that her husband was fulfilling the government's role in performing anal penetration
Station on their child
And the transformation sends a surge of energy to the child's brain resulting in the compartmentalization of the brain
Which is she believes would cause multiple personalities
Dr. Levens also believes that the government is interested in pursuing all persons were opposed to vaccinating
Which is part of the global government plot in collusion with the drug into
Alex
Was a doctor
And wind
Yeah well so they didn't investigation into that ex-husband
Sound
Dumpsters for paranoia
Okay
She believes herself
To be the target of a giant conspiracy because she alone can cure pretty much every medical condition known to man
Herself to Joan of Arc
And told herself with breast
She's a little baddie
That would have been a way to fight
The British
Rebecca Carly is a dangerously diluted a mentally ill person
Well I never want to judge her solely for that she's refused to get the help that she needs and is now being used as a prop by the
Play some groups of the World
And Alex Jones
To create dangerous property
And is therefore beyond the limits
She's been willing participant in the living out of it
I don't feel all that bad for I feel bad for her kid
I feel bad for the people in her sphere that are affected
Because she's mentally ill
She's had every opportunity
To take responsibility
And
Get better
Yeah
Yeah but you probably
Probably should be
Like I don't I don't want
Ever
Experience
Heard
Level it almost
Clearly isn't
Capable of controlling this
Gaggle of enablers who are not only financially
Amplify monetizing only reinforces
The only one to do this
In never getting well
Puscifer
Yeah it's tragic but I also don't feel bad for her because
Department
Wrecked
So
Alex
Has brought her in as the doctor
To verify
His fears about this avian flu relief
Which should tell you that most people probably wouldn't come on
If you.
If you
Googling
Then he asked his staff
To do a just Google her they would find this 2003 stripping of her life
Do you know that she's not a doctor
And all she does now is offer
Holistic advice
Two people
Antitoxoid Vice
And things like that you can do without
A medical license
Do you know all that yet
Present her as a medical doctor with
Some sort of a credibility in order to
Further his propaganda that
This is a pandemic
That the globalists are trying to create
Every piece of the sting
Does a little added bonus
In 2012 Rebecca Carly would go on another
Conspiracy radio show
And call out Alex Jones for being a shill for Israel
Even get the song by this morning
Alright
Horror Story
I'm really fascinated like
I think I told you post
No I mean like the tire test
Didn't like how long was she a medical
Before this
Exploded on her eggs
Profession
I read some article and I believe I don't want to be quoted on this but as I recall it was
Towards the end of graduating from attic
School is when things started
Yeah I don't know I don't care as much
Cuz you if you want to write a biography
All I care if you ever read an unquiet mind
Interesting story
What I'm concerned about is
She's being used as an
Typically about the things that Alex wants her
Next
That's the most important
One last clip that I believe is just
To this whole thing
Clearly demonstrated
Alex's
Truth
Using 911 blogger and Paul Joseph Watson misrepresentation
As if it were Maine
Stream news
Scare people
Into his world
Reinforces
And all this other b*******
Globalist
In
Serviceable
He brings a medical doctor
Pryor had her license revoked
For being delusional
Narcissistic and having borderline
Publix
To be allowed to practice medicine
Now
Here
Is happy End
People watching
Yes say it is a napping
Agreed agreed
Wow
You've done nothing Alex
This is so stupid
Well first off I'm still wrapped up in her
Which is the trash
And also
Anytime
Vistaril
Stop with I don't have
I don't know certain
You kicked ass I'm still on the lake
Holyshit
This bad
Like I feel exactly the same way
I guess I'm dance
I appreciate that
Because they're part of research that I can do
Like I can lay out the facts
Space tomchek stories
Investigation
All that stuff I can do that
Is tell you what Alex believe
I can't right this is a manifestation of
No further I can't tell you when he wrote that are
I know he does
Absolutely
I don't know if
He believed that the 911 blogger
Is accurate
I don't know if his editorial fan
Is there solo
He's trying to pull fast one
And knows that the
Versus bad
But it reinforces my world
May I don't know I got a little cold too
Because I
I would love to tell you
Alex
Right
We're on the stupid evil
Continue
But stupid is still a little
Incredibles
Absolutely
Yeah I agree with you all across the across-the-board there
Just fascinating
Well first off
Just poodles
Other
I think you might have gotten married
Recently
It's not super in
Their personal lives aren't really all that interested
I don't know if I've ever
Experience
Paul Joseph Watson
Good faith
Yeah
Yo what if your entire life is built around
Behave bad
Serial killers
People
Can compartmentalize these really
Parts of yourself
You know be normal already
I got pushed back on that just because you brought up Paul Joseph Watson's wife it's yours
Responsible to
Have a bad marriage
I'm not making you a great guy what is or is not
I'm just saying
He's probably going to kill is
I do not stand behind you on that
Where is sloppiness
In reporting
Rick
Evil
Versus just being a
Being shity at your job I don't think it matters all that much
Cuz the effect is
The effect of prop
Right
Being sloppy
Right the way you're using that sloppiness
Furthering
Evil propaganda
I'm so
We must judge
You based on that
Sorry
I'm sorry about that but
Also we have a drink
The benefit of the doubt
Is not yours is it existed in the vacuum
Episode 200 something that's a pretty good idea that I was probably intentionally
Paul Joseph Watson
Probably
The bad source
Argument
You be like all right
You guys just
Just f***** up this about the Bloomberg article
It happened
You listen to a spot like a
For biotech
And assumed that that was the reality
Textbooks obviously you're going to be Shifting the blame somewhere else
If you report based on an interview
Did Whitney
Spokesperson
For biotech
Then yeah
You're not like you're not in on
The level of acceptable
Swap
You can do
Good Outlet
Respectable Outlets
When they behave like that
Make every effort
Hopefully
Eli's world
Hopefully they do a better job
Five most of the time they still
Directions
Sir they're very low on the
I just
And Alex's
Moana
Malevolent
Yeah
We're done now
Because
I think I I think I meant
Before we started recording
Researching
This was
Do you know deep the rollercoaster ride of The Source Trail
Getting to the check articles
Alex is wrong
They're reporting this wrong
And then a little bit later finding the Bloomberg article and being like wait
This is saying that Alex is right
Why didn't they use disorder
What's going on
And then finding the check investigation
After they've already gone through all the details
So the check articles we're right
The Bloomberg article
Taking out the inner
Alex is wrong
But it was really
All the investigation of like the research that I've done this was the one that's like
Like it really spiraled around a lot more
Then other times
Most other ones have been much more.
Alex is wrong
Close the case
Follow down the rabbit hole
I was just
Avian flu
That's true
All of them
So like a few thousand people
I like
Look look look at this real is
Bio weapon released
In the 10 years
9 years
He did this episode
Zip different
Detox
That's not a pandemic related by didn't come to mine
Speaking of like
Disease
Stuff like that
Rudolph
Outbreak that happened
What was that a couple years ago
There were some text from there but
Amazing how well that was
It was contained as
Efficiently as it was
If the globalist were trying to
To cause some sort of the Bayou release
Ebola outbreak would have benefits
Yeah so
Fausto f****** flat
Nefarious world power that wants
And it seems like if you were going to
To do it
Extent to which you would do would have to then
So overwhelming
People who are at
Acting in good faith
Trying to avoid
Would have to be overpowered in
Creative
But when that Ebola outbreak
Happened
You would have done little things in your power to make sure it's
You would have taken that as an opportunity to do the things
Alex is desperately wanted
Hazel to me
All of this
Seems like bulshit
All of it just seems like
Fear
Spell check
And to get people more deeply
Entrenched
What's it called
9 years later
Use as a multi-level marketing
Introduction man I don't want to live in the present anyway
And it's really funny of it like sort of we know where this all is going because of that
Funny to look at the pics
With the framework of
We know where this leads
Savon
All roads lead to a really weird
Scammers
So fun that he's like just leads to
Legitimate
In terms of like the election
And all that
He had his
Moment in the sun like Icarus
He flew far too close and now he's stuck inside
Mary Kay
Yeah
What a
No
But I always forget to do
Zanies in Rosemont literally this week
If y'all if y'all in Illinois or Chicago
Doughboy
Uncle Larry
Larry Reid
He's been around
For god dammit isn't all of comedy at the Legends
Settings
Yeah that's great people to go check that out
Probably
Find a way to get a list
Giveaway
Just ask night
Call Terron Twitter
Go to our website
If you like what we do to support
The program I am in the middle of
Being very very.
About
Preparing
The reward
That we have
For the
If you want to support that even though it's a little mysterious at this point
We would appreciate it
I love all of the
Policy wonks
I want there to be more of them totally
Please make sure that we only get to 99% of
Do this f******.
The other one
It's further
You have to do nothing for so
Your sort of should be
Conflicted
But other than that man
A die
Feel like there's
Look beyond beyond the multi-level marketing scheme there's like some
Thing that you should
Remember about
Disabled
Yeah it didn't kill any
A bit but there's one
Might be higher than this conspiracy that he sell it
Alexandra Thurston color