Alexandra Thurston color
Beginnings
The same thing so I wanted to drink my roller coaster
As far as the first shot in the dark
A blue sky
There's no bad idea
Okay baby
Let's
Thank you for the
What's going on man
Take me to Best Western
Although I am starting to like the fact that every vague question
It resulted in like long story longer than expected
We don't want to give it a shot
Yeah they're go
When did you first try
Versed
Oh that's an interesting question
But I don't think I have a good answer for that
I mean I mean I liked growing up and what have you sure
Remember my friends had like Dave's
Sauce
Try that
That's just
Gross that's just like really discussed
Never heard of David
It was like an old Pro
Frank sauce
He's staying with her soup
Superhot
So they are the like peanut brittle
Condiments
Sure
Sure they're always filled with exploding
Yes yes
The camp
The last like 45 years ago
I've gotten interested in
I just asked
Play everybody we were in Austin and you spent
God knows mirror an hour in the hot sauce store Ryan everything
I find that I find that in
Terms of a turning into a story but Noble effort
I got this great question it's not bad
Impact
They are
They are good
Does new donors for podcast
You are now
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Perla
Also one
You so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Number names
Except for Andrew Wright Elementary School
Andrew Breitbart cuz your dad and I know that your credit card doesn't work anymore
That's absolutely true
Iran podcast
To one of our other side world
Ocean Project Camelot
Putting out stuff
Putting out a lot of content lately
Where is Buffet
A little bit of a dry spell she wasn't putting out a whole lot
Project Camelot in like 3 or 4 weeks
Assume that she didn't put out enough high-quality
Back to fighting shape
She's
Season 4
The fences
Also there's nothing is going to come up on this episode
The f****** funniest things I've ever heard in my life
But also at the same time
The reason we haven't been going back to Jim Bakker so much
I think we've dealt with
Like I've listened to a bunch more episodes and it's so much crap salesmanship
So pathetic
I've listened to him and Michael
How would we talk about
Exactly the same thing as
Bunch of the other episodes
Oxytocin
But I do Reserve
The right to if you have someone else on like Apollo
Intersection of
Doomsday Faith bucket
In politics
That's worthwhile
I don't want to wait hours and hours of my time
Like fishing in this dry well
Of Jim Bakker
It's a waste of my time
That's where you want me to be pissed off
Start a part of the charm of the show
Yourself so we don't have to
Yeah I guess so
Sort of bullpen
The roster
I've known Alex Jones.
Future
Augustus off air
Bit more about Joe Rogan
A little bit of his catalog
Hi
And go through some of that stuff
And so I'm not ready to do that today
We talked about Project Camelot
And like I said
One of the funniest f****** things I've ever seen in my life
Maybe during an episode with
Jordan Peterson
Not worthwhile Peterson
And God bless him for it
Create other people
It's already been done
But I think there's a story going on with Joe Rogan
Hafthor
He's alright
Not be adjacent
Behavior that is not being told
That is interesting sound through analyzer
That I think is worth
Future
Look
But if you want to support the show
It helps a lot
Towards us
Jamaican D's
Goals that we have a reality
You know bacon to work
Redan easier
We've shout it out today and everyday
Sports show
Perfect
Here is an out-of-context dropped
From Today Show
I have remote View
Okay
Alright Jerry
You can just look up
She's got a remote view that Moon
The Moon
Everybody like if your remote viewing cuz that means you stood on the moon
She has the experience of her astral body being on the moon
I guess
Something like that
I would I would assume it's not
Doubt
Buccaneers
There's going to be a theme on today's episode
Play 3 episode
So Jordan today is episode
It starts unlike
Any other episode of Project Camelot I've ever heard
Eden vet
I don't know why Carrie didn't just say it
Start half an hour later
Cassidy
Has a giant races
I'm sure Cassidy from Project Camelot and
Very happy to be here tonight but unfortunately my gas brewski Saul I think he didn't
Get my
Message
Sort of scheduling him for an agreed-upon time
So I texted him over on his
Channel where he just
Maybe he'll see my comment
Under that video reminding him and trying to see if
Process to the time when he was going to come on the show
Alright
So if I understand correctly we got a no-show
This guy was supposed to be on the show
Bruce don't like the amazing Bruce
Everything is Everything
Resubmission
His name is Bruce Swartz
Message Tim whatever message
Was live streaming at the time unloading a video or something
The video hey
Remember how you were going to do my show at this exact moment right now
And so she still went on air
That's the part that's confusing to me is like
You can just not do it
Is he not do the show
I from from everything I can tell no it's pretty it's pretty inconsistent
Like three or four in a week and then none
Pirate
I didn't show up I got the night off
But I also
I admire the hustle I admire the you like
No we are doing the show
Show dance
Show Business absolutely
It's your business not sure
Hey
How you doing
Beeswax
Because the guy isn't that means Terry
Needs to spend the beginning of the show
How old is basically doing some housekeeping
Love saying like a by the way aliens are real guys I know we're waiting for our gas but let me just run down the list
Things weather weapons totally real that's what happened
North Carolina I don't even know if it's still there
They are actually in the hurricane and that is why
People are dying they are being
Raptor
Retain
That's a next movie
Channel movie right now
Dammit they should hire her
Yeah I totally fell for like a question
And so she just sort of rambles and checks and on
Some things that are happening
Around the world of Project Camelot
I do want to say that Eddie page had his Facebook
Yes toothpaste
If I understand correctly
Haven't taken down last night
Cigar
Something you said
Did not agree with the powers-that-be
And or want to be or
Think they are I would have going to call him and
So Gone
His his channels gone
And
That's not even getting like Stripes that's not a normal procedure
That is basically the only people that have
That would be
The CIA
Although I obviously Eddie page is now hitting a nerve
Okay
Racism
It is the idea of a society getting along
Facebook
YouTube
So it's interesting
10th of September Kerry Cassidy put a Blog up on her website
New info res
Anunnaki or pleiadian
Heritage
Has turned
Freddy
It turns out
Things are falling apart but
This is prior to September
Okay alright
Caribou
Facebook
And if a CIA conspiracy
Next
Okay alright I like it
So now what
Turns out
Is that going to read this
The quote
From
From her
Blog post
Do you who works with Eddie
Turn on the YouTube videos
YouTube channel as well as
Project Aquarius
And Michael Wolff
On the Earth
One of Eddie's Palladium brothers and Michael
Another brother
Who's been in contact with re
From shattering The Matrix
Just another online alright alright
I'm tracking
So
Here's why they contacted
And told them to take stuff down
He went on someone else's show
Purported
To show a photo inside a pleiadian
Mothership
Showed this picture on this other person's show
And it turns out that if you
Reverse image search this or if you just
Kind of know
Took this photo is a snapshot from a video game called Secret World Legends
God dammit Eddie you're being too specific again
Goddamnit the internet will find you also in a previous video Eddie claims
Uso to be
But it's a photo taken
Information that we haven't handled
If this is true
Is Carrie not affiliated
Well I never really went too far
But I don't think that you would like
I think that was more of like I aren't you pretty
That kind of thing
Aren't you
Noble as a pleiadian
Or something like that
I don't like it
S*** this blog post
Is f******
Crazy
Because
It's very clear that any right-thinking person
That what's going on is Betty Page pictures of UFOs
Snapshots from video games
Just like his metals are representative of the real metal
So are these pictures representative
Not
The ID
That they
There's
Here's where Carrie goes with it
Eli's recently pictures of crap
Control panel
On an interview he did with another host called Ari from shattering The Matrix
I'm in contact with her and apparently
He claimed the photo from
If I understand what they're saying
Is the inside of a Palladium ship
Either the photo is from a game
Parenthetically assuming the gamers didn't have access to classified photos of real Plies
Or
It is possible Eddie is deceived because the inside of the ship looked so much like his memory he mistook it for
Should have taken the first out that second one is tough
Yeah might be a bridge too far
Is clear evidence that he is a con man he's passing off things as I got part of my story
Episode
This is my life story
And stuff like that
In reality that's not will get scary
To be like
Oono
What's going on
Dear
From the
I've made very public statement
Revealing my position
Eddie's convoluted claims
The future diabolical
If there is a problem is religious overlay
Advise you must
Control in a punishing God to such an extent
To be a Punisher of humanity
As well as
Confusion or calling himself
Abaddon
Apparently he has in his mind over this appears
Claims in the same breath that he loves Humanity
And that he and his father wants
Just save them
Cuz of his things
He said on the show where he talks about his father and the wrathful extermination of the
Draco
It being some sort of
Light being like
She knows the Pleiadians to be
Thank you must be Anunnaki
You can't just break up with
Quote
This is Keith
Vintage King
His father is just a pleiadian rulers employment
Not even the larger he claims
Not all the planets within the
Is grouper working with many other races within the galactic
Expiration
Which by the way according to Asiana.
Are in violation of the
The peace treaty with
Hitmen of the races are part of the luciferian Rebellion
They are not aligned with the guardian Alliance
Which is a group of races were safeguarding Humanity about the guardian Alliance
Versus the galactic
Confederation
However to my knowledge he did not bother to read the Voyager book
What an a******
I'm telling you right now this is the only reason to not like it
If Eddie is a member of the warrior Clan known as the Anunnaki and is one of the hybrid reptilians then
Are all his brothers
Sisters
Classic if then state
Bear dance
The testimony by Eddie on my recent interview about the Pleiadians shooting down our satellite
Act of War
Is perplexing
And what would happen
To figure out if this was
Disabled
Programs battlegroup communication
In support of The Darkside Illuminati Draco takeover
Or whether the satellite
And therefore belong to the enemy of humanity
!!
A lot of!
Chanel
I think you start to see
The issue that Carrie has backed ourselves into
In that she can no longer say that Eddie is a liar
She has to make him evil now
She now has created a super villain
Because I couldn't until like
Really read into that
Yes in fact I am
Oh my God a showdown between Good and Evil
We don't know for sure yet whether or not carry herself
Is good or evil
Extrude
I don't know she's like a part of the globe
Federation or the alliance what happened
Do you have no standards if we all talked to
Alright well now my narratives going down this road and he's a f******
What do I do
You've actually Anunnaki
This is like that now you didn't shoot me
You spend so much time talking about Alex Jones
Really matter
Halo
That's my life
Bishop things on alien planets
Alright buddy go to bed
Go to bed already
You're no longer useful so
He's super useful now as the bad guy
But not on the ship
Well I mean maybe
What is the head of reconciliation episode not a Showdown episode
Absolutely
Terry takes Guinness in the production room
Would wind up
Switching places
They don't
Mark Richards put his mind at 2 or or
Prepaid claims
I haven't felt like myself ever since I went to Vacaville
Resale good
Perfect Minerva get on that
So many possibilities for this narrative to go in better directions
That would be
Cuz Eddie
To pull it off with a complete lack of
And flexibility
I shut down those satellites totally thinking that that would be a fine thing
Better
That's her out
Her out is on the show
He said that he was
He shut down the
Satellites
Now it turns out he's a liar
Head full of s***
She's like that she agreed with him
On every
X
Yeah it's short span
Like that you never does that with that
Pushed into the front of the line
He's a f******
Definitive bulshit artist
The UK
Misinformation
I like that
At the very least listen to the most
Recent episode of Bettie Page on
Haha
She didn't though because she's recording this episode and saying that
The CIA what have you
Tracy
We going to be involved with this anymore at all lights
This is how she spends her time with her guest camp
He starts talking a little bit about her she didn't interview with
Somebody else
And we're not getting it.
I will say that I did an interview with
Trottier is his name
And II
Posted it
Yesterday the link to his
And then he tried to post it on YouTube and he got a
Immediate message
Saying that that radio show with me
Band and all country
And I get a kick out of that cuz it's like how dangerous am I right
This guy is kind of mainstream
Stoic
Looks like that was too much for them
They couldn't handle it
There's nothing I would love more than
Dog interrupting
I don't think that there's
I don't think anyone's band
All country
Not every country
More countries are very different standards
For what
He passes for accepted
Country has different laws
You like that yeah
For all the time like the first amendment and countries not called the United States
The Baseline
Okay alright interview with this guy
And like
Attack didn't work out a glitch
Something like that
He's trying to be polite or it was a shity interview
Omigod I tried to post it
Yeah I guess
Yeah that
Look at at detecting workout Rebecca
Look what are you in Luxemburg band you know you got to stop they don't even I don't even know what they do there
It's just such
It's just a couple of guys
Luxembourg
Garbage
YouTube
And YouTube says it's been banded all country
Noah
Okay what other streaming services
Spotify
Who gives a s***
Put it on Mike Adams real. Video never f****** b*******
Play still exist
Anyway all that stuff
Now we find out the Carrie is writing a book
Oh that's not a trouble in Paradise
And I'm also finding out that
Apparently my book is like coming in at like 700 Pages or something really crazy
I don't think
Okay something
Are there
Cix
Okay so anyway I just want to say that
Let me see if it looks like he is showing up
Hello
Cherry hi I'm so sorry
I was waiting for the reply
I wasn't sure if you were going to call or not I am here
It looks like for whatever it I can tell Carrie didn't send a reply
Confirm
She just assumed
Aaron went on air
So he calls
Bruce Lee it was most likely
She sent him a message
Do you want to do it at
And he was like
I mean I would probably
Say what's best for you
Shawty
Lack of confirmation in bed
Structure me to expect from
None of it surprises me
But the
She shares with
That is for sure
Alex like checking his phone on air
The play
Even the mix
Okay
This guy
Does he
Everything all right I don't even think
Make that he would make
I don't want to tell you anything I just wanted
Carrie is going to
Give him a little bit of
Introduction here that I can
Greg
So it's great to have you here let me just
You like a real brief
I got your introduction
Operate a Celestron
1400hd computerized 14 inch telescope
Optical to with DSLR and adapter
24 megapixel camera
3910 mm of Focalin
Asteroids planetoids unknown planets meteors
Planets Stars nebulas
Constellations Orion
Andromeda
Taurus Virgo Perseus
Wow you're very serious
Siri serious
Here's how I would
Got it
Videos of
It's a nice-looking telescope telescope I mean it's fine it's better than
Then like you're at your hobbyist
Do you have is a kid to look up at the stars
Is it a comically oversized telescope like you might find in a cartoon
The 70s
No it's right in the middle I will call it a middle-of-the-road but closer to
Impressive than
No I don't know if he has
I don't know what he knows exactly what he's doing with it
So okay so all we've got
Is a guy who has
The telescope
That's not enough
To get on
Project Campbell
There is enough to get on Project Camelot
Drive
He didn't
That would actually be pretty cool thing I would actually listen to
Interview
Where she's like
OK Google
Telescope
That would be interesting how things work
Not project
But look to your right
You're right
Imma call myself
Telescope is not enough
Michelle
Guys got a lot of other things going on
She sees all through this telephone
You understand more than that
You going to break some
Hoboken
So if you're able to bring the small photo
Keep it the same way it is but just
Bring it
This wife
You describe hands
Resuming enhance
Very small
Bending or the sorting and then you can see
Some people think that
Zoom
Are psychologists bigamy
It's all real photography
Very little filtering
Special objects
What are giving me a good hand
Honestly if
I don't know I think I'm not getting out there
So that people can see themselves you know what I have
Beautiful what
A whole bunch of movement
Different UFOs
I don't need to say they're all real if they are already
That's really you know
A lot of people don't realize that
That's actually in my opinion
Impressive
Stop is when you actually have a crap flying and you're capturing that
Gaunt
I would say
Watch some videos to show structures in motion on the moon
Like honestly a narration is crazy
Is it good
This is
Wow that's not good over and over again with like
Let's say
You know it's like I've found proof of x y and z
More like all those UFO guys has a picture and likewise
Stream
Cheating it in so much as like those people were creating fake UFOs
And like Forest
Perspective
Things like that he's cheating
Showing like a blurry pixel art on a picture that you've taken
You're going to get the distortion
And blurring of pixels
Right there
You could solve buddy
Which is why you know
Those really really big run by scientists yeah they don't they don't
No no
Anybody who studies astronomy at all would be able to look at his stuff
Like this is
What you doing
Misinterpreted
Studied
Yeah but you can't have those
Now I'm saying that anybody who has
Science
Astronomy would understand
And I said
Because
I must I must make clear
This guy has not
I don't
Backstory
Is not
Inspire confidence
Driving now I've rebranded as Bruce sees all
But not exactly
Continue what I want to do is
Forget you
To talk about how you got into this deal
Photography how you kind of got
That'll happen
Well I was
What do I do
Photography
Photos of people
That I was getting really good at it
I don't know it's weird
They're notoriously hard to photograph
Very weird
Weird way to phrase
It's almost like I am upset
At my stomach
It's almost
Because of course I have
Station and I'm still working there
So it's a regular job
Taking photos
And then I
1.2 make a long story short to jump into the
Never sold any really
And I got one star
I can say is that it was
Towards the constellation of Draco
Because you know people say where exactly is this
Never given indication
That's a bad sign
You said it like
You don't know where
Any stock
If you're if you're taking pictures where you're purporting to show like
Life in space
Some structures and stuff like that
It behooves you to be like
Here's where it is
You guys go confirm for yourself
It seems like
Maybe the most important
Also
Also even in his back stories like
Put things in angles to make it look
Populate photographs
Which is photography
No usually bring up when you're describing your backstory
Like reportedly supposed to reinforce that like I have hard evidence
Manipulating angles for art
Benefit
Blah blah blah
Some pictures of even a few kids
Probably frankly I would not be
Leads me to believe that he does not have
Astrophysics
Instead of being I work at a bus station in as a hobby pictures
Description of his life
About
Doing this I had a break
What about
No it didn't
Plowed ground here from YouTube
That's crazy levels of both
Right there is enough to be like
No sir
I will listen I will listen
They know where the star
I'm sure that it will be answered by the end of the episode by
I want to
To get this
From you
Does he believe what he's saying or is he
Is he where is he on her stupid evil continue
I would say both
But probably closer to scamming
GoFundMe page
So I don't know how lucrative
The nascent stages
I'd be hard-pressed to say that I don't think he also kind of believe
But it's easy to believe things when you don't
Understand
Like when you don't understand
How space works
You don't understand what you're looking at its really easy to assume that blurring of pixels looks a lot like a building
It must be a builder
Yeah when there's a really easy explanation
Just talked to anybody
Astronomer be like
Photography expert would be able to explain to you the blurring and
Devore thing of pickles at happens when you zoom too far telescope manufacturer
Be able to
Away pretty quick
So
Doesn't know where stars are
It's a little bit worse
In terms of the Assumption
Because you know people say where exactly is a
Star
I never give an indication honestly I don't know
Or could be very far away and is you it was very small
Uh-oh uh-oh
It could be two billion light years in the past
I'll tell you who knows
Astronomer
It sounds like you.
Probably them something
Really no write-up
Bruce sees all explain gravida cleansing
It is president
You know
It's really boring to read a bunch of texts there's a f****** City up there
Write me money
Do that much more gratifying than today
I don't know studying for 4 years
To get a degree and it dedicated your life
Working it out
Like I'd large
Telescope
That's not the people have
It's always fascinated
These these people who are
Essentially hard sci-fi
Boulevard
Hard
They struggle to avoid
Learning anything about what it is they're talking about
The strict adherence to rules
Fanciful
Neil deGrasse Tyson
The house wouldn't have flown like
Close to the border of
Do you like we won't talk about them on the show
You know that that sort of Project Camelot line like
Is this person
Okay
Haha very close to the line but he's on the right side of it
Talk about
I don't think that he's so mentally unwell
And he's on the other side of it
End of episode
No no no no
Star is because big
Small and far
Vice-versa whatever
A really did a great job of explaining perspective
Photographer would do
So now hold on that clip isn't done
It gets weirder
Some surface structure
Very different to the Moon surface
Was constructed
It does look chiseled
Ancient structures that we see here on
The way they talk about the Egyptians
Civilization
On another
Just chiseled out surface in certain areas
There is
Literally no way
Good no matter what kind of Zoom is guys got
You could find some looks chiseled out
Like
Jordans Jordans
There was a service structure on a star
Okay that's a lot of structure and determine
The masonry of it
From his telescope
Is cockamamie bulshit
Implore anyone to go watch any of his videos
The idea that he could tell about the sort of
Technique of the building is all in his imagination
He's just making all that up
Sanitary water
Gotcha
Two dudes
Is this is wild stuff
He also says that I got theirs
Lush vegetation on the moon
There's a lot of colors
Alright understand is it like often times
Space
Of the Moon
But if you take a picture of the moon
From planet Earth
Oftentimes you'll see a little bit of coloration
Intuit you'll see there's like a little bit more
Strict whiteness or even some
Yellowing
That sort of phenomenon and the reason for that is Earth's atmosphere
A picture
Through Earth's atmosphere
Looks different than taking picture from like the Hubble telescope which is outside of a bingo baby
I don't understand how that could affect
What if it's just really really close in Earth's atmosphere
He's also said that he likes to take things
You just did that new forgot that's why you think there's vegetation
There is are
Alright
Not enough
I mean that not enough for you
Lush vegetation
Whatever his
Now I want to say that I don't think
G Spot astronomy is strong
Not great I would save
The indication
I don't know how far away this thing is it could be
Fart
Small enclosed
That leads me to believe that he's not wrestled with the actual work
But this next quickly
Believe
That this guy
He is into cutting Corners when it comes to physics
Can you ask do you have any idea how big
Example
Dimensions of the dimensions of the crop
And then the structures can you even is there even any way to estimate
Maybe seem silly but it seems to me the most
Logical weight
Confirm something using the eye
Compared to the size of the creators
I'll take a very small
Equator
Any frames that I will find the small UFO
So
Phuket
Scuse me sir
Well he isn't Canada I believe so you might be on the kilometer
Conversion
Help carry out
Now the first problem that I would say
With this
Technique of judging with craters
Is the exact same thing she's already brought up
What if that's far away from the crater
How are you touching the sizes of the crater that I decide to the pixel dammit
It makes perfect sense
Doesn't work
To use like to know how big one of these craters
First of all
That's the problem
The vet
I just I think you just like this
The f****** 3-mile spaceship
Buddy
Joy
School
I mean
Tragically
Flawed thinking
Google how large
Craters on the moon are and people have courses you can
See if that was the crater that you were looking at now here here's where things get real bad
For Bruce
Is the
If he did do that
Take those measure
And we
Just for fun
Spaceships on tape
And he does take that
You know whatever measurement is made of the spaceship
Can put it into the
The crater that he have the measurement of
The prospective problem is still a problem
Confirm where that spaceship was
Unless
On the ground
In what is much as it is buggy
You can't do this
But you can't do that cuz even if it's a mile off the grappler
It's going to completely fuk up your measurements your equations are bunk
Literally
Could be
In the exact middle
Distance between where the Earth is in and it would look to you taking a
Picture as it might have been asked
3 miles
According to that
Because it's halfway between the Earth and the only I don't know
60 ft Black it's a pleasure yacht
Horoscope
Spacecraft
I mean look I watch these videos
Get into why others
But
What's more important is
Just thinking that we're seeing demonstrate at
The lack of him even
Like realizing
Huh that could be a problem
For my equation
Play ideas
The
Supposed UFO isn't on the ground
Am I going to get around that he's just like
Oh no
Structure on the
Assume everything is grounded
I'm sure that makes sense yeah
No one knows where that might have been us.
Where
The stars are everywhere always
I will never
Maybe I do
I don't understand that
Reaction
So many people have
Anybody who spent
Entire life
Studying stuff
Like just
La Quinta Inn
Like there are people who started out as like
90 rolls
Literally fascinated by all the stuff they go through school they're their brilliant than they go to college
They tell you all of this stuff
They're brilliant and then they spend the next 20 to 30 years of their life
Building these vaccines in order to save lives and there are a bunch of people are just like
F*** you you don't know a goddamn thing
Like what are you
They're doing it for
It's a really boring thing to do like the human in
That you have to like
Want to make your mark on ship
Is not going to be satisfied by Ray
They're trying to do
Parallel between the worlds of Alex
The project
Black people
It is very similar thinking that these people have with
Inasmuch
They don't look at it that way
They don't look at it as someone has dedicated their life
Studying this stuff and they know more than me
Just because I
Angry and Watson
You know scam people out of there
They don't look at it that way they look at it like
These people got it with probably good intent
Team sucked into the nefarious globalist
So like with the vaccine it's like
Corrupted by big Pharma and you know that took over
You know what they were about
All shity
And NASA is doing the big cover-up and now they're apart
Track if you ever
Any kind
Make
Send snow
No put it it does make sense
If you're looking for a convenient
Easy way to explain
The not explaining
Why is everyone disagreeing with
Yeah
You know
You can't
Cannot
Certain level of trust
Just another human being
Unless unless those people implicitly agree with whatever world
Internet why Carrie gets sucked in by people like
I-80
Because he reinforces
The worldview that she's already
By guest all the time
Robert David Steele on
He was reinforcing Alex
His worldview until he came on and said that their children
And that's when Alex Bruce has
Photograph some of those
But even that
Person that they can
Can ever truly trust
Is themself
The only people that believe you are extension
That's such a bummer man engaged with the rest of the human race
But
This guy was putting the stuff out into the world video
I believe that these are structures
I could be wrong and you know I just want to put this out there
Start a conversation
I wouldn't laugh at him
No I wouldn't treat him like a dick I would be open to the
The possibilities that
What you're seeing isn't
What you think it is
Victor
Booty is what makes
It's funny because the certainty implies
You're trying to pull
You and I can only experience.
You know what I mean like you and I are both
I don't agree with you
So many of these
Well is that you and I are
Default
At the death position
Like is like
There's no way that my first reaction
Or even
Action is the correct
Bro I need to
To make sure and double check
Chinese people don't have that at all that's why this guy I'll maybe make 8500
Hundred dollars into GoFundMe but
No one will know who he is
His wife
Still working at that bus
Ouch
Taking pictures of the moon
And children
I can't get that out of my head
Because this next clip scares me a little bit
I'm trying to figure out
How much harassment do you get
You know in terms of what you're doing are you doing today
Harassment
What real quick you said
II
I need to start that back a little
Because I listen to
Quite figure
Spider-Man and Black
Or if you saying
The idea that I've been harassed by the Men in Black isn't
Tru Hotel
HD has been harassed
Men In Black Vincent D'Onofrio is a little bit upsetting
Vincent D'Onofrio
With the heroes
Listen I want to I want you to track this is Chloe please okay
I'm not sure
What is Elijah
What you're doing are you
Could tell you that I've been raised by the Men in Black but it's not true
Credit
That's that's what he said
Threw me the first time of her death
I could tell you that I've been harassed by the Men in Black
Very honest, I could tell you
The phrasing is a little bit,
Located
Especially for a Project Camelot gas
Yeah I'm okay with
Black
Control tell you that I'm upset
My stomach but my stomach is
Right
France but honestly
Seems really
More nasty and vindictive and try to scare me and
Do something worse than you and I'll play with them
To see how they react
Because honestly
People that are doing this for real
I've seen some story
They say 6 words
Tubalcain
I don't know what those two
Maybe I'm going to
To kill you I am
Right very weird
I don't know what you're talkin about freaked me the f*** out
What's one of these what's the acrostics for the solar system
You know like my very I don't want to say mine
Yeah it was my very erotic
Reminder nasty pillows
Now that's why they're crossed
I don't think so
I believe it is
Because you can put them
The reason that they
No to tell you only
Is because there are really
Write 6 words
Dude it's like D12
There's only six 12 there's six members
Dirigo
There's twelve planets including
He doesn't Alter Ego planet
So Jordan
I don't like the idea that he saying
People threaten
Because
No
From looking at these
Finality type
Ovarian pain feel like they're being threatened when they're not
Running me respond to
Critique
As threats
Which is why I would like to bring everyone
Listen to website called flat-earth lunacy.
To the website that
Takes people to make flat Earth arguments and
Brake sound like
Bulshit is a lot of other astronomy related
Stuff on there
And they did a little bit of looking into Bruce sees all
Right
Very critical
Really believe that Bruce
Diesel
Could be a name
It's like I really haven't really have a hard time pulling with
Bruce
Lego
It's not though
You got wind of
The facts
Made this page
His work
Aggressive
You like posting my stuff huh
You'll have this nice little note tabs your childish website
Everyone knows you're a jealous.
Creator that has no education whatsoever LOL LOL
You guys want to be the top and it ain't about me
It's about exposing what is true
You're part of the light open
Your
But what I
Hey you think your edges
George
My next video will send a flood of haters
I have more than you 100 views a day here LOL LOL
What's the matter of the website and working for you
What's the matter
What's the matter what's the matter
What's not what's the matter what's the matter with what's the matter with you
Yeah you should be all over the news LOL LOL
This is a week
We
PK and website
For your family it appears
These posts against me
Community that I have stirred up a few brainless wonders to the reality of it all
The fact that everything you said about me was a lie
Therefore this post will be taken down
My business will not be attacked by you
You will have brought many troubles your way
I will be watching what you
It's post but it's spelled p Open Bracket OTs
Ethiopian bread
Alright
I'm sure it was supposed to be
Better hear from Mike buddy
Mike ain't so friendly
Tell me a co-worker the bus station
Yeah I didn't realize he was running that kind of operation
The kind of response that he gives out with someone
Critique the possibility that he's not doing due diligence
Astronomy assumptions
Disguises
Skype little bit aggressive
Little Acro
Question the intelligence
People debunk
Kingdom muzic
Austin route
Veal
Via their question
They are not themselves
Don't have a good grasp
You guys think you're so smart
And
You misspelled everything anthro brackets
In the wrong place is like
Guide
It's like hey
I get it that you're angry
But come on
Doolittle double-check spell check your writing an email you got time it's not like you're on the phone but you know what to do
Be it also is an indication of lack of
Trust
And your own
Like that that sort of behaviour to me really indicates the
Bruce himself knows what he's putting out at
Yeah you know when silkies just like
Better attack
Otherwise I'm not going to be able to stand up my marriage
We just a weird distorted
The city
I don't I am worried about this guy and I hope
Attacks us
Weird
What is the difference between that guy and like
The Daily Caller
It's just proofreading
Yeah like Daily Caller has all of the same insults towards disagree with that but they
Just proofread for some reason a huge section of the population
Don't know if this guy is really into white
Or anything
I don't really proud
I don't really know his business
Maybe we'll find a way
We will find a way
Next clip
Carrie
Has a very hard question
Bruce
And that is
First of all I want to understand weather
You stink
That you have ever photograph being
Interesting question
Possibility
I don't think people understand what I mean by being
I'm not seem right now
Anything with
Play shoulders and legs
I'm seeing things right
Or that not debris
It looks like they're moving themselves
Use photographic
The glow cloud
Photograph
There is not
But
Halo
Phenomenon of
End up being
Caught in space like we talked about with the coloration of things
Space often being affected by
You know just the earth atmosphere
Consideration
Cuz even if you're using
Telescope
Clouds
You know you can't see through
Footage of something
Appears to have clouds on the moon
Very high
Spirit
Cloud-like up really high in the troposphere or whatever
I don't remember the exact
Heaven I don't really remember the
BMX
Why is ended up taking pictures of
You know
Clouds
Alive
That leads me to
To believe that
PDF picture
Accidentally captured
Something like
High-level Cirrus
Cloud
EZ's captured that
And is misunderstanding
That's kind of what I'm guessing he made the classic rookie
Mistake of a guy with a telescope
You can only see
The space
You can only speak
She's facing when it's
Right
Descendants
If you watch his videos
To be light
Stuff like that
NoHo
Lake reflection
No it's not it's not
You're not actually seeing like a luminescent bulb
On the moon
Crazy would that be if that's what you could see from your telescope
You're looking at the moon and you see someone like turn on their porch light
Like that
Tell you where the stars are
There's no
Champs
Love you
No matter how powerful telescope that you have
That you could look at the Moon and
Elite
Phonics
It would have to be
Indivisible to your telescope
The reality is that appear to be light
It might be a piece
Flex paste
Or something like that reflecting light or any number of possible explanations
So I don't know all of them
I know there are plenty of
In the classic pale blue.
You see a lot of s*** up
Not not living
All those lights
Glow cloud
Also Florence
I didn't have the
I didn't have
The nerve to watch Carrie
Is two-part interview about that hurricane
Knock knock
Involves weather
Yeah I know
I decided I'm out I'm out on that one
A really f***** up for a long time because
Tomorrow
In this next
How do I how do I
He's just about any
I guess I guess what I would say is
He's trying to
Express
Again
He seems
Fascinated by the idea of
Resume
The ability to zoom on a camera seems like almost
The more I zoom in
The more I see
What people are talking about the hologram
And it's scary
Michigan looking at a corner
Spring or something
Moving
Unfortunately
3000 Geary
You'll never see a mosquito
You will never like this in the window
Would be this stressed out
A blur
You're arguing against criticism buddy
That's not that's not a
Legitimate
Yeah usually
I don't know man
I'm not sure
Exactly what point you're trying to make with the hologram
Business
But I do know that some of these other people like
Somebody's other weirdos
Makerspace Carrie cast
Kind of world
They do speculate there's like a hologram.
Going on
Allow you to
To see what's actually going on on the moon
That's okay
More like if you zoom in
Far enough on
Can see that the entire universe
Now that's interesting I might be what he said I don't know
We just have to you and I are left you're guessing
Cuz episode I don't know
I can't I can't answer that question
Before you
Like I don't have more prior contacts
It's going to help fair enough
But I can tell you this
At a certain point became an incredibly boring
This was one of the rare times that I almost fell asleep
I'm so interested in
Is the kernel of it
Yeah
After the episodes of hour and a half
Stretches
That's a long time for an episode interview
Interviewing your guy
With a telescope
You guys have telescopes
Confirm
You might be asking yourself to work
To the bus station
Does working
Interpret ography lights
She dangles
We know that he said he started taking pictures of a star that had no idea where it is
But it's not
What is assertive
Story end
Facebook
How long have you been doing
This is my second year completed
I couldn't even get you an Associates
Treated my second year of research
I've never done this before
I was very interested in the New World Order
Oh no
Super fly into something it was involved with the government
The secret project
So everything I'm researching now is only from what I'm finding
I'm researching in debt
A lot of
The space program
What's an estate program
Maybe there's some similarities
It could be that I'm finding some
Faraway evidence
Maybe the state program
So I started looking at looking at things I don't
And then
Went to the people who do
Stand up and I was like
Who don't understand them
At all
And I decided to
The secret
Bridgeway program
This is
I started to get into the Illuminati
Alright alright
Okay we're always going to get there soon
Sooner or later I'm being forthcoming with that information
So we got one more clip of this dude
Bruce
Bezel
Versus Ali
I have
Vindicated
A couple things
Lead me to believe that this guy is
Is not popping up
In terms of like
Bunny perspective
Is the biggest
More exam
Oprah for you
Video how about that
But this next clip
Is
Deeply troubling
Unjustly
Understanding reality
What kind of bass
Actually maybe
Just because not because it's those shocking
You to understand what you say
Well if you're having some really odd things going on
I guess it also has to do with maybe the actress that were
We're shifting
The sphere on Earth because
The moon does not appear to be in the same place that you
Now I'm wondering
Maybe
Maybe the moon hasn't moved
This is just an assumption
Is rocking back and forth
Look at the Moon
We're both moving
Universe around us
Going like this
Everything's
Spinning around
But just before it stopped
Really really really really fast
And I often say to myself
Going to be
8020 years 10 years
Hoo-boy
The universe was moving
When did you learn first
Bea Arthur
Second moon was moving around the earth making them both moves
Ray-Ban pattern
Both of them also orbiting the Sun
The sun itself which orbits around the supermassive black hole at the center of our galaxy
The Galaxy itself which is expanding as part of the University
Expanding
Magic or whatever it is the universe is always
What is the universe
What is going on
Cuz that a prerequisite class today after all that much
Broad stroke
Moving and not just
Chilling out
I got
Physics class
Doctor mushroom but I'm not entirely sure
A professor
Headed that sounded a lot like doctor mushroom
Dr. Bruce mushrooms all not care to find out what his real name is but I'm sure
Background
To know that it was that doctor mushroom
Teach me about space
Dog doo-doo
Beyond real
Did he just
Maybe the universe is moving you have to ask yourself what is the dichotomy that's being presented by Carrie
And what day is it
Are you saying
Now if that were the case
Disaster
The tides
Would be completely
Devastator
No
Had not moved
Oh yeah that took time out Jordan
Timeout because the moon not moving is the equivalent of the Moon movie
The Moon
Moving
In her what she's saying is the moon is moving in a way that is not what we would expect
Alright
Expected to be based on our calculations
Feel like his response is more similar to
Yes yes
But that's better
Is equally troubling
Devastating consequences for the solar system
A complete
Everything would be screwed
Either these possibilities were the case
Weed Trucking know it by now
For sure
Is the confidence that it take
Fly in the face of every
Brilliant group of people who have ever studied this
Ever
Really astonishing
Disproven
Calm down man
Equal of like Pliny the Elder
4000 years after
Pliny the Elder
It's not a good look
So this is where we leave Bruce
Sparks up another bowl or whatever
Real introspective
Right
What if it's not the week
Burning butt
I am the one that's all right
So he leave
F******
Fortunate posts
From Carrie
She doesn't have the episode
I don't know exactly
I think maybe because she felt good about starting episode without a gas
And maybe she's like
Maybe a little bit
Unfortunately
She reveals that things are not
I am trying to raise money to go see Captain Mark Richards again and do an interview
And this is a great time for me to do that interview so much is happening
I want to run a lot of Eddie's information by him see how he sees it and
See what he's up to and what he understands about was coming
He's in prison
In the future here on planet Earth perspective
From
But only because of the
Actors who he's in touch with as well
So that's a very worthwhile Enterprise if you can
Donate
Camelot
You just go to my website Project Camelot. TV and click on the Donate fat
And then it gives you several ways to donate
If you just want to send money to my email address
You can do it that way
But I'm not mad at her for asking for money
Support
But you.
New model that should be successful
Universal
But I do think even with universal basic
Drinking with your dad and everyone should have the right to housing
I do think that a
The successful model 4 in
Entertainment
And that sort of thing is
Do you like this thing
Give them a couple boxes
Enter subscription format
That allows them
To be able to create the things that you like
Which is what they like
I don't think there's a
Really don't and I even though I think Carrie is
Unfortunately
Pushing a lot of really dangerous stuff into the world
Weather
Eddie page saying that racism is totally cool
Or lot of these people who are
Hypothetical alien
Being
Weirdly into Russia also
Happened
Dangerous
Flippancy in
Anti-science
Yak that was sort of thing
I hate it but I
I'm not going to be mad at her being like
Did you like what I do please support it
I am going to say
Hey
What does it cost to go visit someone in prison
He's money
The book of flight it doesn't take off like she live in California
Prison you can drive there
California roll La I don't know exactly
At most I've driven down the California coast
At most like
At most
Maybe cost something to have a hotel ghetto f****** Motel 6
60 bucks for the night or whatever
The way she's framing it
Is gross
Because if it is like
Hey if you want me to go and
Do this as a
The bonus
You can support that
That kind of feels better but the idea of like
I need money to do this
Is gross because it doesn't
It doesn't cost
Much
Call Tatanka gas
And maybe a cheap hotel
He is a guy in prison
Now on the other hand
The other hand is this
I think that there's a possibility
Mark is charging her
How to do interviews
I don't
There's a bunny
Interviewing him isn't
She needs to put something in his commissary
In order for him to agree to do an interview
So maybe there is
It's absolutely
Illegal
What could it be
Charging
Like what is he charged us $500 in his commissary
Very easy to do it
It's a version of extortion
The people in prison
I do not know
Oh absolutely I apologize for not having enough
Present but not ones that I visit
Prison wanted
Will do is extort other other prisoners
To get them to get their loved one
To put money
Commissary
The threat that they will hurt
If they don't do it surprising economy within prison
There's a documentary that Lewis the road
I believe it was about
Are you stalking
I still think about very
Very happy
There's this guy
Mentality
The game ain't based on
Which is the idea that like I will extort you
I will do everything
I don't give a s*** about you
Humanity
Sympathy doesn't come into
So
I don't necessarily think that Mark Richards is
Shaking down people or anything like
But he's got a fish on the line
Gary is his being able to be like I will tell you more about this
Secret space program
If you give me money
Right cuz I need that to do all my need to get toilet
Hey
The Conners
That there might be more going on
On here then
Then is
Which somehow
Makes
The only rational actor in the
This entire situation
Well yeah
I mean it's horrible
Reasonable
We've opted
He said that he's just like he's a board dude but it makes way more sense for him to be like
Yeah I'll do an interview where I'll say all kinds of crazy s*** to you for
Yeah that makes perfect
So that clip kind of brought that thought
Into my mind
Which is interest
It certainly it certainly in line with a lot of these
Starting to find out about
The guests on
Jim Bakker Show
Understanding Baker 5000 books
Exactly
And I believe that there's certain Arrangements
It's like that with Alex
I do think
There are similar
Things going on
With Alex's
Consignment
Yeah so I think there is
A much more
Nuanced economy behind the program
Now unfortunate
Well the reason that we don't really understand these
Economies is
Don't do that no
For the insurance
8 interest of putting on a good Publix did that and then
The first thing we say Talega anybody that we interview
Hey we bought five thousand of this guy's book we hope you guys buy we're going to mark it up in order to
Get our cut of the profit
That's why I had to cut out 10 minutes
Mike Kaplan interview
Micro going to sell your seat
Yeah
Gets worse
Because
Thing else that leads
Me to believe that
Again
All is not well
Basically we just
You do need money
To operate
Wasn't able to pay my Webster last week
Actually really down and out financially
Because
Over the summer
So I laid out on a bunch of
Credit cards
Travelan
You can help out you know even a little bit helps
Appreciate it
Carrie's falling in
Into debt carry
Carrie
Do you remember when you got
Scammed by that guy
To the tune of hundreds of thousands of dollars
Sean David Morton
It wasn't it wasn't his fault
This is why
I don't want to
I don't want to be the guy who says
You got this
I do know that money that you didn't have
This summer
Cuz you didn't pay your taxes
She was posting about how she needed a bunch of money because you owed
Backpacks I did not remember what happened
After tax season what
It's tragic I feel bad about it but this is
This all makes sense
Advertising
Amitriptyline
No she will take people and show them around Egypt
$50
Around Egypt
Flight not included
To get to EJ
Critics
Right
I don't know flight
You're not
Dog
I'm in the belly of the plane
That's why
78 hunt
$3,550
Other than bracket
Discover because
She's assuming that you'll be in a hotel
We got to pay for your other
I think
It's unclear from the
Itinerary
Kind of unclear I'm not entirely sure
What's it called amenities not include Star cruise
I like a four-day 5-star Cruise right that might be worth 35
Problem
Anyway
This is
But I also.
Because
Mayonnaise
Where is the people that we regularly cover
Broke
Alex Alex Alex is a multi-level marketing guy areas
In debt now she's at she had to put
Traveling on her credit card
Right
We've one more clip
Mayfield much less pay
Got some other shows coming up I am
Still inviting
Isaac
Happy to come on the show at tomorrow
Talking about pedophilia in Hollywood
And
You know so
It will be great when he gets around to coming on the show
Isaac Kappy the guy who said it's for real
The guy who said that you wanted to talk to him about chicken
And that means that he's a pedophile
Yep. Who was on Alex Jones Isaac Kappy
Project
Do to be like have a conference do they hang out
Images of producer of Project Camelot like
I apologize I forgot to bring this up in that last what she was talking about her webmaster not being able to pay him
The last time we did an episode about Eddie page
On that episode
She's talking about how her webmaster disappeared
And that you needed to get a replacement
Webmaster
And she does not talk about it in the context of I couldn't pay him
Webmaster disappearing is probably
Man tried to come down on you
And she was like
Yeah probably
So she was presenting it as a thing was like yeah
Program or whatever
She would call it
It turns out very concrete. You didn't want to work
There's a concrete explanation
For everything that you
You claiming some
A jack
The same way that you would like
Weird cyber weapon coming at me
You had Bell's palsy
Stop with this b*******
I understand
How to make money
When you're doing something
I get that
Empathetic
Yeah
How blind you cannot have Isaac Kappy on your f****** show
Minimizing of pedophilia
He's a failed
F*** you
He's acting like he's a witch
He's a badass
He's a bad face Act
The bad
Actor
Good enough to get on that Project Camelot and
Alex Jones
Is that what it's called
I wonder if he could Rebrand
It said you like I did
Yummy already called the show the final Edition
Slayer to it book
6 kids
Probably aliens
Got to talk to Alex
Results
So Jordan This brings us to the end of this
Respond for me on a number of lava
Because this guy
He's not even
Crazy in like crazy
He's just bad
He just doesn't know what he's talking about and is managed to trick
Couple hundred people and I give him enough credibility to come on
Program
And even say anything
Two offensive
To her worldviews that goes along with it quite well
But
I would argue that at the end of this podcast
Squarely on the stupid
The end of the
You stupid
That's kind of a bunch of stupid kind of dumb
Expressions
Rotary
Letter like the Unabomber with a series of steps
That you would
Takes that's a different story than a guy who
It might as well be
Or liberal or like to be found personal information
Yeah I just blow their
Studio a whatever
Without any evidence
Early I think
Perspective
Absolutely
Make me on your siding
He's calling man for sure but maybe not as robust
Career of
But I think I've used
Yeah I was terrible stand-up when I was only
Holyshit
Text Julian have a couple minutes onstage it's it's
Two years I'm still 3 years away from me
Good speaking as this episode comes out
I'll be there for tonight
Until Sunday Sunnyvale policy wonks want to come out and check out the show they should.
In the backyard
Not hard
We do to find us on the Twitter
Okay
Now we only do one Social Network I assumed right there's no other
Network that were on right big news for you
We are also
I've been on there for a while
The page that's great
Leave a review on the page we would appreciate
The f****** pile of s***
They changed everything up
We had a bunch of reviews on our Facebook page
Something
All five stars
A two assholes
Bitterly posted one star
Collection of things
And now Facebook has changed it
Recommendation
You don't leave Stars anymore you just
Would you recommend this to your
Your friend
If you know that if you click
I was going to post it on your page
So nevermind
Don't even do that just join the group
Facebook anymore so I like to lurk in there just like as a random
Enter so it's fun as run
Through the Pokemon go
Left out
Don't feel left out
When the original thread happened I tried that everybody so far
Richard's place
Damn
You know
There's just one thing that's been in the back
Which is that
Bruce sees all
Should have seen at
One thing
Did the
That is
Describe tall
Yeah we're here
Number things
Certainly
That would be really important
Right
Me making eggs
Are you sure that's one of the things
Another thing
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color