Alexandra Thurston color
Congratulations
Alright
Comedian time to talk about
There's a show where we don't talk about that we talked about Alex
And I also know that it looks like a big deal
Yeah
We got we got some
Fun to go over today we got some
Light not fun to go over today
Recording this during the day which is uncommon beak
Because you are at Rosemont
It comes out on Friday
You go check out Jordans.
Still time
Saturday night available
Sunday
I know there's a reason that you're out of butter
I remember that being no no I didn't butter sandwich
Some food but
I panicked
The corner store I bought a bag of chips
You panic
I don't know what that means in the context of
What are the trademarks
Very can
Whenever I'm going to shopping
Lendup overwhelmed by choice
People looking at me shopping or anything like that but I will Panic about the idea
Like if I think about this more I will be here for an hour almost always
You're always dealing with the cereal aisle conundrum
I want to go get a candy
From the grocery store
I went down there and they were out of the Haribo Gummy Bears
Chuy's
Send a text
Are there out of those
Milk Duds
Dafuq I don't want
Whoppers
And then I saw a brightly colored bag of Twizzler
Terrible I accidentally grabbed him and this happens to me all the time
Close food
No need to go down this road any further
Jordan
A iPhone to do
Covered with
The Reese's outrageous
Is an overload of flavor
Wait
I don't feel great about
Is our new donor
Appreciate it very much
First of all I'd like to say
Connor you are now
I'm a policy wonk
McDonald's
Experience
Going to be up there for a while
Adele
DOTA spider
I'm a policy wonk
Think about all right
Is that like a spider that like soda that is made of soda
Do you like it
I don't like spiders
But I'll take a soda Minnesota spider
Higher level
I'd like to thank you so much
You are now
Technocrat
Someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
All of you oh so very much the show
We are making good progress towards having to do another.
10% of the way there guys end up having to put a pull-up on
Facebook group called Oklahoma
Also I'd like to give a little bit of a shout-out I guess
To the behind the bastards podcast
Nice of them to
I wish they would have gotten in touch with us
Quite frankly
Because there are little things that could have really
Help put things into
Contacts like
Sprint
Listen to the latest episode
And they mentioned that the
They mentioned the Human Resources Director of Infowars
But don't mention that it's Alex Jones's dad
They don't mention that it's right
Throughout
That's true. You know
Not notice that oh my God
Hey this is stuff like that I think they did a fine job but it's
The same time I think
We could have really
Beefed-up summer
But oh well
Such as life anyway
Thanks for the shout-out weepers
Absolutely
I work and I'm sounding Petty and I don't mean today I don't mean to I promise I don't mean to be
What are those details
How could you expect even if you are reading over it and you're like
Why would you think that it's his dad
Louisiana
Already have some inclination that like
Probably connection
And you look a little bit into it you find oh David Jones
Does that own Castle Dental
Houston suspiciously have the same address for Infowars
Dental office
Anyway
Glock we got some
Business Jordan
LeBron James
That's the order of
What are rainbow colors
Very very charismatic
Although as
Some of our friends
Testarossa
Disabled
Which was done by
Beer
And I can't remember I think LL Cool J
They were the monstars
It is crazy yeah there's a music video for it
That's really hot
Together
Do you like DMX might be on that song too.
Crazy lineup
Also
Redman might only appear in the video I think Method Man the only one actually rapping
That's the best part of Space Jam
I pissed off at everyone like that are Kelly song cuz monstars Anthem is better
Alright
That's another issue
They make
0 rapper
Space Jam Basketball Jones
Whataburger
For sure had basketball jobs on there
Let's stop.
No over March 6th through 8th
We cannot record during the day
Blade Runner
We talked about on the last episode from 2009 we talked about Alex Jones
Which was that avian flu released
85in
Brett Alex made a big deal out of this
Actually mainstream Czechoslovakian
Sorry Czech Republic news
And we predicted very strong
You going to keep talking about this
For a long time
The way he was describing his
It reaction to the news I thought he had the flu
I was pretty sure about that
So
I was not surprised at all when I opened up a March
Episode
Jason bermas was hosting
Alex had to take a sick day
I'm almost certain type of flu
You talkin about
Sweating room spinning he was upset his stomach
He doesn't show up for work the next day obviously of the bug
Well it's nice to have confirmation
Nothing but circumstantial evidence
Awesome
March 8th comes around
It's the Sunday as well Friday off.
Saturday off
Absolutely
They reached
Until we get to the 8th
Is in a very
Strange
Play
He may have he wants to talk a lot about guns
To talk about them
Plus the oppressive
Why is that
From
Do you think it's only goes on to places like Boston
The Massachusetts store out in places like Connecticut
Those are your people
And a half
There's no law but they still go to prison
Now you're saying how does that happen well people going to prison all the time
GameStop
You can watch the court case, not
Chucky men there
I tried to put him in prison and the jury said not guilty
They said it was on their own
Video footage around the country that their freedom is Terrorism
I'm not joking when I say
So that we already talked about a little bit that idea
Founding fathers were terrorists
If you look at it objectively mean
I wanted to reinforce
Talk about that
He has this you get arrested with an arsenal of guns in your car
Victoria's going to
Come up later
We use that as a
The jump-off talked about you get arrested
For not taking vaccine
Then he tries to pull a specific
Example of that
Come up with this
Kelly Russia
Who got arrested for handing out copies of Alec
Spell was the DVD
Material the crime
Or some other crime may have occurred
Arrested for him to go to Infowars
If you was discharged
Good terrorism arrested for that
In reality I'm going to reach you from the Kentucky police
Press release
Investigators with the Kentucky State Police are attempting to deal with a flood of calls coming in to post
After Kentucky State Police in vest
Navigation was discussed
On December 15th 2003
.
Arrested fifty-three-year-old Kelly rushing of Fredonia Kentucky
On charges of menacing and terroristic threat
Russians accused of placing anti-government propaganda in the mailbox.
Radio talk show host Alex Jones discussed the Russian caisson
Radio show which aired on today's date
After the show was over post one received more than 50
Recalls for people airing
Their concerns with
The calls ended up tying up emergency dispatch personnel and phone lines that are normally used for regular police
Most of the calls were from people living in the Midwest
Amber Westco
So
He ended up inconveniencing
The emergency response system
In Kentucky
Alex Jones directly responsible for that lying about the situation
This guy
With meddling with people's mailboxes
Federal mailboxes
Really you know that.
No
No it's just the Box
Mailbox is technically considered property of the federal government
Or whatever
So you can't interfere with the like
Distribution
Collection of
Because
Just leave a bomb in
Mailbox
There are reasons for these laws being in place
So this Trooper
Did Kelly Russian guy leave
This propaganda
Which is a crime
That's it's not like he's standing out
The middle of Lake public spaces
Okay it's a crime
Now that Alex wanted to say it shouldn't be a crime to put things in someone's mailbox that they don't want in their mailbox
Have that conversation
It's a different conversation
You can have it
Except
You're damn right
Also I don't believe Alex actually
Possibly pretty illegal
Advanced that sparked a communication and it works
It could be seen as trying
Call him at home
No
I don't think you should do that
Intimidation
Then that's illegal
If it ex-parte communication it could
Influence
The judge
To go against
Kelly Rush
And the case is like
These people are trying to
The metal with the case
Probably on his behalf
So it is
I don't think
He did it but if you did it's one of the stupidest
Things you could do in a
Alex is gone
And a bunch of people who are nowhere near
Fredonia
Kentucky
Call Mike 911 over and over and over again
Called Airline
Hey this is evil right and then like a cup
For the people
Maybe
I don't know the stats on that
Beginning of that clip he's bringing up this idea if you get arrested again Arsenal in your car and what have you
11 Arsenal are going
I think that's okay
2D
Introduction of that
Exactly talk about it already
Here's a
Police Arsenal found
Ahead of a wedding
Police pulling over
4 rifles and they freaked out and flipped out and
They were all legal
Charging
So that's
Details before I get into the specifics
I would let Alex hang himself a little more in
Text Clara
Yeah I don't know if you had a thought
I don't like
Shooting rifles ahead of a
The wedding is like
His ex-girlfriend
You got to suck it up a little bit
In terms of that cuz it's not
Anything wrong with that
If it makes you uncomfortable
Timmy is a weird thing to do
Here it is next web
You're right to be a little bit.
Your you're
You're sort of the vibe
Sensor is going off
Getting a bad vibe
Wayward Son
Can I see the stories everyday when normally is preceded by
Insurance salesman
I thought you were going to go with
The police
Ohio
Person up over and over again why my producers these people
It's got the point I don't even call
People up anymore
But you know what let's do it again
The gentleman
Luke
Who's Inga
I was on his way to a wedding in May
Semi-automatic shotgun
Why he had some knives all my gosh I don't like animatronics shows the pocket knives
He was going
So Alex is going to reach out and help us
Huisinga
This is another bad case for Alex to be rallying behind
Yeah Alex tell if his innocent kid with four semiotic rifles is getting pulled over by police
No reason to pull over
And if you're pulled over because of the Cross Lanes
Just Behavior
When the police
Responses to questions
And being that it was 12:20 in the morning
That could be an indication of impairment or worse
They haven't get out of the truck and patted him turned up bullets
So they searched his truck
They did not find for
They got a rifle with a night scope at Edwards 12
12-gauge shotgun high-capacity magazines
5 knives brass knuckles in a bulletproof vest
With armor plate
His mother was quoted in the paper as saying that he was quote a sportsman miliar with guns
Perhaps a little too much that's what his mama said
So
What position of most Firearms is not illegal magazines
It's usually a really bad
Knuckles are super useful against
The deer we all learn from
Generally okay
And we all learn from the case of OD
Illegal to have a bulletproof vest
Because
You know it implies that you may find your way into us
Situation
Lake
Go shoot some people
Oh and also he was transporting these guns across state line
So even if they're perfectly legal now they're not
Right
The kids from Danbury
He got arrested in Mass
Massachusetts
So you were across multiple state lines
With all of these gun even if they're registered
Connecticut
You can't carry on Arsenal across state lines
Without a good reason
Shooting with your buddies before wedding is not a good reason
Pennywise
It's easy to hear a story like this
Have some empathy
He's 18 years old
This could easily be a misunderstanding on the part of the kid
Who Loved too much it doesn't realize that he's headed down and anti-social pass
You think maybe this run-in with the cops
We'll set him straight
It didn't
Ingo was arrested after his live-in girlfriend told police he quote assaulted her
Including shaving her up against her will and engaging in bondage type sex
His friend Joshua McGuire told police to be
Be careful when they went to arrest
Because he's always armed
McGuire
Who may want to go down in a blazer
Glory according to the arrest affidavit
Oh yeah
Always
The investigation of the woman's claim in late August LED police to serve a warrant on his inga's home
We're just followed by search warrants
For the property in his vehicle
The emergency response team was called to the home that night finding what they can
Considered items used
For the manufacturing of firearms and bombs
The home turned out to hold a trove of weapon
Gun parts
Pounds of black powder and milk crate
Containers
And a bin that helps thousands of rounds of ammunition
Along with you along with the items
Police say they found a sounds
Suppressor
Silencer made from the metal body of a Maglite flashlight
That's right it onto the end of a 22 caliber gun barrel
So he made his own site
Yep from a flashlight that's not a good sign
That's not a good sign
Sound 8%
Which service frame
The guns other parts
There was a few mechanical alterations in additional Parts could be made it to work in firearms
In some cases those types of
The receiver is sometimes referred to as blank
Don't hold serial numbers they're used to track their ownership
Be purchased online
Why they don't have those
Is that why they don't
I so they can
All the parts
Which is not over
And then make their own gun
Which are unregistered and untraceable and then you sell those
To somebody who just wants to go hunting damn they're all good citizen
His girlfriend told police that Luke had an unpredictable temper
2011 just two years after the episode
Walking to the wall above her head
After they had a kid loopty not mellow and become a good dad
When their child was 24 months old he would spank her to stop her from crying leaving bruises on her thighs
She also told police that he saw him
Cover their child's mouth
The quieter
Just super f***** up
That is really not the way to do it
U b a
Luke would also slap choke and tie up his girlfriend
Did not want him to do
Made a lot of money off selling unregistered
Sergun
So maybe the police weren't out of line pulling this guy over
Maybe they were incredibly perceptive
When you heard the beginning of the story
This guy is
A bad dude
I don't I don't
She is a good
From what I understand
From that he was work
Thing is like a construction
Dad
Cool and selling guns
Look it's a gig economy
Right
You got to come on I sell my blood unregistered gun
Again
Used
Curaleaf
So now we have Kelly rushing
It does not match
Reality
Later on
In the radio show
Historian that apologized
You know it's not a truth
Of the actual
We live in the future we know what this guy is all about
He's an abuser
Violin
Gun arms dealer
These are not good example
A hundred percent
Stuff
The one time
I myself and Doug
Rodger wrestler
And his brother Alex wrestler
We're driving by the way he was valedictorian of his class now has like a top
Not an important detail
No criminal record
And we're driving to go to the shooting range
And we got rifles in the back
Pennsylvania
State Police pull us over
It is down
You know why the cops were concerned
You were driving around with a bunch of guns and a minor in your car
An unrelated minor
There's literally no way for this Rodger wrestler to be over 18
He says he's a few years younger than him but also says he would later go to UT
So you clearly talkin about a time when biscuit was in high school
I don't either I don't like being around other people who are named Alex
At least five or six guns in the car
That that's why the cops
A concern
I think that's probably a good thing
If
Definition of when a country goes down the toilet is
I can't ride around at 18
With 427 guns in the backseat
And a minor in the car with no
When I can't do that I know this country has gone down the toilet
Yeah
Ideal World
The time no no no
Clint Eastwood
You're dumb
Because
Once everybody has a gun no one will ever shoot anybody because the other person has a gun
Which also kind of indicates kind of indicates like
Learn anything from
Like a
Yeah I think that's I think this is a little bit of a Nuance of that
Just thinks that like
Hey it'll be a good deterrent
It'll just wait anybody
Computing another person cuz they know they got a gun
You know how no country goes to war with each other because they all have bomb
Oh my God these people are trying to get us all killed
Missouri dump
So I believe that story
Or something like that
Probably did have the right paperwork whatever the
So who gives a s***
12 guns
So this next clip Alec tells a story Viva vegan
What's a real Sandra Bullock
Do you notice right now
Real quick this is after complaining about how like
Make everyone think
Youfit owning guns
Everyone watches the show scared of guns
So you got a shotgun up on his wall and
Carpet cleaners Oscar
Beck Bryant children
In my broadcast shotgun ride up on the wall
Had a gun safe right next to it
Got a shotgun
And that guy started freaking out about it I'm not going to clean this room that guns illegal
And I was just like what I don't know
On the cover of the metro state
Can I call the car
You understand the country
We live in
I believe anything
I'll believe everybody called him yes mister
Maybe your mean-spirited service capacity someone
Maybe
A train
So black under scary
What is a little bit of
How to say
It's worse because I don't believe the story extraneous details
Clearly fabricated story
Allegheny carpet cleaner be like oh my God you a shotgun on your wall a decorative gun I'm not going to have
Philly
Well I mean the shotgun was
Connected to a
Series of a home alone style trap Goldberg
You would be shocked by that guy
He doesn't have a job
You might as well break up
The other storytellers is like he put a bunch of guns in his car cuz
Who's going to go online
Or something like that
When he was a younger man
The police came while he was away
Because a neighbor called
He's like oh my God isn't this just
Just tearing it
Does hack stand up material
Your business that's kind of like
What's a trope
A bad television stand-up just the idea of like
Nosey neighbor
Feel like I was being a nosy neighbor if I walked by and my neighbor was loading a s*** ton of guns
I think that would just be responsible
I'll be like hey what's going on here
I'm going to camp
I'm not going to ask
Unloading Six-Guns have some
Familiarity
Rapport
Maybe I don't understand the multiple gun
Like
Trustee
You know
You might be going with multiple people also you might want to use dip
You know like if you're up in
Tree stand you might want one gun
If you're out shooting rabbits you might want a different gun
So if you're going out I understand
Disorder
Synonymous for killing every animal in this area that I am going
At this point I was jumped off the gun
Do which is talking more about this Baxter
International
Flash biotab
Yeah mix up that happen
But again wasn't Baxter's fault
The Czech Republic
You get back to that narrative if you Vols a little bit
I regret we have to talk about
But we do
What happened is Baxter Pharmaceuticals based in the US
Mailed in Europe
With the orders to mix
Hn
H 5 n 1 avian flu virus
Your lungs fill up with water you.
It doesn't feel right with young children
And old people
The regular flu vaccine
Nope
French German check
Historically written up on infowars.com
911 blogger
The bird flu
It was super Airborne flu
So
The only real evolution of the narrative is now.
Places with selection of the places
They got things from this lab
In the Czech Republic only three of them were named in the original articles
Multiple places
Or Australia or Slovenian
The samples from
18 number I'm not super I got in wanted
Dig more into this narrative
I know what the truth is of the bigger picture
Absolutely that's possible but they were all placed
The got things from Biotest
Is just like okay
News
You have 911 blogger being misrepresented by Paul Joseph Watson
My prediction is correct
You talking about in the Box
I don't have a bunch of it in because he
Brings it up
It's just their truck
Create this pandemic
Yeah
The globalists are awesome
The chain
Whoopty Doo
Well the things that
It's really insane
Sidious is immediately
Just saying fire tattoo
Weather
Which is based in the US
In the US
Sent the samples
Right
Laboratory
In the check
Republic
That's the impression that if you read the 9/11
Coming from the globalist
I looked into a little more and I found it the 911 blogger isn't like a person
It's a site where a bunch of people can
Can contribute blog post
Oh so this post was actually put up just by some guy
Bloggers who might have
Credible
Standing I don't think 9/11 blogger would at 2
Like online
Anonymous contributor
Another level of
Like nonsense
Which is both because it least
Saudi Arabia
The globalist
Bill Clinton
Larry Nichols
Yeah for sure
Damon Dash
Roc-A-Fella Records
Absolutely their Luminati related
Jumpsuit Jay-Z could make a state of mind
That was after 9/11 not empire songs
My bad
Indeed that's the victim of a terrorist attack
Scrabble
And Jay-Z got together to make Empire State of Mind
Hold on
But the best thing to come out of that song
Was whenever it
Was combined with the Bacon pancake song
From Adventure Time I don't know what are you saying
Adventure Time
The metaphorical Saudi Arabia
So Jordans
Because he's got weak s*** about the avian flu
To do
Needs to related
Other narratives
But he has
He pitches out
And so each
That's particularly ugly and dark
To talk about but I
It's very important to interns
Understanding
Alex Jones does his dirty work in a rating scale
Is going to go is this
6 Guns
Your car.
Situation
I thought I would go back
You can just Google
In the Google you'll get hundreds of news articles
MSNBC pieces where they admit
Bear the big
Apparent
A bunch of cameras
4 years
Was on going until 2000
Factor 8
The media was called to the vaccine it really isn't
No they don't
Hot salsa
Who was the older adult
Baxter Pharmaceuticals
Now what year is a mainstream Europe
The cause of pandemic
Because
Baxter separately trying to get approval for a bird flu
Vaccine
So that's that's mainstream news in Europe
No it is 911 blogger
Editorial
As check media
Now what
Smell real quick Baxter was
Going to working on a h 5 n 1 vaccine
Approval for it until October
Saudi
Lady who lost her medical license
For being crazy
Years Breyer piles of this flu vaccine
It doesn't fly because
They didn't get approval until October
Now the idea that they did
To get approval
For the vaccine
Because like I said
This all happened
At the beginning of February Alex's reporting on it a month later they wouldn't get approval for another 6 months
So the idea that they're trying to fast-track that somehow doesn't
Like they were already in the process of
Getting it through they've gotten
Preliminary approval for speed up the process at all
If anything it probably called them to
Lower staff
Because as we learned from the investigation from the office
Nuclear
The Czech Republic
Navy ravir Greenhills
Wasn't
Applying pressure to Biotest
To make things move
Faster for there
Okay
2000s
Conclusions that they found probably let the
Them to have to slow things down to live
Leading to them getting brutal
In October
Write to all that doesn't really make sense
It's just been spiritual really like what is
Kind of stuff
I got you
Well
Here's the Big B are those the only virus
No but this is where things are going to get real bad
Part of the reason is that Alex is talking about a real thing
Really being
Unfair about
The early 1980s there's an outbreak of cases of AIDs that
It appeared to be directly related
To the use of blood products
Particularly Factor
To the clotting Factor drug used by humans celiacs to make
Clotting Factor
Usually two to three times a week
Or else they'll end up with an
Internal bleeding
I get a cut it won't stop bleeding
Intense process that sucks I watched a documentary about
Some of this stuff
Batman also just
The life of
Hemophiliac
Right
There's a couple that are
Hemophiliac children
Anywhere showing like their cabinets
Full of gauze and syringes
Wow
Do like really adjust
And learn how to find a vein
As a parent is
It really
It got me a little emotional because also
The dad was talking about how like
It's a real tree
To raise these kids
And like even with all of the
Very
Logistical trouble
In this documentary
Those kids will grow up in
That like
It's just very movie
The inbreeding of the Royals in Europe
I don't know if that's necessarily wear
You could trace it all back 20
It certainly was
First cases
That reported but it's possible that a lot of people
Before that habitats
Cuz I mean
Tubi
They never would have found the
That's the case with all of Alex's like medical Woo which is that idea that like
We just didn't know what it was
So drugs
Such as this factor 8 clotting drug
Blood product
Plasma
In the late 1970s and early 80s
The plasma in blood collected in that time.
Could not be scream for something that doctors did not know to look
Company looking to make the most profit
But naturally cut corners
Resort
Collecting plasma from impoverished communities which has the highest incidence of being IV drug user
Some cases
You also have a very high rate
Correctly
Bear
In order not just not just bear
Japanese
Would you
Take blood from prisoners
I'm sure was voluntary but yeah
Compensated
General population
I sell my blood
For plasma now I know from doing this as much as I have
They still Target the impoverished
So that part hasn't
Standards and practice
Blood products being collected in the late seventies early eighties with contaminated with the as-yet on
Unidentified
Many hemophiliacs contracted AIDS
From the clotting injection
And overall there's no way to talk about
It's about being straightforward and
Absolute
What's proper testing was available in October 1984
What is reporting its
34% of
Hemophiliacs treated with the old version
In the factory
I tested positive
It's a crazy high amount
Where does become compounded
Is the cutter biological a unit of Bayer
Continue telling that version
The factory even though
Heat-treated version
Had become available
They introduced this new version The Factory in February 9th
I did not fully stop selling the oil dangerous version until July
Alex has been continued through 2000
And that is not
Correct
Got to make that last little bit of money
Where can I get rid of all this old factory
Text I'm going to go over there might be a little
And I want to stay up front I am not
The foremost scholar on the 8th
Anything like
I read a bunch of reports for
From the national anthem
Help
Some contemporary reports
It's all
Some of the darkest
Sadist
But
And Reagan made it so much
Part of what I'm talking
Alex
Expectorate
There's a number of important
Finally leaving out with your big parts of the
The context
The first is that companies of which bear is particularly its International
These potentially tainted blood products out with foreknowledge
But I was playing fast and loose about what they might have had
Had foreknowledge of
One of the things that has to be understood is that the time. Alex is discussing
When blood products
From people with HIV was being used to me
Make factor 8
Was when Reagan wasn't on
He was President for pretty much the entire 1980s which is when the AIDS crisis
This was at its most tragic
Add one of the things that made it worse
Was it Reagan was someone who stasha Lee opposed
Any governmental regulation
Including ones related to public
So
He was resistant to
Putting things in place
That would have
Help
Mitigate the damage that was being done
Brochure
Even if everything was done perp
Some of these people would still have been in fact
Quit because of the
Mandan
Maybe naive
On the part of
People before they knew what the problem was
So
Further it should be noted that the cause of AIDS was
Not knowing
4 years after the medical community began
From a June 24th 1983 publication
From the national anthem
Streets of hell
Call the cause of Ages unknown
Most likely to be caused by a native transmitted by
Intimate sexual contact
Contaminated needles or less
Infected blood or blood products
83 looks like this
Yeah so that is
Because that means
There is not a consensus
That means that there were people holding out and I don't know if we prove
That right
It's not like we have today
Where there's the denier
Large sex
Legitimate medical community are still not
Convince will they weren't convinced that women had orgasms
Nicole
Even wants the medical community figured out that this was
Is the primary means for
Mission
Even in the National Institute of Health
May 10th 1985 release
They highlight another issue
Because the time from
Tuan said maybe several years
Persons exposed to the virus through
Hurt before
Institution of the self differential guidelines
For blood donors in
3 screening of blood
Antibody in 19
Maybe five May remain at risk of
Before 1983 there were no standards in place regarding blood don't
It was a further two years
After that the donations
Screen extract
3 what they ended up doing this like voluntary question
Alaska
People
Are you in high-risk population
Two years after that before they started screening their actual donors
He's giving them small amounts of money
Forever love you on those those questions
And that's why now they don't let me know juice still ask you a question
In case there were red flag
Right or something like that but
They also test
Exactly
What are the main reasons that society-at-large didn't take this crisis seriously is that initially
It was only sex
With the time or much more marginalized than they are today
Early on the disease with called related immunodeficiency
And as late as June 1982.
Speculating
Behavioral elements
To the homosexual life
Style where the cause
Even suggesting the disease might be
Because by use of amyl
Or Papa
Hemophiliacs and others
Receive blood tree
Transfusions is 20 months of age
Some doctors started to make that connection
Others felt that because the number of France
Infusion-related escapism
Fusion it was more likely that these cases were caused by
Unrelated
Depression related to their existing
Right
No no no you make me mixed up a little bit
CDC health department meeting to discuss opportunities to limited effect
They discussed her blood bank should ask donors questions about their sexual behavior
A run the blood
Your test for things
Since there was no test
And they are
To be a correlation
Between hepatitis A
They felt like it would be a good screen
4 something
You bet
These donations
And that's one of the reasons that the blood bank
Association was like that's probably not a good idea that will make us have no
Donors
Right so we're not convinced
Bloodborne
And resisted these suggest
Additionally, director of the fda's division of Blood In Blood products
Inactivated virus
Blood products was
Underway
Donahue was hoping to find a virus in blood products
As opposed to
Bang the existing blood supply
Free of viruses
Is the definition of backwards
But it is something that they ended up with
Result was saying that we're going to make this better in
In the future but
All the stuff we already got
No
It's not quite that way
They were able to do
On new
They couldn't do it with the stuff that it already been
You have to do the heat treatment on the Vic
Constituent parts
The
Ingredients
Since the factory
Once it's already come by
So they did find
They did find that that was waived
You get around the fact
Test
Keep out right
In the short-term
But then once they're worth
Anyway in early 1980s
Discovered and hypothesized
Does the causal agent of a
By the middle of 1985 all Blood Bank in plasma center
Implemented early screen
However in October nights
80 for the sea
CDC announcement
Laboratory experiment showed
The heat treatment process
Inactivated
So
Solution
People knew and they didn't
So in 2003 and their subsidiary cutter biological
Dollars worth
The clotting Factor
To Asia and Latin America
Owl selling a newer safer product in the West
This gets super complicated
Speaking on behalf of Qatar commented to the New York Times quote continue to sell the old medicine
Because some customers doubted the new drug
Effectiveness
And because some countries were slow to approve its tail
The company also said that a shortage of plasma
Used
I kept her from manufacturing more of the new product
Court decisions made nearly two decades ago
Nevada time
And were consistent with the regulations
Relates to regulations that's probably a fair point
And appointed fears about the effectiveness about
Is absolutely something that's backed up by history
From an article in the Irish Times
Fractions
Blood product
Manufacturers
We're more fearful of 1984 side effects
It's caused by a heat treatment process
The killed HIV
None of the virus itself
Senior British fracture
Doctor James Mitchell
Heat-treated product
Call genetic reaction
This position gradually changed
From Midnight teenage
But
Thrombogenic
I remained a major
Consideration into 1985
So much so that British fractionator
Even delay the release of
Heat-treated cons
Concentrate
So there is
Reason to believe
To some extent
Yeah people
Hesitant
Adopt this new safer
Version
Now
I don't care
Necessarily about that argument
Because the document
When did it come out of
Qatar is internal
Working
Do show a bit of a
The callousness
Do the idea
I was like
Let's see if we can
Find markets
Because
Never an intentional attempt to infect
People with AIDS
The largest
The story is unregulated capitalism
With a background of a
Tragic Public Health crisis
Being worsened by Republic
Ministration
Implement regular
This is a
Human tragedy
That really really really really
Bumped me out reading about
And
There
I stopped short of calling it evil but it's pretty easy
It's pretty evil but the beginnings of it aren't
No pretty women Salvador ignorance and then once you know about it you have
To change your behavior
Just sold the new that he would exhibit some of it
Not only
Could cause a
I'm not I'm not defending that all places and then they sold the stuff that wouldn't cause HIV
I'm not I'm not defending that at all and I'm not saying that
Settlement
People which still isn't
Nearly enough I believe
A b d d
I think they should be punished
White Horse Lake
Isaac just based on us being
Interested in finding out where Alex is lying
The truth is
I think it's pretty important to recognize
Is that
There was plausible deniability
To a certain extent
All medical exam
Yeah
Did the idea of July 1985
Is f***** up
But there is an argument to be made that they could
Find scientist
Some doctors
Who were crazy
Who disputed the idea that their blood products
Could cause HIV
You know what I don't I don't know what
To do with it except to say
This is the reality of this
Situation this is what happened
It's awful
Hurt and killed a lot of people
The reason it wasn't taken more seriously
Is the marginalization of
Sexual community
And
The bottom line
Dollars
And do like a regulation
That's all that.
Base of the story
To be like justifying
His idea that the globalist
Set off a bio-weapon because
They gave all these
People AIDS
Yeah it's not fair
This is a tragedy
Disrespectful to the people
Who
Hurt the most
Yeah
I don't know I just I deeply resent Alex's
This
When you look into it you're the
People talk about
Documentary
Call Blood Brother
He's with someone
The doctor
The phds in automatic
Call.
Hemophiliac
Who ended up
From
Is injection
Alicia
And he has a quote
We believe that he really acts of the canaries in the coal mine
The blood supply
As soon as something goes wrong with the blood supply to the first ones who will show evidence
We are warning system
For the American people
As soon as they see
Thing happen in the
They better be aware that it's going to happen
Tire America
So I think that's probably the best way
Look at this
In terms of
This was
Unforeseen
Tragedy
That was born out of
People not
Yeah
And then resisting knowing
Much longer than
This is so important
It's not letting them out these companies off the hook
They're absolutely responsible
But we are looking at this
From a 28
18 viewpoint
Yeah we're looking at it through this
Pacific knowledge
Being raised
Largely in a. Of time where we understood
And when you have
Situation like
You had in the early 80s
You
There's a lot of up and down about it
If that's okay if that's not okay to say
There's a lot of things that
I am I don't I don't
This is where
These companies acted in good faith
Like I don't think that they did I think they wanted to sell off these
Supplies of things
They knew
I didn't want to have to write off a huge Warehouse
But at the same time
Have the science
Really
Understood as it is now
I don't think that they would have acted
You know what I'm I think they would walk
But I don't think they would
Because they're also regulations in place.
Probably
That goes to
You know a car that has a defect that'll cause x amount of death
Yeah
Equations
How much will a recall cost how much will
Settling case
Yeah exactly
No I think there's a lot of businesses went allowed to
This is another example of it but it's just
Much
Much more depressed
Awful
Family
Like I was reading about that
Threw a bunch
HIV
And in the culture
Forgetting this disease breakup fam
Like the parents
So these people who got it with
Something wrong with
Their kid
It's just such a
Tragedy
So that was a really dark
Bit of research
That I did
Stuff a lot
And his narrative is wrong
Stories
Is
That's always an unfortunate
A place to come with Alex
Where you have to be like
But
You're not looking at
The picture you're not you're only looking at what you want to look at
City on a hill
I don't want to talk more about this narrative
Ignore it
Alex
Fit Factory
Was tainted was still being shipped until 2
They stopped in July
Nineteen85
You have nothing to back that up just an assertion that he's making he's reading this article and he's saying that
This is an article in the New York Times
The came out in 1996
So he has a problem with that is it came out 1996
Doing it for 4 years after that
I don't think so
So you just make sure it up
It's crazy he says that most cancer is viral
True
Rooted in
I didn't know that
HPV
You can cause cervical
That's the accepted
As far as I can fly
Almost all
Is that the dirty I don't know why that would be dirty
Since you don't know that wouldn't just be a regular
Where's the dirty secret because that's why they wanted
Give you the vaccines
Viruses
That would be a dirty
I apologize for everyone that we
Episode
Hour-long interview
With
Pastor to the stars now
Cornell
Because of that says no this is good
There's a real-life sort of roller coaster that his appearance goes on
Good again he just
Everybody
W believe everything Alex Jones says
Buttering up Alec
Begin
But I guess as a result of you knowing that for the past 35 years
8 months ago
And it has happened exactly like they said it
He had perfect
Predictions cuz they all come from the elite
Now what he says
It's important to point this out if you read John Birch Society stop in
Conspiracy
The elite
Insiders
Are the terms
And they use for the globe
The globalist is kind of a later permutation of the term
Incontact
And they told him how everything is going to play out for the next year
Why would this next clip is a little bit long
But I beg of you.
Listen to every word okay alright this is so funny because
To me this clip explains why these Elites are still talking
But also is
Nowhere close
Everything that I've ever been told by them
I told it to the world and a few times I've been contacted and they've said that when you saying too much and you going to have fun
If you don't take action
This is the second time this has happened in 35 years
This gentleman I have not seen for about 25 years
I know who he is
He's 82 years of age now but what you become apart of them you never get away from it
Trouble
Quit
Your video
When is viral is loose change
With millions of views a day
Sensation
So they call you up
What you said was not too Pleasant and I remember very well that
Change over the currency and do away with the Federal Reserve
Well shot
Real quick
Just just pause for a second he has more to say but what you have here is Lindsey Williams
Give me a call
From the global you need to calm down
So
He does
He goes along with what the globalist tell him to do if Alex Jones is like the truth-teller who's bald
The goblets
I don't know if he really wants to be
You bet I'll take down my video and sorry about that
R-Truth
He's a fighter for truth
Do you know is that discretion is the better part of valor true true
Always another video.
Lowercase t
Redo it
Agreed to shut down my website which you won't find it there any longer
That's not the important thing I can do in helping you
Program today
Do everything
Don't let that boy I asked him
How's your family
Your wife has been living since I saw you 25 years ago
Any question
And for 45 minutes time he talked with me on the phone now
If you can imagine
He was talking with me on the phone
That was one crude oil 147.
Workout
$2 a barrel
He said the price of gasoline at the gas pump is going to a dollar in $52 a gallon
He said
Bankrupting OPEC
OK Google
It opens
Getting a phone call
Hey you better shut up or we're going to kill you
Because he's
Polite
Yeah
Yeah let me Williams is a crafting the manipulator of globalist
Royal in bankruptcy
I could
Do you like someone who was friendly with like an oil executive having a conversation with
There's no way this price is going to hold this going to go down to 50 apparel
But that's just a prediction of Market
We're going to make it go do
Kind of believe like if he wasn't just such an outright liar I could kind of believe that he had a conversation with someone and it went like
Editorializing
Econo-pak Williams creation of this
It's like this
He's going to fall out the bottom falling out
Cuz that's an outrageously inflated price
I believe that
Horseshit
That's that's like a like a
But it's
The telling of the telling of a tall tale
Foreshore
I called this guy
He threatened me
I had them by the family
And then he was like
Was down and then I found out everything
Going to happen for the next year yeah I can tell you
Isn't that like going to get you another phone call
Review the Monera that you done bamboozled
Maybe they aren't going to give you a chance next time Monday
Part of your consideration
If you're like oh JFK got killed for going up against them but I'm going to
Information
On the Alex Jones Show
You just
If it allows bond to formulate a plan
Except bandhan say how's your family
Their cups
Real-time
So
Let's pretend
From Russia with Love
So let's pretend that he's not lying
Which is very hard to do
Now let's see what his prediction is let's see what the globalist told him
Disney's daughter prediction
This is him saying what globalist told him they were going to do
It's not random happens
It's this is
Is the plan
So is this is wrong
He's making s*** up
Let's see if he's wrong
Mark my words you are going to see 6 months 9 months maximum one year from now
Complete collapse of the United States
I was told by one of these
No
Actually already
And we're in a recovery because of the
Alex
So
But that makes sense actually for him to be against the things that would fix the problem
Because that doesn't help him sell gold
Flanigan's
That's bad prediction
Blenders wrong
But didn't happen
Or
Which sounds like
If I was the globalist
What am I
I don't
I will call Lindsey Williams and I will be hilarious
Disseminate through that that hole
Network
I want to scare Alex Jones
Can't do it Direct
Call the champ
Text wife
Alex
Exactly right
Bought back because the only thing to fear
Okay
Alex Going to the Country the only type of program
Globalist only fear
You waking p
You are the best
One more clip
And it's the
The perfect punchline
To all of this
See what
Lindsey Williams
Is really about
You want to comment on stage biological weapons
What album is entitled vaccinations and deals with the gift called in about again
One of the DVDs on my big 8-pack concerns that
Okay
That reminds me of a Rapaport
He sells like 10 DVD sets
Text just too much over
Just burning them
That ain't
The 8 DVD sets
Propaganda
The other thing about that is like because he's
About the like I know about what the next year is going to bring there's an immediate
He's really trying to push these
DVD app
Williams is on selling his hot b******* and all of it is
Prelude to his you need to buy this
Alex
Flu / factor 8
Meredith
Weaving perfectly because
Lindsey Williams
One of those
Selling it
Beer through line
Episode
Boggles my mind
Whenever they do wind up saying something that is true
In the opposite
Play the only thing these people
Call Tiara is
The populist
Rising up
Waking up
They do when the list
I really hate these were allowed to rise and take over
Everybody's fine
Not everybody would be most afraid of every time
Liquid
What are we see the Cubs doing their monitoring
Right to the left and right
That is the case is that the power structure doesn't real
Really care about the ideas like stash
Biggest fascist
Love power
So the whole game is really the same it's just
How awful is it going to be
Citizenry
America at why the f***
Jumping
Why would my water be raised
Juke
If people wake up the way that they think that they're supposed to the way that Alex
But they're supposed to all it does is lead to fascism
I mean I mean cuz Alex's people rising up legitimately means militias coming into
Into effect for Oklahoma City Bombing type event
Which leads to a Crackdown and militarization of police
The mentality to the world
Actually precipitate
His rhetoric is again
Exactly
He says the elites
Because that's what he imagined
Division is head of
Leftist
Communist
Socialist
No
Authoritarian
Is complete
What he's helping
Create
And has helped create congratulations Alex your career career is come to fruition accidentally
I think
Maybe so,
Lee Atwater
How do I join this band of this episode a little bit shorter but I think they're one of the reasons is because I had to read a lot
NIH documents
And stuff like that and it was really emotional
Exhausting so I cut it off here
To get through
But
This March
. for Alex's
Of the worst stuff I've heard
You know we're dealing with a lot of like
Real weird stuff
Text me that you're we are you still not talking about the
Tea party at all
He's really not
He's
Kind of dropped
The Tenth Amendment narrative
He was going on through almost all the February
He hasn't brought that up in a couple hours
Episode
So it's interesting to see you like
These establish that 10th Amendment
To the point where now he can bring it back at any point
And that what he's doing is he's laying the groundwork of
Is avian flu
They're trying to kill you in the vaccines narrative
Embassy
Whenever he wants down the road
To see the structure of this sort of
Propaganda
And how it works
I have no f****** idea what's
Lincoln 2009
I have no idea where he's going
SMS
So we'll find out where a lot of narratives in advance
The host of singled out
Coming out as gay
Just in case
You don't remember
Night I forgot that Jenny McCarthy was ago
Yes I remembered like
Carmen Electra was but I forgot
Oh yeah
Anyway Jordan Springer episode but we have a website
Dollartree.com
You can go to Facebook
It will group called
Were there
You leave a review overnight also or just a blanket apology if I if I
If anyone feels like I gave
Short shrift
HIV
I apologize
The big picture but
I think some of that is
Because it doesn't fit
All of it into
The Narrative that were talking about but I want to make sure people understand if I
If you felt that way I apologize
Talk about good service
Mr. how
Bad a lot of
Policies of the
Republican
That will never affect them in a negative way
Probably not
I don't know man Alex Jones
Alexandra First Time coloring