Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work
Alex
Is that like a mythical figure like a bunion
Folklore
Legends
Long after he's dead. It'll be like homeric tradition
Telling
We talked about a minute
The Weeknd
Show's over it
Lakeshore went all out
People got together and decided to tolerate
Something
Is it is a delightful
That's all too often the case that light shows
Confused
I mention that specifically for one reason
On this weekend
Is episode's coming out on Monday and unfortunately we're not going to be able to cover a ton of things
Alex Jones world
Hopefully
Once
Time is past will be able to cover that
First is that in Austin there's a free Alex Jones rally going on refuse unfortunately it is
Is happening after we recorded so we won't know the aftermath until later
On the 2nd is news just broke that PayPal has kicked Alex off
Precipitate a real blow up
I know not all of his money comes in processed by PayPal
Cut a chunk out probably
Not going to be happy about that
Are terms of Tourism
Absolutely
Now that's a whole different world
No cuz he's doesn't understand cryptocurrency I don't I don't think it'll come to that
Probably
Money
I think they still have to
Hold it up
Same time
I don't think that's going to affect his multi-level marketing jeunesse money
Cuz I think
Do you think of these pivoting to
Until June SS
They give it back to him
I don't think him being kicked off PayPal is going to affect that new Hustle
He's got but it will probably cut into Infowars store sales
Knox
You know
Everybody's credit information
Everything
Yeah
There's no doubt about that
And if you'd like to send this donation please send you the message I'll give you the email address to do that
Different way
First of all we've got is just excited about this
Thank you very much
You know we are on the last one
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
I do only want to Daniel's friends in the lions den
If it's a real shame
Maybe
In the fire where that was all that was the whole Miracles now
What the Bible folk I don't know any parent has friends with Daniel and Michael from the Bible
Thank you so much
Are all the all the
Major Bible figures not real but every now and again there's just some random
Tertiary character like oh yeah I'm like 10,000 years old
I don't have any powers or anything I'm just
That'll be great
Is someone else who's going to put the team and appreciate it very much
You're now a technocrat
Start song about until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Thank you so much Laura
You can do that by going to knowledge buy.com quick netsports show button we would appreciate it
I just looked moment
Because I don't think we do this enough
Because they really help on a map
Level with the show existing
Along the way
But that's not that's not the shout them out
Thank you again
Updated thank you
Two are Raptor princesses out there we really appreciate if you make the world go round
I don't know I don't know what every 3 or 4 months
Still love you guys I don't know
In case you were feeling ignored for even just a moment I project brings out a little bit
I don't know how to appropriately show appreciation
Really appreciate it we're just going to text all of our Raptor princesses once every 3 months
Just to be like updated thank you just
Audible really appreciate
Thank you all so much and everybody everybody
No sponsors knocking down
These doors
You do
Message you
PayPal address
What's an order to donate
That way
Would you be able
Oh that's not bad that's close to Babality Mortal Kombat
Let me phrase it this
Interview
They're not there a few times Vicky actually get done by anybody interview
Felt like yeah we had of course Megyn Kelly
Prayer for him to actually sit down with
This week
A gentleman by the name of Patrick bet-david
Hyphenated last name
In a hotel room
But that's okay
The smart money goes but you lose
So we know about this from the last 2002-8
18 West present-day episode
Alex mentioned
When he was talking with Owen Shroyer about their masculinity issues
Walking into a hotel room to do an interview and how you get it
Oh this is bad
She looks like s***
Walking around like a super masculine guy he's like
Reluctant criticize myself for critique
But Alex is drunk
Looks like s*** that's good
And I'm a man with a cross eye so I'm not someone who likes
Batik people's eyes
Cross eye
His eyes are Autobahn
Sarah's at wondery aspect to his eyes
That are just like it's not
It's not astigmatism it's not like a cross-ice situation there's just something f*****-up going on with his eyes
Okay there's a nefarious
I'm not sure what it is very weird what's going on
Could be
Down for a two-hour interview with Bette Davis
Then maybe the reason that he has this
Meltdown of
Insecure masculinity happen on air
It's not because the story why does
He told it where in he walks around Drake
He was looking like a people
Not doing well at all
That sounds a little bit more likely insecure Alex
90/42 our interview with this cat
And he is drunk
I'm I'm going to make no bones about that
He's drunk from the beginning
Okay but I know that
They're drinking
It's very clear there on camera
Salinger write this interview
Like but he can handle his booze
We're going to be alright alright
That is going to be an Untold Story
Because Alex spoiler alert
Talked about how he's ready to die
So we're going to walk through the interview talk about how f****** stupid Alex isn't have drunk
He gets but he wasn't our context drop
Of things to come
Illuminati
That's very interesting
New Theory
When did Biggie die
Who's ready to die mouth
Maybe every 20 years biggie reinvent himself like the resemblance with Bill Hicks
Let's start the interview where Patrick bet-david begins
By asking Alex
By giving Alex's credit
Which normally if you were giving a Galaxy you might say
You started infowars.com in the nineties you built it up from
Something you were doing out of your
Your dad's dental office
Created a multimillion-dollar Empire pick up Mastiff
Terrell
New Theory.
There are a lot of like legitimate credits
You could give him you can't take away the fact that he built this business and
Something
I am sure the credits
So if you follow the news if you follow media you going to see this place again Alex Jones who is recognized
It's pretty fair to say you are
The most controversial political figure in America today
In the world
The given credit
You did
These are this is what makes you relevant
He's only identifying credit that he's being given it all is victimhood
I just I just wrote down his credit is
This we have today the biggest victim in the world definition is like I'm person
Patrick bet-david nobody is more persecuted
I mean it's crazy
Took my children away at the borders they put him in a separate detention
Facility and I am
I'm forced to sit here as I'm deported ways that not him
Advisor
Patrick Curran
Wherefore forced to flee during the iran-iraq war
They lived in a German refugee camp
For two years before their family came to America when Patrick was 12
At which point he enrolled in school and joined the US Army after graduating
In short he live in Counterpoint to all of Alex's narratives about refugees and immigrants
And it's an absolute tragedy and travesty that this doesn't come up at all
In their interview
Now what
Introduction
Patrick bet-david
Haha get more into the salon
This dude interviewing Alex
Well he runs a motivational entrepreneur base
YouTube channel
Oh so he's also a multi-level marketing scheme
You didn't say that you didn't answer with an O
Saturday
Atlanta
Doesn't work
You've already you've already sort of figured this one out
Judging solely from the titles of his books might take the Patrick bet-david is a little bit of
Mako oilfield
Tourist books are called impossible the 25 laws for doing the impossible
Love your neighbor
Also his other one is quick drop out and get school the case for thinking twice about college
Either book titles that basically emulates the strategy of clickbait
Set up for article
2009 Patrick bet-david dinner with George Will
Conservative columnist
After which she was inspired to start a website called saving America the date
Restore America's prosperity to the founding principles America exception
Interesting that in 2009
Bulshit platitude
But Alex uses today
After this Patrick launched
PHP
People
The company ostensibly offers life insurance annuity settlement
Services already escaped
Charity
Princeton article on opportunity lives
Points out that in the six
Here's something founded the company quote
His company is growing at such a rapid Pace that now has more than 5,500 representatives in 33 States
No no
Not real
That would be a massive success story
And one of the only website is labeled
This is where things start getting some interesting overlap with modern-day Alex Jones
To begin with ph
Agreements be of $150
Dot-dot-dot
Then you come to find out anything
And things start to become a little bit more info
You got to have support
PHP agency supposedly about selling life insurance but in reality what it's about is selling you on the idea of signing other people
To become life insurance agent
You make money off of them
Recruiting other people
It on Down the Line apparently it's some people but it's such a small part of their sales
Pitch at all there's
Hundreds of stories that I've read of people who
To their seminars
How old is things work
You big bring people to a ballroom someone gives a speech and then they isolate them and try and convince them to
Becoming a recruiter for that part of us
So the stories are all basically the same
I went to help a friend out
My friends and family also to join
I didn't do that because it was rude
I went to buy a puppy
He hired me
So that's not
User on Reddit right they only give vague info in the interview
Until I went back to the office
An hour later to do orientation
Like was very immoral
But the fries MLM still hadn't entered my mind
When I got to the orientation of my coworker explained the business model in more detail
You make money off money money other people make by recruiting people more people Etc
And also by tricking poor people into buying a shity life
It goes on and on and on the HP appears to be a textbook example of MLM
And Patrick bet-david
Is the founder of said company
Here he is interviewing Alex Jones
Before Alex announces on are becoming a middle-level distributor and another MLM call jeunesse
Gamers unite connected but I don't know how like a coincidence
I went to the bank to get an equity loan the other day and now I'm account manager for the Midwest region
Photos of interesting Lee Patrick bet-david is also a David also advises people not
To go to college
Home
We're not to buy home because those
That might be okay advice wasn't to advocate
Which based upon the business
Has he started up
Even more Surefire route
Towards losing more
So all that money
That you are going to put
Colleges
What if you just
But give it all to me
Instead and then
They called
Exact same sword
Classic
Multi-level marketing
People go in
You have to
Is that all of it
Well open got to pay the monthly for access
And then afterwards people signing up
So I have to have life insurance
One of our provider
Are there providers
Exactly
There's
An ethical business
Model
Is now part of a different one
Exactly models
This whole world
Beating all of his
This is
This is Casey
It really all that
Important to cover Alex
Anymore
He's become the most pathetic pile of s***
And he's not going to leave his audience
White supremacy
Nazism
Anymore as much as he's going
To lead them to financial ruin
And like I don't want for them to have to go through that I think that's awful
But
What is the weather now what is the only way to stop the rise of nine
How to use a medium distributor
So this this
Like
This strategy for hate
Organization
Has always been there
It's a good one
Yeah when you are filled with hate
Often hard to discern
Patrick bet-david
That doesn't come up
In the energy
But this is two days before
Our last episode where Alex had the
The jeunesse guyon
But made the big amount
This interview was two days before
Deal already been up
It wasn't remember when he got on his phone
That was a like a month or so back
Whenever it was everything
Blurry TimeWise on his phone
And that window was there
He had like
He had put out there but he really
Fully committed too late night
Interview is happening
With him fully aware that he's about to pimp his audience
So
It's weird the headspace
Is very strange
Anyway
It is equipped to talk more about his victimhood
I think you might oversell this a little bit
So you've been Facebook Twitter Youtube
Instagram
Over 100 platform
Not attack band you
We just watched a week ago
Supposedly
Your YouTube channel has roughly 1.5 billion views
Give or take
I was just
5 billion views total
If you're 20 YouTube channels
That probably means you're up to
That's not like a coherent model
Well yeah but you have like
Agonize one
In order to put out
How would you even know they were connect
I don't know YouTube
You would think they would have some sort of
System
Yeah
Are 20 YouTube channels I think that's a red flag in and of itself
And then beyond like a
That didn't go to number one
Right after
He got thrown out
Call
Hyper-inflated much like
Gas prices in 2008/2009
He's trying to
Pizza Hut in order to
Really
I mean what do you want this sympathy
He knows that he doesn't deserve it
Alright
Why is this creator of a multi-level marketing
Doing an interview with that
Because he has the channel That Gets like
Reviews for videos
Absolutely
Probably because the guy who runs gymnastic knows Patrick bet-david
I assume
I don't know that's the only explanation.
Interview
Unless there's something else going on
I looked into his channel and one of the first of all
And it makes more sense
Nobody did used to have flare Financial
He offer it was like Financial advice
Yeah Ric Flair on that's cool but then the downside
Shapiro on talking about how to clean
Things are awful
Sharks I think Alex could have gotten a request from him and
Gone through and seems like
Bricklayers
Super cool Perez Hilton
Oh wait what's this kid Ben Shapiro on talking s*** about the Clinton
I don't know there's a hundred reasons I can think of possibly why Alex
To do this
Patrick offer
I don't know I don't know
Also Alex
You know like he's losing all of his access he's losing
The ability to get his message out if he has this guy who
We have a conduit
And is related to celebrities in Celebrity
I could see him being like
Patrick bet-david
Like lives in text
So it's not like
Fly to Fiji
Clip
He was
And how everything is
Fault
Left-wing
Conspiracy
Against him
Run by none other
Nothing to Demons
Spawn Hillary
Hillary Clinton
Soros
About a month before she lost 2016
Figure
Out of context
She went $18 of ads
Real quick on that I tried to find this I couldn't find
Information
Cheap 88
Million dollars
Anti Alex
Look up Hillary Clinton
$3000000 in
The only the only thing
Hillary Clinton
Is it in 2000
Referring to the number of
Primary
Although we weren't able to shatter that highest hardest glass feeling good time
Thanks to you it's got about 18 million cracks in it
And the light shining through like never before filling and the sure knowledge
The path will be a little easier next
Now I can't find any evidence
She paid $18
Demonize Alex Jones
Interesting that the only thing
Is this very inspiration
But you gave
About the glass ceiling
3 million of those were illegal
Interesting parallel that Alex is lying about this thing about her
And the parallel that you can find with that number
It's something that would also really pissed off
Conflated the number things
Make a mad about Hillary
Best kind of my work
Theory on it
Not on how much you
Spend
How much you spend
Person you are attacking everybody Americans for Prosperity
$20,000 in attack in Big Bear
Right away
Charger from
One tenth of what they say
They ran 18 million dollars
YouTube Google and Facebook
TV
Here's Alex Jones
He tells Trump what to do
And me saying something real quick Alex
Also played his own versions of trump saying similar things to him
Around the same time Trump is listening to us
He gets information to Trump has information
And the global is still trying to keep that information right
Making the exact same
$2000000
All helper
The first one
He's talking about the Google ads
Yeah I kicked off of it
10 million-dollar
Biggie's over exaggerating
Once again
Everything was coming after me they were looking for
Which wasn't true
I was like telling trouble to do
Thinking
Are you saying the Trump was making radical statement
But they wanted
Their own propaganda
And then
Almost two years later it has been one helluva ride. Literally
Believe their own BS
I am in charge of prompt and I'm giving him every move
What
Talking about
No one is saying what he saying there's a
No nobody's doing what he saying
What are you talkin about this a lot
This is like I
I was very well might as well be called
The station like he's he's responding to criticisms that no one's making
He's responding to like
Fake versions of allegation
He's responding to things
You think people are doing they're actually what he was doing
It's nonsense he's all over the map
They kicked me out of the gym
Because I bench press
Too much weight
Woman who lies
Throw it through the window
Breaking that glass ceiling by the way thank you ladies 18 million cracked window
Look the
I want it I want to see
Because we kind of
Patrick bet-david
Multi-level marketing
But I want to say that he does
As good a job of interviewing
Is anybody I've ever
Really a good amount of pushing back against him he has a couple of good point
And
I don't want any I don't care
It's too long
It's two hours long
People shouldn't subject themselves to that unless they really want to
But there is a really funny friends
It keeps going throughout it is like Patrick bet-david sort of rolling his eyes and his body language
But there is a lot of that like Alex plunged slouched over kind of drunk
Patrick bet-david looks like what are you talking about
So there is that but he does
He doesn't just let Alex say a lot of s***
You kind of woefully
Unprepared
He doesn't have a ton of information
Position where you could have like really
He was inspired by George will this is
Laughing along with Ben Shapiro show
Patrick wants to talk a little more about Alex
Communication
When the last time you spoke to Trump
Blasphemer
Who are you people
Pause water wet
You want to think.
Ever since you've been banned
Have you had a conversation with him since the band or no
Conversations
Now this is important
Alex said
The campaign
Because he's
The part of his brain that remembers like the narratives
Talk about it still operating
When he says I talked
Administration
He's still operating off that I'm
Part of this
He's not
And I just said listen
Before the administrator
Tens of thousands of Articles a month
About me
This is clearly
Musically one person
There's everybody else
I'm at the supporting
They picked me because I'm flamboyant
Horrible person
And then
Now they are going to
They shut me down
Facebook Twitter
Google
I predicted
As soon as I was shut down
It was a domino effect for everybody else so
That's the plan
Want him
To do the center
More like I want
David
Oh
Come on land
Everything is okay Alex
Except
Enjoy your money honey
Arrogant
You can have a good life
Just just stop
Go to bed
Is like what the Nazis
Patrick
Chuy's credit wants to talk a little bit more about that
Keeps calling him a Nazi
We don't have to deal with other things
You're saying they just mischaracterize you
Burgerville spread
Because I was not a
It's right next
Right
Everybody was fine
Interesting
Get Alex gone
I got banned after him I would like
Gavin McInnes paramilitary organization
Of weirdos who punch each other name in cereals
As an initiation ritual lots of public photos
Congressman
So like this thing isn't like
Good
Like that's the band
First they came for the Nazis and I did not care
Because I didn't
To kill Jews
Sometime if it were thestate doing it
Different conversation
What is the difference
Private companies
Kick Alex off and then oh my God in the aftermath the proud boys are gone
Find that track
So now Patrick does a pretty decent follow-up question
To ask about the idea
Call Dena.
Anderson Cooper Nazi in America
And they say Hitman all this other stuff goes up for me
Happened. For no reason your answer
How much is this Alex
Do you think it's it's self-inflicted by you
Versus pushes hardcore
A lot of people push but there's
Okay but that's not.
Wasn't DC last week with a run up screen.
That's what they say that would specific any major
Real quick
Music
We like
Did you have a specific name
You adopted because
You do that all the time
This is great
Sat question
Party that did that I think it's just fair for everybody
For both side
And I spoke about that yesterday was my turn to say Pappy
These are concerned
And so we went back and forth
Doritos
You're a man has your own life
You say what you say I knew it
If I was Jeffrey Dahmer
Before he died last year let's look look
Charlie Manson
They say don't view Alex Jones what is it
Because they build a strawman learning
They build a straw man
And then they don't want me to respond
Infowars.com
Boo
He's not taking into consideration
Quit smoking
Dahmer
Or Charles Manson is going to be like
Why did you eat
Kill
Sharon Tate why did you do that Sharon Tate
Look it's only part of what I said was he has let's go kill Sharon Tate
But the rest of it was
Politically an interview with Charles Manson
Was Charles Manson
Hey is there anything to help with shelter
You don't like
If you were to see me
Is that interview
Eddie would never
Wrongly accused
If you want
Have the media subjects
To like
Because the question for the things that you said what you've been apart of
Go ahead and subjective
I'm sure they would do that
Interview
Be brutal
Terrible job but hardly enough of all of the interviews that we've ever heard with Alex Jones
That one question is the best thing that anybody is done you do recognize like that Alex is able
To deflect from it
Still like a ratchet
A couple of like if you could
Actually get Alex
Questions
Drunk and acting like a
Did theirs
F****** can't one of them
Dead Nazi
You call people Nazis
All the time what is the difference
That's very difficult
Give a lot of ideas about
Why is Tucker
Why
Alex
Even if
You might be
Alex
Do you think there's at least
Alex just say
One little thing
Maybe you did something maybe it's not entirely your fault I'll take any responsibility
Some
Fault my friend is
Useless road to go down
But he does have other reasons
Question
Going to
Thereafter mean
Because
They can track back
The reboot 1776
Taken
Suppress
Contracted
But they believe George Soros
I'm the first Domino
This fridge movement
Watch Trump
Take me out
Continue
What you want okay
Content creator
I'm an entrepreneur
Hitler
Dominion Hospital Channel
We had Mark Cuban we got Magic Johnson we've got Kevin Hart
Gloria Allred
Smart
Yeah but it's marked the interviewer
But she works with the CIA
Look at but
Dude
This is gor
Did you know his read receipts
On
And then he still doesn't answer
Very rude
That is
Part of something
It's going to pay off later
There's something at the end of this episode
Think it's f****** in
Like
Hitler is a bad guy
Is the prelude
2 up
F*****-up thing at
Episode
Adam teasing a little bit
And then there's also
We're going
But we have a segment
50 clips
But one of the reasons I love God
Or a game you and I are going to have to try and figure out where
Where Alex's brain go
I just want to say is that in case anyone gets bogged down the idea Flickr
A lot of these things that are coming up for things that we discussed on podcast
So it's not really for us to be like
Alright Alex you think you're a victim blah blah blah blah blah
You think everyone calls you a Nazi
Three for no reason
I'm projecting a little bit because I listen
Podcast
I would be interested in learning more and
Hearing about like water
And I
You know I want people to know
Like we said
A lot of it does
To be Patrick bet-david asking
Do you take any sort of personal responsibility for the situation
Can you find yourself
He tries to reiterate that question
Here and
What do you know
And disagree with you who are defending you
I'm trying to ask from you is there any part of it that is self-inflicted
I want a business
We have flaws
Some of it is self-inflicted some of his Mi Cielo some of its my CMO some of its my
Chief Financial Officer
Self inflicted
What is my schedule
What is I-70
Because the mainstream media for jets
Beetle engine
Because they've created
Let the record show
Alex is the one who brings up Sandy Hook
Patrick did not bring up
My whole
Compendium
25 years
It wasn't 1% of what I've done
Within a year or two I said no idea
That's a long
As soon as I said I thought it happen
Ford
Oh my God
Crazy
And then they just
Publix 1080 goes away week set
Challenges harassing
Are houses
He won't stop
Call house
Here's the debates right I just had up as 5 years ago
It Won't Stop
Because
It's like saying
Saddam covid-19
Effusion
Regional complex
10000 * I'm
Party said that I'm done
It's the papers saying that
It's not me
Iraq
So they're pulling on the heartstrings. The family but the lawyers party
Control nation-states
Like the brexit everything else and people are waking up yet
You can't talk to this guy
Because he's so evil me so bad
There was nothing I got answer
I love that
I literally just anything to either way I think he
Like
You know that the question that was
Do you take responsibility
I kind of disagree
The reason that his brain goes directly to Sandy Hook is that him finally being like
Sandy Hook
This whole thing is my fault
Really don't understand
Is why it's not going away
No no no no no no
About so much this one going away
Teacher said something different now
You're supposed to let it go that's interesting because I think that's probably true based on his like the entirety of his career
Apologize apologize
Be able to continue sorry
There is there is something
And he brought up unprompted
That's because that's the only thing that he does
Except like
Big spiders
The question is
What is self-inflicted what do
Responsibilities for a human in a conversation about Sandy Hook
Is the media lying about what I said not what I said
Ad nauseam
Keep f****** literally said I didn't believe it at first but then I saw this
Completely synthetic event nothing happened I thought kids died there but it was all fake
He said that on his show
Literally
I meant after that
Head Robert uncle
Pretended to do an investigation of it
It's not like we had some debates initially and then I was
Happened
I keep apologizing
I keep saying I think it happen
And that's the part where there's like a kernel of Truth
Later did say like I think it did happen that's only because it was such a
What he did was so inexcusable
Which is why he's mad
He said he was but he's also
Lying about what the accusations
People are saying that the result of his coverage
Hitler
To the family
He's being assaulted and harassed
You're not staying
He keeps
Deep Purple
Actuate that
On a massive level
And furthermore
He is incapable of
Recognizing the difference
Well there's definitely that difference
Between the behavior in the event
So he thinks that people are mad at him about the
Look
I said the Sandy Hook was a false flag and I
Now I can continue calling others
Cuz it's just the events that you were mad at
The behaviorism
A pizza still an issue if you say OKC is a false flag
That's still a problem
The point
Don't see the forest for the
Patrick
Alex
Just clearly unwilling
Not happening David shorts
I love
Nbark there's nothing in that area
I'm sorry I respect that
He's a man who runs a multi-level Market
The truth from his underling
Change tactics
Alex
The idea of sensationalizing
Is that approach
Sometimes in the world is the question I'm trying to ask
Sometimes in the world of sales when I work with the people in the world of sales
There are people who sell a product in the world
What I'm selling Alex
Cool. You have to take you have to take your awareness that he's an MLM Drive
It's actually really
To start selling me on his life insurance
But I like trying to get Alex to understand
Alright
Here's what I'm selling Alex
4-bedroom 3-bathroom Corner cul-de-sac kids safety good private schools etc etc
And then I say
Underneath there's a 63% chance that they're spoiled
And you can be a billionaire
Do you ever think Hugo from just selling the idea with already makes a lot of sense
You're making me think
Are you going to let me some fictional life and you get yourself in trouble do not do you ever feel like you've done at work
In trouble
Just because
You know what sensationalize yourself
Are you sensationalizing yourself there's a big difference
So
Question public events
Boo
The
Farthest overhead I think a metaphor has ever
That metaphor was
Cruising at 30,000 ft above where Alex could under
It also so demonstrative why it's useless to
Interview a good way to
Metaphor
I know you're trying to tell me this house
The house has merits on its own
I'm interested in that house
But you're lying to me about the oil underneath it to sell the sold house
Do you think you do that ever truth
Also
One out of every 3 people who eats it
Lives forever
I just wanted an apple dude I didn't need the can I go on Apple
Alex will not stop talking about Sandy Hook also
Patrick Henry
Too much he's responding
To what Alex talks about
Fascinating to watch
Because Alex blames everybody but himself
Situation
Prozac
Things to do
Anomaly
Truth
Tell us what you think
I was going to go to happen
Share the anomaly
Assuming
Horse
Cutting off
1/10 of a billions of what I've done to Sandy Hook
50 more topics
Are you saying
And then the public question
Apologize
What I question
Apologizing always work
I mean that's sad
That's me I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings when you likes
Find for me to do
Completely destroy your house
I'm sorry that you feel bad about
Basically what he's doing
Cowardly.
Building it up I lying about what you did
He's not legally
Like in Jeopardy about the things he did that are
Truly
But that's because the statute of limitation
We've gone over right he's lying about that
Because he knows he's
Harbor legal
Trying to present it as like
The media lied about what I did and I'm sorry they did that to you
When he did that
No course you didn't
Create the idea that
Check was fake
Probably
Amplified it
And that's what he does
Original ideas
No
What is an MLM middle name now not made him a bunch of money
Or other people's ideas
He stole the Hillary for prison bumper sticker from someone else stole the idea
Stolen all of these things in order to co-opt them
How do I f*** this guy
What I'm fascinated by listening
Is that I hear the backstory
What's the name of the Doctor Who Lost
Rebecca Carley
That backstory of
Everything was going great
Like she was
Really really
Successful
Became this
This moment to broker
You know like this is what I'm hearing with Alex is that somehow everything that he's done was going great and then he
He's broken now until
As his life continues every conversation
I'm doing pretty all right but
Man
David Sandy Hook
It's Omaha
At the bar the Corner Bar is I could have been something I almost I almost made
The big-league I got it I got it covered
I had Tommy John
Just never came back
Maybe 1% of those stories you are true and the others are creating a
Hero narrative about why you aren't what you think you should be and you think other people think you should
Very cold
It's ego-driven
It's jealousy it
Lack of responsibility is all those things
To a pathetic level
Patrick wants to
To discuss the idea of Alex not being able to use social
The crippled his reach and really hurt his
So in order to facilitate
Patrick brings up that a couple years ago he lost his voice for 90 days
Condition like a polyp or something in his throat and he wasn't able to talk
And as a sales
Incredibly difficult
Use that as a metaphor for Alex to
Open up about the idea of
Speech and the ability to get your ideas
The cross
Alex not so interested in that but
What's this
Personal moment that could become a flowering of conversation
Likes
In this clip
Just to give you some context
Alex Grafton Apple
So yours that yours
Speak what do I do today
If
Start over
Here we go
Right if I can speak what do I do for today
5 billion views are God how is Alex Jones feeling today
YouTube
Not including everything else
The 16 million
ITunes Travers Auto
Oh boy
Cuz I'm out sellout
I'm Trailblazer
Projector
But we've never had more hardcore glycerin
I'm just I just believe Humanity I'm betting on him at 8.
Try to sell the public
Everybody else
The Big Dipper
That's the first
2 *
The Patrick response
Something nonsensical that Alex says
You really believe that
Which is nice
Yeah I mean that is just like
YouTube
They cut me off then cut off
Too drunk
Now I will say
I don't know if I can
If I could ever hear life is fragile and
Any other syndrome
Real quick
Which is the best way for it
Miserably through a mouthful of fruit
Alex
Kicked off social media so Patrick follows that up I asked
Do you want to get back home
Would you ever want to be
You know figure out a way to be letting you know be back on your social media platform if they never ever let you back
Are you okay with that never again
I'm Alex I'm never changing
What do you take me back when I am never changing a single why do anything
Obviously
Misrepresent everything I said.
Dorsey went on
About to go on
ABC Auto
Jones says he wants to kill the media with assault rifles
North Chicago
Jack Dorsey
It's horrible.
That's Defender
So
Offended YouTube
Confronted
Marco Rubio
The Walk of the Prescott
Jack Dorsey said oh my God
Now I can stand him
Who told you know you soon
No
People meeting telling you that now that you're going after Marco Rubio this is an opportunity for the receipt O'Banion
That were in a meeting with
Check
Joe's Auto I can't band
Alex Jones Republican
This is Dad
Elementary
Alex I know that I told you before we started recording at this
The content they were covering has the potential to be incredibly sad or incredibly hilarious
Very
Very sad
Set like
You don't
That's none
You've created
Constructed a reason why
People took action against
You did
XYZ
You've decided that the best way to
Republican cover to attack
Cuz you already painted all of your enemies
Does being left-leaning
I don't know communist socialist
Authoritarian so
Almost be like
A part of a
Training tape
How to
Interrogate Psych
Psychopaths
Sure
Look you think you constructed a great question
You think that you got something that he's going to have to answer
Psychopath
No you are just
There
If you if you listen to his answers there's so much
Green from like
Psychopath language and how you respond to like humans
Just letting him saying like
Of course I want to be let back on these
Platform
Even though you
Yes I have said many times that if they kick me off that's the right things and I
Only bored.
I don't want
I just want them to apologize to me and tell me that I'm right
Bright
Psychological thing butts
I don't actually begrudge
Patrick Bernard
Going too far down that road cuz
Way out of his depth.
Detroit
Earlier he tried to reframe the question
About
Sensationalism
Understand
And now this morning tries to
Bring back
A question he'd already asked why haven't other people
Why aren't they
Naruto
No answer
I bet used to be the main guy to watch on Fox Amanda Riley we'll go at it
And he was coming up and
He would get up and you would do it show that I was on back one time he would show this up so you don't like
And Hitler
You know and even Rush
These guys haven't been
You've been bad
Is it because they say
No I don't think that's the only thing that would cover geopolitical system
The world government
I don't care
Why is BET not effective
Baked is not a guy that they agree with Liza Limbaugh not offline
I think it's overselling
So getting the kids back to the sensationalizing
Explain more about that
In later clips
Milo is back on and I think he's the worst
Sitting in the house
History of the world Alex
Patrick's wrong about
Milos
He's actually smilo
Arella
The question is asking is one that Alex
Without
Validated
These people
Are not in trouble
The only thing you
You can fall back on his I can take me out so they can eventually take them out
And when that doesn't happen when people just like
It's your actions
Because this
That argument falls apart angle here is to be like
Dancers money
I don't make
The powers-that-be
Smart who makes who makes money whenever Hannity makes
I'll tell you what at least one or two globalist
Troutdale cuz that argument falls apart with back
Cuz he started his own
He started the blaze
But failed
He's not on Fox news or any of those platforms
Or so like the idea that
That that argument would even fall apart on further and out
You have to do some further analysis
Right
If you explain answer and not like
Do not go further with it what you're doing is
Just saying like wow the audience
I hope they can see through this
There's nowhere else to really go with it
You don't want him drunkenly storming out of the
Erin Gallagher
Is where I think
Is really getting good Dale
Zeno's
You say
Dangerous groups in this country because
But they still hate everybody because they weren't the jocks in high school
He's reading and Alex Jones quote
Still the conversation is about Alex Sensation
They use their brains to hurt people and I'm aware of them okay I see
You little rat
How can you say something like that
I remember 3gp
So he's become so successful because this
You know he's not really somebody
You'll take it even deeper
Going to jump to conclusion
You're Sensational come on oh my God
Bill Gates is the Army program on eugenics
Was ahead of Planned Parenthood
Reduce world population
Yeah but
Alex you take it
Two points for the media sitting there saying
Okay
Can hear something listen to somebody like
And you can really mess with a nightmare
Hiddenite
Tell me about it
Okay
Show that is the main human genome
Alright alright
The whole deal
Remember When
They trained Institute
They're both surprising books
For sure
Alex what is it no I'm not
The books
Alex if you know everything that you say you know
And you Potter plant why are you still alive
Well they're murdering my name their assassin
So if you were opposing the most
Powerpool
Democrat in the marketplace
Is so
Force
This is kind of my thing coming to terms with
He got so much mileage out of people thinking
The best thing for him
He's in the same way like the room
You know like
You can pretend it was a satirical farce or whatever but that's
That's real
Purposing their response people had to it in order to pretend I was doing that all along
Alex is doing the same thing and he will
Throughout this
The idea of what I was using in order to
Fly under the radar
D
Cold Springs Harbor be covered in our endgame coverage I don't want to go back in
Go over all that it's
Go back look bad if you want understand 12 hours of our day
But like
I don't know dumb
I'm throwing out very broad vague
Things to do
I got all this I got all this
When you have someone like
Bill Gates
Talking about how the population
Reduced
Not talkin about
He's not talking about putting something to vaccines
The kill everyone
He's talking about the holding capacities for resources in various
The world
How a lot of places
Hazard overburden
Population
That
Arnot
Now the other flip side of that is if you want to have a conversation about like
Treat the rest of the world like there's
Conversation is much more reasonable and much more
You know the idea that like parts of Africa they could have the amount of children that they
Hoard all of the money and he didn't have a history of stealing all their resources
Generation
There's a better conversation
I have about that
Jazz about
Bill Gates
Kill off everybody right
Mosquito drones or whatever the f*** you going
Asked a question that I sent chaliyan oculator himself
From the answer
Vaccine
The question just being like
You can f****** a naive mine
Suggest that you do not have a naive
Right
Are you taking advantage of stupid people
But that's why Alex has to come back with do you know about Cold Spring Harbor
Reasonably assured
Did the first News Talk
Doesn't know about
It's the same reason why I quit
He was losing an argument about
Chemtrails
That out because he knows that Eddie Bravo
Joe Rogan
Don't know that
Exact
Answering questions
Patrick credit for being like
Okay
Now is
Is where Alex
Dark
This is where
The interview
Because I think he recognized
End it where you point it out do you like
You're dangerous tonight Eve mine
It does lead
Alex the realized
Patrick isn't going
Go along with everything I'm saying he's already shown that maybe he's not
And now it's
Just like
Just got to preach
Until he starts preaching
F****** dark
It was a joke
Like a poison I typed rated
I thought it was a job that uses against prom
They were winning and now
Poison
The truth
Is so strong
When a big dose has the Mary a.
And so I'm just older on the globalist leave lunch
I'm ready to die
This is all gravy
Salt
They are already in the system
I thought it was a joke
An allergist doctor
Information never that guy
You think so
Yeah I know it's true
Because Humanity want to live
They're the ones doing this I started their papers
I started the program are you at why they're so afraid
You're so afraid
Got their number
Not afraid to die
So that's where you're at
If you ever get back on social media
I don't
You really don't the message
The transmission
Everything else Dallas driving
Earlier you said he wanted to get back on social media
12 quart
Rampant
How many skips does NexGard cuz it's kind of
Exactly the same as that last one
He talked about how like I've completed
My mission
Like the two people who restart the evolutionary process at the end of a movie
They're both
I have a theory about that this is a little bit dark and I apologize for it
Show reboot
I think Alex might kill him
You think so
I do
Besan I don't I'm not saying but I would be surprised if
Yeah based on the level of
Is life is a
F****** map
And not just because of
Trump political stuff
Probably going to be
Successfully sued by a number of people
Just like I said we're recording this his Paypal has been taken away his ability to process
There's a real life is going to win that custody
I don't know cuz
We have no reason to know
What's going on with
But let's
Imagine a scenario where he ends up losing custody of his children
PayPal goes away
He's not allowed on social media
Multi-level marketing scheme guy
Who's just on the outermost fringes
I think there's a decent chance that what
You doing is largely
Laying the groundwork
For him to become the next in the line of people he's talked about
On his own show
People like Andrew Breitbart
Who Alex
Lies and says was murdered
When he had a f****** heart attack cuz yeah
Already had a heart attack was way out of
Shape
June time to blowout
Yeah
The d.c. Madam
Who absolutely killed herself
4 * was murdered
By the global
All of the people
Using Larry Nichols to backup being arkancide
Yeah killed by the clintons
Gary Webb
Gooseberry
Clearly killed himself
Who Alex pretends his murder
I think that there's a
Is the propaganda
Campaign towards his
Now at the same time I reckon
You're such a massive ego
And is
Not really
Like the idea of killing yourself
The further your own narrative is
Also kind of
Evolve self-sacrifice
Because you are dead
So it does kind of
If not matching psychology
He's behaving really really scares me
It's very troubling on a certain level
That is a path I could
Could see this going down
I mean icm's self-destruct
Okay
But he knows eventually I'm going to fall down the stairs
If anything happens to
And I fell off a bridge
No matter what happens the globalist
I worry about that I'm not entirely sure if you super irresponsible
To say like that is what's going to happen
But I feel shaved
Pictures of I would never to hurt myself
From someone who is
I hope that's not the case
Ultimate
Advice to Alec
Texas
Get some help
Talk to somebody
There is help available you're hurting yourself and your kids is not okay
Despise you for real
You but your kids don't deserve
Yeah and I know that
Personalized or not
On the table for us
But he'll be irresponsible
Before us did not recognize that
He was a swinging Bachelor
I don't think I would
I would not care but his
His actions of
People who don't
Have any
There are so many people who are the human aftermath
Children
Real yourself
Okay well
And all of his children or paramilitary night
I don't know how Grand it is
Hey everybody down here
But
Because there's a
Little bit of a situation when I was trying to record this episode with Jordan
There was one clip that didn't upload
Into my eyes
Tunes where I play all the eclipse from
Unfortunately we missed
Normally
Situation where I would say
You know that's too bad we missed one
No is relevant
To talk about
Unfortunately this clip is actually a
Good Wife
The darkness
Of this album
Review
And so kind of
Be incomplete for us
To talk about this
Episode
Without
Part of it unfortunately I'm
Sitting here now adding
Pizza without Jordan
And maybe that's for the best actually because I
Jordan would never stops
This clip
But
Here it is
Alex Jones
About how he his teacher
Lick
And he needs to
Is WIC
We're going up again
Everything else Dallas driving
Everything else is
Just getting ready to make.
I got to take my legs
Is that why you never
Let's get it going
Tell me what God forever.
Chase Edwards
Dodgers a system where
Everybody's a coward sells out now this
The people that are dedicated
Nachos
Put themselves alive
You got three kids
You got pork
15 year old rights
Tipitina's
I got a 16 month old right after
60 months old
Exterminators program is
Do this thing about Fisher anyway
And that's deliberate
If I don't
So what is Alex
Clearly
To put his family
For the people
He has
Now
I don't know how to talk about
Other than to say that
Incredibly ugly any response
Terrible parenting
This is the sort of thing
That I think she
Be played
Andy's custard
Hearing speak
As you hear
He's expressing
That
My kids are going to have
Their lick
I don't know
I don't know what to say about it
Jordans
Absolutely
Play Furious.
Anyway back to the show
But in this next clip Alex
Is forced to talk about
Springs
Pizzagate
I really want you to track
And that is
The difference in the way that Alex talks about the WikiLeaks
On his own show
And in this interview with Pat
Howell's fire wait
You see nothing
I see nothing
So this whole thing with
Pizzagate Theory not digging the stuff that you have that
It was in the WikiLeaks
Pizza place in d.c.
Ferdibert ever like broken like a Mockingbird
We had it all like
The kids are going to be in the hot tub
Obama wants two hot dogs $65,000 worth
We were covering
And then they diverted off
The DC
Oh yeah that's not what was going on
So they all my God that is Billy doesn't exist
So is this a like
Juicy hotdog juicy succulent dog
And I know he talks about that tub
So willing
They might resist but they want to have fun
Like all that stuff
He's strictly speaking on this accurately presenting
She's not making the same
That he does
On broadcast
Because he knows
But he's not talking to the same people
And he has been showing the Patrick isn't going to give him
Expect
Juicy
Herobrine life
If you drive down Lawrence Avenue here in Chicago Illinois
You will pass I don't know the name of
Provider of hotdogs to the White House
Elaborate scams it's all about male prostitute
I don't know
That's crazy.
Much closer to what
The actor
Emails
Intention
Bowser Rambles about how
What I'm saying is is that
I'm dead already
Already passed the river
So
Everything I'm doing now
This is the kamikaze
People think I'm mad at you text me stuff don't despair thematic manifest
Resistance
SMS WhatsApp
Thought about
It's not about me
It's about what do we do tomorrow
Hollywood
What do we do The Gruffalo
What do we do the demo
What do we do to let them know where
Still alive
Does it mean
You know that
Thanks don't get a little messy
Grandpa
If I met
I didn't watch towards the children's
Shipping a narcotic Illinois
Grandpa were at the zoo
I'm an albatraoz
Discovery
Horse because the Matrix
Apple and Google and Facebook
Grandpa I think your phone
Bart the bear
Sweetie pie
Mark Zuckerberg
Because users dumbfuckery
Angel
We should just roll over cuz
She better sit out
Some people don't care
People
About to bring this corrupt World down
And build a new world.
Is there
Swirling in the glass no big deal Morris school okay
Who's children
My children
Children
Coronavirus
Holyshit
News
The grandiosity
Manifest
Threat to the world
Yep
Stop again
Is a confluent
And they are so afraid of him
The result channels apps
At all
And this is where he
B
Misinterpret exit
Okay
And then
And then whenever we came here it was shaped exactly like Texas right now is it
This is about who
Thinking that he's Colonel Travis
Okay
Which is hilarious a song the truth
Piece of it is that he also blasted
Who's calling
The strongest thing
Oh my God
But they knew that was
I was so pissed off
Dylan Travis wrote The Line
Almost everybody
He's a real sacrifice
Are they doing a little kid
Stop giving yourself
Play Christ
So
Remember infowar
Remember Alice
Nextspace
Happy Monday Spanish
You think what you doing right now
Yes I like
Fearless
And building a future
I wouldn't say it's Christ
Right I mean even his Judas legislative acts that nobody ever
No I bought it at 12 you don't think people back them up
Luke Mark Matthew don't think so I'm asking who's on your side right now
That's what I'm telling you
My dad that we could change the world
Buckeye
Holyshit
Insane
That is great
Set alarm kernel-mode
Paranoid delusions of grandiosity I think I've ever heard in my
Do you think you're doing is christ-like
Yes
Hydrolyzed
Saint Denis
Stepped over that one so I drew another line
Stepped over that one
I mean
The parallels with Colonel Travis a f****** real
The parallels of him being a drunk f******
Ruined
A really long time
Accidentally stumbled into being at the Alamo
Think it's very similar to Alex's accidentally being the right place
Rodger Stone
Manipulate
Over the election.
The election is
He didn't die died
He really wishes
He is a man who wishes for
That's why I'm kind of afraid of it
Yeah but that's why he
That's why I'm not
Present-day episode we noticed a couple things or Alex
Completely invalidating
Entire life
He called for federal troops
To go to the Border
Completely comfortable
Next clip
Like I could not believe
So let me flip that on you do believe in background checks
I believe the Second Amendment I think criminals or any guns regardless
But I do think what mental health other issues
Background check
Call prescription right now you're taking Prozac whatever it is some of the medication list that we have
That is either for bipolar or whatever you know things that we just talked about
Those folks can't get a gun you're okay with that
There's something 30% of women around those drugs 15% man
And
A lot of people
Don't like
Before you respect my ride
People that are on those drugs
We answered says I can make it be a killer
They should be looked at
I think if somebody has been diagnosed
Amazon those drives there should be a database and you shouldn't be a little fire
That's relevant to
But like that
He's so count to Alex's beliefs
Beauty sitting with his guidance
Anyway it's okay for a background check
Any kind of like
Regulation about guns
Is so counter to his bleached Because he believes that like
Gun registration
The exact same thing is taking away people's done
Towards
Gun control is all of the step
Yeah if you were diagnosed with a mental illness you shouldn't be able to because another piece of his narrative is the globalist
Just want to give you full size no Seas
In order to make sure you can't have guns
Because you sitting there with the guy who
Not putting up with this b*******
He's having to sort of mitigate
Come to the middle of little bit
Cuz he knows that his normal s***
Noctafly
He's drunk enough
Be at that point where it's like
Crazy
Of course crazy people shouldn't have guns
Right
Person that I would say the crazy people
To be allowed to have. You know what it is I think it's recognizing
I do believe
Crazy people
On what level
Strategy
Your principles
Problem with the government
Do you know what I would like
You can continue on
Ice cream
F******
I'm out there's a difference between a
Conversation
Televised interview
Not on television
Patrick wants to go down the road of like he's trying to get back to
To the sensationalism stuff that Alex still have
Address
You've been trying to get that
Answer
From Alex
He's not giving it
Initially I asked
What cause this is a self-inflicted you know is it something that happened is there a blind spot is there
A lot of times in business you know entrepreneurs business people have blind spot The Reckless and certain area they're replicas gambling directly
Do you think none of the blind spots for you is sometimes you get so excited
Made it in your energy like you your words that come up so fast is a brain is going a million miles an hour
Over selling something
I'll tune in
I was talking about how Anderson Cooper
AirPrint
Haralson place the CIA invasion
The Arab Spring and he's a jerk
Apologize
Satisfying
No I totally sometimes
Like you hear your rebroadcast you're like
Calculating
Ninety-nine percent of the time
How was it saying that were you okay okay
Are you home
Wow
Devastating questions coming serapis
Are you okay
Say that after I say
Said something
How did that feel things that I've been like f*** you I am out of this s***
Feel to say that shift Q
F*** you I'm out of here
Don't know why that was okay I don't know why that's okay
Show out loud
There's never a good guy
I barely want to listen to the show after we recorded night
And stuff like that
Headphones baby
I can't imagine the idea of being caught
Listening
His parents hot tub
Growth is a f****** less
Even if
Look if LeBron James told the story where he was hanging out with
Kids watching highlights of the 2017 NBA Finals at be like a little a little
At least he's not espousing racism during the game with LeBron's going to come back
Alex
Does taking responsibility only for mixing up Anderson Cooper and Tucker Carlson's name
Did he say that he called
I meant to say I called Tucker and apologize for mixing you up with 8
Cooper called
Anderson Cooper
Yeah mix
Through me for a loop when I first heard it as well
Call India
You could call
Psychic
So he's willing to take responsibility for mixing up bass
Fact
Terms of like I got the name wrong
I made a state
Not me
No no no
Here's what happened
But let me tell you what else did he tell you what else
It boy could Bush or 911
You take it a lot
Okay
Exaggerated
Do you know what double-talk is
Of course
Yeah yeah
This is 2 hours long cut out a lot of like
Just heard there's a lot of me
He goes down the wrong
Still can see what
Trying to do that
But it's kind of like
Dealing with Alex Jones this is the wrong tack
You don't like that well I'll come back to that later once I softened you I'm over here and then I'll poke over here again
Starting to slow down
Right exactly what you're talking about
Pizzagate came up earlier now it comes back up
And it is much more problematic this time around
Because Alex has just admitted that he exaggerated
Yeah
And suddenly you say
Outside
We have the Wikileaks in New York
That is exactly what we were talking about
Washington Post
No
Pizzagate
MPI code words where they use Pizza Italian food
Is it place we go look this there
Demonize house and blackout
What's going on
That's what's going on
Okay you did it again
I told you I was okay
Regenerate
You lost credibility
Nice nice nice
You screwed up
Screwed up you didn't screwed up
Wow
To what Alex is
In the room
Yeah but if you were actually responding to like
Alex literally
I'm only responding to the Washington Post New York Times reporting
Conspiracy theorist
Club
4chan having all of these posts about this job and him being like
Replay the clipping took off the internet where he's like
You know what it's
F***** up
You got to check out their menu
Exactly
So
Why is it that a giant piece of s*** is the only one who's interviewing Alex the best way because he's the only
Funny person
And has access
Never interviewed by us
Oh yeah
Behind the bastards
I could see a pretty good job of interviewing Alex
Perhaps
But you never agree to do that it
Probably seems like a really spray
You need a you need a mafia sting
Have somebody like
Bet-david to interview him
But beforehand talked
To someone like
Yeah that is
Probably the way you would ever
You need someone
Like us
Or hear other people not just.
Someone who knows
Deal
I mean I suppose
PhD
Packer
Your life story
Invalidates Alex is rhetoric
It's some point in the interview bring up your refugee
At some point bring up the fact that you had to flee a Ron
During the iraq-iran war
You are now
Bring up the fact
Become a productive member of American society
Ostensibly a success
Disagree
I think that's the wrong way to go
Conservative
As being the people who are against illegal immigration
Where
Legal immigration
That would be Alex's response
Yeah I have Patrick abs
Transcript
About people like him
And then Alex
Please explain the contacts
You said start with your purse
I mean
Not
Begin the interview
You could throw at him
April
Arrow in your quiver
But you said leave out the part where your comment
Well I'm just saying
The presentations I say
Lead with being
Well that's how you
Yeah
Burp burp
So is all this
Done better
Appreciate Patrick pushing back
On Alex's
He's telling a story about pizzagate Patrick is like
This is where you f***** up
He loved Alex was called into the principal's office
The news like
Hey look
You did something wrong
What you did was wrong
Or something
Live more about
GameStop Patrick
Is trying his best
To be like
Do you understand what you're saying
Shooting
What if you wouldn't have gone that route
What if it was just purely educational what if it was just I'm going to get here
The New York Times Washington Post
The conspiracy theorist say there's a
Is it fair to say that that I never covered that they supplies
The Washington Post New York Times
Not true
4chan
Bunch of operative
Supplied all the BS
Alex very recently
Antifa contract
With George Soros
Organizations on Fortune and has been reporting it is true
During Pizza
He didn't change
He didn't change all operative right
Great whatever
And then my report
But you have been talking about Parts Authority Sports
Pacific
Grocery store carries and cheese
Am I a hamburger
Askew
Stop harassing the Sandy Hook family
I looked at her I said lady I questioned that five years ago with other
She knows a few Russian
What the media
Told me I left
I don't want to talk about
Stainless pot
When you hear that hitting his fist on the app
He's just going to
Yeah did
This is
Hardman
Crazy
Get through already took him out of
And I have
I have tape of everything it'll prove me right
He's trying to present himself as
The victim again
Took me out of
Context
You know how that
Feel
Alex
Every single
Rape very hard to heaven
Empathy
Alex is something that I think
Super f***** up
And I didn't know with something
You might believe
This is really bad
Man versus
Right
Who's nature robot-man versus
Robot robot
Just focus on what you just said to me about
You said
I didn't bring up pizzagate
And then I started talking
Right
Fine that's kind of like you saying
Add an event guns
I just used it
So you took that story
That they started talking about
Mnu sensationalized
That is like a lady must first holyshit
Now Alex's conspiracy is that that shooting at Comet Ping Pong to happen
Best and I don't
Really appreciate that petrogen pushback on that
Whatever you want
I don't know what do you say to that other than like
Are you just going to not acknowledge reality ever only thing as the interviewer
In this case is make sure that he says specifically what
The Patrick doesn't
Worker at 8
Out-of-work actor
Set the media got to do this
It was all fake
Interviewer is today
Without realizing you
Interspecific
That shooting didn't happen
You know who the victim of that shooting was
James Oliphant
Threaten to sue Alex and got a public apology from
Yep so now he's on this
New platformer is being interviewed he said the shooting is fake
That is now James elephante standing to reopen
Consequences of because
Alex issued a public retraction
These could be
You know what's crazy though is that this is stop sounding like an a
Interview to me and started more
Sounding like a
Like
I'm taking an employee into the back to explain why they
Cleaned up the floors
Look
I don't think what you're doing is bad I think you're bad at doing
There is kind of spo2
Patrick bet-david
David's
His background is
Entrepreneur
Being sort of
Advice guy
I think that his sort of worldview and his
Is
Brenda is chi
Kind of that coaching
Yeah
Alex
How can you do what you do better
Do you understand you f***** up you don't
He doesn't understand
I think you're a great
And I really like the way you're going
However
Do you think you made some
What is your fault
What do you think you could improve
Imagine pulp I would admit to more mistakes analysis
Fucken love that guy
At this point I think of Patrick kind of recognizes that those wrote that he's been going down or kind of
Idea of the sensationalism the idea of other people
Kicked off to save
Exaggerate
Right button turns of
Actually getting anywhere with the p
ORD Sandy Hook
Alex brought up himself
Cuz apparently that's the only thing that's breaking Alex's brain right now
I think he realizes
Nothing we can do about this
Let's save it onto.
Just like hot topic
Yes Tim about college
Alex yes
Education
Burping up booze question about how much you hate College
What is your thoughts on the current occasional system
I think the total scam like Rush Limbaugh used to say
I went to college
So I was in sales
I was like 19 years old
And so I just thought it was more of an indoctrination
So real quick if you was making $100,000 in sales
As a nineteen-year-old there's a
She was working
And some sort of a Cutco MLM type he might have been a very successful
Entirely possible hundred thousand dollars as a nineteen-year-old with Noah
Credible
I think he's exaggerating
Heelys
Probably was happening
But it was some sort of
Thing like that
I don't know we only have
Information to go on
And he's a liar
Who knows exactly what he's talking
It seems like that might be
So it took many years and that's why I got up
Occasionally
That's where I stand on
Do you need me
Hard
Ace Hardware
Narrator
Raised our job
Uni School
Anything outside of stem you don't answer
The kind of what you're saying
Maybe the concern is that the big debts
Do you have a strong opinion on how you would improve it cuz I'm curious to know if there's 12
Indoctrination
Real
Today real world
Application for engineering
4culture for saez
4 jobs
Not about until they are
Patiently
Education
All of those things are political
Today
In 2018
Interesting
One of those things that he mentioned that is not inherently political enough
Even take that out of it
Just uses words
These things
The problem with education is very political
And make it about engineering
Hulcher
He says
Coach
In what it supposed to be
What are you saying
You know what you just need to go in the most
Training for jobs being a lawyer being an engineer
But the brain
Culture being part of it
Leads me to believe
You just like wow I want
I want a white Mist the apartment
Yeah when you say culture most people think like Oh you mean Humanity
Accepting
The white culture that we have
Well because
Probably
Currently colleges are brainwashing
It's because of the idea of
Plurality
And diversity
Exist
College students protested
Support
Black
Anyway
Farthest
Firmus
Evidence
Did Alex Jones
Is f****** s***
Yeah
Patrick brings up David Brock
And Alex comes up with
You don't know the guy who
Runza
Alex
But
Alex comes up with a joke
And won't let it go
Basically tortorices toilet
George Soros
Sonera
Solace globalist
It takes hundreds of millions of dollars to
Attack the First Amendment
Infiltrate the organization engagement
All sorts of Marvel activities
Absolutely traitorous individual
Is George soros's toilet
Sohu
Got it
I fully get it
I get it
Next
Awesome
Because
There is a question that a lot of people
Alex Jones
Yes and that is okay
Boxers or briefs bro
No it's about 9/11
Now I don't like to dive too deep into Alex
Super productive
Hagar's alot of other people covered it
Do that on your
I just don't like it all that
You talk a lot about 911
What do you know about
Let's talk about 9/11
Since today
Is 911
Who was really behind the 9/11 would Witcher studied over the years
And with your spoken about
I don't know who's fine
You should really know if you're the guy who
On your show you definitely presented as if you know
Do you say it is
I mean okay
About it all the time
You know exactly who's behind
You know what those terrorists this is the exact same thing as what we talked about
She has
A pitch that you'd like
We recognize the Patrick's going to ask him another question
I'm going to work I'll just say I don't know
Eventually lands on
Dick Cheney
As being sort of
But he brings up the project for a New American Century documents
Building America
Which is very unfair
Rebuilding America's defenses
Before 911
3000 people that says this
Weapons
I was more liberal
Waipouli
Then I was more of a liberal
Still didn't want to kill I delivered to that like three times because I thought that's what he said
I was more of a liberal back then
And I still don't want to kill all the most
Staples
Of course I thought like oh my God how drunk are using yet but now it's clear
Back then I was more liberal
But I also still don't
Okay so that
I want to pick it up
We got raped and the problem is it'll kill
22%
70% blocks
Cuz Arabs are a mix of the two
But we should be ready to release it and I'm like reading this
Can subpoena documents
And they're talked about killing everybody
World government
This Republic
You can
I like the idea that he sort of think that people in the Middle East are like a chocolate and vanilla swirl
Brown people obviously that's his wife was black
Elementary level
Chinese is just like a part of this place
Saudi
Project for New American Century the peanut document
Sort of a boogeyman
For the anti-rape
Part of Alex's
Yeah he made a lot of hay out of this and a lot of people who are
Sort of left-leaning Alex
Types will bring that up as
These people did 9/11
It is bad but you look at the documents f****** bad
Teaneck document is pretty shity document that does absolutely lead one to suspect that should the people who wrote
This sort of thing
Seriously
In order that they might be able to exploit a tragedy in order
Push through
That in no way proves that they
Did 9/11
But still should learn all the races a trip to the
About the rape
Proof that Cheney was
Is behind
Very easily could have been behind seriously could have had a part and not
Yeah
Because
Store things they would like to happen in order to perpetuate their agenda
Possible
YouTube video about them wanting
I have a bunch of
It's not in
Further the process of transformation
Even if it brings revolutionary change
Absent some catastrophic
Catalyzing
Like a new Pearl Harbor
Proof they did 9/11
Thousand people
I hope that ships that would be weird
Like I said some sort of
Well we had a we had a
Statistic I go back through history and we found it
Cadillac
Is the Transformer
There's a Mendoza Line
Above that
You can still go below that
People don't care
Passage
Information Systems
Becoming important focus of attack
Particularly for us enemies seeking
The short circuit
Sophisticated American
Advanced forms of biological warfare
Target
Specific genotype
May transform biological warfare from the round of terrorism
Politically useful
About
The United States
It's important
Didn't realize
One thing
The name of the document is rebuilding America's defenses
And if the entire context of the passage
Threat
That the United States
Mike Faison
In the coming years at
Technology
And malevolent actors game
Various unforeseen it
Advantages
So hypothetical
Things that could be stuff we need to protect against
As opposed to we have developed a specific bio-weapon
Sweet Leaf
Take this out of context
Which earlier in the center
Crying about other people doing today
Now
The other thing
Consideration
It's very important
Is genotype is not the same thing as race
What
Damn
But I went to Community College for a couple of years and I learned all the stem fields
Are you telling me that they didn't throw that in there
Weapons that could Target genotype
Conceivably think we should be
Be worried about someone developing
Yeah
It's not the same thing as a race specific bioweapon
According to the NIH
Strict categories exclusive an exhaustive in which each human being is
The basis of genetic characteristics
Are unattainable
Genetics
Definitive human classification system
To address the many facets
Health differ
Is almost a
Not thing
Race
Primarily exist to the social constructs
And that's the game that Alex is operating on
Yet he tries to
Use it as
Some sort of
To bolster narratives like this
None of this is to defend
None of this is.
Nothing for unfair
So
That didn't exist saying that goes specific bio-weapon
Bio weapon
Scan the color
Right right
Genetics they have like a Optics
Computer it's like drum
So you know the most rates Pacific bio-weapon is
A white guy with a gun
Is that a really specific really race specific bioweapon
So let's
Take this
Bacchus
Patrick Wilson
What do you know about 9
Alex said
I don't know I don't know who that is
Now Patrick
The follow-up question
Problematic
For Alex's
Entire
Sense of self
You make it easy sometimes these people to take shots
Some people also on the flip side say
Alex
Could have contacts on the inside with the CIA and DEA that he knows people that are feeding him stop etcetera etcetera
Is there anybody you know that on the inside of connecting you and telling you stuff because of that is true
You would have more information on 9/11
Because of the stuff you're talking about 5 billion views then
Wouldn't somebody from the inside
Who is opposing like rhinitis into somebody on the inside that's working with rum that opposes them
Somebody would contact me I like to send information to pass them to you real quick
Question for Alex which is
If you have the sources that you claim to you should know more about 9/11
Deep problem for Alex's
Groceries 5 years ago
No
Defend the country were trying to stop War I don't talk
People about what happened 18 years ago
Today's Dental
Talk about
How you doing
Talk people
You know in corporations in medias
But it's not like they're just American Patriots like I am
So I'm not like sitting there
Talking about
17 years ago
We're trying to like
How we boost the stock market how do we fix the country
How we make America come together
Why did Brianna ever was by the way
Everybody together in Glide
Peaceful
And how we make the world better place if they stick a literally
What prop
How do we make a better picture
It is not a leftist
Religious War
We want unification
They want a free market system
We want Justice
Your mission is to empower people and have them believe they're powerful
Whether Christian or Muslim or agnostic or gay or straight
To unify people around
Human victory
Definition of anon
Because
Call Ziggy
Probably could be achieved by
One of your sources telling you what happened with 911
So that's like
The answer again
He's the weakest link of this
Cuz
We need to find a way to
And then in the next press
We need to get radical Islam out-of-the-way
Right
What's your definition of radical Islam
Georgia
Is all
Islam so how do we find a way to not be war with Islam
Way of saying we need an ethnic cleansing because they're divided
I mean
Hey you combine nuclear material within the nuclear material there
Text
Weird
About language in the way that we use a euphemism to say
But if you say it directly
Everybody get
Mad at you
Well but they would give you for using that euphemistically they understood
Junior saying
Or at least like I think that Patrick would push back against
She had more of a robust understand
You might as well have stood on top of a federal f****** soapbox and said
Kill the Islamic but if you if you are someone like
I assume Patrick bet-david
Who thinks that there is a like a
A problem with radical Islam
You could hear Alex say
Radicalism
The problem there are all those terrorists
And stuff like that and not recognize that in Alex's definition
The word that is
There is no room for moderate Islam in his world so
Dangerous
Two are Beyond
Prepared and have interviews with people like him
Because you will accidentally be tricked into thinking that they're saying something
You and I both know
Alex is advocating for the elimination of a religion population
Now speakers
It's just like okay gif
An example of Defying Gravity
What's your motto
Spring of genocide
Who tried to pull that off earlier
Patrick
An interesting question about Nazis
Did Alex
Is
Stove
F****** adverse to answering
Then I think it means something I think it might be
Jordans
No this is there more than one word in it
It's probably not a date is a mic down
Here we go
Bashas the
You know a lot of times I'll say
You know he is so nice
You so kind
What you have to say about that
It says it's like a mentally ill
Go online
Knox
Ologist
So what do you think about
Nazis
Play Lost World War and
Okay babe
I think they need to be tracked based on whatever they're whatever they're doing right now in
Hey Blanca prison
Goodbye great
So what are you going to
So that your opinion is wrong
What are you doing I'm asking you
What are you doing
What do you do about knots
Probably
Because you actually are in this world
Maybe I disagree
What is Earth
What world
Am I supporting Aziz
Tell me you don't support kindness
Meraki love free market
There's no group that attacked me more than
That's why pitbulls are statement that
Because the average Nazi
Is a
Southern Poverty Law Center 80 alarm
Okay
So what we've had is
Alex asked about whether or not he supports what the Nazis support
What's the situation with jfg only walked
Flip the question
Go ahead just off the top of your head
Nazis that's got nuts
Bed bath
Of the accomplishments that the Nazi
These have made
What is their top five worst
Things that they
How you feel about Nazis
You could say genocide is that right
Actually Alex I accidentally
Sort of agrees with
Anti-communist certainly a big part of their programs was to
The Kill
You know what my first response to why don't you like Nazis influence
Aloft
And how they're it Legacy
Still tons of people who are on the street and actually right protest
Alex Jones supports and refuses to
In anyway say negative things about you know what you know what I wouldn't say my biggest problem with the Nazis
They lost
No cuz it sure seems like his biggest problem with the Nazi
Why would I talk about Nazis
I'm talking about the all right
We rebranded
So many of the people that are in
His world
Which one
Patrick
Tries
Do this again
Tries to refocus and get Alex
To actually
Answer the question which is a super easy question
People save yourself.
No not f*** them they're up crazy
Organization
Name
They're hiding under different banners
Nationalism
Even the free market but there are people who are using those terms
In order to mask their Nazism
And their white supremacy and I disavow that entirely
To make the argument that I'm making pure and that is really just about nationalism
I have a responsibility to call this out within our own ranks
It is that
You further till go in that last
That they're losers and then
Plch
Not good
It's so much worse
Seriously it's like asking me
What do you make
Alice gildea on I-45
What am I
If it's sometimes
The knot
You say you know this hit or did it back in the days in America doing the same thing
So
Give me the first five minutes you said that
First 5 minutes of duration
You want me to reply for you
Now it's
Tens of thousands of Articles of month
Never showing what I supposedly said just
This is clearly
What the Nazis did Hitler but I'm criticizing Nazi Germany
No you're not pro-hitler what you're criticizing that
You bring that up
Okay well
No I said
So you don't support what they stand for
Socialism
Yoo-hoo
I'm not
Tell me another
Check timer
When have I this is the craziness of leftist there's a double standard
To find anywhere that I support Luzerne
Let's just go through a list of Alex Jones's
Tommy Robinson very frequent Tommy Robinson is the founder of
The edl
The England Defense League
He also has
Two Nazi groups in England
So there's one very
Strong white supremacist
Not be history before he was before he was on
Stephen yaxley-lennon
Existed online
Without his
Because of those Neo-Nazi groups
That he was apart of originally
There's one
2nd Marine Le Pen
Heard
That's her
Her dad was part of the European front
VIP not be lingering group friends he was apart of
We just want to go European
Now if you want to talk about the guest that Alex's had on there's a
The bunch of them
On Red Ice Radio
Which is a literal
Nazi
Group
The does a Nazi podcast out of Europe
The photo was recently against on Red Ice Radio
He still my favorite crazy
I just imagine
Batman
Now if you look into the narratives that Alex Trebek
Overlap with
People like identity evropa
Vanguard
Even places like
There's a
Honda of overlap in
Things those
The world and would Alex Dance Force if you want to talk about concrete
You have those people
That are influencers of Alex
That are also members
Neo-Nazi organization
Now if you want to talk about the narrative
Maybe you want to talk about people
He has on like
That are specifically
Their existence is only to fight
The question
How you might say answer a yes or no question
Right so your yes or no question
Do you like Nazis
If your answer is
Now yes or no
With the question not even another step question I said
I don't like them
Take another step
Wrestle with
The fact that Alex
Stanley calls George Soros a Nazi
The collaborator when that is not
You have some sort of deflection
It look into how to use a Nazi propaganda whether it be
Already
Before that but they perpetuated very heavily
Idea that Jews commit bloodline
The idea that they poisoned the well
Those
Very deeply entrenched in Alex's narrative
Further his ideas about the globalist
Reinforced by
The
Forgery anti-semitic hoax the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Adolf Hitler used
His propaganda campaign
American Nazis like Ford
Used
And their anti Jew propaganda
Presidents dad
Right electric President's Day
I meant
Discussed in the endgame
This idea of Alex's world
Contingent on the ideas
The Rothschilds
Nathan de Rothschild
The Battle of Waterloo English
Market in order to buy
Pattern and the bottle
That Alex uses to talk about these other globalist
Conquests of countries
That's based on Rothschild
That is a Nazi propaganda film
So Alex would you ask
You challenge me
To bring up the things that make
You kind of a Nazi
There is my aunt
And then the officers all day
This is pathetic
Because because because you have that like four minutes of him refusing to answer the question
About the Nazis up and then at the end say I challenge
Like no I don't like nothing
Like that's the expensive
Then you can answer that question fortunately so many people don't know
What was that
If we had this interview with Tucker Carlson or Ash on hands
Have the answer ready
So they wouldn't be caught doing
Unprepared
It's so easy
So indicative of how much Alex
Don't believe in all of this s***
Call Aunt house
What yeah I wonder if
Interviewed Sean Hannity find out Sean Hannity
Actual Nazi beliefs
What kind of Rich Man interview
Oh yeah by the way
I think
Just listen to him
But if you watch the interview.
The David
Rolls off the tongue with Ben Shapiro
Push back this heart
He's doing it specifically
2 hours
Right
Because Alex has a lot of holes
But then also
He's asking the second
Which in this instance
During this exchange about Nazis.
Question
Alex
Fire
So they get off this topic and Alex makes
Probably the lamest
Claim I've ever
Okay
Music
Didn't Jesus play the Makaveli I don't I don't know if I'm saying Jesus's Big Boy level I'm not talk.
Straight up
The next level
What you're saying
I really want prosperity
Globalism
I want to sexual
And I am XL
Turn up okay
Control
I love God
Bebop
Bobbi Boss
What is a mutant
Rizzo price
You're so products
But I wouldn't
I sell things t-shirts books
To find myself
But that's people
Compromise
You're selling you making money
You can't be bought
What can be bought
Skellington's is only fuel
Carry out my operation
Selling fingers to fuel to carry out my operation
But you can't be pods
Yeah like that money is not
Doing good for Humanity and Wang is where I want to go and so I'll sell t-shirts books videos
Attwater location air filtration
Airforce.com to fund myself
In the past Alex's advertise for
The Israeli
Ministry of Tourism
While he was saying negative things about Israel on air
For the most high family ministry a literal cult
This is such nonsense
And right now he knows he's about to unveil on-air that he's a multi-level marketing guide
I can't I won't sell poison to
To my audience
Is
Exactly why it's point
Interview Alex
He pushed back
Exactly how he showed up
Alright I'm going to another level and it's crazy because he
F****** drunk as s*** here is not going
That penetration
He's going to say things that are super
Feeling like that Nazi
He's not going to let you understand
I love money yeah yeah cuz even as f***** up with you if you knows the cameras are on
Right so
So here's the game at the end of this interview
Like I didn't see this coming at all
This is the awesomest thing
Then you could ever do
I will give Patrick bet-david
All the credit in the world for this
I'm going to give you a wart a name
And you tell me two person
Georg little bit longer than the person that comes
That your brain is at
First one
Now
Yes I'll tell you in advance
These are not words
These are people's necks
So he's going to say people's names and then Alex's going to say the first word that comes to his mind all right I will play
The person's name
Deposit
Have you have to guess
What is Alex's response
Edward Snowden
Who do you think is going to say
Patriot
Iraq
Are you the next one
Ted Cruz
Alright
Julian Assange
Patron
Super Bowl today
Bernie Sanders
Vampire
Close
Putin
I don't I don't I don't
Probably. I don't want to
But the
He does choose
From all of our understanding of his feelings about Putin
You should be able to guess
Haha
Take a break from the negative
This next one. There's no way for me to pause it
So you just have to hear
Beto Beto is the one that's going to get pissed.
I would definitely have gotten to -1 on that one
Arabic
Criminal
Wow
Even all the legitimate complaints he could maybe have
Indicate your brain not operating on a really high level
Here's the next one
Bill Gates
You might be able to get this one too
Jealous
Part of the globalist plan but perhaps not
4 - 4 no maybe
Elon Musk
You know what
Eugenicist
Scared man
So far
Self-destructive
LeBron James
Oh no
I don't think that girl
Not much not much better
That's code that zip code
Also by the way
Interesting because
Patrick bet-david
Accidentally psychoanalysis his response
Like that's racist
You're getting racist
Colin Kaepernick
What do you think
I quit this game I'm going to retire with the Warriors record in history actually don't care
Trader
Shockingly
No one else labeled
All the people before that
But also one of the reasons the phaedo is most
Irrelevant Alex's
He is someone who is standing up and saying
That
The police are killing black people
And that is unacceptable
Did Alex word compartmentalize Beto into part of his brain deals with I am racing
Right so
You're the next one
You might be able to get this one
Steve Bannon
Patriots
Trader Trader Trader personally
Text to Alex okay
I think you stopped keeping score
David Brock
Owner
So I'm not going to go away
Vampire vampire
Hillary Clinton
Okay
He's going to I'm going to go with
Amigos like a vampire
Or something like that
Like a level above like Serranos
Hillary Clinton
To give you half
Okay fine
-4 1/2 Rock Obama
Just a vampire
For a third time
Really don't want to say
The r word
You know what I'm just going to stick with vampire let's go then
I'mma tell you right now.
Make this respect
Bush
He doesn't specify which bush
But I would
I've narrowed it down to
Let me give you my thoughts on
Could be traitor because he does want to say vampire because
Is the bush isn't like
Part of the globe
Not like the same part of the Lego no no no no
Okay
Because now the reason that I was going to go with vampire in the first place
Cuz I feel like at this point
He is lazy in those two
Maxim
Vampire
My favorite thing we've ever done
Trump
This is again
He's the obvious answer is like Patriot
But now I want it
To be like
He's got to step it up a bit
I'm just going to go with
Okay is there anyway
No no
Okay I'm going to go with baby daddy
Okay interesting
I got like
Like I got
You're crazy
Text LOL
You say next level
Next level
Trouble
Elaborate would invite
The real freaking day of my God knows it
All clear
He's probably Emily wants progress
He is one of just he's alright everything these
I guess they call that deliver
Crumbs to deliver
We've already seen it
Already seen everything suppressor
Flowers
Everything's waiting right
What is Moses
Which kind of leads
Believe that the Promised Land
Feel that you're bi
Being lead
Out of Egypt
The things that have been happening
Thank you sayings
There's only one
Especially especially if you are a
And your ideas that you've brought grass
There's only one thing
That he is made far more popular
Ever was
Beforehand
King Sooper Pharmacy
Fat bombs
It's f***** up
Expected
Accidentally revealed
Doesn't realize what he's
Alex's brain goes there is no sacrilege
A man also
It doesn't disturb his to this interview that he doesn't like
Demand Alex
Specifically like what do you mean by hold is
You're saying
Either deliver
He's going to lead us from what
Alex
Into what
Says that Trump is next level and then
Patrick
I need to make clear that all of these other one
There was no explanation
Cut it off after he said vampire
That was the only one that he's like
What do you mean
So
But that's not
Good
No
Being alive
No it was really fun and really ever happen
Alex
The only thing that happens after this is Patrick bet-david
We've talked to him you guys get to make your own decision
And throws it out to
To the end this is Alex's lamp
You have to
Humanity
Do that everything else
So that's it.
You guys a question over and over again
Is because I don't feel
I've already been around
That's scary
Cuz I'm not busy
Shut up
FaceTime
Paradox
Sure
Okay
Cool call Rich Brazil yourself to be a
Not apology
Very racist religious zealot
Why are you surprised the platforms don't want you on
When did we've already established that you exaggerate stuff
Sensationalized
And you're very clearly as Patrick
You are dangerous to naive mine
So
Yep and that's why I have that sort of little piece of my brain that thinks this
Absolutely needs help
Yeah and that's why it's really hard and I don't want to be in the present all that much because
In the same way that I resist talking about project
Clearly likes is manifesting
Like this is yeah you need
To go you need to be hospitalized
I think we're getting to a point with Alex in 2018 where it's like
This isn't funny
This is this is
The crisis and the fact that no one is helping him
Is
Like a disaster
The ideas
Patrick bet-david
Allowed this out
Is kind of like I understand where you're coming from you want more
But it's an irresponsible
Nothing in terms of Alex's mental
This is a disservice to
The fact that his dad is an HR
Head
And doesn't tell him
I need to lock you up
Yeah you need to go to hospital
Yeah
Owen Shroyer
It doesn't say
You need help
The fact that David Knight is been there for this long
Deterioration
It isn't like
You need help
The fact that Rodger Stone
Isn't staying
You need
Memes with no one around him is
Is recognizing
Very clear sign
Did he is becoming a danger to his own
Recognizing it and realizing that it's
The best thing they can
Make better for Rodger Stone than / Alex
Maybe for Rodger
Yeah maybe
No
I don't know what that sprayer
I'm just actually around here
Responsibility
Take care of him and
Is their own aisle
You're an adult all that stuff
Testing signs of like
This is a breakdown
This
Is this interview is like is hilarious as it is at 4
Like it's it's a it's a clear indication of it
Deteriorating
Deteriorating mental state
Continue down
Road
Is liquid
Forehead people Center
Because there were people around her who cares
Yeah
Suggested the same thing is that so many people around her also invested in
Getting her and her flame out
Undeniable
Self-destructive tendencies
Are going to
Person
We care about anyone around Alex Jones
I beg of Thee
Do what you need to do
Cuz the next
Couple months
After this
Don't look
Good
Especially
Coordinate with the aftermath
We don't have any idea
The idea that business
He was before he introduced
The MLM scheme
Before he's kicked off the
Payment process
Defected
Was
It reads
To believe that
It's going to get worse
You have a responsibility
Gift for kids
One of them is under two years of age
This is not okay on a human level
I hate to be preaching
But these people
Disservice
To the world and to other people
How do you Broach that subject
When you put
I get that I mean like even for themselves
If you are Owen Shroyer
You can watch that and say
Well he's just defending what I believe it
Thrones
Jaime Lannister
Beaverton player
Or whatever
Be whatever you need to be
Mythology around it if
You need to
Owen Shroyer is the Young Gun
He can create
Some sort of idea in his mind that I'm pure in
Alex
Is
He's lost his way
He's a danger to
People around him
I will do what I need to
To do as much as I
To do
To make things okay
Like what do they see in that interview like we see was obvious
No I mean a I think even if you take the content out of it
The presentation
Clear aspect
But I'm ready
When you need to
Let's say someone who I philosophically a mostly inline
Let's heater or Michael Brook
Yeah I saw an interview
Like this with them and they were talking about like socialism
Brother talking about the diversity
Equality and they were presenting themselves like that I would say
Get them to a f****** hops
They are okay
They're going to her
Weather in through an accident or their own hand
It's not okay
What I would like today
Is that
We have all the evidence
Did Alex Jones
Is going down
The deepest darkest path
There is available
Yeah I think the Goldwater rule is thrown out the window after the
We don't have any professional response
People who need psychiatrist
Which gives us a perspective
Me the psychiatrist
Hillcrest Estates Pacific
What the problem is
There is a f****** problem specifically what the problem is
It is big
No
I don't pray for Redemption
The only thing I hold out hope for
Where is Alex Jones
So he can be there for
Because that's really the only thing that matters
To us
It doesn't matter to us in a real way
Write the reasons that it matters
You don't deserve
They don't deserve whatever is going
Happened next
Dim Alex's
Bizarre I'm going to blow up and
Kill the New World Order near right right right
Cuz when he got kicked off of
Stuff his immediate response was
Go f*** with people in the streets
I'm going to go to washing
You going to escalate more
When I was
My family was in
Think about how much better a comedian.
It will be because
Is there
They were born in the face
Family with the Coco
Leader I've seen Rex doesn't have much jobs
I don't know maybe we're going a little overboard
Except there wasn't
It does come off a little bit I think
If possible for some
Me being like
Grandstand
I don't know all of the coverage of like new
Media Matters wasn't like
More like Alex Jones reveals again why he needs psychiatric help Lego
We all just
If we all just let all of our other stuff go like we've already proved you're a f****** races
Now we need to get everybody on board with you going and see
Somebody wanted
I always liked battle rap
When I was younger
And stuff like that
And always
Kind of like
When there
Well laid out
Personal
There's there's a lot of examples
But I always thought
The most potent
Diss track
Ever heard
Was Ms Grimm
Is the Book of Daniel
When you wrote this
About MF Doom
And how am I doing
Lost his way
Right
The track that you'd made after you've gotten out of prison
And you made it with the Monster Island czars
That were their old crew when they were coming up
And the entire District isn't like you suck
It's all
I love you
Why did you do this to ya
Yes
One of them
Doom Song
He talked about like how are you
It was part of a group
Called me jacinta
Like making fun of m i c
Everett
And the whole song
Is just a laying out of their history
About how like
I thought you gross
I would take a bullet
Why would you ever
And in the end of the song
Home home
Yeah I love you
Prodigal Son
Much more
Like a disc
Then just like
You suck
Yeah
That's the spirit I want to come to LA
Not that I love you
But you need help
I'm with you
Home home
Anyway that's the only way to wrap up the show
Never acknowledged right. Com
Knowledge underscore fight on Twitter Facebook we are on there with a group called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Tell your mother
Downloads
Support
To go home and tell your
Your brilliance
Very exciting time
I really appreciate it
Support
Subscribe to view all that good
Stop indeed but Dan before we go
It's hard to be sympathetic for Alex
Because there's one piece of information that you
What is that
Audi
Thanks for holding
Alex