Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Have a conversation
What's the
My friend
Is that I know a lot about Infowars and Alex Jones in
In particular
And therein lies the rub
Where's the fun of this show
Back
The red wine
Cuz I pointed out that's what I
Jones is
Is the actual Manufacturing
Is the name of the gnarly head
He puts his head in
Scrapes
Using the weight of his head he squeezes it down
That's why all the time
Too much grape acidity
Inside a little piece of the grape skin out
If you're going to be covering
B Thursday March
9th episode of The Alex Jones Show
We're going to
The ups and downs the whirligigs and all that
But first
I'd like to give a couple of
Shoutouts
You will not be cover
Alright from the Thursday episode
It ended with the
Special Report from Batman
Creeper to the shadow
Because
First of all
We were texting about the
On Thursday
Those like I think
Talk about
That I realized
Only
Flight 1
He might talk
Possibly
Also he still has not put up that picture
Still the picture is still on the the ground and his man cave I was hoping that I would turn it on
The picture will be up at
He definitely listen
Eva is
The pictures
Like are we doing a reverse
Dorian Gray gets older and the picture gets younger nobody
Haircut
It's unfortunate because him with really short hair
Makes it clear like how crazy Muppet
Google Eid Natok
Ridiculous
Pretty pretty long-ass
Pretty long.
Celebrity looks like short hair
Yeah
His report is all about
Vaccine
And we don't need to go into
We will actually have to go into it because that is now the predominant narrative
On Alex's show
They're terrible
Diseases and we need to have those otherwise
Another pharmaceutical company
I won't make the money
Slightly different than his
Well
Need to listen to this show
Rapport needs Elizabeth put up a picture of a shout-out to Portugal man
Never heard of that Alex is furious
American Girl music video
Show themselves burning a copy of an Infowars newspaper
That's pretty great Alex
Amanda looks like
Was he wearing a hat okay well that's all I needed to know whether or not
Wear a hat
Yeah and he's like all the Indians know I'm awesome be in the streets
Thank me
Oh man
I'm assuming if you did go to India he would be
Absolutely
This is something that needs to be pointed out in the last
The f****** Overdrive
Okay almost everyday is putting out like our lungs
Specials after the episode
He's putting out late night with Alex
Like FDR's Fireside Chats if Ser were a raving f****** lunatic and also
DJ diesel
Before he was doing Monday through
Friday
The three hours
The first three hours of the show and then he put out
The special two hours Sunday show every week
This week
He put out a Saturday
And I wanted to go over to miss episode but
It's not f****** worth it
It's okay
But it goes back to what I'm telling you about the vaccine
So we're just we're just all on the vaccine
Is going on currently
But vaccine
It's too much news to cover but it's not news and it's nothing
Right it's like I listen
Then
I need start
I like
Hockley showing
Hey
IMDb
This is what specific theories cuz he does go into his
He's just like a insert from a vaccine music
It says it will give you diabetes
I pulled up the insert and I read it and it's like it just has a laundry list of side effects
Theoretically
It is
More research into you find that it's basically that's
A catch-all
Kind of thing
But there was a discredited
Study from
Sixties Okay so
It doesn't actually give you diabetes because that doesn't make a goddamn liquor
Be safe they put on there
Give you diabetes
Great my understand
Fantastic
Indicate
Of course
That's not even have diabetes
Work
Nope
Does Alex know what
I think he has the broad Strokes
It has to do with sugar
I think that's
Where he's at
He's afraid of it so he has
Filled with insulin
In case he gets it
There's always doesn't look like
He's just going
Buckwild on this
I get it
You got to be afraid of something
A lot of the news that he's pitching is stale and there's
But it's looking real bad for
Looking real bad for a lot of these dudes rogerstone probably in trouble
Jones are
The best friend
Yeah that's I don't know if we can hang out
Finally look up
The the
Tattoos
Send Rodger Stone has been
And wow
Do you know what his
Quote on it is
I don't remember
He has this line he uses
To pick up girls
The only guy with a dick in front
Dick on back
Jesus yeah right
Classy guy left legs
To spontaneously
Is the pressure
To keep Rising on
So he blows
Himself up
Call man
Keeps on
Angry
Racist
Horrible person
Under under extreme
Stress
Maybe he blows his brains out well no I mean
Just recently under all this stress he ended up accidentally admitting
To WikiLeaks
So you're member whenever Hillary and Bill had that didn't they kill a guy that that Garden
Vince Foster
But
Rodger Stone
How many great books are going to read about how Trump and Putin assassinated
Broomall in the pot mix it up and we got some great conspiracy theory we got globalist
Episode today is a little bit all over the place I'll be honest
A lot of things that are sort of
A little bit
One of them today we're going to be talking about a bit is race
There's a good bit of race
Lies
The show
With
He gives a shout-out to our friend Rappaport
Right
Goes into
And insane rants
It's really good
JustBats
Great
The few people actually listen to it like
Midnight if I'm still up I'm doing work at the run for Dolly
Volunteering
You get her into that tent
I don't know why I'm volunteering that
Fairway
My grandma
Beautiful woman before she was soft killed by the globalist
That's what happened
Talking Alex you're getting control myself
When he said that I could not have been more excited
Alex getting so mad
Calm
Is
I'm just excited to know that he thinks
Emotions are a
Brent Alex entirely
I'm not I'm not broke ass Alex
Whenever whatever I'm just slightly mad I turn into a duck
You know I'm pissed off
Because it's so ridiculously obvious
Demonic
Christian slug did not see that coming
Ramos Ramos
House of world
Social engineering
I think we should eventually work up a Supercut of people being on
You can't sit with me at lunch
Dermotic
I've studied all these people
I know Donald Trump actually wants a giant middle class
Off of what they stand for not what color they are
Ecology
Entire universe different and better
I know you
Social engineering
That is not a Martin Luther King
Yeah I don't I don't know
Wikiquote
Documentation on Martin Luther King
It's been in the white paper
Absolutely
Phasing out Humanity I've read
4 books
I have ready at all at all
He has to say that
What is gumbo
Absolutely
Super run
Books
Social engineering books
Justmaiko
Seawell's
I want to know
He's about to lose it
Okay
Can take a sip of wine
Some good old-fashioned
Dumb down population
A perfect person but
I like life
I like Hospitality I like good
Miami primitive
Darling
Modern scumbag
Fundamental
He said how could anyone be nasty
Do you want to drink
Absolutely stopped their heads
I want to see the spirit rise up
A big joke out of the fact that I get to stop
The persecution of our species
If you don't have it
I love it
Screaming about empathy
When everything
Over the course of this show is bene
Glaring lack of a
I'm such a big
Fan of him revealing weird shaped like
No higher intelligence
Modern scumbag
Cars
Take your women
He's like my lawyer
In general.
I'm no big city globalist
But to be fair I think when he says that I'm a caveman
They're calling him
I think it's Buzz Marketing for his bone tails
I think that the bone pills not sold all that well
Baby cuz their bones
Eddie introduced that new
Anti mold product
In the middle of the week
Like a douche
I don't know
Infowars
So
In the middle of roof
No vaginas are pencil Mexico
In the middle of the week he's got like all these plates spinning in terms of like
All this Russian
Stuff is b*******
The Wikileaks new Vault 7
On everything
No no documents
That I've seen
Have anything to do with WikiLeaks
Revealing that they want to break you
Venues on civilians
Probable
Not prove
Yeah
You got to listen everything else I say because I'm right all the time
He spends an hour
Of his show
Pitching this new anti-gay East
Anti mold products
He has his weird doctor doctor group come in
Fake he comes in and also looks like a surfboard doctor
Doctor bro
Tire hour of the f****** shows
Yuri
You're hurting
How do you hatch a product for an hour
Just repeat a bunch
Stuff about how the globalist
They're putting fungus in the air in
Just like that one time just be like
Is this you or know I'm covered in mold
You're going to need our new pill
Basically do
Yeah okay I mean it's not far off
Full like
Chill
For a product
Wework
This way to
He's always been a huckster he's always been like this
And it's never been
Scuttle
What does Super male Vitality on the line
10:30
The one that I remember
Nonsense that I remember seeing as you was talking to some lady on the phone super female vitality
Daddy is like
I don't understand
That at all
But
Just a female by allowing Alex
Well I assume it's a fake call from like one of those serve
Or friend of his
Employee calling from the other room
Poor employees pretty hard on this episode is Paul Ryan
His health care plan
Sucks
Greek
Is issue is
Ram
Paul has a better plan
Rid of healthcare burn down Hospital
It's a lot like when the Nazi
He's burned all the books
Rand Paul wants to make sure that we can't
Yeah we have the votes to repeal now
Which is
Brilliant
Because you already see how United
Quickly they will get a replacement health care bill totally agree on something
They'll replace
It'll take only about a month or so
Not
All of the years
All of the years they could have been
Developing a healthcare plan to compete with Obamacare
They did
Yaldabaoth
Is Bill with a photocopier
Here's some thoughts
SNL's probably done like a
Right
I split them in half and they just argue with each other
You're right
And then
Power presentation
V
Sociopath
If we could harness just for one second
Like
We used him
That is exactly what I want to go on TV and say
I don't know I feel I feel like the blowback from yelling like that is pretty
Credit
He needs to
F****** sacrificed himself so that all of us can live
I don't I don't really disagree with that
Mad about you
This keeps coming back to this team that Alex has it
Projection
Will you put it on people
Feel like
You know you what your alt are you faking election rules lisping and you read one of these books I've read them all you think you're better than me
Paul Ryan
Rockingham and ignore
Petro
Is it people who act
Can we listen and engaged
You talkin about
Dirty
Absolutely
I do like how he really like
Couple of times
He was really close to saying
This isn't better than Obamacare
He just
Can't do it
Bring himself to say
They
Thought of a plan that is even worse than the garbage plan we hate
Did slip and say it would be like outside of his philosophy
Cuz if he said it's worse than Obamacare you could easily cover that and be like
I expect more
Who's going to be
This is worse
It is worth
You gone too far
I will try to come up with an Alex Jones
Metaphor which is the concern
The rest of the clip is where Alex says one of his big thing
Which is claimed that someone who disagrees with is an enemy of
Comment
Toronto Congress
He's a bigger enemy
Hillary Clinton he is the enemy of the American people
Call Ryan
Eddie Munster
Anatomy of the American people
I don't want you to say that cuz I don't like that phrase
I really think the enemy of the people
And stuff like that is a really dangerous thing to do
It's very much
Dictators do
But also
If you're doing something that is going to lead to the deaths of
Thousands upon thousands upon
Doesn't feel like you were an enemy of those people
I think you wanted
Look on was never on the people side
He was on something that you can express
Using that verb
I know it's a fine point to make but I think that in the same way that when Trump says
Fake media is enemy of the people
This place where it's really extreme other I don't like that
Fake media is not the enemy that people because fake media is not murdering thousands
What Paul Ryan is doing
Make no mistake
Is murder
Gentlemen I do believe
That it is 100% murder
We can agree
Upon thousands
The people that died
For Taxco
We can't agree on the substance
Agree to disagree on the language
But I think the more important thing that I want to bring up
Is that Alex Jones
Always
Talks about how
People call other people racist
In a manipulative trick to gain power over them
And then he calls people the enemy of America
People
In order to gain power
Point out that apocracy
I think it's probably more important than my little
Quibble about I don't like spinach
I don't like that
That Yusuf
Anime eyes in people is really bad
Another
Or he protects his own blog
Is Avenues
Get to the internet
Killswitch
Infowars.com
The show
He's like it's in the news
You don't store say anything
There have been repeated instances of people sending you
Prank messages
That you end up reporting as the news which is fantastic
Paul Joseph Watson
VMware open itself or multiple
Damn thing
It ruined all of your credibility
So when you're reporting something and no one else is there's a reason
It's because you
Don't
Have journalistic
You don't have an editorial process
So you just put up
Well I mean
It is something that's repeatedly source
From his sources
Or from themselves
Who have never revealed themselves
Ever
I guess
Dr. Steve pieczenik
And Jesse James
Who is adopted
Who may or may not be.
I believe that
Next clip
Let's see what we got going
Just a nice fear tactic
Pics about liberalism
To get islamophobia
Misogyny
The last maybe 45 seconds
Hateable way
Understudies
I hate yourself
I don't hate you
So that's not how anything
That's incredibly stupid
I don't think anybody is
Recruiting people
Nurturing
Feelings that already exist
Send some people
Or making it okay
Pretty before already
Brands at a very young age
Not feel like they're f****** weirdo
Also
Hey
Let's take a step back
Well I think
We all know
Women go through the change of life
You're no longer a woman that's what we're not that's a No-No absolutely
Oregon
Take it out
It's absurd
To say that that is the root of
What's
Being a woman is
It's
More or turning women into baby Factory
Supposed to people
That's true
That's what is ultimately kind of
It is not that women have any age
Empty at all on their own
Baby Phat
Is there there
To push out kids
And be quiet
Things lost in the shuffle but I also don't think that
Women's studies classes
Text Manda hate yourself and roll over to Gizmo
Now we're going to
Stop drop and roll anytime in Islamic man walks
To the Rogue 101 is that like
Just feminist Theory
Georgia O'Keeffe
Paintings what-have-you
Second-level is
Just be cool with Muslims cutting off your clitoris
That's Victaulic programs as a dumb idea
But you're much like Alex going to take what I'm saying and contact
Any of that
Our national pulling clips from our own making fun of our cell
Bottle episode
Is that
He's never really been to college
So
He's never been to college he went
Two junior college for a little bit and dropped out
Experience what real colleges are like
He's never
Avenue kids are old enough to be in college at this point
I don't think he has any real world
Experience with what
Campuses are you just read
It's pure propaganda liberalism taking over colleges
He clearly doesn't read articles that he talks about do you just seems like
Campus activism and he thinks that
Is Terrorism
It's it's
Completely insane
You know that's living in a bubble you you actually do make a really
A really good point
Even though he lives in Austin
Beer
Multiple college campuses
The only way he get that information
Is through that
Fart Town
Yeah that kind of propaganda
I bet
Breitbart
Right
Listen to the world and it's
Tragically flawed
Yeah they do window he's looking out
Is covered in dirt
And he doesn't realize he's not getting of you of
The landscape
Instead of white
White wine suck
Speaking about Focus Alex Jones has laser focus
Alright
Wants to take down f****** Bill Gates
Cuz he's a eugenicist
Okay
Evil and wants to
To kill all the third world populations
That is
That's a super villain
Absolutely
What is fascinating
Back when I used to be a little bit more Craigslist
Eye exam using that
I didn't believe them but I was one of my big reasons for it is like
What I'm doing is essentially making the world more interesting
Cuz I don't really believe this but I entertained the premise as a possibility
Then if you know it's not that I'm just going to work everyday living my life
Yeah
There's a
A hidden enemy behind every door
A superhero movie narrative go on behind the scenes
When you're seven anywhere like you know what
I'm actually at
Secret Ninja
And I'm just waiting
For the opportunity to show my
That was Alex
And I like the movie Surf Ninja
Really love the movie surf
It's not a good movie
It's one of Leslie Nielsen's last movies
Who was great
I bet his act. Sort of stale
I do want to save it like coming out the other end of that sort of dabbling into
Conspiracies
I'm much more comfortable now
That I was that
It is interesting to me how
That is the
A sensible idea behind it is that you're making
The WorldMark
To me that is
Fake order
Is more interesting
Because
The world is in Memphis
Just saying if you just see how none of it makes any goddamn sense
Instead of
Instead of being you know
Adam Radioactive
Epitope exploding all over the
You hit the nail on the head is more comfortable then
Except
Cons of chaotic and
These in the world that all have their own interest
And the rubbing into each other over and over again
But it
Some
Crazy crypto group
That is pulling all the strings
More
It's somehow more comforting to think that there's an alien
Civilization that can
Can shoot an asteroid at
Time for no reason with nobody
The world just might explode because that's how asteroid
Yeah like
Maybe one of them
I'm just lands on Earth
There's no Rhyme or Reason for it that's just the universe we live in
Instead of
There's always somebody app
What rejecting
Chaos and Randomness gives you a sense
The power
In some ways because at least
Everything that happens isn't
Adjust the Victor will
Complete coincidence
It gives you some sense of power over your own destiny
But then on top of that.
These particular version that Alex cell
Like with the globalist and with all this
Worldwide
Con job that's going on
It's a sense of
Having some
Power button
Within
Powerless
So it's
Of everybody else
Yet at least
You're aware that everybody else is at
Are you get to yell at everyone else
You stupid
Michaela
It's incredibly sad
But I
Bill Gates trying to kill us
Cept
AI
Ferrari overpowering
Resistant or becoming immune to it
Publix level resistance
Because the ones in charge are so cowardly so wicked so evil
I understand there's a good chance they're going to lose
Emergency escape ships
Underground bunkers I mean big facility
Yeah you are that's how I would do it
With a bunch of demons
Hell no
So yeah that's
That's fun
What are you got there what do you want
Did you take her already overcoming Nai
He thinks AI has already reached the top and
Or are you
Haley Joel Osment
Coward in the globalist
Or or resistant to diseases
Does he think that
Diseases disappeared not vaccine
We're all just immune to smallpox weird nootropics
City sales
As we all know smallpox
A hundred percent
I bet she said that word for word
Totally Alex is really good at quota table
Nope
She said
Was essentially
That all of these people who are spreading these can
Conspiracies
All this negative
The end the fact of it is
People dying
Because it's a lot of if enough people
Get on this anti-vax
Train
And outlaws
Populations will die
Ancient diseases back to our modern-day
You guys remember how all your friends didn't
Smallpox
Yeah another
So that's what I'm saying is real consequences
Yeah it's also kind of a threat
Right
She's pointing up
This is a threat you're threatening
Human Bean
More like she telling you you're the threat
As opposed to she is to you
So it's wildly
Open why would that threat make any sense
Talking
A lot of you will die
Why is that
How does that make sense
As a threat to him
Shut your mouth
Conspiracy theorist is it
They're going to
Cast
But isn't that the whole thing that he's saying they're going to do anyways
I don't know
Don't stop talking about the vaccines were going to give you a b******
Melinda Gates
Yeah
Turn on wetwork about Melinda Gates
Wetworks
Super female vitality
What
It's like the premise that Bill Gates wants to kill people off with vaccines
Is flawed
Crema just
The premise it has it has some good
It's one of those another episode I just don't think we have the
To do it today
I do think
Critique of him
Is built on the craziest found
Can I get into that but someday is wrong is a lot of other
It is
You know whatever
Since we are paid by Soros
He did tell us to go after other billion
Right
Gave us our marching
Define Don, we will we will
Just indicate the show at no cost
Website
Not a good deal
But
Idzik in terms of the theories that he has
There are ones
I don't know how you came up with
And those ones are like
I can see what you're misinterpreting
I'm saying that this Bill Gates one is that
Catch I can see why
You are
Misunderstanding this
Not like
Is holcroft
He has to know that he's
Misrepresent
This comes back to another like one of our arguments
I think my feelings on it is a lot of the time you have
If you are a complete
Gutter repair
You could
Interpret
I could definitely see that
Because here's the thing that he is always
Talking about
They exist
Exactly you're always talking
Melinda Gates speech is not too
It's to Alex Jones
Yeah when she says anything that involves
And then a closet
No consequences
The consequences are always
Drawn to him directly to Alex
Directly to that man
So I can see him not like
Purposely
It's possible
Oh well who cares
Alex Jones is really only interested in talking about you know
Therapist
No that's not the case he also wants to talk about pop culture celebrity women
That's always a good
Here's the part of the show where Alex Jones
Trucks a little bit
Out-of-school maybe a little bit I don't know
It is about our old friend
Katy Perry
Non go to war with Katy Perry
Witchcraft
I just thought
Ancient Battlefield with nuns
Carrying Shields and swords and Katy Perry dressed as a valkyrie from
Whatever dumb videos just standing there
Katy Perry vs. nuns
No she wanted to buy like an old nunnery
I like this is not a worry in LA
Because of
Some of her
Dubious religious
They don't want to sell it to her
There's a conflict going on about that
So just like a property 2
Basically
I don't know I don't know all the details
One final dance off
In order to pay off
A Golden Globe
I don't
I don't know if they still live there or if it's owned by the Archdiocese
B u b b
From them
End of the conflict about it because it
In the past
She has an interview years ago where she said that you wanted to be a Christian artist
I initially when she was younger but there's no it wasn't marketable at you couldn't be
Successful
Hey so she said she went to pop music
If you freeze it is selling her soul to the devil
Which is
Sort of a creative flourish
Yeah
But people take meth
Seems like
She just said
That she wanted
Christian nonsense
As a good business
Decision
She didn't
Yeah so that's why they're not telling her no
But she actually sold her soul to the devil
1930s Blues
No
No one has lost their head in any of her songs
I still really like you right now
Nobody's had their head cut off by train girls I like most
Slipper socks
I think a more accurate
I can see why you want her to buy the
A more accurate sort of version of it
I would be like
Lyric
From
Don't let me get me
She has discovered your weird
Popstar
The big record
And told me you'll be a popstar all you have to do is change everything
You are
That's sort of amor that really touched
Hello I just remembered absolutely but I think it's a more accurate version anime
I think it's a compelling narrative mostly be
Because she used to be
Christian artists
And her real name is Kate Hudson
And as you can't go by that
And Grammys
Thoughts about her
Spell out the specific was a Christian music
Decided to dress up
Yeah
He has he has more thoughts about the
He's going to get into
Some witchcraft stuff
I'll break down a little bit further
When we get
He's just going to stop
From there
Let's talk about this together
Fairies for Lady Gaga
Also podcast say that every time I talk about Katy Perry
Or Lady Gaga
I do it a lot
Katy Perry Lady Gaga
All the time
People think I'm the lunatic
Oh man what are we going to get rainbow snatch recording
She might be on the bench
Use not that she's not.
The last week or so
I'm making up
Watch the Super Bowl events are you watch the MTV
They are chopped everything from classical Satanism black magic
Egyptian occultic stop it just runs the gamut
I've covered the only person ever sneak into Bohemian Grove
Time to get out the photos without being arrested
I'd also like to again remind everyone look into the real story of that is not at all
Also I really love the
The Superbowl show do you remember the one where Alec
Aleister Crowley did it
Yeah
Was there cuz
I don't know I don't know
Pink Eminem
Alright alright you got it
I like I like how is witchcraft
Whatever you believe
Witchcraft is real
Sure that's his leg
Like how Neil deGrasse Tyson whether or not you believe it
Sodas witchcraft
Apparently universal truth
But witchcraft
They're witches
I mean like if you want
People for it if you want to look into the history of satanic
Panic and like how much danger it damage
I don't know who cares what happens over and over throughout history
We just keep getting scared of demonic forces
And it just makes us to Portable thing
You go back to like
Tons of
Cases of what was the McMartin
School case
Does happen
Mental
16 years ago
All of that
My uncle might be a part of that
My uncle
He just had religious ideas about psychiatrist
Haywood tractor
It's pretty hardcore
I know
And so
Yep he's a preacher show
Long pause
Is fully
Aware
Of what she's doing and what she's up to it that you supposedly get power
In this world
Imagine
Nationalism
Christian Roots of Europe's bad I mean whoa
Bassinet
The devil
Morningstar
Franklin
Pope Francis is the devil
According to Alex Jones
Pope Francis
Does the dark pope know cuz there is a black pope
Well if you've ever seen the fantastic movie The Order
What's his face
Hottest women alive
Take it was great it was a terrible movie so I love you and 40 nights
I can jack off for lunch
Josh Hartnett
Him with a rose petal
She's easy
All that stuff you were saying
All the stuff you saying is again misinterpreting
Quotes
One of the Pope
Things about Muslim terrorism not existing
Broke down
Why Alex is lying and it's honest about that
When he talks about populism but the pope was saying is
Historically populist movements have ended up very poorly
Know that
Christianity the nationalism
Witches are
Both the enemy of Christianity
Witches
Yeah remember earlier he was going there again
Christianity
Nationalism
I must have I must have tuned that out
Can just put Alex in July
He just becomes white noise at some point
And
But
Again it's another misrepresentation of what the Pope
Demonize him and pretend
Alex's version Christianity
The mainstream version is Dima
Hope the pope is
The devil
That's heretic
That's pretty bad
Especially considering in the same interview where he talks about populism ending up
Which I think
History Bears out
Most of the time they've been populist movements it's ended up in disaster
The French Revolution work
Okay no
No
The Arab Spring
Germany that was great
No
They put in the same we don't have a lot of good ones
Is there about
Like the idea that people think of him as
Different than a normal person
A easy song about how like
I'm just a normal believer
I'm just another Christian
That's what I am
We have
Revealed that he may not believe in
Basic tenets
The Christianity
Alex
I think the pope has at least one or two under his belt
Galaxy
You basically just said
I just can't believe in anything that even relates
To your and I up
I don't know I
But I think he also probably
Maybe believe some of the
Stuft Pizza in
Like the Lost gospels and s*** like that a lot of his books
We're kicked out of the Bible
Probably include some of that metaphysical stuff
That you seem
3 super into
Where is mainstream Christianity really doesn't have a lot of
No but if you get into like alarm
If you get into the Lost Books of the Bible and forgotten books of
Or the like the Apocrypha
Didn't feel like all of these books that are part of the normal Canon
You end up with some
Some pretty wild stuff
The pole first women there is evil in there
The gospels just f**** every
She is evil
As we all know
Used to be a kick-ass music
Wish I was old enough to go backgrounds
It would have been good
More Wichita
Music
I want to make you feel powerless they want to throw stuff out but also deny it
Make you just give up
There was that witch
Energy
Thing that they did in their wanton Worthy
Yeah nobody believes in this s*** but hey
Point your energy
Hippies trying to levitate the Pentagon
Liberals don't believe this
Is everyone
But you take it seriously alright
That's why people think you're insane but the other thing too is that there's a long history of Alex Jones being
Trolled by satanists
Right
Okay we want to put up a satanic
We're going to do the Ten Commandments we get to put Satan up there f*** you b****
Firm logic
To be like okay you don't want to take down your religious thing
You must tolerate
Public building
Otherwise you are religious
Falls for it every f****** time hook lion
So he's talking about these witches getting together
Pray for
Wright Medical
Who's that using spells to get bring down President Trump
Where is before
He would encourage people to pray
Against Obama
It is
Spells are very different
In one you chant
And try to appeal to a higher power to influence real
You chance
And then like probably
One of them is theoretical
L.ron Hubbard does
You know
And I was part of that
Spotify
We don't support Aleister Crowley
Who is pretty cool
He came up on the podcast
Time before the right
Who is El Ron Hubbard
Spelled
Magic
Anyway who cares that's irrelevant
Today we got to get to
Jordans
The uninviting Seas of race talk
Alright alright this is one of the big narratives on Thursdays show
About Jorge Ramos
Right
He mentioned his name earlier and now we're going to
Is the exactly why
Jorge Ramos is
Univision TV
Alex frequently on this episode called him George
Which I think is installed
But he
You can't hear interview with
Tucker Carlson
That which is what
Is going to be broken down by Alex
Promises the one kicked out of the
I don't know
I believe I believe he was
Okay I'm not
But
He is
Univision
Yankee recently had
Speech
Where he was talking about how there's a lot of immigrants
To be here
And it is not verecund
It is all Ark
That could be misinterpreted
Understood
Country now b****
That was not what
That would be
Pretty funny
I don't like I don't like the idea of this being anyone's country other than all of ours
Maybe he was thinking we should trade
Like
Bekins Moving
It states all the
States moving to the mini Balada Beach down there the food is
Great people
Just
Even trade
I don't know if I want to go move to Mex
Tacoma trade countries I'm just eating frozen pizza
Alright
Another big part of his point and he'll elaborate on it a little bit
Is that
Within twenty years or so
White people will be
A minority
I will be able to redeem Authority country
Everyone will be minority
Threatening idea to people who are super into being
Threatening idea to me at all
I don't like
Anybody who's super into being white
Yeah it's
It's worrisome
Historically is very murder
These are the main thing is that this Ramos interview
To do with
Alex takes it
2 weird directions
Add frequently called Jorge Ramos erased
What race
Help which I want to be clear
If you ever use the term race pimp
And you were quoting Alex Jones
You're welcome
Problem also if you ever
Use the term
Explain to me what that supposed to mean
You're pimping races baby I don't understand what that
It means
Think
You're making money
Trying to get races to fight each
Or something
Which
Kind of describe
Yeah also
Note that still doesn't make sense using the two words put together
Race pimp
That suggests
That you are making money
Selling
Racist
Well yeah
Kind of
Now
Or talk about
People are we talkin
About
Astros
Painting face
That's really what I think Alex is saying is that
Jorge Ramos
Spell
Black face paint for a day
It's possible it's possible
Possible
Here is
That might be a fun service here's the introduction to Alex talking about this interview and
I can't confirm
Any of them
Things he says in this
I don't care
Cuz it's
It's super weird
Ramos
Also I want to say that
Alex one of his big argument that he's trying to make is like
I don't care about race talk about this.
Yeah it looks like
Too much
When we used to think the people here were Indians
I think he's pointing up
That it's bad that you
You got Native American
That's what he saying right there
It gets so weird
Circumnavigate
Mexico
Honey
Cuz there's not one
Images of American
Person
Complete
Absolute
What is
Oh boy whitesplaining Hispanic Miss
I have to pause just so you could get that out before he gets well or whitesplaining it okay
Let's find this out
It's not just in Spanish
What they are
Oh I'm going to sit back and let this I am going to watch this over my head like
Like so much
And they were Arab
African
Search
25% of them have African
Basically Germanic
A little bit African
And in some Asia
Chinese
What is
Sound through the top
I'm countries are on the continent today of North America Central America South America
Colonial
With almost telling you this
Spaceships
Okay good good
Good on you there at the end
Yeah
That's interesting right
That's pretty good
Pretty good stuff
Pretty good breakdown
I don't understand
Bora Bora
Creative hierarchy
Knowledge
Very poor
It's a very very poor
It's surface-level
Also
China
You can't be Chinese
10000 years before if you want to be generous to him
Is be like sort of genetic
Why
Become China broekhoff
Yeah
They were from the land continents of
Right as we know it
Is
Silly
Like because because if you're going to if you're going to pull this s*** just say everybody was in
African
Just do that
That's where human beings came from so we're all Africa
Now if you say we're all African
Right
I mean
I don't have a full understand
Meaning of genetics
Oroville
The history of genetics
Blonde hair blue eyes
That's Nordic
I know enough that I know he's wrong
That's where I'm at
I can't
Without
Like taking a college course on why he's wrong
He's he's got this like
This fundamental mendelian
Jeanette
Concept that we all know isn't real
If you have to be plant
You're going to get
This is dumb
Everything he says is dumb
Another that make sense
What is even this point I don't know what is even his point is this
They're saying hate White
People when you don't know that you're
A white person
Or your Arabic
Chinese
What is his what is his ultimate point there at the end of the day even if he's right about all of it doesn't
Really
Theme to mean anything
Thing other than
You think you're you think your Mexican but you're all these other thing
Coast you so close to talk
About Colonial
Like the ruling class
Mexico
Is he
He's really close
There
They're not
Hispanic
Because they were colonized
That's what I think
It's possible
Then you saying that
The true colonialism
The Mexicans
Maybe or the Moors
Before that
What are we doing
But but his argument then is that in 1776 America was trying to undo all that sort of stuff
Don't know there was a middle-class whatever so very much
We can
He doesn't
Drawing in this like middle classes
OK Google
Of the United States is a strong middle
Yeah
Strong middle classes
The positive negative
I mean but yeah that's
No
There's always a strong middle class
Does he not want to ruin class if you have a middle class you have the other classes
You don't just have one middle class
I don't know if I want to stay here forever on being
What we're doing is
Info on
Communism
I think we were social
And then obvious
That led to Communism
And now we're going to overthrow
Is the opposite of what most
Crazy people about socialism
Let's get to this Ramos clip
He doesn't remember we have a rich history on this phone
If you
Native American you're Chinese
We have a rich history on this show of
Looking at Alex's
Media criticism
Right
Truman Show
So I can go into town
My favorite part of all of these media credits
Is he never criticizes
So it is always
Let the guy get two words top and then
He looks like
He looks like he just had sex with other men all the time
When is face
He's a pedophile that Facebook's everybody
Still not great
Groceries half-Hispanic
Tony
Free market and private property and guns and raising your own
Kids
He's saying this about like a and private property
Property
Don't you want guns
Population
Country
People are passing along the torch
Pre-market
His idea is substantially worse than what Jorge Ramos
Abortions
Deadly inoculations
He's doing a teller
Brake adjuster so much.
It's going nuts
Every single episode there's some crumpling paper and if you're watching the video
Like you shuffling through papers boy
So awesome
I love it so much
Sickening
Absolutely
Completely
Sickening
This is disgusting
The monster
What school does what kids are forced at California
Good old-fashioned
Can't wear American flags
School referral ladybug
If you actually go look into the night circuit decision about that just as a quick reminder
Kid being bullied by kids on
Cinco de Mayo
It many
Pictures of harassment
Buy kids wearing American
Flags of being like suck you on Cinco de Mayo
And the night Circuit Court rule
Not that you can't
Where are American flags
Specifically on Cinco de Mayo
That was okay
That wasn't it wasn't
Against free speech
Which
Is not with Alex
Jorge Ramos
Erase Pimpin Ain't Easy
But it sure is fun
People like
Ramos
Oh boy
I wonder who
He does I wonder who he's going to tell
Katy Perry
Becoming like a dark horse in the bed family
I don't know man
It's fun
It is sort of our principals
Business bringing other people
It's not that what he's doing is shity and we can call it out
Because
It's against our principles except his kid
And we're still not mean to him
So like
Well it's whatever he's accusing us of doing he's doing that gives us free reign to do
About his family
But I don't repeat on the air and I don't think it necessarily true
Anyway
Mexico
Separate from
15 Generations
Slug an enemy of humanity
You have your job wide-open
Okay
Hispanic
KKK
Step manager
Racepak
I didn't know all of those words could be used to describe the same person and
Could be undone if he adopted a quote
People first
I'm not sure
Does he think everybody who hasn't talked to the Korean is raises
Knowledge fight donations for a raising our Korean child
Search Air
Another co-host to Korean
We're going to get this ship ethically sound
According to Alex
Just by introducing the third house
Google gaga
Are we going to
Okay good.
In the US
This is also our country
Is our country
Whose country is it
Adidas
Weather
This is not a white country
Population
African Americans
Songs on channel Monterey's Club
To explain a
Who is
Who believed that Latinos can immigrants
Obviously there are white people that are tribe
Ilysm
The Bulls and the point is is that the left has broken the
Social compact
I'm bringing people in there hard Waters
Alright
George
You and other people.
Guadalupe Hidalgo treaty
Ramos is playing
As a blanket statement
Their country
Who says
If Mike Hunt
Meaning you don't get to
Choose that your country is
Exactly what Alex figured out and somehow got wrong still
Yeah Alex
It's remarkable
And if you stay I mean what he saying is that. Just
For tribal
Ray Ray
I think you're misunderstanding what he was saying
That little
He was trying to say that racism is really
Just tribalism
Right
And that is
Is a I think
Clunky.
Some of it is
No some of it is just
Good old-fashioned
Country
To try and Rebrand
Racism is tribalism is to take some of the stink off
A little bit
And that is what he was doing
I mean
I might be wrong but that's my take
If you remember tribalism
Usually
It doesn't have it doesn't carry the same modern connotation
And I believe so you're right
He can get around the racist
The boo yaa tribe
Ivan the name
We all try
Really
Well what that was like
My internal monologue was
Damn I'm proud I pulled
Very good
I think a lot of that is really awful
Alex's interpretation of that
Tucker Carlson is not
Understand what Jorge Ramos is
Isaac Wilson
He says
You're white
And I'm pretty sure he's talking about
Skin colored nuts
Genetics or
Which Alex
Previously has explained
Which is
You're like me
An incredibly white person
Right
Bowtie on air
The you are white
You and Paul Ryan
Kitty White
But it's certainly within Tucker Carlson sort of modus operandi
Do not understand people intentionally in order to try and bake them into
What's my name to giving a sound playback like therapy
We went over and over again
He got his new show it
Ratably
He used to be terrible
Liberty was on CrossFire
I know you so much
Daily Caller
Infowars light
Yeah but they also have like
What up
Warriors
Listen to this podcast
He has
Roughly 3,000 articles
Printed out
On this desk
And he's going to shuffle through them right now just
Read the headlines
That's great Folly work
About some headline
Rate tips about
California City
In defiance of trump
I am in that
Close to
Reasonable
This photo is like a trouble shared online is generating quite a buzz
I mean
High school math teacher gets probation for traumatizing male teams with bunch of sex
I'm not going
This model's Instagram account is out of control
The Daily Caller is full
It's it's
Did he have sex
In front of them
Is this
A bunch of time
Terroriser
It's 27
Hooker
Britney Spears
Just put in
!
Entertainment section
This is some b******* right there
The standard
Infowars light but they also have
Daily Caller
Terrible
Terrible website
Tucker Carlson
Ramos interview Alex
Is not done by a long shot
5 minutes
Gilmore about
Paul Ryan
Portugal man
Music
If you're burning an Infowars newspaper I'm on your hundred percent
So are you get back to Ramos eventually and
Let's go ahead and go back to
Sister Ramos
Drudge Report
Dot-com
Almost
Will become minority this is our country
Bowser tie his clothes
It's all our country
He is saying that
That's exactly what this is our country
It makes
Do you think this is Mexican country now b****
The Drudge Report headlines
Basically
The first part of a set
Cut out the middle
And then
And then also different together and made it seem like Ramos was threatening everybody
I can sentence which gets into all of the
The unity parts
What they do what they do
Narrative
Is that we're always
They're always trying to take
Which
Is interesting because I don't think anybody the one thing that white people I have never
Giving away
Is whiteness
No nobody wants
Nobody wants
Good is
Nerdy
Which
We are the apps
Sense of humanity
Sure I don't want to I don't want to go into like a
Indictment of the idea of whiteness being Define
And as not
Other phone
Which is really the historical origins of white
Because I would require
I mean
Whiteness has always been defined as
In contrast
Two other things
Which is why
There are large groups of people who are like
His wife
Is deeply entrenched in the history of the concept of whiteness
Horrible
Damaging
Philosophy
Alex Jones
Super into
If you go back to history
Anytime we will have met another Society
Start bad for them
Every every time every time you read a story
From history I'm always like
Welcome to the White
People in in your head it's like
Horror movie
Absolutely
Highway
Race them
System
Daniel Leach little subgroups
Off against each other
Disgusting
That's how they do it
There's a little turtle of
Like truth in that but Alex doesn't recognize
She also does that
To an extreme
We can't celebrate
Him staying one right
He's accusing other race
Yeah of being involved in
I think if we just give him posit
Feedback when he's right
He'll eventually
Learn he just wants
People don't like it but what episode
Cuz he wants us
To like him
The what episode where we talked about how great a couple of his philosophies were
Didn't get one bed pictures still not hung up
Nothing we can do that we haven't
Put it down
Picture of
That's really our main.
Latinos
So even right there
Ramos is
A really great
Distinction
Non-white population
Asian should be
Accepted into the
Music country
It's not only there
Which is a nuance
It's really understood
Absorb that information synthesized
And then changed his
You might be wrong
I might be wrong
Endom and we have to leave and be tormented that's exactly what I was
Where he says we have to be Multicultural live together
Like that
American flags in public school system settings
Because they're Spanish
Stop it
Again that he's bringing up the exact same thing
Interview
These kids were being bullied and harassed
Chesterfield
It's like you're a p****
You victims
Horrible
Alma Court
You are a dick
Where where are you
Racist
Commenting on another racist
Being racist towards a Jorge Ramos
So you can pull up
I did pull up that ruling
And you're lying
Alex
Don't tell people to pull things up
Don't do that that's really against your self-interest
You need to not encourage people to look into some it's a really really dangerous
Give advice to Alex if you want to keep lying like this
Consistently you need people to not looking
The best way to
To keep people from looking into it
Tell them to look into it
From your like DUIs or matter what you look at
I know I'm right you assert with confidence it's much like what episode
Probably true
This is this is
Political correctness
Beating up Trump supporters
You're intolerant your bullies
That's not politically correct
Only place that I specifically heard about Trump's life being in danger
Infowars
I've never seen
News article that talks
Advocating killing Trump
Right I've only seen dumb
Possibly
Then
Advocated for
Alex talks about it everyday
Maybe
He's creating a ghost tomorrow
He's going to kill.
Ultimate Manchurian
Wild
The best episode of knowledge fight
Who are covering breaking news
Alex Jones
Kill the president
Would be
Astounding
Crime of passion
With a different radio
Such a Betrayal on a love try my God
Pennywise
They're right here
Seriously
Does the number of movies and
TV shows we've got a right
Hispanic
Bad Country
P******
Classic American
Problem to
Problem
Population
That's why we had to bring in
Aldi's
Other population
Refuel rrr
People Force
Because we were boarded
Half of our kids
Imagine the population growth
We had aboard
Crazy
Absolutely
Alex Jones
Show
His for multiple abortions
Just keep that fire
In case you were wondering whether or not
The third world
Is being used as a weapon system
Against the first world to drive down wages and that's why the Republican or Democratic
The biggest immigration histories ever seen of the unwashed masses
Diseases
Health problems you name it to bankrupt and things down they want to blow
Out Western economy and consolidate control that should Mitten cloward-piven it submitted in the UN strategy
And this plan of globalism to flood the first world and implode it
So that they can dictate the terms of our must be stopped
So there's that part where you recognized
A slight truth
Conclusion
He brings up
Cloward and Piven a lot and I think
It was exactly what it is
The cloward-piven strategy of the political strategy outlined in
66 by American sociologist and political activist
Richard cloward and Frances Fox Piven
The culture overload in the US public welfare system
In order to precipitate a crisis
That would lead to replacement of the welfare system with a national
System of a guaranteed annual income
And thoughts
Okay it was
Put into effect
Can't imagine
A couple of professors
That was
Hey
Guess what
Are entitled to benefits that they aren't taken
There's a lot of people who are eligible for welfare
Really if we create an awareness campaign people can get all of these
Things that you're entitled to based on your low income
What would do it was it would end up
Bogging down
S*** on a local
And state-level
So much so that these simpler way would just be to give everybody Universal
It would create
A crisis
That would make
The federal government recognize just how many people are living
Livable condition
But also what they are
Entitled to under the current
Welfare rule
So it isn't which word
Bible God damn
1960s
But he uses this is a thing that you don't know what it is
It sounds like a law firm that I would
Play higher that's
It sounds like some mysterious
But if you came up with
In the sixties
Isn't
In effect
It's not real
It didn't
Get put into effect
Nobody actually listen to it it's a liberal Boogeyman
Absolutely
Special
You think so
Maybe I think the law of unintended consequences
Consequences would destroy that
Running is not Universal basic income
But the exact opposite
And Universal f*** you to everybody on welfare
Yeah that that is what a lot of thinkers have said
Suggest
Is that you end up with scapegoating and demonization of the poor
Look what happened with health care
Right
Do you know who got scapegoated and demonized whatever we started making sure people had Healthcare
People need help there
But look like
Direct example of how that doesn't work the end goal of it though I think is good terms of like
The heart was in the right place in terms of
Create a way to make people recognize how bad it is
4 people who are living here
I think that's positive
In the way you know you're walking through a minefield
And you probably couldn't navigate that wouldn't be able to do that
Much like Agenda 21
Is a
Did you end
That has no enforcement to it
Is just a set of ideas
That is not forced
It's voluntary
Almost the same thing
It never was put into place
It happened
Nigh on fifty years ago
That's the problem with all the names that we've come up with
Look if you and I co-authored this paper at home
One with whatever that
Paper flowers
No that's carry the fries at home Zach would really hate would be amazing
Do deaf people like kerosene prices
He's not dumb.
Lower
Your house to be freezing your home to be freezing
And Jorge Ramos and others and the Pope Francis can jump up and down with their race-baiting crap
Population
Pizzeria
Endom and we have to leave and be tormented
What immigration restrictions would you favor in Mexico
What's the restrictions in the country Mexico
Wicked Ways
People that shoot Coca-Cola or Sprite
Great America
Guatemala Guatemala
I mean
Harsher than the US
Tell us
Controls
No
Didn't do it
Mexico can open itself up to Central and South America are you crazy
Castle countries down there are in total turmoil with people starving on the streets everywhere
Most of the
Animals the cats and dogs
The elite
You want us to be like that too
And you're on the big New World Order multinational owned Univision
Got to eat those seals
Got to eat the zoo animal
Cuz he kept saying I'm not saying that's a good thing
In the voice of
You mean like torturing
Too far
I think I cut out the part where he says but he mentions the wall between Mexico
Irm South
Again that's the one that we
That was just a chain link fence
No estan meme
He just ran
Arizona Arizona then one that's in Israel
Westbank
No this is no wall it is
Lush vegetation
121 in an apartheid state
And the other in the state of Apartheid
I don't even know how to respond
Anymore
What is What is the
Forgot too cuz I think
Carlson
But it's trying to pull a
There right there
Like you supposed to be like
Oh well you think American should do this with
What do you think about Mexico and what they're doing
Scorpion charger
Really easy
To answer that would like yeah I don't like the way Mexico is doing that
And
We're starting to do that
So don't
And
That's perfectly
This whole thing
Dictator
Now that's rude
And you're just a dick
It's gauche secondary thing is that like
Just because
Some other country does it
And we haven't
Stopped
Doing it doesn't mean that we don't have
The power to stop them from Detroit
I look
I'll be very public
All other I said you're opening yourself up for attack for
Mostly from the southeast
Lower
I don't think of it
It's fair to be like
This country does that so what about that
I think
Two things can be bad
At the same time it's a logical fallacy
Critical
Mexico's bad with it
In the same way that we are being bad
We can't get off the hook
Could someone worse
That was that the thing every time there's a Time
The right-wing always goes to like
Well it's better than Arabia
Combat
Males
Go to close
No it can it can both be bad
We should try to not be that bad
And then
Still not be as bad as we are now
What can improving be fun
Yeah
Christo's
To progress
It's not happening everywhere
That makes perfect
It's just very Ikea frog
Otherwise nobody have to do it
Wacky stuff for Less
We're going to get Leanne Wackadoo up
We are in this
Bii
I was trying to really put the
English
Biatch
But I wish you fart
So this next
Alex
Been proven right
TV is listening
It it all of us that he's been proven right
And again
Therefore
You must believe everything else
He takes the opportunity
To Double Down
Oh no
Indignant
Credible
Yarn app
Is just
I've titled this one
It gets worse
Oh wow this isn't really Alex
Wow
Listening
Cancer viruses
In the polio vaccine in the MMR vaccine effective
And then wait till a certain point
Ourselves
Literally did not pay you unemployment
Retirement money
The world
We're all been implanted with with with with
Termination switches
So
The only documented evidence I can
And see if this is that
Between 19
5 + 9
There were some
Contaminants
Polio vaccine
I was
There's no way to track
It was contaminated
Bye
Some of the byproducts they were using
It hypothetically could have caused
Some people
Between 1955 and
But the problem
And corrected
After that point
Any other evidence
It was not
From everything I can find
It was
What medicine was like in the 50s
Yeah it was not broke your leg
The good old days in Metairie
Yeah it was it was very Elementary science compared to what it is now
Yeah and so they use
To create vaccines you have to use
Some of the live virus
In order to
There's there's a certain amount of that
True and not true like
What everybody think
A vaccine is is like
Dead version of the virus
Yeah right
It's best not every just like
No they don't Hammer one down we got it
Some of them are really easy to understand
And that's why people get it in their head that all of them are
And it's not
It also
When you're trying
No
They're not waiting for you to take unemployment
They're not
There's not like snowboard
Like a giant like
Pictures of like
Hip like record producers room switches on it
They're one of them says Jordan home
That's why I got that MMR vaccine
What you're saying is
Kanye West
In the recording studio
Flip the wrong switch
Yep
This this thing with you talkin about
Hypothetically affected
98 million Americans
Ending a night
Hypothetically affected that many
There's no evidence that it actually
All of those people got cancer
They didn't
No probably some of them did
And it's unfortunate
And it's also possible they would have gotten cancer anyway
Kids crazy
In the course of
Medicine being
Living Art
And being Progressive
Even moving somewhere number one
Killer in hospitals
Infection first
Mercer virus
You're just in the wrong place
I like that the end there's no way to perfectly decontaminate everything and
Not enough doctors wash their hands and all of that
Medicine is
Bulshit
Crypto cancer in the middle
Triggered at some point when you
You're stressed out
Is complete b*******
And the only thing that is documented at all and I can find
Is something from
50 years ago
Good
Strategy accomplished
What it is
You're looking
To do
We just keep
People from unemployment
Probably.
Vaccine
It'll be probably easier just to pass a bill
We talked about earlier about diabetes that was based on a disc
From years and years in the past
We got lied
Thoroughly debunked
Stripped Away because
Did NFL
And poorly run studies
We got lies on lies
A lot of the arguments
Then there are the positive one
That are
Again much like you've already
All your friends ain't dying
From
Pollo
Yeah which is a very real
Everybody had
You know anybody
Good I bet it's because they have autism too much autism as we all know
Autism kills polio
Bolillo
See there we go proves my theory
If you thought
Write your flow
F****** Raw
It gets worse
That's literally what I was
Just talkin about the sv40 thing to use
C3
Of
A particular vaccine
The Hyatt
Estimated 98 million people got that vaccine
So hundreds Plus
Million
Even then
Wouldn't you have heard about the hundred plus million of
People who died all very similarly around the same time
I don't know
But also
I I got my information about
The vaccine and in all this
Like the backstory of it
From legitimate sources
I got the 98 million
Total
From
Crazy
Right-wing Bloc
Okay Daddy number artificially inflated
Then him artificial eating and artificially inflating
Already
Ridiculous
Yeah
Expertly into
The idea that first
Hundreds of Millions
Confirm the CDC got cancer from SB
V40 s*** is just
There's no basis
And even if there was the CDC would never
Confirm that she let me know where.
They're putting cheese
Go into the nerves
And then
Activate later upon stress
Actuary
Yes you've been given
Switch
Don't worry you haven't
By the way
Ways to reverse it
You're supposed to rain
Probably
I got a butt in Africa
You will scream
I guarantee you're going to scream
Fuct
The General Public
I was talking about
I was talking to the inteligencia
Liberalism
British population
You didn't get the vaccine
Even
On a scale of 1 to 10
You know
Say that pumps
Auto and truck coming out
Resurrection
Here's the Big Lots
Is ever telling yourself you're part of the power structure
You're fooling yourself
Atop Rockefeller or Rothschild
Or somebody
You know what JK Rowling
Colorado time
HP Lovecraft
After book
I love that he's dropping references to lesser-known Lovecraft books
You know what basically describe the plot of the island
50 time era is 425
How does he know that chimeras
I am before clones
25 years
Is great source
Wouldn't you start with chimeras
Maybe I don't know video of Alex Jones
Camaros for 50 years
Heat flashes up a picture of a National Geographic article
Human pig hybrid created
This is January
No
4 months
Before it died
The idea of it here is
Every 10 minutes a person is added to the National waiting list for Oregon
Plant without an organ they need
Inside an animal
It's not pigs with human consciousness
It's that
Part of their organs will grow in a way that we can extract without
Killing them
Human organs
I would like to know more about that
Talking about
What they flash upon the screen
As evidence that he's right
The screen that's behind him into Studio
Is showing this article
That I read that I have in front of me here that is
Not about chimeras
With human intelligence
Pick bodies or whatever the f*** you imagine
It is about
Harvesting Oregon
Also
If they've had it
A 25 years
Nope I don't even know Geographic
What is allowed to trickle it out
Because they're getting us
Using movies
With predictive engineering or HP lovecraft's stories
And out of time
Colorado time
Good book
Isn't that book I recommend a lot of crap
More anti-black to be on
Oh okay
Look why don't you go off on a Lovecraft
But his racism is mostly in his earlier works
An antique
You can really see you like the
The strain of that
His later career
You could tell that he was almost
Yeah he's getting
He's a product of his time
I don't
I don't think it's good
That he had to some races
Just believe
But
I think
You can still enjoy lot of it
Without
The case of Arthur German
Don't f*** the monkey
You realize we're off to a good start there
His later career
My point is
That I
Out maybe there's
Some Redemption for
I don't think his trajectory is going the same direction as webcam
Is like okay scholarly paper the Lovecraft
Does Alex Jones the artist
Spell represent
Using
These things
I-22 prop up a Target
Timer on top of that using this idea that he was right about one thing to be evidence that you've gotta believe in butt
I mean the Clones
We've had
50 years
Everybody knows the fruits and
No I prefer the
Genetic code is through
Okay
Put it back together
In the way that
You know we want it
Okay
Like the biggest breakthrough ever
In terms
Genetics
Okay that is not been around for 50 years
Impossible
And it's not being used to make laws clones
I think Alex might have gotten a phone call from somebody who told him this
Or maybe a DM
Maybe you got
Gamekeeper
I mean I'm just saying that if I were Alex Jones
I would want to watch
Adaptic
Clone myself
For an eventual
Infowars
Clear background clear about cloning
You don't get a second
Cloning works
Is it full grown
No you don't get a full-grown you it doesn't work that way
Ucreate
Something with like identical genetics essentially
Which
You could
Which is
Not really all that scary
In the movie The Shining younger than you cuz
Time for bed
Clayton identical twin
And it would not be any it would not be similar to a human clone
Because it would have
Totally different life experiences
Gene's turn off and on depending on our environment
Environment
It's not real
Veritiv
He takes this
I want
Takes
To like
A really dark place
By the way there's a movie with Andrew Garfield
Oh that is about
Spider-Man
Herb City
That very thing
Where there's a
So it's all of these
At this Hospital
And their entire life like a go through their entire life it's a great science
Story
Where is like they're born
Organ heart
Monday
Theoretically they have all of these
Life experiences within that but therein
Entire life is
Is built around
We're eventually going to
I can't pay attention to this because I just keep having
Farmhouse by Phish running through my head but with clone Farm
Farm Oregon
Farmhouse
Anyway Alex
Do I f****** dark
Propaganda play
Excellent against the globalist
And I want to be clear when I get to the end
Alec
He's smiling
Oh no really getting into telling him about what
Talk about
You're signing on to Harper
Destructive force in the universe
He's talking about signing on with the global
Crack
Neutron stars exploding
Centrifugal force
Oh boy
Play clap
But if you'd come face-to-face with it you'd never curl up next to it
God's protection
Up against it
Just like those kids
All of you that have served if you have open the door
Everything you want you're going to get it
Jamaica
Because God is a Jessica
Isn't that awful
That was gross I was so gross
Families doing that like
Relishing in this idea
Joni don't exist
In all of this
AZ State result
Girl up
But it's going to
Asking to be just like those kids their backyards
He's just
Disgusting
Ruffling paper Foley work manipulative
Yep
What a dick
Roast
From Thursday cuz
He also had an interview with Dave Rubin from the Ruden report
LG also don't need to cover
The guy's just an a******
The root
Report
Twitter suggested
Recover that
I don't want to make so many logical leaves that don't make sense
It's just it's boring
For 50 years
Chimeras
Oh my
See now I just
Mixed with a Pug
Like I want a clone of me
And I wanted to be mixed with a puppy
So it's a lot like John Candy in space
That's really want it
Peterborough cat personality
The stress of aloof over it
Send us what you'd like to be
Please hit us up with your Chimera choice
Will make it
We will we've had chimera
Technology for 25 years
We will splice you with an animal for a small donation
Also if you want to email at knowledge fight at gmail.com
Riverview all those funds
Absolutely
This has been a delight
Manhatta
Catlover you
I'm nothing if not a policy wonk
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color