Alex
Indeed we are
How many belts has illness
May I can't actually even remember
I mean never been hangovers
Stuff that it made
Give me Second Life
You're so but
Mild
Food
Terrible
From food weigh more than any normal person
I can't remember the last time
You limit your exposure
Population
No
I know I don't I don't think that's why I'm out and about
Just like that I was never ever sick
But my girlfriend is
School
Yep so now I'm now
I appreciate you coming in
Fighting through it as we get this adventure where I
Do you know what does
If I ever heard it was
Give a shout out
What's to couple folks
I really appreciate it
First
I'd like to say thank you for Isabelle
Thank you very much appreciate it
Because I'm much at to Joshua you are now
I'm a policy wonk
And then
Get down to the old to brass tacks
Like to say you are now
Oops
But then after he corrected
You are right
Thank you very much
It's not okay
Every week
Literally
Forget cuz we don't record on Wednesday
Every week completely forget
Watch the little bit of
Camelot
Don't shoot the messenger
I thought you might be talking
To us through the screen
Who belongs on project but it was she was talking about
You what you have
Understand
Is that most of my whistleblowers have been mind-controlled at some point
So obviously they're going to lie or bunch
Which of the time
And you know what if they tell me a lie does that mean everything
Goodnight
Just made me feel really bad and I
I don't want to talk
Time for a while
And if any page comes back that's going to be a new episode for us
A soldier and like I don't know if I have it in my heart
Made a new player
There's only one super soldier in that's Kurt Russell
What do you mean a racist alien it stuff
Anyone else
Compare quite frankly so
We'll see what happens
But for now Jordan
They said Wacky Wednesday we're sticking back in the
2009 episode for Monday
We did that interview
Positive
I really appreciate it
So desperate
The cover a lot of ground
Did a couple days
Taking care of
But I could
Today we are just doing March 9th 2009
Just one day Just One Day 2019
There's a happy there's so much to learn back that every day brings us a new
Huge July but he's telling it's very excited for someone like me
Those were exciting times
We were just emerging into Barack Obama's presidency Wendell IB
The truth we were Wednesday
Stuff recently
We found Alex Jones
Pretty much
Whole Hog
For about a month
In a tenth amendment resolution
For all
Weird wraps on
Bizarrely racist
All very problematic people
And they all come on about how the states
Juggle a couple more narrative
Fall story about the avian flu release
Buy into check
Republic
And so we're all over the place
Trying to find out
Start song
And when he
Besides ice tea party
He's pretty cool
And so far we've seen absolutely no indication
Either of those
Question that I probably should have answered
On our previous
Is 911 water still going strong
I don't know I didn't look at any of the front page of it
Irrelevant irrelevant
It still up
There's that somebody still renewing the register
Find archived County
We're in a place where it's at
Super weird you know I opened up this episode really
Strongly
Continue down the avian
Trying to build
Nothing
In the world
Could have prepared me for this
Being the beginning of the episode
And the hour today
Blockbuster film
Was released Nationwide on Friday
The Watchmen
Mulled over the characters knightowl the comedian
Doctor Manhattan
Silk Spectre
I have never seen Illuminati in your
Propaganda
Spoiler alert
I'm going to
It's just unspeakable
Speakable
Ozymandias
Apparently is unspeakable.
Because he keeps
Calling him
30 time which is hilarious
You know what else could have called him
Asia if you didn't want to call him if he has trouble pronouncing
Commandeer
By all means
Gopher
There is no other way there play by Matthew good
That is exactly what Bill and Ted would have called Ozymandias if he was in Bill and Ted's
Who's the really funny thing about the fact that Alex
Really highlight ironic absolutely a proposed
Mispronounce consider
Like it was just a random a name
But it's not
No it's a reference
Really
On the nose name for Alex today
Another name for Ramses the Second
There it's the illusion
Poems from 1818 by English.
And
The theme
Those poems
Inform the understanding of Ozymandias
Rosy Mound
His name is Ozzy mandamus
Doesn't recognize me
The name of the literary allusion
He doesn't really have that much of a
The name Depp
Review,
Absolutely not
I bet he doesn't even know who
Probably not
Apropos
Sing for
Reference
Considering
Frankenstein
Contacts
Situation where
Seems seems that way
I was expecting
Science
And Lex Luger
So when I jumped in and
He comes out of the gate being like I'm going to tell you all about the Watchmen
The info Warrior Nation ears or Alex ghost
You can't stop
Himself from not review
Just yet but he wants you to know this
Are saying we don't understand it
In a New York Times in CNN
I understand that all too well how could someone
Okay
This is Wacky Wednesday
Future of the human race
Through the Wire
Never be truly wacky there's going to be a element
Craziest f****** thing
Baby show ends in a way that like
I can't believe Alex didn't scrub this
Butts
It's
It's crazy
Ozzy man
Alex
So
Stupid but Alex predict that Bernie Madoff is going to walk
Which
The Bernie Madoff take the death
Image living on an island
I don't know either
We like
To catalogue the times when Alex
Does karaoke
This instance of it I don't want a catalog
Is a very angry
Have I am doing carrier
A Country Boy Can Survive
We are back live your
Call Zack
Are they
Radio show info
And realize who outed me about this
So I only kept that in 1st of August
Country folks can survive
Good night night time
I want you to hold on to that little that little ramble there at the end
You know that they're afraid of us
Inspire people
They're afraid because they know that we're going to rise up and they're going to prison
Hold onto that I know it's a very standard Alex
Right thing
The fact that
If you getting into that sort of mode
F****** hilarious
So
Where you at
Are you wishing that you got through is Watchmen review already I guess you didn't
Know how to use it for you
What is it
She plan on doing for the 1st
2 hours
Play Rambles about Madoff
Mark Cuban
The globalist threatened to murder Mark Cuban's kids
Please put up some of the money behind loose change
Yeah
I don't know how
Yep
Jason bermas showed up on Shark Tank
Marquis would like I'm buying
All right and he was extensive dollars or one of his companies he was going to distribute
Also
Circumstances
If you got to bust
And Alex has completed the two it's being like
Sequence of him
This entire thing where Mark Cuban
Threatened in
Alex
His also recently been embroiled in its
Situation where people were abusing women
Crazy
I can't even begin to tell you how bad this thing at the Ender
It may be one of them I mean
SpaceX
Absolutely
Call
Does it take a few calls
Peculiarly
Howling
About Alex's interest
His business
Back in 2000
Different
Yes
Open hunting backgrounds
I'm kinda
Find out if I can
I know I can but I'm
Did one verse in the Bible that says
Know this also then last days perilous times shall come
Get to it this time or could have been back in it
Depression
We are going to be faced in perilous times according to everything you've been reporting
But I like to be able to help
Some people
If that's possible, give a phone number and
Be my personal phone number
Or somebody will call
Website then
Sure go ahead Bob
Okay ww.w.
Zemo.
Imo
Health health
Dot-com
What is
It gives you
Like I'm trying
Did you like that
Some energy gives endurance people workout computer
Missouri
Interesting what do you do mean you've got a Siri
You mean you got till some limericks
You got to bring some content
To the show before you went out loud that
A little bit later in the show here's what he does
Tyler Palmer
Thanks Alex thanks for having me on again and hello to all the listeners
Grab
He hasn't ecoloblue water filtration
Sponsor
He sent you a call earlier you have to bring some
From Compton to the show going to be
How many has
Embarrassed
So very clear what's going on here
Ridiculous
Chosen Nut Farm or ramshackle appealed
We made it does now
Like the idea that some dude
I want to help you
What are you talkin about
Go to my website
WWE
Jot
Dude we
We've all been around the internet
Feed still 2009
That too.
Alright alright I apologize
It's it's
There's a fun
Intuit
He broke Alex's
Rules on etiquette
He gave his website
Chances are money is tight
Landon
Planet Honda Limerick on a slant rhyme like that that's no good
Etiquette
That was I feel like I should get points for attic
You should never end
Our only limerick
You've been craving it
You didn't have to wait too long
Get to the point where Alex
What kind of work you put in
Watchmen
Because I've always
History
R Kelly Street
The Watchmen
Similar to the film itself
I'm going to work on my basic research
Graphic novel
The most revealing thing Alex has ever said
I read a lot of pictures of replace with like
I read the headlines of the the graphic novel
Zbigniew Brzezinski is in the Watchmen I assume Really wanted to understand this
Thing that I'm
Labeling is a grave
Threat to humanity
Sorry
I know it's a long
They doesn't take more than like 2 hours to
Patches were there like full pages of like document
And it's not like
Did you get through it
It's a f****** graphic novel would like with a book there's a
Standardized
Through the movie
Down the street
I was really worried you're going to save the black kid reading the comic on the street
I don't know why you wouldn't just go ahead and read it if you thinks it's like the Illuminati Bible
IHeartRadio
Physically hard for him
Hurt him
And some way otherwise I don't see why you so averse to doing it
The gist of it
But I think he might have done that
Cable
Some of the wrong man
And maybe some wrong message
Pictures about the movie
D2 and one of the first ones
Is a Illustrated Alex
You cannot breathe on Mars
I don't care
But here's the first what I would do
Describe
Massive
Misunderstanding
Watchmen
I've done some basic research
A picture of Watchmen
Mason
And end all of this Illuminati
Cookie also Alex and 28
When you're drunk doing interview in a hotel room
Also that I forgot that that's the reason I brought that up is that in order for
Is like a narrative
It's some point between 2009 and
In that nine years the Illuminati had to have literally been
It's some point remember him
Idea
But
If you look on the cover
Smartest man in the world
Call CDI in forest
Breastplate
Misrepresentation of the misunderstanding
Then I would seem to be having is
Is the leader of the hero
No he's the villain he's literally the entire point of the book
He's a complicated villain much like Rorschach is a complicated hero
There is no
The book
He is the leader of the heroes
Like he is somehow a he's not
In the in the graphic novel that you skim
Ozymandias is present
It is a much more cumin
Flawed figure where is because I think the ACT
So terrible
Did Matthew Goode
It was able to get those note
And
In the movie by cutting out the entire part about the dark freighter
You lose a lot of them
Contacts
4 oz mandisa's character
The humanity of
Being
At the Villa
A sacrificial Ville
I don't know
Extraordinary Gentlemen
Some of his stuff I worked at a movie theater in high school movies came out
Encephalitis are Killing Joke is really good 12
He does a really good job of like crap
Complicated
Stories as opposed to
Hero Stories that may be good and bad
There's blurring of lines
I'm serious
I never read that, from hell I never read the comics
Did you watch the movies
I know I watch V for Vendetta
Might have watched
Cuz that came out when I worked at the theater
They don't have a
Catalog
Stephen Fry
Absolutely
Killed it and beer
Yeah everybody else you know you you win or lose somebody
I don't like that movie
It's just
It's like an aesthetic masquerading as a movie
What I watch watch
I didn't think it was terrible
Like when I watch the movie I thought like
I I did I really didn't like how
People like the comedian
Superhuman strength
Guys and stuff
Didn't like how knightowl was presented as like
Contradict
I really hated that guy I liked
Wilson literally everything
It's not like a boy
Yeah
I think there were a lot of problems with the movie but I still had a positive
Experience
Like it got me a little bit
Perfectly cast
Who played dr. Manhattan
Yeah Billy crudup
Salvageable
It's not
That's good
Also crushed it in Princess Mononoke
I don't care
I'm not embarrassed
Memory from Pieology
X
Times it's been stolen
I went to somebody and never come back
House burned down a lot
Copies
Been stolen from me and then I wouldn't have worked out
Amor does great work but
Crazy massive misunderstanding of the text
To think that Asia mandamus
Is Bagheera
You could
You can make we had back-to-back great
Davis
You can make an argument that Ozymandias was trying to like resent himself
And position himself
Leader of all these do
He wasn't the leader of the heroes
You wouldn't even l
I think because
He wins in the end that's why Alex
Maybe
Cuz he just
Assumes that the
The hero wins
Which is which is another.
Looks looks
He has a any more to say about that
Glaring
What kind of depth
Text Jeff
He is so dumb
Illuminati New World Order
To let the public know what they're planning
Magical powers
What they're doing how they operate
In all fairness to Allenmore
In His official
But he himself
And promote Illuminati
They reveal the Illuminati
And what
Trailer
Play the trailer
Which is Grace
Of course
Play the trailer for an audio medium radio show
Slow down version headlights
Sound effects coming out of the water
Message will look up to me and say help
And I will say
No
Smashing Pumpkins
Concept
Like that is just
You keep saying that Alan Moore is amazed
I don't know if that's true
Care
Books about the Masons
And I'm not going to watch the rest of it
So cute
That's a great conspiracy
TV review I love that anytime there's a anytime
The Templars are the ones who are real
You are
I don't I do not like the idea of it being so much
Anti-woman
And no it allowed all that stuff yet
This documentary
Heretofore unknown
Believable access
To the temple the the Masonic temple in London
Yeah I would just like the biggest
If they are f****** straight-up dorks
They're all dorks
Who are really into ritual
And they show them
Rehearse
Doing a dress rehearsal of the ritual the Grand Master of the lodge
You got the script of the ritual and he's like looking over it while the new acolyte is
Like rehearsal
These are Peter Tork
Turn up my friend
7 or 8
His dad was a mason
Memory of the Masonic
Temple
There was a magic the Gathering
I lost my friend
One he's really really good at these people getting
Together for the most part to have a Social Club into do these little mini plays
Give you that same charge
That you might have if you did plays there's a real thrill today and then also
Baptist
Directions to regalia of the aprons and out about everybody loves them
It's so fun
Talk about a bunch is the idea of
The reason that the stonemason routes
What they do
Try and help people
Become better
Through the metaphor of build
But the idea of building a house you put a breakdown
Another brick
Put another breakdown eventually you got a good house
That's the way you feel is one of those bricks
Sure that's the way you can live your life
You can make yourself a better life by laying brick after brick after brick
It's not it it doesn't
Filas
If you do that that's
The great wisdom
So anyway
Really invested in
I don't particularly care about that
Watchmen
Alan Alan Moore
Are you
Exactly
Any number of things he could have pulled
Then they already pulled exactly the wrong song
Bright
So Oliver has made me the best
Quicksilver like what you have here is you have a guy
Characters Ozzy mandamus
Ability to understand
Prince to a poem about the hubris of rulers
Their temples crumble
And s*** like that
Wink
What do you remember Neil Gaiman
Illuminati
Talkin about
No clue
It's crazy
Going to talk more about how we going
View the film.
That much just talked about
Important
Watchmen
Reviewers
Yeah.
These are the superheroes
Stop
Alright
Goodwill
Grassy knoll
Warshak
And we'll break
Their plans to the public
Think about that for a little while but Alex before you understand any of this
You need to realize
This is a fictional universe
Big Blue Magic Man
Life imitates art that has
Here's the other problem
The false flag
Stop and all that
In the book
The movie presumed
Universe
Where there is going
To be a nuclear war
Is awful
And horrific and it's why he's the villain
But
In that universe
It worked
There was going to be a nuclear war
Vig
Dear
Essentially like
Would you
Pull the lever
Alright you got one person on the train you got five people over there
People and kill one person
Right
Apple watch
All of the narrative
Flourishes
Characters
Is utilitarianism
That's all it is
No
You killed because
But he is incapable of stopping
Irregardless
Flight differ
Will
Which kind of suspect
Yes that is the thing that's going to wear deals which is the entire
I have to not do that destroyed
To his own destruction
Which is
I don't know man
I love you and Alex gets into literature
I love it
We have one more clip of him breaking down the Watchmen
Because he doesn't really get into too much
Wait I thought you were only doing
We are
Bigfoot
XSport
The thing is that he doesn't really
He plays the trailer at is it the Illuminati Bible
It's going to break coming back and being like
Number one movie at the Box
Quite frankly America
And then
Related to other things
TV show The X-Files spin-off the lone gunmen
And play the clip from that where it's at
Things to talk about
Aldine HAC
I was on his show and said that
At the CIA
911 plot
Coronavirus
I think Alex just like
Anybody who describes himself as a lone gunman
Regardless of
X-Files Network
Don't know if it holds up stranger
Watched
Just cuz
Not one of my things
The X-Files
I feel like it's too late
Enjoy.
Netflix
Kind of thing
Safety companies
A lot of fun Gillian Anderson
I love them both
Yeah that one was really good
She was great in American Gods
All this is to say that his analysis
It doesn't
But this next clip
I think really sums up to the first misunderstanding I believe is that Ozymandias is a good guy
I thought it was his name was Ozzy mandamus
The double prong misunderstanding
What's true
That is the first like
Essential misunderstanding
Bring
Send me related
Nicole misunderstanding
The wound in the earth that looks identical to the mall out of World Trade Center
American flag
And he says to
Doctor Manhattan
Twin brother God
This stop
Now the Soviets in the United States
And
The bad guy Rorschach
Doctor Manhattan children
B****
And that is the message the world is saved
And Lucifer
Man is going to travel the stars as a universe
Earth has been saved
The band
Has been killed
Warshak who's against child molestation against
Police brutality
Because
Has been defeated
Alex thinks he's Rorschach
Wow you really does think he's very shy
Alex
Deeply identifies with Roche
Verb
BB comics in history
You really onto his own deck
That that Rorschach
Character
Yeah I know
You could fight his way out of
A prison cell
Alex
More with the like
You think I'm in here with you
You are in here with
I mean there's no other way
Entire thing
It's based on the misunderstanding of
Alignment
First of all good vs Evil
Alex
You think you're
Hindi story
You think you're the best
This speaks volumes about your psychology
Ostensibly
The character you most identify with is presented as a couple
Navigate to gyro
You still find a way to be the victim
Fascinating
Some sort of
Paranoid
No.
Through so many different like different tendrils different ways
It's fascinating
A movie review can't be done without getting into some sort of
This is about me
The globalist
Audrey Mann Davis
And Doctor Manhattan
The global
Coming together against me Rorschach
I guess Jason bermas is night owl
I don't know who else is around Arab do is this the funny
Take me to work
It goes to Commercial and comes back
Linda Rob Jacobs
Comes in
Studio talk about Watchmen
Yeah
There's no extra analysis really
But you can tell
Rob comes in
Hiroshima
Uses to say Ozymandias his name because he knows without you
Keepsake
He'll know that guy
Call man
Advance
To the end of the watch
Portion of the show
Affiliated familiarity with Motrin
Absolutely
That is
He gets everything so wrong
And if you want to stay
To get everything
Because the Watchman has a lot of themes that
Everybody can really kind of
Understand no matter what
Like even if you're even if you don't agree with like the overarching themes or anything
You can find one or two like
Why does
Alex just go like
That character the comedian he really knew what the f*** was up you know like that's kind of what he is that's
Region
You know
Problems from that character
Exact
Play Alex
Fair enough
Move along I don't think you got to the bottom of anything
You never say what you wanted to say all done in like 5 minutes
They are bad
They made a movie trying to say I'm bad
It was all about me
How does the movie
What did dr. Manhattan blame for the attack on New York
There's a doctor Manhattan Society
She's going to live in the stars or whatever and then he realizes he has to be the bad guy
Psychics
Becomes into
Manhattan
The better end
I think the movie is worse than
But I think the
Because in the movie
Manhattan is Blaine
At the end then what that really
He says there's that
Is the ultimate
In order to
Fight in order like
Break yourself
Constant cycle of violence
Interesting perhaps
Perhaps because what is Doctor Manhattan other than
A physical
Sure
He also says with the symbol on his head is like a illuminati but it's
Yeah I know it's just a regular atom
Like
If an atom is the symbol of
The Illuminati
That kind of
Everybody
Yep fun talking about this
It's always fun
Whenever Alex
Can actually enjoy
It's kind of fun
Impossibly bad reader
Interpreter
Fascinating to me the level of missing the point
I don't know
You've got a
If you ate
Freshman
High school list
Kind of
Ability to understand
Subway
Has all of this
Pent-up
Rage and inability to
Process
But if you if you live like if your
If you're reviewing a piece of narrative fiction
Yeah
It behooves you
Predictive programming
It behooves you to live within the parameters that that Universe set
Because otherwise
Is the story of differ
There if you try and stay
Real
And like
121 applicable
To real life
You're you're depriving
Work of its content
Depriving
When you're supposed to be specially respect
Superheroes
Ennard X scream
Or whatever like
Alex
So here you stupid again he has another Gaston
On this episode
No longer
Cs50
To just talk to his
Water filter sponsor
Here's another guy
Hjm 17 in Oregon declared 10th Amendment
Sovereignty
To my friend
Couldn't you just like
We missed it
We missed he is a little short about
Looked into
Representative
Denison
Dennis Richard
Interviews
10th Amendment resolutions
Reasons that are just there to hide the fact that were angry that the Press
Dennis Richardson
2007's from the House of Representatives
More likely to abuse children
Statistics
Being different than normal marriage during Portland are more likely to
Abused boys
Also in April
He sent out an email that started
Exhaust leak has been like no other
On Monday the world witnessed
The tragedy at Virginia Tech in Blacksburg Virginia
On Tuesday Oregon
The passage of domestic
Sick benefits for same-sex
But the fundraising email
Of course that's the way he's bringing fix though it's a tragedy that has befallen us
Call Tom
These Pilots
It's just to say
Hey man all of these dudes
They all are either racist
Stuck in a
Very white
Good portion of History
Interesting
It is like
Statistically
Impossible
All of the people Alex would have on
Habitat
A random sample set
Even people who are
Possible
Have bigotry in there
Yeah I might have gone down the wrong Panther
The fun thing
About Obama being
Is that
It gave all of those
Rite-Way
Racist
You know you and I would call Republic
Like
A common Boogeyman
Their other hatred
Kids at Bay
You know
President
Navigate to go towards everybody like immigrants
Like they're just shooting hate left and right
So many teenagers master
It's smoke them out of their holes
This is also can be frustrating
Miraculous
They're all the same
This is a very weird way that Alex
Comes back from break in the middle of the show
The world's population
Add more than half the world's wealth
Why in the world
Perfect
Conquer the world
Country
South Africa's got roughly twice
What is a squall
Wonder why I wonder why
A version of history that
On par with your understanding of Watchman in terms of accuracy
100 bullets
The idea that it's so
We just play along with
The Sandman that we used to have half of the world's wealth but it's all been stolen
So crazy
Wait is that what he said
Because I thought you meant
We have half the world's wealth
Because we stole it
Since the time we used to have it is all been stolen from us
Sure doesn't
Rate
I'm pretty sure
Had a good run
Now we come to
The last guest of
The Alex has
He's done his he's said his piece he's giving his breakdown as Watchmen
They want to plug things I got to bring content absolutely table or you live
Elvis is totally cool
And now we get to this last
Yes I'm of the last guest
Just from a guess
Compton
I don't know why
Danny Bonaduce is he going to have Danny Bonaduce
I don't know if he's ever been on
And who years it was important
Greg pound does great work at free our kids.com and free our children
Everything is always told me turn out to be documented
I want to talk about that
From
Tony Alamo Alamo Ministries not familiar without David persecuted
I'm even closer to ship me the news Clemson articles for about a year
So Tony Alamo is being persecuted we got the
Is Greg pound coming on to talk about it
Let's see where he goes with his why is this
Greg
There's always so much going on because you have
Lost her sheep
That your wife had another baby she's in hiding so they can't get the baby out
Producer
But the thing is is is Alamo ministries.com
Is basically I mean they do the starting and we know as parents at these these immunizations
Start the best thing for children
When there's no rules Charlie Sheen children
Because he doesn't vaccinate
I want to vaccinate the children
Alama Alama
That I guess that
What's the narrative I mean
You know you do have a right to put your children in danger that way I guess if the parents decide
I don't know I mean it
Sure I mean look how is that is that the story where we're going to be going with
I mean I don't resist going to change
Well I mean
Some parents spank already
Lake-Link
Angela
One of the things is
If they they did say that they had
Rain scheduled and it was up parents
Thanking their children nothing
Children
Because Tony Alamos
Not vaccinating and then there's
Family members were in
Buying or though you know I mean this guy
Clearly persecuted by the hour
There's no
Hey Giorno to tell you a little bit about Tony Alamo
Born in 1934 Hoffman
Tony Alamo and his wife in mission for God in 1969
They formed Alamo Christian Ministries and set out to build a congregate
If there's anything I know about people who form their Ministry 1969
No Sinister element that all
They did so they built their church and preaching to the deaf
Drug-addicted promising
Them food and shelter at their Church
Of course their church was located in rural cross
Four County
So once the folks got out there
Did realize they're kind of stuck in off and decided to stay
And ended up working for one of the lawn mowers business is already is farm for no pay other than room and board
Right now
But in this case Tony elamo demands that anyone who joins
The church takes for them to be a member of his church and simultaneously taking
Valerie is really just cutting out the middle step of them having to give it back to the church after he's done
Jesus
4 years
Basic exploitative religious
Bass community
Advantage of the people
Also offering them drugs
Treatment Services
Here to be some good work
You know it
His wife Susan
Tony went up
So this is f****** Heaven's Gate situation
For six months
She kept Susan's body on display in their church because he believed that he was capable of bringing her back to life
All right that's not good according to Alicia Frank Alamo compound at the age of
She and other compound children were told if they prayed hard enough Alamos wife Susan
Who died from cancer after the compound move to Arkansas would rise from the dead
Each day she did not awake
The children were feet
For everyday
Go
That does not mean to Tony was
Total lunatic cult leader
Before then
Tony
Stripping them of their
I told OregonLive
You slept on the floor in a sister's room
You didn't have a bed
A few of the chosen ones had beds
You didn't
Who controlled relied on an Insidious level of social shaming
The cat people in line
Again from Diane Bach
Call
They were told what to wear what to say
To think all meals were served in
In the cafeteria with no choice
She said that anyone could be publicly rebuked without warning
And most of the followers lived in
In constant fear
One day box said she petted a llama on the ground
Soon an announcement came over the
Speaker during a church service
Susan Del Amo
Who said there was quote something mentally wrong with Bach for petting the llama
That was the message
There was no explanation
The rest of the prayer meeting was a blur
The rebuke meant that others in the compound refused to interact with
In any fashion with Bach for several months
Brand-new behavior for a
Naturally Tony got more abusive
In September to September 2008 Federal
No it September 2008 federal and state police raided a lamos compound after receiving some
Complaints
Investigation
Remember the Alamo accused of physically and sexually abusing children
And when asked
The same reason Jesus's living
When the dust settled Alana was arrested and convicted
10 counts in a Federal indictment accusing
Transporting minors across state lines for the purpose of sex
He received 175 years in prison
Guy behind bars
Somehow not long enough
Now
Put his body on display for six months
Beat anybody near him praise doesn't come back
The stories that came out in the investigation
The trial of the sickest
Of the sword
You always hear about call later
Tony Lama was running an abuse fact
Bringing young girls
Of 8 and 6
Make them as brides
His attorney appealed for Mercy ask Court consider a lamos goodworks to which one of his victims
Do number two said I can't believe you have the audacity to ask for mercy
What Mercy did you ever show up
One day less
Or 139 strikes as a board instead of 140
Did you ever once have mercy on an eight-year-old body
Quote from trial
One of his victim
Google call Harry Barnes was not interest
Branson elaenia
And he said quote
This court believes you should be incarcerated in federal prison for the rest of your natural life
Someday you'll meet a judge with higher authority than me may have mercy on
Your soul
Earlier this year in 2018 two of Allah most child Brides
It's came forward to share their stories
It's as bad as you would
Amy Eddie was 14
She was forced to marry
Pebbles Rodriguez with 12
They lived as brides for around a decade and we're regularly beat and starved and raped
Describe her time in the called quote I was terrified that if I didn't do what I was supposed
To do what you told me to do it no matter what it was
I'm going to
Amy and Pebbles were two of the young girls were free during the 2008 raid
Which Alex and his guests here on this show are trying to percent to some
The government,
Stealing innocent
Children
Because they refused to
Get back scene
Or respect by their parents
The way
Presenting
Serial child
At somebody who's likely
Almost
Alex
Care about the
Now here's where here's where things get real messy
Alex
Repeatedly already in the s*** that we've listened to
I said he's
A year to look into this
He's claiming that if
If you'd looked into it at all key would find
Liquor
Video the arrest in the raid was
We're in 2009
We're in March 2009 you're a lot of this information has come out
He's not setting
Until September
And the children were taken out
F****** wrecked
These are people like if you listen to Amy and Pebbles there
Telling of it
It was a being spayed
If you listen to hear the accounts from other even adult members of
Of the church
To escape
It's the sort of thing that is last
The rest of their lives
They're like 50 year old people who still
Can't make choices
Because of the brainwashing
In the abuse that they stopped
They all this church was about
It was about him stealing all of their money
Mentally f****** over it abusing all of these people of child bride
Totally f***** up
What are you I hate
Continue saved
Like I'm a
Get the
Sometimes just got a f******
You got it
You can't
No
Just know like you're not a member
Hope the human race goodbye and if you're a truth-teller if you're someone who's doing the radio show where you prefer to have
All the best information
You can't
You cannot allow some
Guest
You blind and make you endorse the elamo church
Wild f****** late
He's actually supporting a guy
Yep
Alex Jones
Straight up
Is endorsing Tony Alamo
Yeah man
I told you was going to be one of the worst things ever even worse
So Jordan
Trial
Across the street a cheetah makes
Shred
You reap what you sow. No mercy
Mixed
Three children ages
4 5 and 6
City of John and Jennifer
Colbeck
Fugitive is wanted for allegedly
Beating kids and adults
He
One of the former members of
The church kidnapped three of this lady's children
She's not feeding them send
He's a fugitive on the Run
So Alex is entire
Story that he's telling about the idea
The government came
A kidnap to be people's children
When they were rescuing child Brides of a cult leader it actually
When you dig a little bit deeper into the story you find it that cult
Did kidnap people's children
He's on the exact wrong side of this
No no
I don't have it I don't have a follow-up on that I'm sorry I just that.
I hope he's good
He did
Are poppies
Still allowed
Can we get a posse together what you need to do if you need to go out in public
You need to go out in public with a big boombox like your radio Raheem and just play beer for my horse
Play Willie Nelson
Respond
Pictures are real
Totally
Real
It's very f*****-up
Do you like realize
Hey minutes further f***** up for me to go about my business doing this show and learning
And then stumble into on the show where he's
He's f****** hilarious Eliseo
Identity
How do you do on the same episode waiting for you to sue me for PTSD and 3
Years like this is my fault
Can
You can't how do you
You do this
I just don't understand
Like isn't that why we're so fascinated
What would happen
That broke a human bring to the point where now it is
Completely divorce
From any concept of
Empathy
Or even simply
Just just
Non exist
Just a few or creature
I don't understand it
No it's even more f***** up is I don't think that's
The fairest
What hours is doing
May I really don't I don't think at the end of this episode him
To this guy
Accidentally
Personally endorse Antonio
He's acting himself
I think he's trying to
Cover his lack of
I think he's trying to spackle over how stupid
By pretending that he knows about this
Actual case
Yeah he doesn't know s*** about
If he actually did know anything about it he would
Absolutely not be on board
I don't know
You know what I want to I want to say I want to believe you
I genuinely do I want to believe that
That what you're saying makes sense but the more we learn about Alex
He'll defend anybody who
Who like I can't exist outside of what those liberals want you to believe even if that includes
Food ratings
I find it so impossible
To believe that
Would be something that you would be okay with
Like
Just my my feeling that there's that
But I might be wrong too
I don't know
I think it's more likely that he's just
Stupid
Expect
Talk about just vaccine bowl-shaped
Can't show apps on air
Or just be like
Let's read book I have more thoughts about Asia Matt Damon
Yeah it go with that
I don't get the head off
That yeah
I think he's I think it's probably
Mostly pasta
I think
But that might be the most optimistic
We now know about once again the stupid
Evil continuum
Comes
Mexico
This Greg pound guy at
Part of the alarm
So this guy is actually in the game on tomorrow
I can't say 100% That Bass
Hopefully this will let you see what I mean
The way he's praising things there's a lot of inclusive language
20 talks about
The group which led never directly says I'm part of this group
But it is
Fuels like
He's expressing
Communion
I want to thank you for being there because every time I've called you have open
Your program up in order for us to cry out as parent
I haven't seen my kids now for over a year this is going on for four years for three years we could only see him one hour a month you should know
I'm ministries.com in look at they put under website
Did the stipulations when they go to visit their kids what they can and can't say that can't whisper to their children
If this is what they doing your isolating the parents in the children and if they destroy our family we have no Nation
Christians everywhere protect religious persecution
So I don't know what to do with this Greg
But I don't know what to do with a box to put him in
In terms of him being like a facilitator between or
Actually
I'll tell you what
I can't find any information about great pound on the in
Who is the guy i k
I probably was born
What
Bernie
Whatever
Yeah so
I think that he should have started the end of
With this and then
Continue the interview ever
And also not
Brag you know a lot of times
When you call a
Come on I specifically know
Everything going to be covering the Alamo Ministries recap anything else you
Well if
Alamo ministries.com and if you just go there in 30 this ministry
It's hard to believe that they can take
37 children are there then have a pickup order 420 more
Snot
Very gracious
The best I could do for the
Pore sucker
Kids
When you come on you got to let me know what we're going to talk
Hey that's good
Should go with that go with that
Admitting that you don't know what you're talkin about don't allow this guy
Alamo Ministry
Don't do that you don't know what you're letting this guy plug
And then Alex says
Greg bring you up
Get like an hour and a half with you and Pastor Tony Alamo
Almost everything
Map
You know I guess you talked to Pastor Aleman
Alex the church is like a sleeping giant
And if the church doesn't wake up in America I mean if you could tap into the church and get the church woken up
I mean I mean this battle Beyond
Yeah that doesn't work that that sure
Are we
Nope
I mean that speaks for itself man that's the that's the
Disgraceful
Awful
I don't know what else
To say other than Alex
Through whether intentional or
Stupidity is
Running a propaganda PR front
The guy who marries kid
Well you could always go visiting with a f******
Macron
Bran
Yep
Price I know that's a real bummer deflating
Episode.
This is why the show is still like this is why the show in 2009
For me is so
Interesting as opposed to in the present
In the present were seeing the self-destruction of
I do think it's kind of dangerous
It's not really fun it's harder to laugh
It's too hard to laugh at him
Promoting
A sex cult
Abusing children
Define abusing children
Agree
Any kind of swinging sex called
This is a fascinating show
Article archaeological
Anthropological
Looking back at this this isn't
Fascinating the way you can
Set out to
Deconstruct watch
Get everything wrong
Come up with a bunch of other b******* along the way
Try and sell some water filters
I meant tumble like mr. Magoo ass backwards
Dorsey
A child rapist
Ostensibly most again
This is a fascinating
I don't I don't know how
I mean that
That is
It is interesting
To watch him be wrong about
Everything
Always
Like this episode is maybe the most
Wrong
He's been for a
Contiguous. Of time with no root
Do you mean
One month
Yep you know what you're not wrong about that why you're not wrong about it is wrong but you're not wrong about it
And then what
He's an unrepentant
Ignorant bastard so fun because it's different kinds of
It's like he's trying to bat for the cycle
Within an episode
Single double triple a homerun over wrong it's crazy
Hertz
It hurts your Humanity
This sort of thing
But at the same time
Like this
From Miami
I would do this all day
Has been on
Before but I've not heard it so you haven't been on in 2008/2009 episodes that I look
Alex was
Of Alamo
But I don't know
For sure of grapes
Other.
Alarm
I'm convinced
The emphasis on the 2nd
Syllable
But I know
Alex is also being tricked by his love of Colonel Travis and the Alamo
Tony Romo Tony Alamo
So yeah
Probably talked about more
Like CPS is taken
Kids kind of narrative
Vaccines are being forced on people more germane to Alex
His bread-and-butter
Where's this
Find me the way that Alex that even in that clip like you got to let me know we can talk about ahead of time
Stephen of departure a little bit
From what that you would usually talk a little bit uncomfortable
But not
I think the uncomfortableness is
Arrangement taken up
He's slightly out of his death
With authority about
Obama Ministry
Right you can't bring up like
Documents
Passive
Is out of position
Poker
Terminology
You know it's just
It's weird to
It's weird and it's super weird on this level
You look at this
He's not playing good defense
But he has the insert
Yeah you know a little
Yeah yeah
I don't know it's just
I don't know what I don't know
Cuz I feel like
I feel like anyting
I feel like anything I say is to
You close to like
Intellectualizing
Horror
That is the end of the
I don't want to do that
That is part of the Fall
The Detachment of
10 years old
If Alex was doing this and present day
Brave
I don't know
With the years you're like
Well I mean of course he defended a child rapist Lego up what that doesn't make sense at all
Fresh president Kavanaugh
Might as well
Cheese's pizza
Guys man
Wild
They're everywhere
Fondant not fun as is the case with all of our episodes
Simultaneously in separate our brand is hilarious
No no no no no no
There's not a lot of shows
They can go from Ozzy mandamus to
Like
Hard to do
The boys
That was Environmental
Our website, they're going to check that out
Some stuff coming in the future are there places
Where you could find us that you
Could not perhaps
Alex Jones
Twitter
You could acknowledge underscore
Yep Facebook
You were there
If you would like
Sports show to go to website knowledge flights.com
Put that sport the show but would appreciate it
I'm sick and tired of telling my blood I'll still do it until like
I don't have to
I was in there today and I text
Did you about this Jordan there was a
Aggressive conversation going on about the Bill Cosby
There were two people yelling about how
Schoolboy
Abilene
They're never going to lock up Weinstein cuz that guy is a Jew
Gotta get out of here I can't handle this
I don't know I don't know if this is a reverse Pez dispenser I don't know what's going on
The conversation
What's going on over there
Blood Center
Reviews being a Highwayman
But
If you want to support the show you're going to need to because that's the only way we're going to get one
Locked up apparel
Also you know it's hard to say what's worse about Alex
Being a public relations
Sky Ferreira
Childbearing
The fact
So we always need to remind
Holding
Alex