Alexandra Thurston color
Yeah
I feel like if a DMZ is Court like
It's really frustrating
So that was like dealing with this
Yeah
When I was 19 I got a DUI
Really
I was driving home from the party
Pretty bad about this book
I was driving home
And I've left my coat at the party
And you know it Central Missouri
Everybody drives drunk
It's you don't need a pre-emptive lead Avenger
That's sort of Worlds that I was listening
Everyone
Survive
For the most part we don't all have been eligible for
Party I left my coat there it
It was really cold outside
I was driving home
That's pretty far away from anything
Like any businesses or any
Black ice
My car slid off the road into a ditch
Yeah and I tried to
To get the car out of the ditch
Like reverse and all that
I didn't have my coat
Forever had a cell phone
And so I'm like
S***
I need to get
Out of here what do I do
Supercooled I looked around there was nowhere I could walk
F*** it
I'm just got to bite the bullet on this
So I put my flashers on
I've had a few drinks
You are not good at preemptive defense if that's your opening line
Might turn combatives like I might
I wasn't afraid of the cop or anything like that
Going through this I just told him I have some drinks let's let's
Take care of this
They took me down to the station
I got
Then I got in trouble stayed there a couple hours
Can pick me up
Top
But I swag down the coffee
It also has a couple Missouri so he's like well everybody maybe a little bit of
But
Written the judge I might be
It ended up becoming stiff
It wasn't even amidst
Because of the Court
A bunch of money
Take a DUI class
And what have you
It was horrible wake up call
Never got behind the wheel of a car
With any alcohol
Really I have not ever done that my car slid off the road
Cuz I hit this
But it was so terrifying
That moment of feeling like completely out of
Control
Like viscerally imprinted on me
Because
When I hit that the ice was the problem
But also I knew I'm too drunk
Putting in terrifying
Fun
Story
The cop who ended up
Ended up being the security guard at the theater that I real
A couple years
Later
Security guard
And we said hello.
Diagnose
It was really
Alright super cool
I was actually in
Some some small-town it was only 25 minutes away from where I grew up
Middle of nowhere
Comedian drunk
Like 130
And I'm driving home
Drunker than normal human being should be but it doesn't affect me as much
Driving home
Get drunk
I ran out of
And I am driving home on the highway
Get off
At the stop on my hometown
And
I'm like looking around it's 2 in the morning
No cars for a million miles so I'm just like
F*** this red light and I just take a left and start going
And turns out
Directly behind me was a cop he pulls me over a man
Pablo Ramirez like what are you doing
Now this is where being white
Was
I would also like to say that I recognized
Oh yeah how lucky I am
Oh yeah
Here's what happened
I watched you just do that was like
You do know there's a cop
What's going on here
You know it's like 2 a.m. there's nobody driving and I really gotta pee
Any bike well don't do that anymore
I'd like to go immediately like that was it
You're wondering why
Lil B tiny bit
That is correct
Better Business to go over
To take a
From Alex Jones stories
Run-ins with the police
Today first of all I would like to say thank you
Someone who has just joined up and
Supported the show
Thank you so much
Tiger whale
I'm a policy wonk
One last thing
For someone who has level
I'm probably going to f*** it up but thank you so much
Cloudkill Darius
You are now a technocrat
Natalya brilliant someone sodomites
I don't want
Thank you so much also
I agree with you wholeheartedly but sephiroth did deliver the killing blow Cloud near the end
Just couldn't do it
So how dare you
How dare you sir
Final Fantasy 7
I heard that I've heard that
Do you know how real this dude is
What's up
Something Borrowed
Japanese translation
Eros
Is the American Transit
Or person jumper
Much thank you very much if you out there would like to
Really appreciate it by going to
Do knowledge fight.com or website
And cooking support the show
Jordan we are
Still back in
Because I
Handle the prospect
Listening
Alex Jones
In the present
I know I could I could tell you what he saying
I'm sure
50 women who are accusing Kavanaugh or Liars it's deep State operatives there is some b******* like that
How could we not top
Hot
That unique of a point of view on this particular
I don't foresee anything that he's not coming back
To some sort of dumbass
Deep State b*******
Or something or it's just a conspiracy that the clintons are putting together
Impossible
I don't want to go into any
Don't feel like it's fertile territory I don't think what he's going to bring to the table
He's going to be in any way interesting
I meant we already know that is modus operandi now is
Being a multi-level
Marketing guy who's
Possible self-destruction
Field ugly to look at it
I don't
I don't think that
Even though we're being critical
I still don't think that it's
Good to look at
Get that
Maybe we'll check in eventually and I'll try and sort that out
Children in
Distributor
They're they're coming for your children Angela
Do we know how bad
2008-2009 time
Are we involved
The crash the dollar oh here's Bob Chapman to help me sell rabbits
Unemployed
Working for the man the globalist want to destroy the middle class
Is your ticket to the middle class
Which is which is why almost
I wouldn't come to it
I did not expect for Ozzy mandamus to overtake
In terms of the audience
Response but
Review
Really hit a lot of people
Close to home
Apparently graphic novel fans in Oradea
Can't imagine why
Clyde did not kill
On March 10th
Day after
Endorses B Tony Alamo sex cult
Weather Marion kids
I'll be honest with you when I started this episode ice fully expected him to come on Aaron be like
I didn't know about the Tony Alamo situation
I am so sorry
Without the information
But I will say this
He does make one retraction on this episode
But I will not tell you whether it has to do with Tony Lama or not
No
Rapist is bad
Egregious
Linguistically
So here we go where to start where Alex starts
Episode is going to be talking about
You know the Tea Party
Is it going to be talking about
Beef Louisiana
Flu stuff
He's building up to
Is it the Tenth Amendment what is it going to be
Powerful
Litchfield is going out
We trust in God we know it's going to make it out we know it's going to get it on
7:40 broadcast
So far all he's been doing is promoting the Obama.
Is that which filmatography
Can you redo
Directions
Towards Alex
We're going to
Because this sucker is going to blast the New World Order
Big time
Is it going to put them on blast
I want you to get it and I want you to put it on every MySpace account every Facebook account
I want every email list over and over again
Posting every message board inform out there
Liquor store hours
I want you to tell him
This is the red pill
The Matrix
Nothing more
Bush and Obama
Do you truly want to fix things
Here's the red pill
Countdown
We're launching early
Fabric
It's just so much is going on so much has happened in the enemy is moving so quick I want to drop now
Lycamobile
Can we release it now
Or should we wait
Building up the momentum
Building up the big dynamos the servos
Fire
Has to have to tape
Deception to their face while he says exactly that
Scottsdale
Gross
You spent
20 minutes of beginning of show documentaries
Mi maybe not
I don't know what I'm alright
Not really discussing any per se in the beginning
This is 20 minutes of
Before our show I know that that's that's a whole lotta
My DVD is coming out in DVD is coming out
Not only
It better go megavirus
Mega Megabus scenes absolutely
So this
This clip is one of the end
Episode
It made me realize that I
Like a lot of songs that I didn't
Realize I like
And it might just be because the juxtaposition with Alex is like
Do you suck so much
That I actually
Kind of like the poem
What do you mean you kind of like the police
Shore Bank
Fight back against the bank
What day is it
Friday
We're all over the map in terms of 12 things going to come out
If your best way to fight
The bankers
Criminal
Also I'd like to point out to the audience
The Jordan in the middle of that clip wrote down on his notes
What's an!
I think they're f****** Revolution
That's fine
Walking on the moon
Soft music
Then I realize or care to know
Compartmentalize them in real easy listening soft rock, category
I'm genuinely serious like
Anytime I listen to the police I'm always listening
Fair enough
OnPoint
Turn on.
Immediately
Attack
That he's got to get this out cuz
The deathblow to the globalist
Yeah
That all is the first like going on in the world
The first like 40 minutes
Interminable
He's talking about The Obama Deception
And having seen The Obama Deception
A little irony
Now Alex
Two-story
It's out of the degree
Canada
Okay
Alex Alex
Number of really
Equally problematic
Errors
Reporting the story
And this is going to be
Flu all over again without 911 blogger call
Prison
Neverland
Duties would include Mass internment of citizens
After terrorist attack mirroring
Militarization of law enforcement in u.s.
The Canadian military is reorganizing a post
911 world
By creating reservist units for each area the country that would be tasked with providing domestic security
That's a quote involve such roles as the mass internment of citizens in the event of a terrorist attack
We get is a very aggressively worded measure if
True we've got
You know in another instance of Alex
Just reading about Joseph Watson article
Right
Planet
Problems with this
The first of all
Is just
Foundational problem with this line of thought
The reason that American troops
In the military
Serfdom
Plastic operations
Except for at the whim of the
The governor of the state
Is because of the Posse
Which is American law
Knox
Now 8
CID CID
Is another hurdle that we're going to have to
Just get over from the jump ever heard of Rome
Cuz they're pretending that we do have the same
And that that's a problem for their
Also there
A 1920
Defense Act which lays out the rules under which their military could operate
According to section 6 of the
A little bit too recent for Alex to know
Well I don't know I mean such a super like a really interesting history in terms of when they
They broke away from the UK
To like tournaments are you
19/22
Confections
Centex and I quote
The Canadian Forces are other elements
Any officer or non-commissioned material
Called-out
Super Service in Aid of the Civil power in any case
In which a riot or disturbance of
He's beyond the powers of
The Civil Authorities
They're pretty clear that the Civil powers can utilize
The commission person
Four things that they filled that they can't handle on their own
Section 6 even goes further to say the following
Nothing in these parts will be
Impose liability
Deserve
On an officer or
Member of the reserve Force
What is enrollment
Liable to perform Duty on
Active service
People who are opposed to being used to assist
Request the Civil Authorities
Have the right to refuse to take part if they want to
There is nothing like helping out after a flood or something like that they can just say
And I don't feel that appropriate
And they're not required to do that and they're like
To do that under the national.
Basic
Foundation document of the Canadian military
Can be called out
If there's Civil Authorities.
Situation beyond their control
Actual article that Paul Joseph Watson Road
I was just reading this post by Paul Joseph Watson
Sensationalizing
Existing story or Alex
In this case is a story about some reorganization
Missions going on in
Canadian military
The story comes out of the National Post
The conservative-leaning paper out of Toronto
If you pay close attention
Find a very
Paul Joseph Watson
Intentionally blurs truth and lies in order to
His angle super
The first is in his opening paragraph
The Canadian military
Is reorganizing
Priorities to sue the post 9/11 World of the country
That would be tasked with providing to mess
Security
And involves rolls such as the messenger
Spermatocele
The event of a terror
That is what Alex just read
On the air
And it is the
First paragraph
Apple Joseph W
Times articles
You wouldn't write it down
It'd be tough
To do that I mean anybody
Is usually the sign of a dictatorship
Fascist
If you know where in the article he's performing to cover Disney
Canadian military discuss Mass
Civilian
This is just Paul Joseph Watson Zone assertion being passed off as reporting
The closest the article comes to supporting that idea at all is quote
The units will include perimeter security
Prepare to cordon off an area if there was an atomic detonation
Nuclear accident
Or similar source of wide contamination
And arts
Response
Operate
In the far north
There's a big
Big difference
Between a unit train to cordon off a dangerous area to
Fallout or an outbreak
Specialized
People in the places
In case something
Something like that were to happen
Post 9/11 World
Paul Joseph Watson
Referenced in
Is open
There's a guy who's
Yeah and after that after 9/11 we all sort of realized
That we need to
Kmart in
Into domestics
I don't think that's
I think that's
Second happened
Do you think that it's a good idea for the military to be involved
Were there to be some sort of
Nuclear attack that resulted in the genetic mutations
The area
Make sure that everybody
It's still just like
DIY wooden
Cordoned off an area
Mental picture of a bunch of mounties with like police do not cross into Atomic crater
Route there
Cordoned off an area Snidely Whiplash
Terrible
Deals with this problem that the text itself.
Mass incarceration
Talk about cordoning off an area
Were there to be a disaster
The way you do by filling his articles
Isn't based on anything other than his own
Paul Joseph Watson
Do not have a good internal compass
He's a psychic
From his article quotes
Of course the necessity of
The changes dressed up
By using the notion of
Helping
People in the event of earthquake
Slugs in nuclear
But we also learned
He's at the reservists
Undertaker
Would be nice intermittent civilians
Or quarantine zones after a biologic
Terror attack
That is
Completely of his own design
Interpretation
He's making that up
Right that is not in the article
Extrapolate
From
The article but the mass intern me
Camp
First Citizens
Fleet liaison
Last time with the avian flu
He was lying based on lies of 911 blog
Just taking an article
And then Alex's
Bring It On Air
But I mean like
Looks like what is it
What if you do
Reidsville
And then just sits around being like
Well how can I write 500 words about this
Fairly innocuous
100-percent
He gets up
News probably try to find a
A few things that fit in with Alex's package
Planet
Alex Alex
Can men take the prison planet article and read it
Where is the valence had to read this article out of the National Post
You have a much more GIF
Difficult
Because there are exclamation
For the things that they're trying to lie about it
Does he work for
Pjw
In present-day cuz I will be a smarter move
We talked about this
Unless Alex Own Prison
Alex had prisonplanet going apologist Watson was
The editor-in-chief of it
I believe Alex
If you
You know what else is very dumb
Not the biggest idiot in the world you would have retained right
So doves goes on to use a quote from the article to jump to an unrelated
So this is from
Is his art
Actual article and follows it up
With someone else
Quote the Ramada
Heavy under analysis
The remodeling of the reserves will see the development of specialist units in
Informed the military's Regional division
Quebec
Ontario and the West
Navigate
This is an open announcement the Canada has been subdivided into military units and will be policed by
Military reservist
This is not an open announcement of anything of the sort
If you pay close attention
Quotes
This is development specialist units
Unit in four of the military's Regional division
These Regional disease
This is Justin implementation
Specifically trained in dealing with catastrophe
It did not seem likely before
But have entered people's minds
Hey so you know these guys who are trained to go do this one thing right well there's this new thing maybe we should train specific guys
Used to doing one thing
Don't just do that one thing to the people suffering from the new
Most of what's wrong with this
Prisonplanet article and Alex Jones
Take on it is fear mongering
But he's not done Alex isn't done talking about
But now you know that
Jean Colin
Do you like everybody
Horse Club
I don't want to be a casualty when they're dealing with the Canadian people
So that
Isn't the original article but it's not really
Context in the original article
Yeah but if I were to read that
Is Brigadier General is
Do I see a situation when we
Possibly
I would respond
So do I
Bright and instead of just letting people run
Accident
Contagion
Situation
Themselves get the smallpox
It's basically just the idea of
Containment
See any way around this
I don't trust
The powers-that-be in the world or anything like that but you need better than this
You need better than this if you're going to make these arguments about disproving prison in
Internment camp
Some s*** like that
I need more from you
That would that would never be allowed in our constitution
Anyway in the city
I'm going to get back to what he really wants to be doing
On the show which
Which is lazily promoting The Obama Deception
FEMA camps
Overtaken by the private banking
This weekend you got bored in the middle of your own story
2533 139
253 3139
I want you to get the DVD
I think Rob dude just hit him with a blow dart with some
Call it
Obama zombies come to your door from oettinger Northwestern
Launching
Obama Deception
Ladder
Hellboy
Like when you starting to yell there about rope and bondage
His arm is gone Noms and punches
His own arm
To try and get the feeling
He's yelling to try and excites himself
Wow
Irwin Alex is propaganda
How weak is b*******
He's like
I mean
I guess what
The Obama Deception is coming out not even in
Hour into the episode
Alex's episode
And you now have the second time
And I'm out
It's not bad but I think it's
It's not specific enough I wouldn't I wouldn't hear that and then be like
Still not good
You need this V in there for zombies
Obvious
That doesn't make me think of zombies
Kind of
What's interesting about this
Oh
Sex-bomb Tom Jones
That's why I asked
Alright
I'm sorry
Now go crazy
And that's because of
Couple days earlier Paul Joseph Watson
Another story about the military in Canada
Any references
In
Is Mew article the one that Alex was
Just going over
So Alex brings that by virtue of covering
And that one's actually even more
Finishing up with historical
Considering using trips
No
This is really interesting
Because
Glaring reporting errors
Paul Joseph Watson
Boxes that reference
6 days prior
Please
He is 100% wrong
What Alex's Alex's woefully misunderstanding historian
Diversion he's telling us that these troops from a nearby army base or being used
Because the drinking spots in that town or out of control the military
Come in and Felicia
In reality if you review The Toronto Star article to Paul Joseph Watson
Disposed on
Stories very
According to the star quote
City police on Camp Borden officers are
Using joints
Street patrols to help keep the peace
Peace and berries busy Entertainment District on
The military police would deal only with their own personnel and not
Civilians in Barrie
Fairy police chief
Waiting for
Soldiers would be less inclined to cause trouble if they knew would come up with their bosses on Monday morning
It's like an Army in some country
And instead of being allowed to I don't know
Rape and pillage to their hearts content they were supervised by some sort of light help
Since in many many many many historical situation
Really interested in is deacon
Instructing how Paul Joseph Watson is
Back in 2019
Interesting how he misuses
Like what we found with the avian flu thing 2911 blogger
It's really a
Interesting to see how like there's no way
Intentionally absolutely no chance
Realize that
Is it he does take a quote
From this Toronto
Star article
Just call yourself to Picayune
Everything fun
He uses beef
First half of a quote
And doesn't use
The 2nd
Which invalidates
Oh God Paul Joseph Watson doesn't
In addition Joshua Abel a berry bartender
Did he not heard any reports
Military personnel starting trouble
However
The part that Paul Joseph
Watson
Include is the end of April,
On the other hand if they are in civilian clothes
How would you know whether or not they're in the military
How do you leave that phone out cuz you're trying to make the other point
You're trying to trick people
Part of the quote
I wouldn't know they were military to begin with
Present bi
Idea that there is no military
Rowdiness problem
Police could help keep an eye on
It's all just about
The fascists
I am FEMA in Canada
Federal emergency
L2
PJ dubs
Not have
Some sort of paranoid
You might also
It could be a dozen
You're not wrong
You can have a latent paranoid that
You choose
To use
You know how a lot of
Stand-up comics are supermental
Unhealthy
And they use that
I think there might be something
Something like cuz I think at this point after so many years
Is Paul Joseph Watson
Slightly crazy
Yeah I think you would recognize like
I got to stop there
Or something like that
But that might just be me painting him with a little more Humanity
G8 Self Storage
And completely lying
Is on point
Further reading
That's fine under Canadian law
If they like the police in Barrie
Decides it like we could use some help from these troops
Well within the law for them to just do that
That's not a problem
So all of this is a hot load of nothing but
The reason that Alex
Is kind of like
And a little bit of ignorance
Yeah it's because he
Kind of thinks that Mexico Canada and America are already the North American Union
And also kind of things we all are subject
Back to the Queen of England
I do not know that
I believe he does think that
Based on this next clip
We are under control Obama
President
Republic
Left the Bush Administration
Dictatorship
We are in trouble
Quick Charge
I mean you might have President Bush
Using a Saudi Prince hands and
I would guess another president
Before the queen bee
I don't know that to be true
I also don't care if they do
So this whole Queen character
She controls everything everything
She controls everything
Oh so I have bad news
Bush People
Referring to wear British citizen
Technically Day Camp
Talking about the people from Australia
I think if you're not a bruise
I don't know how that works I don't know how that works either f*** that part
But if you're not a British citizen you can just get an honorary title which allows you to put the suffix
After your name
But you are knighted
Do not call you
Seltzer
In 2009-10
The latter has a bush guy
Calling Ted Kennedy
Is pretty much a
Big Stretch
Before that it was five years
American Impala
Ben that was Robert Brewster
In 2002
Birdy of course short for Robert in 2002 Alan Greenspan and Rudy Giuliani
Got the owners
Being named
America's Best
Honorary titles is not
Not always gone great
People in 1923 Benito Mussolini
One-time Nicolae ceausescu
Kbe title they know that one
Do push players have been awarded
These titles
Present
Even Obama administration
We got Bono
We got Angelina Jolie
We got Steven Spielberg
That's the cool thing about these titles if you aren't British citizen
Become a British citizen
You're automatically
If you become a citizen later a bunch of people have done it
Goddamn
You got to go
Around and try that they would probably annul it
Yeah I know Kevin Spacey
I assume it's just a wig
Missingno is like
Some sort of a relationship
Britain
I'm sure with Kevin Spacey
Some sort of action
Do you have
And of course be willing to wear sunglasses
Flowers
They've misfired a number of times to say the least
The British Monarchy you bet
Murderers Row little Murderers Row
Each of them had a moment when it didn't look like they were going to be as bad as they were
History before they break terribly
There's a glimmer of hope
And that looks like this might work out
Maybe if we give somebody the Peace Prize they won't commit genocide
And that's just not been the case
I just not been the case
So
Now we get to about the hour
Michelle I only know that because
Alex comes back
Break right in about an hour
He's got to the doctor
Ron Paul
Real romper
Are you surprised
Okay fair enough
It's been a long time who gives a s***
Cuz it's just in Spain
A lot of the time when he's on
He does
Sort of
Pieczenik roll
Steve pieczenik not back on the
Already playing
At this point
Alex got narratives that he wants
Enforce
External Authority
Credibility
To get his back
What about this
Okay
Basically
Hey dude pretty race
Interesting you should bring that up an interesting take on Bernie Sanders in 2000
Like so many of our issues we bring different factions together liberal
And conservative under the Constitution
Because if you're a good honest liberal the like
Bernie Sanders
He's an honest person
So Alex even is like
He's very liberal
As if those two things are shocking to have
According to Alex
John Birch Society none dare call it
Conspiracy root
Socialism
Get you into communism
Authoritarian
Is Ron Paul
He's great you know he's a good
Kind of liberal
Socialist but that is a good idea that socialism
It was a tricky when the communism on auditing the Fed
Authoritarianism know
The enemy of my enemy is still
Alex is on the same page
He's very Pro Bernie Sanders in 2009
Because he's
Working for
In the aftermath
Really strong propaganda effort to get you to not be on board
Like his messages
Really kind of universal unless you're a billionaire
Like there's no there's no if you're just like a regular person there's no like
The rich pay more taxes than me
He's the kind of guy
There's a lot of possibilities
Misinterpret
That's why the propagate
The right
Israeli effect
Politician
I want to take the piss out of Ron Paul
Probably involved in taking over
Dominica
Problem
Writing of his race
The staff newsletter for years who knows
F****** dumb ideas about the economy
Good morning
Intervent
Great
Goodwill Akron
But
You're a dick hole comes on Alex Jones Show basically wants
To spread fear about how the dollar is going to collapse
That's pretty much
Standard operating
Procedure for most of his
Back in 2009
Let's see if
Dr. Ron Paul's any different
We all have to be prepared I think we should prepare our families and I think financially.
Either going to destroy the dollar I don't see anything wrong with people believing in the constitution in
Bowling with a talk should be legal tender and only a few gold coins a few silver coins and on how to defend themselves
That's what the founders talked about
With a focused founders
If I understand correctly the founders mission
Was like yourself no big deal that's
Write it up
Alright good work founders
7 year old man
Is VX
Zaxby's
Coming
Spinning out
Some of the very similar
Bureau God-fearing America
And Alex
Promoting
He is still excited with the idea of giving out these DVDs when Obama zombies come to your door
But he takes
Further
The stinks of desperation
Is every time they come to your door
He needs
Go out
Sounds like
Yobama
Do better
Alright
From the
Stan you earn
India
Every small town
This is like the early Nazi party
You need to rush out to them
Alex
Completely imagine
For people to go edge
Places with
His DVDs get video of it
Understood the value of that sort of
Sensational
It's kind of impressive
I'm making prank videos back then
Harnessing that is
The marketing Alex
Is very
He's telling them to go out and bait people into yelling at you
Which he convened use for Market
Innocuous DVD
The Obama Deception
Deception you shouldn't be allowed
Anyone ever bought one
What I'm saying is that every Library should have like a metal
To text copies of the Obamas
Deception
You have one you have to leave it
At the door, Colton never would buy
Best deal
Just on YouTube like for free
Did Obama take office
Prisonplanet.com
Soccer
You got a bookstore or a church
Forest School
Orb
Credible
That's another imagine
Interaction
Anything Obama sells
Please buy my s*** in bulk you'll be able to move you everyone's going to want to buy
A bunch
We all know how those DVD racks are full of quality program
All the times that we got it done roadshows ended up at like some f****** gas station with a shower in it
Killing a little bit of time of that truck stop.
What's this fake Iron Man movie
All good
I told you up top
The beginning of this episode
That
Yes
I know I f****** hoped it would be about Tony Alamo
Because that was pretty
Disgraceful at the end of the last episode
It's a retraction and zeinab Issa
And Then followed by a beefed-up
Classic
You good you take a bath
Is really actually right
Recipe for
Who wrote the Watchmen comic book reader
I just got the book Sunday
Incorporation State and Terror attacks
Appointment
Manhattan was not a god
Is that developed
Like one character
Even the character in South was like
And neither can I
Regardless
Alright whatever
Neil Gaiman write
No no this retraction is like he didn't really but there's some crossover
Graphic novel
Spiritual connection
In between Alan Moore's work
But there's also a spiritual connection between Allenmore is working
Lovecraft
I think I remember Rorschach showing up in good Omens
Who this is
Interesting
Impotence of like
Alex
Misinterpreted the hell out of Watchmen
Kept saying Ozzy man Davis
And then said that
Allenmore did Sandman
Wichita retracted one of these
Most
Actually
Enterprise pronunciation
It's so interesting
Need to do that
There's no reason to do that this crazy somebody who works there
Probably there was just like
Look
Everything was cool
It's awesome
But I'm not going to fight you on
But seriously
Sandman is maybe the greatest
It's not a graphic novel ever written if you're not going to respect that it was Neil Gaiman
I got I'm going to quit
This is a resignation level offense Alex
You won't notice
She's not listening to all of this
Alex
At all
It doesn't
Like there's no indication
Vicky's
Realize he was wrong
But also he doesn't say it
Of it
It's most likely he know
That is a retraction
Are you interested
This is a mic down
This is this is a mic down to Joe Asian.
Jason bermas is about to come in with some Allenmore wisdom
That is so crazy
And goes all over the place
You have to hear all of it
So
Preemptive
Is it
Wisdom about Alamo
Alan Moore's wisdom
Or is it wisdom with an allomorph
Supposed about Alan Moore
That actually below
Betrays
And a pretty misogynistic
Services
Real quick I just want to stop there because if you
What is a practicing
Geico
Yeah probably
A bunch of dumb
So even in his like insinuation of like
I mean admittedly you said that was all bulshit that he was making up to make people like me
Like
Yes it is
Synonymous with art
Supernatural Realm
The fact that more can get laid is evidence of the supernatural
He believes that magic is the ability to use words to make changes in the physical world
Magic magic is essentially art
Believe
Oh my God that's a philosophical
Clefairy
Perspective
And I create something that I
Evocative
Thing I want to express and people
Read it
Changed isn't that somehow magical
I think it's a very interesting perspective to have on the
Art Exhibit The Act of Creation
And the axe
Taking in a creation
Which is again
Highly recommend
That's not the most high-level like
Thesis version
Like understanding how art effect
But like they're stupid about
It just falls on deaf ears
And then the part about like
You look at how this guy looks
He's married or as or has a girlfriend
He's getting f***** you know there's magic involved
It's just like I don't know if
Joke
Like I really don't
Because they don't laugh afterwards
I don't know
Supposed to be a burn ever heard of Alan Parsons because they have no idea what's actually in store for them
I think about that
He comes in with the Alan Parsons
Alan Parsons
RCI
He doesn't
Demonic made
Oh God
I'm so Georgia
The only way more gets f*****
Is if magic is real
So now we get into
A portion of a child
At from like a
English 101
Has a freshman would be like
Hey you know
There's only one criminal said
And that's using
He paints a picture with
With words
The other thing is
Whatever the f*** you just said
Go away
Forever is using more than
!
WhatsApp
Exclamation
Is portion of
The show that is probably want I think one of the most
The longtime on Alex
She has to fill time
He's got a couple guest coming up towards the end
Call
And he gets some f****** really bad calls
Yeah
Super Inn
Interesting to me that Alex
Handles those calls
Very well
This is a mark of our show
Is
He has a couple callers who are like
The depth
Of how stupid does not handle them
I will admit that when he does do something good it is evidence that magic is
Absolutely
This first one
Is a poet
Clarion California near worldwide
Yeah Alex
Disturbed
Yo yeah
Iowa V
I do not support the troops in Iraq
I like the iPad 30 minutes home
I am going to lie making a song out of it is called
If you
American with a gun in Iraq I hope you come back in a body sac
If you are American with a gun in the Middle East I hope you get the gardai the Beast
If you're an American with a gun in Pakistan I hope you die when your stand
Listen I have to have family
Overland Iraq and Afghanistan
I hope Iraqis don't die
I hope the troops don't die in Combat League American
I understand you're angry and upset
You know what I appreciate your call
Like particles we know we know about Alex
Like everything else that is
Professional handling of call
No great if you have the ability to just hit the mute button so
To that guy
Yeah I don't think at the moment I would be able to do that well with that guy
I'll probably be like what's the next day
Pretty cool
I mean yeah that I would like to know what the
Also that last one was a slant rhyme and I don't appreciate
Perversion of poetry
Impute
Close today
In a rhyme scheme with a a
Jordan
His next call
Alex receives is worse
Very much worse
Yeah but also
I got to give Alex a
How we handle
Terribly so would you say that
Is that a poem
Malaysia subscribe I've been Distributing your materials
Beginning with America destroyed by Design on thf back then
Then I got a big deal Rockstar
We've only had prisonplanet.tv there for 5 years without appreciate Mana subscriber
I've been Distributing your stuff
America destroyed by Design
Awesome event tonight 11 is I've lost
Three friends two of them
We're blown to Smithereens by controlled demolition Incorporated
You don't know where this is going
I beg you to I know we just had a mic down clip recently
I'm just afraid you're going to yell over this experience
This is a contrast
Call me to come very fast
And you'll get whiplash
All right talk about 9/11
I know people who blow up over a dozen loved ones that fateful day
I just like The View
What are a few grievances briefly in it
G-rated Nana
I'm extremely peed off
I wish you'd put up a Fred sobon gonna link to the book
Did 6 million really die
And talk about the persecution a single question
See how quickly you get arrested when you enter Canada
Inguinal Germany
I know that you sometimes hang up quickly or not thinking the people who lived in Italy criticize you and then spend five or 10
The more minutes
Drive responded to a screaming guy the Holocaust
Promote Alex to promote other hotels tonight for 3 p.m.
People he knows believe that the Holocaust was a hoax
Yes the holla hoax
So all of this is to say that this guy we're getting a nice cross-section of Alex's listeners
Is this guy's been promoting
Come out and say that the Holocaust was a b*******.
And then immediately fall
That holla hoax is not already in Alex Jones documentary right
Touched
He knows better
You got time but like
I think you can appreciate what I was saying came out of nowhere
So now we get to keep stalking for a little bit
9 not real
There should be a middle
Fynx on fire so I don't think Alex is responsive
Perfect
But it's pretty good
Okay after you just connected them
Seems you found a lucrative career in the
Patriot business making poor people went around facing at 10 wealthy no real
Sitting on the radio every day.
Removing try to get the States to declare sovereignty
We are moving to have the bankers arrested that a congressman on saying it 30 minutes ago
Real quick it's not great
First initial reaction
To rebut is
Is the idea that he doesn't offer solution
Cuz that's what he's doing
Are you saying
He's responding to the guy you don't offer Solutions
Sounds like we have all these 10th Amendment resolution guys on
Ron Paul is on talking about arresting the bankers
Deal with the most pressing issue
Ufirst
But I understand you got to spend your wheels a little bit
Get your bearings
35 minutes
We are moving to
Say no to martial law you come on here
Insult
Acme
Say all these terrible things
I make a film is cost me probably $80,000 or more to me
And release it for free
You calling me Sam evil
You know I don't like the things Israel does and I criticize Israel
Associated
Megastar live to Simply hate Jews and everybody else
Very very simple I hope you realize that
I respect that
That's not have someone who's coming on your
Is far as actually promote
These people who are Holocaust deniers
Call
Put on another level because Alex
Ethos of
I'm not going to screen my calls you guys can
Cummins like on the last episode he's talking about
Used to sell tracks
For sale
I kind of respect that in terms
Letting people speak their piece
We are such a stark contrast
2009 in the prison
When he was in that drunk Hotel interview
And he refused to engage with the idea that Nazis
People who are not really into him
Here we have an instance where a Nazi was really into him is calling into the show in 2009 talk about the Holocaust
Real and Alex
Go so far as to say
I don't care for this real doing
But you people who are anti-semitic I don't want to be associated with you
I don't like Israel and I don't like you see that's what I want
That's my favorite part was
Which is a line that I think I'm going to start using from now on
Anytime somebody makes me mad I'm just
Listen
I don't like what Israel's doing and I don't like you either
I like that
He's lying about
The Canadian military
Desperately trying to sell his stupid documentary
I can't say that I don't respect you know I do think
Good response
There was it there's another way you could have answered that
Call and I think he would have answered it differ
Now
I'll tip my cap
To Alex for the
Ya Coulda done way worse
We come back to the show
He's gotten through these calls
Gas to supposed to call
I've kind of spinning his wheels a little
Spell The Obama Deception a little bit more
In
Where we are now
Do you still take calls
Can call in
People end up saying we're going to start rambling about bulshit
He'll take one call
And then
I'm out of time
So people do
It's like there are still call
I'm just I'm just interested to know if I would say that in the episodes
Best real radio and podcast
It's hard to imagine the people would know exactly when he
Broadcast live
Chinese on Airport
Say we're going to take calls on every
Yeah many times
So
It's a crap
Much less part of the shows
He still pretends that is apart of
Yeah that's
So in the next clip Alex gets back to selling The Obama Deception
Things take a turn
I Was a Highwayman
Behind the scenes right now here
Surreal
You only live once
Are you leaving aminos the sleeping giant is Liberty freedom is rising
They know you have power
Everybody right now The Obama Deception is going to drop
Probably dropping a running prisonplanet.tv Emmy for
Operation launch site launched at lunch right now just made that decision
Operation right now
Cherry Brushy you're on the air
What just happened
What is going on right now
Yes
Okay
Watch the operation
Hit that big button
Deploy the operation
Is Jim Cramer's
Crazy big box
The release the documentary but
So whenever you had the Walker Texas Ranger
Houston I've made the decision put it out on all platforms
And then the long pauses
Terry Bradshaw on the air
So I should tell you the website USA
And he's all about how
Checkpoints around the country
Immigration checkpoints or sobriety checkpoint
You don't have to talk to those
You can just go and say like
Have you just keep saying it's all eventually let you go I remember those videos that people used to put up on YouTube
Fourth Amendment is one of the biggest YouTube guys
Neverhood
He was actually even interviewed on episode of This American Life
About his actions
I don't want to get too into his appearance on Alex's
To show because
Like you said I'm not super into
Checkpoints whatever I think
Too much whatever
But they're deployed
Yeah yeah
And also
Here's that he's a sovereign citizen
But I can't really prove it I can just
Get some of it
Gold from his word
Like you guys talked about how were free to travel
Which is a really big
He keeps using like really sovereign
Admiralty law
Dead to rights do that's what you're about
But it's pretty clear that he's tired of it
In that in that world
He gets done with his Terry Bressi interview
Alex
Going through some
Okay
Continue on here
I'm here right now
Panda
Just so sick of the New World Order I'm sick of all the crap
They are we know what they are we know what has to be done
I just wish people valued how serious and how will this information
Constantly
It's fun to fight in the feet
Not fun
Kind of sounds like how I feel about his presence
Michelle
Ouch
Describing a moment
Am I the bad guy here
No I don't think so
But
Much like
F******
WCW viewer 1998 New World Order
My dear might be off
Today when they weren't and that is the day we are
Get it together out
You're not being threatened
What do you think
Maybe some
Trolling
I think that makes him like
Distribution issues where is
His lawyer is
Cleared some of the stuff
I know you have cleared news
Music orgasm
Got all the signatures
For the interviews or right
They haven't figured out
Is this immediately after
But he's kind of
Two trailers coming out
It needs to do that but
Establishment
The FBI is one of dirty tricks in the under the Patriot Act
What's going on
What
Which by the way there are congressional
Hearings
Architects & Engineers for 9/11 truth next Al-Qaeda training videos
Cyber-security takeovers of the entire web
Security
They admit northcom in the Pentagon and everything else is for the American people
So
You know you got this you got this we're the most repressed group
F*** The Blacklist
This is David.
The Patriots or the one who
Sneak-and-peek
The FBI's up in my s***
But you know what this is this is part of
Has definitely been a
In that very clip what you see is
The truth and the false.
About his
Campaign
Display sort of advertising
At the beginning
Is exactly why he's not
Launching it as he just screamed on a
It's because there's a bunch of trailers that he put out
In order to get public-interest right in order for the release to actually work the way he wanted to
Why is the idea that there's enemies
And the FBI with the Patriot Act
Heather they don't want you to put the information out that I'm about to put out
Right
No he sounds like a petulant child
That's the reason
No I I hear Siri
Pretty well done
I was like oh it's his dad is because
There's very much dislike
I meant America
Daddy
Developer
Advertising
Bright
Buckley is giving him some my calm down advice
Probably true
Psychological but I don't
For a second that I like
Is any point during
Michelle
Part of the
Dissipation game
It also creates
Dissolution of immediacy
He's really trying to develop about the movie
Like on this episode this might as well be
Entirely a
Sort of infomercial
For the Obama
Yeah there's a couple of narrative pieces
In a couple of interviews
Call her
But
Most
Easy
Like going on this Arc of should I release it should I not f*** it I'm going to do it
And then
With never walking it back
Coming back from break and being like
It's coming out later
I need to put some ads out in order to make it
Doing this back-and-forth thing
Highway 2
Create
Image that it's a heart
What it's mean
He just needs people to think
Because then they'll assume that the globalists are trying to threaten and behind-the-scenes which will bolster
The actual release that makes sense but I also
Fuckingawesome
Pretty good
I think he drinks a lot of people so I think that I think
Pretty clear they because the transparent
Varices
Through
It has ups and downs
There's just
He's trying to
To get the listeners
Excitement
And make them
Feel like
And when I say that I think
Well done
I think
At the moment
It's well done
Yeah even Chuy
Weeks later this stink
You know like
Two weeks later if you went back and listen to this
He was clearly f****** around and you already liked
He actually does
I believe so
Godwin
I'm actually confer
Alright
Wild Ann goes back in fur
Going to an in-depth
Discussion of Final Fantasy
T7
And how it relates to
If you recall president shin
Ufirst disc
Is of course murder
Whether or not
Sephiroth
Time however
Ghost
Is never really address
Actually died
Years before this
Question
So how is it
Saffron
Essentially forced projector
Angel place where you can kill somebody
With a physical Katana that is roughly
What what is it like
12 ft long damn
It's a 12 ft long katana
You're not answering me
Okay so
We have that and then we have President Rufus who takes over
Now why would the son of the current president
Then become president
Unless we were living in some sort of weird
Dystopian
Technocratic future
The release date 2009 on pretty much any stores I can find no idea
It would be exactly the intended to from the gym probably that's
Yeah
This is so wild
Parents
Clearly showing
Of
I'm there's a
Attacks against me but
He said something
That if I were Alex Jone
I would talk about for the next
Okay fortune favors the Bold
Sick and tired
This was serious
And all the throngs of soulless minions
My wife
Snooping around trying to shut down doing here
The truth
Our information is going super
You picked the wrong side of the New World Order
Justice through courts of law
I mean yeah
Sure
The Obama Deception
You need to see it
You need to have it you need to get it out to everyone remember
The enemy is scared of
Remember the Tony Alamo
Better believe I'm on
And most of all
I like
Stormy times
If I were someone who had the mentality of Alex Jones
I would hear the end of that he's like
He just called himself the ministry of truthettes
To 1984
He's clearly making it allusion to
The propaganda Outlet the ministry of propaganda the ministry of truth from 1984
Feelings a method to get to represent
The reference
He told his audience to the ministry of truth that's externalization of the meth
You can't blame him for that
Scandal
Right
That's so f****** stupid because when he complains about like
George h.w. Bush saying New World Order when he's discussing
Anu
SeaWorld hours
New Arrangements in the world
He just said Infowars of the ministry of Truth
Very specific language
It's not Irish
I'm not cuz I understand
Understand
His operation is
Process 888's Leica it's like an animal farm
Is operation of Dance
There's no band conversations
In terms of Jason bermas two-leg
Big bad El say that
So I don't I just I like that because
Again
You can very easily see how like this what you doing is
Just trying to
Sell your truck
Movie doing
You're doing a play
Nrt radio
Peter kind of
Orson Welles would be so proud he would shoot himself and then murdered
Like I know that recliner.
You never let anybody else
Is Obama
The ministry of Tourism
So
This is just
Demonstrate
You're f****** stupid
I meant robot
Stupid it's not like there's any
There's no further nefarious game other than his
Fleet inability to understand
Interview with someone who
Took me
F******
Hours
To find out
Because his name is Chaz
Chad can't spell that
That's a good
You spell it
The French word for house
Which I also do
Is the beginning of most restaurants
The house of blank
Look
People who secretly controlling the world
Is on the show
He's on there because he sells an AM transmitter
I am so Alex
Isle of the Lost
Lower Stakes 2009 I don't know which one
You selling
Because the what I was able to find on the way back
From his website
Right
I couldn't find the actual text
So I don't know which
Models
He was selling
But like really good
Transmitters are going to run you in the thousands
14 about
$80
Used
Version of it
So the am transmitter if I
Are we talkin about like an actual
Radio transmitter
Pirate Radio
That's what I was better.
Yoga just wanted to be sure there
Which was truth a.m.
Alright I love it
Alex is trying to get all of his listeners
To create a Pirate Radio Station
Play he has evidence of
Most people aren't knocking down your door just indicate your ship
No absolutely not
It's an interesting thing
Because if you go to this guy's website
It was
Truth am.com
It's no longer on the air
Find on the way back
What are the things
You find is
Is that like even on his website
You got to get this transmitter
You still need to set up if you want to broadcast
Plug
Show you could easily play it through but if you wanted to like actually through your own show
Require
Bunch of other equipment
So that
Whole bunch more
But it's so fun that you
You get a glimpse
To like
Alright
Alright rocks not knocking down your door to put your radio show on
I'm going to guess a lot of FM stations are there
AM stations are already playing Rush blind bag
If your
Buckingham
If you're Glenn Beck
You don't
Half hour of your show talking to a guy who sells a.m.
Transmitters
In order for people
Play cure show in
You have 500 f****** station
Play in your show in major markets
So Alec
I think it's pathetic he's not doing well
I do respect the hell out of it I like the hospital
I think
If he was like
He was like
We're not doing great
The globalist
Don't walk me on station
That's the way we're going
I respect that
Presenting it as like
Atossa side
Right audience
Be the radio station for him
Yeah
You're so f******
You know any time
Could all go away
Chess
Very long
It's
PSG
I think it is
You could throw a z on their butt
I think Chaz
What's the one word the couch but it's also a
Are you sure it's not a shady
Games
I don't know
I've got nothing more to say
So
5th next to this court
Is the beginning
Chaz
Wavy
Interview
Helen
It sure has been a thanks for having me on there like the other side of the lake from you of there in Dallas
It's not a paid interview
The reason for that
Sing to me is because why would you bring it up
If your other interview
I'm not sure what this means I have no idea
Guyon
It does lead me to believe that a lot of
Force
Conversion
Informaron
I'm not entirely sure
This isn't my only complaint with Chaz
Kane the other one is
That red Beckman interview you had a while back it got me to get his book the walls are mines and tell the difference between
Politicians and Statesmen I decided you know I want to be a Spaceman
And that's why I did this so
The information from that in your Waco video most people Bobby
Haven't seen that one
But it does show at one man can do and it
Taught me that we
I was involved in the neocon side I was
That happened
And I finally woke up to and I said if anything's possible
I was actually going to Trump University
All I thought was a vacant do Waco they can
Do anything
Reach for the Stars
If they can do we can do anything
The other problem that I have there is that red Beckman is the one who woke him up
Text protesters we talked
What about you
Because the Jews worship
Look we've had a holocaust denier we've had a holocaust
Apologist
Thank you understand
Makes this so difficult
Who is recommending Holocaust
Denier people be promoted on his phone
Being
Good is
Jarring
To some extent
And then you get a little bit later in the show in this chair and is saying
I got woken up by your interview with red Beckman someone who believes that the Holocaust was
Deserve cuz Jews are upset like that
Deny the Holocaust was one of our greatest achievements that's f****** hard to Russell
Content
People read Beckman
He loves me
He doesn't deal with it
Cool let's just pretend
I miss guy reads
Books to get to work
That's not in some of those other books weight
Wasn't a denier
He was a supporter
Against
Denier and love the guy who the Holocaust
Answer at the end
Guy was saying
Alex is responsible
I don't want
Beloved
Dick's like you
I'm against
Israel but I hate people who hate
Hate Jews
So even his response
Should be like
Hey man
What about red Beckham
Now.
You start to see this
Difference
Like
Who is to toxic
Red Beckman is somehow like
Plausibly like
Is really just a
He's concerned about the legality of taxes
Or something like that how it's going like he can sort of hide because he was working
Quirky is hell
Is it okay
For number years he was there
Because it wasn't a scape Escape
Varied if
Distinction
Alex Rashid
And this is
Part of why in present day
He refused
Turtles of adhere
But it's
This bringing up of red Beckman never gets into
He is
I don't know it's just
Wildside
Yeah
Alex Telles
Grace of God
We have told the truth the whole truth and nothing but that truth
The brother luck
I smell victory
Just release
The f****** thing
If that's all
Victory
Just do it
He already said earlier we need to
Come out in order to get interest
Bubbling yeah
Please self contradictory ideas
To say that releasing this
Will be the death blow to the New World Order
To hold on to it
Buzz
Like that
Apparently
Impossible to reconcile the bugs
Second war might be a part of
You know you lie
So now.
Chuck
Hurt Alex
A lot on the show
Do karaoke
We've heard him sing
Talk right
Is range
Is eBay
Better like I don't even really know
Is perfect pitch
Little higher than you'd expect
Now we've heard him sing along with song
No we've heard him
Move bit get out the way the Ludacris song
Oh s*** I remember how great that was
Here is Alex
The hottest 16 bars
On the street
Over there
Control
Hot 16 bars just him just him sings dumb
Instead of Summer
Infuriates
Somehow
Like that song
Just saying things that are about
To be sad about
Slightly off
That run that song
So much more races
It's so weird
Content
Perhaps
You dropped this
He's talkin to Webster
Who cares this interview isn't that crazy mostly wants
Talk about how like there
Obama's ill
Popping up like Hoovervilles
Right
But these aren't
Zorbing
But then also Obama in office for Zion a month
At this point
Going to do that dance
You remember how Hoovervilles popped up immediately went to Hoover became president
That was already
Demolished
Webster actually
So I don't want a clown on him
Hear it
Terrible poem
Tarp
Are you sure he's not a character in a children's
Detective novel I'm positive about
Obama's approval rating
The first couple hundred days
Patient
A couple hundred days were still in March
March 10th
Right now
Videos
The election
Inauguration
President
Yeah somehow I feel like that
Months and the two weeks of the week so Alex is it Obama's approval rating
According to Gallup cuz they keep track of all this
Google it
This is only true if you only factor in Republican
41% of Republicans
Approve of Obama on inauguration
Supposed to
6% on March
So that took drop off
15%
Do 41% of
Hiding
The fact that they don't like that it's
Black
For that day or maybe so that they will feel better about themselves for not being
Voting for a
I mean who knows what the reason is
50% of
Publican
The drop
Inauguration
10-day overall approval rate
It's not really all that important because now it doesn't matter
Talkin about the time frame of the
This drop
He's imagine
Obama's
Numbers are down 15
20%
To look at it
Just embellished
That part
You wouldn't think that the
Time frame
He's talking about it
Unless
But that is the only
Metric
That actually matches the
It comes from
Inauguration
Look at approval rating
Democrats
Inauguration day was 88
Among Democrat
Fungus among independents
Gross lower number
So all of it
No matter what if Democrat
Republicans went down
And Independence
You're the only have a drop of like
In the gross
Yes
Yeah that's
Whitlock
Really
Is
Because I
Cow Trump
And he's rambling Prescott
Dude I don't even want to
He repeat what a f****** was going to say
2% of the females
Figure he's just a
White women
That he got
How did women of non-white persuasion
I don't think this warped uses
Fisticuffs
People like
Do not think
Is there
They just don't
Consider the people on
Unlike themselves
Okay
Percent of the
Females vote
He's using the
Statistic of white women
Because that's all he cares about
Yeah
Obama's numbers went down
Percent
He's pretty
Pretending it's
Among everybody
Right
He doesn't even think the rest of the world is relevant to the conversation
Consciously or unconsciously
Exactly
Do you make an absolutely perfect point
Regardless of whether or not they're thinking about it that way
That's exactly what they're
F****** cute
Problem
Jordan
We
What are the
Been trying to look at
He's primarily
Alex Jones
Journey
George Soros
And so far the only thing that we found
Is Alec doesn't know
Cirrhosis
A very long time
Then he's brought up by bobcat
Equipped
From Davos
Talking about
Ramification
Price of oil
Believe this
For no reason
George Soros
Bidding
Oil in order to attack Russia
Swayla
The Daleks
But also that wasn't anything.
In Radcliff
Been over that
So now
Howard Springs
That backup
With Webster
Not going to get over his
I understand
Based on the fact
These episodes
The only thing I
Everest
Really about
Is in reference
Again he brings Soros
George Soros
The world depression
I'm sure that that he would he would say that
That's not
This is
I don't want to
Goger ballsagna
But this is the Big Lot
This is the
Strategy of the Big Lot
He's played the clip on the show before
And we've heard it
If you understand
Soros's not anyways
We did this
He's only staying here or there is
The effect
Summer
About the fact
Right that the price of oil has lower
Brett Alex
Constantly repeating
Soros admits
But you lower the price of gas
Russia
Venezuela
That is the strategy of the big lie
Because eventually
He didn't play the clip on this show
He hasn't played it since
The last time we
He's going to let that
Of the clip
I think he's going
Bill.
That later
In the same way that he
He does in 28
With
He's a Nazi
Yeah that's
His big lie in the
This is a small
If you repeat it long enough
And loud enough
People believe
Webster Tarpley
He says I believe he would say
The day of letting go
All Webster Tarpley knows about his words and
Protecting yourself against rain
That's all he knows
Spider
How do you feel about that do you want to give yourself a might as well for that one
Feel like it's like
Alright we'll call it a push that.
Next one
Alex going to train
I wouldn't tell everybody out there listening that we may launch The Obama Deception early today or tomorrow
Prisonplanet.tv
Youth keeps changing the goalposts
AR
I mean we're over this week talks about there's a f****** hungry
Timezone this episode already
Heath
Maybe Friday
So when is it
Like this
You know that's being tired
I believe that
Man I don't know he's so
Especially during this time. There's a part of me that is willing to be convinced by
Absolute commitment
You know what I mean yeah I understand
Especially with this kind of situation is that
There's no transparent b******* because it does
Seem like there's an actual internal struggle going on between him
I'd like anyssa taste like good and evil like
Want to release it now
Money
I'll release
Later and I'll sell it like that
But I'm a good
Cats
New World Order
That and I like that kind of
Angle I hadn't
Considered
Mostly because
Probably
Yaya
You would make the movie
If you had some sort of like good angel
Only the possibility of
To Demons on his
And shoulders
Self-sabotaging self-interested
You have principles I want money
That dichotomy is
Ludacris
Could be like
You make money more by waiting
You make more money by jumping on people
Iraq
Strategies
I believe that that's possible
Mortgage
Now but one day it'll be an hour
Uno's
So you like to make fun of Webster Tarpley
And I understand why
Funny name
Weird
Someone who helps
And stay dry
Tarpley
Carries the characteristics of a tarp
What reflective tarp
I think that most of his
Interviews pretty terrible
Is wack as hell
But
About
The
Financial crisis
Is on America
Webster has
They are anathema
To Alex's world
Alex
Not push back on
Either of them
And I kind of
Agree with Webster talk
I got a lot of people are looking at apocalyptic scenarios right that it's going to come to some kind of civil strife
I don't think we're there yet I think it's time to try politics
You got to have your own program to get out of the depression
I have one light White.
Thesis and issue 0 credit production
Credit for production have emergency Federal Leaf relief and set up a new world monetary system full points
You get out of the depression that's the big prize
He said at the end
Set up a new world monetary system
How can Alex let someone say that on his f****** show
No it's
He's talkin about government regulation
William
He's not the way to get out of a depression
Who does that
Federal government
Zero interest money
Got to come from
Somewhere.
Push towards the people
Alex would f****** hate
Anu
World
Cancel order
April system
Monetary
Webster
To be saying things
Did Alex
Nada
Because he
He's already built him up
As like
A credible source
He can't push back on him legit
New world
Monetary system
That's crazy
Elizabeth is next
Get put in your ear
But you you don't get out of
The depression unless you make these changes there is no automatic exit from the depression there is no business
Michael it's going to lick you out of the depression and I'm also afraid there is no free market solution to the depression
If you call for the free market under these circumstances basically
Making everything that much worse
I think about food stamps right there 3 million people in Texas
Living thanks
The food stamp benefits a free-market take that away well
I think that the question is how long will it take for people
To throw off the chains of ideologies and all the Illusions and all the claptrap of the past 40 years
Against All Odds
Don't make it.
Dunks a basketball card
I mean they Webster Tarpley should not be allowed to dunk a basketball
I don't know
I don't know enough Manning play basketball
I've heard a number of like appearances by
I don't believe your sources I don't care about what you're talking about this is interesting Larry Nichols
Or something
I swear it's like
The idea
You have someone on
Who's
Expert
Who's playing
First of all
New world
Siri Siri
Advocating
For social
Benefit
A government intervention is no
Free market
To the financial crisis resolved
And staying
Earlier
Regulation
Got to get rid of these derivatives
How the market can operate for big
Monetary system
Global
Government
Here's what
The most amazing social safety
What's most amazing
Alex doesn't fight back at all
What Webster Tarpley
Just
I can't believe I'm saying that name and it serious
The ACT
Actual stimulus package
F****** dip
Yeah far to the left of the f****** bailout
What he is saying is literally
We need to keep the bags
From being allowed to operate the way that they are as opposed to giving them a loud
Far to the left of the liberal President we ostensibly I apologize
Tyrannical Overlord we ostensibly elected in 2008
Josie Joe
Events
Jordans
Webster Tarpley Auto Show
It's almost like
We said it three times
Did Bewitched
We have one more clip
What do you know
Kind of salad
You're the worst
That that
5:30
Adjust articulated
Exactly
It's coming hell or high water is coming eventually they are also I fucken want to get those
Glass
Good, Denny
And this episode is
Literally like
Chicanery is going on
The Obama Deception is going to be out
Runs everything
Holocaust denier or helicopter Porter
Jesus
Tyrant
Treason
Obama's
Who is owner of Amazon
Do you actually not know about that we talked about that or alive
Show in Chicago
Breitbart was on there about Obama's
Enemies list as Alex
Probably has
Has an enemies list
Today was Dan Brown
Depression
His wife makes him do Emily got information
His wife's out on its brutal anyway
Probably
Desired life
What time
If you guys like to follow us
ITunes
Scribe
View all that stuff
We keep
Engrossed
Everybody
I'd like to know how to do it.
Do open mics
Chicago I don't know
No
Arsalan
Crazy
I agree with that but also
Too drunk to communicate
You're like
Don't get it Fergie
And that's what I would say is our principal
Guitar podcast
You get it you get it
You don't get it
Shut up arsalan
He probably didn't kill a guy but Alex Jones
Probably
Alex, first in color with your trip and I love your work