Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty beverages
How do you feel about Lil Wayne
I don't give a s***
Do you feel like it's a return to form for a scooter
His fastball for the past 45 years
Everything was downhill from f*** the world
Great songs
Alright
I don't know what
French lady
I don't know
Reserved
Lil Wayne
New album
I'm not telling you
Kendrick crazy narrative
Voices
I'd like to
You asked me what
Coincidentally end up
Pictures of dog
Provided
That that dog is very pissed
With the group
Everybody was like get well soon dad and then people were mad at me
Turn off
Well that's because I
I can't do all the stuff that I have to do what I'm rising in a ball
Anyway that is kind of rude of them
Apologize
Anyway
In full effect
To be here
I'm excited about what
What's going to go down
Today
Oh
Yourself on The Bachelorette
Exciting
Say thank you so much mr. Matthew you are now
I'm a policy wonk
Message Matthew
Mister math
Could be
I call people whatever comes up
That will never know we'll never know
Very exciting
Heartfelt
Dispersion
An elevator
Alex Jones
Don't get mad and tell her you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
The real Alex
I really sorry but I just don't think you can afford to donate
You got to save that money man
And what should be supported
I don't want to make
Difficult
Like alternating
Taking really hot
And laying in bed
Skyrim
Cuz I couldn't barely move
Great great work done I wanted to jump
With this Alex Jones full show
And if
Wewewewe recording this
Beginning of the week
Thursday was
Weird things
You things have happened in the
In the world
Particular like
I know that a couple things were posted
The group
You think about this
I thought at the beginning.
Be good
Give a blanket comment on a cup
Yeah a little bit
Blog post for a sore
Surprised that Alex Joseph
Football players kneeling
And my comments
My comment
Why is this person
I have no comment about that
He's very much
Afraid of
The big part of the narrative
We don't need to spend mainly afraid of black people exercising any kind of Rights
Replace
Not a fan
Actually got a message
Scrum up
This is actually really
Alex Jones
We crashed
But what was
Weather
Charlie warzel from
Withal
Talkin about
To derail the proceedings
Superhero
It's super ironic because part of the panel what they were talking about was Alex
His situation and then lo and behold
Derails
The ability of the
Anime
Well they offered
Him a place on the diets they offered him to engage
Just kept yelling
And appointed Jonathan brought up
As soon as I saw the story
I don't want to talk about
This is just
Him further deteriorating
Declining
He's no longer on place
Going to go bum rush
Somehow
Iuc a mental
State deteriorate
He's just yelling slogan
Was like
Substance
Just yelling
Anime
Another really good
Is interesting that we haven't brought up with
Sincerely
If you look at the way that Owen
These days
It's kind of like the child of an hour
Alcoholic parent
You know how like when
Turned on Trump
Alex maybe we should stop maybe we should
Do you know
That's sort of like trying to
The out of
Control parents
He brought that up and I thought that was really interesting I wanted to
Give him credit for that
It's an interesting thought
Not worth of doing a breakdown of
Him crashing his
Yeah well we have called
Basically
Alex Jones
Daddy
Like that's that thing but
Buff's
Freddy buff song
Coming up
I'm sure Alex
Bulshit about
Kavanaugh
And I don't really want it
Talk about that
I really don't want to scream about any man
I don't have I don't have the emotional
Probably
Investigation is a sham which is something that the news
It is yet to exist
Couldn't really get it up
For that
Am I still recovering
Thankfully
The Gods
Down upon
Literally
Prep episode about
Man who
You're right you're right
I know I told you
Kerry Cassidy came out of nowhere and surprise
For a little bit
And I was like oh I got
Okay we got to do that
Turns out in
2013 Brett Kavanaugh
These days
Project
Where we will
Another element of the
What have you
Beginning
What carry gives the
The guest credits
Cisco's a little bit long
But I think
Telescopes
Sushi okay
I'm going to let this play out as it plays out
Hi everyone I'm sure Cassidy from Project Camelot and
I'm very happy to be here tonight I thought
Sophia Stewart with me
And she's going to be on the
Had some strange camera failure and so I have to go onto my
Other computer kind of a different look than the other one
We are live
So I just want to say that it's great to have you here Sophia and I would have been to do is
Put a bit of your bio on the strain here and and go over that with the audience so that we can
Cover a few other points in there and then asked you to sort of
Elaborate
So what we've got is that
Basically you're the author of The Matrix in The Terminator
What is an you have claimed that Hollywood
And made them obviously into blockbuster movies
And we have an extensive bio here it's on my website I'm putting it on the screen as I speak
So that you can see it there but
Briefly
She is with a basically a prodigy child prodigy
Poet creative genius
And those are terms that were used to describe her
And I guess store
In the
Well she received a Bachelor of Arts
From the city University of New York
Miners and Lawn psychology
And she came under the guidance of various celebrated authors Riders
SEPTA's Matt Siegel was a former journalist of the New York Times
Emil
Hell Yeah Usher Edgar an STS and critic
And Paul
Cherry playwright on Broadway
Public broadcasting station
Wnet thirteen
With the oscar-winning film documentary
Producer Penny Miller
Adato
And her graduating class was honored with a special
Letter citation from Jimmy Jimmy Carter is 979
Give me President Jimmy Carter
I want to play
Beloved
She wrote The Matrix
Is embedded in there
It seems like that is otherwise that is all
These are alike
Right I know there are reclusive
I'm trying to get
Who's the weirdo
This is not
Prodigy
Good Prodigy backstory collegiate
Accomplishments
Or another about
You're graduating
Jimmy Carter doesn't mean
That being injured
Really
Pretty heart
That was looking for listings
Google is very interest
Yeah
Max people died in 1988
The mule cast 2005
Call Cherry died in 2014
Henry Miller adato
Probably not going to feel.
Request
For comments on
97 years young passed away earlier this year
Biblia part of her story in as much
Is there part of her
As her mentors are alive or
Confirm
Which is mildly suspicious
He reminds me of
You know that movie
The movie Mumford no
About a psychiatrist
What's a psychologist
He's fake
Psychologist
Lady gets in trouble for
For being a fact
The characters
Mumford Mumford
His
He's not a real.
List of
People who have died
Needs of that whenever I hear this list of all these rules
The same
Story but for a quote
Creative
That you do for a man who is in the
23 likes
Okay dude
You're on Project Camelot
Even if I met you in the street maybe I give you more of a benefit of the doubt but if you're on a project Camelot
Some questions
CIA
Started a lowered state of credibility
We'll just kind of unfortunate
And whatever carries reading the Bayou
I'm like alright
I smell something
Kind of weird
First of all
But that is also Neo
And they stole her lights.
Wrong character
But hold on
Getting ahead of yourself
Even though Kira
Wrote
Sophia can come in
Give her own
Version
What's important
An elaborate for you Young Thug
New York City
The last time it was on
Kericho is a while ago
I won my court case
4 years ago actually September 25th
A day ago
25th September
2020 18
Of my win in the
Utah federal courts I want on really celebrate
Believe that I will give you the court docket
It's so you can read it for yourself
Everything has been going really great
The fourth installment of The Matrix
Around the entire globe
Seen it on amazon.com miniquest my website
Matrix Terminator.com
That movie
Becoming
Cable Ford wonderful it's often a 30 million dollars for
What
And it's billionaire came along and he updated 5 more million
Which is 35 million.
I'm disabled right now
That's a lot of money for some context
Avocado
The gross profit for writing the screenplay for
Jurassic Park
Which they already knew ahead of time physical
Refocus you
Yeah
30 million dollars upfront approximately 10 times as much as
Is anyone is ever paid for aspect
Examples of a billion dollars
For such a thing are generally stories of Hollywood
There's literally zero chance that anyone is off
Sophia 30 million or 35 million
That anybody anywhere this is how movies are made
Way Beyond the possibilities
The biggest Blockbuster ever even so
Even sells one setup that Cliffhanger ending that we were all waiting to find out what
What makes would be like
2020 resolution
I really want
Before this episode
I don't think I'm not
30 bucks
At the 30 million dollars out of
Perhaps a good book
So okay that's cool I'm really thrilled for fourth anniversary that that's all
The Matrix
Terminator
The only thing I find
30 million-dollar
That's impossible
You don't like
If you look at the movies budget
So
Everybody in the world is
Hankering for a
Everybody
Name one person who doesn't want to see me
I'm fine where it is as bad as
Fart before
Terrible
But I watched.
I didn't think you were nearly as bad
Baby
Took a little too long to do with maybe some parts
Superfluous is help
Whatever
Easter's next movie was a was a
I think so
It is
Literally unwatchable
I've never finished
I don't know I
Basic
Play music
Why you're saying that
Figure of 30 million percent
All of her legitimate
Right
Because there's a lot of people out there
She doesn't
The Matrix
Terminator
Articles about that online
Why is it that some
Articles there was one in 2013
Who was saying that some reason that they said that your court case wasn't
Was that because it hadn't settled yet at that point
2013 article
It was before I won the
Fort Chaffee
2nd court case which was never done in the first court date
The inner in my copyright
Derivative movie
Fancy dinner in Austin
Do the derivative movie
Creator
And two federal judges
The Magistrate Judge
Edward J Park
Airport federal judge defensin
A ruling validated
Movie scenes derivative movies came from my third eye matrix script and book
I can send the document over to
Anyone
Want to dispute it
Preemptively defensive is not a good way to live
Carrying O'Neal's on the internet
Got this messenger
Aldi descendants Warner Brothers Kaylee and her James Cameron Indian language
You f***** in all of these defendants they never
Run that chase a lot of them terminated out before then
Just rolling
Because they were scared of the RICO going to jail
So go to jail
You can
You invoke the RICO Act
My friends because Joel Silver
Warner Brothers
They all got together and formed the criminal syndicate
In order to rip off Sophia Stewart the rightful owner of
The Matrix and Terminator movies also throat
To go down everybody's going.
Syndicate
That's why they
Tricked everybody devoting
Arnold
Governor
Two-part I'm sure that's a piece of this
Just don't have time to get into Nevada Sophia
Assume
But
Is one of those things
They like
You off
People
Are making these
These audacious
Clams
Awesome
Alex green around racketeering Rico stuff all the time whenever he's
It was in The Dark Knight
The RICO Act
Wachowskis
Warner Brothers worth
Terminated out of the original
Oh no I got lost
Get it I don't get high
Being sued
Biggest state
Excuse me
I believe you forgot that
So
Sorry
Her version of adolescence
Accurate
You know
Who knows
Man when we get to the reveal of how this court case actually go down I think we're all waiting with bated breath
This is it this is f******
So would you understand
You might be thinking like why are these two
Two things connect
Diddy's to IPS
Seasonal actual proper
Explain
So how did you came to write first of all the Matrix and I could
I think that's the first one that came forward
And then the Terminator series
Terminator actually came first and
Terminator and Matrix is one Epic story is five presidents
Future time travel
Oh I get it
Future
Terminator
Beginning of the story Sarah Connor
It's really Neo mother
Second coming of the Christ
Evolution
Consciousness Man versus
The machine
Another word for the machines here the oracle's prophecy
Baby is going to be born that's going to grow up to
Future
I've actually been terminated
Coming soon
Sarah Carter
Without
Because they look just like we look wrapped in flesh Killah cannot be
Looking for Sarah Connor
Kill her so the baby Neo will never be born
Right
John Connor
Jay-Z John Collins
I get it
The Matrix
What does a matrix
Check 1984
And my copyrights or 90
3 + 84
Way before the movie
Hello they did was the Jap
Mike Griffin my foot
Scream
Immediately
Indiana 1999 March 31st
The release of The Matrix
That's when they treated The Matrix
Trilogy
One thing that's important to consider is that like
Terminator came out
You're 1984
Began to develop
Or anything like that
Especially a movie like that in the early 80s
Year-and-a-half
To make a movie
I would assume the editing process
Right right if you can actually look into the history of houses
Terminator movie
It took a while people didn't have much faith in the idea and
We were like that dude can't even speak English there's no way this is going to work out
Right now is I guarantee the producers of the Terminator were like well
I'll tell you what
This
Governor of California
I do like
Like like you responded to the the idea of like
I want to see
Crossword
Look I saw Alien versus Predator that f******
Suck butt
Matrix versus Terminator
But you know the reason
Very old archetype
I was going today
Sort of blend
Together
Because they both
View sort of Savior Ark
Archetypes
Technology
Yours
Since we started making robots
The technology electricity
So
That's why they
Come together
Drawn Together
I will say this
Siri can do some research
And you can't find that
Sophia Stewart
Trademark
Just heard from February 19th
On her
Book
Third eye
U.s. Library of Congress
Copyright office
Copyright
Third eye
It is
Listed here as
Tired
I believe
Here
6 pages long
It's a manuscript
Treatment
Yeah it's
Read the manuscript
Treatments that she shopped around and if it's only six pages long I'm going to guess it was not
You can't save
Zakir what that you put out a book
She's basing a lot of
You can't take away that it was
In 1983
Presumably a year before Terminator came out there isn't a copyright that she has on file for this third eye
Than any other project
Suzette alone I think
Lee Vista
Cheapest with a little dog
Because of media covering it up
Well and Schumacher
Terminated the loss
At 14 years ago different covering it up in the media
Magazine Southside / 4000
Media Sophia's
Disney broke my story October 7th
Around the world
But things have covered up
Story that I won
And that's horrible
People my fans date they call me
They checked me the email neither on all the social network
Fairytale adventure cover up
News
Creator and that I own the major
Terminator
Everyone deserves to know that true
Didn't she say everyone has the right to know
Which was actually sent
Notarized
So far so good
Which is a
Very specific date
The chi
Really really likes
You might be asking yourself
That lawsuit
What I'd like to know is whether or not you in your
You're winning your case whether you were awarded any money
Gordon Thomas a half a million-dollar to attorney fees and
3.5 billion dollars and liens on all of their property
What happened was
I have three
CPAs to come in and validate that they own a 4.7 billion dollars
EPA certified public accountant
Their testimonies for $25,000 each
3 + $75,000
Witnesses
4.7 billion
Okay so 7 billion is a lot
Billion dollars
Matrix in The Terminator
There's no way they can afford to pick nose
Accident closed on Warner Brother
Marvel
Iron Man shows up in The Matrix
Croswell
The possibilities are endless
Ever showed up
Connor like a double whammy
I was getting the for law firms that
The same time then it's sabotage
20K
It was supposed to been on my side but they were paid by one of us
Sabotage
Terminator
FBI
Coj balance 827
Do that in my second court case in Utah federal court
70 life
7 years to
September 25th 2014
Cuz he was dead
That actually was one of her mentor
I don't think so that guy
I honestly
Did her dirty
Girl a little bit
Clips explain everything
I've been trying to pretend that she has a good point
I really know is
Terminator movies for 4 billion
All right but
Where did you saying that that you sort of had a lien as you called it I think on certain
Individual
3.5 billion dollars
Perform a debtors
Where they have to come in open up their plugs
Show how much money did they have to pay
For the property
The money order
Or I can
Sam's sell the property
It's been 4 years and she has using the present
Are you talking about
Who's property Warner Brothers or the individual
Wingstop James Cameron's property
In fact I can send you over the lens
Captain show
And you can actually see the property that I cleaned up
Leonard into the court and the judge did not
Check out the wings
Lions are good
So you're a citizen like
So now I have liens
You can choose anything you want
It's strange that you can do that it's not like the court as a responsibility
Yeah
Cut this out
Albany
Billions of dollars of property
James Cameron
3.5 million dollars
Billion
But you only have
3.5 billion
I really don't think she's going to win this
I really don't think she's going to take this one.
So you really interesting
She's talked about in the present
She's explaining it all
So you might
Okay fair enough but how long have you had the lean
Laser good investment
Why have you not asked
Particular
Question
A lot of people don't know that debtors exams money when you do it
Money to collect
ERS when they collect on your land
Trf
If this is where I fibro
This is where I said no way
Because if she
She has all these billions of dollars
Anybody
I will play I will pay for this debtors exams you give me a million on the back
Just served I get a millionaire
Give me 300 million of your 4.7 billion.
Look more than I normally do hourly
Adored
Afford to be leaned against like this and he's going to lose weight
Weller know he's settled but
He's got
This is it this is where things get kind of Interest
What do you want to know about
About her copyrights
HUD you know what
First thing I want to know
Is she actually a published
Probably
I apologize
Most likely
Simon & Schuster knocked on her door so I don't think we got to have the force
So they could be part of this Rico
Dollar Store
What's important to know if you look into this
You find it there
Yes veggies
What you doing a little bit
The one in California
The first case for California
Yes in this case to recharge a suit
To file a lawsuit against the Wachowski siblings Joel Silver Warner Brothers
And 20th Century Fox claiming the Matrix and Terminator movies were based on her book the third eye
In June 2005 the cases
Dismissed
Sophia Stewart failed to appear at the preliminary hearing
In the Court's ruling
Judge Margaret Morrow the central
District Court of California dismissed
And her attorneys had not entered any evidence
Upholstery
She claims or demonstrated any strike
Similarity between her work and accused directors Phil
Somebody
Really want to show up to
The court that day
Considering its
Big deal
Case
California
Is open-and-shut
Now the Utah case starts on August
First 2007
What's Sophia Stewart
How many of them or name is John Doe
Anonymous
She's doing in court
The named individuals were people who are involved
A California
Louisville.
The court dismissed the case
Brown and said that you couldn't do a bunch of anonymous unnamed football
All those people
She sued for breach of contract
Mysterious Coronavirus
Search for breach of contract breach of Covenant of good faith and fair dealing malpractice
End conversion
According to court documents
California
Sometime around July
To deliver his services
The California action
Mister lubell
Spoke with Miss Stewart
Over the phone
Home in Utah
Theory arrangement
Where she executed
He is not a real lawyer
Mr. Lube
Assemble a competent legal team to assist with
Represent
The other name men Brown Weber and brought in
And that's why the Chargers
We're just miss
Because they were
They were mere accessories
In action
I kind of wouldn't have mattered in the end because she was never going to win that
But he was clearly acting poorly of
The results of the California case
Sophia Sophia was ordered
Pay the California
Attorneys fees and legal
Bill
Brothers Brothers
Joel Silver 20th Century Fox
F****** bill serious lawyers
So because of being terrible attorney in that case
Getting it thrown out with prejudice
Being charged
The opposite sides
She got charged
4.7 billion
In the Utah trial the court
Was still guilty
Having ROMs
And they filed a quote
Mr. Malpractice
Breach of contract
Breach of fiduciary duty
From the money she paid under the counter
And attorneys fees and costs awarded against her the California action and lost damages
If any based on the underlined caliph
If any is a super important
Two words there
Okay so
Lawyers
Shona
Well that's what they again
Found to be entitled to damages
Sitting okay so if you read that what it's saying is
She's entitled to the money that you paid him as a lawyer
The Lost amount
That she had because of you
Attorneys fees
Charge
Because of the
Resolution
And then
Lost images if any based on the underlying California copyright case
Fat 4.7 billion dollars
If any
Is in there
If any is 0
Raya
The Sophia one damages in the amount of $305,000 930
That $5,930 in
Which is the amount
To pay for the attorneys fees in California
Blame off
Interesting Lee the only place
Things come up in this documentary relationship
Send it to the California
In three states
Prior to the judge
Which were then released
Probably what you talking about there
As for the case of bourbon that she owns
The Matrix
Quote
Approximately
15 billion dollars in Damages
In this case
The game of Hearts
This is straight from the court.
Billion in Damages
In the case stemming from an attorney's failure
Document presented expert witness testimony
This award what are these documents
Consists of a response from a Time Warner entertainment
Company lawyer to a patent
The trademark office
The exhibit also includes IMDb printouts
Gross profit figures and budget
Various
Well I'm glad
She printed the message from an audit
Figures for various Matrix movies and spin-offs
Estimated total
Mr. Also elicited testimony from Witnesses art Toshiba a friend and
CPA
TV rating of friend and licensed financial representative
Castiglione
Investment
In addition to router
The court finds Miss Stewart may not recover damages on this
Even assuming the merits of the underlying claim
The California defendants would have been able to establish deductible expenses and the prophet not attributable to mistress
Without question the California defendants incurred deductible expenses and making butter
Terminator
The gross revenue numbers Mr provide
Do not constitute
A proper measure of damages
McKay's
Recovered
That much
Even if her lawyers had knocked
The court therefore recommends The District Court award Miss Stewart
If you order adopting and
So it's nothing
Divisibility answer is 0 0
0 out of 15 billion
Any order adopting this report and its recommendations they lay out the
Entitled to just over $300,000 in damage
What's
Miss Stewart
Subjected to these damn it
Entitled to damages connected
The prophets of the Terminator and Matrix movie trilogy
For reasons stated in the report and recommendation
Objection is overruled
So
Website
I don't know why don't know weird thing to do
On her website and
Another source
I can I can say that they're not like doctor to anything
The
Appleton
Conditions Gamble
I'm going to put these up here
So I'm just going to clean it says what I want
She is
Filed a bunch of
Certificates
Copyrights
Forex.com
She posted some screenshots of the certificate of registration with the US copyright office
The chi
But this is absurd
The first problem is abused copyrights are largely for things that are not content
For instance to place the copyright in 2013
Play titled the Holograms
I love it
She created Terminator
She wrote a screenplay called Terminator 5 the Holograms
Copyrights area of law where fraud is rampant
For something
Could get a patent
For it without ever making
Yeah there was literally four broadcast
Claiming to have
Copywriting
Specific thing
It seems kind of important
Prove that it was
So one thing that threw me for a huge Loop
Is that one of the things
Sofia is a certificate of copyright for is the animator
Birth certificates from 2030
The animatrix
Released in 2000
I was going to say Denis and Amanda Matrix came between first movie in the second movie
Lingering
Plot details that the second movie just kind of didn't even bother
I thought this was really strange
Flyy the producer
The animatrix
Godavari that have a copyright on their works
But then I noticed that this copyright was specifically for an artwork
Where is the rest of the copyright she claimed
For screenplays
Most likely got a copyright for a work of art
Call Dad
But doesn't violate the existing copyright
As they would be in a separate category of copier
Right similarly she has a certificate of copyright
Parenteral
But it's for work described as
Enter the Matrix is a video game
They would have a completely different copyright over that exist
So she has these
These things
What appears to me is that Sophia is doing what you doing is filling
Totally fair copyrights to the works that
You created like Terminator 5 the Hologram tomorrow or the fourth Matrix
Venice 13 copyright claims
Properties
Under differ
Categories
Knowing that the
Purism having a copyright with the name animatrix
Will trick most people into thinking
That you didn't
Desteria server validated by her writing in all caps
On her website
Sophia Stewart has won the copyrights to The Matrix and Terminator movie franchises
The government has settled the matter
The Enter the Matrix copyright
All the shell game
All the kind of mood though because according to
Do the government copyright office close
Copyright does not protect
Concepts
You may express your ideas and writing or drawing
Copyright your
The copyright will not protect the idea
As revealed in your written or are too
Copywriter only
Specific works
The first miscreated
Express in one piece of writing
That might be mirrored in
So she's also saying that she owns the Bible
I mean she'd have to be
She's she saying that she owns
Hero's journey as a con
Alright I like it
I like it I did again
She has
Pleated balls with chrome
There's no doubt
And if interview gets Wild
Okay so you might be asking yourself
Do all this stuff in like
Terminator 1984
You know about them
When did you realize that your your stuff was stolen another words what was the process by which it was stolen
I want people to realize there was never any battle or any
Boring going gone
What I what I did
Go to the movies and I-84 because Cyrus
Pregnant and
I was married
Play March 31st 1999
Being a paralegal
Attorney
Can a doctor I called up one of us
Legal department
I come from a military law enforcement family
So I know the law
That doesn't make sense but they offered me 5 million dollars
Cactus when I was 11
Like H&R Block I was getting
IPhone 6
Understand
Just why H&R Block
But I was already in Austin for New Orleans
And doing also at the
Teenager payroll
Creating grown people's paycheck
49ers
Sam's which is nothing but pure math and they wanted me to come and work for them
The number that's why you
The Matrix
Binary code
Quantum physics
Calculus
Sacred geometry why are we throwing in ancient sacred geometry
No you got to throw it in
Did she just
Did she just say that the reason that she
No she owns The Matrix
Is because they use
Because she
Countenance
At 11
I don't know
I think it's
Spaghetti on the wall
Okay I was pregnant
United 84
And so
But now she's
Yo comes around
She's going to movies now
Kids AR-15
Free movie tickets
Get the ability to watch movies
The Matrix
She's like
Gall darn it
Of course
The lawyer
Seems a little bit preemptive
It is next week we just talked about our work
Is copyrighted
Good carry-out after
Okay
You trying to get to that in this
Are you saying
How did you know
What was the process
She tries to understand
How did this start
In other words how did they get your work where was your work did you submit to
It's kind of sounds like you didn't submit it to a film company
Send it over to 20 Century Fox looking
Ford
George Lucas
When I saw Star Wars
And I didn't know this song
What's the director
And I wanted yesterday I wrecked my work because I wanted him to my work to Lucas
Alright
Book to him at $0.20
Was vice president creative affairs
Was commercially
Is she just
Ronnie and Gale Anne Hurd
Cameron and all these people in database
Appreciate that but your name was on it your copyright was on it
How did you get submitted over
Steve anything
What what
That's pretty ludicrous every Studio
Just like a hey unsolicited Scripts
This is this is cockamamie because
She and other places
Claimed
That the wachowskis posted that they wanted like
Submission
Things for science
And that she sent her work into them
Craigslist Craigslist
Who gives a s*** if you don't have engine
And you did have ages
We're going all the way back but I'm just saying they like that story is even different than the
Story that you tell
The text
Call Trump because she was helping George Lucas
Direct
First one
3 movies
Video only directed the first Star Wars first Star Wars movie 7
4 years after Star Wars
I don't know why she didn't referee
American Graffiti cuz that's probably is best
Director Empire Strikes Back
No
6 no
It was a something I'm pretty sure it was on the 8th
Noh8
That's why Harrison Ford is broke
Little tough
It's a little
Gluten
Red
Flags pretty much everywhere
So I'll just say it
Any kind of convinced that there may have been like some sort of case for her where it's like
Ocean you put together all of the
These ideas
Well it's one of those interesting
If you go
Sugar website
Dot-com
There's 11 blogger of
Truth about nature it might as well as of her copyright
Copyright for the Matrix 4
And if the date of it
Is July 20th 20
The evolution
I don't want her helming The Matrix 4
Nature of the work is listed as movie
4D movie attraction
Hologram clone
Lifted and listed as new machines
Just just new version copyright on the Hologram clones which is the new machine
It could be another copyright troll hair
That was from 2010 but cheap
Claims that
She wrote it into
2000 which is fine but legally there's no proof of that
Until this
10 Dates
Enter the Matrix
Text
She is copyrighted
Is from 2015
But you claim
Big Data
Completion
Was 1981
That's just based on her own reporting in this
Basically an affidavit
Copyright
Famously published author in night
I assume everybody
We can trust that
She was riding
Soul Man
Trucking manual
Scraps in
Screenplays
There's just no way that you couldn't
Credit Acceptance
I just don't
Sorry
I don't believe any of this
It interesting
Because Terry was talking about how like
Hey you know what
LogMeIn
People I've been brainwashed a lot of my sources have been brainwashed
Because they lied and Liars that's
Another thing that you was really trying to stress
Is that like
Just because I have someone on doesn't mean I agree with them
Sometimes I'm trying to
Cuz I'm
I'm an investigator
Because she's like you know any page
We can have a conversation and I believe him
It's clipped
She's Not Just investigating
She 100%
No it's kind of funny you know it's it's it's
A lot of people have had their stuff okay
And what years is one of the most outrageous story of flagrant
Cases
Okay
Copyright violation
She is out well I hope could it not be
The single largest court case in history
Utah court
To award her 3.5 billion to live here
Because
I would guess
They would try and appeal that
Just lose the case and be like
3.5 billion Ono we got leaked
To keep the other one point five billion that we
Recognize
Is that like at the end of the day
Even though the Matrix is a Mastiff
Successful
Franchise
That doesn't mean that it made a lot of
It doesn't necessarily mean because of all the money that went into it
Right there is still a decent chance that they barely broke
No they
Well I don't know
But
Would you always assume that like
80 million at the box office
You might have paid
80 million
People talk about budget
Figures that are included online
IMDb
Often don't include
Advertise
Saving budget
Extra expenses that are on there
I'm not necessarily these movies didn't make money
But the figures that you assumed about them the picture
Team billion
Stuff like that
He's probably grossly
Exaggerate
Was fairly low budget and it had very little effort
Why everybody was
Surprised
Read the release the first Matrix
Has been wildly pop
I know you got to have that
Next
Merchandising
Figure out
Stuff ends up making money for like
Hico the paint company
Dartmouth clearly all going
Go to the witch house
Filmmaking and all this stuff is a lot more,
Is it
Sophia Stewart is far from the only person
Do Warner Brothers and Joel Silver
Claimed
Fanaticism
Inspired by movies
Super ever created
One such fellow lived with a guy named Thomas
Who claimed his screenplay The Immortals had 190
Similarities
Probably not
Repeat
Netflix jump
So this case went to court and the judge
Immortals
Immortal
Jim Reese finds himself in the year 2235 18
Excuse me
3580 battling to wreck the plot of Adolf Hitler's son
Excuses excuses I would like you to pay the difference
Frankly I want you to pay the cost of me being here to death Subs
Pensively differin
Eastlake nature of Neo I was similar to
Character
Picture of Christ
To which judge Plus nursing
Christianity
That are not generally protect
Interesting Leo houses
They both claimed that they
Dora Brothers silver stolen
And pass it on to the Wachowski
This makes absolutely no sense
Because before the Matrix the wachowskis were not
Store folks the movie companies would be
Be committing crimes to bolster
Before the Matrix the only two movies they made with
Unforgettable movie
Assassin
Supposed to
Percent of rotten
Tomatoes which of the witch house key
Unsuccessfully tried to
Haven't actually written out all of their country
The sexy Noir crime film starring Jennifer Tilly and Gina Gershon
The movie at the box office
Steven cover the film's modest
4.5 million-dollar bus
I love Jennifer Tilly
She's great have you ever seen the wrong man with though
Portillo's
Legitimately one of the funnier movie
Please deliver senior
Promise
But their first two outings
Responsible
Set them up to 6
They work like somebody
They weren't a team that was like oh my God we've got a
We got a f***
Absolutely ludicrous dude it's due the 3rd be this
Puracy in order to get them these intellectual property that have been stolen
Based on the fact
Get there first two movies
Didn't even really breaking
Frankly
I still don't Verity
Well I mean crimes committed
Alright
Melbourne
Interview
Takes a bit of a turn
Sofia is about to
Make a claim
Means that when they come in they're going to arrest all of them
People
The copyrights
At some point it'll be some kind of task force
To come in and do this type of work
Especially when it's a conflict of interest
Make these arrests
And then you would only get rest
They told me because
Copyrighted work
Rico
Offense
What it is
What what would the task force
Like you got to swap
Right everybody knows
They are highly militarized probably
Two military special weapon
Text
So your tax
Force though for a
Rico
Scituate
What do they look like
Justice swimsuits
It's a normal and now I know you got to come in casual
You got to come in you're going to come in like office you got to come in like
Hey
Bunch of tourists we just wanted
Universal Studios Rico Suave
Does shirts
Rico Suave
Now we find out something we all probably should have assumed about carry law
Because you know I worked in Hollywood right you know I was not actually wrote screenplays I tried to
Shop around
I met lie these players you talk about
Is the case with all of these people
Weird
It's really weird
Scary mystery
Why not that would make more
Well it would make as much sense you would lose
Where is with a cold
Was trying to break into Hollywood obviously didn't work out cuz where we are now
She wants you to know
I worked
Yeah pretty deep in many years and they never would let me in
But I was quite psychic and I tapped into in her lot of got lost
And whatnot so I know a lot of the story
Faction
I can tell you that
What went on with your screenplay with your book in your ear riding
Some people knew
That's dangerous
That's a dangerous lying to be taken with someone who is clearly
Is Sophia Stewart clearly is
You know if she's willing to post
These
Like these court documents prove that you
He's wrong
There's an element of delusion into
She's putting out to the world I worked in Hollywood I was in deep
Not really in that I was psychic and I heard gossip
Play the gossip part
I heard gossip
I heard Dokken
If you are going to gossip definitely don't gossip about a second person who can f****** remote-view you while you're
She knows if the stuff is Sophia thing or
Because she's
Just throw out whole lot
How do you say
The other part
Like you were psychic
Chicken more like somebody was like
Okay
I'm going to be honest with
Find a knock
I saw something on TMZ
This is not
Like many ideas are stolen maybe not entirely like
Everybody sends in scripts and all that
The rights to them
Maybe somebody has an idea somebody else right there better script Base outside
People do commercial auditions right
Sure commercial audition and you'll have a great performance
Yeah but we don't want you
And what wines of happening is
The guy they do choose
Or the person they do choose
A wind-up feeling imitation of the performance
That they really like
It's tough
But Sophia
I'd like to know read some of her down
This is an important document
Hold on
Pedicure
This is our time scale Club
Deals with the Earth during the year 2110
By that time planet Earth
Experienced a spiritual Evolution was underway
Also man was finally moving from
Conscious conscious
Spiritual Development
That seems like the reverse of what the Matrix is but find us it seemed apparent that the spirituality Woodson
Prevail over lasting quote-unquote
Unfortunately members of Earth
Largest
Incorporation
By controlling the mass media
Secret organization with
Fellers
Creative genius Rockefeller
What's the definition of clunky right there
Colors for I can't even hear you say those words anymore
They convince people on Earth to rebuild their Weapons Systems as a means to provide money and jobs for everyone
War Began even before the new weapon systems are most of the population
Liquor bottles
Weapon system
Development organizations
His organization was instrumental in building the Space Storage
The most secretive highly Advanced devices known at the time
The Rockefellers
Commanded econ
Tyranny
Econ accepted the assignment with number locked in
Just before
After The Happening
Organizational tasks
Beatles
Turtle
Does not it sounds interesting
I said it
I want to read The Matrix
Still I know that's that's terrible
But you know what
Even if you are a prodigy
Literally means you come up again throwing Haymakers
Unique color of her skin to reflect her inner emotions
Unfortunately
Contact with
Econ's growing spirituality
Conditions conscious contact
Dan sexy
Pecan
Pecan in his people escape
Caps
Hostage
Do you know what
Really
Element
I can't remember
Anyting
Remind me of the Matrix so far
Between them
Closing into Earth combat
Affected by powers of the third eye
That's really nothing like the Matrix I don't see
Any similarities
I mean there's a ship in the bay
You could make sort of a flimsy argument that
Spiritual in nature
The stuff in the mail
Like what Morpheus is trying to impart a spiritual in nature
It's more of a user manual
It's not really a spiritual awakening
It might be presented that way you can but it's really not
No anything but
Pretty early concrete
I mean it's
Infected
Rooted as as those that spiritualism itself is a function of reality as opposed to
Which is a function of
I don't know man
Perpich.
Ronaldo
We all are
Carmatic
Let's pair button
Mixquic
She might slander
God
And I did pray to God and he
He told me what
Right and I wrote that she and I didn't know
Becoming a judge
Attorney named Larry long
Call me up with a witness
On the phone and he was laughing
Greenville evaporation he asked me how did you
No I said what
Suck my Johnson
God told me
And I wrote it in a legal phrase
Top
With no evidence God just told her that was
I'm starting to think that she stole the copyright from god and goddess
To be awarded
That's that's my position
I feel like there's no way to
Need that outing
Really shouldn't
Look I don't know a lot about you
But I'm going to guess they are immediately going to be far more hostile to your case it might prejudice
Gorgeous
By the way no matter what you do
Because you blew a lot of guys to get
I would like to court my prayers
It's written it's also very strange that God told me the thing that I thought before I ask is weird
But what I'm getting Petty as hell
I think at this point remember when Elijah was like
Too many dicks
Getting sucked
I think they were pretty much done with her
Matrix
Talkative
Terminator 2
I'm not going to say that I could be a lawyer and
Walk through this
But for a podcast I think I've pretty well laid out what the deal is
Everything is the episode
It doesn't end
Lake Harriet
Seems like
That's why she's there
Is as the chocolate
About
The Matrix.
It becomes more
Clear why I don't believe her about the Matrix
Because she starts to get real wacky
Is it because she tries to
Describe the plot of The Matrix and gets it wrong
No that would be amazing though
Illuminati told me and this year 2016 the Mason
Illuminati
Wake me up
And the Rothschild
And the Matrix and Terminator
That guy would have a second walkthrough that I would win that lawsuit
Then I would play a major role in world events
Before I even initiated a second lawsuit
All right.
They already know what's going to happen I'm telling you the Illuminati
They know what's written in
They know what's going to happen and everything at so what I'm trying
Say to you is that
Did everything in their power
Put Hillary in there because they were going to get everything the same with Hillary
Usual getting away with everything
They knew that Trump trump it was part
Chocolate part of the
Wow
Famous like a trumpet
Oh f***
Railroad
What are the creator of The Matrix
Illuminati
Praying to God about this horror who is pissed off
Night shift
From her point of ripe
Not
Sex worker.
I'm not trying to be
Okay hold on let me know
Better turn around
Important
Let me start with the classic
Did anybody here like impressions
Pause for the audience
Turn around
Petzl rotometrics right
I just heard him say I did
God dammit you told me I was not going to win the first lawsuit I don't even know why I fight so that wasn't that
Illuminati
Wind
The first song
Give the so much
Jesse legitimately
We got to work out our relationship
It was God
What could the Illuminati wanted Hillary to get in because then they can keep doing their dirt
Sino somehow I'm fine with that
Well it's for project
Taylor and that's why Trump
Superman
There is a
Familiarity with
Trump did a lot of these like
I started to think about
The peeling across so many weird
Disparate
Because with Alex
I think it's
Like
You know his business model largely relies on
The deregulation
If you want to take from that level on a craftsman
Materialistic level
You could make the argument
Decided was truck because
Cuz you realized
Democrats power again
That there would be trimmed towards
Putting
Restrictions on Lotto
The things that would make his Empire crumble
This this billion-dollar unregulated industry of selling snake oil
Maybe they might regular
Possibility or you can look at it from the angle of life
It's very clear that Trump has been a white
Forever and ever
6 wood
Joy.
Superhumans kind of America
Territory
You start to look at people like
Yeah
She's crazy right
Somebody says I'm going to release all the
He's f******.
But he keeps
And that gets you like hairy chest
Who believe that there's some sort of
Nefarious
The Deep state
That resonates
Cassidy
Paranoid
Right
Baker Hughes sort of milia that whole world
One level.
Being
Blade to support Trump
Is because people like Jim Bakker
And a lot of
You make money off religion
Realized
Is that Trump is going to and have moved
He's
The rules
Churches
To make money
Didn't know that the con man is not going to hinder their content
Bunch of diverse
There's nothing really bringing all of them
Together like
Mortally doesn't seem hyper-conservative
She doesn't seem like someone I mean
Political in that way
She's not on the we need Healthcare trip because
The Trump Administration
Is going to finally release the Hologram bed then he'll everybody beds
I think that everybody in different ways
Being done to them by the
Makers in The Voice
People like Alex like Jim Bakker
Jim Baker's leaving a lot of people astray
Insinuating the Trump is going to be a blessing
Christian
He knows that he's business is protected by
Right right
IRS investigation of Jim Bakker
Weird
Yeah as long as Trump's in office
Zoo
Same thing
It's weird to me because
We always want to overcomplicate
I think it might be
Yeah just a lot of people realize that like
He is way too busy
Covering his own ass
He's never coming back around
He's the kind of fire entry
Well it's kind of like if you're a kid in school you're at like substitute comes in hungover
You kind of intuitively know like
This guy is just going to be we're going to watch a movie everybody
I think we're still drugs right in front of him he's going to be like
I don't know how much
Fighting more than
Probably people one egg
Your theory and I'm not saying
100%
If I understand correctly
When the Conners
Who are used to calling these dump
Sarah and John
I can't talk about that
Wii releases
Realize
That man was going to be
They directed all the
People they were coming
To support the con man to be present
Play the con man who knows the
Is it going to
Which is why
Alex probably hate bush in the other guys
They're Republican
But they're not common
They're just liars and stupid and
Maybe
I don't know I think there's much more.
Thought
Anyway
I told you this is going to be
And it is next
Carrie asked Sofia
If she's
Thinking about aliens
No sense
Are you thinking about the incoming Ary that's basically alien technology
You know I'm a lie alien AI
Where is your mind going with everything now
Ambidextrous meaning is that I have the same
Both hands and it means I'm using both lobes of the brain
Doesn't that I cracked the codes on system so that's why I never
Fetty trademark whatever
Trademark login
Feed them in any law because I can practice
On anything that I do
Nothing that you can't even imagine
Hold on
Huh
Alright
This Mexico Jordan
This made me feel
So worried
Because it is an instance of like
I think that
She thinks that movies
I know you remember cuz you reading the major
You do remember the virtue
Car
Yes hologram card that starts up with a musical note
I think I do
No clue
Go back and look at it
Car
The Virtue car
A virtual Wireless
Hologram clone
You saw the Holograms in the movie
Instead in the Black Panther movie Heist
Sophia
Call Jess Sofia
You do know that the order
Facial AI
Saudi Arabia
That they made her
Yes she's getting paid a paycheck her name is Sophia
Call Matt
I got bad news 2016
AI in
In Saudi Arabia
Orchestrated 9/11
Give me ideas virtual cars
Call her attention
Cartoon
Invisible jet
And then her saying that even in there
So they said hi Sophie
Storyboard watching
The Golden Girls The Walking Dead
She should also never agree to meet with
Countless Russian Queen from histories or Sofia Vergara Sofia Coppola or Sophia Loren
I don't talk to him
She could totally meet
Embodiment
Of wisdom
Sophia Stewart
Is that a lot
She is
Terminator
The Illuminati say she's got a lot to do with the future
The Future shoes
Things that
We didn't even realize she's helped
Oh no
Surety
Autograph
Security called me up when year
And they were totally thrown away their resumes
The Roswell incident
Blue
Ship back in the ghetto
15 cigarettes
Aerodynamic
Fluid silly sewing The Matrix
4 cup
Fluid magnetic ring potion in the reversal of gravity
San Jose
Walking visit
Break the time barrier
Speed but how they also come like helicopters
They broke the time
If you don't believe it carry I will send you over the classified information that they say
Cetme from Outlast
I just had a dream about the other night yeah there's a lot of Grey
Crazy stuff.
Lot of crazy stuff
Target Kapolei
This is so far
Why
Just going to get some serious copyright top Dan
I have always wanted serious copyright talk
Now we're getting Illuminati time I try and have a substance
Discussion with you about the real issue
Our about the better is rough without the
She did she did so
Beats from Whataburger
Was that
WhatsApp
I remember
Penelope Cruz
Cameron Diaz
I remember Tom Cruise's
So
Yahoo
So strange
If I understand
This correctly
She saw the Roswell
V
Share classified information to somebody who's not allowed
She sounded more Alex Jones even I think
Anybody we've ever heard on
Project Camelot in that she's like
She's totally claiming that
They called her up
How did you know
I do like I just reverse engineered it
Yeah
She will go into later talking about
Astrally time travel
She's able to go to other places and then ask them how their technology works and then come back and
Alright so she's a butt
Screenwriters and clearly we know
They can't
Because writing is X
Actually hard
And dialogue isn't
Yeah yeah
They're not good with that
Knock
Being writers rooms
Just like throwing out if you put them near a whiteboard
You're going to get something
If you are in a writers room in your trying to write like Black Mirror episodes if you if you have Leo zagami
Me in there and just tell her to shut up
Unless he's Pope
You headed we don't need your help when it comes to the actual
But I don't know where
Smart idea
What Pokemon can just say that it's a nice
But you notice
Recognizing earlier that
She seems that a lot of dates
And then what you talked about the Roswell thing
National Security agent
He called me some year
They called me pure
Is a few specific date
I'm going to go later
Many moons ago so she hasn't had
Contact
Yeah
Let's see up there was some another question I saw in here someone wants to know
Have you been basically do you feel that you've been contacted by aliens abducted
Well I'ma say this
Why was writing the Matrix and Terminator and 1980s dream where I saw
The shift
You saw in The Matrix
Significant Azurite saw the ship
In a dream
But I didn't know that the ship was an alien ship and chill
Homeland it wasn't contact
Me in 2010 or 2011
Set me over
The Pentagon is a picture of the ship why
Which I will give to anybody when they give the Matrix 4450 give you the All Blacks
Security
Pentagon information it's real
I think that's illegal
Illegal but it's not
Mark of her sort of
Technique I've read interviews interviews but I've read pieces of people have written about it
And oftentimes to brickwall whatever you ask for evidence
Bhsa like bye-bye book
Can you can get it it's just intended to sell the book
Carrot that use dangling out in front of it
Secret Pentagon pictures of the Nebuchadnezzar that proves that my book is that
Actually
Blah blah blah
I respect the hustle
Because you're old
Because it's a good group of people to hustle or hopeful
People really not hard but any any halfway right
Person with here like
Oh I buy your book
Integon documents
Yeah we have f****** right
A dozen
So
I have I have
Huge pet peeve
Like
All of all of those little thrown into Ark
I even though they're not
There for any reason
The one word
Basically what's going on
Yeah removes kind of
Attempt to sound smarter while using
I'm boiling this down to the particular
For you when in reality
You are absolute
Dodging
Cuz
Let's do you feel that you're what I would call a precog see the future
The Oracle was created after me being a visionary
She's the Oracle not only
James Cameron laundry list
But you should go after
Just about everybody
Socrates
Oracle in The Matrix
She Wrote This vaguely
Treatment
Early 80s
The character of the
The Oracle is
Kindly older black lady
She identified with that character
Because she's
A little bit delusional
Kind of
Put a bunch together and then was
And then everything went off the rails
If that's what she identifies
I assumed
Because that was essentially directly take
Chicken from
She doesn't know about the sources
Actually came from
It's like a it's a it's a great movie
Because
Like we said
The beginning of this episode
One of the reasons that it's so
Mixable with other things
Because it's so base
You know I had such
Archetypal
Imagery
And storytelling
Is it took this
Very simple
Universal story
He put it into a weird sci-fi
Cyber
Punk
Aesthetic
And then serve
What is a proof-of-concept of
Slightly stolen verse
Filmmaker
Time stop
Be the interest
It was like a stolen from Curacao
Get it
It's tough to come up with ideas
Originally
People didn't come up with the heroes
Describe
Describe are you sure
I mean 84 somebody who is
Greek
I have no idea
How it is possible for you to know where archetypes
Come from
But anyway
Play One Last Cry
What are the things that ties all of these
Disparate worlds of
Of calling people
Weather
Whether it's Alex Jones
Whether it's Project Camelot
It's a lack of
They're all afraid of CERN
Using
Create different weather patterns
Later
Indigenous people that lady's butt using
Dance with the rain the rain soundtrack
Xbox arranged oz of water
When it had a drought
Grow plantain
But these people are using the CERN
Troy
People so they can bring
Wealthy ocean
Call Kaiser
They wanted they wanted Hades they wanted Puerto Rico they wanted Cuba
Search for Dale Dye
But you know what was holding them back on Vudu
And hate are in Haiti
Akubra
Vudu
Okay couldn't get around the voodoo
Swear to God I say that on a daily basis
Getaround even in that clip the carries like
I'm a remote viewer I don't know what's going on the moon
It's such as such
It's amazing that are thirsty
Clark's quote
Any technology
Indistinguishable from Magic
It's a
Frustrating
Truth that that is
True even when the
Technology
Is explainable
Right like it's not Magic
Do a weather.
Noah
Also
So whether dances are real silver what is just a big
Eva weather today
Puerto Rico
They wanted to take Fidel.
Ulcers
She goes on to ramble about like Louisiana New Orleans
No that's true evil weather weapons and
Being very strong against these weather weapon
The voodoo is strong with
Hurricane
Most
So I can get around the voodoo eventually that argument flawed if your argument is that
Vudu
Voodoo negates weather weapons
You got to get a room
Who wrote The Matrix and Terminator movie
This is one thing that we can all
Getaround
Take it around
So I think at this point
Decided
A lot of fun and it was a lot of Alex Jones on Friday
Sprite.com follow it someplace
How about if you wanted some
Alright
What else
Nope
You know what though
On Thursday
Tomorrow night if you're looking good
Aurora
But you know what
Sophia Stewart
Lying about
She's not killed anyone
Alex Jones
Probably did kill a dude
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color