Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Alex Jones
Yes sir
Great Bud's Chicago dragon games
Cubs
Buds
Walking funny out in like a social life
Funny guy on Twitter
He had this thing with you
Is B that he kept doing where he was a
You kept accusing the guy was selling.
Progressively got worse
As we got drunker but
It's a super fun time
I know I don't care about baseball or the Cubs really at all I know
I always go Cubs Go is the stupidest song in the world
This game that we went to was the end of the regular season for the Cubs ended up winning the
There was electricity in the room
And it was
They won it was an exciting game
Like the game is ending everyone
Can stadium is singing Go Cubs Go
Find myself singing along to you
Baby is insane I really it's one of the types of warsong that everyday
Way worse
Boston one
That.
A lot better
I like Chelsea Dagger
It was that really interesting experience
I said I hadn't really had much of an my life is
Just like really blending into the hole
Like I became part of the stadium of got it but
Well because we're recording this on Wednesday and last night they lost of the Rockies in video
And are eliminated
Sorry about that
Sorry about that, Stan
Time I tried to go to Cubs game was on Friends
New York comedian
Rhinebeck
Tile layers were both
And we tried to go to a Cubs game I got rained out
25 bucks on beaters
That was a bummer
That was that's more like a Cubs fan
That is a bummer
A couple of new donors
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
David David
It was just join up
I'm a policy wonk
You could have bumped it up a little
Appreciate it very much if you'd like to
Support the show what we do
Helping us out
Mayfield pitch a couple episodes to cut it out of the episode
Really gross about it if you want
If you donate
Bucks a month based on the number of episodes we put out that's like
Expensive
I don't know what that means I don't know if that's compelling
Deal
More people supporting the show makes things much easier
Not only just logistically in LifeWise
But
Freedom's that I don't
Experience in my life
Website
Like having all of your blood at all times
Another thing to is that like I've been
If I can't go sell my blood
Because I'm sick I risk getting tons
People sick
Who are also in the
Plasma center
If I do you responsibly go in there
Freedom of my license taken away
And I can't do that if it's been almost a year-and-a-half
I don't know if we can do that
Look at Rodger Stones ass with
I don't know I'm not here to
I'm not going to stop doing the show at any point
Tattoos
What does things that I've liked
And if you guys
Support the show and you like what we do
Little bit any little bit helps
And thank you to everybody who don't support the show
If you don't want to support the show financially and you just like listening to it
Fuckingawesome
Enough will all of my everything
Help us out at the end of the day
If you wanted to donate to charity
I did
How dare you
We can hear our show
That's exactly right
A hundred percent I agree with that
Today we are interested
As always
Is the case whatever we have a really fun episode like we did on Wednesday
Today weather
The chat afterwards about the idea of like
Are we just abandoning the present and Alex Jones
And we both realized.
It's outside of our job
We have to talk about the present
MLM
Middle management guy now
Even if he's publicly deconstructing to a gross degree
We kind of still have to talk about the present or else
We're kind of leaving part of the equation
Unsung
I'm so today we would just forget what the present is is
We constantly live in the past like
Where we would be like like we were in Futurama
Which is an unending stream of being poured upon all of our faces
All day everyday with no chance
The station today we're going over Tuesday October 2nd
I don't know I told you
That I didn't
Go to the present
I can kind of predict
I was wrong
Yeah that we have known and listen to
Iraq
I have
No idea. No one would have predicted that alright so here is an out-of-context drop from
Today Show
I don't claim Jack diddly
Squad
I don't know what's going on me neither babe
You know what's going on cuz I realize this and that drunken Hotel interview
Like I don't know did 9/11 I have no idea
I recently watched on Rogan show
Right all the time
He knows what's going on 99% right ninety-nine percent of the time and
Everything
It's possible it's unlikely that the gambler's fallacy is that
Does October 2nd
2018 episode
Is a thought going to be super fun
F****** hysterical
Alright
Beginning of the Rock
35 days until the most historic election in
World history
I know
Referendum on nationalism vs. globalism
Global
Emily Dark Age
Really really dropped
The Weeknd
Tidewater research
And by then a lot of other people have done research
Cool
And now
We have all the documents
What is
Big ball information no wonder
Social media are able to share information virally
Because they're going to make a bunch of dirty moves the next 35 days
The information we're going to
Stunning
Can't
Alex Jones I have dropped the ball
And let me tell you how bad I dropped it
But only because the other side hasn't picked it up yet
Anythink
I mean your first instinct
Believed Anita Hill
Nope
Oh no
Is Captain Obvious
Crazy bulshit
His narrative about it has been constantly evolving as
He posted a story couple days back about how like
She has travel pictures and that proves he's a liar and s*** like that
Well maybe that's
If it's not a hundred percent truth and that means that she's a hundred percent
Can Amplified and exaggerate
Conservative talk
Pinpoint about her
When we get to what the ball he dropped his
Oban
This is what I'm saying this is what I was talking about at the beginning of the episode I predicted that like Alex is going to be running
Interference for Kavanaugh
It wasn't like I don't need to go listen
These angle on this
Is unbelievable and he begins
To get into it here
Last Friday because
Gaston Ford
Our story didn't add up
Write for criminal trial
You do for criminals
Not for a job
Began to look at her CIA connection
Or she is just the embodiment
It's on
I bet it's unbelievable
Okay I'm listening
And then her
Father
Grandfather
Brother
Brother-in-law
Work in the CIA officers that produced
Dossier
State lawyer
Believable
Rosetta Stone of everything
She's finally come for now know that she is part of the team that set up the field
She's part of the team that is behind the eyes
Well her brother
UPS open involved
At some point
I'm gonna leave alone
Play Bingo
Vicky is a right course it's not a surprise but he's with me.
Listen regulated does one thing
In terms of her family being CIA I don't know if that's true I don't think there's like a database
I can just type someone's name into it pops up
I don't think it works that way
Betty would obviously be true because his dad is totally insulting somebody
Version of the CIA
Saudia her lawyer is
Involved with
McCabe I also don't know if that's true I don't care
Mukbang
Your lawyer represent the daily Stormer
Like
I don't think it's a problem that they do
I don't I really don't if that's free speech issues and they take our clients
Who are like
Disgusting to most people and have like absolute
It's part of the whole affair.
That but I don't think they like just because you're a lawyer who has represented a Nazi
Makes you a Nazi
I don't think Zack version of Association really work
ACLU
F***** if that were the
I think there are lawyers who are.
Equivalent
So I don't judge Alex for having a lawyer who also represents.
I don't think that
Frankly I judge
Having a lawyer that helps also represent Al
A little opportunistic representative
You can do better
Right
So all of this is kind of
She's involved
Mind-control
Yes that sounds right
Where do we go
I'm not going to try and pretend but he's right like I did on that
Know this
Before
We recorded that episode about Sophia
You claim to Matrix and Terminator
I did some research
Two dice radio
Vista illegitimate
Supremacist radio show its legitimate whites
White supremacist
I was looking into it cuz I was like I noticed that there were a number of Alex Jones as guest
NY
For some reference
John Rappaport been on there four times
He's not leaving the house
Sophia Stewart
So that's an interesting little Rico
Her business
Now we get back to the
You can't get around that voodoo.
And Alex's life ezclaim doctor
Is involved
It's even worse than
Follow your specialty is implanting false memory
God help us
Psychology professor
Are you a Scientologist now what is that
You're at the fields all the enemies are psychologists
Alright
Whatever
Go I think I think already we can start with
Her specialty is implanting false memory
False memories
It is not the
Anything other than the actual Act
Oven planting false memories into a human being
The movie Inception
But in a person
Before we get to any of this
Tries in heaven quotes
Dumb Road
And this one's my favorite
Adjust the midterms
Brett Kavanaugh
Kill Kavanaugh
Shut off
I'm get to that later
Look
I'm not saying I'm for it I'm just saying if somebody would have come out and say that that's what we should do
Let's not there's a Georgetown Professor tweeted some stuff
Analog reviews
Been up to
Reinforcing the system
That allows people to assault women
They deserve to be made
If you're uncomfortable as this makes
Survivors of assault
I'm liking this person so far
Painful death
Cuz I think she got kicked off Twitter for it
Prominent woman getting kicked
Twitter for Scotia
At the very least
A response to a horrible Injustice that is being committed
Odd
Weird
Very weird
Justices
So I don't think his delivery especially if they want to cut
You're welcome I'm fine with it
Already did
I'm kind of for that for Supreme Court Justices
You know what I mean
Interesting things to do
You want to have
Well ovaries of the female Supreme Court Justice
Supreme box but it would be interesting to put on some sort of
You can't have kids
If you're on the Supreme Court.
Because that would buy us your opinion
Future stuff
Saying is that
The Fantastic thing about what's going on right now
Is that reveals the Supreme Court to be the Sham that is always be
Subway has never been anything anybody has ever had
Impartial Justice is all they need to do is look at this now and be like
Anal that's full of s***
You assume it has especially like in earlier times
20 years where the Supreme Court wasn't awful
Baby where the Supreme Court
Aurelia get your argument
I'm still not convinced the black people are people
Right right there was a tough time
Something for every
Here's the deal
I'm not telling you the
The truth about the story again
But part of that is because
Point in the show we're maybe like 20 minutes into Alex's episode little bit less than that
But Alex realizes on air
He hasn't read the story either
Like he doesn't actually
Of course.
He doesn't realize he realizes in the middle of talking about stuff
He needs
More contact than the headline
And he doesn't have it
She just knows brain control program
She implanted memories whatever you got like the bullet
But he can't
You can't do it you realize
Two important of a story for me I should probably skimm this thing
So he fakes
Beyond air
Very regularly
This is pretty funny
Surprise surprise
Long
George Halas
Intuit
Plainview
In Plainview
The most information
It's right there in front of us
Try
Is the most
Crap I have ever seen
Tell us what they've been trying to do
Comeback
How long is the Oscar for
Like 10 minutes
Commercial Insurance
Eddie comes back and most of what he's prepared is not so much about this
Got a couple more Beats
What he's done is he's gone in Ringgold articles about the Unabomber
Extra
James Holmes the Aurora shooter
And that's about it
Quite literally went back into his office
Cauldron
Said toilet and then here we are
He just went to his office
Found that little
Wall mount that says in case of emergency brake
MK Ultra stories
That's my theory now the story is a little bit more robust
We can talk about a little more
Any has this basis of
The Unabomber
And James Holmes
In order to
Into the idea that she's running a mine
Control
Operation
And
Way ahead of time
I think Alex could get sued
I think this is liable not a lawyer
I don't know exactly but if I were doctor Ford
I would sue the s*** out of Alec
He is absolutely lying about her
And it is
Dead to rights live if the lawyer for the daily Stormer isn't listening to this
He's on this episode
He herded in The Ether
What I don't again
If I were her I probably wouldn't
Because of the difficulty and how much of a burden
Some process it would be
But I think she has ground
Dr. Ford
Father brother and brother-in-law CIA
Hairgum Harrison the second letter since junior
Recruiting program
Stanford College
Bald in the recruiting
Can't prove that
Then it got even worse
Connecticut
And more
Instead and how dare them
Yeah she was in some program to help people
She Wrote
And ladies a gentleman
Murder She Wrote
Major
Classic MK Ultra mind control programs
Wards.com
Job.com
Last night
Physically ill
Because I already knew all about this at my stomach
Yeah so cuz he already knew all about it
But you heard what you were there at the end there I think one of the very important pieces that just might slide under the rug to most people
But it's that Mike Adams
The health Ranger
Is the one who wrote this story
Natural news is Alex's source
For all this we're basically the equivalent of Paul Joseph Watson
Spiritual health
Apparently super rich
Having a large part of it is
Sky Zone
He makes a lot of website
Like really good urls
Good feo kind of management
I meant Bells advertising on
Network
This is what I understand I haven't fully looked into it but from what I understand he has
Hon's if you are elves that are
Quickly marketed
First Pacific
Epic searches
Just makes tons of money
From the ads on those website
Which one
Of the main one
Being this site to put that
Disinformation about help stuff all the time
It's so frustrating
It's so frustrating that we do show where we study all of these people running great
Lack of morals
Fiber to do whatever it is
Requires a certain
If you will
I don't think you do either
You
Can have my daughter I have
Nothing to do with that
Sorry
Then I saw this last night
The article
I forgot today
Does Media Matters article is
He's more guilty than he knew
I don't care about that I didn't look into the letters article because
I'm going based on
The primary source
Oh that's the actual information
Alex Jones
Then they're not making that claim
So whatever
Like Media Matters and Light
Be saying which I'm sure Alex is
Misrepresenting
I don't give a s*** about
Yeah I care about what Mike Adams
The health Ranger
And Alex Jones
The freedom range
I have no response
Joe Carroll
Heading it up
View
Author of a mind control study
Very clear like what is claim is is not changing
It's very consistent
He's running these
Mind control studies
MK Ultra
I think you were
This is not at all what you would expect his ankles
No I was not going to I was I I actually kind of appreciate
Women are always lying about sexual assault
What's great about this
You would probably saying that women are always lying a week ago talk about
This is great
Because it gives us an Avenue to
To discuss Alex Jones is crazy
David Cavanaugh
Ford
But at the same time we don't have to dwell
Deeply in
Basic stuff that you hope humans just understand
Very very first off
You shouldn't be on the Supreme Court
No matter what
Because of his views
Behaviors outside of the
He should not be anywhere near anywhere
Ever
ESPN
Supported
And propped up
And and
Defended by the people who probably did this
Attacking a woman
It's literally
I don't know if there's any way you can
Comeback
Like her life is never the same
No
She's it's not that I don't want to I don't want to say
Oh she's gone and ruined her life she has
John something in one moment that will a revocable
Any aspect of her life
Forever and ever and ever
China irrevocably changed his life
Exactly like 121
To that but you have to stand up
No matter what
Speak it to death and I drink
Look who is
I think for most of us there's that that sort of Mighty Mighty Bosstones
Thank God I've never had to knock on wood
But I wonder if I could do it
Don't have to make that decision
And I think that anybody who judges
That decision without
Understanding of
He's being
Remarkably
Not only to her but
Mini
Many other people have done much better analysis
This situation
Weary
But that is
Is a bisque
In this next
Familiar
Criticism
Ford like the kind of things that you would expect
Figure Alex
It's just regular old there's no bottom to how bad conservatives bowl-shaped
Alex
Dr. Ford
Psychologist
She loves reggae Scientologist man I swear to God
Film
So I did the Hillary Clinton won is because that's basically what you do
Back there 100
Anybody who gives us why we need only
People who believe in the right on the Supreme Court that makes perfect
About being an executive for an ru-486
Cuz I have no idea
Selectors the morning-after pill that isn't supportive Phil but if you are
Too late for that
Rent-A-Car will u46
And it will cause
An abortion intermediate period between
Late enough for you to have to
Disruption of hormones and cortisol that ru-486
But I've heard
Reposted or natural
So the Smoking Gun that Mike has dug up the doctor blasey Ford is listed as one of the authors on
It is Publications put out by a business
Corset
Do the pharmaceutical
Puts out
Miss Crystal
Capitalism is crazy but it's not back
I have no idea what has been around
Talking about it on Loveline
1520 years ago that was about when we gave him the right
Ford Mustang
To be lying about her accusation
Checked abortion
Because of her financial stake
This business course
Tracks
Perfectly
Corcept website
Miss Bristow treatment in olanzapine induced weight gain and healthy men
Risperidone reduces weight gain and improve metabolic abnormalities associated with risperidone treatment in no
Normalmente
Administration of selective corticoide glucocorticoid
Antagonist attenuates electroconvulsive shock
Go coracoid receptor type to prevent game
Call Tobias
Olanzapine in rap
Selective
Glucocorticoid receptor
Discovery of a novel news non-steroidal gr antagonist Within
Vevo
Efficacy in the olanzapine model in the
Okay correctly
What she is doing
Is
They've got this product
That
Risperidone
Which is
And she is like
Early they were like hey
We could use it for other stuff
And she was like
Reduces weight gain because of the effect
Is abortion has to do with corticoid levels and 41
Chemical that can be used to do all kinds of things
And we just found out that I remember from when I was younger with Wellbutrin
Under another name
The things in the
The pharmaceutical industry of very common
So none of this research has anything to do with abortions
It's not
Palo Alto University document
Sport is the director of biostatistics
So even allowing that she might have been employed by them 3 years ago that doesn't prove that she is now
Which kind of hurts this motives are
Strike before
But you trying to protect this
Pro Financial
Further it appears that if anything Ford was working to study new application
Crystal
Is a pill that can induce abortion
If anything this should be seen as proof
The Destroyer
To keep abortion legal is the argument is that she's financially motivated by the interest in the company
The article and the basis of his argument will be flimsy as hell on its own
But it's made
Completely unacceptable by Mike Adams inability to stop himself from also calling for the hor
Throughout the article
Christine Baisley scrubs her internet history to eliminate evidence of hazy drunk and sex parties documented in her High School
Yearbooks school yearbook of Christine blasey
It's full of accounts of wild drunken sex parties attended by Glaceon others
He concludes by patting himself on the back for a job well done
Now it all becomes clear Christine blasey clearly fabricated the false allegation
Kavanaugh
Protect her own income
It profits from an abortion pill drug company whose future might be impacted by Kavanaugh's confirmation on the court
What I have to say about this ru-486 angle
It makes no sense
And the article that Micah Adams wrote about his full of s***
I mean
It doesn't just remove the motive
It actually
Complete 180 degrees
Where at
If abortion made illegal
Her research would be even more important to the company because they've got this thing and they got to find another use for
Yeah Subway but I still
This whole thing is bulshit but I'm just saying that if you're going to pull that argument then it doesn't make any f****** sense.
Make
The actual fact make your argument week
And
Lightly.
Ru-486
Organization
Instead of looking at what she did
University
Public
Control operation
So again
Very clear
His assertion
I just want that
To be driven home
Implant memories
Better not real
But
She can also remember he's that are real
I don't think that that's legally actionable if you think that she can do that
I'm just calling you a wizard
You don't like ours I think it is legally actionable to claim that she's involved in that sort of
Study for nefarious purposes
And s*** like that
I wouldn't be there but I think you
To the point where Alec
A little bit of my
Likes report
And now let's see what is actually in there
According to Alex
And then I'll tell you on the other side
What's in there
Christine blasey Ford
Hypnotic
Induction
For those of you can't see
Danny's Raven use eyebrows
Keep saying words cymatics
Neuro
Nothing going on
Starting bombshell about the hoax accusations against Brett
A few years ago
Official
Situations did you hear that
They are under total mind control Emily Weber.
Sure
Mind control
CIA
You can't prove that anyway
Are nowhere near proven
In any of this
Don't think that they're hiring I don't think that the hierarchy is like a
I don't believe that.
I apologize that I couldn't
Series wagon
Neural hijacking the way that he did
Euro
I can't I can't like with my throat in the shape it's in right now I can't do it
Neuro
Future
Movie
What are the difficulties of being on the mend from this
Now it's time to Barrel I enjoyed listening
Alex repeatedly bring up the cheese in mind
Control studies
And all this because here's the exit
Alex Jones claims he's found and red studies the doctor blasey Ford was engaged
Are there evidence of Mind Control
11 researcher
She wasn't even on it
I would guess that Alex was very intentionally not reading out the name of the study
Because even that would make it look Super Why
Here's the name
Meditation with yoga group therapy with hypnosis and psychoeducation
For long-term depressed mood
A randomized pilot
The pilot study participant
If there were any differences
Outcome
Depressed
Treated with medication
Which is really just a form of therapy that involves Edge
Vacation about mental illness
Weather
Educating the actual patient generally it'll be their family members
Some friends to help them be a support network for the purse
That's all psycho
Let's rejoin mysticism around this this is
Here you are a depressed person
Medication
What
Depression is
Experience
You better in that way you don't feel the friction that you get whenever you're depressed all the time where you feel like you're alone and miserable and nobody
F****** around it's been shown to be there's been indications
Successful event
Visual therapy
But I don't know if there's
I don't I don't know if that's
The consensus opinion
Education
You know when you're depressed your default is I am being ostracized
Gives you a like a workaround for that where you like
Not only am I not actually being ostracized but I know that I'm not right
I'm all I'm saying
It sounds
So you got psychoeducation that's one
In this
Tripartite
The 2nd is meditation and yoga in addition to
Hypnosis
Again with the addition
Psychoeducation
Is a pretty standard experiment with a control group in two variables
There's nothing nefarious or scary about hypnosis being used in a clinic
Control
I've been in therapy that used hypnosis before
NetSpend
Sometimes a very very useful tool
Incredibly annoying
Not this isn't doing anything
I am not
Getting in any kind of
Comfortable
In fact
Annoying me
The article in Infowars is written by the health Ranger
There's a textbook case of cherry-picking words in order to war
And it should serve as a perfect demonstration of how Mike Adams is a less trustworthy source for medical information than me
High School Dropout
I was getting a little petty what I have.
I do like this all made me very mad
So in the article Mike says quote
The full text of the research paper describes methods
Create artificial situation
He then goes on to start a quote from the tech
Text with an ellipsis
Assisting the retrieval of important memories and create artificial situation
Sonic
Emotions in a safe
Manor
So
Right there
The create artificial situations planted false memories
Who trying to make
So that there is there that start Steel
Situations
Contacts
Sounds a little bad but it also sounds like bad grammar
What is the first Indiana Jones
Jason Dawson
Is this rhetoric
Does that quote very intentional
As just before we start discussing how hypnosis
Therapeutic tool
And in fact this goat is bold is not from the discussion of the study at all
Hypnosis
Here's the quote
Hypnosis is a form of Highly focused attention
The relative constriction of peripheral awareness
It has been used successfully as an
Adjunctive therapy
In 1964
Abraham's suggested that hypnosis
Could be used to improve Rapport in the therapeutic relationship assist in the retrieval of important memories
A pretty artificial situations that would permit
Client expressed ego-dystonic
Emotions
Genesis Manor
Gotcha so you have right there that he's completely taking this out of context to imply that
That quote isn't relation to the actual study
How about the history of the
The use of hypnosis
In therapeutic session
Like this is incredibly
This is the clunky thing I've ever ate
It's not monkey it's intentional
But like if this was someone who is head good
It was coming from a place of like I actually believe what I'm putting down
I've ever seen in my life
Your
Doing it terribly
It's intentional an interesting
Situation though
There is that
He kind of
He kind of gives us into this place where you ask
Stop the question
Should we
Sad face
How to read
Who acted in bad faith had a
Or
Should we teach people who act in bad faith how to read better
Because he is doing both
The points that would
Show him to be a liar
See what that's what I'm talkin about that would be
What I would believe if someone was operating
Promo codes
Position that they don't understand there's
This is not stupid
This is Louis.
Malicious
Oh yeah you're right now
So I'm guessing that Alex Jones Mike Adams uses
Selective use of quotation
Stuff like that
Involves math
Because the study setup
Had a group
Is referenced
Hypnosis therapy
The reasoning of the researchers is that group therapy
Effective in treating
Has depression often includes
Cuz you clearly already brought up
A major Elementary field isolate
Like no one understands lyrics
Experiencing
So putting people in the situation where they're getting
What is jump
Really
A guided way to focus
Your attention and two
Cut-off peripheral stimuli or meditation or whatever
So did its basically too
Lightfoot
What is Hypnotic Focus
And the other is
Meditative
Yoga mat
I don't see anything suspicious that the idea of like having a group therapy session that involves hypnosis
Whether or not that provide
Is it better outcome for
With those memories
Here is the study of
Conclusion
The present pilot study examined whether meditation with yoga and cycle
Patient education
Could affect diagnostic status
Compare to psycho-educational loan
Among the sample of adults suffering from long-term depression
We found promising preliminary support
The use of these interventions to improve diagnostic
Status in ward off the development of further major depressive episode
We did not vote demonstrated
Stickley significant Improvement in overall symptoms
To report over the course of the study
The conclusion of the study is the most effective
But the hypnosis is better than just psychotherapy
Irrelevant
Conclusively
It's a little strange that Mike Adams makes this declaration in his article about this site
Bliss paper co-authored by Christine blasey Ford
We know she's intimately familiar with Max hypnosis hypnosis in mind alteration process
All of which are being deployed in this assault on Brett Kavanaugh
Through carefully crafted leaks cover-ups and media narrative
Almost half of the nation is already been Mass hypnotized
If it believing that it isn't man is a deranged serial rapist
Such is the power of CIA mind-control to Floyd
Nationwide
So
You see the argument that developed
Because
She is involved with a
Mass mind control
Study that's what she's doing
To the world
You know it's really fascinating
Because
To see the diva level by which they
Give me where they're like there's no
I mean obviously yes if they're doing a study they can control mine
Like even if the study's results
Well we did a lot of stuff and
You know us to Pista clean it was
Maybe better and kind of insignificant we would need to do more research
Yeah yeah yeah
And what they're coming up with it
Do any of this other controller
What's the winter
Alex
Mike Adams
Relationship with science
It didn't send through the way you're describing which I think is pretty accurate
Like they have 20 forever
Sort of nebulous force that they're up against they have to be omnipotent and also completely f****** stupid
The only authorized their enemies
Is because that's the only
Space in which the con really work
Howard
Craziest
What is convenient
You can't you can't tell anything about the climate from research like that
It is with
Stupid
Look there these infinite beings who can travel through space and time and all this
Fly B-25 bombers
Your imagination is s***
Kind of like eyewear
Historic black
You can't even imagine a wave
Your liens to be prosecuted about you pay for them
F****** figure it out
Right
Do a second draft on your b*******
First Niagara
This stuff
Isn't done yet
Unfortunately
This is the main
Tell good
Pilot podcast project
So unfortunately
All of this idea of mine
Control trailer
But Mike Adams articles actually about a whole lot more
And Alex in this next clip starts
To touch on that
Edit
So
Exception
Neuroimaging
Biological
Drugs chemicals
Voices for some audible frequency emotional mood
So this is from
A study that Alex's again
Taking out a contest
But
The stuff about
The
Implanting voices
Stuff like that
Talking about what
Have that weapon
And s*** like that
You shouldn't
How how is it that we live in such a
Tiered world of like
Alex doesn't even understand the words that he's
Like you shouldn't even be he shouldn't even be allowed to read articles about science without take
Making a f****** Bachelor
Please course
Because he just doesn't understand
Like in this situation
Obviously he's using them in bad faith
But he also has no idea what they're f******
If you didn't read this or stuff about it all literally only operating off like atoms
No
Stuffy's operating off
Paul Joseph Watson
Sympathy
All of these people like Mike Adams like Paul Joseph Watson like curtain Mo back in the day
Like Steve Watson all of them serve the most essential purpose
And that is
They take whatever Rob material is there and turn it into fuel that Alex
Confused
Use the raw material
He's not creative enough
And
He is
Can't be bothered
So he couldn't take these original articles or those studies
And do this with it well that first one actually wasn't
You guys got to learn how to throw f****** there before I pay any attention
Dr. Ford was involved in
In 2009
The second one
One was a little bit more
The beginning of the clip Mike Adams
He's making this argument
That this group the mental Insight Foundation
Funded
The original study 2008
And another study
On interception
So you can say they're a bit miffed
Interoception
They're trying
They're trying to bridge the gap between these two
Was involved with
Dr. Ford study
Simultaneously
Dido
Even
Broom Orchard
Set the second study that they're talking about doctor for today
So here is Alex talking about this
I can study
And I will tell you this ahead of time
Is looking at a diagram from the study and imagining what it means
Organs
That talks about in this huge paper
Vagus nerve stimulation presentation of information during different phases of visceral rhythms
Assessment
Look at these documents
I did
Document
It doesn't
Include a picture of the human body
Pictures of
And then wait for me
Alright and
It's very clear
From about
A hypothetical
Amplitude modulation
Superimposed on a static
They're talking about
The 3rd of homeostatic
Rhythm that those organs are
It's important because this article and it's not
Waves that are happening to
Worst incline these like this is how bad the
Liver stinks like I'm fine with that
Facilitating Zack misunderstand
The first one
The first article is weak
The title of it is yoga meditation
Hypnosis
As a treatment for depression
If they read it they will find the conclusion being
Maybe
Statistically significant
Participants in this
Has nothing to do with anything
Nefarious adult
So
Demonstrate
Because that's the case they have to dig a Little Deeper so they come up with the most flimsy connection to dr. forge
Make their argument
Mike Adams
If you ventured even deeper down this Rabbit Hole you find the same mental inside Foundation that funded the master
Hypnosis mind control study
On which Christine Ford work
Also help another study
Wealth fund another study called
Interoception and mental-health a road
What problem is this article nor any of its Lake prove that Mental Health
Foundation funded the depression
Speculative Anansi
Shaky start
The health Ranger then tries to make Ford look super
Suspicious
Because the company that allegedly provided funding for 11 researchers on
Daddy that she was
Wasn't involved in a later the McAdams is scared
Smoking Gun
Even if everything you saying there is
True
Has zero to do with Ford
This is deeply disgraceful and so f****** a
Because this s*** is weak to
Mike Adams has to play a three-card Monte game with this article in order to distract her from realizing he's saying nothing
He brings up the entire reception article talked about in the middle
Very quickly go to how the globalist have created Sonic weapons
In order to implant that idea in his readers heads the article must be about
Talking about
Right
There are wiggling
And then
Related to that says
You know
Things are real and then comes back to it only Joe
As though those two were related in the instead
Sonic weapons are like a non sequitur
Squiggly lines
Sonic Sonic
Of this idea that
The mental
Foundation
Has done both of these studies
Ford isn't
Wichita
Not at all
The Sonic
Crimson ghost
Even playing tonight
Which don't exist
Then he excused
His main flight of
Warm it is unbelievably dishonor
After implanting the idea of Sonic weapons in his readers
Quote getting back to Christine blasey Ford's working
Interoception neuroimaging
The paper funded by mental Insight Foundation openly admit
That the neuroimaging roadmap can alter decisions behavior and even Concha
It explains quote
Recent years have witnessed a surge of Entry
The topic of Interest option
To doing part 2
Emotional experience self-regulation
Importantly interoception is not limited to the conscious perception or even
Dr. Ford
0 to do with its article about interoception
Nothing
Her name isn't on it
No organization
He's involved in
Is involved in this art
So getting back to Christine blasey Ford's work on interception neuroimaging
Is a
Dishonest
Deceitful
Way to present
So-so
Oh s*** so he pulls the the trifecta
Chico's
Unrelated thing up top
By the way I'm related things
Now let me
Getting back to the thing that she was not involved
But I'm just going to say getting back to dr. Christine blasey Ford and then grammatically
You have no choice but to accept that when I say
Really
Not saying that they're related at all
He's very clearly
Grammar
In this
Really which isn't
It's really it that's why I said the sleight-of-hand
He's unprofessional
It's trying to paint a picture
Absolutely not real
She's only the health Ranger
She's only involved in that study about yoga and depression
Mike link to article
Company found funded them ten years apart
You can even prove that
Additional
About interoception
It's not about what Mike
Interception is basically just
Internal perceptions
What one's body is
Experience
Essentially it's a word used
Describe how the information
From your body goes to your brain
From your experiential Oregon
And if it's paper which is not a
Just described how external input is interpreted by the body and
Experienced by the brain
Ultimately
Interoceptive feeling today is 1
Because Mike Adams got me to read this long boring science article for no reason
Even if it was about mind control Wichita
It has nothing to do with Doctor four-door anyone
Shown to be involved
Mike Adams is nada.
Nor does he have any qualifications
But because he called himself a health Ranger and runs of bulshit medical conspiracy website
Lend some authority to his disgraceful
Embarrassing charades only intended to create a grand conspiracy
Rug Doctor blasi
Before
Not believing her is not cruel enough for people like
Not caring is not cooling
People like Alex
He's lost for being a
Is not satisfied unless you publicly argues that her story
Or actually attack on himself and all men
Digital Foundry
They've no further words.
Is
Shameful
Done now
There's a little bit
You know
You did you did get it right
I think
Right there
This entire list
Entire thing
If
Like to the point where
The only reason cuz you you have to
Think about this
There're others
Who would be Justice
There's so many other judges
It would be just as awful
This isn't about
This isn't about him being judge this is about
This is about men
Isabel Mendez
Drawing with like
Beastly
These dudes yeah absolutely
Clarence
Clarence Thomas's in there
Like
Infinity I feel like
This is probably not true but
If you go to a place in your head hypothetically where it's like
Some guy
Goes in front of Congo
This dude was
Is drunk all the time
Terrible decision making
He cheated and all that stuff
There would be none of them
Because it was a woman
And it was specific
Prickly about sexual
Violin
Every one of these
F****** planet
Who are are
Predisposed
To say that
Women can never
Experience
And if they do they were asking for it was always their fault all of those dudes came out of the woodwork
And the subconscious level of
Just screaming like
It's not real
That's what all of these guys are screaming shortly
Real
Ever
It is not possible to do this
Because women are either asking for it
And then it's their fault
Or they're lying about it
That's sort of the mainstream right
Especially Collins
A lot of those people because Alex the band
To be special
In some way
Breast specialist
Is by abject cruelty
That's not good enough for him this is his manifestation
Funny like we can laugh
Sheila falconer
Behind it is
Deeply cruel
The motivation behind it is
I think he takes his red
It didn't happen
He doesn't care even if it offends most
Right-thinking people
Is just like in place
What do it look if you want to just hear about how all women are lying about this s*** go somewhere else
Let me tell you about what's really going on
She's lying about that
Clear in that Mike Adams article
The entire charade
The entire thing of her coming in
Speaking to the Senate Judiciary
Isn't a temp
And also the
Did it come out about it
It's all a mask
Gnosis
That's being perpetrated on the
The public right
That's the way to invalidate everything
Even if you are somebody
Normally support
Conservatives
Normally support everybody
But you listen to her
Can you realize holyshit
I can hear a
Human beings voice
And a human beings voice that is
Experience
And even as far gone as I am
There's something
Intrinsic about when a human voice cries out in
That I identify with
Let me tell you what I got for you sir you are you are
What I got for that
Mike Joe very get rid of that women all you want
I want to talk about this
Yeah I don't want to talk a little bit more about how bad a f****** dude like Adam
Let's f******
This guy
Well
How does Georgetown
Sorry I stepped on your joke
So I'm not going to give you like a breakdown as like Adam greatest hits or anything like that
To get a real with
How bad
F****** right
Use
How bad of a Storyteller he is Within These articles his actual articles before
It's really funny
He's trying to paint this
Organization
Organization mental Insight Foundation
Arch-villain
Circle
He shows off his ability to Google things
Eastbound
That's a good skill
It's so funny without like throughout this entire article he says things like that
We are not fairies unethical or illegal activities on the part of mental Insight Foundation
However to help other internet researchers follow the money leave now uncovered in all this we're publishing public information about the
Foundation that's readily available
He just got done
He just got done in control your mind
Dr. Ford's testimony was a literal attempted brain control the country
Hey
Hey come on
He ends up listing a bunch of
Resemblance to persons living or dead
Is purely coincidental
At this point like really steps
The mental Insight Foundation took 80 million dollars in 2015
538 Broadway Suite A Sonoma California
Which appears to be a single family house
This is complete b*******
You can go to Google Street View and see if the address is in the commercial downtown district in Sonoma California
Is across the street from Sonoma Valley Museum of Art
It is exactly 406
63 ft away from Sonoma Plaza
The literal
Not to mention this week
The address which generally isn't a single family home
Also you can find Adventure Race run his locations
Beef
Maybe that's been traces to afflict with Dr forts mind control weapon program
Bigger family
Address
Ben Tre
I want to hear more about that
It's like I like you a little bit
Specialized software Vineyards can use in order to keep track of supply
Edwin
Grapes need to be harvested
You know what it is exactly the same sort of software I've encountered in other job
A specialized
41 no one else would know.
We made it super specific single-family homes
Corporate offices
You you hate you hate the feeling
Learning about Vineyards up there
That addresses listed by Virginia
A small firm that says it offers quote
Salting services for Family Foundation
Is Micah done any research
He would know that they share an office
If you looked at it
I called them
Phone number Republic
Call them right around lunch time and I got the answering machine mental
Play f****** company
Me Maryland and the kids and we're just running these two separate don't call it dinner time
Assigned
2006 tax form
Show The Virginian
Is listed as the foundation managers of their organization
There's nothing weird about this
Virginia Hubbell Associates
The larger umbrella
Consultant
And am I at is an entity
Be there towards
Grant
Lot of art programs by children's education race track
Mike Michaels on to list businesses that Virginia
Curious that he chooses only to include the seven
Corporate client
And not list Las Vegas
The City of Albuquerque
You just explained everything city of Sonoma
Wine Country
The City of Reno
Well
Berkeley child
Who knows what projects
Starcross Community Romanian babies Health and Welfare
It's a special place in my heart rate of time growing up in
Bucharest shout-out Romania
You list the clients
He does he can make this speculation
Quotes
Most of the clients appear to be genuinely helpful organization
Society
But they're probably worth a second look
Internet researcher
Probably
Notably the Levi Strauss Corporation recently came out in favor of destroying the 2nd Amendment by pushing gun
In control
That's super weak
Client
That's one of their staff
Obviously
Quotes of the jockey
List the officers directors trustees
Key employees of the mental Insight Foundation
Notably
They're all paid nothing
Except for the treasurer
In other words
But the management
Consultant Virginia
$1,000
We're not alleging any unscrupulous activities among these individuals
They're public officers of
Republic Foundation
Listed in a public document
These individuals are any list off the officer
Which is not
Unless
If your nose is a lot of Captain names on this list
It's probably because one of the primary sources of income
For the Metrolink
Play Foundation
Kimpton Hotel Group LLC
Which generated 2.3 million dollars in revenue for the foundation
In 2015
There's nothing illegal about that
It's just an interesting.
No it's not
There's nothing illegal about this
And there's nothing interesting to know
Old money
The patriarch of the family
You went to the Army
And after he got out he became a typewriter sale
I assume you're not reading from Mike Adams articles
If I kind of just went into the history of the Kimpton family
Mike Adams research for this article is so bad that I feel the need to show off by telling you about the history of the computer
The patriarch of the family Bill Kimpton
He eventually got into Investment Banking and made a whole lot of money
What you use to make even more money by opening the kitchen family Hotel
No
There was a time where you could go for bigger typewriter sales
Investment banker
This door
Created this hotel group represents now over 35 high-end hotels in 29
But money was not his God
Once during an interview with Success magazine
Was over
Earning money
Real success you said came from devoting oneself fully to family and friends
She said I've been partially success
Mr. Coronavirus
Mental Insight Foundation
Is thunder the number of research projects into
The various forms of metal
The foundation is particular interest in treating depression using therapy and meditation as alternatives
Prescription drug
Would you something to Alex should be
You would think
Kempton and his life's work
Should be something to Alex
A hundred percent
Rent
Bill died
April 2000
Elemental Insight Foundation lives on his wife Isabel
Husband land dell'amico and other family members that I can't sort out who they are
Actually Sophia's mint
There's nothing strange
And seeing the family's Hotel Group.
This family's charity all this information is public
At all
Later just Googled Kipton light goes on to say quote
The foundation donated money to the following
We're not alleging anything nefarious on this list by the way
Disclaimers in one article
You're lying out your ass
And he also knows how unhinged
The people who are the internet researchers that might
Follow up we want internet family's house
Bodone on them and then Byron.
Potential harassment
Right exactly
Braiding damage control in the article interesting
Music pathetic
He was probably pissed that he had to put it in there in the first place he was
He was probably like I can't even make these.
Created
Tell me about harassing David Hogg
In the aftermath of Parkland shooting
He created Hogwarts
God that was just a webcam of some Hogs that would actually probably be great by the way
Sarah Shahi
Tweeted something recently
About
There's a fat bear watching
Eyes on fares
I love it
Bear watching
End
Gritty
The mascot
Are the only thing
Sack bears
We're so familiar with
I hate to say this
We're getting into a very bear v shark
Nail this home
Read it over Mike Adams
All I have to say is
This is the definition
Of pathetic
Sloppy amateurish
H & H getting the bottom of these stories
I personally offended by how lazy and childish this article to my cat
Put out it
There's literally no substance other than outright lies
And irresponsible
Conjecture
He could disprove
For 10 minutes of work
F*** him
And f*** out
Cuz we know why they're doing it
Very clear
You know what dance sometimes you got to
Pull out all the stops
To confirm a monster to the Supreme Court and then just destroyed
Alex actually later in the episode with all his cards on the table accidentally
It makes it very abundantly clear
The only reason
You fight hard
For Cavanaugh
Is because he supports
Trump agenda Alex literally says Cavanaugh
I told Trump
He's going to push his agenda
That's true that's disqualifying pretty much the only thing that
Is the greatest
Liberal possible
A dream
Liberal
President was
Yeah
No come on after the first couple of
Present
If they had some sort of backdoor meeting or backroom meeting
With potential
Supreme Court candidates
And I'm going to put
Push your agenda through
I would say that's absolutely just qualifying
Even though
That is not how the courts should work the point of what we're living through right now
Becoming right
Absolutely
Recognize it
Complacent
Treating it like War outside
Recognizing that the other sites
I don't think
I don't think the right-thinking normal people should see it is
Prepare themselves
Like actually f******
Protest
You don't like I mean I don't I don't mean that and I needed like
Hey let's go
As long as there is anybody in there
I'm I'm saying
You know
We might
End up seeing night
68 convent
We might be in that position where
We all on the left
To get ready to get hit
Where there
That's it that we've been real for f******
Can you get elected president
We were all like well as president
Maybe things are going to be better now
And they just been f****** fighting a war that we thought was a thought was I think
Maybe I can speak for everybody but I think that a lot of people
Probably thought like
Conversion therapy
You don't like yeah
Spiders going to room with spiders
Yeah you don't like my brother keeps
I'm terrified of me
As his friend of the show Matt drop
Tuesday bee house
And next week is not f****** with me
Recognizing the generally
They're doing something
You're flying all around me and not touching me
Feel like I'm not f****** with them then
That is a form of immersion therapy
We're kind of hoping the idea of like a black man being an office is very scary
You right but
Do you want was going to happen
And then
Propaganda
Information Warfare
Of the like that
It's too effective and it doesn't
Respond to reality
Response
What is the meth
What is the
What is the targeted
Because we've already talked about all these studies
It's f****** b******* we don't need to talk about it more
Yeah
Alex says that she advocate
Torture method
In one of these studies
Unusual this specific language
Trees down where in the studies.
Paragraph about using
As a therapeutic
Who are guys
What because
Select application text
Like they're talking about it or contacts.
It could create an emotional response
It could create a right
Warping it
To report it
There's a big difference between saying hey get a loan in this tank
By yourself and
Deal with your own thoughts
And
Hey we're going to pour water in your throat
Choosing
Call the United States
Course
Literally
Destroy the Supreme Court nominee
I think you meant to say 2 + 280
Echoes 5 cuz that's a sort of
Normal thing
For which means it's two plus two equals five.
+ 2 equals
How dare you
What is this
What is non-euclidean
Get the f*** out of a recent episode Alex
The ministry of Truth
Which is the people who put out two plus two equals five
Not sure what to think about anything anymore
Tell you what I think about the truth
Don't matter
I told you earlier today
Shows up on the show a little bit
He shows up and we have gotten
Is Mark Randazzo
We have filed a action
My rights in California
In San Francisco
Because they tell us the last 10 years
After we filed an injunction Infowars Falls emergency injunction against PayPal in federal court
Doesn't know about Alex
His Wares
Interesting Lee's been kicked off everything else didn't do anybody else
You chose this is the one I'm going to f****** because
Bottom line
Firebird
They posted that online
Posted
Complained
Outside come on
Okay seems to boil down to two
One of them
Is about
The idea that
His civil rights are being violated
Doesn't sound right because they are targeting him because of his
Political
Now protected
Classes political beliefs
This is not one of
Just because it's not listed as one of the classes in the you like in the actual
Doesn't necessarily mean that it could not be in later on in ya does include
Separate sexual orientation isn't listed as a being included
The idea on that basis
Can make an argument I don't think that's what PayPal already be people to do it I don't think it's
How
You keep
Doing things like you're doing on this
Argument was like
Oh I was only attacking me because I support Brett Kavanaugh
Right you're like
Alright well know
Probably not okay
Or like you could make prep
Probably is in
Huge scare quote
If you wanted to make the argument of
Something like I got kicked off because I believed in trickle down economics
I believe in small government
I believe in the right to own guns
Right
I think of you
Unruh
Human rights civil rights
In order to make that argument
Kicking Alex is because
He keeps
Being
Dick ruins people's lives
Nmd don't need to prove a criminal act in order to kick him off the platform
It's not like they're a bank
Or anything like that
Oakes financial transaction
They can do that all they want
I don't have a problem with that
Cuz it's not his political beliefs
They're getting in
The second argument that he's trying to
To make in this brief
Is there
Infowars
Is the news
Infowarsstore.com
Is not political
And that is the only site that
Uses PayPal
So PayPal
By cutting off infowarsstore.com
Forum contest
All right this is an interesting argument anyone outside of a courtroom
I don't know how that works cuz I can I can absolutely
Truly understand like where that argument is coming
Speech Systems Incorporated
Tough to see a disconnect between the two is being operated as separate
Right foot sure you doesn't post harassing content on infowarsstore.com right
So I don't know
That like all of them everything
With the sales
From infowars.com
None of it is hosted on
So all of the PayPal stuff is all on Infowars store.com
Lose
At least it's at least like
That's a classic
Has the portugee wrote the law realize that you were full of
Bulshit like this
Yeah cuz if we'd written those laws we were like
Oh and also if you have a URL that's similar like
I don't like to be deposed in this case like I would like them
Cuz I would like to give testimony about
Live.com
Absolutely
For survival
Weirdo
So
That's why Mark Randazzo is
Not going to work
Although I'm interested in it more than
Interested
Because like
High-speed is a desperation
Because it's all he can
Like he knows he's
Probably going to lose it but because
Legal action
Into place
He's allowed to use PayPal for like
Two weeks long
Results of the court case we cannot kick you off PayPal yet
And maybe that'll by him enough time to
The setup
Whether or not exactly yeah
Completely different thing
Gold
I don't know man
Now this is where
Brooklyn.
He does.
But
Here's my theory
Mark Randazzo
Is actually Gray
No he's figured out the game
She has taken these
Like he is taken
F******
What are remoras
What are the ones that the little
Fish that
Suckle on the shark
Dammit this is a weird
Never going to get the lawyers that the sharks
So he's like
Lawyer up on these dudes nobigdyl
Like white heat if he is filing this lawsuit
The best thing that he could do to say to Alex Jones
Don't make me file this lawsuit
We're going to lose
But
He does not make any money
If he says don't file this lawsuit we're going to latest episode
Billable hours billable hours building hours
This is a great place to go cuz he's
Desperate
But
If he was super Craven and just some sort of like
The billable hours and horror for all this stuff
You probably kiss Alex
This clip
Alex is going to
Compare himself
Martinez
A great response
This whole move by Holt Industries
Black folks
Oh my God
I also would not go that way
Superiority
You know you're going to lose
Hippie the great spotted publicly I will not agree with that
For sure it's exactly like black people anyway
So the check
Clears on
Zero's on this that you did not maybe expect they were going
Alright alright
Send it
Comparison tool
The next comparison
WhatsApp
Everybody knows system
Ecobank
And so this is happening I'm all the free market your business
Are you butt
Beard
People
In those companies of said we were not working
Colin Kaepernick is proof
I'm sure that nobody within those companies
To be like look we're cowards
We're just waiting for someone else
Incoordination
All right we all going to get rid of him
Contextualize the world around him
Do anything against him
Giant
Broad
Giants
Cowardly
Jews in the Holocaust
According to Alex
Imagine Alex
Like this whole situation
Brings me to this like
Mental picture of
Like in the 1920s
All of these
Rich investment banker sitting around the ticker
Tapes
Showing the stock prices and all that s***
M Emmet one of them just seems like
Oh my God PayPal kick him off and then the rest of her like
It's all
Just fantasies about
Life and how would the world
Randazzo's.
But also he doesn't suck
Totally
He's clearly pushing back at least publicly on Alex's dog bowl
And he's also not all that into Kavanaugh
Which is nice too
And
Listen to Alex Azar
Outrageous
Supreme Court
Intentionally or unintentionally
For prejudice you against
Experiencing that was a great moment
Yeah if you
If you take all the argument out of it
9 people who do this for like
Forever
I assume maybe we shouldn't find a normal guy
How about that
Alex Cooper
Super defense
That's about it
Come back after the break
On the spot
If you're innocent
And they accuse you of
Because of are there was Alex Alex
No
Goodbye
Also
You owe me Double H
I almost I almost halfway expected
Blackadder
The bottom line
Specifically for these hours
I do know however that if he's going on Alex's show that's because there was a line item somewhere in the invoice
I was like
For bulshit that you need me to do
It's interesting because Mark's been on the show before we even covered in episode
He was on before
When he was just his lawyer in others
Nothing I hope never
I remember this guy cuz he was in my lawyer from
Others are
This instance has far more than other times
He seems a very unhappy
He seems like he's under duress a little bit
Alex lays out
Beef
List of accusations
I got stalked
Ford
And then make
Very unfair
Comparison
That's a reason she doesn't like
Or are you again.
False memories
Funded by DARPA
A cooperator studies
You got a whole family in the CIA basically
You got this
Project
DARPA
Aurora shooter
Psychology today
All of it
He's
LSD trial
Ultra stuff from
And stuff like that
He also showed articles where James home
Mass shooter
Responsibility
Hey anyways we should murder Andrews
Continue
Yeah
Came back into my life
I told him earlier the show
Looking into Red Ice Radio
Big fans
That really bummed me out
Anyway
This list of accusations
Is really talk
Based on everything we talked about already
I meant he gets
Home they're involved
MKUltra program
The only thing
He's trying to
Is that the people who were the subject
Of the studies
Dr. Ferguson
The next crop
Exact creating Unabomber doing is within
Rocky with yoga meditation
Study
About
Curing depression that had ambivalent result
That's how we got the Reds
The Red Skull I'll tell you that right now
Sure
I don't know
He's talking about the
Ideas
Sol Cavanagh withdrawal
And then of course
The next choice
Is Judge Amy Barrett
Presumption
And she would be the person
Victor
Gets put in his place
So he lays out
This is Mike.
Okay no problem
Circumstance
Amen at the end of this Alex says something
Stalking
That is so far
We left
I saw her slip
Whoever they put me
So is that a plethora negative
I don't know what he's doing there so weird
F******
Free Speech lawyer
Is trying to
Stupid idea about what could happen if Aries mean
That's one of the weirdest deliveries I've ever heard
Real life
If somebody staying under their breath
Lawyer is talking
Bear rape
God dammit
The implication
Presented
Update then say that
Little kid throat and drinker but the only person who makes
Is named Alex
Jim Jones
Use words from the 1300
F****** amazing is that
11:00
No
I bet if she was nominated in the court
She would have been approved by like 56 members of the f****** send it because the Democratic Party
Are you speaking garbage
Probably they managed to pick for you
Only
Who would not immediately confirm and the reasons
Their masculinity
I would act in 880
But they still have to f****** allow the guy because
How dare you say that men could possibly do s*** like that f*** you but unfortunately
I don't think
Certify
What is that when
Entrapment
Defending these positions the way they have
Was there first
I think the reason they got back
This is Victor
Chose
Who would win
Exactly
Call disappear
Recharge Buffet
Like they could just
You know what
F*** you Kavanagh go back to being whatever bulshit you are exactly
The best move for them right now
For them in the Strategic move is washing your hands
Even trying someone else isn't going to play at work like Barrett
But
What they are doing is exactly what
Is happening to what they're all watching happened to Collins and murkowski right now where they're like
Well
What if they don't vote for
Kavanaugh
Cut Vero
Women
Not because
Any other possible reason
Cuz they're women
So we can't trust women to always do the things that we want them to
To do
Even as they watched
Collins IND murkowski be the
Dumbest f****** senators in hits
I don't know what to say
Is they're all dumb as strategic as well as tactical level
When I hate it
Really
I don't really know what
We're done
I guess
For the minute
The sort of
Bernard defense
Weird shoe
Weird
Yeah
Can control minds
Presented enough evidence where I can safely say that she
Controls the minds of anyone who
Is a narrative
Different narrative
F******
The lgbtq p.i. pedophile
That's not part of it
Love Letters to learn
Reply the video of that
Your children
No it's not
This is a story out of the BBC
It was about a classroom
Discussing
Wasn't in America
UK so
Sprint
Is the teacher of the teacher of the class made an assignment where the kids
Right
Love letter from
To the other
It's not if you're a girl write to a girl
If you're a boy
It's a write a love letter to somebody else
Within the context of this story from the perspective of another character in the story
Gave an interview and she's talking about the idea of it like
If you grow up
You're fine just divorced
Be around you
You're going to end up running
People of different identities
Different orientations
If we
Makepeace
Comfortable with
That is children
We won't be weirded out by it later in life
It'll be something to be able to
Empathize with
Going forward
The icing
Nothing wrong with it
Because it's not like
The teacher is
Write a letter but I want to suck
Don't
Yeah it's not that at all
If you really want to take issue
You have to take your issue with all fairy
You have to take issue with heterosexual stories
Being in park like romance jewelry
She was 14
Coba
So desperate to me is
Opus Bumpass
You hear Alex again now every time he
He makes a point of bringing in the P making it worse out of amazed that you make
You can
Absolutely wrong
In one sentence
In all directions
Hey America's just an amazing
Inclusive country
The first thing you said was invalidated by the second thing you said
Weed makes me think so
That the first thing you said wasn't even
True in the first place
Not an inclusive place in it
Hens to f****** be in the people who were trying to make an inclusive flights
Are the 12 ring murdered by your f****** dumb
How dare you how dare you
What did I do
I don't want him kicked off of Facebook
And all of that for all of the horrors that he's done
Being able to say America's an inclusive plan
But why
Have everybody that would make an occlusive
Language
Three falls under free
Free speech like I don't think you should kick somebody off
I just wanted to make sense
Oh I would love I would love for free speech
Advocate Alex being
Sing for saying things like
Lgbtq equals p
And this is why I should be
No it's fine
Education campus
Trigger
Do you know what happened
Christine Ford planted in that memory
What's 20 *
Camp to you you think
Call Larry Nichols office
He haunts me
FEMA
Provisional government
Which is
I thought it was very weird today on the 3rd
Recording it on
Cuz you are you have a show on Thursday
Today
All of us got a text
From the Press
You didn't now lucky you I did everybody almost everybody got a text
From this
Of the
FEMA emergency alert system run by the president
Alex
You have this
Super
Terrible fear of
FEMA camps
Which were Hearing in 2000
He hates me
It's all about
Vog the continuity of government
In order to put people in f****** camp
And then kill him off
I'm not going to wait my family
He had her article on infowars.com today
About
This
Text message to everybody in America
Babies being put out
President
Right now it's a great idea
He's mocking the idea that anyone would be against
The article on Infowars legitimately was
No telling all these dumb Council and knock you with move
All for it
I would generally have the artist this existence is miserable I had the article up on Infowars
Dot-com
Screen I was going to keep it up so I could
Look at it
Yeah but my browser
Yeah Google
No longer a super smart
Close that window
But the entire thing is just this long
Making fun of
Libtard
I got
Who are shocked by and against
The president using
FEMA in order to text all of them at the same
Then
At the end of it
No don't do this don't give me a stinger
Selfie
Don't do it
Alex
But if you want Infowars news on your phone
It's amazing you f****** a****** it's crazy
Juicy in French
Topeka that pivots
But he's got it
Shut up now
The Frog creator
Settle for nothing
Because they just want to tell me what images I can use when it's very used and he said it was very good
I need you to find her operation
Hold on hold on
Hold on
You did not get to do it at pivot
After you say
You think I want to see this guy
He wanted to settle for nothing
He did he did
Literally said he literally said do you think I want to see this guy who just wants me
Me to save
Whoops
I don't want to do that
We need your money to fund this lawsuit for no reason with no steak
This thing and I missed it
I wonder if he misspoke
Like I do Wonder
Cuz you're right
I wonder if he misspoke
Just that all four
No I think he wanted
Settle for nothing
I bet he would just apologize
Yep something like that
Way before the others
The first one was against
Rutgers cernovich use
The cover of his book
Right
Use it in any like I mean the other lawsuit
Against Alex
That was way earlier than those right
There's a little bit earlier and it was literally the other lawsuits
If he'd known that there were going to be eight other laws
Sorry for using pepper the Frog anyways it's just a f****** frog character moving on
It was earlier than these other lawsuit
But it was later than like
Elefante and Hamdi ulukaya
Which word in the middle of
It's sort of like you know what
The f****** entire modern history of Alex Jones
Is jumping from lawsuit making apologies and likes Hazard of not
Having to pee
Like settlement settlement General Lee over libel lawsuit
I on the kindness of
But you survived only at the whim of people don't want to crush him
Yeah like hungry look higher could have owned
Probably
God dammit hungry now you're alright we love you and now you're William B
I still think
I still think that even is an admirable choice
I understand
Because there's no reason to be vindictive about it
Based on
You did make a video apology
Yeah
Here's my view on that
And this is something that I didn't
Really learn
Until
A couple nights ago
Watch she was watching
Latest season of The Walking Dead
The end of it
What is f*** doesn't kill the other f****** guy
After there's been a whole f****** fighting like-for-like
50 people have died but then it's just like the one guy in the other guy that's like I said I'm going to kill you and then he doesn't kill him and his
Like you're going to be an example
The whole time I'm sitting there like
Zombie situations for sure what is Alex Jones but a zombie situations
You just got it look
Look
I get it
I'm all for it we got to Build a Better World
But don't build a better world with this guy we got other guys to be like all look this is the guy
I sincerely sincerely believe that we live in a society that
What is room for
I don't think
Instachat
Terrible play
What about that one
Well look dude
Because I did not want any of that I don't know
Actually I thought it was actually good
Thoughts were as I had watched any of the season
I watched like the last episode
I know I know but her point of view is like
I know this is really good
Claire's
Contain
Something like an Alex G
Force
It's just that it requires
Everyone else
Aware
Unaware
Healthy Society
Can contain Alex
Because people read stuff
Have a good night handsome
In a society that's already
Kind of
Rotting
Or there's there's a cancer within that Society already
Their defenses are going to be
Be there too
To fight
Or two
Mitigate
The damage that
Alex Jones
Do right right now we're living in a
Cancerous
Awful Society
It Alex Jones
Exploiting
The cancers
Yeah
Trump is the cancer
The Avatar of the cancer
Nugenix for sure
Yeah
Proper
Everything going well
Our society could happily flourish
With Alex Jones
Doing his
Crazy fun bowls
And have fun
But unfortunately we live in
No
We don't have the immune system
Fight back
And it sucks
But just
Because we don't have the immune system
Reply back against
Doesn't mean that he's any different
You don't think
We are more susceptible to it and the damage is
Worse because
That doesn't mean you shouldn't be able to do what you
You do it
Some of the counter ice cream
We could handle somebody
Like Alex
That's all
Exactly
If we can handle somebody like Alex
Do you have to take away the clock.
Which Alex Jones
Maybe we take
The Alex Jones to which the extent Alex
And put his f****** head on the Pike and then the other
I want to cut off smell so bad
Hellboy
Novelty menu cocktail
So
I don't know
You wouldn't enjoy our nephew
Famous
What you and Elsa's bald getting married
I would not go
Think you can do better
Okay Paradise
Girl triggered
Triggered
Angry whenever somebody accuses of his
So angry all the time
In that sort
Because that's not what this is about
This is Alex being triggered by
Watch that
Which I would argue
Flashlight
Watching Kavanaugh being accused
Call Chic you so much
That
I want to get very aggressive
Nothing to do with that
Over you
I just don't know how to
Deal with that
In any sense other than
For him to say like
If you're a Democrat and you say anything
I can't believe
For me the only reaction is well if
I can't believe you
Yeah there's no way for us to communicate if you're a medium
Your immediate position
Is
Nothing you say is Meaningful and everything you say is a lot
What do I say to
You know
Right like you you just
Goodbye
Any possibility for communication
Basically
Okay well then goodbye
F*** off
By so many women
How many women a long
Laundry list of women who have falsely falsely accused me of so many like rough
Sleeve for 25 hundred women
Have falsely
Definitely not any of them being correct 100% all of them
I think that I was a lot of like
Legitimately I'm making a motion
You are
Actionable
Against
Agree
Not
Zagg
But actual statement
She's running
A mind control CIA
DARPA funded operation
But yeah
This is
Okay
It's not funny
Stove top
Aesthetic
But you says this towards the end of the
You don't want to go on there and say that Christine
Wazee Ford
Is a CIA mind-control operative
You did she works on
False memories on
Program is connected to that that's helping really is a whole thing
And the brother
And it's like it never ends
Embarrassed
I was assigned to stuff like that
Christian
Isn't it funny how you parody did exactly that clip earlier in the show it's weird isn't it f****** weird
That you were like
Funny how joke can imitate propaganda
It's like a
Bummer that no matter how
Full disclosure
No matter how far you try in Paradis this
It doesn't
Go far enough
No no
Crazy these guys are
The next
This is exactly how crazy we are what am I supposed to
Jokes about the insane clown
To hear that
This world
Like especially now
It wasn't this way years ago
It was fit more restrained
Dishonest
Absolutely I agree
The level of
Lake Observatory
Bulshit
Like
The owner
Unrestrained by decorum
Oh yeah
Unrestrained
Themselves
Right
Is it possible to
Naked joke of like
Well here's what they're going to do
Give a 50% chance
I was very active you making the joke they make it real
Justin speight
Schroeder's propaganda
This is a weird weird
Sing for me somebody who's
Not old enough to have lived through it by like
If you watch the late eras
Between
Carson and then like
You like Carson
Could tell a joke
That was
Devastate
That was like
How could you do that
And no
Jimmy Kimmel tell a joke that is just like oh that's just a
That's just
Sure like that's just
Like the late-night host gig is
Turn from
Parroting to just like reporting
Reporting with
Using of humor
Activity vision is even better
But just like with a little bit of Comedy
Brian stelter
And Johnny Carson just be like
The next thing they want to do is
Remove kids from their parent
I honestly think I'm going to give you a contrarian position
It's exactly what we
Because the start of state of times
Do volatile
An awful
If you had somebody
You was making like
Really
David blows
You don't need that
Zipline
Because
Deserve
What does
I like that I like where this is going
Totes
People like
Jimmy Fallon
You know
Rub Trump's hair and B
Call f***
School
And then James Court
Avenue
But mean nothing
Should be just
Yeah
He's great
James Corden
A couple of great Epic
I do
Love Doctor Who
Row
You could do it
You do it easily
Yeah in this climate of like
Comedians
The various voices that are out
You could do that very
You could set up
They would not make you any
Free money
That's why there aren't those
Plenty of comics who could
Develop that's caving row but they're not allowed anywhere near the shows
Here's what I would say
The internet is allowed everybody
Just make what
You can just
How late night show
If you just rent out a theater
50 bucks
And have some.
Camera equipment
Or if you're on Facebook watch
Are any of those like
You can do it yourself
Is it the soft launch for our Facebook watch
Geisinger
Like Autumn map
Level I don't know if they have
But not to the level of like
All right we got a demagogue
Yeah
I don't think
The time deserves
And I also don't think it would work
Because then that person would
Unilaterally
By all the various propagandist
Right right
Mike cernovich would accuse them of something
Answer the f****** crime they didn't commit
Drinking children's blood
And all of a sudden they get bogged down in a lot of bulshit as I can do with
What you're describing a Zafar show
I'm not I'm saying
Lend itself
I mean even
Early David Letter
Butterly
Early David Letterman
Late David Letterman
I think about this I don't know if this has anything to do with it
Cultural entertainment largely
Liking things
Like I'm not saying that isn't
You know that I've made it clear that I get sucked into these Rabbit Hole Irish people try thing
Have you ever seen Irish people try things
But like there's there are there are things like that
Million
I started to look into it a little bit more
Empire videos
I watched a couple
I don't understand
BuzzFeed
Diculous YouTube
He has videos on it
Are we all just get old at this moment right now
BuzzFeed has
Millions of
Millie workout videos
Crazy
And I'm so I got
Watching
Speakers
I would watch one and it would be like there's one there's one
They have work
These two guys going
Tri-C
At different price
It's called
So the two
Go to
When's really cheap
The middle one soup
Super expensive
Riley
Which one is
The best
It's priced right and that at the end of the day after the supermarket
Fill their cart with the most
Supremacy
A pretty interesting premise
I guess with good editing
It's something
You get to see
Three different restaurant
Which is what all those
Like food TV
TV shows really about Diners Drive-Ins and Dives Guy Fieri right about
These fun restaurants
So you could imagine
Turn yourself in
Right
So you get to
I think you also get
Yourself into
Because who were they but 20-somethings who have a good job
Right ba
Gifted
This position
Because of their
Yeah protect yourself there a little bit
Kind of Bud and then oftentimes it's
Hahaha
Vigo dolls
Videos
What are the guys in it
Seemed to have a really good
Comedic sense
Ability
I enjoy this
I accidentally started
Videos no
I ended up down
Cole of following him
By the way it's Andrew
Gru from the
Steven Andrews
Two guys on
No idea fine I don't know you
Too excitable.
You just described me
You don't have the frosted tips
Frosted tips
So I started
I watched other
Finding myself
3 minutes
Videos about
And I I don't
I didn't join
But I kept watching
And I didn't realize what was going on
It sold the other night
I was sitting there like
I'm to watch one more
And then it was
So disappointed
As I watched
Because there's like
Just
People doing something boring
Commenting
But I want I want
More
Sonic
Next
And I click the next one
And then an hour later
You just repeated that promise
Over and over
And I realized along the way
All of these videos that I've been watching
Over 7 million views each
There are tons of people
I think much like me
Hookah tender
The end
Caught in the cycle without realizing it
Of like
Slightly Charming
I want better
You guys can do better and then the none of them
You can do better I think
I don't know what that mean
I totally feel like I think a lot of
Are craving Escapist
Videos of like
I don't f****** know that's watch these people leave dumplings
It somehow
Like a good jump
And then you're never satisfied
Are you looking
Little bit more
It Never Comes
2 hours later and you've watched a ton of their ship
And I think the people mop
Is that really well
Yeah I don't know if that's
Intentionally a business model
I think it's f****** stupid
Addicted
Candy Crush
Are the game of vacation of
Addiction
Small bit of
Well I'd now that I've reset base level
Keep going for that bass level
And no matter how far you're always chasing the
I'll tell you the Irish people trying stuff
Because at least I actually like
A couple of their fur
Like I watch
Damn High Point from the radicals that I've
That lead dope down
Haha
I've watched
Too many watched
0 of those BuzzFeed videos but I still think that's too many
I've watched too many of those videos just
Only like
Baby
2 or 3
People
Of The Buzz
Empire
Which is why I drink
Little red all over
A personality
As depicted in their V
Meanwhile
Were the Irish people
I would say it
Pretty cool
Have you ever been to Ireland
I want to go so bad.
Ireland is one of the most fascinating groups of people who hate everyone
One you will ever be
Let's do a show credit
Let's go to Ireland
People love
Uncomfortable conversation never been made more uncomfortable by saying hi than in an Irish bar
And that person
Love me
The other Irish bars I've been to
I felt more comfortable
Super Bowl then when the person
Images like
And that was it that was and I was like I love you too I don't I didn't know how to
I'm not positive
But
I do it I do respect that like wipeout
I don't want to say that for it is of hooking
That's not okay
In this next court Alex
A bunch about whether or not he
She wants there too
And I'll let you decide
Where he come
I'm saying is
It's not martial law if the president calls out the military to protect the White House
It's a military protecting us from Global's funded enemies
Better
Of what we're going to do
Polish
But
You understand
Could I'm not backing down to interview people
Let me do nothing
Not that was so
That was crazy
Hey Alex
Isis
Is Jordan from
Chicago
Hello.
Speak
So you just said
Use Force
Oh man the cop should
Fun
If a cop
You know if I were to use Force against you
Then the cop would be
Be justified
But what if I
What if there was a standardized response
Swearinger
Kid
And you're walking away from a cop
How many f****** murders
Is that
Is that okay
Set okay
Alex
Should there be standardized rules
You know you know what I'm starting to think that maybe it only
F****** matters whenever it's on your
You know it's super
Thought about this like
Experienced
Bending over
So far back
In order to
To justify
Cavanaugh's
Discretion
Everett
Tapestry of b*******
Stupid article
Just
Get away from
This guy knock
Getting on this
Court like we've already been
Someone else could probably get into
Neil Gorsuch
It's not some sort of thing like they're going to
Create demonic smears of anybody
No
It's really crazy to have a situation like
For such a loose
Expulsion
Alex's
Defending this
There's a piece of self
When you see things
Laquan McDonald
Or
Other
Is of unarmed
Murder
He doesn't
Create
Fabricated Naruto
He doesn't even talk
You just never covers
F*** off
F*** you
This is this is weird
Laquan McDonald nightmare. This is a punchline
Listening now
Record
But in a world leaders top box
Top Fox News hosts
Congress
But this is like Fight Club
You can shut him down for a reason it's the gas
It's why the system wants infowars.com shut down
What scares them so much
The truth on 60 Minutes
Willington
You might have missed it in there but Alex just broke the first and second rule of
What's that
You talk about
Did the shows basically Fight Club
What
Almost like even in his fictional argument
The sentence he makes an argument he invalidates that argument mean
To bring up the
Jordan
Jordan what's the latest episode if we can
Whatever women aren't allowed to speak
Episode
Demonstrate
Simultaneously
Present
Answer same time why we
Kinda gotta talk about the
You're not going to get this
It's B Razors Edge
That we end up walking
It's awful
To sit here and listen to Alex Jones Davis
Disrespect
Falafel stop
About someone who
You
Can hear her speak
Look at the reality of the situation
Oh yeah
Court week
Very
Clearly is credit
Like I don't
I'm not I wasn't there
I can't say it happened
But there is no part of my body or my being
That thinks
Right
It sucks
To hear Alex create this elaborate
About
Situation
But it is going to talk about the idea.
Vicky has created right yeah that's how I know
Crazy defense
I don't think Trump would even try
We'll see in the day we've already talked about how parody is not
Existence
Pastor like
Call for the bench
But like
This this
I don't see
This level
Complete
Bucked up
High strangeness
80s
Arch
Arch I will say at the end
Respect
Of having to go into the
As much as it is
Payroll check in
I wish we just
Anything from this except for
About the law
You know
80's phone on some level I like learning about that to Bill Cuban kiptyn
It's family I don't know
Not yet
So what
Tell me some s*** about Laura
It actually doesn't want to work at Burning Man
She created
I know I know my love I know
A lot of it is about the like
Symbolic destruction of it
Violent
Destruction of her own artwork
Like shooting it
A ritual
Yeah
It was a parody of money
No s*** it's hard to take that away from me
Begrudge
Having
You should give away a bunch
Which
She does
Riverbend Dental inside Foundation get rid of
Haikyuu
I don't want
Implies that there's a possibility
How do you spell acai
We
Water for you
At least
Thrice
And it's about time that you went to the knowledge right website and click the support that we would love it
Sponsorship come around
I like straight-up I'm buzzed enough right now
I'm going to send an email offering a sponsor
2 or $3,000 per episode
We will continue to say that you are.
If you like blackmail
Oh my God
Imagine
Imagine every duck
It was on that carousel
Imagine wanting not people to
Carousel
Kodak
It's a bad version of the first episode
We got to website dollartree.com
Go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Fun fun on there
Do what I'm going to be at the Improv
Next
Thursday
God I wish I knew what dates work
I want to be the Improv in Schaumburg
What's the date events
B11
Thursday the 11th
Featuring four
Some of the we're probably
Check that out
Episodes Premiere Ryan I'm trying to plug
I'm not doing good at it
Nah
We are subscribed
Leave a review on iTunes
Helps people finder
Please Libra
Review on Facebook
It does something
F****** do I have no idea
Where does really super happy people keep fine
Thank you for being
Absolute
So now I
Doctor
Blasey Ford
Troll work
Don't think about it
Never killed anybody
Has anybody
Alex Jones
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color