Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty beverages
Dan
Earlier today
Got my car
Go to work
But hopefully this one
Hey sorry we didn't have an episode on Monday
Technical issues personnel
Well we recorded it on Saturday
Write following
Existence in revealing that
The Supreme Court is
Nonexistent
On any sort of executive power
We split a bottle of whiskey we may have gotten a little bit
To f*****-up
First
45 minutes out there were technical issues that I just was not keep
Because of
But when I listen to about like the possibility
Quite right
Covered Kavanaugh's livestream Kavanaugh
Confirmation
Glad to hear I got the vote as
Is it work and there was something that just wasn't quite right there was an element that was missing
Answer today what we're going to be
Going over what I believe is the element that was missing of that
Well covering the important points
Alex
Cuz live stream of
Cavanaugh's
I know that's a little bit complicated little convoluted maybe to understand off the top I promise
Things will make sense
As we go along
Annual
That was missing from our original
But it's one of those things that auto show it's kind of difficult
Cover
Like immediate news
Because of just the
The time can
Strafe
The contextualisation
Needs to be done
Pulling
Pieces for luck
If we rush things
Sometimes I think that we miss Elam
Correct
It's hard
And we have
I have nothing but respect for a couple of new donors
Two couple new people who have signed up with the first of all likes thank you so much you are now
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Stella Stella and friend anyone else
Who would like to
DEA Groove return
Angela Bassett
Morris Chestnut
Forest Whitaker
Idiom
Less less fun than Forest Whitaker
I'm a policy wonk also one last breath
We appreciate it oh so very much you are now a technocrat
Natalya brilliant someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a car
I don't want
Thank you again
Thank you very much
You can do so by going to knowledge fight.com quicknet sport the show button
And I would appreciate it
You know what
If you can't support the show
Find the nearest person with disposable income don't even tell them about the show
Just tell them to collect the support the show button
We don't need listeners
Actually
A lot.
I'm going to walk you through
It's going to be
Confusing
Probably
Maybe slightly nonlinear
Make sense
I think
Hopefully we'll see
What world
Do you want what someone else has gotten less it's
Alright now this is why we can't release our drunk episode alright
But we don't want to Monday episode from us that sounds like a whatever episode from him
That and we were talking about Harry isn't it cool to steal someone's very attractive Broad
Wework
Doing primarily is looking at some of the
Between the day that Alex Jones celebrate
On-air on his livestream
The confirmation of Kavanaugh
And
Some of his celebration
From
The 2016
I went back and I tried to
Find the entire video of Alex Jones on election
52 hour livestream
Pure grape
Hours of Alex in 49 hours of his underlings
Spilling in it but I couldn't find
Some of the lake
Really really talks
6.
Because Alex's YouTube channel
So most of the videos that he had uploaded
Disappeared
And a lot of the people who have posted Infowars coverage tonight
Right after Trump gives his victory speech
But that's not when the show
And everyone was celebrating and a lot of the stuff
I've discussed about the idea.
Watching videos of Hillary supporters crying and
Like that is from that
So thankfully I didn't have to re-watch it at that
Necessarily
That stuff towards the end of the night where
No became clear what the game was
But going back
And listening to a lot of that
Nike stuff
I realize that
The missing piece
Steam the parallel
Between these two
Two very major celebrations that Alex has had
Pink Give us
The key that we need
To unlock
What he's really talking about
Dim sum
That's interesting that people who keep those clips would ended at
Alexa
It's like
We're at the end of America
But they forgot
Watch the beginning of
Cruel cruel
Cruel replacement it's far more important
22c the world that we are going to become
Within
10 minutes
Of the world we were ending
The only thing that remains is a video that you can find on Paul Joseph Watson YouTube
Taking down
I don't know why but there is a video about like
Cry-Baby Hillary fan
And so there is a lot of video on there of
You know this video that they were mocking
Instabulul on Election night
With like wind sound effects of interspersed
Pictures of crying baby
And stuff like that
Okay just bring me back some of that
But it's not good for our purpose
It's not the same by Audio then
I'm in the studio
Just apologize quad Cinema
Report
Where is dark here with
Is from the cabin
Confirmation
Stream
Where Alex
This for you
They're almost done
Just like a 20 months ago
The Democrats
Is it the first
The next one we win
Slide with a red wave in 30 days
Election fraud two pizzas we are going to win
Michelle this isn't a political realignment against Realty
You made the comparison for us this is like Alexa
Now one of the things that's really interesting in that clip is the he is making the pre-emptive excuse for the midterm
That if they they're cheating works
Yeah. R r
Phase of this
Triggering our or whatever he wants to call
Now that's interesting
Because I went back
At the beginning of Alex's stream
He didn't think Trump was going to win
Even on Election Day
Didn't think Trump was going to win
Listen to this s***
But I look at how Christians in the West
Ended slavery Friday in sexism and tried to build everybody up
And the Very people we tried to build up
Just roll reversed
When the Christians
Who tried to end all the tyranny
And they reverse it said you're the slave now
You're the subhuman
You're the reason there's problems you're the white male you're the mobile
I just wanted freedom
They say it's over
Heil Hitler
As they destroy the West
Running
On the planet
Cares about people that
I'm not the prey on you but I got up I got to pull back I got to isolate myself and just let you kill yourself okay you want
I'm sorry the Vampires will now have I'm sorry
CC there at the end I'm sorry the vampires because
Preemptively emotionally preparing
The Narrative to beat Clinton is going to win
And at the beginning
I should have prepared you for that and Subway
Go ahead and email me that clip so I can play it during my f******
Myself Christ what is anybody anybody f******
Christian males
Are the ones who wanted to free us
Kill myself they only wanted Freedom where everybody murder suicide a crime
Yeah
They wanted freedom
They work
To you know help women equal
And they got rid of slavery
Wichita
Specifically about minorities and women
That support Hillary Clinton have turned around
And are now trying to they flip the script only
Great Christian men
Spaceship
In society
All the rest of the world is barbarism only white Christian man or really the
The people who are you know they want to go around and
Maybe they want to build things
This is not
Thursday there's no there's no way to be like well actually
Evinrude history
Life is meaningless
Rihanna work
Why
Why are we bothering with these people in that clip like how important these victim
Is to that identity video
Of the white Christian Bale
He have to
Package it within the idea I'd like we try to help you so much and now you turned on us while you do that
I really I really
Ted now
This is what I'm saying I'm not saying why why are we reading
Some people think you know what Trump people think being white is great
Every profile of a trump voter to just be like
Hey you know how wide is these people think it is
Chanel
But
He goes on
Steal from his at
His livestream on the election
Sunday
Within the context again of him believing the Trump isn't going to win
I'm sorry the Vampires will now have I'm sorry
It's what you wanted
I'm sorry you won't get tax cut she won't get prosperity
CNN in NPR
Telling you how you're in your car
In a fantasy
That you're in charge lie about 40 as a woman
We'll try to find Amanda men won't want to be with you because
They're scared
You bought it before the liquid acetone dissolve the fertilizer to grow the elite cross
With you
If you want the villain
You were just a species women being killed
Show this grave marker
For your death
A planet
Will be your Victory as you die full of morphine worshipping
And so it's Contra perceptions reality
That you never exist
Azad's
Analyze
You worship Al-Qaeda you worship Isis she worship burkas
You worship anything destructive of the West
Because the West is such a beautiful goddess
You were
Ashamed of yourself
That's a little silly
Look
Be prioritizing getting with a western man on clothes
And then you'll be so happy and all the men who'll be around will be available for you
Daniel get into serving and then they'll give you an acid
Like for real does he know what Venus
Look I mean I mean it literally means
The genocide of alias
Domino's side
Yoshino morph
So even though even while he's saying like this
Suggest that working with aliens
To get rid of
We're fighting against aliens or maybe all people who aren't white people are aliens
All non-white people are ate I think he believes the globalist are working with aliens
He sees himself as alien
So that word
Might actually be appropriate in the goofiest way
Like maybe we're not from here
Maybe we're not even supposed to be here
Okay maybe we're not
What can I look at a summer home
Let's all get a summer home
Live on Mars
Where else you got
I think that's a great place for white males B
Mall in there keep you safe and warm
Okay we can go and visit every now and again
Pick another possibility
It wouldn't involve space colonies people growing up
A little bit but
Alright alright
It's a rehabilitation Colony you have a sporting group
False
Place
Where they're separated from any place like a
Oh no nevermind so far left your other fashion
No I'm now getting what I that kind of sounds like and I don't think it's a good thing
Alright
It's interesting here
To hear that
The election day
2016 Alex
Was pretty
Emotionally prepared for Trump to lose
And in preparation for that
Doing all of this like
Oh you idiot
You've destroyed the West
Because you women are harpies and
All you blacks that we wrote that's white Christians rose out of slavery
Value Pawn Donna turned on us
How do you not realize that we ended slavery
So Alex is in that place and it's Super Why
Weird as the day goes on clear that Trump is going to win
He changes over the course of it a little bit
Something that I find
Freemelly interesting
Is there a couple of
Direct
Parallel
Linguist in Stylistics
Between the Kavanaugh confirmation
Stream
The election
Here's the first of them
Is from the Kavanaugh
This will be a day long remembered
We've seen the end
Will show us in the end of George Soros
I apologize
That was from 2016 the election
This
Is from
The Kavanaugh
This will be a daddy long leg
We've seen the end of Hillary
Wilson
Upendra
We paid a lot for this
Please don't take the girl
Total human domination biological operation
The difference is a little bit more
It was pretty
Right but I don't think
Fighting back against the rose wanting to
Make your kids trans
Or something like that the last time the Koch brothers gave an interview
See you there we go
I don't know what they're imagining their fighting back again
The real world
Hi women's rights Union
You know there's really Gotta Fight Back Again
Climate change
I mean
You got to fight back against doing anything about climate
For what I make
Like
A decade from now only you and your Rich Pals will be
What is a pre-emptive economic maneuver
Very smart
That is super interesting to me that we here in both cases I am doing his Vader voice
Ain't saying the exact same thing we seen the end of Clinton will soon see the end
That alone is kind of like
Cuz I don't hear him say that he doesn't like the Vader voice a lot of the emperor
You have done what he does that a lot
When is this supposed to be Churchill
I don't think so
Star Wars
That will be long remembered
Maybe it is
For me to think it's
Just kind of blend together
Adjust mix metaphors and character
Similarity another one
This very very specific
I want to salute you all
I drag my ass up
25 years ago
High school graduate
Texas City AutoZone
I decided I'd kick that ass cuz I looked at my enemy and they were a bug-eyed pussies
Wisconsin
Because big jackass Cruise website
So
What do you seems to be offended by
That makes that makes more sense
Big old groups in the bug-eyed knows that's where you go
But uses that
Is the idea that go around and I want to piss all over everybody
What's from the 2016 election stream
Here is him
On the Kavanaugh
The Democrats remember
Hundred years when America was
We were asleep we weren't awake
You weren't intimidated
All you got to do now
We get
Politically
Arms around your neck
Sew-ins again
He seems to think that is the way he expresses
People doing him wrong
Kp.org
Enjoy a lot of people
Straight up you know you could turn it into a sexual pleasure
Documentaries
Is that the fear you're going with Alex Jones
And that's why he's so unhappy with he's got.
And that what
I don't think we
We should be
For me
I think you should vary joyfully if
You see Alex Jones
Asking politely if you would like if you if you would like you to Piana
The resolution of our New Year's resolutions
Hey man I know what's up
Do you want me to pee on you
We're having a good night
Maybe on your leg
With your consent of course
What is it one of the interesting things I
Is to look at state
And look at
What Alex
Who's presenting
To the world as what's going to happen
Various
So here is a clip
From
The 26
16 election
What are you talkin about
You know how
And Hillary immediately conceive
A little bit later in the night
She called Trump
We can feed intro
She didn't give a speech until the morning
Alex
In the in the intervening.
Is convinced that she's not going
Concede
And it's War
So he he comes up with this Theory
The Trump needs to immediately
Come out and give a speech declaring himself the winner
Because possession is flaw
Which doesn't make any sense
But he has this idea that if he can
Get Trump
To give the speech announcing that he's won Hillary can't undo that
Or something like that
I believe
Termite as a trick
Dibs are real at as long as you say your president your president
Feedback
Is going to be like that's going to be
In the Constitution
Alex keeps Rodger Stone to call Steve
Give the speech already like that's very weird
What year was Alex expressing some of his fears about what could happen
If Trump doesn't
Declare himself the winner
Plane will not spin tonight
Axelrod on the Clinton News Network
Malamute
I'd say he is the winner
Have Obama launched a nuclear war tomorrow at by the way
I got a bad feeling I'm not saying that
For a fact
People know I don't play games okay
Better get that to their heads
He only plays games
But you have to give his speech
She's going to have Obama GoNoodle somebody in order to make sure that he doesn't
Or something along those lines
I don't know
I think he
I think it another point he says that she's going to Nuke Russia
Probably
So
Now if you were to Nuke
Somebody that would be
A lot of death
Certainly
Great song title
A lot of death
We make it like a slow jam
Dire Straits
Guitar licks
Get it going I'm into it
Let's do that
End portal
Real negative view of what the globalist are gone
Really weird to hear Alex say something like
On the David Cavanaugh
Supreme Court
Describing his best case scenario
Of what is going to happen now that the Patriots are in charge of every
There is a path
If we take it this God give us free will
That has limited problem
Billions
Remedy
Futures
Space time continuum
Because again I am a psychic and I have said that multiple times
Towards a real victory in the future
And it's a limited but it's like
Chicken
Bullseye
Try to get it for you can't do it
You've got to just decide you wanted spiritually
And I want to demoralize the Enemy by telling the truth right now giving a big secret
Which they don't have next level
Naked
That's why they're so pissed at me and others
In about 95% of
Possible futures
We went
Sahara realizing how to that
And if they do succeed
What would be like
He's nightmare scenario on Election night at Hillary's going to Nuke someone
Make sure Trump doesn't become
Then multiple billions of people dying
Which is describing in more present-day as being
The best
Case scenario for
His movement
Surviving in women
Epic
Fitzwater freshest thing
Sure
We're going to win 95% chance
You know results in the less violent
If you just let us win now we're going to have to
We're going to have to do some of those other 95% Futures where
Here is a way
Yeah it's really like that
If we are to win
It is going to require us
The team who is going to win
To inflict
At least
At least two billion people dying like
What is about a third of the world's population has got to die in his
He doesn't believe in climate change
So he doesn't believe it like that could be a
Extensible argument
Or something he's trying to talk about
So he thinks there's going to be two billion people dead
Just from like we're going to have to kill all the Muslims
I have very little doubt that that
At least a large piece
Of what use Imagining the best-case scenario
Is Betty
Please describe
Which
Profoundly scarier than
His
Very baseless idea that Hillary Clinton was going to have Barack Obama nuke
This is he
Does he have like
After the billions
Lex is so far his stay in Utopia of some sort where everyone has guns
Everyone has their own
Money talk
Slavery is just sort of like it's just an economic agreement that anyone could enter into theirs
Who knows duress isn't a real thing and everybody gave us free will everybody would have their own competing
Currencies that you have to spend
Figure out how to
Transfer among each other
You couldn't
Usually I mean if you're able
Missouri dollars in Illinois
Or if you do they probably be worth less
Excellently are in Missouri
Missouri's economy is not going to be
Backed up
Well that's Preserve
Andro courtware if you
With someone you have your favorite Court
You go and appeal your case in front of they probably have their own Court
It is now
Justice system is
If we end up in like some sort of a libertarian
Competing currencies
Screw up all sorts
The transaction
Everybody's Australia antagonistic towards each other
Billion people
Hooray
The worst
I mean a lot of people are going to die in the Visa vs. MasterCard
In order to figure out who becomes the dominant credit card holder
MC get of army
Doesn't already have a bit of an army tucked away Zone
Like
Incredibly insane
Good scenario involves that much.
Is that lead me to believe
I think you probably got it
Perfect that's almost a threat
Exactly four goals a lot like a threat
Navigate to another like real direct similarity but
Queen of the Kavanaugh
Swearing-in vote day
16 election
Alex brings up
About the people are against
Suicide
Very
Very similar
Here is him talking about
The stuff on
See the Kavanaugh
Vote day
Which confirms and defense of free speech
Defensive new process defense of
Party operatives
Try to block the nomination of a good man the Supreme Court
Really here is a referendum on the intimidation
George Soros
Group
Where they kill gays and enslave women in
Forcibly abort little girls and kill little baby girls
You've got these women out here
That believe in there fighting
Your father brother their son
Since we're all one species
Some women are good some are good
So he invalidates criticism by
Start of everybody's on everybody
Which is all great
The standard stuff
That's really specific there is the idea that these women
Are just mad at her dad
It's
Show us a fan of him immediately invalidated
What he saying in the middle of it like these women angry like
Yeah because you just said
With absolute disdain
You just said just these women as though you're like
Why are these
I mean I have to call them people I spoke
Ensure
Bad women
You know the good women are the ones who do whatever I tell them to lock her up
These women like us they must be mad at their dads
I can't possibly be I'm an ass
Kind of rhetoric
He's expressing that these women are just mad at their dads
Is a pentagon
To take cars around the time of
The election
Also some women who were pretty mad
Things to say about the Democrat
Mike down
Because
You will not believe how this
And the Democrats are running around slumming at the mouth
SSS
Car culture
Look up don't have parents I feel sorry for their money
18-wheelers is Daddy's come over on
I-35
David they saved
Donald Trump elected president
136 Central
236 East
We're not hearing
They'll probably announce
Wasn't there.
Christian David
All I know is we're going to continue on
We're going to fight the New World Order
Because we believe in prosperity
We don't want to rape you in your family
That's why we got free shipping running before the
Watch Big Discount 40% off a horse Florida
Oh my God
Because we all want to rape your kids
You don't Sephora charges for shipping ohmygod
That was so wild
To me like that.
No add pivot can ever touch that
That's why we have free shipping
There's only one reason maybe there's another reason the use of those words like him
If you could just you could disconnect
Basalt
You could be like we're going to keep fighting because we know that they
Want to rape your family and we're not into that
By the way by the way
Completely unrelated we have free shipping
That's why it's 20% off
On our way
Jesus
Democrats who are protesting against Trump
Have Dad
They don't have it they don't have parents and it's so sad they're like Duck
Alright man
It's it's a good way to sort of
Empathy dehumanize
Your Pony
People who believe other things than you
Really
The only reason you're mad is because you're
You don't have Tara
Steal your right
So here is another
Almost
During the Kavanaugh scream and the elections
This one here is from the cabin
Know that we could rule the planet
If we only submitted
We built
Surveillance system bhagat
So he can have more power if you was down with
Here's what he said on the election
I can't bring myself to see if I did I'd be
20 times more powerful
I mean it's sort of like a preoccupation that he has
See very clearly
Good
I must be good because I'd be more successful if I was bad
Which suggests
Success is because I am
As opposed to it don't have done bad things along the way
In spite of you being good
You are still successful even though
Which considered a multi-level marketing scheme
Is literally feeding on people
Absolutely literal 12
Forgetting people tricked on auto-ship
Or something like that
Or trying to convince people that they need your iodine in order to be healthy
I'd like just trying to cook convince people that they're somehow deficient because of what they quote globalist have done
In order for you to monetize their response to those ideas
Is the definition of feeding off people that's all he does
This is like earlier he said he doesn't play games he plays so many games
The gamesmen
He's a parasite
He is a
F****** parasite
Sucking the life out of the
Or something to that
So
Able to find the
Before videos of
The the display of Cruelty
It goes on
At the end of the 20
Election
I'm glad that
You know to not necessarily watch that all over again
But
I will say that there's a couple
Very Stark parallels that relate to that
In terms of
Mice
Barnes firm conviction
Is that
Alex Jones
On Election night
Made
Everyone involved
Maybe they went out of their way in order to victimize the
People on the other side
People who are crying
Show videos of them laughed at them
Just made
Fort out of the idea of like haha look at these losers
Aren't we great we're not them
Their loser
And you don't have to sort of buildup IS idea that those
You know I don't notice
20 year old
22 year old girls
Women who work
We're somehow oppressing
But be that as it may
That was the demonstration
On
It was what the show was largely about outside of
Alex getting a little bit weird and saying but
Stupid b*******
The visual That Remains
As evidenced by the next Paul Joseph Watson putting out that compilation
Of people crying and he put his ass out
Exonerate
What they wanted to drive home is like look at these these stupid loser
Crying because
When the Cavanaugh Street
Alex is trying desperately
To recreate that
So he kept going out to Millie Weaver on the street trying to get video
Of her finding people crying
So he kept trying to make it happen
The only way he was able to 6
Get that feeling back at all
Was by having Darren
Mcbreen
Come into the studio his employees
Video producer Darren
Brain
So the two of them
Could get super cruel
About the idea that
Cavanaugh going on
Supreme Court was going to cause liberal
To cry
Pontificate all day but
Coldwell on Greg Harwell
All the s*** they've done. Us and finally we're winning
What's better than the confirmation
Is going to be the aftermath
List all the butt hurt and seeing the crying and ended the the total liberal meltdown
I'm going to just
Bask in the liberal tears
Stream of the election night 2016
We get to see the triggering now I mean they're they're going to have them in those jeans today.
Or something right
Too bad acting up it
So there's a young lady to get a word in edgewise
Well Joe Biggs
David
Stephen trying to say something awful and they wouldn't let her
God
Yep wonder where she is now
Probably
Interesting
Wild almost like that
Kind of what it's about you know if these guys were soldiers
Play somebody is
War crimes in space
Pretty much all my God
A hundred percent sure they would as long as
Long as we get to see them
Because it's funny
Feel like it
Another human being
I mean
It is it is pretty f***** up but it is what they are all about
Here if I'm election 26
Trending things on Twitter right now
United States of anxiety
America is over party
America has now been Vindicated
The American people have now been heard
We have taken over everything
Using social medias we have completely
Transform the narrative
For so many years
What to do what to think
What's a way to do respect people
Bowie told to do
What was the oppression
And if I start to make other people feel bad
Do not suggest that maybe I'm the one who's doing something wrong I can't allow myself to think that for even a second
What is there
Faking feeling bad in order to make me feel bad they're victimizing me with their feelings
Hang them to act like they feel bad real enemy is
Monster
Literal monster
So Joe Biggs is mocking the idea that people are tweeting about anxiety which
I imagine as we've discussed
Ad nauseam
Obviously felt like
Ability
Vindicated
Here
Judge is already calling it for Trump and also I just tweeted out pictures from inside
Hillary Clinton's our celebration area
Hit the glass ceiling
Play sad
Is it
Is a small version of what I've been talkin
Things that I remember is not just
Joe Biggs David Knight
And around blasting it pictures
These people crying
He was in the studio later
But that's exactly what was going on
You see that and that's a dark picture
That's a dark picture of Anubis operate
He just said
She was hitting the literal glass ceiling
He did say that
So that means knows that the glass ceiling does exist
And he
Enjoys and appreciates that it does
Whatever the building
So you was using it as sort of a
Rephrase
To be a dick
That's pretty awful
So later in the night
Part that I can't find the video of
They sit around and watch the footage of people at Hillary rally
Crying
Bunch of white dudes and whoever that lady is
Ben McAdoo
I wrongly of said the Jakari Jackson was
Forgotten that
I think it's all white people I don't see
Single
It came time
A the Kavanaugh scream
Alex like I said was going out to Millie Weaver trying to
Her to have footage
Trying to get protesters that they can do this exact same thing
Talk about haha look at all you triggered liberal
Hahaha
It didn't happen
There were people crying
There were people out with
That's what Millie Weaver was
Capturing
Xvideo
And Alex wasn't getting what he wanted out of it
I want to see some of those videos
Reaction to Trump's inauguration for election night
The trailer for
Rodger stone is really good who shows the lepus on?
This is why
The left hates
Infowars
Show them
So
Because he couldn't get what he needed during the Kavanaugh stream that he was putting on
But that was the presentation he wanted
He needed to hearken back to
The original
Where he was super cruel
What again
That's
I don't want to wind an
Winning is boring I want to
Steal them
Under my boots
Yeah I want to feel them I want them to
It's almost like I want them to know what it is I'm about to do to them
Before I can do it
Almost
I want them to
Feel the pain of what
Going to get off
It does seem that way also considering that Alex's dream during the Kavanaugh vote
There's not really any conversation about like what this means for the court
Or anything like that outside of like haha
And Alex drawing a lighthouse
Please paper and trying to shoot
His own camera with the cork
Champagne bottle
Twice
Except for him desperately trying to get this footage from Millie or wherever he can get it from
He tries to get it from
Let's go back to election night let's get that
And then later in the show
Save
Do this
Play my video
Play your video it went they got roaring a roaring last at the crowd
Prediction
The 5-minute video of protesters crying
Millie Weaver on Ganda computer 12
5 minutes ago
They believe that they have a five-minute video that mailing his shot of protesters crying which they don't have
They end up playing a video where it's Millie Weaver Wunderground a protest
I just being a bunch
People locked
A bunch of people changing
Bunch people with signs
No one crying
No one is doing what they need them to do in order to
Exercise this cruel spirit that lives Within
They don't they don't really get what they want but they pretend it's there anyway
Your Defiance isn't making this fun for us
Stop.
There is there is a little bit
You can you can speak like Alex ends up ending his dream
The cab
He gives a really long to toast about house
This champagne is 17
Penny goes off air
Realizes that he didn't do a good enough job
He needs to be a little angrier
3 dozen
And then slams down the glass of
On the table breaking
Glass
And stares into
To the camera
After he breaks the glass
So is that feeling of he's not getting what he needs out of it
Going
He does like
2 hours
And that that Kavanaugh stream
He's not getting what
Which is this visual did he got on Election night
Of people crying
People victimized by
Hughes
Quote unquote
Except
That is what he did
He needs women
Tears he needs minorities
Feeling scared
Or else
What's the point of this operation anymore
Person on my way home so I can get hard
Why are you making this suck
I mean
Calls back
To what he was talking about earlier
Necklet from the 20s
Something about the idea of
Christian
Got you out of slavery power with you guys have turned on us
That is why
He feels
So desperate in order to
Get those tears
That's why he's so desperate
To get that victimization from them
Because he feels that they've wronged him
Treated like he
He feels that they have wronged
His whiteness and his maleness by asking for equality
And that's really really hard to
Look at
Because
First of all it
It's so
It's so dumb
Clearly his Narrative of
Look white people raise you up we brought you out of this whole thing
And I mean sure we ended I mean yeah sure we enjoy making you feel miserable and
Flushing you under our boots
Because we love raising you up so much but you have to be raised up to exactly where I want you to
If you're anywhere else
I'm going to be swinging
And if you get
You know
Out of your station or whatever you know
The terms that would have been used for
I don't care.
Iraq
And then you won't have to cry and make me feel bad
It's your fault
I'm a crazy
From your country and sold you into slavery
You are the one thing in a Libertarian world you were the one who said hi
You should never have done that
Now you guys know what we would have done if you guys came to our country
We would have separated from you if you from your family's we're not getting sold into slavery
We learn from your mistakes
Insane high in offering us food
If it sucks but this one's from the 2016 election
Although I probably the biggest
I really do I think what they tried to do is essential
I don't know if it was a hundred percent
But that was what they ended up doing
I think that was where their instinct
Took them and they loved it
I think that that cruelty displayed they had of laughing people crying
Because they feared for their safety
I think that was sort of an improvisational
And then because it was so good
And they made so much hay out of it
Quote unquote
Viral pieces out of it like Paul Watson
Today
They tried to do that again
The pageant that they tried to put on
That was the entire point
So
I don't want to undersell then
The big piece
But Alex
Is a couple more really f***** up thing
But I don't I didn't remember
From the 2016 Street
But I think I might have
Subconscious
But I don't remember it like that
That is one the next one
Listen to the language he uses here listen to these
Syntac
Because you follow pronoun reference
You're going to hear something
Supremely f*****
The evil has been showed how they hate you. They want to bankrupt you how they think you're dumb how they think you're scum
Here's the problem thought you were something
And now an Abomination you use that power to turn us into your slaves where's the news jackass
Hillary slaves and the ruling classes slaves
Those are those are you blow all the same damn thing
I understand you hate strength
Because you're ugly
So
Forbear
Gave you the right to vote
And now you're using that against us
I'll talk to you about vote
Prosecco
Originally only Wyoming want to hear 3/5 of what you have to say
Originally only white males in this country that constituted 6% of the population
Hypothetical
It wasn't
Except the last date they waved
Boulevard
A good eight years after the country was founded
In 1870 the 15th amendment was passed laws to prevent voting
On the basis
Color or previous condition of servitude
Naturally most southern states immediately put into place tons of restrictions message
Disenfranchised the New Black voters
Fun fact
The really even though there was a constitutional amendment saying otherwise
Practice still it was mostly just able to
In 1887
Native Americans were granted citizenship
If that's the ability to vote
On the condition that they break their association with their tribe
You got a
You got to get out of that tribe entire Heritage walk away from your past
And everything that connects you to your ancestors
Your lineage all of that stuff
Your culture everything just get rid of it you can vote you can vote if you want to act White
I would consider that not being able to vote
Demanding a massive sacrifice of people
For the
Privilege of voting
37 years later the US government finally just a alright fine you don't have to leave your tribe
In 1920 The Nineteenth Amendment gave women the right to vote but let's not pretend for a second they were given that right delete
Nor the passage of this amendment
All was well
Disenfranchising forces that were used against non-white
We're now being applied to help diminish the voting power of non-white women
Still in play
17 residents of Washington
SeaWorld allowed to vote in general elections until 1960
Residents of Guam the Virgin Islands Northern Mariana Islands Puerto Rico
Vote in general election
America
Samoa
So they're not there
Also fun little fact is that
The right to own property
The lingering effect of the Chinese Exclusion Act
Can't imagine they were allowed to vote while they weren't allowed to own s***
Hey if you if you want to own s*** you got to vote
Abusing the power that we gave you
Whatever it is
Is that your forbearers giving you the right to
Because some of this stuff is shocking
You know like
First of all for those like
Us
People US citizens in like Frederico Guam
The Washington DC was the last generation
That's like Alex do 10 years before he was born
1920 with the 19th Amendment
Not your forebears at your grandpa
He says your forebears he's talkin about the founding of this country
He's talking about he's shaming White
Listen to this again
The evil has been showed how they hate you. They went bankrupt you're dumb how they think you're scum
Here's the problem thought you were something
And now an Abomination you use that power to turn us into your slaves will hear the news jackass
He's talking to white people who don't fall into his
Plan
Don't fall into his program
Talking about the people who got the right to vote
Later
I don't think
That
To use this is like a general like
Are Fairborn our forebears gave all of you the right
It's about instead he is saying
Are Fairborn our forebears
Why can't I say that
Our ancestors
You
White men
The right to vote
Have used that
To become
Raiders
You race traitors
You were given the right to vote you weren't you weren't subjugation of the king anymore
And then you turned that and used it to remove white peoples headphones
Post
Well that's the most likely
I want the right to vote over the course of history
Which is first of all time
Xbox 4
And were beaten and killed
In the process
Get those bright
Right
I need Mike literally think that everybody was allowed to vote
He might
He does believe in a lure
But if you go that ain't saying is
So let's say
You blacks and women
You were given the right to vote
And how dare you
Vote in ways that are in your best
So even that doesn't
Well because if that is
Shockingly white supremacy
Supremacist it's a non-zero-sum game
Zero Sum game
If you if you are if you vote for what's in your best interest
Truly that mean that you're not voting for what's in my best
And if your voting against
Pinterest then you're abusing me with the right I gave you
You should be voting in my best interest as a as a an active
Great
In order to make sure that I continue giving you good things
It all it all doesn't make sense
Like from
Sensible
You look at it through the prism of
Rambling
Bigot
This next clip is from the Kavanaugh
Stream
It's one of the other thing
The entire
16 election
He has to present this idea that the left is
Out of control and they're rioting
This is a narrative that he needs
For very specific
Civic reason which
Wolfie in the clip
Right after
B place of safety
He's making all of it up
Here we are just
25 minutes ago they confirm Kavanaugh and Alaska
We have live feeds on infowars.com
Cuz you just insane
This is
Total
SodaStream that he's playing from infowars.com in Millie and all them out on the street
Show liberals
Unless people standing with signs and chanting
Or too freely congregate or any of those things come out
Cuz you lose
I think I hope
God I hope not in the Supreme Court
Alex
People on the right are very desperately
Have been for a long time
The idea of all the liberal protest
Are completely out of
Control
Recently wanted Trump rallies he was talking about how he left
And Democrats
To become ungovernable
It's the rule of the mob and all day
This is that language coming in
Its final form
Alex is the Alex is one of the first
People who was
Really going out there and pushing it real hard
Has been
For a very long time
I have the function of it
Is 2
Now
Try to delegitimize
An entire
Side of the debate
And it's working
There is no other side there's only good meal.
Sure
Sure you mean there's another side what you think you have a good point
Evil doesn't have good points
Good only has good points
I mean sure they're ripe
That's that dab dab
I don't want to hear that that makes white people feel bad
Evil things
Tell me why
Suck
This is going to be dangerous
And hopefully
It's already too far
The president of the United States going to
Some weird
Unnecessary cult-of-personality rally
And
Delegitimize
Entire opposition party at
Ungovernable
You have now entered into
Like
This is
This is what history warns us about
Don't know it
Telling me tap for MS
Open people do this
Bad things happen that doesn't sound right
You are the same posts along the way and that's all I'm saying
Is that
Hitler did give you the right to vote
Wait no he didn't did he
I'm not sure no
Play my history
The reason that this rhetoric is really important and the reason that Alex
Reddit
Send the world the first or the only
But he was one of the very strong voices
Is there any leads
And in this clip
From
His head was feeling
On the night of the 2016 election
We're here where that rhetoric is intended to go
And we'll go on stopping them forever
Because
Big jackass Cruise
They take some nice man or woman who just a hard-working good person and they think we're webs because
We don't want to break their neck
And so they attack us and pestilence into things until
We finally stand up against some of the
They they fight us we decide to break their legs
Python movie
Don't keep saying I'm the night to Gosney
Continue coming
You realize that
You just can't give these people
Court
Won't be happy
Metaphysically
Stomp
So
We understand you can't tell exist with us
Because we're altruistic
What's wrong
We don't want to hurt you
You want to hurt people like a little Tasmanian Devil piranha
And show
We're just going to stop here at it
And kiss you on the deck
And it's no hard feelings
But it has to be done
You can go around and find Radical Muslims you can find abortions all day you can
You can be a weapon lie about what you really did
But we're going to man up to
And the final equation
You belong the ashibah ministry
No one wants to be around you or with
No pleasure
But you tried the better
You may have shot Humanity in the chest
Willie Nelson
What was Merle Haggard
Was Johnny Cash
You'll never get the best
Supremely ugly
Do you know what that reminds
And in the Sandman
There is
Storyline
Where
This woman goes
Accidentally goes to
Convention
For serial killers
And all the serial killers
Irr living under this
Delusion that they are there the hunters there
Inhumanity stronger
They're the good guys
They're there for a reason
And at the end of it
Morpheus shows up
And he gives
The greatest curse
In history
Which is he just shows them he just
Shows them who they really are
Like they see themselves
As they really are
And
Everyone like
That is what
Alex
Like I'm waiting for Republicans to outlaw
Like what Alex
Actually do it
Like all of the things that you just described
That they are
You hate us cuz we are altruistic
All of this stuff is like
Coexist
Weakness for altruistic
Exactly
Like please like if he if he was forced by some Twilight
Himself
Like that's that's the only way to truly punished Alex on the road to
Because what are you staying in there is all this like
You keep saying
And the only examples
Can come up with are you fund radical Islam and you fund abortions
Abortion thing I don't even give a s*** about like that
You know Alex
I know I know where you are on that
What is radical and what is not
He's afraid of every single Muslim that exist
Covid-19 you support Muslims and you
Support women's right to get Healthcare
That
What pissing on you is
You can't coexist with that's what requires you to
Stop someone's skull
That makes perfect sense to me
Like
I don't even know how to put it into words but it's one of the most pathetic tragic
Things that come out of his mouth
Specifically you have this idea of like
Talking about
Actual rose
Look when it's just people having rights fathers
Rhetoric
So
Uncomfortable
Because I I
I don't know how to deal with
The
Truth of it
Because the truth of what he
You saying is this
No matter how hard
No matter how hard we try and
Stomp on these
Whether we were move their arms and legs
They will keep,
So the only way to stop them from coming
Is 2 killed
That's how we end up with it
Exactly
How do you defeat
Nothing
Like what what if we what do you do
Like how do we do that like a Beyond
Metaphorical mirror that shows them for who they really are
Like how do we stop
Because look we had a good run
Tons of liberal policies
F****** keep coming
I think in the aftermath of World War II was
Denazification efforts
In the same way that after
Apartheid
There was a Reconciliation committee
I don't know you need something fairly
In terms of
Levels of understanding
And something that would be very uncomfortable for everyone to go through
But it probably would be the only way
To do it without
Without
You know is
This career option which is
Is people actually hurting me
Yeah I mean
8834 all voted for all of the things that I say like
When it when it comes down to
The people who most embody the things that I hate
Are my family
You know like I don't want
I don't want them because I'm not on their team
You know like that's gone
How do we how do we
Cuz changing their mind sure didn't work
Or doesn't work or isn't working
No communication
Weird
Where ungovernable
Demons
We're evil
For doing all of this stuff
We're slandering a good man Dan where we're tearing him down
How can you trust
People who want witches dance
How can you communicate how can you talk to these people
Saying it to them
So what are we f****** do
How do we do how do we do it
I'm not certain people who have their minds
Made up about the top or under the sway of very powerful propaganda
Would be able to get outside of it without
Some moment
That really weather
Some sort of metaphysical mirror
Able to see the real
Some sort of world event
Realize
Yeah that's really what I was apart of
I thought it was something
Because there's a very small fraction of the people who
Are on the right
Who actually
Support
Noxious
Mentality
I have fallen under the sway of
The illusion of populism
The idea of what they're going along with
There is
Something that would open their eyes I don't know what it would be
Not just one story
Multiples of children
Children under the age of
Shouldn't that have been a Flashpoint
Was saved by Kevin Automotive
In any situation the only reason my family got out of
Was because they killed a kid
Right
And you would think that a Nazi rally where a guy murders a woman that would be a Flashpoint
Nope
If the inertia of this movement
Continues along this line of
Cruelty and it's only accelerated it's only getting stronger
They're not losing people
You know people aren't Jumping Ship aside from a couple a****** columnist
You don't like
Reaction
That's going to break that inertia is only going to become stronger
There is only going to need to be stronger
What's going to stop this
Is not going to be
Be good for anybody
I mean what's what's going to stop that. Well obviously the way they were going what's going to stop this is climate change
Radical displays of love
Caring and
Possibly
He could have
The very strong
Ensure
Yeah I see what you're saying
Maybe maybe I'm idealistic
Maybe I don't know but I also think that you know
Look at the history of
Being attempted
Generally speaking it's not so much
How much do radical empathy in Lovitz
Expressing radical
Kicked out of them
The Jesus
We're talking about somebody's going to have to
F****** take one in the chin for us
Like that kind of
Situation
Well on the right imagine that the second coming is around the corner so maybe something like
Some artificial version of the second-coming could fix things
I need to steam
You really are and I don't know
What can
Yeah but I think that's one of the problems
For us fixing everything is
Something that we do
Touchdown a little bit
Over the course of these
That we do
Alex Jones
People like him
Especially
Propaganda
They speak
Whether it's a
Intentionally difficult to figure out but I feel like it is
They sneaked
To get rid of the Avenues by which
People can have that waking up
Try and limit access to outside world information
Like the internet that could disprove them
News Network
One of the Prime
Focuses of people who are
Play
Discredit the idea that
Anything in the media being a cure
Tucker Carlson
And Dulce
Trumpets f****** true don't worry about it
Those things really
Limit the ability of people to save
Give themselves
And it also hurts ability to view to talk anybody
Use primary sources
Chinese people
On property
Did a lot of State
Oh hey
You can bring those things
I believe that
It's just it's just believe
So I don't know I don't know
All I'm going for
Is I want you and I
Big enough
Where
We get invited
One of those
Haha because here's my dream Center
Alright I don't want to do it
You like my bow ties
I love you
Just wanted to bring you here so I can
Insult your shity beard all I want
To go on Fox News
To do is just
Damn
And
I just want to say this
You're a giant piece of s***
Thank you for having me on I'm going to get out of here
I'm going to get out of here
Nod
Booyah
I just want that moment I want one mocha Carlton cries what I'm saying
Video camera
I need a live show
Some friends
I'm sure, I have to really stretch it out
Control for a minute
Control for a minute then
Well maybe you'll be able to overcome their delay and get a message to go fuc yourself
Afterworlds
I have to say I don't think that would be the flashpoint
There is some sort of
Flashpoint possible
Do you think about
You know that would be the
Real world version
The metaphorical mirror
Or something like that
What you would think
Climate change deniers
All of the hurricane getting hit with another hurricane right now
12 years left
Those alarmist of always buffet in Superchick
100 otherwise
I just want to try and get carbon taxes going
Is it not over it finally comes home and
F****** swabs of the coastline are just gone
I think that's so much as
Can be like
I think even though
Weather weapons
Canada
There's always
Exactly what I hoped to achieve with this episode
I noticed
Those Stark parallels but
Between
The Kavanagh stream and the election
Stream
Hangout
I don't know
Whether it's worthwhile or not
There was that cruelty in the Kavanaugh stream
Did I really felt it was important
Time for us to discuss even if
We didn't go over the entire screen
Trista
There wasn't all that much outside of the cruelty that was worthwhile
Alex just Rambles about a drawing of a lighthouse that he made for about 5
Define but
The things I do
The parallel
That you have made and I think
The one thing about it though
Strangely hopeful
What the parallel that you've made
On Election night
We are
Crying we are all
Watching the Doom of America
Cavanaugh's inaugurated on Kavanaugh's confirmation
There was no crime
There is none of that
Everyone
Was ready
Everyone was raising their fists up everybody whip
Staying
Not this time we're not crying mournful situation
This is a fight
The would-be victims of Alex's propaganda patch
Put on
Lady Vols
And we're getting more Act
Where is the glimpse of Alex as a propaganda Outlet
Head not evolve
He was trying to do the exact same thing
That is slightly optimistic Democratic National Committee
Every
Even now people are like I don't know if we should run Warren
She's too angry
She's too shrill for the Democratic voters
This is to say that times are ugly ahead
Let's do let's do Clinton in 2020
What do building in there
I don't know
To sum up other than to say I mean everybody knows where we stand on
Yep
RIT website knowledge where else could you find a trailer where at
What about another social media like
Smaller social media
What if you went to iTunes and
Very nice that would be great any of those things would be great
On Kavanaugh
Call Kevin Alden.
And we saw Alex very similar
Between those two days
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color