Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Beverages and talk little bit by Alex Jones
Yes sir
How's it going
Car accident
Quite a while
Is always the case whenever I play
My house I know you're so you're so into building your house
And absolutely not in
Building
I'm not really so much maybe it is
I'm not so into a lot of the you like
The quest stuff of the kind of boring ultimately leads
Do you like the end of
You do X Y and Z test
That story's done
Where is the Biltmore House
Keep tweaking things
I don't know
Let's say I'm playing the game wrong if you want
Do you know who is building our house special thank you
Start things off by
A little bit we appreciate it
Kyle you are now a technocrat
Get Mom and tell her you're brilliant someone sodomites Italy
I don't want
Thank you so much guile appreciate it very much
With the team
Thank you very much
You coming around the corner
And because we get to keep the
Who's just joined up with
We thank you so much Eric you are now Apollo
I'm a policy wonk thank you Eric
Appreciate
All of you oh so very much go to our website
We would appreciate it very much and people are coming on board
We are
Do I have to announce that we are very close to reaching our goal
Another documentary
On what documentary we're going to break down
It looks like it's going to be the Obama
Ono
I want to do that and I'll say one of the reasons why is that there are
Such good resources online that already debunked
So for me it would be nearly as much digging I could use
Use those resources
And it wouldn't be as much of an exercise of should I found
Right on satisfy sources don't have anybody screaming and making
Dick jokes in the back
Is police
State for the rise of
FEMA
The name of it or was there police 8133
First was actually police state 2000
I don't know what the subtitle that one was
3 is total enslavement
Total enslavement
Documentary
That I think might be fun to do
It's called strategic relocation
All about like bugging out
Bunker in the middle of nowhere having a strategy for relocation at work
A lot of fun problem
Educate us a lot
Just a really long interview with Joel skousen
One of Alex's
Yeah it's so
It would be unsatisfying on that level but I think
Hot Topic
It would be maybe more interesting than a lot of the other stuff that kind of overlaps the stuff we talked about all the time
Be able to do in about
His uncle
Cleon W Cleon skousen
Number of books that are really
Influential in the world
John Birch Society Robert Barron in the 1910s you might as well like the naked tap
The naked communist
Books that are really really inspiration
Channel 4 Alex
His world
A little bit
It might be that I'm kind of like
I think
Are worth it and I don't want to do f****** loose change Alex didn't even direct that
Is produced
I don't want to do like 911 roads
The Tyranny because I'd we're just going to
I don't want to talk about 9/11
I don't
It is
It's been long enough where we can make eight hours of 9/11 jokes
That I have I just
I think a monochromatic
Episode
Documentary
Long
I don't know how fun that's going to be
I think that there's going to be a little bit of like I love steak I don't want that much
Okay alright
Alright that's
I don't know that's just the feeling I have
But voting is open on go home and tell your mother you're brilliant on Facebook
And so if you want to check that out
Get your votes
You can do it
Is we are back in the past
Yeah I feel like a what happened to us
The beginning of the week is one of the difficulties
Please of
Present
And that is the Torso immediate
Much worse
Because the things that affect on
And the things that
Being a real s*** head about RX
Abusive
To our present
In our future
People we care about
Answer
It's hard to take an emotional distance
I think that makes
I'm so it's good to be back in the past
I'm very excited about this today will be going over March 11th
I cannot
Tell you how crazy it is that every f****** time I sit down
Hey listen to a 2009 episode
I like
Alright I know what's going to happen I listen to the last episode is going to be talking about birds
Blue again
Everytime I f****** surprise
I don't know what's going to happen one day he might be pretending he's going to release the Obama Deception
This is no exception
I was
Entirely off guard
By what ends up happening on the March 11th and 12th episode
And here is an out-of-context drop
You sound credible
Yep
It's W shoe on head that you very much
Call Eric Alafaya
You sound credible but we are going to have to look at the shoe on head
Please don't take offense to this Wednesday
I've been burned by a people silly name
Frankly I wasn't real
Today
We going to drop
Police state five back in the habit on feet
Very interesting turn of events
Today
March 11th
Linear
That's how we do things
Interesting
Alex actually starts the show
By talking about
There's something overnight
Before this
It's very unlike
Start the show actually talk about
World
Firearms
Serotonin reuptake inhibitors
Also not the news
Actors are going to try and take our guns away and that's something
That chimpanzees
Every Which Way but that's alright
Are monkeys
Serotonin reuptake inhibitors
Because
Hugh things immediately after talking about a chimpanzee attacking somebody
Ninety-nine percent of the time chimpanzees attack
People
That's not what he's saying he's talking about shooting
Pictures of it like every chimpanzee when I get to like 8
Put on Prozac
Prozac
Mass shooting in Alabama last night
16 in Germany
We can
And
And the media advertising
Is a school
Dreamworld state
I really don't think that's
That's unfair to
You know we talked about it all the time marginalization and other ring of people who try and get that help with
Emotional distress
Mental health issues is just so ugly to look at
Hate to see that sort of rhetoric coming out of a ding dong like Alex
But
You know
Where we have here is Alex jumping
Leisure these people
We're on
SSRI drugs
And then even in that declaration
Qualifying it to say I bet they
Maybe saw psychologist rich
I mean that's the safest pet in the world
Is it someone who ends up going on a violent Street probably had some sort of an issue they made of
Help for unsuccessfully
Can help
Right
Even a lot of people who don't get the help they need
Make effort
At certain points
If you have somebody who commits a violent crime like that
Almost passed some sort of
Interaction with mental health services
The night doesn't
Mean that Mental Health Services in anyway
Cuz them
We just want to
Many
Incredibly shotty logical leap City make
It's going to be a
It's going to be a mess
Pretty sure if I remember correctly
Correlation
Causation
And this
Hey I know this
I've read the math and I'm 99% correct all the time all the time
Most of these Mass shooters
Have eaten
Hold on to that level of Lake Zurich of deductive reasoning
Because it's going to come in real Handy episode
That's sort of real shotty attempted a syllogism
Is going to come into play
Did this sort of rhetoric is especially dangerous because Alex is talking about how these people are mentally ill
And they're you know they're all wacky
You know that's
A newbie bad enough he was just trying to other them or create some sort of
Societal Shame about Mental Health on its own
But the reason
Even worse is he says things like this
And they are moving
Is a mix of good hard-working
Mothers also a lot of spoiled rotten
We should all have firearms
I'm going to defend myself by my forefathers
Numbers up
Insurance
I don't know car wrecks
Last time I went to the world
Here's the problem with this sort of rhetoric
Drowning
Here's the problem with this line of thinking
To go and look into this
Statistics because bouquet
All except that he's right about all that
Sure this is a more serious problem
No one has mass drowned schools to children at school
You can't do that you can't mask the kit like
You don't Outlaw swimming
Because there's
It's not an attack
Swimming isn't an attack
Most of the time whenever there's drowning its people who were like cotton to Riptide or something like that
It's a natural force or whatever
There is a crime being committed
People in bass shooting
It doesn't
Exist generally speaking with drowning
And a lot of times with car
Just
But drunk driving is also illegal
What you said but then you said there's no master rounding
And I was like flash flood of school I don't know how you
You do remember that
Connected to you and they were like puppets
Kind of
You get five
So you got
Drowning as well
And you're holding somebody else I think it makes perfect
Hardee's
Yourself
You can't get you it's tough to get for others to Mastro's
That's hard to do
IPhone
I don't understand
I think it's just it's like from a cartoon I remember image of the
Costume or whatever
No I do not drown the puppets are helping you drown
Other people
You do puppet scan
Marionette technology has not till that part
Jordan I got to be honest I think you're crazy
Whatever you're imagining
A nightmarish
Torture device
So maybe in that scenario could master
Like a school shooter
That's kind of
I don't know
Whatever you use those are the statistics to minimize the idea of like mass shootings are like
Are you talking about
The limiting access to guns
People dying drowning
Grounding
More
Isn't that stupid because one of the one of those things
You can't do too
People in a school
Maybe you could
At gunpoint is a school has a pool
You still probably couldn't you could also if you were Poseidon
Yes but if you have magic
That's the scenario wherein you could Mass drowned
People 100 times the amount of people died in mass shootings in mathmagic
Right
Everybody
Dinos
It just said nobody's talking about media isn't going to talk about
When are we going to
Let me have my bucket
So anyway back into the little bit later and I'll discuss the
Realities of them at that point
But just for now.
Fagundes
The past that we were going
Alex did that
About pocket
I'm really single
As of March 11th
But
He's starting to talk about
The s*** that's going on behind
Infowars
Calling up
Harassment because your office physically located
Tell us where your servers are located
You need to send me a subpoena
I am right now
That's where you're at
Did the more likely scenario that I imagine is
Culligan
Something
2009 you have to know that Alex Jones is the definition of Oppositional defiant
Unless you walked him
To say that the FBI is calling him
You know you don't f****** call him like that
It and it doesn't serve anybody's best interest except Alex
So that means
He's making it up or
He's taking a prank calling for 10
And this is where he turns it into
Fishing line
That's a 98% chance
Okay
Months of Obama being in office
Inaugurated a month-and-a-half before this
He's making it a f****** priority to get
Get on
You better harass Alex Jones and make him scared to put out that documentary that's not going to have any effect on my
Career
Drawn and and and
Housing crisis in all of this
But you know
Who I can't stand right
Yeah
FBI
Call him up
Angel politely ask for his address
Google
That's
Do I find it
To be the flimsy
To get people more excited about the Obama Deception
Set that earlier episode was like I'm going to release it now
Hey maybe I'll release him
I don't even know if
People excited about it now this is the all man
Certificates
It's very crispy marketing
Technique nothing more
Shooting
Alex
In this clip
Please start
Play talking about the Alabama shooting
So gets off track
Haha really fast
Into
Nobody's talking about that chimpanzee earlier
It might come back up
Is obviously you know about Alabama
Assault rifle
He spared no one not his mother
Alabama
Coffee County coroner
Preacher said we don't know what triggered it
Real quick he wasn't married and he didn't have a
And
He threw a fit and killed Mommy
We burn down the house with apples that kill one person
This sort of ranching at Alex's jumping-off Intuit
Really crazy places
Is his way of not having
To feel anything
It's his way of turning this into
To some sort of
The new world
Feel something
Well your own head off of things
So you kill him
That would be a very different Missy
We are
Now
Ripping your face off
Was on a Prozac
Things you don't normally do that
Someone
That's one of those things
This is Elementary Alex rambling
Yeah the place this ends up going like where his mind goes so he doesn't have to talk more about this story that he's already
Pretty clearly misreporting
Like the idea that his wife left him and took the kids
He's just making that up that's not that's not part of the story at all he's just
The media tells you to do not blow your head off
Kill himself
Like the shooter
To avoid the consequences
Man
Oh man we get a weird glimpse
Listen to Alex
And his family history as this clip
Meander's
Monkeys
That's a very different Muscle Man
This sucker weighed 200 lb
Thousand pound linebacker
No linebackers
My dad's
Twice removed Uncle Houston
W
Ship Chevron world came back
German depression
Until my dad stories
Ocean
What's Millwork Suites at Maryland
No problem or whatever
What the hell
I don't know
Read about that in history book in your life that's an interesting fact
Obviously
King of underground chimpanzee boxing
Texas the Tudors
I come from royalty also part of my family
The Tudor line I love that how his mind worked at least at this point
I don't really have much more to say about this shooting but man I like talk about that
What all right that I was up on all these Prozac drugs
He was crazy dude is involved in getting Rodeo dudes the Box
Illegal
What
That is admire the hell out of
At the end if he realizes
I need to make this make sense
You don't need Bela karolyi to come pick you up after this one
You're Bela karolyi reference is amazing
That is that is
That is solid this is Alex inspires
Stupidity
He's putting forth great
Underground fights with Bela karolyi gymnast
At the smallest gymnast
To fight each other they put gloves on but they couldn't.
And I don't know if you know this
Most gymnast when they get to the age of eight
They just can't handle it anymore and they just anytime they see a human being they take it as a threat especially if you smile
Is it really
Challenges
Man this is funny
Dumb s***
I love that quote
I wish I could live inside nightclub
He is like
Whatever whatever you talk about Alex Jones being the biggest monster in the world now
That dude back then but like this is what I mourn the loss of
My uncle was a monkey fire
Spell shootings like
Undermines a lot of like the narratives that he wants one
Alabama shooting
The shooting was perpetrated by a guy named Michael McLendon was the 29 year-old weigh
Despite what Alex's reporting was not married
Did not have kids
Are you living at home with his mother difficulty finding work
Do you failed
Complete basic training
When you tried to enter the services
Found himself in a really bad position
When is Mom
Killed most of his mom side of the
He ended up doing that and you left a note behind
Explaining
His actions
That he would pay for making his mother and him suffer
He went on to write mama was very sick
Had lung cancer I think I put her out of her misery
I'm sorry but mama has suffered enough and so have I
Some of the people who made us suffer will pay
After everything was said and done his mother received an autopsy that did not support his claim that she was sick
And she definitely didn't have cancer
There in case
He was depressed but no indications
Receiving
Then what it is is probably just a down-on-his-luck
Very diluted
Leo person
Who had imagined that his mom was sick
You wasn't getting
Support you needed from his mom
Will probably
You know not happy with
All their positions in life and he decided to A6 blame on his mother's side of the family
Saudi was mercy killing his mom
Punish them
For the perceived lack of
Support
So it
Just someone
You know not just
Someone
Alex talked about
Reality
All of the things that he rails against
Accurate
Like that
The violence against women in this case is
Perpetuated under the office
Episodes of like Mercy
But it is still a violent Act
His mother
And towards other
Members of
Her side of the family
Still obviously
A crime that has some sort of resentment or anger towards
Is Mom
Diversion of the mess
Violence
Doesn't really work
Look for Alex's
Alex is just
Using that probably should have been
A bigger story
Now it's interesting because Alex wants to
Demonize ssris
Desperately
But in this next clip I think you'll see
Then he doesn't understand pharmacology
At all
And I think he thinks the Prozac
Then it is
Texas Network
Butcher knife
What
Your
San Marcos San Antonio and
Just like a chimpanzee the people's ears what happened
Both cases
Invocation little guys would just turn the person's face off
You can't use stories about people on PCP to demonize people on Prozac
I think Alex thinks they're the same thing
Maybe
Anytime there's a
Acronym
Yeah remind me of PCP
Again not related to Prozac
No indication that those drug dealers were on Prozac
This has nothing to do with anything he's just trying to
The couple the association in his listeners Minds
The effects of PCP are the same as the effects
The Prozac
They're trying to give you that cuz I end up like these PCP
My uncle was a monkey fight
That's the level of logic is going on here
Someone being
Cautious about over
Prescription of
They're very legitimate arguments to make about how they
You know Farmers a big business
And people get put on drugs a lot of the time that are superfluous.
Weather conditions
The drug reps are often
Insidious in there maybe
People don't need or
Kind of need but could
Get similar effect
Through exercise or something like that I understand that
That conversation
Is well worth having
But this one isn't
This one is just an outright demonization of the idea of
Of getting mental help
The idea that some people
Do you need
Medication in order to help them live productive
Decent live
And that is not a slight on them or a shame
And anyway
Is disgusting
No I mean Mighty my very first psychiatrist
Prescribed Abilify
Commercial
F****** up
That can happen. Blame him or Abilify
That's that can happen to anybody people found Abilify being incredibly
It was a very much like
Even while he was
Prescribed
I could actually hear the drug rep
In his ear like the the little demon on his shoulder
Because it cost $700
For a month prescription
So you're like
That's the problem with Abilify
The medication works that is a
Runaway Runaway
Runaway
That's what you can talk about if you want to do that there's 100 example of diversion
And then there's the simple benign version of like
You take a medication that doesn't work and got a switch
Family members
Taking things that it like well it worked for the cause
Like massive weight gain
Drastically affect
Can get to the right place
Decreased sex drive
Lethargy
To be on
Reason you know all of this stuff I like I tried probably five or six medication
Before I found something that actually work for
What I need
Very small numbers
I'm very
Minut
Portions of the population you can have
Yeah
And they aren't
Like being on PCP
And it's not
The same age
You take it you're fine and then one day you have a bad trip on your Prozac or whatever
Incredibly negative reaction
Based on their individual chemistry
There there
Do you need
Fingerprints of our brain
Sometimes don't work with Xbox drug
Demonizing that Drogba
Because of the small amount
Of negative reactions that happen to it is
Absurd
Stupid
It is regressive to the point of just
Just go ahead and Sciences
You might as well
Well
Because magic kills
Hundreds of thousands of people a year.
The worst thing that can happen with these drugs is not
Hallucinating on the top of your roof
40 year old woman on her roof
The worst thing is you get a rash
I will say that I'm cutting their breasts
Depressed I don't want to say anything
Like it sounds positive
But the Precision
Required in order to carry out
A massive
Mass shooting
I don't think you could do that
I think you could try and punch your way through a school or something like that
But like you wouldn't have the time
You take Pleasant great video game by the way punch your way through school Japanese arcade
Want to punch behind
I wanted posters
Montage
I don't know maybe I'm maybe I'm wrong about that
Medium media
It's pretty rage
Fault
There's no idea and I've no interest in finding out what's the lot of episodes of
Cops
The punch through fence
Itsfunneh
That's one of those drugs they like I will never do it
I will never
Know what it's like
But I'm very curious what
Feels like in your brain
You know I've done enough substances in my life to know like
Altered States are very different
How differ
Like who's really drunk I'm like
I kind of know what you're feeling right now
I can empathize
It away was like
Alright alright
Titus
I do not know why you thought it was a good idea to punch to the only reason that we do really need
Take me to Knollwood
Gills like
To take some of the really crazy
You know I don't know if you could
I don't know if you can recreate
I don't think there's a Safeway to feel this picture
Anyway
Alex
He's way off on
Everyday
Might have a good point about that yet
German shooting
Surprisingly is also off
German six
I'll bet my bottom dollar
This guy was inside
I think I want to be discovered
Services
I would like to take that back
A case after case
After Case has five more
Guys shot up a school's name was
Medication
No indication that he was
Confine
Inpatient treatment
The condition of him
Getting out of this house
Yeah you spoke to a therapist a few times in the year before his murders
Is witches therapist towards his parents about
His parents denied the claims and said he never received psychiatric care
Kind of Falls in line with a picture that painted of his parents of being kind of delusional in in denial about
Their son having
Any sort of default
Extension of themselves
Like you got bad grades
Was unable to find apprenticeship
Deep denial about that
He was on a tennis team
And people said that he was very difficult to work with
Hard to be on a team
In denial about his
His behavioral issues growing up
So there's a pattern that emerges with his life
Any idea that the therapist like I told them
The most I could do League
No one said anything
And he wasn't even in psychiatric care or psychological treatment at all
And also the No.1 with
You know government intelligence
Just gave him the gun
Is Dad
20 gun
But you was a good
About the most part he was a part of like a shooting club
Recreational shooting
His son stole one
He was
In breach of German laws
In terms of
If you own gun
Once you have to properly lock them up
Yeah you didn't lock them up properly
Yeah he had to go to Courtney was found guilty of being an accessory
Holy to the school shooting
Which is appropriate
Stomach
Drastic of a sentence
Which I think is also
I think the
I think I think that
It's awful
To beat the person
Who has
Given access to
This weapon that killed a lot of people but at the same time I don't
Treat that like he actually
We did the
Wright and his response was actually pretty admirable found
I bet he had
One of his guns
Have been taken and used in this crime
And he immediately offered to relinquish his rights
20 guns that he used for this sporting
Hobby of his who's like oh absolutely here
You guys
Clearly
Story Alex
Who's pitching about this guy that he was
On
Occasionally
Someone in the government
I'm a gun
All of that is not true
He's reporting willy-nilly and just saying what he wants to be the king
Which I'm sure later he will say is MacKay
But it's not
None of it's true
Is your daughter f****** chocolate
Are masquerading as one
Will you think that you know things
And you don't
You stay single
All the time
And when you have a big old chip on your shoulder
I'm always right
I mean
Do you really need to defend gun
Yeah really need it
Just don't think it's not
That's why
I don't know maybe there's other reasons
Digipak on mentor
As it were
Call from
Jack McLamb
For he's a big old
You can find a song about him
Episode
Resist
Stupid
Fear-mongering about there
Abominations are phony president
Guns
He's a communist he wants all the guns out of the hands of the people
And so our military until told us that we would see more of these mind control assassins going in and shooting up
Their families
Killing their families and killing children and killing
Masses of people and that's exactly what's happening now brother so you're right on target
And I just wanted to tell the people that we have here
That are two police military Association that issue that explains
Governments five easy steps
The creative mind control assassin out of anyone even you
Ego into your psychologist
Psychiatrist
And they put you under hypnosis
The government can tell them to make you a mind-control assassin it only takes an hour for him to put a key in your brain
Oh man
I mean why would you ever go to therapy if you believe that
Would you ever get help
Do you believe if you believe that there's a possibility that the government is going to tell your therapist to put a key in your brain
Within an hour that can turn you into a mind-control assassin
They only exist
Because Obama wants everybody's gone to neither, Dustin wants to
Create a depressive State why would Vicky if you're feeling depressed
You have nothing to help
No resources
Nothing
Did the government published that self-help book
The five easy steps
He's selling it the seven highly effective
You selling it and later Alex I have him do a sales pitch
Resource Financial
The greatest demonization
F****** idiot
Because I think we've
Said our peace and we've allowed
Dickheadz to say their piece
Alex Jones gets a call
From a guy who's not on head
No this isn't you on head
If you get a call from a guy and brings up a new story
That Alex
Will later report as true
Based on the fact that this caller
Is bring it to his attention
Which is the problem
Is a fuking idiot invite as well
Andy in Montana you're on the year
I do not like so I just wanted to know if you'd heard about the explosions in Bozeman Montana and white
Call Montana
We're two American Legions were blowing up
When did this happen
This happened last week
I don't even in our news and it hasn't made news at all
Was it in Washington State
General Lee
That means it's a real terrorist attack
Because it was real terrorism
Without
Given the implication babe
Means that it's probably real the guy a couple of Americans
Or building
First
If you're going to ask Alex how he's doing
To say
Route
If he is admitting in the sixties and seventies there were all these bombings happen
All over the place
What then
Do you think was perpetrating those bombings
Do you think it was Muslim terrorist
I don't think so no do you think it was black people bombing s*** all over the place
I'm in the weather
Terrorist group
Contrary to what
Constantly says
If he's if he's even saying this at all
There's a lot of like eco-terrorism
That involves
TheCHIVE
Primarily white people
Situation
Real f*****-up
A few things
He's found a headline that works for it
Basically
American Legion
This problem with
Double drop
First problem is the scholars to American Legions were blown off which is not true
A couple of reasons
The first is that wild explosion in Bozeman did
American Legion
That is true
Is there a bunch of businesses around American Legion
Was one of them so he's already implying that it was the American Legion Woodland Park
Now the second
Did not
Affecting American
It affected a restaurant called The Legion Street Grill his caller seems to not know the difference
Does the word legion
Isabella
Issue here is Obama
Bozeman was technically explosion
But it was caused by a failure in the gas
But some people theorize that set off by a minor earthquake nearby
Businesses
Caused by a faulty Refrigeration
Universal Whitehall is Thoroughly investigated
They're only suspicious as it relates to whether or not the businesses or the gas Mains were up to code
Also plenty of media cover these things they're deeply traumatic to the economies of those town
And the blast killed one woman
They were pretty serious events you can find new stories
Is from local media and stuff like that
There's just not really that much need
The national media to cover
I'd like
Right
The New York Times cover it like a couple days later a couple days a week later
But it's not of immediate concern necessarily until all the facts
Right
Is just ludicrous b******* Alex
Wyoming
If callers
2 oz
Pretty crazy
I don't know I don't know how to respond to somebody who even if
You tell them the reality of it
They're going to say it's a cover-up
Probably
Because it was an actual terrorists
Bacon
Tell you the truth of it
So they hire all these fake
Things are real not know either false flag
Because the Earth is Hollow
Whatever it is
Where
Without any feeling
So about the Alabama
In particular and one of the reasons for that
Is that
There were reports of
The military being in
Involved
After the fact
Of course
Respond military out on the street
Fort Rucker
And Alabama
That we're helping out with
Darius Colonel Rucker
The issue here is that
These shootings took place
Multiple City
Very small
In Alabama
They have very limited law enforcement
My capability
So the response to it
Stop
People from Fort Rucker
Deemed
Is it appropriate
To help out
They helped out was very limited
But also they did get in
A article
Military.com from October 20th
The fact this is October 20th
Investigation found that soldiers should not have been sent to man traffic stops in a small Alabama town after 11
People were killed in March
During a shooting
Army report released
Associated Press
Monday response
Requested
Dispatch military
Please
From nearby Fort Rucker broke the law
But an army spokesman said no charges
Has been filed
As a result of this finding
The Army took
Against Italy
Least one person
Yeah so they found it it was a breach of
Posse Comitatus Act
Would like them too
Bring up
The officer who made the
Have the authority
Responses
Hurricane
Okay
Intent was to be a good army neighbor and help local
Civilian authorities
Difficult unique tragedy effect
The local community
There were apparently no adverse collateral effects
Inappropriate
Ministrator
It wasn't like
We're taking over
Yeah isn't that what we have a military for that's a big part of it
But they were really good
Broader picture
Has heard these reports that there were
Military officer
And of course
That gets him
It's very excited about
Get in touch with someone from Fort Rucker
In Alabama
Alex
Never goes well
With someone
I haven't heard
After shooting providing
Security
Regular US Army on
What's the time
Thank you very much for calling
You seems like a polite
Interview
Just alyx
2 questions about like
We go out there you were out there trying to insinuate yourself
The police
It is very
Polite
Responses
I'll have a good answer
But at the same time
The pudding is in the eating
Sarah defecation sound to tape
His interpretation is not what the Army decided was the case
But I do believe him
Cornel Wilde
In terms of
Previously there was a
Shooting going on in Alabama with regular army responded
Wilshire I mean we wouldn't respond to it we would not we would never respond off the installation in a loan for
What we what we
Will provide do is
Support functions
We will provide assistance
You know to our partner community
Military police though
Yes sir that is a law enforcement rolling that we would not do here at Fort Rucker I can't
Speak for what northcom
Or the army war college is trying to put together
But Here at Fort Rucker we would not do that
All we were doing with his what was enforcing the cordone
And I just directing traffic around
We work we weren't stopping anybody we were engaging anybody we were just directing traffic
Soda
Distinction that he's trying to make it
I see where he's coming from a very limited Manpower
So they used some military personnel
In order to man these places where they were directing traffic
And then the other thing they did was
They guarded
Like the morgue
People break
Who are the local line
Enforcement
Appropriate Authority
All that stuff even in the
Even in the
Military zone
Temecula Valley pictures
Where
Misunderstand what you're seeing
Cuz military police
Book like Direct
Traffic looks very similar to them
Having a road
Because they had whistle
Play the white gloves and every
They're dancing around
He's a trying to get something out of this
Guy questions very politely
What do you think about that
Cornel Wilde is response
What I believe doesn't
Like personally doesn't really matter
I've got to go
Was trying to like
You saw his words against
Called into the show the show is
A good-faith position
Himself
At which of course Alex later characterizes
Which is what happened
Call Dad Alex
Prep
Yeah exactly
Incorrectly
Alex reached out to this base
He's the one who handles
Calm everybody down
Nope that wasn't our plan we were just trying to make sure that people didn't go into what
Hey me a banana
Shooters
You know it's possible we didn't know all the facts
The time
So we're just trying to provide some kind of support
Because the local police
Had like
4 guys
Or even afterwards
Not an active shooter
Keep evil away from
Curiosity or something like that process
Might be people who
I don't know I don't know what the suspicion
Look like you deface the morgue
Sing like that
I don't know if that's
To secure those
Even the bodies it India
Immediate time are still
There's evidence
I get the info
I don't personally have a problem
With military
Personality
Especially
In stretched
Very rural areas where they don't have
Large police
Right
But I also do see the other side where it's like
Any military doing anything to mess
Stickley is inappropriate
I kind of see that argument to Alex's wrong
Who cares
If your
If your community all they have is like
Boss Hogg and his two deputies
Just anybody with any kind of authority
She just be like
I don't know
I don't know cuz I I see
ICC
Do you like principal argh
What sort of
But I also seized the logistics
More
Rationalize
Poolside relies on the idea of like this is a slippery slope and if you allow this then they'll be
Next will be pulling over your car
Which I think is foolish but at the same time like
Alright whatever
Slippery slope argument especially in this regard
Flimsy at
Yeah
Slippery slope argument
In general
But
In this case
Alyssa
Just let this one go
It seems
It seems soft
Jordan
March 11th
A day that will live in
Because W shoe on head
Because
On this episode Alex Jones
Is going to do a guest spot on someone else's radio show
He leaves the show commercial for The Obama Deception
Then comes back
Yeah when you comes back
He's Furious
Howard Stern
It's not Howard Stern
I don't even remember the name of the show
Recognize
It's a show
Not a fan of treating Alex with respect
I like that
That's ironic that Alex
Get the taste of his own medicine on the same show
I haven't listened to that interview or anything
About that experience
But all of that
Is washed away
Because he
Has received
Document
Someone
From the Missouri Highway Patrol
Asportation
And on their computers sending Alex Jones a secret.
That I regret
He's a real document
We are back in the world that's what you
Here is the miac Strategic report
The modern militia movement
Here
People believers
We just go over in a little bit
But this is Alex will in the future called
Very
Very big teeth
Mythology
Peace
Of all of his arguments about how the government is trying to Target people like him
It is
The stupidest argument
Possible he's going to go over all the
Very interesting
In history
When Alex is talked about like secrets.
People contacting him
You never really gets into specifics who never talks about the names of documents because we have white papers we got to ask for documents
Who's one of the only
Senses that I can think of where he's
Saying the name of the report
Which leads me to believe it might be one of the only instances of people act
Now
Then it's further variant
Everything about this
This is martial law
Someone is sent this to him
And he's going on are and Reporting
It has been public
Send
No it was written in February
Law enforcement
It's released by WikiLeaks
2 Days Later
Two days later Wikileaks has a copy of it and they release it
Alex is already released on Infowars
What
I can find crazy I can
Find no instances
Anybody publishing this before out
What is one of the only times that I'm firmly convinced
Yeah it's weird
I don't know what that means but at the same time
Someone sent it to Alex
They also sent
WikiLeaks
Longer process of
Trying to confirm the Providence of it
But I
I don't know what to make
I really don't know what to do with it because Alex is almost always
He was ahead of the game
Jesus David lies about the document itself
Only 8 page
Yeah it's so rude
Shorts
I'll give you a little bit of a
A primer on
This miac report
So what day is is the law enforcement community
A gather
I think they put out these reports from time
The time just about things
To be online for
Radar a this one is about the modern militia move
It's called
The modern militia moo
It goes into it starts B
The roots of the militia
Which started in the
AP tonight
Resurgence
In 2009 which day
Really fun thing from
From the second paragraph of this
Article
The paper
Yeah
Really
You reading this
And knowing what we know now
9 years later
Some people saw like the alt right
In all of these white nationalists
Bubbling
Coming
So here from the second paragraph
Academic female and minority empowerment in the 1970s and 1960s blow to white males
Powerman
This combined with a synagogue
Yep this combined with a sensor
To defeat from the Vietnam War increased levels of immigration and unemployment Banda paramilitary culture
Disco
Such as Tom Clancy novel V Soldier Fortune Magazine the glorified Kombat
This culture glorified white males and operate Heroes who are mentally ill
Physically tough
There's a lot to that
It goes on to discuss how
Many individuals and organizations
Began to concoction
Series 2
Explain their misfortune
These theories vary but almost always involve the globalist dictatorship
The New World Order exploit the working class citizen
United Nations troops were thought to already be operating in the United States
In support of the New World Order
Much of this rhetoric would become anti-semitic claiming that the Jews control the monetary system in
And in turn these scientists occupied governor
The Malaysian of Montana became a key organization
Individual
How to form militia Oregon
So this is all just descriptive
Bad news
They discuss how
The 90s early 90s
Incident
Like Ruby Ridge
Waco and Oklahoma City bombing
We're firmly
Catalyzing event
5/4
Radicals
It led to a surgeon
Different militia organization
And increased militia activity
It goes on to list
Hundred tons
The reason
Why people should
Afraid
About this
November 9th 1995
Oklahoma Constitutional Militia members arrested
They plan to bomb the Southern Poverty Law Center
Clinic
December 18th 95
A drop of ammonium nitrate and fuel oil is found behind the IRS building in Reno Nevada
The device failed to explode
An anti-government protester is later arrested
January 18th 1996 member of the Aryan Republican Army is arrested in Ohio after a shootout with the FBI
ARA was also associated with bank robberies
390 94-90
July 27th
One person and injuring
Eric Robert Rudolph is later arrested in the other bombings at abortion clinics
October 11th 1996 seven members of the Mountaineer militia were arrested for plotting to blow up the FBI fingerprint
Records West Virginia
You know you get $0.02
You see all these
They're not
Trying to paint an unfair picture
In this side
This report
Suffice it to say this is a scripture of
That the movement
In the 90s
The resurgence
Where are you
Incidents like
June 29th 2007 six members of the Alabama
Free militia arrested on weapons
An explosive charge
ATF agent we're going to testify the five
All of these all of these frames
Anytime
Other people
White dudes go f****** batshit
Crazy
What is a joke
What is your thought process where you're like a man
These people are
I don't know
At least getting towards it so I better get a gun and blow it up
Childish
It is
The talking about their about
The idea that there
You know they're tying Indies
North America
Explain
Commonalities that they found
That a number of them
Are motivated by
They don't say
Believing there's a North American
Memes that you're apart of a violent militia
There's
That a lot of these militias
Also have
Right that's a very important distinction
Write this
And you know how to read
You will see
Just that
These are these are things
That malicious
That carry out attacks
Like described
In the beginning of this
They may hold these beliefs
Not
That holding these beliefs makes you
Suspected to be a member of one of those
This is a very
Very
Very important
You do if you see smoke sometimes there's a fire
Sometimes somebody just grilling
True
Sing is trying to
To accept guilt by association
So that would be
Believing
The opposite
Is expressing
Because they aren't
Baby mechanic
Be there in a little bit ago
A little bit guilty
Are you going to be super irresponsible
Niagara port and not
Because you could be you could possibly believe that
If you don't read this after Alex says
I could be your world where
The the law enforcement put out a report that was like
Hey
A lot of these dickholes believe this
They probably one of those dick holes
It's not like that at all
Criticizing
Even handed
It's Alex ideas about Tuesday
Another piece
Of his.
His argument
Image training manual
Don't tread on me flag
Guys
We showed that
Guilt by association
They're coming out
Vetta are digested by
Aaron Russo's film
Freedom to Fascism
That's weird because those were actually they were actually referencing Ted Turner
Also Alex Alex goes on later to say that the Turner Diaries
Planted on Timothy me
Which is
That doesn't seem necessary at all
So now I'm more importantly just because
It's a nice
Side Road to go down
Alex brings up this
Financial Times
London time
Of course he does but he always calls
Financial Times
Times of London witch
Whatever
Sure I'm so this article and noun for world
Sexually
And now for a world government
Eagles it now for World Government because that's what
Russo called it
In his film
Alex may not have actually but it's a great title
And now for World Government it has the tone of someone
Introduced
As the next
I know show
Hey and Now ladies and gentlemen world government
That uses film from freedom to Fashion
Got everything wrong
And instead
Actually
Helped contribute to America going from freedom to Fashion
Almost like the titles ironic
So I'm a little bit here from this Financial Times article called
And now for a world
See if you think this
I never believe that there's a secret United Nations
I've never seen black helicopters hovering over the sky above Montana
But for the first time in my life
The formation to stop
I'm sort of world
Is possible
Is plausible
Do you think
Do you think that
This guy's saying that's open
Sprays that what he's saying is that for a long time I thought people who did this
We're crazy
And now I'm starting
I think maybe they have the smallest kernel of appoint
He goes on to say
That the formation of a world governed
Is it what you didn't believe before first
Is that the issues that are facing the world are international
Looks like terrorism
Climate change
Are the financial markets call working in concert don't give a f*** about borders
The problems
We face every move into the future being International
Who makes sense that we have some
International
It's really hard to regulate a business that
Functions all over the world with dip
Look at Google
How do you regulate Google when Google is
Kowtowing to China censor
World governing body
Where is in the past
Relax communication
Transportation technology that would be required
To make the world accessible to everybody the telegraph was not necessarily a great way to create a world governed
Logistics
Climate change World Market
Those are all problems
Or issues that in order for us to navigate them successfully require all of us to
So the solutions
What's the problem
Who's that are international in nature
Nationalist
Countries that are out for
America first
Horchata first
They're not going to be able to solve these
Integrated problem
Dan America solve terrorism
We have spent
So many years
Solving terrorism
We mailed we absolutely didn't create an environment that
Terrorism
A million times
That would be crazy America first
Thinking
You're going to talk about how like Obama now coming
The office
Seems like you someone who is much more interested International cooperation
He goes on to bring up this
Ramanujan Global Entry
Security project
Good babe
This group
Are you working on
You're working for a legally binding
Climate change
Agreement
And working
To strengthen
So
Okay
Obama's associated with John podesta
Someone who is into working with
The UN
Their position
Mom baby
Indications that the world is
Is becoming more amenable
To that
But
If you actually read the article
If you read the article I will quote
But let's not get carried away
Well it seems feasible
Push for Global governance
Be painful
A slow process
They're good
The bad reason
The lack of Will and determination on the part of national political leaders
Well they might like to talk about a planet in Peril or ultimately still much more focused on their next election
At home
But this problem also hints at a more welcome
Making progress on global governance will be slow sledding
Even in the EU the heartland of law-based international government
The idea remains
Unpause
That's just he's being very blunt
Yeah it turns out people aren't that interested
This was
What 2009
Yep this is probably a
2008 start
Even in the global governance
Is an unpopular idea
How many years later
Brexit
Catalan
Country
Italy
Getting out of the EU
All of these different places we are not creating a global
Now they're actually Act
Sibley tearing down even the slightest cooperation
This world government article ends with the world's most pressing political problems
International in nature
Political identity remains
Until someone cracks this problem
The UN
Even in this article if you actually just because the title is and now for world government
It's not announcing a world government in the way that Alex thinks it is
So he likes
To play this game where they come read between the lines
The world government is gear
But if you look into the author
Critical of world government
He was against 2001
Publicly you passionately
Against the idea of the UK taking onto you're always one of the
He is a pencil this s*** his name is Aaron Russo
But it's like
You know you can't use that
This author clearly doesn't have some some
Versus Pro World Government opinion
Article
You know the trend Uno the world seems to be heading
Directions
Plausible but unfortunately
Unfortunate
Because the problem
Cesar International
Nature
Aren't interested in that
Yeah
That's just a little flight
The road
Is it is an interesting
Things to look back on now
As
Describing the
Global
How
Many if not all of our politicians
Oceans are far more
Themselves
Elected
When we look at an International Coalition of scientists
Saying like hey
Within 12 years
If we don't take Act
We're literally f***
And everybody who read that report everybody
II
When you read it I assume or maybe
Did you read it
When you have too much Alec
It was not like
Going to work together now I was immediately like we're what
Yeah what
What should have been the conclusion of that article is not we should all come together and deal with climate change
Somebody needs to work on geoengineering
Real quick
Abandon this whole we need to cut down on carbon emissions
That shouldn't going to have
Solve this problem
Liberty some enterprising Young
Not full of s*** Elon Musk is working on that as we
What's up
Alex's
The world
Forecast Trends better than
Anybody
And we going to start seeing riots in major cities
That rival wayser Panther
Those that we
We saw
Back in the 1960s
When cities were being burned down
You going to start seeing the same thing
Indiana
Faceware forecast
By this summer
People
You better prepare Bubba ray's baby
Exactly remember how many US cities Burns
To the ground in the summer rose
Also I really hate sleepy so
I hate it I like high-register sulentic
We're going to see
A lot of rice
You know in the cities
I don't I just can't people who live in cities
There are all kinds of people
I like it when you excited
Preoccupied
Discuss
Visa vie
His response
Do it but
He hasn't actually read
42b just got it and now he's on air still
He's still dealing with that bad interview
Yeah
Just decides to announce that he's right
North American Union conspiracy theorist
Mexico
Trade the dollar for the Amero associated with serious concern
MarketWatch
Mexico
Crisis
Books now
Yeah it is approved as a book that f****** Jerome corsi wrote that letter
It's not crazy that the North American Union is being put together is this article
How realistic is a North American currency
From January 28th 2000
Again oven article
What's a title that does not represent
The content of
Did the body of the
The article about the idea that
Is combining
Need the three countries
Because there are natural resources to be used in Canada
There's
Quote
With America and Mexico
SO3
Coming together as one unit might be competitive on a global level
So he discusses that possibility
Some ideas
And then if you look
The end of this article once again
Quote this particular path isn't something one would wish for but cumulative imbalances that steadily built our finance
Economy must be resolved one way or another
Therein lies the critical Crossroads
Read together face
As our weary World attempts to find
Yeah
Not so much at least for the time being
Possible
Certainly although all again offer that it could take years but
Prickly puzzle Fallen
How to play
Effective money manager
Potential outcome
In factoring them into our decision
Well the notion of a seismic currency shift may seem obscure
We must respect the possibility long before because
Comes from page and
So you saying
Again
Probable
Not so much
This is a possibility
Way far off in the future if it
Even happen
Because
Effective money manager
Dictate
We need to
To discuss any possible
Talk about the Rams
So the article
How realistic is a North American Union in one currency
Not very
Not very. Very likely
That and the Jerome
Seabrook to try and prove
That like to North America
Community
Real and he's doing that because the North American Union and the NAFTA superhighway
That that we covered in our endgame coverage ad nauseam
Are listed in
That my ex
About
It conspiracy
Is that people in these militias
Believer
So Alex has to be totally real
I really have no idea
There's a very strong possibility
That
At least spiritual route
Tucson malicious
My feeling is that
He's not
Personally in a militia
But he's like
Once removed
Like he has plenty of
People he knows I wouldn't are Emily
Back reports
Because he's like
And
All of the things that they described as being like things that
People in militia groups believe in red flags
They're all things that he believed
So it's not
It's not that like
This report
Even
And if you look at the entirety of it
And you say oh I
Describes me to a T
Yeah that's still not saying that you are a member of one of those malicious
Right or that even you should be suspected of being a member
They are
People in those malicious
They use this sort of
Iconography and believe
Conspiracy theories
Here's what I would but I would say
It's Vista
It's saying
If
Many
Members
Like
Being y
Yeah it's not saying
If you like thing why
Then you are a member of group X
That is a transverse thing of
Infra
You can't do that that
That
One does not follow from the other
It's like saying
Many people who are neo-nazis
Like to wear leather jacket
If you're wearing a leather jacket then you were probably a Neo-Nazi
850 exact same sort of logic
Just doesn't work when you flip it it doesn't work
But you have to understand logic
In order to
Actually you don't even have to understand logic it's reading comprehension
History comes on air
Reporting this thing as I
They're calling us all terrorists
And so we get to the 12
We find ourselves
Meeting up
Sleepy Owl
One one thing that's
So important
Is that
Alex
Whenever it is done to him and his white supremacist
Every Muslim is a radical Muslim
Osher
What if he's not quite on that tip yet
Right now in 2009
Somehow
Portrayed
Alex
Radical Muslim groups all use
Iconography
God's warning
Alden Elementary level
It's so stupid
Because Eve
I'm a left-leaning person
If I saw like a police report
Some Boulevard forcement report that was like
Many terrorist groups on valette
Use this sign
Many of them believed in this
I wouldn't be
Really self-conscious if I also believe
I would
I wouldn't think that they were talking about me
Because I understand
12oz Tire
He's real tired
Complain about it
There's a reason
No rest for the wicked
Association
This radio show
4 hours a day
Is available right now
DVDs
It's freon
The Fanfare that you probably
Would have loved
Comes on errands
So go watch
He did.
And now it's here
Explains that like I don't even want
YouTube pay
Me for that
Just be able to cover the bandwidth and stuff
Getting the truth out there
But then he accidentally keeps talking
What
Thinking I'm great I'm in the defeating criminals defeating the New World Order
Here is a giant multiple boats
Just made all of the descriptors of himself
I don't like big houses
Alex
Yeah
Really just fun
Do you like waffles
But really didn't
I'm not really in the broad
Well I got to be honest
I think that's a good introduction to what's about to happen
Because Alex
Real f*****-up
About
Women
I don't think that I
In my listening 2009. A lot of chauvinism
There's a lot of Alex's.
I think I've heard stuff that is this overly like
Rui my jaw open
What
What are you saying was that also in the miac report massive amount of misogyny
Signifier of
Second paragraph
Part of the reason why I'm saying
Prescient as hell
I would say
Alex is shocking
We close to understand
Understanding
We couldn't be further away
If that makes sense
Parents share their daughter's apartment
This is a stray thought but I'd also like to point out that taken
Came out on
January 30th
Color alive app just come out right before
So-so parents
Daughters all the time
Parents share their daughters
Another States
Nope
Firearm they don't
Grocery store
Pancake mix and strawberries
Midnight
This is actually where I was thinking the beginning of like a bad stand-up
You know
Next to the other one
This is not going to go
It's always
So paranoid
Younger Archie Bunker
Believe me
Whoa
You're so you're so close
It's weird the more paranoid
Pull up
Back on
Out of control
My girls
Qalandar
Is weird to listen to
That is gross
He's almost there
And then he goes as far away as possible because the observations are but the empathy
Tell that women are afraid
King himself to understand exactly
Are often attacked in parking lots at midnight
When you're alone in a parking lot and comes over
You probably expect at least some interaction
Or something
Hayward
Most women have
Have experienced something like that or know someone who has told them about it
Most people's at least second hand
Experience
Absolutely no I was coming back from Zanies one night
At like The Late Show Saturday got Outlets
And I got off the train and I'm walking home and I always walk
My headphones and I got my head down
Not doing anything
Find myself like
Just looking up when I'm 10 ft behind this other woman walking by yourself at night
She turned around notice me and scream
And I was like
You right
She should have been
I had a gun cat no it's like
Horse babies age
Pictures of thing
Terrifying
When you're by yourself at night and there's
No one around
I'm a large man with a super comfortable
Doesn't put that thing together
If all of these women are terrified
Maybe there's a Justified reason
Right there's that too
I'm the reason we can't do that is because all of his fears
So there's that
We only understand fear from an irrational
Necessitate
Creating victims
He has to be
Important for him
To be on the side that is dominant
In many ways
Empathize
Having a legitimate
His
Survation very easily
Understanding
Dealing with it isn't possible
That's weird it's f******
It's so weird
And then
Because he's such a gross dude
He goes interview like
It's always the ugly one
Get a break
Experience the world that doesn't actually work
Like actually
Even more diluted because
It's rooted in his idea of like
Women flirt with me
Matter where I am no matter what time it is
I'm going to a hotel interview in like 8 I can't get my eyes off of you
Underlying
God forbid I'm black
Sprayworks
What
He spoke for a minute and a half there
They just Express
Ripon underlying racism misogyny
Disrespect
Disregard for people
Engage with people's
Subjective experience of the world
It was incredibly disgusting and he still has no idea why
Everybody hate them
0 ideas like what what what
My women
Domestic
.
You know what I said that possessive
A male chauvinist Pig
Defector by women
My woman
Not cool
Survival Instinct out of you
Feminism is being cowardly and scared and shaking five locks on your door
It's a woman
Karate chop
She's going to bite you
Scratch your eyes out of
Gilded chicken
Cowardly
Yuck
Another version of feminism
Maintenance man. Doing s*** like that
Way to respect
Casting
Going on
Right now over and over and over again
These idiots talk about Kavanaugh
The more they talk about this they're like
Oh they're just taking men's Bernardo
Just just
Turn it around for one second
Like they
You're unable to
The possibility of what you're saying
And then dismissed
Consider the possibility
Of what anybody else is saying
Cuz you only believe that cuz you were cut down raised like a little week
Requires domination
Feel like a man
Like that's it that's some sort of like an evolved
Lizard brain
Be able to murder somebody at any moment
That notary
Feel secure
You're not
Really
Empowered must have a submachine gun or you were willing
Bucked up
It's idiots
It's an insecure scared childish position
It's just it's gross to see it
Described
Women
Although I do love
Ladies like my grandma's my woman
My mom is my woman
Whoops
Oh man what a
F****** moron
A pretty dumb
The 12th
Opportunity to read this
Cam
And a lot of people
In the comments section saying
Nah
Nope
This pisses him
People.com
Call the phone number
They refused to come on
And we just rode up blurb their names what they told us
Bob Barr supporters
Constitution party supporters you are terrorists
Throughout
Call the phone
Okay
You're lying
And the reason is because he's misrepresenting what the report is
Evidence for the first time he can literally point to something be like
I have a real document
I can spread information that you literally cannot get anywhere else right now
Let's do towards the end of the miac report
Militia symbols
What are the headlines
Anti-government rhetoric
Militia members most commonly associated with third-party political group
It's not uncommon for militia members
Display constitutional party campaign for liberty or libertarian material
These members are usually supporters of former presidential candidate Ron Paul or Bob.
Again
They're not
You support your a member of one of these militias that there
Members of these militias
Ron Paul
This is
Vet this is
Really the sort of reasoning people in junior high should
This is
Ludacris
Getting on air
Suggesting to his
Like to read things
This report is staying
Ron Paul you're a terrorist and you want to kill
Because it doesn't say
Which it doesn't say anything close to that she is also
By doing that
Probably pushing more people to join these Berry
Oh you bet
We'll see look
The threat is real making it even more
That is correct
There is a certain amount of like Alex's own propaganda doesn't serve his best interest
Sandusky
70 not ours
He misunderstands the miac report
Even more brings up
His old rhetoric
To touch on for a second
In order to
To bolster
His misunderstand
We put this out with other
FBI training manuals
U.s. Constitution
This is specifically talking about FBI reports about Sovereign citizen
Yeah this is not talking about
RockAuto
Constitution
How's their behavior is generally
Bring up the Constitution don't make sense
That is something that is a threat
Because police have been attacked and killed
Traffic stop
Setup is unrelated
Do the larger issue of what you trying to come
Fields similar and Alex's
Kind of sympathetic to Sovereign
He brings it up in order to
We've this happen
Even if they're not violent if somebody believes that the sheriff is the highest law in the land
Beware
Prairie
Can existence
I also leaving with the sheriff is the highest
Whatever
Like if I believe that
Never affect
Because I don't have I don't
Run into law enforcement
I have a privileged position in life where and I'll run into cops
Breathing like that
I don't have to deal with
Dirt
Senators
So if I believe abstractly that the sheriff
Was the highest law in the land
I could just live my life
The problem is
The problem is but if you drive around
You don't have license
Place a driver's life
You're awesome
If you don't believe because you don't have license plates on your car
Then it's going to be
Become an issue
That's much more problematic
Justi
Quirky
Belief in the shower
Going to misrepresent
A little more
There's also Main Street Pub
And then they're secretly violence
Anybody
So this is childish
Thinking once again
Envy repair
Part of it
The entire thing opened
They talked about the organization
Number these militia
Events that are open
The Publican generally recruit public
These groups desire to
I'm sorry this is the sub-headline public
Yeah
Which is a subcategory of
Militia
These groups desire to Aid the county sheriff for governor in emergency such as a natural disaster it is not uncommon
For these groups
To be seen in public doing community service related work
Public groups are less likely to poop
Pushbullet
Militia
Never traditional military-style chain
Expanded leadership
These groups have been known to form underground units and provide training
And guidance
Do new or forming organization
These groups have been known to does not mean all of
Do that just means these group
You see a public group
That is into
Institution
Or Ron Paul
That doesn't mean that there
Does not imply that you
Then become suspicious
That they also have underground sale
The only way you
That is if you're warping
He should learn to read
So
In the interim
Between the 11th
The 12th
Alex
He's had Rob Dutra
Investigate this my Act
That must have been like a Three Stooges
He had one job and that was basically to confirm this and get some
Quotes from the Missouri Highway Patrol
No
He has a confirmation
That is a real
Document from talking to
To the people at the Missouri information analysis Center
Is what my ex
Express what he's worth
And then we see what
And I called him he's at the state highway patrol I want to see if you want to come on and talk about the report
Give me the date I said we got this in and if he's interested come on talking about we love to talk about and he confirm
That it was theirs and it's
He wanted to give me a quote
MBA
Any normal operation
Four officers
Pensive quote and quote
Safety purposes into track Trends or changes
And he said more but that's what I wrote down that's all I want to say that
Paraphrase reporters do that basically what else
So this is exactly what Alex did when Rob do talk to his investigating
This is what
I was trying to be a reporter
He's unwilling or at least busy
Inclined
To just embellish and make stuff up
Prob
Reporter
You don't have to have these standards that's
Not what reporters do
You can just say what did you feel when you were talking to him
Hey Rogers
Rub you rub you literally was just like
Analysis like
That's what I want from you the part that's making you do a terrible job is your inability to
Just Bluff
Just
Take the governor off
And start sucking
Pretty much all the stuff you'd already said which
Cuz they confirmed
Training
In law enforcement
And yours without
I respond
Alex
I said what he said
And now I'm going to continue I'm uncomfortable with the position you're putting me
There yet Alex
I'm not ready to lie I need to take UCB level 1 class
Flow with your b******* man
Yeah so
Eddie McGee
Frustrated cuz Rob do just repeat the same innocuous information that he got from the phone call and say this is how we respond
Now we already covered that was a short conversation
But you know
They don't want to talk about it they want to hide in the shadows
Give me the
Rob Kovach
We're going to get the head of HR
Fitbit next
And a teach you how to lie
Right
Get Buckley with a baseball bat keep you company
Just flap it against his hand
Although
Deception
Super funny
Keeps
You just won't go for it
Be exactly the same
Is like I said with his uncle
Situation
Just saying the quote has kept trying to get him
It's fascinating that he is such a bully
It's up
Exception
Which is understandable
It's a documentary release Alex's
Says the FBI's afraid of them putting it out
Ends up making a claim
YouTube channel
There's literally no
And by the way the Alex Jones Channel which was
We appreciate all his work
Number one
Paul Watson
The link
Bachata number one YouTube channel
Numero Uno
Uno
Very very very
I don't know how exciting it is
What are the number one channel
It's exciting
I am
I think we would be excited
More
I would be laughing I know yeah
I know ASMR I hadn't really taken off yet
I'm still going to go out of the Alex Jones Channel
They're actually
What is number one
I mean both subscribers most views what does it mean or what is it mean
He's being so vague as to it not being anything you could possibly look up
He doesn't have the most
Subscribers that is
Is that now that information public it was some kid
Skip-it 2009 was the
Does the number exact
Red
I missed out on a lot of Internet culture
Most downloads
Him either that that's not
The only thing I think
Is possible is because he's just
Release the documentary
Deception
It's possible that he's Rising
Through the ranks like maybe he got mostro through whatever
Yeah yeah those lines
Interpreting that as being the number one channel
You're number one in
Yeah there whatever that chart would be called
Are you saying
You're not
I bet
Excite even could be like
Just some random ass blog was like
My number one YouTube channel is out
Zenni Optical
It's possible that he's number one
Some sort of like subcategory
Like political Channel
Looking for books
Stuff like that
These crazy people like that Alex's
Are you
In the subcategory of like
Army
Survivalism
Breakdown of all the subcategories
Number 2014
Got to do better there
Anyway it's almost
Supercilious
It's all I mean it's just
It's almost with button
It's redundant at this point
Alex
Nope that would also be redundant.
Is about the miac report
This is really
The Narrative that he's going to put forth
In the future
It's taken shape already here on March 12th
And it's
Bully
Fully intact
Okay they didn't report that Ron Paul supporters are all day
The articles
So that's not if it's just not true
It's not true based on the report
And now that he's already put it out and that's his narrative
He's going to move forward with it to the point where
I remember episodes in like the 2015 stuff we're talkin about
In the past you've brought up the miac report
A childish
Rhetorical
It's entirely babe
On Alex not understanding
The rules of inference
And how language
That's all it is
Just saying
Most
Militia members
That we've studied
Support
Individuals like Ron Paul
Does not
Equivalates not be president of saying
If you like Ron Paul you're probably tear
Yeah
Just
Like this is why I talked about a lot
Maybe much more in the past
I still believe it
Essential education
For children
Has to be under
Understanding of
Has to be logic
Like those sorts of things
Part of every curriculum
For every kid growing up
Because if you understand those things
You can't be tricked
You just can't
If you understand
Baseline
Linguistics logic
Like not even Advanced predicate logic
You saying those words but if you just understand very basic
You can just go in and look at this and see like
Oh I see what they're saying
Cuz he doesn't
It allows you
To cut through the b******* you
You can parse the argument
Parse the sentence
And it's
Ez2c like
I wish I could just sit down and talk to you Alex
Do you know why
You're misunderstanding
Send a text that back realize
He doesn't care
Probably jr.
This one kind of leans towards the dumb Spectrum
For defensive
Are you at you and then like
Misunderstanding or how long for
Yeah
BFB I edit most racist wasn't even like
Black Panthers are violent terrorist
Everybody needs to be put in jail but they're not all violence
Sure
Darling
Jesus I'm excited because like I said earlier
Beginning
I am coming in
Next episode
March 3rd
Expecting it's going to be all more my exports.
I bet it's not I bet I'm wrong
I bet crazy
Hour-and-a-half of March 12th
Brings back onto the show
Doctor not dr. Rebecca Carley
Great
Is the doctors
Years before 2009
Had her license
To be trusted to practice
Anna public
Sheroes anti-vax movement
Because that same to look
Congratulations Alex
So much weird shift
I actually
Stepping back now I really don't think that I did a great job of explaining
Because quite honestly I could have done it
Much prefer
I think I could have just said
It's a description
Militia groups
1/4 minutes.
Commonalities Trends things that they've noticed
Albertsons misrepresenting it by trying to
To invert the logic
I'm saying that
Commonalities these similarities
If you have those similarities about you
You are that abolition
I think it's that simple
Explain it in like two or three sentences
Hey wife
It's not good because at this time and in the 80s
A lot of law enforcement
Infiltrated
These militia
There's a lot of
Militia groups there is a copper
Undercover just monitoring just like hey we know militia groups bomb places
Let's have a guy who's going to let us know
Like a lot of that whenever you talk about
The we stop this militia group from blowing up
Oklahoma City
That most likely because there was a guy in there providing information
It wasn't like a cop was walking by going like
Over there
Like these guys have Intel
It's probably part of what the miac report is written
Undercover
Sharing information about the different
Militia groups that there
That's why it's accurate sure the report is it prescription
Aren't like hey if you see a guy who is a sovereign citizen
Doing all of this stuff
But that's the thing it's not even prescribed
It's really just ripped
It's all just a study of the militia groups that they have
They have
Overabundance of information
And that's why when you look at this
Ashley 9 years later there is so much
Rings so true
Like all of you guys
You guys knew about this back then
Right
We should have done something
Infiltrated
Portsmouth and the military Arts
Crazy dance
Here's the thing
What they described in there
Is unfortunately also
It's true
Like the idea that people in militias that are dangerous
Support Ron Paul
Is true
Generally speaking
That is true
Zeitgeist
The Turner Diaries
An anti-tax documentaries like Aaron Russo freedom to Fascism
Is also
True
True true
True ohyeah
Shutdown
Nature Reserve
Will like nothing in here necessarily nothing in this
Rings
Think descriptively
False
Alex talks about like how we
Ties run pulse
Supporters in with whites
The part that they're talking about like milk
Wilton anti-abortionist
Christian identity
Members of the militia movement often subscribe to the ideology of other right-wing extremist
I meant describe Heroes
Is really bother
Because it's
It's so basic
If your
It's maddening because
It's such a low bar understand
Hahaha
40% of the country cannot cross
Alright
Yep
Dollartree.com
Probably
Direct Realty
Documentary
Contest
Toronto
That's up there on our Facebook
But no
2009 Alex Jones
Just a childish
Misogynist weirdo
There's also another thing about
What's up
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color