Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work
Alex
Oh no I think I just lost all back you are the world's worst
Do every question that I want to know the answer is that right
You would wanted to ask me
Swim first
Eclectic
Slime
Today
Two months ago before you started doing that
Michelle
Is today that I know a lot about Alex
That's correct
Episodes
To take a little moment to end up in supporting
First of all
Policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
We appreciate it very much
Welcome aboard
Seaworthy vessel
The fairy difference
We do not
Throw anybody off this vessel
But
Nautical Showdown
We got to give a couple
You were once
A policy wonk
But you are now
A globalist thank you so much Andrew
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
Bumped it up in your globalist
Even if you are Andrew right
Braham Elementary
Need to talk to somebody about that Andrew Guy
You cannot hear the name without getting mad about elementary school or some s***
Andrew has come from the larval stage grown into a butterfly that is a globe
Thank you so very much
You are now a globalist
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
Grow into butter
It requires a
A small amount
Caterpillar
Natureworks
Thank you so very much
I've been thinking about you
Beginning of H2
To the Izzo
You know that's okay
Listen to and
Spending that time
It means a lot
Take your time with us
We appreciate y'all out there
Anyway Jordan
Suck
Brick
We had a good run
No
Doing today quite frankly
And it's because here we are starting this is Monday episode starting off the week lot of the time
We'll start off with 1,000
Talk too much
Auburn
Some of March 2000
Alex immediately has jumped into
Territory
I am prepared to do the next 2009 episode without reading
A couple bucks
Because
He said some really
Pacific bulshit
Gets into some World War I need to dig my teeth into
Before we go over
Purcell
But I'm not prepared
Also I don't want to start the week off
For the project
Aw episode
Call Dad
Women either Spirits race so I was
Quite a quandary
To what I should
To do
I started
Attention
Thesaurus Smith
In other media
There's a number of other
Bow tie
Audi
Soros
This is just
Hey
New new updated version of
Going on forever
We talked about it a couple of years
I'm not saying that they haven't pointed out some stuff
Like that before but it wasn't new article
And there's another
Argument that
It could eventually
Called thesaurus era event
We make it out of this thing will look back and be like me
Thoreau's narrative in the same like
Kind of like
We will if we get our bearings
Things back because the Koch brothers will also have paid for the end of the world
Maybe we'll have
Things are Written upon stones
About the Jews
These articles and then there was also course
It was last week
Week might have been a little bit before that time
These days
Lawyer
The president of the United States
Retweeted about how soros's demonic
Adorable with socially are you telling me
Trump gossip trailer
We just all have to deal with it
Why are we even bothering
Throw
Throw tomatoes at him and then
Sure Kavanaugh hearings
With that
Court nomination there were a lot of people coming out of
Sometimes done
The idea that serosa
Does paying off
Which is been a trophy
If it's been used
Free single
Left-leaning
Cause
Of the last
Apartment the Parkland March for our lives
The women's March
Especially
The age of trump we've seen
Soros gets
Thrown under
This is all just because of his jumoney
Aruba subbed
Text that's what
Protests in a violent manner
You could even say
Cause physical harm to anybody who disagrees
But whenever say millions of women get together to call for an end to
What is Ben
2 million years of sexual abuse
70 something year old Hungarian
I started to realize that
We're going through 2009
And there is
Do you know.
The biggest
Reasons to do it
To find out when Alex started talking about
I meant secondarily what was the deal with
And so far we've gone through almost two-and-a-half months of
Beginning starting in January
He has not
Register
It's easy to forget
I forgot entirely what do you keep finding these weird things that happen
The avian flu
People like Rebecca Carly that show up to learn about
We have
Had a lot of things that have sidetracked Us in 2000
Focus health
Generally bent
Try and learn more about those two things
Essential
Things to nail down
In terms of figuring out
Who is really influential to Alex
Where are the
The threads
You can pull
Lead you to unraveling sweater
As opposed to
Just being like
So
We've gotten nowhere with either
Quite frankly
We've heard Alex
Bring up
Soros in two
But only because of
The one clip that
He's heard
He doesn't see
Seem to know Bowie
The really at all
So I'm
I want to know
I really do want to know these things
I'm not saying we're leaving 2009
But because
These
Stories are popping up
The mainstream Concha
Dismiss a lot more people to talk about it
I feel a greater pressure
To learn a little bit
And I decided
Skip to the end
I don't know the address that's the problem
I don't know what the end
What did you go with
Here's a f****** date let's see what's going on then
And the odds are that I would find some
But who knows if it would be
Useful
To Ferrari for me
I started to think that I realized the most
Disgraceful thing that's ever been done publicly
Media about
Is
On November 9th
Rudy Giuliani
That was that one
Scrapes
On November 9th
Glenn Beck air date
Tonight
Expose
Of George Soros the Puppet Master
Not the first time that George Soros
To come up
Boogeyman
But it was one of the most overt
And one of the most
Deeply a
He was pulling on Alt
Tropes from
They haven't necessarily
Eat when we heard Alex talking about that clip
In 2000
He's not talking about anything about Soros except for
He said he was going to crash oil when
He's not using any of his
He's like
Globalist
Blood-drinking poisoning the well
Protocols of the Elders of Zion
Inspired
He's not
He's not down that road at all
I believe a couple years prior Bill O'Reilly
Argan oil
Is Joe and pets
Scales
Glenn Beck
Zummo's
Flagrant
The most outrageous
Things that has ever been
Done
And the mentality that it embodies
Is exactly where I live
Call Jones's today
In terms of George Soros
Being the Puppet Master
He's the one who calling all the strings he's paying the protesters
He's Satan
He's behind Hillary he's behind Obama
All of that stuff
These spiritual
Or
Of What Glenn Beck was talking about
Tonight is that
Is where Alex Jones ends up
So
I thought it would be interesting
Listen to Alex Jones
Show
On those next day
The 11th
November 2000
What happened
Listen to that Glenn Beck a little clip of it
The 10th
Of November
Talk about
Is it all
You talk about TSA being
Evil people
And how are there taking pictures of your dick
It's not my favorite thing I will say that listening to it was a little bit
Because it was like
It was someone
Making an argument
I don't want to waste 3 hours
Here on the off-chance
The two hours into this you like you know who sucks Glenn Beck
And unfortunately
We didn't say a word about
3 hours left
Flown
Realize you're doing
Whatever
Profound talk
But
He does good at Miguel
Now that my
Sometimes because maybe hours
Giving him the benefit
You have a two-night series I'm not going to comment until the end
I highly
I doubt that
I think it just came to his attention
On the
Little bit of context
Here is a clip of Alex Jones
September 13th
Talking about his relation
What's George Soros
My mom always said PBS on cooking dinner
Directions to Monmouth football whatever she was always there
Gourmet food
It was always on PBS in
George Soros
The overthrow countries
He's the sweet little Nazi collaborator you almost kiss his little wart-covered booty
Implying Immaculate that he's known since childhood what is gourmet dinners
What is embalming even have to make gourmet irrelevant irrelevant
About doesn't also have to be legendary
Worthy of woman as we learned episode
Because he's a
Mom makes
Only coming from him in another context it might seem better
Far from the
The point is that
Expressing this idea that he's known about the Roses
Country collapser
Extraordinaire
I mean what would that be he was born in 1974
8 girlfriend country collapse
So what does that make we're in 20th actually on his business
2018 Audi
As a horrible
Currency
Destroying country collapse
Son-of-a-gun also on his business card
It's a long without the title
Here we jumping
Be November 11th
Episode and thankfully
The early in the episode
Alex
Cuz if you didn't I was going to throw something across the river
Today
Handle the New World Order
The Puppet Master
Not just because
Could guess that
Beforehand
I have multiple sources at the highest levels
You got mold
Predicted ahead of time that Glenn Beck would say that George Soros is
He has sources inside
Not inside the new world
Levels of the New World Order who are in contact with George Soros
All this information
Business execs at Fox
Blue dog
You get that information from
Page
Ohio level
Undercut his like predictive abilities
You saying like
So
I don't know if you
He's talking about Soros
Mikey talks about him now
Here in Twin
He's going to say Glenn Beck
Over exaggerating
Soros
Interesting you should think that's the way this is
Is going to go or not going to find out for now because I have to talk about how absurd
With Alex Jones
Glenn Beck
What would
I particularly don't want
But he's doing more harm
He's going to be
20%
18%
What's up what are you doing
Alright
For the guy who's supposed to be obsessed with you
You're the one talking about him a lot
No
That's true
To talk about him
Because he's always watching me
There's a little bit of that feel to that
But he's done something that's got him 80%
Is 80% on his side
He did this
I like him right with him 80%
I'd like to 80%
60% nonsense talk
Kismet meaning
But it does well I like that
It does seem to lead you to assume
After you know what happens the last
Year before this maybe Alex is already onboard with Soros being the Puppet Master
He predicted ahead of time because you know like
Affected any research this is what he would find
It turns out that what he liked about Glenn Beck
Here is what he has to say
About the idea of Soros being the puppet
I will reveal
Puppet Masters in 2 hours and 15 minutes
Give me
Give me a break
Wake me up piece of that George Soros bar
Is not the dark Sauron of the left
Give me a break
Since 1988 that George Soros was the biggest demon
Collapse
Goodnight
Is pretending that he's known for
He's giving himself a little bit of a mythological backstory
Whereas
We see here
Very clearly
Alex Jones
Is not on a George Soros tip
Herein
Yeah
Did anybody ever like
George Soros from the beginning
Was there like 60
Or is it just like somebody found out that a Jew was a billionaire so they were like what we got
Stop this
I think generally speaking as is the case with
The protocols of the Elders of Zion itself
There is probably a
A Russian influence that leads people down
Specific
The cast of
Destruction
Plot basically population
Wildfire
And in this case
It seems very clear that
One person in the entire world
Who would have a vested interest in demonizing George Soros
Is Vladimir Putin
Inasmuch
Is George Soros
The open Society
Have been in
Instrumental in trying to bring
Democracy
Do a lot of the parts
The former Soviet
He's he's trying to help
Democratizing
Liberate
A number place
Not by overthrowing governments
Do democratic
Innovation whether it's through financial support
Or logistical support giving them printers
Print off material
To give to people
That is one of his big
You things
It does make sense
Well it's impossible necessarily for us
Without knowing
Much more behind-the-scenes
No that is a very
Reasonable I think
Conclusion to make
Suspect number one
It demonizing Soros
Putin
It's clear is that here 22
Thesaurus
He is very much
Another tip
He's promised
At this point that at the end of the show
The truth
He teases that
Throughout the entire episode because of course he wants to stick around
Find lessons
We still don't know at this point
Okay
If you don't agree with his
You know a certain that Soros is the Puppet Master
What is it that you
About that quote
Glenn Beck
Text work
Let me find out in this
Has coming out and talked about government-sponsored terrorism
Prison
Why does the left knee this violence will listen to
From a democratic pollster mark
How can the left
Win country
Watch
Cabinet stones
Don't really sell thanks president of South have to reconnect for the people remember
Oklahoma
Obama needs a similar a similar
Obama needs a similar kind of
Event right
City
Come home
Then he'll politically be in good shape
All right there I get what you doing
I got it
According correct
Because
It's All Coming Undone this week
I will be the guy who causes the neck
Oklahoma City
Veteran appeal to advertisers
I'll Fox deerfox advertisers this part of it
No one
Left another Oklahoma City the next assassin
They are setting up
Another Oklahoma City
And they already
The one who caused it
But don't you miss Wednesday show
Buddy pal
Exactly where you should have in exactly the right way
What we have is two fundamental intentional misunderstandings that Glenn Beck is perpetuated
The first is in that clip which is from Hardball with Chris Matthews
This guy Martin is making the argument
Speech made after Oklahoma City
Event it
Yeah he was saying a speech like that
If you want to make that argument
He needs a moment of
Connection not necessarily that there needs to be a terrorist attack
Buddy buddy pal
You are
A part of the system
To be radicalized in such a way that leads
This person thing the next time something happens
Will have blood on their hands
Is Knox
Preemptive blaming for a false flag attack
It's
Warning people logical consequences of the rhetoric
Demagogue
Inflamed
White nationalist
And have the capability
They're usually the ones pushing people towards the capability
Sort of modus operandi is also 2
I'm inflamed feelings of deprivation or victimhood
That are lying right behind or perceptions of equality
And plurality
Which is a good game because it's very profitable to assholes
I am making
Terror attack
And because
Can stay there
Planning
In order to blame
Right
By being guilty of it I can claim that I am guilty of it
Brighton State and it works really well
Really well like it almost
Cannot be
Coincidence
Unintentional
Can't wrap my head around the idea that they would just
Jambalaya backwards into something Ironclad Behavior
InTouch way it's amazing
It really it really
My hat
Bora Bora
Stupid right and propaganda
These are the two
Like really essential misunderstand
Alex
Transversal
Reversing the association
Of the logic of
A lot of people who are in militias like Ron Paul
Demon
The same sort of misunderstanding is being done here
It willingly with this Hardball clip where the guy is saying
Bill Clinton
People back on his side with that great speech that he gave
Praslin back is arguing
Do we need a terrorist attack
People backs
Can get
It's okay
The government which is the misrepresentation
If I had to guess I would say that Alex's theme be tremendous
Glenn Beck has been having
Since 2009
Because of the like freedomworks money that's blowing into him
Because of the 912 movement because of the Tea Party
And I think that Alex
Probably like
There's a way that I can have an olive branch
I can say that
Another Oklahoma City let's see if I can get some of that money
I think that's kind of what's going on I'm getting released the vibe
Like that I wanted play this next
We aren't being unfair
Not interested really talking about Soros
I can find no fault with what he's doing other than the fact of
Roast
Puppet Master
They are getting ready to stage
Fair enough
Coffee with way too much milk
You piece of s***
Find no fault
Glenn Beck Behavior here in November of 2010 with the exception of
Of him saying that
He should have just said all the juice
Not just one
Lame
Clipit Alex play it is obvious interview on Hardball with Chris Matthews
Mark
And
Previously posted
Glenn Beck
Right
He's not mad about
He's not he's not really mad.
He f****** do we post that photo
Mischaracterizing
Cinemark 10
Exciting
On Monday
National Television
So you called him a Clinton
Kind of app
Problems
References
From Clinton campaign and is also a Democrat
The Sara Lee mean they are excellent
November 2010
MARC Penn was the chief strategist for Hillary Clinton
2008 run
Barack Obama
Guy out of nowhere
For a bit but then
I'm reading from source
On April 4th 2008 The Wall Street Journal reported Colombia's ambassador to the United
States on Monday to discuss
Apache the presidential candidate
Hillary Clinton opposed it
So
It turns out
This company that he works for
Would you call
Lobbying group
Text Kristen marsteller
Had been contracted in 2070 Lobby for Columbia on behalf of that by
Bilateral
US Department of Justice filings disclose it in March 2007 VM
Marsteller
Hundred thousand-dollar one-year contract at the Colombian Embassy
In March 2007 the managing director of burson-marsteller
Washington Regional Office in chairman of its issues and advocacy practice Roberts
Columbia
So
What was going on is this Mark
Was meeting with Colombian
It is at the embassy
The Colombian ambassador
Under the
His job with burson-marsteller in order to work on trying to
Path to this bilateral trade
That Clinton was supposed to
He was the chief strategist
4 at the time I'm not sure but it is very
Inappropriate on April 4th
2000 when the Wall Street Journal reported on it
You got that right
And so he gets kicked out as her Chief strategist
The meeting was an error in judgment and that will not be repeated I'm sorry for it
The Senators well-known opposition to the trade deal
Probably alive
Would modify the Clinton campaign But ultimately
I also
Columbia took offense to Penn State
The Columbia government considers this a lack of respect to Columbian
Response unacceptable
I'm a big fan of everybody
The guardian
Yeah because he was still you still like a fairly credible pollster
And like pulling out
This guy even after that
Used some of his pulling data
What is a high-level strategy
And he got booted for all this s***
He's not a very big Fall From Grace
Some sort of a liberal or anything like that
Is kind of disingenuous because he has links to let's say big
Tobacco
Anti-union causes
Did Hitler
He has a deep history of working against
And lobbying against
What are
Traditional
Liberal colleges
I don't feel like
Inasmuch as he's on Hardball with Chris Matthews
He is
A talking head we talk
That's what he's doing
We we need a terrorist text get Obama up in the polls that kind of a speech
Bill Clinton gave in 95 after Oklahoma City
On as one of
The great speeches especially of our lifetime
A galvanizing moment that brought people
Altogether
So
I don't know
Even to Alex's
Pretending video
Nautical inn
You can't even get your Clinton pot shots
You can't say that he was an Obama strategy
Just cuz he was on the team that was against Obama in the primaries
Anyway
This is all to say that
There's very little for me to look into Ennis episode so I had to look
This this is all the say that
The chief strategist
Clinton's campaign
Associated with a lobbying firm in DC
Good graces of the Colombian government
Jessica
So in this position
I want to play this little 5-minute video, me
This Edition is carrion crow
On the left side
Carrion crow
PBS documentaries whereabouts
Whenever his mom was making those Gourmet balser bring his girlfriend over
They got PBS on there
PBS geyser
Just going like
Again tonight
Soros
Joshua
Make an argument that Alex
I would probably
Try to make
He would say that in 2010
What's the acceptance
Heroes through the ranks
Later
And the argument that I would make to that is easy
You study things the way
You have all this inside information
You would know in 20
The George Soros with earmark
To be the next
Puppet Master
Because this operation does not operate without a clear
Chain of command
There's not a
Continuity-of-government
If you allow that term to be used here
What are you say
Leadership of the globalist
I don't think they exist
What is Alex's version
Leaderless resistance kind of
Model absolutely hierarchical
2 is the answer
Someone at the top
Who else is going to review
This episode
Those guys all have a
DeKalb underneath
Sprite
Do a certain extent there's circles within circles
Inner and outer circles
Stuff like that
Besoros
Right but right now it is stopped
Could be anybody
I must
That there is literally no way Alex
Can make the argument
Do you make
The world
That don't include that
If Soros
Puppet master of few years later
He would have been earmarked
It's not like whenever the Dalai Lama dies I got to go find them
With the globalist leadership structure
They know
Isn't there another guy
Which is probably better position to be in
Let's
You're not you're not
No way too much like
No accountability
But how many of those guys
Afterwards
I f*****
Broad Promenade
Brewing to accept
Buyer's remorse on the Dalai Lama
Grad school
Pennywise
Alex
The big good
That they're going to Stage the right way
And actually that's a little bit of a
Tell on Alex
How excited
He is the Glenn Beck said this on his show
Because I was also on this shows that Glenn Beck has three million viewers
Glenn Beck with three million viewers is saying this
He has less
Could say that
Property
Lucas Pizza
He also Alex Alex also realizes
If going back is staying
Bet the government
Is going to
Do another Oklahoma
City
Make fun of other things I say
Because now is glengoyne
Whoa
In 2010
Alex is critical of Glenn Beck
Because
Has a religion of hating Muslim
It's almost like everything he was mad at Glenn Beck about in 2010 is exactly who he became
The other religions are Muslim
He believes the George Soros is a puppy
Glenn Beck is obsessed with him
Unc's convex
Out of all the time
Sure Alex wants to be him with his listenership Alex is gradually turning into him in order
But that's because I don't think it's forwarding listeners
I think
Quite frankly
It's
Money
And whoever was
Influencing
Glenn Beck
Alex want
Piece of some of that simple
Or those people is already
Yeah and Alex
Maybe if it's point doesn't
Realize that
These are
Two hands of
Anybody going back or both being used
In order to radicalize the right-wing
Possible
Incredibly likely that the reason
The Glenn Beck goes this path
And then veers off
Last year was on Samantha Bee Apollo
Call Jason for s***
Because that gravy train ended for him
Whoever
Was trying
To get him
To do whatever he was doing
Decided he was no longer effective in what we need him
Interesting
Alex Jones
Become
Him
Suspiciously
Almost
Is the new Glenn Beck
Baltimore
I don't know though
Dark Horse
Leader of the
The globalist
Mark Patton
Now
No I would like to be like you to give some
Legitimate
You'll never be able to guess
Suicides at the top
But I think
The round button
Quite frankly
Yeah
What about wrong
Tableland
Farted in Obama's face
Does it come up once
Nearest Obama
Okay
Nobody would ever
To be a puppet for the puppy
Master narrative
Plus that's one of the central conceits of the Obama
And it can't be
Still bva the Rockefellers
Isn't like cuz that's
Boring and not sexy
Throwing Soros in there
You can't then throw the Rock
Fellers back
That's no fun you're going back don't have Soros throne
That is true
Hey bad news
It's the Rothschilds and Rockefellers
Creative
Progression that is able to do on his own
Because
Thinking person who's ever lived
You are so should know that
Also
That's not who he says is at the top
It's pretty crazy
It would be absurd
For him to be the Puppet Man
George Soros is a bad guy
Exciting
Is it
Depop
The 80s movies
That guy who had madame
The puppet battle flowers
Is not is not whoever used
Howdy Doody
Navigate
None of those pompous of gold
Nope nope
No there was a ventriloquist
Syriza ventriloquist
I don't remember if there was ever actually
Ventriloquist
Did those or if it was just the
Builder Hatcher Bennett
Involved
Diesel power
The spirit of stories involving Trula quisim
Situation without
That's where all ventriloquism acts are
The ventriloquist says dirty s*** in the games the puppet
Of course that's supposed to be about
Any does the voice of something else
So crazy
So
Soros is a globalist
Sure
Fine
Yeah but he is
It would be
Razee
To call him
Crazy
Alex is like
So bad after all
And now he's being set up
For the next
Buildings
Dot-com
You will see a banner
Solutions
Fox Karambit
Stop
Emerson wave catcher
Using material
That is not a cooking knife friend that is a 7-night
Cool cool cool cool
People who are super that I am with guns
Because most people who are super into knives are just like those guys who are like
Creepily in the butt nonviolent
Around New York with a sword over the weekend
Yeah I do
To hang out with one very much
But the people who are into knives are usually like
Simmering
Willmore outward
Supernanny
Better
Display rooms than the
The gun display
You know what I mean like
When you go into a nightmare fuel to
Craftsmanship
Poquoson denies and stores and
Words like what are you going to do with gun
I forgot
Parks
To make it all that aesthetically pleasing
Urien no matter what
Making you a nice that's a nice
Come on to make me
Alex
Is very clear
About
He's possessed
Most
To the rest of the clip
Are going to
Just Berrian
Yes
Soros is not
They had the
Globalist
He is
Down the totem
He's not important
And
We'll deal with why he
He's saying that at the end of
Cuz I think there's actually
We've hit on a couple reasons
But I have an overarching
Siri
There's a little bit of that
A outbreak more about his mole
Exactly
We are the true Liberty Movement
If you immerse yourself in
Start focusing on what you're doing is patient
Bulshit
What are you saying there is
Is so invalid
Tony bowls cuz I know everything
If you know what's happened
Then you should have been like you know what
He's wrong
Cirrhosis
He will be right in the future
Keep stressing
If Alex has real information
Then this shouldn't be this
Response
Soros isn't important
HEB
He's in line but
He's still waiting for the Old Guard 2
Disappear
Rebuttal
Alright let's talk
Stalin
The globalist
New World Order
Instead of
Earmarking Soros
Further
Right
The chance to pick a
So now all of these guys
4 position
Killing each other
Tipsy who's the globalist learn from the lessons
And now Heather
Rigidly hierarchical because of my
Everyone has learned lessons
I always equip Alex Jones
How exciting is that quick prepares
To reveal
Who is
At the top of the pyramid
Yes
The real
The progressives
2 days ago
Years ago
Create a blog
Write the end Alex
Clearly watch
Some of Glenn Beck's show is like that
I really like that chocolate
Whataburger
Becoming the neocon
That's all I
There's so many lines I could draw
Soros is a
Step above that you can only have four to six servings
But who is at the top of the pyramid Alex would never say this sort of thing about like
Now
Weather
If you have any kind of intellectual consistency
Body don't
Now we
We get to the reveal
Is it the top
Bill Belichick
Okay
What a disappointing reveal
Entire show
Exciting Federal Reserve
Docu
The Federal Reserve is what does everything
Everybody all the globalist to Alex's worried about their religion
The bidding of the Federal Reserve
Because the rotate
Have to be part
Play can't be the puppet
Is like
Stafford
You know regardless of what administration is in office
They're always there they're like a vice president
Bugle
And play I think I
Someone
4 steps down the hierarchy of the Federal Reserve is actually exactly
That is an essential piece of this
It if you are the head of
The Federal Reserve which is
The top of the globalist New World Order pyramid
Your job only last
Years or whatever
Vivint Soros would never get the
Never never
The idea that the Federal Reserve is the Hat
Is what he saying
In 28
Years prior
Soros
Never been
But it's suspicious
The Federal Reserve building
Is appear
So here's where George soros's
George Soros
But above him is Henry Kissinger
George stults
Middle-management operation
Work from time to time
He's middle-management type
The people above him
Even a plainclothes manager at Footlocker
He still has to wear
I still have to wear it
Is where we get to know who are
Important
Is Rothschild family
They're all right
With the leaf
Others
Scoreboard cartoon
Controls the strange
Enter the nation-states and the petty regionally
Trilateral commission meetings up here and endings
So if you hear it is an oligarchy
A tube
But if you
If you hear what you saying are you saying at the end of sauros people like him on his level
Who just get brought around so they can feel important
Hanging out at lunch today Bohemian Grove
With people who really do matter Bilderberg Barnard's Offspring or whatever
Even if I was a
Rockefellers Rothschild soup Airport
Specific
Of the New World Order
Okay
David Rockefeller
I think you said that before I did it again it's just
It rolls off my back
Omnibus
Before but I think you said ombudsman
Let's try it
I just didn't catch it because he's allowed
You say that it's not like
Consistent
Miss you
You know like it
Pronounce one day that's wild
That's crazy nobody is it correct
Cowboy
Exit
He pronounces it every time
Going on
What does he always say for all intensive purposes
I don't think he's ever said
Child Federal Reserve is at the top
Is how Alex closes things out on his show
Disparaging George Soros
Even more in this
4 minutes out
3 hours
Yeah probably 4 minutes real time
Neocon
He's got to go
I would like that
But yes it was services in the servant class
You billion dollars would be really bummed
YouTube
The Richmond
The numbers game
Secret society never get to party like that
I just want to go to a bar and get drunk
It is very similar to RiverWatch
John Hodgman
On The Daily Show
Billionaire character appearance
That deranged billionaires
5 + 10
Jon Stewart
Going up there like
Who does the menial tasks
You're not going to do that when you're up there
I'm a player
Like a montage of clips
Commercial space travel for millionaires
Implying that the millionaires
Your rights always a package
Be wildly disappoint
And I think very unlikely
So now
We have to ask ourselves a little bit about the timing
Because
Where in November 2010
And this is really about a week after the midterm election
So what happened if you don't recall
Is in 2008
And there was a lot of
5 seats
Blue Waves
A bit of a blue whale
What happened in 2010
Dualistic mentality largely from
Look up brother Sheldon Adelson freedomworks
Prospero
A sound economy
Which is what became freedomworks
Right
Because of that influx of money propagandist like Glenn Beck
But they paid for Sean Hannity
The movement
Became so
Heavily covered by the media
We end up in the situation
Here where
The Senate
Republican
Game 60
The house
The game
And the game 6
Text governorship
The Republic
Completely destroyed
The game
In 2010
They took over every
That is why we are where we were
Because when they take over every
They immediately set about sucking everything up
Kind of been trying to close those doors
So it can't
I'll be done to that
Over everything
We are about whether or not we compromised
Well we have to do this based on a republican plan
That way the Republicans will support it
Interested in bipartisan
Well the reason that I bring this up
Edsby
Cuz
The situation that we have is very similar to the situation that we see in 28
Inasmuch as
The midterm election
Something happened
Continue your rhetoric
You know needing to fight
And all that stuff
When you have just one every
So we have
The house and the Senate and the governor house is all going.
Deeply Republican
In 2010
And if you're someone who is a partisan
What you need to do with evolve your narrative into something that's much more Insidious
Your enemy isn't
The Democrats because you've already beat them
You have all the cards you hold all the power
And you cannot be
Realistically
You can't blame them
Four things that don't work out and cover
Because your team can just do anything
And so
In order to keep
Propaganda machines going
And to keep this working in the prophets coming in
You need to create a deeper narrative
And that's weird
That deeper narratives that Glenn Beck
Chose to do is this George Soros is
Behead
Of the
Deep underground secretive New World Order stuff that's really what the problem is
Right
Certain extent
Because the New World Order the idea that
Behind the scenes
There's all these Shadows
Trouble
Is when we look at the parallels
To the modern day
After the 2016 election
That is where
Alex
No longer had any
He's guy is now in office
The Republic
Controlled both houses of Congress
Wasn't
He's in 2018
In the exact same position
Glenn Beck
Was
In 2010
He was the propaganda
Glenn Beck was the propagandist in 2010 it was leading this tea parties s***
On board with it even though Sean Hannity and Rush
Were
You know at least mostly in favor of it
He was the figurehead of it
To Great degree
Cuz he was willing to embrace what it was really about
Racism and
Conspiracy
And he was wholly funded by the people who were pushing
Rush Limbaugh
But they still have some autonomy they didn't
Have almost
Entire ownership
Yeah so the reason that this isn't
The same position
Glenn Beck was
We still ramping up
Thesaurus stuff
Is there before now anytime anything goes
Anytime there's a
Left protest
You see Soros being blame
Much like Glenn Beck
Jump the shark
In 2010
November 2010
With this Soros
Alex is in the middle of a very extended shark jump
That he's doing
With every single time
There's something
Oh my God look at these contracts I found on Fort and approve the Soros
Is funding antifa
Exactly the same
We see a 6-year mirror
Here is Glenn Beck
Alex Jones
We look back and see what Alex Jones
In 2010
We see him saying
You sir
Are a fool
Alex I would ask you to look in the mirror and see some of yourself in the past
Calling yourself a
Republican
Actually already
Fred Meyer preme
Allowed to look
In the mirror ever
Behind
I think
Yeah
How to put a button on this I don't know what I think I don't know exactly what conclusions can be drawn
From their butt
It's weird
It's very weird
We can safely draw this
Alex Jones
Is going on
Man something is rotten in Denmark
Expression
What's the temperature
What's going out in Denmark it ain't no good
I said out initially looking back
Deeply Patty
So if
You go back to the point where
Glenn Beck does his presentation
Soros
If he was already talk
That would trigger him to the point of screaming the
The entire show about how Glenn Beck
Is ripping me off this is my s***
Of course so I knew that if you want talk about it
Response and if he wasn't talking about him
Is there
He would need to be like I know more than you
Of course so the conclusion that we come to
The latter is
He doesn't think that
Cirrhosis
A big bad guy
And that means
Investigation in 2009 wheat to find out the tea party stuff
But that's the question would not be answered until
So that question
I don't know what we're going to do with that
And saved us a lot of time
I don't know if I did
Conclusion is
It's not 2,000
I don't know how to
Live without just saying
Doing here my dear
Here's my
We've been trying Proto
What if we try
Their own
I don't like where you're going with it I really don't like it
On TV and I say
You're right
We have been paid by
But the only reason we've been paid
Is because we are
Not being paid enough by all of these bosses
Where's the same time those bosses
Is our pain
Senators
Who's really getting paid more money as its approach
And the Senators are the ones who are directing
They're the ones who are secretly controlling
So you have to say that the Koch brothers
Secretly controlling Trump
And you can't trust them Trump
We actually all
Protesters
But he doesn't know it because he's being convinced
We can convince him
That was really going on is that the Koch brothers are laughing at him
Just like when he was a millionaire in New York City and all of the big
They were like
Oh he's a McDonald's billionaire
Nothing still doing that to Trump
Listen to us
Then I can just say you conductor that audio that's bulshit they all that s*** up
Truck can only trust us
We're the only ones you can trust because
We admitted it we admitted that we got paid by George Soros
And then you say all well
They're mad they're mad because your money
Play we all know this to be true
Exactly
So that's how we do we are only Isaac
Just confusing enough to work
Have we tried cheating
We got to try
Why not
You still think that
Cheating
Even if you believe
Is that the end result is good it's still like
Sort of
Take away people's rights
Will
I'm not trying to
Trump Evan on TV
Every time
It's like I'm talking to Rachel Maddow possibly believe that
I will continue on with this week
I'll give it I'll give a big old winkle be like
This is
I was I was scratching my eye that wasn't awake you're still going to end up inadvertently tricking a lot of pictures
See this is where you getting to real Danger
Creating a mythology that will run away from you in a way that you can't control
Brothers created
Party got out of control
Control that anymore
You would face sort of weird blinking mythology
Maybe some sort of like a demon side
You can't prove that
Careful back on YouTube trust me
From my resort to these people
You can't prove that he's not a deterrent
Empath
We cancel each other out
I don't know what to say I hope your plan works out
November 11th
Send Alex Jones
Does not care about Soros at all Glenn Beck
He's misunderstood
Is nice
Thinks he's a fool
Taking thesaurus
The Puppet Master
Of the New World Order
The Rothschilds and Rockefellers
On that
Frog
Crazy
Anyway we're website.com
Knowledge
What if you wanted to find us on social media
Underscore fight
Is there another one
Is there a smaller place
One of those social media Networks
Could you find
Subscribe
It would be really nice but you know it's not
What's that
I know Glenn Beck
Hasn't killed
We don't know that
We don't have
Do you know they're probably killed a guy
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color