Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Dan
Question today
When was the last time you yourself tortured in
Dismember to journalist never never
University of Missouri
I wrote for my camper
Rosen College
I would routinely go to
BJ's
Is the is the building at all the journalism
Apartment buildings
He was my roommate at the time
We are a couple tiny dicks
And get a 12 pack
Debeers
At the house watching
Mostly the same rap videos every weekend like I was raised in the project
Project Pat good googly-moogly by Project Pat
When you go with one and then two to the answer is eight or nine
This whiskey I know you take the 12 pack and go crash parties
Man I
I could have been like I wasn't a dick to people but I was
Inept yeah I was going to say unskilled I was just
There was like a sensitive like
Sirius Force
I write for your paper and you even know who I am
And there was f***** up by the time I got there
It was that it was not the best time but
Fond memories
I stopped
Anybody
Shouldn't admit this
One-time weekly idea dismember
Jump in the air and fart midair so I could fart on some
Now closed
Do not torture
Is a
Coronavirus 19
Excel
If you're in Missouri at the
Sure anything about Alex Jones but now I know a lot about him
About Alex
Chicanery
Mr Mario Party
I regret that very much
It wasn't that terrible
Time out of my personality and character
15 years ago that's hilarious if you done it like party last week
34 control
People shirt
Really fun apps to do before we get to it I would like to give a couple
Thank you not at all well
To join up and support the show we appreciate them oh so very much
First of all thank you so much
Do Travis
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Travis
But I'd like to do
For someone who took their donation and bumped it up a little bit
Crk
But also they gave they definitely used a fake
Email address
I generally don't pay attention to people's email addresses
Notification
Supported the Shelf
Fake email address
Not as dropping
Alright cool a Charming 2
Pump it up a little bit out of you are now a global
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
Now Jordan special
These here parts
Then what we get to do is we get to induct
Sport the show ended
Appreciate
Just very nice emails
Very much
From the bottom of our Alex Jones
And propaganda filled hearts
We like to say thank you so much Chris
You're now a wrestler princess
Dogs get mad and tell her you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
How to read
Control
I bet you money are few living black people have been abused by white people
Joseph Stalin
Scott
Appreciate
45 seconds
Wacky Wednesday
Very exciting
Got to tell you
Straight up
Jerry Cassidy went back to Vacaville
Talk to Mark
Time for
Installment 90-man of horses possible
What more can you buy Aladdin
Actually there is some new information here and one of the things that she
Same goals I think that she had was
To like run other
People stuff
By him
To fact-check.
With him which seems like a Fool's exercise quit
Your heart is in the right place I don't know if it is but if I have to
Fall back on
How do I know if she went there if he doesn't give her any
Nustep I'm positive
She did go cuz she spends about 5 minutes
Was told that her outfit wasn't appropriate
Okay fair enough you can't make that s*** I was like I'm not allowed to wear high heels because that's considered a weapon
I get inside and I see other people in high heels
Maybe she's a higher standard of security
Seen you talk to this guy and other times
This isn't for anybody
But you
You're going to hurt yourself
With those shoots closet later
You are f******
Nothing this would be the place to do it if ya really make
So Jordan we've got installment 9 of
Oster price
Blotchy calls
Total Recall
Because
Track
In prison
Because he killed a guy murder murder
Live
Mysteriously
So she goes
I'm waiting for
No Saudi Arabia was off-planet at the time
She's allowed to use recorder when she goes an interview
Please mark she's allowed to sometimes
She writes
Bizarre stupid questions
I get to enjoy
I'll say this door night I sort of references as you
You came
Department today
I worried that we wouldn't be able to do an episode
When I was listening
To this
Yeah
Earlier
Kinda is boring is she
Little bit boring
I listened back to it again
Was just my first
You know sometimes you read a book first-time through doesn't grab
To realize some of the nuances
Literally everyone feels about a separate
I don't know anything about it
I can tell you
New fiery before we go any further
New Theory
Alright
The prison itself
0 limitations on what sort of recording devices that you are allowed
Okay
Mark Richards
Is f****** with
And he is convinced a few of the guards
To go along with
I'm not sure I did actually find
It's not specified either way or not you can have a pen
It's not lip pencils and pens are not listed in
Approved
Material but it's also not listed in like
I don't know I can't say either way
How do I
Restart this episode as we start every Project Camelot episode with introduction
To her
Project Camelot
You go over
The notes from my recent interview with Captain Mark Richards the secrets we
Song of the Dutchman and I believe in this
His grandfather would have
Now I understand it'll light not have listened to our Pact
Adventures
With Mark Richards
Before she gets into
Carrie gives a little bit of a breakdown of
The relevant information you need to know
About
Recently went to interview Captain Mark Richards who has been involved in the secret space program since he was a young
Child actually
And his father was also involved as well as his grandfather if I understand
And his father was known as the Dutchman he was
Quite famous in those
Save the world
Multiple database program circles if you want to call it that the military
As well as in the British in Britain with the British and so
Has a long history as I say with regard to the secret space program
He
Basically grew up in
Basically grew up and he's like a Jonathan Taylor Thomas
Why is that the only child actor idea why that happened he grew up in Show Business
Jonathan Taylor Thomas
Absolutely awesome career
Odd Squad
Carrie sort of really understanding this Richards has been involved
Space Program
The kid
He also had like we reference
B of A sentient spaceship named Minerva
Can fly around it
He is married to a lady named Joanne Richards
It goes around again
Peaches on his behalf
An actual real person
A human being and not part of the grand mythology
Photo married to Minerva in
Confirm is the Cheese's
PA
The rest of the stuff is I think she's being tricked by her husband
Is she
No idea
Never find
We need to hire her
Mythology
To know is that it
Because
Was
The orchestrated the murder of a guy who
He got
Do kids who worked at tire shop I believe
Something along those lines
Sea-Doo from that you offered them $5,000 in
A car a car Pursuit
When the murder was committed
And I date
So
Seems like
Cost more than that and yet it never does
You know
AAA
Really cheap
You know
Of the job
Needs to be done
Is it function of the desperateness of the
Your lawn mowed for like $200 by a profession
No crew or
$3 to
To the neighbor kid
A meme for $200
Can convince the neighbor kids
To kill the professional long possible I take over the business
From living in reality that Mark Richards
Straight up did that s***
As far as I'm concerned he's one of the best
Whistleblowers out there
The fact that he is in prison and has been for over 30 years
Is what the
Powers that be considered to be
Sufficient enough to discredit him
So that he will not be believed
So he is at Liberty to tell me quite a bit of information that you can't get anywhere else
This is how we work the sort of rationale
He's in prison
He's been discredited so much that it doesn't
Matter who tells the truth
No one's going to believe him cuz he's
Murderer
So the powers-that-be are like whatever you want big guy
Have fun there another
Even if he had murdered zero
And we're free
I would say so I mean
There's a little bar for Carrie
Episodes with Carrie talk
I have a hard time believing they are not
Eligible for
Do you know what I mean like if anybody really wanted to look into it
Every single item probably of tax crimes in there in the past
The delowe
Low-level
Almost all of them I would say
Have
Maybe a civil fraud case
Go to prison
They all should be sued by somebody
So anyway Marcus guilty of this
You're being orchestrated murder but turns out
She is innocent of the crime
Infor and as I say spent over 30 years paying for a crime he didn't commit
And he is
You've been in prison
Like
Two months shorter than I've been alive
He was 19 years into his presence
Let's
Said to be the Mastermind
Two other people who actually committed the murder
One of them got out off
I guess bye
The other one
He cut a deal because he was like oh my God I'm going to be in prison for the rest of my life
I will cut a deal
Very common
As well as Mark
And now this guy whose name is cross and David
Uber
Apparently is
Talking to a journalist too
A radio talk show host in Britain who has decided to make a documentary
Supporting
The murderer
Against Mark Richards
I was promised them that they would be nice if
After
Is the murderer ended up taking over Marin County
It's amazing I can't wait for
I would love to hear what you told these kids perspective
Viking what they
Experian
Girl no
Throwing caution to the wind
To be fair
It is in the next clip carry will explain that Mark can't talk about his legal issues
And
Kind
Mark Richards has been working with the lawyer
Which is long overdue
And this
Happening on the side is is not a good thing obviously
A documentary that is supposed to
Being negative influence I guess on the public
Attitude towards Mark but nonetheless
What's happening now is that they are not able to talk to anyone about the
Simply because they are involved in
Guy with a lawyer in getting a commutation of his son
Hopefully that will happen
Doubt it
Call Richard you better have the lawyers
He has life without parole
From what I understand the guy
Committed the murder
Has the possibility of
Parole
So I would say
The f****** psycho
Yeah I think the facts
The case bore out in such a wave
Who's the most dangerous here who has the potential for rehabilitation
It's scarier that the kid would actually was the one who did the murder
That's scary
You would think that
Come with a heavier set
At the same time
I think that is probably
Pretty reasonable at this point 30 years later 34 years later
Affect
Kid now
An adult has
Rehabilitated
He's not going
Commit another murder unless another Mark Richard Getz
So like
The idea that that kid could get out and Mark can't
I'm fine with
So I belittle
Knows so much more about
Cakewalk prison
I bet it's
And may our story I could find was from a couple years
It was like a big fight
Broke out in the prison in the aftermath
A guy
Who was cut in half
Totally specials
The whole process what is totally
Guy in half and stuffed in like somebody
Disposal
Well that's right to hide the bodies in the investigation they found a couple of his organs were missing
From the articles I could find anywhere so I didn't.
Didn't look too deeply into this I'm sure there's a resolution somewhere put the stories that I really like
No one knows what happened what
Alright
Here's our plan
We're going to sell a liver
Why not
40 feet of
But we got to start a huge prison fight
This is Ocean's 11 but it was one
Fairmount of like lockup
This story was like
What the f*** I think I want to learn more about the
Related to work I'm supposed to be doing
Get I kind of get wanting to
Pretended imagine
Fantasize about the ID
Commuted though you're living in that sort of a
Mark was at
But that's terrifying
Who did it
I don't know
The f****** lieutenant
No no Mark Richards best because
Minerva
He's off of Oregon
She needs a few organs and he was like listen I can get my hands all over
You got to cut a guy in have I was
Praying
Not praying
Make me happy but
I was kind of interested
Recognize any
Players in this article
Like the guy who died
Related to Mark Richard
I'm more interested now in like being called
To deposition
Commutation
We have brought in
2 random ass guy
Do you guys feel like
I suppose we have to have a
WYD
All right there wouldn't be a commutation hearing because there's no
Hearing it's Justin
Governor Whitmer
Or something like that
Commuted
Because Carrie knows something
Terry knows something she's gotten some information
About the future of Mark rich
For those of you that know that I interviewed Simon parkes
Many times and recently used to be a council person and
You carry who would like two or three times a year would leave and have sex with
By far the most heroic character on Project Camelot
And more than once he has said that Mark Richards
Will likely be pardoned very soon
As a result
After what
What is basically the indictments that are going through right now
So the indictments are being pursued there something like 40,000
According to Simon parkes once those
Mike Richards will be
So
Alright
Is it
Hunan's conspiracy in the
Excited
About it is
The part of the narrative is
Is that the justice department
Filed 4050
Sealed indictments
Shoulder just ready to go
And that's why they keep making all these stories up about like Hillary Clinton
Leaving the country before these
Indictments get on co2 cuz you know she's going away forever once I do
Shirt so that's
That's a big big
Piece of the Q10
Non-Stop
These indictments are going to come down they're going to roll up all the
Evil forces and government
Part of that Trump is going to
Mark Richards
For some reason why not because he knows about the
Trump knows that's why he's doing space force as f****** Mark rich is going to be the head
Alright
One thing I don't care
Now that I know a guy's been cut in half
I kind of am fine with the no pens or pencils kuleto's
Crayons
Totally reasonable
Unreasonable to think that Tycoon on stuff is
Is true and if somehow it's going to
Intersect with Mark Richard
Still going on people are still into it
Cuz
People get tricked and so there is like a there's a ego aspect
And later is like
I got tricked by Bosa
There's also a pack
Republican party is it like lost time fallacy
A year into studying this qanon stuff
That time is now decide its all full of s***
So I think that a lot of people who should be the light
And be like this is all nonsense
Walt because those forces
That's a music
A28
Reimagining of nunsense okay alright
Just got a direct sequel It's just nonsense but it's all about
These sealed indictment
Saying it's
The Calm before the storm
Alright I see I see a little bit of Mamma Mia
No no
Jerome corsi
No but he's an interesting
Conduit
Tell the story
I bet it turned against him
So if you'll be an interesting protagonist
He's the only person who has a
This point
Oh my God
I was just trying to harmonize I thought you're going to go for another line
Carrie went to prison
Go talk to Mark but you should know
Did this wasn't the only interview that
Did she had plan
It's also important that people realize
Where are where
That I went to interview someone else this time as well on my way
We had originally been
Interested in doing an interview with me
Suddenly
And what happened
I think he must have been intimidated
Nope she suddenly acted as though he barely knew me and so that works
Affinity he was no longer available and on top of it she said he
Knows nothing about the secret space program even if they did it would be a felony
To divulge anything about it it's real
No it's not
Basically
So but that he's no longer able to talk
He said this is not the time for in-person interviews
4in person discussion
And
So this is what
With going on
So it's very interesting because this is a very
Tents time
It's quite an exciting time
A time when the
Trump Administration the people that are backing him basically the military
These indictments are coming through there's 40
40000 to 50,000
A hiver actually pursuing them as I speak
Inferior
In reality
She's just sort of combining ethology with Cuba
About the military being
I meant throwing in the qanon sealed indictments s***
It is time to be alive when you're into this stuff
A year from now it's not going to be that exciting your parotid hasn't
Revolve the doll
2012 credibly exciting
Sure you have to hold
You could do the whole thing and maybe 2013
Top there's a hangover
Got a little bit of onion
We got to start
Do the whole thing all over again
So carry thinking that she's going to go interview someone in the guy being like no
.
No I'm pretty sure that confirms everything that Mark Richard says his trip
Rubber back on that episode where she was interviewing the guy who works at a bus station take pictures of the moon
Thought that you confirm the time of the interview and then got on airs like I don't know where
Sure I'm talking about the professionalism of setting up the interviews
Confirm the time
There's a load up
It's somebody's play sounds like this
What do her lack of professionalism
Aziz Aziz interview
Yeah we didn't agree on a f****** time lady don't show up in my goddamn house
Children who think I'm normal
Possibility
And none of them in the real world are
This guy is f****** scared cuz
We're talkin
The only way I the only way I could think that
She has any kind of option
As if it was another guy in the same
Prison
Listen I'm not authorized
It's to talk to you
I'm not good at Improv
My eyebrow Waggles suggesting that whatever it is you said was true is not up to par
Exactly
Because my response is going to be like
Come on man
So there is a fundamental problem
With carries energy
But she does with Mark today
She's at the end of that life either crazy time
Yes question reduces the idea that the times are so crazy
The mark Maybe
Talk about summer
Because it's such a height and time
She was not able to
Talk about certain things with me he has been instructed
On what to say and what not to say
He does not have a working with the military
In the secret space program
And she is
No longer reporting cooperate he says
Bobby Ray and Menace no longer involved is how we put it
He is now
I'd like to say that I think that's code for someone called Bobby Ray
According to a different
Sector of the US military a division that he's not at Liberty to disclose
He said one of the reasons
She is able to talk obviously and other people may be more hesitant to do so is that
She is in prison and obviously has this disclaimer
Which is an
Fasten sort of
Credibility issue
No s*** is
Well first of
No I fully I
Really
Finally come to
Conclusion that none of this
Because
Well, I've had a long day
Bitter rivalry
They have been playing
Space football games every year and 8
This makes me think of you know Howard Kramer
Power climber who loves
The ocean
Program loggerheads
Mark Richardson
Synthesizer
Attacked by an octopus
You just punched
Godot
I love first of all time
I think that
He has needed to get the specifics out of some of
Story
People look into them
Military organization
Which is good that should have been the case all along
Because this is a load of hot b*******
Carry that must have been like the best mom
If you don't give
Specifics I don't have
The defendant
Is it so much easier
Right right
How many can look it up
Video game
Your military organization
Mothership is from this
Now I've got it
Baker's know about media you making this so complicated
I'm carry the curator okay
Canelo Jordan
I know that we come from a position
Of assuming that Mark
Because he is
You should know
But you should know something about it
He basically told me he would always tell me the truth if there were ongoing operations that were being conducted
By his side
Or the side that involves the Raptors and the military
Is she reports to
He would obviously not be revealing things that could endanger
Their operations and he wanted me to know that
You better know
Know that information
The jeopardizes the precious Raptor Force
How dare you assume I'm going to lie to you if it
Reality winner
We can't be doing that to the Raptor Raptor or not reality winner did not deserve
The mark Richards would agree with me on that
What's that
What what
Is the sentence
Could do it
You know Sadie Kerry Cassidy
I will never lie to
Right
Disqualified
Continue continue with I will never lie to you
I will not divulge information regarding the
Sensitive receptor operations that are ongoing people who make
Unnecessary
Just sort of
Out of nowhere black
Usually you're overcompensating a little bitty baby
Yeah I don't know that's just something I felt
I don't know maybe Mark Richards is trying to
That's what I feel a hundred percent
Trying to send that nice Edge
Her on a laser level
Eddie would never bother
Payment there
Thrill of the hunt I'm like a serial killer part of
Thing is I want
To be caught kill a rabbit
They can't hurt you
You could kill sucking
Tiger
Bright
Excitement
Yeah yeah
You going to
Like Icarus is flying
Too close to the Sun
I never f****** love you
But there's a new documentary
This guy who
Free climbs
I don't see that s*** all
Memories everybody on the like
He's free climbing this incredibly
Play Moore's
No safety harnesses are at all bro on
Sing about the movie though it's like
The camera crew
Are we
Is it okay for us to film a guide
You might fall and die
Is that okay
Share any fault
Does a GoPro on
Cuz that's going to be whether or not I
Because I
I've seen those videos of them like climbing up buildings
And stuff like that
Hundreds of feet in the air floors in the area
I feel it in my teeth
So f****** uncomfortable Turner on fire in a way that you can't comprehend
Triggers
Passed I passed on
GoPro I will I will tell you this right now
You shouldn't
Slightest bit
Seen and read about it
It's like
Hey have you ever had your balls drop later in life
That's what he feels
I'll let you be excited about that
Memory and I will
Continue to be
Coming out on
Super Nintendo
I love that Louis making so much
Mario
And put into a painting
That makes more sense
Anyway
Yes
We find one of the first instances of Mark having something
You can't talk
The Carrie brings up
The yarn about it
Guess what this is one of those things that I can actually tell you
The other end of this play
We talked about then the Sun and he said this was the an area he could not talk to me
Me about
Or couldn't say much about
We did talk about the next the New Mexico Observatory that has been
Close is very well known at this point
A lot of misleading stuff in the in the mainstream media and also and they alter
Lot of people not getting the real story behind it
I have had some very excellent source material on this
Coming from a secret Witness
Do you say infiltrated that
Channel chatter
Going on at the observatory there were seven others around the world that were also tells down
Is not hold water
The FBI was certainly we're simply that they sort of
Pony show that you were supposed to be misled by
What the information I got was
From this soda Secret store
Marc's
Trading of information more-is-more to the point of what really goes on when I talk tomorrow
Brittany Ray weather observatory in New Mexico
And the other Observatory
They were attempting to use a kind of superluminal
Technology which is called
Possibly based on quantum mechanics
So
Come on
Jurassic technology
You got to jump to quantum computer
Vanguard
Distance right now
You can't say
Possibly based on quantum mechanics
What the f*** you mean she doesn't have an explanation
That's where her explanation visit
Yeah possibly
Like she started this ends by saying there's this technology
It was being used that's called
It might use quantum mechanics
There's this theory about
Strings
So
He's brought up in a couple of
There was a
New Mexico.
Do you know about that
Because they finally found the Sun
No more need for this
It's up there
It's
So curious version of the story
Scary version of the story is at the national
Close down
Along with many others
Yes you brought up there and they clips
To do with an unnamed and unexplained
Curious technology that may or may not involve quantum mechanics
I just pretty much always the case I'll project Campbell
Gary's reality is far more fun
Show me actual real
From The Washington Post
What triggered the observatory
Complete shutdown was it
Distribute child pronography
According to court documents
Kinder was Distributing c****************
No no no no no idea that this Nationals
Solar Observatory was closed
B
Community online
Explained
The closure of the
This place but in reality when all the dust settles
The details were
Distributing c**************** on their Wi-Fi
Well there's more to it
Okay
Yep
This is according
Newly unsealed court docket
In July FBI agents investigating child sexual exploitation trace the location of several IP addresses
Pornography
Interview with Federal authorities on August 21st of this year
Facilities chief
Observers said that he was found on a number of occasions
The same laptops
And running in various seldom-used offices around the observatory
He described the contents of the laptop as quote
Not good
According to court documents
Let's
Really sums it up yeah. Good look at that.
Good if you're investigating child pronography and you're
Gnosis is not good I can assume that in my world that's the single worst thing that could possibly happen
Understand why the chief Observer of this
The place might not want
Potter sucks
Or something like that
I can understand someone using
Colloquialism
Authorities Authority
Yeah
Okay Vision only
Please note
Take it away from my eyes forever please
Chief Observer when
I spoke to they adore
Yeah federal agent was dispatched to investigate
Taking that laptop
And it was founded
The day after allegedly seen by the chief Observer leaving the office
The chief Observer interaction to Federal
Anyone that entered the office
Because the cleaning supplies he had left there were missing
Later the janitor claim courts Observatory late night in order to steal the wireless internet service
And express concerns about lack security Court
Report
What you see here very clearly
That guy wasn't even f****** try
He's trying to cover his tracks
This turns into outright
Again from the washing
You can post
The janitors actions allegedly became even more bizarre
Become worried about their own safety
Feverishly search the facility
Did the quote
It's only a matter of time before the facility got hit
I believe there was a serial killer in the area
The killer might enter the
Annex
Acute somebody
Because of his erratic behavior and his references
To the potential murder someone at the facility
Facility down
And evacuate their employees
The FBI did not make that decision
And it's against their interests as they were still engaged in active investigation
Everyone online misrepresented
Misreported the event is the FBI's shutting down
Because it was an actor
Give investigation
No one in the know with willing to officially comment on it until much later
Basically until mid-september
Reality is
Guy shut down the observatory because he was like
Not just him
Hey people are going to get murdered if we don't know if I can deal with it and the FBI
You don't know that for sure
You can't take risk and that's a situation
Using bootlegged Wi-Fi in order
To distribute c****************
They start acting super radically when it's clear that there The Jig Is up about the pasta
Ability
Did someone
To be murdered
Because of the killer in the area that's going to break someone has been breaking in at night
Get it like there wasn't me it was someone else to broken now he's using that someone's going to break in and kill people
Is not
Super crazy to think
Only like if they left it open
Call Bev hanging in the act
Probably enough
Information
Evidence in order to
But at the same time
It would be much easier
Controlled environment
To allow him
Be under surveillance
And commit the crime
He was already
In order to make a
That much easier
Arizona
No New Mexico
New Mexico
Not far away from the
You should have just bail
Photos
From when
You just can't
You can't stop yourself from
Expressing
Decent whether it's for villains or Heroes
I should be a consultant
Amoral
Consult
I'm from when of the
People in charge of the solar Observatory shutdown
And the time when
And the story started to come out
When
The FBI had enough
Evidence at their disposal they could talk about
Hey people we're getting the
Clearance
Comment
Observer
Credible sources
Internet bullshiter started
That the FBI shut down the place because they had spotted real alien
And this was a he
Huge cover-up
Even Outlets like zero just got in on the ACT reporting about the closure as if it was somehow suspicious
Along the way was pointed out that
A bunch of other webcam
Reservatory
Offline around this thing
Time
Took it must be a smattering of solar Observer
Rotary closure
Probably because they thought of giant Sunspot that was going to destroy the world
And they didn't want that info getting out
Kind of
And her
Siri when she's bringing up all these other places that
She's not willing to be so
Specific
That's fine
The online conspiracies were
It primarily initially about the idea to take it sound real alien and then secondarily
Unclear if there were a bunch
Other webcams that were down
Other Observers
Runaway from being jumped
And then it became
About the ideas found
World-destroying event
That was
Yeah exactly
So
Whoever pointed this out
The observation
Yeah on the front page of the Soul
Heliosphere
Observatory website where you find all of the
These webcam
There's an announcement prominently displayed
We are updating the code infrastructure that provides access to srrho data
We expect the work to take several
Their website and does access to streaming app for webcam
Temporarily
Completely unrelated
The situation
So what you have there is
Influence of
Again it's all intention
Understanding
Of information
Immediately in the aftermath of
New Mexico
Trattoria being closed
Kept really tight
Think about what you could roll up
Who are you in
Business
Yeah I know there is a possibility of absolutely
I think it's
A Dangerous Game
Play because you don't know what kind of Rogue variable this guy is
If you're law enforcement
I get it
No one's going to be able to talk about that
That's so.
The world
Carrie Reichert
People online start
They find all these webcam they don't know how to read
So they don't see the warning that says we're updating the website for take bunch of weed
Will take about a week
Goddamn
These pages
At all possible
Carrie is still in Wellington
If if her version
Then there are so many people
Who has
Willingly perjured themselves for
For no reason
Like all of the people swore affidavits
About this janitor
All of the law enforcement
Who wrote These warrants
The people who made these
He's 39 page
Decorations
Like all of them
R32 50,000 indictments are coming down Dan you think those people are involved I guess if you believe
Give that thing
Amazing
How escalation actually works
In this circumstance
Because like when we're dealing with Alex Jones they were talking about
The conspiracy is always there
Covering up pedophile
But in this case tonight cuz they were actually covering up but they were covering
Whittier
I think I accidentally
Realizes
Epicure Non-Stop
Yeah I call a lot of these
Sealed indictment
Weird globalist pedophile network operations
Both
All this is
Coming down the pike
You just got it
You got a trust
Trust the process
Going on
It's all going to come to light
Indicted already they don't know it
Meanwhile we have a situation here
We have a situation here
Dude
Who is
Distributing c****************
In a government
Building
Angela
Cover up that's just a cover story
Macabre story
You know ahead of the solar Observatory
Cornelia
Movies they love
Storiesig
Overarching fiction
One of those ways
Be very easy to do this would be a great episode Law & Order
Because of the
Great Gatsby
Alright are you make this work
Alright
Observatory
Who looks at
There's all these kids out there looking at the sun
That's how they
Call solar Gleaners
I don't know if that wasn't
But a way to make the story more compelling for Carrie if she wanted to like actually look at
The reality of it
You could go down
Organic
My time
But the gender was there
Because his parents
Contract
With a bunch of places
So there is
So there actually is a conspiracy theory story to be told Eric I mean if you want to stretch for it really far yet
That's one of the reasons that you felt so protected
And yeah career there and maybe one of the reasons why you didn't
He's working there under the office
Powerful contract
Company
With a bunch
Other love
Probably a number of
Stuff like that
Working at this
Seefeldt
Entitled and Celta Bulletproof
Something like that
I think that would be far too much for us to
Yeah
She should go
A cover-up of something because it's a lot of bulshit
From Mark
Consulting firm
This is going to be like
The first
First rule
Underrated option
Bail and run
You know
Like there's so many times if you would just really committed to bailing and running
Probably would have been fine
I would say won't be rule number one but it will be in the handbook
Run it's like
I didn't say just run I said it's an underrated
It's not even that it's an underrated option
It is an option
Available to you
For a while that will not available eventually
Malaysian Teton running you need to be aware of it
There's always
There's always account
You can
Freelee
But there'll be a time
You can run
You might have to like you're not going to go anyway
Your car over a barricade or something to run and then a little bit
Beware of that
Villain
I guess
Alright
God we got to get rid of our morals are holding us back
Oh well I'm okay with that
So in this next clip
I think
Not positive but I think I've done a pretty good job
And now I carry has some
Talking a little bit more about the Sun
Simon parkes also had information about this
In addition my source and Simon parkes is sources
And you can watch my interview with Simon parkes that
Happened in
Jalisco in September
You want to get this straight
You know the story straight from him
As to what his sources were saying and what my sources were saying
And how that
Basically the Carrabba's
Corroborate the data
That there was
Also some ships close to the Sun
We're being seen by the solar observatories there cameras
That artwork
Acting the frequency and or possibly according to mark
Attempting to trigger what might be
A solar event
And this is also something that my source was
Alluding to
Oh no
Solar event
Look at this look at it
So when it went to solar events
Quinceanera
Set event
Usually celebrated
I don't know they're talking about
Trigger a masquerade
Right that's right
Can harness the power of the sun 2
Create a Coronavirus
Destroyer or productive
Look if you have the power to launch a nuclear weapon somebody
You probably have the power to not launch a nuclear weapon but still do enough damage
Targeted way
Instead of like a destroy the Earth
That level of achievement it's sort of implied
100-percent always
But if you have
Reached
Category of attack there's other things you have other options
That level of the pyramid
So
She had Simon parkes coming
More or less
Confirming stuff that a secret source
Wink
Eyebrow waggle
Confirmation
She's like
I've got
Are you f****** Liars all on the same page
So something is going on with the Sun
You better believe it
I think you can reach the conclusion there's definitely something going on with the Sun
That they don't want us to see
One of the things that they were trying to step down the frequency
He actually said the good guys were trying to do this
Because the Sun affect the Consciousness on planet Earth
It is a rising too quickly apparently estimation and
It's right
And so they are trying to interfere with that
Temporarily I'm told
Sun is rising
Alright
Hold On by Jordan
Good
What
The sun is rising too frequently
None of the frequency is rising
Too quickly
Because the frequency of the sun affects
The consciousness of people on earth
Which I guess is a
Some sort of dumb space poetic way of discussing
Seasonal affective
The frequency with which you gets done
No that's not what they're talkin about electromagnetic band
Frequency butt
Who liked support life
Something along those lines
Fair
Come on
What are you talking about
Are you hurt
Reaction
Maybe there's factions
Do you sure
Just trying to make some
Remnants of
Trying to make slime
Of this
Bulshit story about the
The closing of the solar Observatory along with these webcam
Down
Narrative
Which is what
The business of doing
Is what Mark Richards
Is thrilled to do
24-karat
With these Quest
Karaoke
Confused there are only
2 ways to
Which is either go to prison
Because
A lot of this stuff it like when you're confused by her hearing her stuff
A lot of it stuff could
Easily be
Ironed out if you just
We get to another little bit of a
Bulshit story
Carrie's been going on about for quite a while this is another one of her big
Herbig go through
Spaceman
Then unfortunately
Okay
There is a relationship to the recently lost satellite and there were several
That were lost that we lost our contact with
They weren't
You know
They weren't demolished
They were simply they went offline so to speak
And there seemed to be a sort of war with the satellites going on in which
Some satellites Wii game controller
And some weight loss control up
Related
Do this shutting down
That's somehow involved with the
Satellite
Wow
All right. We lost contact with multiple satellites
Some sort of weird
But the reality different
The first instance
I know the first instance
That is Ventura
Is what we covered back on the air
There are strong indications that Russia
The space program was engaging
That they were maneuvering their satellites
Restricted areas
Drop on other countries.
This is a piece of news closely matches up
But the timeline
Conversation
But interesting
News
I think might be misrepresenting
Firstly
On April 28th
India lost contact with one of their Satellites after something went wrong with the engines
Meant to raise it to a higher orbit
Most likely this is
Result of something
As it was the second satellite related failure since 2017 for the
Space Program
Which by the way is Loki an awesome
Space Program 2017
The orbit from a single rocket with 104
Pretty f****** cool set the world record India
How high and eventually come back
So there's that
They also won the Indians
In 2014 for a ridiculously cheap 73 million-dollar
Compared to NASA
But them
Wow Indian has a really great
But they have
Lost a couple
Something about 104 in ones
There's the
Here's the name of the
It's
The acronym is
The immature for to Aurora Global exploration
Satellite
T-shirt
It's called image for short
Image was launched in 2000
Magnetics
That quite well 45 years
Before NASA completely lost it
They have no idea where it went until they tried their best they couldn't reestablish contact
With this
This image satellite
A shout-out
Then
In January 2018
An amateur astronomer named
Without looking
Sky searching for other satellites
But the transmission from image
The satellite that have been missing for 13 years
Now I assume by this place
Like it became that dude friend and they started talking back and forth it was like
I'm really lonely up here man
Pixar's next movie
NASA
2005 quotes
Solid State power controller which Powers the transponder
It uses to communicate with ground can
Filled with a sense of hope that maybe they could Salvage you win from the jaws of defeat
NASA scientist course by Major Tom
NASA scientist started trying to reconnect with image
Collect data that it would have been
Collecting
Unfortunately though they were able to get Little Pigs back and forth
Yeah you weren't able to get it 2X
Respond to commands
Appropriately because
As usual
Let's power controller
He's what powers do much of the functionality of the spacecraft
Grown Apart like it's tough
Forever
It's so it unfortunately it ended up not working
And at the end of August 2018 around the time that carry
Eddie Maine
They're barely receiving a signal at all from this image
Satellite and they announced that it's probably lost
Greg so we have a situation here where there's an actual satellite
Was lost for 13 years
That some guy was able to find
And then they reestablished contact with
But then went away it's possible that that's the story that they're basing a lot of this we lost contact with this satellite
Not mentioning that we had lost contact with
A 12 to 13 years before that
That is but it had a programming in it
He was going to go
Eclipse was just going to automatically shut off while it was inside that eclipse
How to predict whether or not it would
Because they had lost contact with him but when it came out of that eclipse
It turned out a dick
Self back on
So that's probably why Scott
Rediscovery
And nobody was looking
That is so f****** fun it's amazing I love
It's another great like mini-documentary like a 30
4:30 but this guy accidentally rediscovering the satellite has been lost for over a decade
Attorneys I mean far more explanation
Before I'm willing to accept that this guy just like
Email NASA was like
Hey you guys been looking for a satellite I found it up the back of my truck from what I understand is he started to get rough
Sort of
Transmission
From the satellite that he didn't quite understand
I'm so he reached out
Dakota
The people who were working on it
Satellite
Also Jordan listen satellite
Losing contact with satellite
Credibly common
This is disgusting
Article you can look up
It's surprisingly easy to lose a satellite worth millions
Every year they're stories about a bunch of satellites
Just lost contact with
And not just the other countries
Like I said earlier in the year India had that satellite the 2nd of
Lost
Russia lost contact
A couple of satellites earlier this year
Suez
Satellites
It does happen
I don't want it like nobody wants
NASA to come out in like an ounce every
Satellite that they've lost
Because then you're going to be like Wednesday so I can lose satellite all the time it'll be in space or the Smithsonian
Explanation
What happened second Rock misfired
Interviewing the head of NASA
How did you guys lose this million-dollar satellite
F****** hard
And this is
Expensive because so much of the sunk cost
Exactly
You just know sometimes is
Level that you could never ever ever comprehend
Who is on a level higher than we can comprehend and we can comprehend some
Dude
Completely uncontrolled
So anyway is what happened
With satellite
I can find no evidence
But that doesn't matter
Inevitably wind up
Something is rotten
In space
We did have the help of the pleiadian to help
Give us the code to take the satellite back
The ones we were able to take control of
Is something that coincides with the Eddie
Page information
As well as Simon parkes information so we have three
Confirming
That information
At this time
Is Nazi a return of
Biru he does not CS
Upcoming invasion of Draco in the near future
What's Cointreau to the predictions of
So
Ouch
I'm going to figure out that quote one of these days
Trouble in Paradise
America's Paradise Mark Richard
Do not see eye-to-eye
Mark Richards
Might
But you know what I think that I look I say the n-word all the time
Sprouts
South suburbs of Chicago
Look
Mark Richards is probably a little bit worried about his place as the
Throne
At the brown project
That's not the only thing you have to
What's he's got trouble
He does say we're in a very bad position at this time too for a number of reasons
A great deal and that his
I don't know if it's his daughter his granddaughter and I wasn't unable to confirm which person
But someone in his family was
Recently diagnosed with a brain tumor
Jewish families having a very hard
Time right now
I mean that sucks but don't try and pretend that someone messing
She started presented as like someone gave this person the brain
That's awful
Himself
Like that seems like only I'd be willing to
You just brought it up
In the vault
Hey you made it let's cut let's cut out this whole bulshit for just a second
And I want to make
A real human
My family is a
Experiencing
My daughter has a brain injury
Open with Joanne
Is it possible that Joanne gave her that information
You know that Carrie has called
And she has said is that her Bell's Palsy with a scalar
Within her worldview
Information
He's created that narrative
They're trying to attack me by giving my daughter or granddaughter
First moment that I have ever thought
It has an
Yeah I didn't realize that either
Right I didn't realize that he had reproduce
I mean I guess
He was out of prison
Like 20-something when he went
Went to prison
Also conjugal visits a good attitude while he's
Conjugal visit
Oh yeah actually when I was looking up the rules for visitation and stuff like that there's like
Oh no that wasn't married
Is even possible for a like you to have a family,
For 48 hours
And stay with you have like a holiday
More like various holidays
I don't know
I don't know I don't know if that's true for prison
But they do have a program where
You get approval and everything
Obviously not in yourself 48 hours
You celebrate a holiday
That's really good
So much wrong
So what's wrong but I like that I got.
First thought is abolishment and then my next thought is
I don't know
How do you figure it out
Don't need you my first thought is Legend
After that is
Well if we do
Do that then what do we do and
If we do that then what else
If you get off track
Humane Pre-K
Because it's so different for every different
A person like what is valuable and what means
You might not be the same as it may
Tumi
Environment for everybody
What would be considered humane
To you wouldn't probably be the same as
Is 2 mi be a very
Predilections and corks
There are things that are super important
Like for me
I think it'd be awful to be a prisoner not be able to take a bath
But yeah now that was kill you for 30 years
Yeah
Alone
For 30 years
Book
I wouldn't be happy about it
I obviously would probably be there if I did something to deserve
I think you'll be inhumane baby shower that whole time I look at that incredibly difficult
You probably would
I wouldn't even
Pop up
I mean I would think about it
Time to time but it wouldn't
To what extent is prison isolation versus
You know like you have a sec
Like
How is it that
Infinitely better living situation
Third time for weed possession
Can you know
Also about Ender's brother
No
Has anybody caught him now
Glenn Beck
In the aftermath of the attack
He referred to
Victims of his attack at that camp as being like
Hitler Youth
Because it was a political unit
It was very
Very disgraceful
So hey there's an intersection without
Alright
Alright let's get back on track Jordan
Accu back on
Appears to be unimpressed with Eddie page
Not a piece of s*** about the
Draconian is racism on that tip tube
But come on
So he's on impressed
Was that
In the sex Club carry brings up another one of her
Newer sources I guess
I did talk to Mark briefly about scientific
Paper that Paul Price Road
Or he's going to have to mail me more
Information
Cuz we didn't have time to go into it in detail smartphones respond saying
That it did not contain enough
Specific equations in the formula was too General
He did said say he would send me a better analysis villamil
Ouch
Mark Richards fired shots fired on this
Cool
He's probably
Enough courtesy
The world
Through is a valid criticism
Into everything that any of them have ever said but I like this is Carrie's met some new weirdos
Mark is not
Retelling of real Liars
Now that would be fun
A place of light
These guys
Call Mike confidence
Missile
Yeah it's almost like a state
Alpha Behavior
Nmd like a pickup artist
Bright
Suck it
To all your
Real dad baby tell you about the warp drive
Not enough
Page Six
He's got more information about your in a little bit
Realized
To the prison where she has met
His roommate
Analysis of this is like
Soaking
Okay she does have a cellmate at this time who is
A relatively young man who has a scientific background parently
And he is also very tall
Cuz I saw him in person
I wish I fall
Sound very interesting
I'm not sure I don't want to pee
Course not
Same time
Being told
He's an alien because he's
Nope but here's the thing that I think she was trying
Express but did so super poorly
CID video scientific
Check background
He's Barrel
I found that very interesting
Based on
English pronoun reference is referring to the fact that he's tall
Not the fact that
The other thing that you mentioned earlier that is a scientific fact
And then settings.
And he's tall
Humans don't do that
Imprison his
Pacific background
I find that very interesting
Also he's called expressions for being like
She has a roommate in prison who has a scientific background
He's tall
Such a person
Being his bunk mate is
Interesting to me
Who's 100 ways to express that you chose 31 along the way that makes it sound like the only thing I wanted
I didn't
Or something like that
He has the sexual version of a Napoleon complex
Napoleon
You only goes with a squat
I don't know I don't know the way she's expressing
Very
Very confusing
However
She's doing it unless she's doing it the way that
You saying she's doing
She doesn't ever clarify at all
That you just mentioned that
He's warp-drive Converse All Star
You got to do it
We get one of those rare glimpses
He's going to have to like
Take them up to a higher level
On the wall
Private
Stop
Can't even reach
The level
To put those at eye level
Here's what we're not talking about
He's 84
He's one of the Giants of the Old Testament
Maybe is also the tallest human being ever recorded
So this next clip Jordan
Is one of those rare
A couple of Clips was head event
One of these days
Kerry bringing up something
About her space bulshit
Branch of
What is the rare bulshit
In these
Mark Richard
Interviews
That she does
Where something is said
Diddy's clearly
Code
They relate to all real world
They're just talking about the real world but
Using a lie
Mike down for this Steve
If you can
The code
I think I want you to scream right now
Also talked about the Grays house
Report to the highest bidder and that there is a
A selling out many of the
Journalist out there right now are
Human hybrids and have been influenced by the greys and so they are obeying the Deep state
And The Darkside
Because they are basically kind of Solace and or
Emotional
Feeling so they don't connect with Humanity
For you are you're a you're a push away from
You're real close
To this
What we doing
All the Press are grey aliens
That's doing
Oh man we don't get a lot of news in here but I'll tell you right now
Love it when Saudi Arabia murdered the journalist
Before that so
Like 5 days
Overweight
Yeah I know but the the reports were
Initially that he was missing
Know their brother
Okay I suppose that the reports were initially that he was missing
If you recall if you recall on our first episode missing I was like
Arabians murdered this guy
It's not a conclusion
Cuz they're all about murdering people that they don't
Querida
Caribou
All journalists are grey aliens
I mean it's just an old England
Yeah buddy
It's not like he hasn't
Intimate relation
Breaking news service
This is any more closer relationship with
Good point
You have brought up a pickup at I cannot ignore and imprisoned
On the media
If there's one thing I know about me enough
The Free Press
Top of the list
I've been very like so long ago
Dwight and no other voices are allowed to be very resistant
Like talk about the idea
Possibly
Falling in with
You'll not be grabbing some stuff like that when I was looking into it
Found that like a guy just texted organs missing
Astoria like
Prison
Years or in that prison in other
Wright has become acclimated
Like we like to imagine
He's just some sort of weird.
Crazy
That lives in prison
I meant that are very generous
Comes up with his
Narrative bulshit
Or whenever Carey
Or someone else comes in
We can tell them about it
Incorporated with
Some
F****** bad dude
We hear Carrie coming in and talk to him about the
Media
And he's a
Expressing
It's all gravy alien
They've all sold out they don't even have souls
It's really tough to hear that and not think about other historical parallels I'm not going to
I know every journalist
Is a grey alien
If you gave me like a roster in picture format of
Let's call it journalist from
Right and have all their pictures and kind of a situation
I would be able to drop
Bullseye's
Over certain members
Those organizations
There might be like
Single unifying thing that they might have in it
It's cuz usually media but that's only because
But all Jews are bad
I mean to me when I hear that clip that is so clearly
Adjust the David Icke
Kind of thing
Aliens
What he's talking about
Veterinary Clinic
Is very
Clearly
Entrenched
With MP7
Now I don't know if that's Mark's whole bag
But that's what he saying
Find out why
He does not believe
80 Pages Mary
It is a draco invasion
Yeah
He said the war on and off planet Earth is intensifying
Our allies
Recently destroyed a moon of the
Several races right now are given the Draco a very hard time in the Orion sector
Galaxy
If that were true that would
Bestow
Beetlejuice is one of the biggest stars in
The Orion
And it turns out that if
That did go supernova and blow up
Yeah it really wouldn't affect us.
It's far far away enough that it wouldn't affect us
Cuz I was thinking like okay they blow up this Moon we would f****** coz
Johnny Carson
Consolation
Like you know you never
Usdan
How many light-years away
But I'll be able to see if they were giving them a hard time as we speak
We would not know for another 15 to 20 hit read probably
No like way longer
Cute I would weep
You and I would be dead so all of this implies that they have faster-than-light communication
First
It's taken as read
No concept of this
Until after you and I were long.
Yeah it's alright 140
1360 light years away
A lot of trouble right now and we're going to experience
I'm going to take this one on the you're totally right you're totally right
Lightyear tracker
For it to become
Fine
They may be blew up that dub I got it
Of all the things that I decided to take a stand.
This is one where I'm going to eat crow I'm going to eat crow on this we cannot confirm nor deny
Blown up one of the Drano Max
Enter Ian will know.
Because he can remote view every
You can go to revolt Riverview restaurant
Astral travel
Who cares
Little bit more
So in this next clip again we that we we have that last clip where
Exactly the same thing of like
Before you
Journalist
Kind of hear what you're talking about
There's another
Weird
Thing where you talkin about the real world
He said
There's an interesting bit of information about
Aliens who have been
More or less given free rein in South America and Africa working now to expand their territory
The other part
And especially North America
As they have eaten so many humans
Expand their hunting
Is it called
Alright alright come on come on hide it a little bit better than a little bit
Better than that
To hear that
Specific regions of
Talking points about like immigrant
Invasion in Southlake
These aliens have been allowed to hunt
Helium kill and eat all humans down there and now they want in on white territory
To hear the exact same
You hear out of Alex
Robinson
Out of all the
Canary right it's right there
Give me a gist
Give me
Atlas say two examples
South Africa
And one from South America
Where the right-wing has very public talking
About how white people are under
Just give me
Two examples
I don't even need a lot then
I'm sure there's no way
You could find any examples
One-to-one comparison
Between right-wing talk
Aliens that he is
Describing here Dan this is a complete
It's right
He believes all of the alien narratives that he's
Nothing it's just
That would be crazy
It would be crazy what's less crazy
He has kind of
Who's in prison
Also a little
Express himself
Walkthrough little bit of Flowery narrative language
Explain things
How to say
Or any
Any other slurs
Show me
Is there whatever it is
Reptile
I don't know how I feel about all that
Not much just racism
How's the weather for Saturday
Conflicted about how to integrate that into the
The bigger picture of a lot of stuff like it does become
It becomes difficult to
To look at
The bigger picture of Mark Richard
Quote-unquote philosophy
And worldview
We keep seeing little glimpses
Right
And it's not
It's not super
Covert but if you know the truth
There there
It does it does really
Raise the question of
How much of this
Is part how much is
Do you know he's play
Bistro
So that's the part that I'm conflicted this is a huge question that I cannot believe I have never asked you
Mark Richards went to jail
Story
In 84
Yeah
Right
There has to have been an interview with his
Can you give me a comment
Right
He went to the trial
Or maybe you did maybe just maybe
First level comment that the Dutchman
Truth chance
I mean
Uno's
There also is a chance that he was mad
Dad didn't know him we don't know I don't know enough about Mark Richards actual real life
It is possible that he was
Is that right
For his story and working backwards chances are strong father figure
Thoroughly
Positive
It's even possible that his dad was on the
Open what-have-you
Ivory
News organization that wanted a comment
If at that point years of
Like a
Deteriorating relationship between the two
And things not going well then
Murder
You don't want to
Play out in the news
I tried to help him
Yeah why
You want to live your life especially not if you are part
Absolutely
There's a real world version
Of his dad
Would not appear
Frigid frigid then there's also the
The Dutchman
Who also wouldn't appear in any text
Showboat
Both both no matter what the evidence to
It could prove either
So
Fair enough
So if it's like swept Jordan
Bubba Bubba
He hates Eddie
But it turns out
Are you done work yet
It's not just
80 Pages sayings
Go invasion
Turns out
Empirical evidence is what you see
Regarding Eddie page he made a special point after I left
To contact me to let me know that
She had
Either he had or read that he's a very good remote viewer
Took a look at any page or he got information about him
He says that he is heavily programmed
He also said that if we spent 10 minutes with him he could tell
If he was truly ugly alien
Mark was married to obsidian
A lot of people don't know that
But it is in the history of the interviews I've done with Mark in the past
She can go back and look that up that is
True back and look that up because I was like is married to that Rancho princess
Turns out he was banging around with that Raptor princess he was married to
So that that checks out
Remember that one for some reason
You got you guys could ferment your story
Bridget
Oh my God this is
What else is he lying about
I'm going to go in
Everything
He's been truthful about everything
Except for
The fact that there were real Raptors
Dinosaurs
And address
6park
Does Raptors
Spielberg
Perhaps better than the
The real ones
Sometimes
So I don't know man
Bettie Page. Remote viewed by
Marque Richardson
I found out all this
I love the idea that
Put me in a room
Because
You bring
I really want that to happen
Take me to be beautiful escalation forward
Carrie has to insist
Alright Daddy
I have some questions about yours
The only way that you're going to
2ba consist
Piece of my show in the future
Is if you agree
With me
Seamark
Right
That has to be the next
As part of our consulting firm
NFL run at this point you just got it
You got to come through
Yay
Look it escalates
The feud
Escalated Feud
What do you mean what do you mean are you we already know
We already talked about this
What is anorexia
Your ass to become the devil
He has to become like
Yes absolutely Marcus right I am not who I pretend
Interviewed
Greatclips.com
I have some
Demonic information
M4u
Work
There's no real
No you're right
Affirm
Still based in the real world
I forgot that we were hoping for situation
Where
Mark
Would be on the same
Ego-driven
They each want
To be Alphas
Oh yeah
Yeah I can't
Each other
Counterbalancing
Eddie is
Evil dark brother
Mark Richards
Degrees of him
He is risen
Use the noble one who is doing 30
Years in prison
And we'll be back for restless leg
Because he is so good
That sort of thing
Has committed so many crimes
Sure
Probably
Skip this next week cuz it's just carry talkin about
The devil
Galaxy
Very superficial normal not important
And they always do what she's like
She's on with the literal.
Avista Corp Georgia
We running to sort of issue
Where
Here is the beginning of the episode of said that Mark is still a captain
GM secrets
Should have gotten
Yeah at least sergeant-at-arms
Chairman of the Joint Chiefs
It's a difficult question to answer
Astilbe
Active member of
Ambien prison
But thankfully Carey
Odyssey
Mark is in a rather delicate position because even though he is
Trusted
A certain group of the secret space program
He is very close to the Raptors and this
Keeps him in sort of this gray area of Suspicion
Simply because of his relationship and
In a certain sense control of the Raptors
Which makes him a real force to be reckoned with
Who is the Raptors
No I don't understand how that makes sense
He controls the Raptors
We didn't know that before this week you'd still controls the rapture
Okay
Let's just play
Like
I would like you also
Like start of the bottom
Alright
So
Raptors
We're still saying that the Raptors are good even though by association with Mark record Mark Richards
That suggests that they are in fact that I'm at the reptoids are good
If we
Look at what 0%
Mark and the Raptors are good
So that's alright for now
Princess
I think so
Series
You're f****** alien
It's standard operating procedure allegiances
Alien
All the sudden you guys were
So now he exists in some parts of the secret
Space Program
Except that this man is trustworthy
We can believe in him but other parts of the secret space program
Earlier with
From the last 30 years he's been
Prison baby
Terminated by the Demonic forces within the thirty-year-old guy
Richard
And then you're going to tell me that Mark Richards controls the
Building up for f****** chocolate
Wicked pictures of the good guys
So you're telling me
The even though
Who Now controls
We doubt he does controller everything every single time
Raptor eats chocolate
That's what they consent
It's a demonstration of failure at leader
What if
He ordered the hit it could be the kinky Boys in line
He's got a very Lacks
It's like it's like he's Erik Prince he's the Erik Prince of the Raptors
Not good intelligent commit war crimes
Baby
We're going to be fine
It's interesting because
I have sort of a mercenary space situation
To talk
I'm going to go with Mark Richards
Has abandoned
Addison said going into private
Private Contracting
Much like a brisket
Using his
Relationship
With the Raptors
He's back up and that's the only thing
Bring him from
The hypothetical threat of referee
I ran into
Wife
I'm going to be like
Have fun
Have fun buddy
You
Far
Wherever is not harsh
Terminator
Yeah man it's weird it's
Super 8
Terms of like
Universal politics
Park Record
Controls the Raptor
And that's why
Is here on Earth does he control Raptors
Program has like a like a
Restraint
Respect
Because this other alien race
He's on board of them to in
Buc-ee's
He controls all of them
Much like
I don't know did relationship he has with them is
Is similar to
Star Wars parallel
Now I'm the only one
Techui you're like that
It's not
Eventually
I don't like those move
Dario
Everybody can
Not everybody can
C-3PO Campbell
Yeah that is spelled
Correct that I apologize
It was
Never made it clear what she was trying to say I want subtitles
How about you go to Kashyyyk
I'm learning the language
Dance
In this next clip Carrie has
Yeah and that is like
The answer is no
I asked him if the generals around Trump know who Mark is and if they are red in
And he said some are some aren't
He said General Dunford
The chairman of the joint
Is in the know and by the way Simon parkes also referred
The General
Saying that he was instrumental in
Backing up and
And making
Trump's Administration possible
Some of the generals around Trump really don't know anything about the secret spot coffee and they don't know who
I said tomorrow
And Mark
Krispy Kreme
You know what
I'm going to go back to
Don't agree
Say that you don't know
Cover Under Wraps if all of the generals know about
Exactly if you only want the guys were empowered
And Joseph
Necessarily know if this is a thing that reflects negatively on me
Leon the world we live in
He's still the chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff
Okay
You can understand why why you not because
How many different
Chiefs of Staff
Like it's it's reasonable to not be sure
If you know anybody in a cabinet-level
Yeah yeah for sure he's been
As long as
We've been talked about people who reference
The entire time
Doing this podcast
But every time
Chief of Staff has come up
He is been
And
Is even in my memory
There was that time that
Alex
Come up with John
That's why I haven't come up with the name
Well
Am I even
That can't even come up with me
Greatest prop
Annette like toolbox
Basically
Is thankfully Terry
Sodas
Mark. OK Google
Bang
You can find Dunford on Bang
How to tame a c
Clips
Alright
We have
We disagree with
Science
Evidence
Those sorts of
Tell me those things
Though we can only know
Roughly 100 to 1000
Yes
But the rest of this kind of like asses bulshit
At this point
Kind of tickets
Into a situation where
Now the narratives
Just going to be this like
I don't even know
This
I know that
It's what Mark is
Telling you
But
Regarding Elon Musk she's been a daughter
Recently as you may know and
Apparently
Mark Zuckerberg
The rocket deals
That
The rocket deals that were part of Elon Musk
Stop
That's not great
What
Is that how that works
Mark Zuckerberg now that Elon Musk has been indicted by the SEC and Tesla still exist
Now that he's on work has been indicted Mark Zuckerberg who has not a rocket company to his name
You now get to the rocket deals that were apart of Elon Musk
Stuff
All right you are
You create a company
Built on
Perhaps the Sham idea
Futuristic technology
You haven't been doing your heart
Now
At the most
A slap-on-the-wrist we can't do this
Bridgeview anymore
Fraud
Lost a lot of people a lot of money
That's a crime in the world that we live in that's a crime
It's a real shity thing however in the world we live in also
You're rich
So nobody's going to bother you
But we can't trust you with these Rockets
Does rockets go to Mark Zuckerberg
He's working to give these Rockets
The guy from The Social Network by Aaron Sorkin
A real fictional movie
I'm going to need you cuz I'm slightly fix
Dialogue look I love everybody masturbating to his liberal bulshit dialog but
I'm going to be honest with you doesn't sound like the way real people talk
Conspiracy
Version of Mark Zuckerberg
Rockets
Set versus not involve rocket
Infrastructure that is
Required
What do you mean are you saying that the Facebook campus is Art building rock
No
For business what Mark Zuckerberg is
Feeling
Information installing it
To the highest bidder
That is not the same business
That is it
Involved with actual
Like
To build a rocket
It stopped you need a lot of different departments
You need
A lot of specialized
Scientist
He's not in my bed
Mark Richard
Is
Look
I'll guy
With the right company
He's out of the
Picture which is not
Mark Zuckerberg now
Rocket
Ludacris I do like I do like the worlds of every billionaire
He's also Scorpio from Scorpio from the Simpson
Irregardless of how you made your money you are also Scorpios evil Superman
I also like the idea of
No matter what
If you're one of these people that were taught
To be afraid of
These these figureheads of businesses
You are
Like you might be varsity
You are you are the six
Superman are you
Cuz I think that's what you're about to say
You will
The Social Network
You know how to build a rocket
That's science
Science magazine
That's about science
That's crazy
You really said that
You really said that Elon Musk because he was indicted
All of his contract now went to Zuckerberg
Is Rocky
And then let's hear the end of this road
Bears hearing
Heaters out
The rocket deals that were part of Elon Musk
Couldn't even come up with portfolio
Better than
You know it's just
Zuckerberg gets his stuff
I wish I could
Chicago voices
We all know
That
Marc rich
Remote view that ipe
Right and that he could smell
Pleiadian
If you be able to tell for sure
Kind of races
Now youse married
Which is also
Basically we get this
Mark is trying to
Really invalidating page
Through like
He's using language
Which is sort of like
He's trying
Do an if Aven
Beavan see
Is really picking up on the Scylla
Sad because he was married to pleiadian he knows quite a bit about them
Does not believe
Play Dance can be mine Patrol
Eddie's Casey said
She thought they could be mine control if they allow it
Okay when does wonder why athlean would allow themselves to be mind-controlled by humans
Does opened
The question as to which races are
Does does open
The only possibilities are what
Exactly
That Eddie page is a
He is chosen
To become brain what's going undercover
Probably
He's lying about
Pleiadian
Because he is mine
That's established
Used
He is my control
If that's only corroborating evidence
He is mine
So we have both
Avenues
And both are Eddie page
Suspect
I don't trust
Britches
Obviously
Super 8
Advantageous
Because like
I'm protecting my
It's also super
Sports
Because
Page
He's become too much
I would much
I would much rather have my
Narrative with
The greatest whistleblower in the world who's in prison
That I can completely control the narrative
I can just
Whitewashing
It's so close
The two peoples
Pinterest
Better best Servite invalidating
Are Kerry Cassidy
Mark Richards could have expedited this visit
This secondary
He started to smell bad
You could have done that
Like this siren
Yeah
You hear someone saying that they're an alien
So in this next clip because you
He was married to
Right Mark Richard
Heisman watch
Tell who is Apple
His dick
Summerville
Very reminiscent
Other care
Did Mark did say that helps you tell
Creating is that they don't like to look
You directly in the eyes
They have trouble responding
Two everyday chat with
Appropriate
Micro expressions and they tend to copy or imitate are micros
Expressions during conversation
Consciously
Any used an example
That humans lick their lips
Involuntarily
Even during the conversation or something but that's something that
And that
Adopt
That behavior
Purposely and so it would look quite odd
And so this kind of visiting a giveaway giveaway on
I mean I guess that's better than where I thought it was going like they're probably
You can never trust anybody on the artistic
Spectrum
As opposed to where I thought he was going which is like
They
Swim and they like watermelon and fried chicken like I would have been better off know you better off thinking I don't know why
Good
Okay
He's not saying anything negative about the
Weird
Characterization
Asperger's Spectrum
The autism
People were reversed
Do I contact
Social cues
Jews being
Misunderstood
What he's described
I think he read an article on on that sort of thing
Pretty good about
Because the
The Palladium
In that world
To the fact that
It's not like taking
Neuro
Group
He's there
To tell
Who are the
The good Among Us I mean at the same time though.
That that gets into the end of The Stereotype game
Racist towards Asian people
No
You are a great you're pressing it as a positive connotation but that doesn't necessarily mean that you're not being
A complete
Like he's he's definitely like
This movie
And I'm going to tell you right
He
This guy this
Pleiadian
He kept saying
Is crazy
Like
You're right it is like
But for the bar that we
It's better than the other
Yeah yeah
Autism
And applied
Get to a negative
Evil alien
It's not great
But
We got a wreck
Recognized
Justin
I'm not a fan of
Anyone
No
Are we knows it like
I mean mark
Just wrestling
Yeah there's a lot of
Workout through
Interviews
Yeah
I know that earlier in this
Pure Express
The Raptors
Kill people
Has been brought up by Carrie and Mark
I think that you're foolish
You think that is
Not to trust
Is it
If explained
One thing he said was an interesting comment he said the Raptors mantid played in
Ionians are loyal to us just like in WWII
Sure
And he says that we're allies especially in deep space of really stepped up
I'm taking up the fight
Draco
And he has never been double-crossed by a Raptor
And
Even she used to be suspicious of them because they used to eat people but now he feels they're totally
So calm down
They used to eat
Mark Richards
She wasn't
Grown
Through it and now it's Jordan
Jordanelle
Headshave
No back in the Pathmark Richards was just like
He heard
And he was like
No not cool not cool
But he's
Track record
They've their loyal
Just like in World War II
Yeah they got our back
Raptors
Now they
Admittedly eight people for chocolate
We all have a lot of straw
We won
At one of them is
Miami
Of course
Super contagious
Free to be like look I know that
Spanx
Just blew up a
Draco
Hey are you going to sneeze on that we never would have stopped Napoleon if the Russians hadn't had a lot of land
Or World War
Yeah we never would have stopped to Hitler The Rush
Had a lot of
I don't know
Entering
What I will say is
That the new
Mark Richard
Game
Quite frankly project
I know
Did every single time you do an episode
There will be
Race of alien
That comes up
I like this game
Will introduce
To come in
What do you
You think that racism
I will tell you
Did I will answer 5 questions
You cannot make a guess
Before you ask those five questions
Is it a mammalian species
Alright
Is it a repeat
I actually can't say
You can ask you can ask me any question
That's not one of your foot alright
It is considered
Reptilian species
But the name would not leave
You think that it is
The name is not a reptile
But the people as reptilian using graders that you have ever said
Alright
What sector
Space
Not clear
That is even if I answered that it would.
Okay, three
Alright you need to really just start asking questions
Are they
Evil
Number three
Non-mammalian
Reptilian species that you mix
To be reptilians is not reptilia
Alright so we got that established
Narrow is a what
I honestly don't know the answer
The question but I will say based on.
The name no
Okay?
You should have
Different question obviously that's why we aren't doing yourself
Last question Georgia
That you would not immediately assume as reptilian based upon their name
Certain
Continents
And if so what kind
If further so
Is that an island continent that could be explained away as evolutionary
Is a three-part question that I get away
How can I help you
Alright I'm going to go with
Campy dragons
Something to go with Salomon
So I also ask Mark about the Dragon
Because I wondered if they were attacking the Draco as well
Reptilian
Corso
It's interesting you want more about the dragon moth
Ashiana Dean Voyager books go into this race as well as others
Highly recommended
Are they and Mark is aware of the Dragon moth said he did not know what their involvement is
He knows that they're in play but he doesn't know what they're up to
He said I know about them I don't feel like they're part of this
It's pretty crazy that you were like
You did say drag
Being right before like
The dragon moth
Also that was a very misleading answer
He's everything a reptilian species that
I didn't I play the tape back
They are considered
To be a reptilian species
Space
Research
Looking into it
Dragon boss is not a reptile
Like if you are at now that makes sense
Cuz if you ever
It is
Confusion is venmo
My creation
Dean book
The Voyager books I looked into
These books
A little fun fact
You can buy
Copy of
The paperback
Check for $75
On Amazon
Must be great
I've been in print
So many people on them
Dragon Ball
Fairy Mothra Style
Is that actually
Tickled me so much
Hey it's like
Gary gygax
There's a Hooter lien
He's a reptilian
The boots
Well that's that teams at the at the very least that's Direct
There's also blue
Just blue people
Cutelaba
It Came Upon whatever
Bingo
The Appalachian
Literally like
I like the Third Reich
We got reptilian a tractor
We got Dragon bolts now
This world bugs
Is just
Increasing it's not it's never not bug
I don't always understand
Ants aren't number one on the alien species
I feel like they're in there though when you talked to like Halo worth
Definitely talk about
Makes more sense to me than any of this other
If there was a hollow Earth
I would assume
Of course they did a lot
Congratulations
Dragon moth you are now part of our
Now Jordan
I've been hold
Going back a little
Yeah
I should tell you that
Cassidy
Episode
In this next
Keenly aware
How much
Probably miss
The things
Mark Richards
And
Fixing something
You should never have said
That what I'm doing with Mark is trading info and in some ways it's a lot like
The sort of all the presidents men
Throat
Where you basically you say something
And if she nods or he says nothing is mean
You're right
But
Information
I guess Eva more sensitive nature
And I am sharing a lot of background information with him
Be in our sort of when I ask ask a question
Sure he understands
Where I'm coming from
Tell him to give me the answer.
Dynamic flowers in general
No it's if you show that you know certain amount
Will come and meet you halfway
Then you won't learn anything
No Kevin
Sort of an interesting Dynamic I wanted to make people aware of
If you come in
It's really not if you are talking to a con man
And you come and meet them halfway
They will use all of the information
Presented
Call delivery blow
The first thing you do is you let the whistle
Baked all the noises that it needs
To make first
Almost as if you communicate with the whistle
Yeah I'm here
What Cheese's
First of all
Richie's talking about like
Let me just say
Of all of the podcast that we
I think that might be
In the running
It's damn for the dumbest
Any human being
Has ever said
Cuts her entire fluffy
Entire life's work ability to understand
Eid
I talked
To Mark and sometimes he doesn't respond
And then I take that to mean
That I'm right
That's a flawed
How do you know good
Real good
Well I'm not saying
Jordan 11 comparison
What do you think is going on with Saudi Arabia
Do you think that is
Some kind of a
Power grab by a ruler that
Hey is unwilling to accept any kind of criticism
Alright do you think that maybe
What's going on is
Ruler who is willing to accept
Decided to overreaches power because
Really he was kind of just wanted to test how far is power
Can you do something
Publicly egregious
On the world stage and still get away with it
Okay
I get what you say
This is evidence that I know about this and I don't want to talk about it
That sort of
Level of of reason
The dumbest thing I think we've ever
You can't you can't live
In a world where people think like that
He's not answering
Questions
Do do Orchestra calling you for
Yeah I know baby terrible
We should elected president send second aspect of it
Is the cheese like
Is I give
Context
Question for asking
Official answer
Which is
In order to answer the
The question if you want to real quick if you want a real answer
From somebody
Who has
Quote-unquote remote
Viewed information
You need to
Troll group
You need to have a
Completely
Non
Bastardized
Information
You need
Kerry Cassidy
Say nothing
Kmart
Embark state
Here's what I know
Now is
In that case
Does
Don't care
But it's better than when
Scary things
YouTube Simon Mark Parks Belize
I respect him he's really great
I'm not sure if I really like him
And then
What key spits out is
Agree with what Simon
Sing
I'm going to
Eddie
I remote viewed him
He's deaf
You said that he
Mind control
He definitely
When I go
To Anna strout
I always provide them with
All of the information
What's going on in my life
Clear indicator of what it is that I hope
Can you say hi
Stop stop
Wild to me
How accurate they are in there
Their predictions
What I want to happen in my life crazy something that happened
Pretty good
But they even charge me for this knowledge that they
I feel pretty good.
Almost
Criminal hitters they asked me all of these questions and then whenever I answer them
Give me the answers I want to hear
Banana
This is what she just said
Hundred percent how
Opa definition
How to run a car
You give information
I am running
Yep what you just said
I'm allowing
Khon2
Run
Who cons the con man I don't know
He's making money
Play some innocent
But
Great
It's like if you had a psychic
Cleo was in prison
Her to sell your mother tell your brother
Information that
Mark which I suspect very highly
Is charging her to do the
If we can find
Even if
Be still
2 still making money
I had to cut out all of it but there's like
I'm
I'm recording this from
YouTube video
Sprint hours
Hiram
Throughout Oliver
Is weird
Thing for me to say
Mark
Carrie's relay
I feel like Mark
Kaiser Realty
Creator and I mean if you want to talk about
March
Foreman
Mark Hart
Just can't afford that s***
Jordan
At this point
Think we get
What's going on
Yes I am
Once again once again
We are dealing with
Two person
Who is the
The propaganda
Carrie is doing this
Because she tried
Record it
No
She tried to
Defiled disappear
She thinks that's some sort of
Nefarious
Interference
Whatever
Computer has Bell's palsy
Who cares
We've lost in episode
So because she's
There are a bunch of people in the Stream
And she gets one
But I think is the most
That is ever been
On
Project Camelot
Here's a response
So let's see
Nomar Christmas is not lying
Do you know
Okay
These guidelines is this guy lying to you
Because
You making peace
Think about that
I got straight to think about
You come to the end
A lot
Kind of
I think
Maybe you can
Appreciate
The beginning of this episode.
First time I listen
Through it I thought that was kind of like
It's not as though
Salacious
A lot of the time
Cuz there's not those like big reveals of like
I told her we are like
I mean you're dead
You're dead
Because yeah
Hours upon hours of it
Where is I've only listened
The clips that you
Curated
Right through even at my most
Project Camelot interviews
Self it is 1/100 of what it is you deal with
So when you listen to this episode
Like that kind of
Yeah but even
From Mayans
Like
Don't
Listen Minerva
When when when Alex Minerva
Mark's park has lost from his narrative
When Alex
Disappears in the beach
Podcast
To be called Miss
Where we just talked about
Where we
Minerva is right
Now we should do a bonus
Only for an hour
Might be having
I agree on probably get more
She ate it hope you enjoyed it
Will be back on Friday
Tonight sehat
Alex Jones episode
Arizona website
Buy.com
Acknowledge
Name a smaller subsection of that Social Network I know
I would say
Rehome with
See what it says
Social network
Mining all of our data for
Prophet that is still
Brilliant
Downloads
Fun stuff tell your friend please
Not on any of the places
Promodis all over the internet
Grenada
Badass
We're tragically bad at it
Gotten from all the
Love you we
The world
Might not
Receptive
As we need to
Right
Honor this relationship
We would never kill you
Also we do don't make guarantees on this podcast
You know one guy who is probably killed
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work