Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Blood place
The blood bank
Phlebotomist
I don't even know if
Clean enough
Mostly therapist office
Generally not in
All my life
Bantu
I feel like you know
Or needed
Yeah I like way back
Wayback
I got broke my arm one
Really late at night
Hospital overnight for that
I broke my arm late at night and there's
No story behind
Just 10:30
You trip as far as I recall
Me and my brother had a bunk
I fell off the
Broke my arm
Play in the middle of the night
Course
Physical
Cool
My medical history
The podcast
Medical history and also Alex Jones
Maybe because I've been to mental hospital
Do knowing about Alec
Bango
Sing episode
To go over
Reporting the show
And we appreciate them oh so much first of all
You're now a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Also.
Thank you so much Nick
You are now
I'm a policy wonk
If you yourself out there
Picking up to the portal
Up at the top
Big announcement
We have reached our documents
Yep we
Raptor princess
And gentlemen
Friend of the show
Threw in a bit
Kicked us over that line come on man you've already done so f****** much thank you
Thank you very much but also I think you should not be
Cuz now you're going to have to
To do a documentary
You know what
Six months later now
Around 6
Take me to the last one
Will start
Concrete
Decide which documentaries going to be
It looks like The Obama Deception
I want to make
I want you to give every possible up
For the
To say
I just don't know
I don't know if I want to do that documentary
Determines if that's what we're doing
Hopefully I would like to
Disable start putting those out
Beginning of
I'd like to say
May come into place or will
You know who knows how in-depth some of my research will end up getting
So like it
Hope
November
He could have if not
Then made
Too late November 1st
And
We always knew that
So thank you all very much
For forcing us into this position
Be sure to
Get that for you
Real soon
We could only waffles waffles limit for today
What I wanted to do this earlier in the week that I was working on the 2009
Stop
By the end of the week the cake
You probably be baked
Cake is not bake it is not settled
If so I can
I got to put a pin in
2009 Scion xB
Probably
And so I thought everybody likes
Alex Jones to see what he's up to
People tell you that it wasn't a good sponge
No we have chaos all over the place
Single moment there's a new facet of already existing chaos be
The
Dire warnings
Things coming out about investigation
Trump's family business history foreign countries
The property
All this stuff is going on it's crazy
Stephen King in Iowa coming out
Cairo
Acela white supremacist Faith Goldy
We have to start fights in New York
Mitch McConnell fulfilling the prophecy
Six months ago when I said that these f******
A way for them to actually a text
33rd
Program associate nursing
I don't want to take away from your predictive abilities but that's one of those
It was sound
It was it was
You didn't need a Kerry Cassidy style dream
I hope you see that future
6 hours there were a lot of fires in
TuneIn 95.7
Mitch McConnell
Yeah
Here is an out-of-context drop
From today's show
Oh no poor man
Now I would say that I was
Kind of forgetting that that's not just Kanye's that's also
Alex Jones
It's a little little
It would have been
That's your best
Signature
This morning which is kind of
Set up top
So you would think you would think that delete that Alex comes up
Would be you know something hot
Real import
The geopolitics
20 days 12 days and the title wave of total censorship
Had gone into insane Overdrive
Unbelievable information coming up
Facebook Twitter you-name-it are Banning tens of thousands of pages of anyone
It promotes the NPC memes
It's really a remake of the idea of a
World
NPC memes
Cool man
Memes
You're not on social media so you're probably not even aware of this is the biggest deal of the World by Prince
Oh absolutely
World we live in right now memes memes are the biggest
Number one
You know what that's fine
I don't care memes
Please gray faces on the actual Twitter Avatar not create like a full
Version of them
And then also there's other ones that are just at
Impression of people on the left
Parody
The idea that there was thinking everybody saying the exact same thing
Like they're non-playable characters in a video game
Who just repeat dialog when you walk up to
If I know anything about the right wing
This meme is
Hilarious so funny
Quite like the right way
So funny
Amazing comedian
Overlooked
I mean you got Nick DiPaolo the list goes on
What's his name
Who's number two
Dipaulo's not not
Also
She was relevant 25-year
Alright alright we nailed it
On the right
Lost track
I think he was out making copies
Still relevant to today's office today
Stihl products
Ignored it when it was soda popping around
The people were tweeting about it I was like fell right this is
Cuz it's basic
Like a visual way of them saying
They just figured out a new way to articulate this idea that they
Had all along
And they're acting like a
It's new
And then on the other
Spot-on
The other side of it to that should be like horribly apparent
Anybody who travels
In or listen
To any of the diverse voices on the left
What you know is that basically you just have a bunch of people in places like
Reddit 4chan
Where's the beef
The are their own Echo chamber
Created this image in their head of what Justice Warriors are
And then
Pretending
But that's what everybody sounds like
And now they're creating a parody of this false version of the other side
But they've created in their head then engage with reality
Created
Facsimile of a human
Out of some sort of
Yippee ki-yay
What was the name of that song
Hey dude on Nickelodeon
Donkey
This year
I really do
I don't I don't care about it
I understand one of the reasons
Twitter is like cracking down
Getting rid of somebody's account
Is that they are targeted rest
To a certain extent
If you put
This great thing over someone's face
And you're pretending that you're them
Sure I can go on one level.
Constitutes
So I don't you know I see both sides of this
I think this is up to Twitter to make the decision and live with
You know
To just choose whatever steak you want to make it it
We'll see how the chips fall
I don't Advocate them banning all of them but I also don't think
M2
Don't care at all
No that's my position firmly on the
Yeah
Keep coming back to bunches that like that idea
In life you kind of got to do triage a little bit
Sometimes you may just have to
They're Alex's like how they were gray faces in
Which was I believe the studio there pretty
Sound for Lucas
No no that's that's it was actually one of the beat the roots of that though
Who did the sound for that a lot of Luke
Closest Feldman's
He collaborated with George Lucas on THX one
Which is base
No no no
Talk about it in the same breakfast
Like
It's like
The globalist model for
The future
Basically prophecy
Putting refuses to bring up is that it was basically just a student film made by George Lucas when he was
USB
It was a man
You got funding for it and made it home
First
Directorial film
Yeah it was the working title was American
Thh
Right
Correctly notes parallels Brave New World 19
Thx-1138
Because they're absolutely
Lucas was a goddamn college student in the late sixties in Southern California
Thx-1138 1984
Philosophy
If you borrowed Soma from Brave New World
The bouillabaisse
Lucas wasn't good at making things yet use a young artist
Also the end of the movie is clearly stolen from Plato's allegory of the cave
At the end of the film
Is out running some some
Police drone
Because that
Because they're over budget
Priority for him to
Stop getting to the above-ground realizes
There's birds up there
This is all just
It's just it's very derivative work much like
George Lucas
This is where we are going to be
But
If you take some of the more purely aesthetic stylist
Stick touches which of the things that Alex really gets caught up
I'd like the idea that everyone bald
Aaron shave their head
If you really get rid of some of those stuff
The movie really contain
Central ideas about States
Control one is forced drug
People and
Instilling the mentality that
The economy and money are more important
People's commands
Donald Trump
Has been in office
There been many reports of ice
Independent contractors for medicating immigrant children
Been separated from their families
In order to make them more pliable and man
This is a direct result of the approval of the
Trust
Grisly murder of Jamal khashoggi
United States internal is for the washer
You can post
It appears to be carried out by Saudi Arabia
They're spending $100 on military equipment
Things to create jobs for this country
I don't like the
The concept of stopping an investment of 110 billion dollars into the United States
Because you know they're going to go they're going to take that money and spend it in Russia or China or someplace else
There's almost a literal definition of putting money into supposed economy
Me over someone
Humanity
I excuse about jobs in the economy
Is Ally
From Fox
Overall the private us defenseman just
Does directly employ a lot of us workers
About 350 5526
16th Court
Recent estimates
From the Aerospace in
Industries Association
But
Defense workers makeup-less
Sweet 5%
US Labor
And that includes every person whose job depends directly on the sale or production
Airplane tank
Baume & Service
For the entire US military
It's unlikely that many of them if any depends directly on weapons sale to Saudi Arabia
It's also unlikely.
These jobs advantage of Saudi money
So
You're saying
That the United
Government
Is
Defense
Indefensible idea already at least one guy is
I cannot imagine any
Where in the entire US government
Bekins lying in order to support
Decision in the first place
I would call it a turnover
That would never happen because 110 billion dollar number is not reflect
Civil contractor actual deals
You really look into it involve the convoluted mishmash of letters oven
Letters of Interest definitely nothing really buying
At least
The true number of how much is coming in for these deals it's unclear
But it is definitely
Lower than 110 billion dollars
So even the lie in support of the bad argument that is indefensible is built around another
At least embellishment
Probably outright lie
Target this is also probably from the hill
President-elect Donald Trump registered eight companies during his presidential campaign that appear to be tied to Hotel in
System Saudi Arabia
According to a report in the washer
You can post
The companies in August
2015 shortly after launching his presidential bid
According to the poem
Also at a campaign rally in 2015
They buy apartments in forty million 50 billion am I supposed to dislike them I like them very much
But Saudi Arabia is going to have to help us economic
Just deported indefensible argument that is actually covering up a mass
Corruption
Yeah
I don't know him from being president in the first place under some sort of
Great cool as he things like Pat Robertson come out on the 700 Club
Supposed Christian dude
Why would
This weapons deal
It's great it's great that we now live in a world where I'm sure Jim Bakker saying similar
Obesity
Rallying people around the idea of selling billions of dollars
Weapon
Because that somehow helps their regressive domestic
It's so crazy
Live with
Suggest that we are selling
McFarland
Billions of dollars
Even those billions of dollars which we are selling are then being used to
Commit atrocities
Christian it's going well
Really old crazy dude
But they are with
Just went over there I think you're the nice Bridge
Malik
He's obsessed with that NPC meme
Brittany dog
Are you about a meeting or not
He bridges that with THX
Who described
You listening
Most of the
Sub
Which if you don't
Understand the points of
Really point the finger at the exit.
Trump one of which is this
Humane response
Inhuman
Response
2D
Looking like
Assassination
The regime which I wrote
A very different film
I would say
In the fancy
Be on the side of the guys
We were like
This train
He's a great
Yeah I think you would be on the wrong side of that leaves us
I'm talking about
Indispensable
Group false flag
Iran
But not under his control
Just like Trump isn't controlling most of the FBI
I almost
Are most the CIA
Command
Hillary Obama and other
After this clip Alex had to take
Half an hour off of Ashoka
Throughout his back stretching that far
Razor
Wow that's
Maybe baby
That's maybe the most convoluted
Terrible plan of ever heard
If true
I respect for Obama Hillary and others
Always my favorite Alex meme
I hear this and I'm like this is
Weak stuff
Man
Clear motive
Might be the
Meme
Easter evidence
Like the motive is overwhelming
Because Alex does
Recognize that there's a motive
History of
Disappearing people
Because I reckon
Recognize that there's a motive or
He's not willing
Except
Is very concrete real-world cleartype
Reason that khashoggi would have been
A target of the Saudi Arabia
Like to
They are 20-30
Enticement of
Foreign business
Infrastructure planning
That they're doing this big
This big push
It makes total sense
Garry's Mod
I remember when they did the very first
The very beginning of the beginning of this
Where they're like
Post journalist went into the Saudi consulate
Journalist
A history of
Criticizing the Saudi government
Disappeared inside the Saudi consulate
I was like
Yeah motive motive was not hard to come by
In another lifetime
But I mean like four years ago
Alex would have been screaming bloody murder about this murder of a journalist
Very long time
Dwight
He wasn't totally wrong on that front
To some extent
I don't understand the kids and such a
This is a crazy
Is it
The next eclipse
Popular
The population
You better believe me
Shut up
I mean it'll be recorded because it's in
The consulate
I can imagine
Still exist
You betcha
That seems like security
Then beyond that
Alex
Who are you man you agree with Sean what are you doing
I'm always against
Iprint
The idea of us other countries government
Prorock
You straight up roller on me hates the idea that these neocon Tsar demonized
The Iranian government
I don't I don't know I don't I don't know
I don't I know that
But it seems very difficult
For me
Believe that he's changed so much that he's now for
Some sort of an intervention
In order to prompt receive
So far outside of Alex Jones
Vocabulary
It seemed so far outside
His principal
This is just
Your gun-for-hire you're not even you don't even stand for
There are no prints
I suppose there is not
Post
Team whenever remodel before that
It's it it stopped being about Eddie
Policy
Strategy
And it just became
The Liberals don't
Alex playing
Information about
Situation in Saudi Arabia from
It makes
A surprise you that it's not research
Bazooka
21st president
MSNBC
Saudi Arabia
What's really going on
Deduction my dear Watson
No that's not good
That's bad
That's real bad
Eliminate all other
Don't
Stop trying to defend those possibilities
Batshit
False pretense
Is like that the premises
To be the BNN always lies
As he doesn't believe that Saudi Arabia has a motive
Which
I mean I'm fine
Believing it's possible that
But if you make premise
Saudi Arabia doesn't have a motive
Your argument is bogus
To begin with like from the jump your screw
Whatever conclusion you come to is meaningless
This is not how detective reasoning work
In a like a productive
Do you're just playing dumb
Distraction
Here's to Falls things
Lead to whatever I want you to believe
Not good
Here's the thing
A101 logic
You thinking
We're getting booted out of freshman
At a junior college
Junior College logic
Embarrassed
I know about this
It's
Start with the result
Right right right
Supported in a flimsy way
Women are made of abortion
That's true
I've heard that
Truth it's not about
The news
You know what it's about we all know what it
Right-wing propaganda
Christmas special
Cyber Monday cycle
That's just the way people are
Not sure why we have ourselves
I'm putting them all together now Christmas Black Friday
Score.com
This episode is October 17th
2018 for sale
365 * 0
Everything
Forever forever you know you are doing good
50% off going out of business sale for the next three and a half years
I love that like
Christmas sale starts
Because everything is so awesome
Don't nobody I doesn't know
Far we have heard not one word
That makes sense
No
And it's going to get worse I mean
Very little where we end up ending
Episode is legitimately I was in here like
Why am I doing
I'm not an idiot
Slick nothing like a
Coronavirus
For a very very long time
Fitbit is it matters to the world
He's just dismissing it with
Terrible argument
The end
Just lying about the structure of his argument
And then the other stuff that
Profoundly.
Crazy
Fight
Before we get there
We have to learn about how the global
They don't want you to use
But there is something that you want to use
A Mite surprised
Welcome back in the middle of the meme Revolution
To make everyone Chicago
Going through their Congress
Did you just find a Socialist Party
The Fabian socialists in England
Serbian Awareness on his part that he's late to the meme party
And he's been resisting
To fully embrace
Sing the
BB stupid right-wing meme
Goddamn
Fitbit goes on
He's coming in as if he's like
Oh I know about this all along is part of the Fabian socialist
Alright buddy
Alright
So I think what Alex is operating off of is
About the temp
Fifi meme thing
And maybe it got boards used to talk about
I'm basing that on the side in the middle of this episode he plays
Paul Joseph Watson
Entire report
I am sorry about this
But I do need to play yusupov Joseph Watson
Listening to him because his style is so
Obnoxious
Snarky
It's just full of fast edits and insulting voices that he does in order to characterize
Please be like
This
So just to get two people on board a little bit
Cut this clip is sort of indication of his style
Just so you can get a little bit of a flavor for what you'll be sitting through a few
That's pretty indicative of his thing he does these voices that are characterized by
People he's lampooning
You'll generally use tweet
It's from people that he doesn't like and then doesn't insulting voice
Is robotic usually but that's trying
You get the idea of like all these
People are saying the same thing
They're all otamatone
Lame
Yeah it's pretty late
A bummer how lame that is
You're supposed to be on the Vanguard
Conservative right now
Be better than
Rockstar of the
There's a new punk rock is he likes
To say
Sure you'd be a little bit more
More interesting than just like using other people's tweets
I've proved that everyone that he's against believe the same thing
Like he brings up like a crash
Brothers
I don't know I don't know anybody who agrees with that
Critics
Huey Lewis and the News where the next big thing in Concord
Huey Lewis and the News
He's just trying to take
Alex is like
Rob Reiner speaker
Sure
That's undercooked
Paul Joseph Watson admits
He really enjoys about me
Disconnect
Is it pathetic
So I like bullying people
And I engage in playground insult
Enjoy yourself talk about you
Quick cut
You can always
How heavily ever imagined your job
That you can't speak coherently for I don't know
4 seconds
Like we do edit the show in terms of like sometimes we have to go to the bathroom
Or sometimes
Flips out
Looks like an inside joke
Think like that
Couple things out
Every now and again
But generally were sitting
You're talkin straight through
For two and a half hours
Bill we do not
Embarrassing to look at Paul Joseph Watson
Fantasy Lake
Why why'd you cut there
Those almost the middle of a word
The least exciting
Some sort of Longwood
Everybody
You know it's already liking but remembering Birdman whenever they was that
Interminable long take where they're walking and it
It's filled with drama
And eventually
With the drums playing behind
Attention attention
Exploded
Orange 18 million cuts
Between every single f******
No one remembers rope
For a reason
Now
Call Joseph Watson document
Use it to hang yourself movie
Nothing to do with police
Disconnect
I couldn't ignore
It's because it's go to the central thesis of his
Video
And it speaks to what Alex is trying to pitch
Articulating install
Clearly using Paul is a source
Material for his own reporting
In this clip Paul Joseph Watson
It's making the argument of why people on the left
Are opposed
These empty
DC mean
And one of the arguments that I've seen posted in articles and stuff like that is that it's dehumanize
Anyway
She could what you do if you put a blank
Face over someone else's
Space
And it's like to say all of you are the same
I think Ike mean I understand where people are coming from I don't think I don't care
I don't I don't think
I don't think that
Schoolboy Q
Shirts
Is is necessarily a real
Reason to
Be against
Leave memes I think that
The target is harassment aspect of it is much more salad
But Paul Joseph Watson's version of ateez
They hate this because they know
That the left
Can't meme
But the right
Baby we can meme
Edit doing so in making this argument he cites something
Here's the issue with this
No We Came Upon This
Because it's very Damonte
Super horn
Poachers bottom is misusing the study from the University College of London
Because of course
He didn't click the link
In the BBC article that he's summarizing or in the vice write-up
That he is saying characterizes
Is the study
Do you really have no idea what even says past the characterization the pole in the Donald are effective distribution
That's the only
Messenger
F****** read the study
If he had some information
It doesn't really help his argument
Cemetery much at all
First from the study
Our work focuses on for Webb community
Twitter Reddit Politically Incorrect board
Be even later safe note that we exclude mainstream communities like the rest of Reddit other than the
Donald subreddit
Twitter Hazard mangle
Fringe web
Communities
The only looked at four places in the study
The concluding They Come Away with his at the Donald Borden
On Reddit
Import
Give me platform
Really the conclusion more accurately state is Gavin Ghost Town
A Twitter mostly exists to the secondhand store or Thrift Shop of
That's really the conclusion that you should take away from this
Now
Second
Paul Joseph Watson and read this study
You would have found that one of the main takeaways for the from the study was
Communities within 4chan Reddit in Gabby's memes 2
Are hateful and racist
Among the most popular clusters of meme
We find variance of
The anti-semitic happy Merchant
They say in the study that means that these communities are used to
Express racist
Quote evidence from the popularity of the anti-semitic happy merch
Which depicts a greedy and manipulative stereotypical caricature of a
Verjus contrast Twitter
Play Heartless neutral meme which are rarely used in hateful Kant
One of the big takeaways again from the study was quote
Capture hateful and racist meme at a higher rate than mainstream communities
A considerable number of somatic and pro-nazi
Fosters
This trend is steady overtime for for chance pool board but ramping up recently with gap
Quote there are several takeaways from our measurements of
We show that Paul is generally speaking the most influential disseminator of memes in terms of raw influence
In particular it's more influential in spreading
Relatedly Paul has generally more influence
Terms of spreading political memes than other communities
What the study ultimately found
Is the pole is the most
Influential meme Source in the realm of their state
But they were woefully inefficient
Which is to say that they post
Tons of memes there
And a lot of them don't catch on but the ones
You are really popular
In contrast
The Donald subreddit has a way higher than expected
Efficiency
Which is honestly what you shouldn't
That's the prettiest large just base in little more than a means of weaponizing infer
Information and misinformation in a coordinated way
Exactly
Define Alone number of unique meme
Each one push
Any unique
Unified
Focused way
Paul Joseph Watson
What to use this study
Two things that he's a starting namely that it demonstrates why Liberals are afraid of me because his side is better attempt
He needs to accept this entire study
Not just a piece of it feel good to him
I know that would be inconvenient it to the middle of this darky rant. To just stop and point out that a large part of
Dissemination
And how the very places
The framing is being on his side or full to the gills
With anti-semetic characterizations of
And more less never-ending racism
Cuz that would be very difficult to put in with your
Is there a weird
But he likes
The quote
Bright everybody just assumes
Right now
I've explained to you what that study really says
And why it's not really
Any evidence that Liberals are afraid of me
Is Egypt again
Just studied
Fringe places
You going to throw away
Then
Demonstrate
Ain't nobody on Gap but people there are
Paul Joseph Watson is coming in
You know with this like I read an article on Vice
Said this one to act like I know everything about it
Just
A minute later it is Special Report
Paul Joseph Watson
Serious cultural engagement
Where is the consumption
Florida Blue
I mean
So
Is that the right
Is so
Great
His argument
Is those that
Let's just say
Consume memes
Easily digestible passive pieces of culture
With political opinion
Just a modicum of research
Help you
You need to go says
Once Bitten
Vice article and then decided
What are we doing research study dickweed I know it's hard but like
If you're going to end up exactly
I feel invigorated by glycol I did read that study
Slightly different things or what
I just hate I hate it the in the same breath
I have such a robust
The mark political beliefs
This is what I do
Research into this.
In the same sentence
Manifesting not doing research
And then he ends with a false characterization of
People
Nazi
Playground
I'm not triggered by this I just think it's
You don't I mean
I think generally speaking is best not to talk about
About him cuz it's it's a game that you want
Yeah
I just
It's fun
It's fun went dumb people act
Bit of Silence
Or pause
Proves far more effective
Or perhaps
More interesting
Jumpcut so there is
Is literally no space
Between the end of
Any
Freakish and disconcerting
Because if you pause too thin
For a single second
Can you be like
Oh that's f******
Much harder to edit
His stuff
You like those
Vic Berger would have a much harder time using Paul Joseph Watson
Footage
Oh yeah
Make precise chops
In order to get
Clips
You would want
Here is it
Here's what he saying
Because he's talking to Michael a minute
And there are no brakes
In the dialogue
What is Eddie's job is terrible
He's terrible at his job if his job is journalist
He's not bad at his job is
Distraction
Rodeo clown propaganda
He's pretty good at
Within
If
You consider
Like if you look into
What he saying
Yes
Gambit the gamble is always knowing
Terrible but Home Improvement was a very pop
Snarky comment about that about how like
But not about Home Improvement How I Met Your Mother
So Alex and the next
He's back
Use related to check 11
2mp
Casey meme
But then he also relate
Commercial from 34 years ago
The one where the lady throat Hammer throws into the big television
I don't remember
I wasn't watching 8 hours ago
Just
But that was from the Olympics
This is Alex
No
Okay
You need to call
Need
It's a little
It's a little unnerving
But how much potential he thinks
Cuz you know what's funny
About this
This is like when we
We go back
To 2009
News about
Who's house blew up Alex's veritiv for a find out
Crazy dude and then like a week later Alex's
Listen to
All this is going to be the next month
That's what this is but just did
It's like in present day
I live in igloos
I don't even know why anyone
UCare this is
Cotton candy
It doesn't feel you up it's not good for you
It's
It's just there
For the right-wing find a way to make that
Cat
Prices on that Call of Duty
Guys are terrible
Regis.
A little bit about
His best friend
Donald Trump
He wants to tell you that
He's basically Jesus
You sacrificed so much for you
If you don't even
You don't even care
Really
2% control
Tim Duncan's net
Enemy
Withstand all the peer pressure the two billion dollars he's lost his fortune lawsuit
Golf Course deals Boston
Us
I love this country
Show me to be president be present but I got to do it
I just can't watch him
Watch the country
Everybody Skrillex
A good map
Scotland
The point is is that
Trump
Charity never tells anybody
Liver kidneys
Aspen
You need to stop listening to Rochester
Charity was
Famous for I thought it was giving away so much money to charity
30 was out to him and his family
You know I don't I don't
I don't have concrete proof that he doesn't help
Videos of employee
You bought it
I don't know that
To be true or not but I do know other things that are true such as him not paying it
Contractors
Consistently
Like if you have somebody who's such a
Generous
Giving person
I bet they would buy an employer house cuz they're having a bad time
Something like that
Generally wouldn't
I'm not sure what he says the tightest people alive I'm not sure if
Old timey slang for drunk
That's old British slang for drunk
I don't know I don't know if that's the case
Probably
Shoehorn
No idea
Is Mom now Alex
New York Times
New York
That was up
What's up
His father
Good
So I am fine from
Violent
I can't find any evidence
The Fred Trump ever beat up a bunch of Communists in New York during the skirmish
However
On the Border
Cool Cuts Clan
And Italian fascist sympathizers
There's which led to the deaths
The Italian
Why were they later
Later in Queens a little at least members marched
Memorial Day week
Pissed off a bunch of folks
Another brawl Stars
And the aftermath
One of these men was Fred
Donald Trump's dad
It's unclear based on all public records exactly what he was up to but the bra when she was in was between
Representing Protestant nativist outrage
And the Catholics representing
The group that the Protestants felt they were being oppressed
Trump
The other six men who were arrested were all claimed
The argument has been made that the other six men were charged where is Fred was released at Dusty must be
Maybe the pace equally likely he was the only one
To be rich New York
A lot of people have
I tried to make the argument that before this
Fred Trump
And that's not true
At this point he'd already built over
20 homes or houses
In Queens
I'm sold
So he already had a pretty
Good amount of land
At his disposal
He wasn't the billionaire
That he would end up
Multi multi-millionaire
20 loaded
To bribe
Notoriously corrupt
New York judicial system in the 20
Cheap
Notoriously corrupt
You didn't you didn't you needed
Slightly upper-middle-class
Did you did you just a good bright now ask for comment about this Donald Trump with less than subtle
He has nothing nothing to do with this never happened this is nonsense and it never happened
This never happened
Little over-the-top all night denial
Anything is possible here except for the idea that
Did Fred Trump beat up
There are some reports that I can find I'm not sure
Exactly how solid
These are of
But
Some reports
Contemporaneous
Worrying Clan Ricky
I don't know if that's the case it's not from the New York Times article
But there's some indications
Costume
Lawyer
Call Mama
Alex
Send a text with explains why Trump
Esports the NPC meme
30 showmax to cover today it is just unbelievable
We have
Honduras and Guatemala
Aftermath
Launching
Sterilized
And it's been going on for years about a body
Humanitarian
Promise
This morning
With an H
Honduras and Guatemala responded
Migrant Caravan after Trump
Associated Press
Diplomatically
Confront playing a foot down
I notice you got borders
Story that Alex is trying to
The page that Trump threaten to stop all foreign aid
To Honduras
Guatemala
Caravan
Presenting a story is being cut and dry
We're trying to come up from Hunter
Trump threatened to cut for
To the country and their president
The couch across the Bold americafirst machismo
No no no I don't need to hear these Dan obviously correct we can move on
Trumpism
The first problem really been to the will of trump
Mexico is
Deport the refugees in the Honduran Caravan should they end up
In the Border
The most Honduras Ministry
Maybe people
Making false
Promises to the refugees that they'll be able to speak
And that they should not let themselves be
Movement that is so there is obviously political
And upside is meant to upset governability
Stability
Just possibly me and you ask yourself
I think it's about Whitey
I was just
No
Read the rest of this associate
First article but if he
Read the article.
Beauty quote
Fernando Andrew leader of the governing National party planned opponents of Honduras president
Behind the migrant Exodus
It's a strategy plan opposition
Familiar rhetoric
American
Maybe not so popular presidents
Who is gotten into power
The Association of America
States have been like
There's a lot of irregularities with your election
And now he's trying to
Demonized
How to get out of the country
Soros is behind it
The second issue here is that the threat of cutting off
To do anything
It was threatening to literally close the southern US border and send in the military
Do that
In the strongest terms X
Mexico Mexico to stop this onslaught
And if possible to do so I will call up the US Military
Adult apps
Close our Southern border
It refers to ref
Trying to
Steve their lives
Buy Coming to America
And on
It should go without saying but according to Alex
Belief about the president
TV's RV operating to mess
Alex to be livid about that tweet
Unless you consider this not a domestic action
Which advocated war with Mexico
And I guess Honduras
Save it
Castaic Lake
On the Border
Put in 10 to the four corners
All the states of the same time
Okay
About 4
He said he would quote
Countries with
Which seemed to have almost no control over their population
The thing that Alex Jones yells about the most
The biggest fear that he's ever had the idea of a government having
All over their population
AT&T Oculus comment from a politician he doesn't like
Is magically transformed it approved
The government is trying to
Control him
Weatherby B
Precious gun
Or just by making a
Feel bad but he's accused bigot
In reality
This is largely a replaying out of attention
What happened back in April
When a group of about
That people walked up from Central America to the border of an annual symbolic Proto
As well as an attempt for many of them
The Border
Intentionally turn themselves in
Libra silence
Trump's our report about this on Stockton
Immediately
Tweeted out that this was an invasion
I threatened to send in the National Guard
According to the guardian
Cut off
Earlier
Both threats were ultimately
But
In April Mexico did not stop the rest
Fugees from reaching
In the Border
IRadio music
We were afraid but the Mexican Government responded humanely insensibly
We didn't expect that
We thought they would came to Trump but they didn't
One of the members of April Caravan was Chanel Smith twenty-seven-year-old trans woman
From Honduras
Discrimination
It said gangs were approaching the trans population to Peddle drugs
She refused and was told to change her mind Within
Open 24 hours
Instead she West
Another was Jocelyn Amador 22
Who operated a small business selling mobile phone accessories in San Pedro Sula Honduras
But the also had to flee after being Unable to pair of
$125
Extortion payment
Another was Isabel Niro Rodriguez
2 years old who also played after extortion
She tried to open a bakery in El Salvador but again
Hundred dollars
As a fee for starting operation
I threatened to kill her grandson if she didn't pay
The Mexican Government respond to their destination
Sending them back to is very likely
In June 2018 the Department of Homeland Security reported that from April 19th
To May 30th
At least 90
895 children were separated from their families at the border
Navigation
To come out about rampant physical and sexual abuse of detainees
Medication
Administration to be considering implementing the family separation policy since his literal Inauguration Day
Put a policy in action
The Mexican government
For not stopping the refugee Caravan in the spring
This isn't just me make me lose conjecture
The guardian even makes the connection
Very clearly
The Mexican Government allowed hundreds of migrants mainly Hunter and
To reach the US border
Irrigating truck
Initiated the family separation policy soon after
Beyond the human tragedy
Artifact on Refugee
Further analysis
The cost of housing people who were detained under Trump separate
Implants averages out to about
$775 per person per day
As opposed to
$6 per person
A day under the
In order to compensate for this
Cost of being cruel to
Almost inhuman level
The Trump Administration announced a plan to shift more than
60 million dollars
There was supposed to go to HIV and cancer
Recovering cost
The separating
If I had to guess
I would say that
Doesn't care about other people
But because who knows
Holographic
Med badge
The Cure All diseases
Are right around the corner
And spending any money trying to cure cancer
F*** all that noise
I don't know I don't know how to put a button
No this is all is all bad
Sitz bath
What's sex
From the show first
Ouch
Stop recording for a little bit
Take a breather on that
Alex b-monster about
Very predictable things
I think that we've seen
Play out already even the last
You know it's really tough
Experience that without having
Some sort of visceral reaction
That's wrong at all
I did not predict how
Necessarily
Propaganda
Will you swim in this all very viscerally affected
Viator
Is anybody else
At the same time
I didn't say that
The immediate reaction but
Whatever because
I mean I'm not saying you're succumbing to
Is the judgment
When you have people who outwardly
You talk and relishing the idea of
Bullying
I'm in trying to make
People angry for fun and Sport
Whenever you spend
14 hours a day studying
Andron digging into
The methods of their propaganda
It gets to a point where for me
Especially
I realize that that's part of their game
And I'm
So
Averse
Them getting what they want
For everybody
The first time that
That's true
Initial reaction
You are doing this
Listen to different way where is it
Is all just hitting
If you have enough desk
Jordan
What's good news is
Look
Bleak
Real bad but there's one Shining Light Of Hope
And that is that Alex has a plan
Infowars.com
Betty's very bad
Everyone just keep making
We're going to create a whole section for me
Like some sort of
Racist racist
Because it's means that threaten the most
Superfast
I do not know why
Online I do know why the first thing he comes up with
Not racist whatever
One be racist meme
Is well-served on the internet
There's not a need for another one already
Swimming pools going to fail on that level
Second
Alex
Check out
Message Board already check out
Your comment section
Plenty of racism already
Yeah you don't need plenty of Christianity plenty racism
No not at all
Already accomplished
This is like
Just discovered this is like your ex
Explaining to Grandpa why there are too many browser extension
It would be like you
Be like damn
I got to tell you about that going
If you're telling me today
Exciting technology on the ground
It's f****** cat
They can play a goddamn
Piano
I don't even know how
Not as many points there
It's just a little katsuto keyboard
Jordan Jordan
If you heard of Starbucks
We got to get some
Comstock
So what is a Macintosh
Like what is a Macan
It's looking at
The kind of apple that's why Apple named
Clever
Alex
That works out there
No
Facebook
Wannabe band
So that's what he says
Now immediately after that
Show eyeshadow
Miserable just don't go further that you don't let them go
Govern
What Akshay
I'm going to go on there and say what I really feel
Before the election
That really sounds like he's like I'm going to get them to Vera me which is intentionally getting yourself.
Because I'm saying things that I hourly or would have stopped myself from
I don't know either
Cool out
There's a piece of that and then there's also duck opposition
Defiance human resource director
Or to the idea
So I'll be the first one in the band pool
Or whatever
Say flagrant
Misogynist
Or antisocial
Employees
Thank you Dad
Iraq
This whole episode
I should be
I turned it off
Because
Gino's in weave
We've gone down these roads of
Outer bulshit smacking like
Just eat human on
Most of the time that we quit so we haven't played our all him talkin about this me
Over the moon with this mean
Then
I don't understand
It's a good to me
It's really my baby in socialist
Ian
Because it restricts speech
You need you need memes
What
Look it's not
Then he gets a little bit of
Hatred for Beto
The Rock
Because Alex
Super into Ted Cruz
I would remind everyone that he was
What Donald Trump primaries
Lion
Even says it's a national emergency
Doesn't win
His election
And I take the
Two pieces of this one
Solve this seriously before cuz
Take the beta was a serious
Reading a lot about
Pandora support
I think there might be a little
Need
Really anti
Here's the first clip of
A creepy pervert
Like run a mortuary or something to like kidnap
Shop
But
He would be
Text Michelle
Cool
Like the subway founder
Worship
Shut up
Central Casting pugs
Look like slime pieces of crap
But you wouldn't let children
Abort your children
Kill yourself
Cool man you just hit the trifecta
So in his mind got bingo
Terrible if he called them pet
He can say they want to kill your children before their
Sure
Pedophiles
Central Casting
Give me their great-great in fantastic public service but they look like
BV like a
Like that
Gross
Like what he's doing there is so gross
Coupling
Like
Elementary
Irresponsible
It's loathsome
I just listen to stuff like that and I'm like
That's the kind of thing I don't know I got better
Call them pedophiles
As a brilliant
Get get all the riffraff to quit Infowars cuz you are at
It like my life as it is
Like maybe
Possibly
Maybe I'm fishing in a dry well by really trying.
Understand Alex Jones
I understand
But even I
Is fully committed as I am today hear s*** like that
I got better
I don't know why this guy's
Even doing the showing this is not
Add in the added layer 2 of like
Did you nasty stuff
The multi-level marketing Incorporation
He's got in on I don't know I haven't heard about it but I don't listen to
I don't anymore cuz it makes me feel like it makes me feel like I'm not doing any
You know th
Point the finger at Paul Joseph Watson for a snarkily saying everyone should do research when he hasn't done any himself
View about the
Deandre
Caravan stuff
We can do that
Sure
But the rest
I want to tell you something
Say what you want
Scene with Darth Maul at the end of
The show is dogshit
I'm doing nothing
Next clip is about where I was like
Alright I'm out
I wish you well Alex I don't need to listen to this anymore
I'm sorry
How you doing
Problem a transmitter
Somebody great right-wing comedian
Waterrower
That was not good
California
Affect
Obama
Just get out of my state you scumbag
Beto grew up in
There's
Alex is not as good as his daddy.
Trump at coming up with the
Answer people cuz
Scallywag O'Rourke well because he's a said carpetbagger right before that
Associated is fine
Scallywag
I don't think it is I think it's a bad term
I remember I looked this up a while ago I think it's actually like
He's just ignore vernacular but we don't
I can't remember what it was there's another one I looked up
Scallywag cantankerous
That's weak
This week
Comedy bit of like my earpiece isn't working
And it goes on forever that clip is almost a minute long
Pecos Eva
Further with it
I don't know
Like I hear stuff like this and I'm just like I got it
It's kind of like being around someone you don't want to be around
My job to be around someone no one wants to be around your Valley
But like I just like
I want him to do better
I'm not getting any
I'm not getting anything out of it
And I'm just hearing and be like
Beto O'Rourke
This is
On the same show the Paul Joseph Watson
Is basically saying like
We just do playground insults then when you respond poorly to it we keep doing it cuz that's what
Hear him do this this name-calling game I like
You can do better
He hasn't yet
You could do better maybe.
He is like the
Curt Schilling of radio host
That nobody pays
He's lost his fast
That is fair
Resort at 2 noises
Because
It's so bad so dumb I don't know
I know that there's not a ton of people listening
Somewhere
And something better places for your raising
Like
If anything's
What did diminished quality in Alex's show is probably doing
Is pushing people too much harder
Stop
You know what's going on there
I'm laying here having a meeting
No
Bennigan's would no longer handle the alright anyway got to respect Bennigan's
It's not a popular decision they're going to get a lot of bad Yelp reviews but
Pakistan Subway
Yes or no will be back on Monday with whatever probably 2009
Cuz I can't
I can't do this yeah we got it
Take a break.
Nothing but a trap
Knowledge underscore what if you wanted to watch The Social Network
You could do that
I think you're
Do what
Cuz I was that how you would do it maybe maybe it's on Amazon Prime
Baby fight on YouTube
Alright can we
We can do the whole thing
What's up Dan
I feel like you've got some information
You been hiding this for
So long
Time to come clean well I would say
I don't have a lot of experience
Dance with gaming
It's not like
It's not a big part of
By and large
NPC
Non playable character
Have dialogue with
Like
Skyrim have you talked to somebody
Yeah there's a lot of that
Generally speaking you can't really play the game without the
Precipitate a lot of the action
And a lot of the time they don't kill you
But one guy I dunno
Somebody
Probably
NFL
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work