Alex
Bit by Alex
Name three cities in Australia
Yeah
Perth Queensland
First Melbourne and Adelaide
Play whatever I'm America
Riverbend
Shut up
Shout out to Australia and sorry that I've mixed up with cities we're not entirely sure
American
I'm coming out also sorry about the political situation in
I can actually
Pretty calmly say to everyone
Apologize
Giuseppe
Welcome aboard so much Chris
Chris thank you so much
You know I got to
Very exciting
Someone has taken a donation and bump it up
Bathroom
It'll be about.
Thank you so much from the bottom of our hearts
You are now a Raptor
Princess
Someone sodomized
I don't want
Tara Reade
Control
I bet you money
Abused
Joseph Stalin
Photos
Welcome to McDonalds may I help you
Report showing what we do you can do that by going to our website knowledge fight.
Cast about Alex Jones probably is not going to get Commerce on our side
Micro Target ads
But be there
We're going back
We are speaking
Track
In the investigation
Yep and we know for a fact
Soros
Mystery will be solved
Come back if you were doing in the middle of 2019 maybe we'll have a name
Panther portal
Still download the episode but you don't need to listen to it
Will be for the reveal
I guess I don't know.
It's just a big buck right
I remember when I was a kid being overwhelmed by the size of it
I just did I just
What do you mean there's a sense of accomplishment
Read the last page
Going to be that great but if you read all of it the last page probably awesome
Pretty great
Infinite Jest
Austin Dune to be like two examples of books
That just needs to be as like sort of stereotypic
Example
I don't know
I'm just
I think I kind
Sure
Once he gets to the list of movies
We're going over March 13th 2009 today
He's a big old day in history
I know I mentioned last week that this episode was kind of difficult for me because he brings up a number of things that
The research
I didn't want to take
Too many
We end up
Discussion about something we end up with that
6 hour episode on
The fight because there's a lot of meat to get into
And then on top of that
There's something you need to know
Chuck Norris
Eastern
Nearest shop email
Leaves
Minute Alex where he's talking to his
We really got to get these emails together I understand
I left at 6
602 View
Motherfukers
Furious about it cuz I'm in limbo right now
I tried to write him back this morning but I haven't heard back
I'm on air now what am I going to do
Come on man
Did you leave your work at the office
It's 602 let me tell you something
Chuck Norris
No my work email if Chuck Norris
And be like I'm going to come roundhouse kick
I don't know
Check already was
President
Metaphorical
But
Pack
Episode
I also I will say spoiler alert Chuck Norris
Okay
What things it pisses me off so much
Play The Walker
Ranger theme
Play him onto the show
Cuz it would be perfect for him
Play the theme song from that's my jam right there
Weather Ranger
I love that pizza me and Nikki gift live together back in Missouri he was going through a bit of a walker to
Texas Rangers
It's a realtor.com
Valuing that show man
Okay
All of them
And they're all the same
Extra tall
Anyway Chuck Norris is going to show up a little bit later
Wasn't that was not show just essentially
Texas Ranger
That really doesn't make me feel comfortable
Turn around
Yeah yeah
Anyway the reason that Alex wanted to have
He's going to
To do
Episode of
And
There's talk
Videos going to
Is going to make a big amount
You're absolutely right
He just wants to scoop
Eddie and the mad about this
To check doors
Conceivably since the last time he mentions in that club
And then
Kiri check
Is going to be on Glenn Beck show and he's shooting at an email
ASAP
This is the response
Becca's going to take this one from me what am I going to do realize there's a
Decent chance
He's already
Cuz I don't think it's alive.
Two are so
Let me let me just put the pin in this
There is no scoop
Alex
You could announce he's running for president of Texas
Because that's what like really bad presumptive media it started throwing away a lot of the blogs that Alex
Information from
Been like
Is Chuck Norris
That sort of thing is going to be the one who brings us back
Bowflex
Really badly
Here's the clip
Of him disappear
Get them on before he talks to Glenda
Hours notice
If that will happen because obviously I can have them on next week
He's
Chuck Norris's
Probably going around
I think he's doing a lot of fat I think in 2019
Is it the Chuck Norris fact
I seem to recall around this time
A big part of his PR strategy was really embracing
Does joke
Congratulations everybody
In this next clip we get back to one of the narratives
It's been really robots
Did Miss March
. of time in that
Is the documents
Alex
Misunderstands much like a junior high
Eli's more about it
Two days ago we broke the news
With a standard system update
Are they also recommend
Sergeant
Phone numbers
Additional
It is real
He's making that Elementary
He makes about
The idea that
Just to drive it home again
The idea of this doctor
Commence sayings
The people who are malicious
Often
Are supporters of Ron Paul
Does not mean
If you are wrong
You are suspicious to me of being in one of the
These groups
He believes those two statements are equivalent
Depart
Vicky thinks
Disinfo agent
Are saying
You're wrong about
And choosing to respond to
If what they're saying is this isn't real
It makes the next Baltimore funny
Realize
But there is that lion
People say we exaggerate the other way around
Overestimating
It's far worse than
He's holding restraint
He is keeping himself under control for your benefit
What if there were a billion people on the border
His narrative right now like in 2009 involve a shadowy group
Of all powerful
Super rich
Individuals that are all working
Sing together
And their plan is any
The dollars and when civil unrest breaks out they have can't build everywhere
People in forcefully anybody who talks up
They will release bio weapons
At which point I guess the rest of
Ulcer
To these globalist to have armored without
And then I guess kill the rest I don't know
How could he not be like
At least trying to say he would like
That's what he talked about 9% of the time
At least
That's actually part of
The FEMA camp
Committee
FEMA all the Federal Emergency
Goodwin right now
Because I hate masculinity
Well then I guess it's
Sure
That's religion silly but in this next clip we get to
Start at the beginning of one of the B
Neat
He's going to be talking
And this is actually super complicated
That I'm able to adequately
Break this down but I also
Dua to stress that you should have Quest
Because this is
Anyway here's the first clip of Alex
About
Globalist
.
Record
Powerful group
The same thing we do everyday
Conquer the world
So you don't care
Just do it
And the Brain
You don't say
Conquer the world
How can you do it everyday
How can conquer the world
Wow there's a new worlds to conquer every time you wake up
Upser
It seems like
We're going to conquer the world
Do you see it is boring I see it is like a motivational poster
So in the middle of this episode here
Alex
Impromptu history lesson
Which offers us
Context clues
He's getting his information
In this case
Because he mentions The Milner
Literally no doubt
If there's only one
Part of this is because most Scholars many of them don't believe that the Milner group
Conceived
The formal body acts
Do we ever exist
Okay
Group of work together in the British
British established
In the early
All the information about The Milner group
Books by Carroll Quigley
The anglo-american establishment
And tragedy
In the books
Professor Quigley lays out what
He's researched about these groups that operated
Behind the scene
He's concluded that groups like The Roundtable group
The society
Association of helpers
Elements
Which he is titled
League of Extraordinary Gentlemen
Absolutely
Extraordinary
Sean Connery playing
Everyone knows it everyone knows
You don't have you don't have them there I thought I had a story about falling asleep
Boring story
The group The Miller group is named after Alfred Milner
M1891
The story presented in Quickly's work isn't interested
Until
It's something that lacks back and support from a lot of other scholar
Quigley himself offers Vista
Adduction to the anglo-american
Establishment
Naturally it's not possible for an outsider to write about a secret group without falling
The errors
Terrorism
I feel also that there are few Miss statements of fact
Except in one most difficult matter
He doesn't care
Whew misstatement
The facts
Accepted one most difficult
The difficulty arises from the problem of knowing just who is and who is not a member of
The group membership may not be rather on frequent socialist
Incense the frequency of such Association
Different person
The person
It's not always easy to say who's in the group who is Notch
Caveat
You don't know who's in the
The group I got the broad Strokes of it
A major players who are definitely
The fiends
Deeply involved in British foreign policy colonialism in the early 1900s
Percent but then a lot of the conclusions
Are based on assumption
Who is or is not in
Dissociative
Even innocent
A unified
Or if there's just like
Oh this one group is
That they do act
This other group does why
But sometimes there
They're a little bit
Hitmaka.
They're working together
We are discreet stepper
Groups
There's a difficulty about that
But foremost
Facebook
Islam
Until
It reads
Like a scholarly book
And it doesn't seem like he's making
Seems like
Plausible
I just don't like any book that opens with a preemptive
Sure I didn't tell the truth
Sure it is tough CouchTuner like
How could I
Until there's a little bit of
About that
Interesting
Because they don't say what Alex said they
What does the same thing as Alec
What is the Naked Cowboy
A 1970 book by
Your buddy W Cleon skousen
Love him which is little more than attempted
Quigley's tax
Never said
Quickly instead of scouting book
Book is full of Miss reference
Plantations and factual errors
He claims that I've written
Conspiracy of
The super-rich were pro-communist
And wish to take over the world and that I'm a member of the
You're going to save to the whole life
He was lying about it
Because how else could he know this information
Member of this group
Pieces of
Carol Quigley's worldview is
He's
Describing these group
They have the influence that they had
The time that they had it
That influence
Deteriorated
40 Sprite
Is work when it's being used by
Skousen
He says
No
They never stop
And to say
Just have some influence
Had all of the influence
Make that make sense
W Cleon skousen in the naked capitalist
Argues
Part of these groups
And this
Partial revelation
Is
Hiding the real truth
Which is worth
Cleon skousen
Edward Alex Jones
Pretends is what
So it's almost like
Skousen is saying that the Eastern deity company is X
Are we still in operation
It has been running
You can make that analog there
Only 8000 copy
1300 page book
But no publisher would expect to move copies
Enter W Cleon skousen
Who's the
Add extra pages
Anti-communist propaganda conjecture you have a book with Mark appeal
He claimed a year after printing that he sold over
55000 copies
He was being distributed through the Liberty Lobby
If you don't recall the Liberty lobby with the outlets
Willis carto
Found the populist party
Through the Liberty Lobby cardo published Spotlight which was literally created specifically
For the purpose of quote mobilizing the public
He sought to use of publication
The fan the Flames of government
In order that they come together again
Against the Real Enemy
And quotes
Right communism nationalism
Picture here
In essence Alex Jones has mold
Around the absolute
Temptation of Carroll Quigley work
Which was published
Demonize communist
And it was published
Promoted by Holocaust deniers
Who made their life's work
Demonizing
You are going to move
If you call it Harry Potter in the middle
That is going to have
Vitale
Is getting this from Cleon skousen
Absolute
But he never said that
He always says that he's getting it from white papers
State tragedy
He never says oh I got this from a notoriously Santa
Communist propaganda
Who is aligned with the Liberty Lobby
W Cleon skousen
Has papers you can get
Barry White
And the funked-up thing is it's not be
Because W Cleon skousen would be a name that'll be like a verb
Alex's show
His nephew
You Joel skousen is on
He's a regular cat not like
This would be some taboo I think Alex on sublevel knows that there's more credibility to
Carroll Quigley
Then Cleon
Angle
This guy wasn't
Presented as the original Angela
Birthday Ava
Research something that is unknowable
And
Lying about those still further
Sure one of the other things
Cookies and Hitler early on
You bet they did
If they absolutely did
Crucial error and regret it
So
I think
Most people did
And that boat one Holocaust anything
This might have been a bad idea
Holocaust
Now we're in the kind of like
224 Holocaust
Minimum
For people to change their mind
Glimmers of what Alex
Is getting misrepresented
Cleon skousen
If you look at
Attacks of
I'm here I'll read you a little Passage
1936 whittler
Just broke several
Treatise
Members of The Milner group in of the British can
Conservative government
The fantastic idea
They could kill two birds
Eastern Europe
In this way they felt that the two enemies would still make one another or the Germany would become satisfied with the oil of Romania and
The weed of Ukraine
It never occurred to anyone in a responsible position to Germany
And Russia might make a common cause
Even temporarily
Against the West
Even lasted it occur to them that Russia might beat German
And that's open all Central Europe to V
From Carroll Quigley
Who has looked at their
Friends
Among the people that he's writing about
Yeah
Does anybody who's had
To the folks
But he's writing
Jesus hurting
That
This was an oops
You hate to say that about WWII
They chose
The single worst
Strategy that you possibly could
Until it was
To like
MMA were and then they were like
Foolish view of
Everything foreign policy
But you can also kind of
What's the British
Early 1930s headed distorted
But also from that
Part of the angle make American establishment
Integrate
How
There's obviously
Issues
In France
Doesn't care about
Some sort of balance
Giveaways it
You could
Not have all that WWII preferable
Until there's that Holocaust
Talk about this without getting a little bit
Is
This Miller group
Supposedly main forces Bhai
Alfred Milner
Cecil Rhodes
That is cousin
Derek Whitman
No
Do you know how Rhodesia got its name
It's named after Cecil Rhodes
All this saying that Alex
Who's lying about all this
They were deeply involved in
In the colonization of Africa
And
Did horrible
Here is the neck
Best clip from Alex's
Discussion of
Hitler David David
The Milner group
Said something else
Me to nowhere
Divide and conquer
Fascist or right-wing
The Socialist
Big 4S
Western Europe
Hitler
So
This
Creative life
Which would be
Very ironic
That would be
I don't know I think Alex is taking the real pieces that exist in the world
Hitler and him being supported by
Industrialists
For a while
Udoka
Avenue
Become more serious when the party power and stuff like that you know
Has never made that mistake
We can't really understand now
Understand
Do mean
He's getting this from to
A 1971 Gary Allan's none dare call it
Conspiracy
In once
I'm from and misrepresented Carol quickly
Quickly
Much for none dare call it
They thought dr. Carroll Quigley
Affect
Bitlord Milner the dominant Trustee of the Cecil Rhodes trust and heavy in the group
Help Finance
Through the greater part of Milner's private papers and found no evidence to support
Sing about the Creator
What was reflected in
B that I read
You from his book anglo-american
Come up with some balance
Power with Germany in the middle of Europe
Andrusha / 2
The Beast
And hope everything works out
That does not mean that they created a Bolshevik Revolution or they
Created Hitler
Alex
From these bastardize sources of the original material
The Fall Guy Dan
You know who is funding them
Probably the Rothschild
Alchemy Soros Soros
Sherlock
Westeros
So in a March 23rd 75 article
Hampton post
Okapis began to spread across the
Quickly began to grasp with a selective unauthorized quotation from his work
The approach to history taken by the authors
None dare call it
Scholastic sensibilities
Against the misinformation he felt was being disseminated with the aid of
My reputation
Can quickly said
Scholarly historians were going to say he's one of those
He's kind of feel for the guy you know cuz there's not much
Can do Willy's response book was 800 more pages
Regal Research
Distinction
But what you
Claims with
Sentences and then just say
Me a book filled with tweets
The other real tragedy for Quigley to was that like
Because he wasn't getting a 1300 page scholarly book
Unexpected
You then you got Tucker
Cleon skousen coming out selling 55,000 of it in a year making all that money or the Liberty Lobby
A bunch of that money
Arise quotation of his work
Then by the same token you now have
Gary Allen coming out with none dare call it
And none of that movie at money is
Rawlins
That sucks
His books
So we can get Ken Burns
Can Lily take shows up
This is the last clip from this section
Talking about
The misrepresentation
Please work
I only kept
Because like
The real
Function of what
He's doing
Is really just
Kind of lighting
Gettler roster
It's weird
Cuz he's super close at
I think in the next Clipper saying
After I take in Europe and then knockout
Jimmy also want the Elder of Downey
He would only let Jews Escape
Palestine
Oh yeah
Like it's not
Denial
Pure is denial but
Man this
This is so close to the rhetoric that you see
In all sorts of places
Blame
Hidden behind the scenes for the Holocaust itself
Write the Rothschild
I used to really hate
Betrayed I'm really starting to feel for this
Like he brings up that
Rudolf Hess story
About him
Parachuting out of an airplane
With
Or something like that but I remember that episode
But do you really caught me off-guard was that Alex
Rudolf Hess with a war
That's not
He's sort of
Swallows
World War 1 hero
But even that's not great
I don't like letting Hitler off the hook for everything
MN calling Rudolph
Looked in you have a lot of misconceptions
That's because you've been reading the liberal history
Is that makes you a race traitor awesome for me to say race-traitor
Because that's what's really important
Seems like that
Yeah so now we're done with that section today so we can move on to Alex having
More fun saying stupid s***
Henderson urges caution on community garden
Ricky Gervais
They're cracking down on you getting your own food because they want you hungry so they can get you into those FEMA camp
Are they are they going after subsistence farmers
No this is about a city council meeting
In Tulsa
Henderson
Tulsa City-County
Counselor
And what the issue here is not about Gardens
It's about community
Actually this article is less about the marijuana issue
That you don't stay here
Growing vegetables
Is there going to be someone inspect what's growing
Community garden
Kind of understand
I don't think it matters that much
But that's just one point that he brings up
The main concern is the ideas like
What land are we using
How is it going
I meant what is it falls into
Repair whose responsibility is that if it just becomes overgrown
Is that the city's responsibility
Are we going to have to
For that
Play
But now you have a community garden here and then the homeowner
Or the property owner is then responsible for the overgrowth of the garden
Yeah
There's more issues here than just the idea of
On the other hand
I mean if the community garden dude everybody
Everybody just kind of has it has a weird
Pop up
Political system that grows around those where
To somebody but you don't know who for a while and then yet
Meet a couple of people in the know and then you find out who's running things and you ask for a plot
And the person who's running things
Self-appointed because they just showed up
Probably
The bag lady
It's also Erica
Wait where was I going with that I'm not sure but also in this article it says that they would support the amendment and if
Pressing problems
Go back to make sure
They want but it is this article that he's reporting on
It is really
Just about the city code enforcement
And whether or not it will require
To clean up places
Fall in
Being
If it's a private place
How are we going to make them clean it up
Look there
About it
What are we doing here because it's a simple way for him to
His pre-existing narratives
Into a story that doesn't
Listen to
A lot of these on The Cutting Room floor
I just heard a telephone Oklahoma
Parking
Buy $0.05
Reviews
And now we can't get it anymore
I don't live in Tulsa Oklahoma
So
We move on from this story
Who's breaking news
On the Alex Jones Show
Courtesy of
A family member of Alex's or should I say
Whistleblower
Do people be brainwashed
Sororities and fraternities
This just happened
Last week
Crazy
Sew in
Dentist community
They are warning
Dentist
They put their colors in their teeth
I would only believe
This was
Kappa beta incisor
I would only believe this in anyway if it was about like
Look out for people
Or something like that
Only white
A dentist's is always like
Play the Paul Wall video and they're like
See if miscarry
It's in the back is like
Dude I make
Millions of Grey
You guys are losing money by being racist
Yeah that's
Good song
Anyway
We get again
He's our favorite South African gold exploiter ladies and gentlemen
Bobby Chapman
Remember that
And it's in comprehend
To beat it is what two pieces
Expected from the
The people who control
Are federal
You noticed that immediately I didn't think you were going to text
Everyone else
Boy
This is one of those things
It's really essential to understand
Berkeley in different ways with
People
Only
To talk about the dollar collapsing and Snelling
Anderson
That's the only reason he exist on the show
Why comes on all the
He's a credible source
Order to force people into a mindset
Difficult
So when Alex wants to bring up the miac report which is Big narrative it
She's on now
In order to make it amenable to
I have to get to which is selling gold
He has to bring in if
Dubai gold
Yeah
Perfect I am looking
Chuck Norris buddy throws in
See there we go
You guys if you can decide
River Phoenix
Speak of the devil
It is time
Chuck Norris to make his appearance on the show
Chuck Norris
Come on late last year
President president of the u.s.
She's really excited
He's
I guess if you're the president of United States
Does Alex consider do the president of the United States
True
Work there
This interview
Is weird
Cuz it will say there is a piece of Alex Jones interview
Chuck Norris
Turns weird
I'm kind of cool with
And that is like Chuck Norris talking about
I know I guess
Exercise equipment
Kids
Schools martial arts
Some stuff like that you know martial arts are good ways to have discipline and
You know all that stuff
There's two examples people I know
In the media who are real into martial arts
32-count Eddie Bravo
We got Chuck Norris
Joe Rogan Eddie Bravo
All of them
Seem to be in great shape
But
Proclivity for hanging out with fashion
Karate until I was like
Only now looking back I realize how many of those guys were like
A lot of people want to take a ride
Self-defense
Some people
To know how to straight up murderer
Industry
What if it
For one of those
But if you if you're
Super into karate
You're allowed
I could see that mentality being there
I think it's wrong or weird at all to do martial arts
But I wonder if there's something in the nature of
That
Discipline
Ability to
Get that control over yourself
I wonder if there's an element of
In martial arts that is so predicated on
Subservient
The master
And I wonder
If that there is a necessary but I wonder if there's something in there that leads towards a mindset that is very
Malleable to authoritarianism
You know what I mean I don't know if that's the case I'm just depends on the
If you had like a hard line Realty
Yes master you kind of like I am the king of this
This
Another word for dojo
It's small but it's all about discipline and
Submission version of yourself
The display of the master
Why would
Be something
That you have now have practice
I don't know
I think that's a weak link
I mean I think it's I think
It's more likely that
You're getting people who are
Incline's of violet
Syrian government
Give them
Free rein tax
Exercise
Whenever they want to
This interview
He's very strange
That is very strange
Is that
Alex wants this a noun
He wants
To know what it is
Do your run to the president
Glenn Beck that's all he really want
And unfortunately
I don't think the Chuck Norris knows that Alex Jones hates Glenn Beck
Glenn Beck
It started the yellow thing called
Do we surround them with the means
9 principles that they do that.
We America should I live by America's good I believe in God and
Center my life
Much more honest person than I was yesterday
He don't think of that sort they are than the 12 values of honesty rapper
Hope Thrift
So forth and so on
And so really
Glenn beckert
Trying to say today
Back to the values that we had
For many many years and we're drifting off
The Bad and The
And I totally agree what they
So
Alex wants to scoop
Gotten back
Eddie's accidentally doing the commercial for Glenn Beck yeah celebrity guests
12512 movement
What ends up happening
Never join
The pity party
Because I realized
Glenn Beck
Get that machine moving
But no
It's already in high gear
On March 13th
They're going to start pushing the 912 movement
Which is what the announcement is
Bentley helping
I think there's a decent chance
They're what ends up happening
Alex never really
But
Consistently says that he's the real
Makes way more sense
Why I why I think that might be the case
He's never going to.
And we still have no idea for another year
You know how when you do an experiment sometimes you will learn what doesn't create
Fire
Find out to chemical explosion
It's not so much
Do you know what this is
He's as much as it is like it's
Method
We've knocked out a couple of possibilities
We had a good we had a good day
Information to leave
Just be like
Any of those things are possible
But we'll see
Because Alex is so pissed off
That Chuck Norris is on his show
If you goes out to break Alex accidentally called Chuck Norris Glenn Beck
What's that more about setting your new book
Rebecca Glen Norah's over here whatever this
Patriotism
You can get the sense
He's really
He's not happy about this because
This is supposed to
To be a
For him
You got walk around the show man
So they start talking about how Chuck Norris like
Which I do want to get it
Involved
Russian bass tab
Income tax
Property tax and stuff like that would go away
And you just died as a lot of tax for buying
That's kind of the idea
This variations of the fairtax
I will never not be surprised by how bad their ID
I want Jessica
Consume
Consuming
And Alex
Glad
Bubba's 33
Chuck Norris
Isn't insightful
About the IRS
Taxation
Retired bad news
Factor thing
Is that the
You know the IRS
What was only became conch
Institutional 1913
The IRS
Accident Constitution
Until 1913
When the government when the congress met.
Amendment
Ever since that
Yeah
I got bad news
Because it wasn't constitutional for women to vote until it was I mean what do you want to do
What is this mean
What is the Constitution
It doesn't
Constitutional before can never be constitutional
Remember how that was written into the, man
There definitely wasn't some sort of like
Okay
Maybe we need some amendments to the Constitution maybe it's not
What if we rode in
An actual
How to add
Series of instructions are followed
Institution
That's so silly
Glenn Beck
Comes up
His love for him
If you listen you can hear Alex get out in
Exasperated sigh
I get the answer
Supporter of Glenn Beck
Consider him like you I like that really
Are you a crusader Knight
Considerate
Later
Because the whole thing is
Douching
We're going to lose it
The globalist have already hired Nick
For a long time
They had with a developer
Deal to steal
To Note 4
Two-part series 0-2
Chuck Norris
Star of Texas Ranger is on the show and he's telling us they were going to lose our constitution is Glenbeigh
Doesn't work
Douching
It doesn't make me feel better when he says this about the concert
Diffusion
You know what did John Adams do
Second president
Tuition was made only for a religion
I really believe that
Napoleon adequate
The government
Have any other
Maintain our faith
And I'm moral value
Constitution
Dissolving
Which
Your Christian theocracy bro
Is that what you're into Walker
Very much
And John Adams saying that is exactly why we need them
6th class
Listening to Walker Texas Ranger be stupidest s***
I just don't understand I just I don't get it
I don't get it I don't get how anybody
With a straight face
Who seems to not be
A monster
Necessarily like I don't know any Chuck Norris is done
Like this on the scale
No no
He could have killed a guy I have no idea guy
The cure somebody who you do you assume
Isn't a total monster saying like
Wow
The Constitutions really only for religious and moral
People means that everyone must be religious
If we're going to have this
The Constitution doesn't apply to not religious
Like a religious Folk
So you don't either those conclusion
Terrifying
Means people of old
Immoral
Follow their religion
Tenants letter of the law
I would assume so
All religion
The Constitution so much he remembers that in the First Amendment
Sidekicks
If Chuck is Chuck Norris wear a dictator
Do you need a psychic
Have you talked about him in this next
This doesn't make me more interested in his version of government
So you don't
Saying I don't know if I told you
Anyway
Glitter floating around for the last two years haha
Peter Schiff
If that was true
I would go to watch
Congress
And I'd have Ron Paul who I
Play playlist the most honor
Member of Congress
Point out
Be honest
Walking down the road
Aptoide
And I'd say
You're fired
And if you didn't move immediately
I took him unconscious
Nancy Pelosi
Nancy
You're fired
All the Time in the World to leave hahaha
Can we just
I don't know how I would say
Person in the senate or whatever is that he says
I didn't mean the first person
You know
I remember all of the sexes
Successful government that were room
That way right
I'm trying to bring Liberty
Division of a dictatorship
Who can cover
That's crazy
Is I would hire Ron
Chuck Norris himself is the Executioner
I would like to go on the record I do not want
I feel like a
All the Amendments would disappear we would end up
So much like Alec presented the miac report
Gold
Pizza Hut
In place for Bob Chapman he was earlier on
On the show
Now that Chuck Norris is on
I'm sorry that he doesn't say anything about the karate in
Feel this isn't information
Revolution
I have the government documents I have the secret State Police reports that the feds give them
This is what the Hydra
Mainline
Libertarians and
Yeah I know
Like you Chuck Norris Chuck Norris need the hardcore
True that I'm bringing cuz you're in danger report is about you Chuck Norris
Report
Chuck Norris why the f*** are you talking to Glenn Beck
And the other thing that is
Really really funny
This because I just assumed it was
But Alex has another
Manual
Vapes
Hueytown
Is proof
That that the government
Just trying to crack
They hate these are the Patriots and all that
Him
Believe
I don't exactly know they came from
But it came from I know
In Arizona law in for
I believe it was a guy named Jack
Glam is coming up later on the show but
But I can't prove it
What's the timeline matches up
But I went and looked at it
Supplier
Flyers
Play folded in half
And it's just giving law enforcement
Things to look out
It's actually better
Like I said
Description
And based on the study
But they've done
This one if you open up the
You look inside and it has a list
Two things used to be on the lookout for
There's two
Did you want to look out for
It isn't quote in the dark
Defenders of the US Constitution against
Foreign governments and the UN
Parenthetically
Super Paper
And groups of individuals engaged in paramilitary train
You should definitely be looking out
If you were in law enforcement
Conceivably could be concerned about
If someone engaging paramilitary training
Is really
I don't want
But that usually doesn't happen in balance
People with a good head on their shoulders generally aren't in the woods training for war
On their own
Demi Moore in a cell
Together
Who are
Sickly consistent with
And they learn how to use weapons
The practice
Necessary
Neutralize
The anime
Do you know they're never going to use those
And they'll never manufacturer enemies real or imagined
Right and it'll never take that anime is real or imagined
Kind of blow it out of proportion and then turn it into a local issue
They would never
The tution against
The federal government
Anime
You should be concerned about 2
Because that is
Upsetting
You know what I mean
People who don't think that the constitution
I mean that's Alex's
Well I would still believe
Right-wing extremist
Now you go down
Is neo-Nazi
Black separatist
Those are all groups
You should be aware of
Enforcement are generally some groups or maybe do a crime or two
Open
Common-law movement per pound
Oh yeah
Maybe didn't have that name
Fictitious license
Plates no license plates
Pictures of driver's life
No driver's license
Refusing to identify
Themselves
Request why are you stop
Make a numerous references to the US,
Institution
Police the police
Those are the things you should look out for
Send it to you
You might be talking to a common-law
Moon
Maritime law kind of guy the least
Play version of Jeff
Then there's single-issue terrorist
Terrorist Urban Riot educators
Find to everybody else
Doomsday
Sure
Weapons of mass destruction is on here
Don't need to tell us to look out for that
And then also there's a little section like this
Cartoon
Giant
Just being like
So you going to use that
Constitutional
You love so much
That is a problem
Left
Political motivation
Is usually marxist-leninist philosophy
Now
Hi
I'm not an idiot
And I say
You know what there probably are some left-wing groups that have marxist-leninist philosophy
In no way do I look at that and say
If you are into marks
You're into Lennon
Then that means
That would be how I would have to read it if I was playing the same stupid games Alex
Picture that I wanted to bring
Is there's a bad luck
Terrorism is included in Paradise
People for the most part
There's a small part about right-wing
Extremism
He ignores all the rest of this
In order to be like they're trying to
The Patriots
I can play the same game with you like they're trying to
Do you understand
He would have just as much
Validity using this Ark
Using this
How to spell
Stupid
Anyway
In case anybody was
Turns out
Here's where I get a little bit of empathy
C4 Chuck Norris
Okay so the interview ends
How fast
As soon as Chuck Norris is gone
Alex starts
Condescending
Keep creating going buddy
Analyze This
Go to the military
Destroyed
He supports the state sovereignty movement you just heard that
That's sad
MeetMe
Volunteers
Restart
Keep rambling from there
I think it's really fun no just being like
Cuz he's hanging out with Glenn Beck was not a c student
One point or another
Soundly patronizing
I can't imagine North wasn't still listening
Has anyone heard that been like
Almost immediately after
Rather than angry at you for mentioning Glenn Beck
Repeatedly
To promote his appearance
Chucky
You would have no idea why Alex was just
Call the sudden
Yeah now it's called him sir and it's nice to his face and was like
. my gut tells me he's a good guy but he doesn't know much
Now
Shity
Another
Comes up after Chuck Norris
Mcclam
He's a former police guy from
From Phoenix Arizona
Realtor
This guy
Is it on
Not necessarily
It's worth mentioning
He sounds a lot like
Chuck Norris
In Atherton
Yes we sure are a brother
We're getting more and more
Email I get 200 300 a day and then
That's nothing to what you get but
Soldiers
Other people in
It's fantastic how more
Time
And I've been praying every night
That God would give us
Second chance
Oh and forgive our night
Sam's for throwing him out of this nation and allow it to go forward
F*** are you talking about
Commandments and his laws and throughout these evils
He literally
It's heard that last part you said throw out
Evil man's laws
This constitution bolted advocating for Christians
Theocracy Broadway
Lean and doors
Describe
Almost exactly
Playwright
Is the false Christianity
Acclaimed appearance on the show
Not aware of
About The Oath Keepers
This great cool new group of kids
Out on the scene
And you know what they're all about
I like to keep a nose
Could you make a note
They sound eminently reasonable Dan I assume there
No other details to learn about them
I just keep up I'm saving getting into them for another day because I'm going to go Whole Hog
And the reason for that
Is Arab military is because
He was talking about
Glenn Beck
Visibly and audibly
Put off by
But also I think there might be a piece of his mind that was like
Because
When Jack McLamb comes on
He starts talking about
10 things
That I Hate About You
Keepers have like
We will not take away people's guns
Guys they love
Jack McLamb spend 40 minutes
Breaking down
The rules
40 minute break
I meant to go to Commercial and I was like
Those all again but I'm going to editorialize
Everyone will talk about it
He's like
Really really excited about these 10
Rules of those keepers
They make Smith
Take that he's going
Full auto
These guys never talked about the beatitude like there's never a
Treat others the way you want to be treated there's none of that stuff it's always like
If you have the chance
Sure
Now just because
I needed a little bit of
I decided to check a little bit
But I don't know I don't know how much we talk about I know we haven't talked about there
I found a video
But he has put out of his radio show
He put out a
List the episode of his radio show called was Hitler upon
Which interesting Lee relates back to a bunch of stuff Alex was talking about earlier
Here's the quote
From that video
What's that one go
You can't because you can't cuz your butthole into all of these
Basically Nazi adjacent
Anti-communist propaganda
A propaganda sooner or later you're going to have to run into the problem of
If all of the guys that I like
Are telling the truth
That means Hitler can't be a bad guy about it like
Intelligence sources
Very happy quotes
Bilderberg Group
For the spotlight
Which was the publication put out
Specifically in order to turn public opinion against
Great-grand worldview
About
It goes on to this day
In the CFR at all this s***
It's based on
A mist
5 W Cleon skousen that was published and promoted
By the Liberty Lobby they would put out there put together by Willis carto
Who wanted to demonize Jews
And all of that ends up
Being mixed into a big bouillabaisse that ends up
It's alphabet.
You were too young to understand what you were reading
And you have a family that is for
Probably a little bit crazy
To be like
Alex
Has never had
Crisis
A political identity
He's had this stupid world you since he was 12
Like someone who's walked around and never had to question actually what he believed
10 reading these dumb book
Being challenged by the experiences
But he has in the world
He gets defensive about them and yells
In order to be like no I'm going to
Vociferously defend my opinion as opposed to
Consider the possibility maybe I'm wrong
Wish that we lived in a world where if you started digging into your philosophy
And you eventually
Defend
Hitler as your as your bedroom
Better be like Hitler
Maybe I should dig myself out of this hole
But with these guys there's just nobody
What else we got part of the mentality because
If everything is
Nothing is what
You thought it is
Yeah he didn't do it
What Hitler upon
Festival
That's the video that was put out by
Jack McLean
Here's the quote
Was Hitler upon this is fascinating so I wanted to share this with you because it's by one of my
One of my favorite jeans in the world
One of my favorite in the world Henry Makow
Jordan Henry Mack h a noted lunatic
Conspiracy theories
It's also worth pointing out that
Weird
Amongst
Is there a
Beatles were in Illuminati
Interesting late
He wrote a book in 2000 called
Blurb of the book from Amazon
In the Philippines Henry Makow 48 discovered a Tropical Paradise where women are still traditional
And the husband is the head of the household
In marriage to a young Filipino
Nothing like an uplifting story of an ear fifty-year-old Man flying to Southeast Asia to marry an 18 year old
Gensol
I like
The reviews on his his
Tibetana
I also recommend reading this book to anyone who finds themselves sympathetic to Macos views on his website
It's the perfect antidote because it's painfully obvious
The problem a cow has
The world is a
Actually
I understand people
Socially unacceptable
There's nothing wrong with an Intercultural marriage orientee traditional role
But the combination of
Property a 30-year age Gap
The three-week courtship is a bridge too far
Lincoln
Because they were getting a real money over throw the Illuminati
Control the money
He also believes it was the Jews that were to blame for the Holocaust
He's Jack McLamb
Favorite Jew
Just
Don't want to die
Historically it's a bad idea.
If that person is a white nationalist
A lot of the argument is to lay out in this Holocaust
Denying
From a 1941 publication
Quote I was Hitler's book
Written anonymously at
The time we now know was written by Captain Karl Mayer
This is proof that there was someone as he sure point
The mayor is Jewish
Who is pulling Hitler strings in the Holocaust
The problem is that mayor was only Hitler's immediate supervisor
20 when Hitler was a general staff
This guy is a good here before you become fewer than
Before he became Chancellor of Durham
Fun fact
Power mayor flood
Sprint rewards with anti-nausea for
Buchenwald
Concentration camp
Interesting Lee
If you do read the article I was Hitler's boss
You see from striking parallels
77 years later
The leaders knew that to please the majority and minority must suffer
German Jews were made
Cheap scapegoats because their destruction would gain millions of votes for the knot
Small shopkeepers hated Jews because they owned a chain stores
Farmers with Wister destruct
Because they were indebted
Jewish Bank
Even intellectuals were jealous
Because juice help lucrative position
The Arts and Science
Professions
The Nazi salesman offered anything and everything
Thing to make the people warmind
They're still talk was Germany as a have not come
Other nations have all the wealth Germany
Fight them successfully
I'd still be entitled to that well
The Patriotic slogan
Everything for Germany with nothing more than salesman
No one cared in the least what would happen to
The rest of Germany
So long as the result via restoration
Of the good old
The further argument laid out in the pieces that Hitler was
Booty idiot
And the bad guy when there was a supervisor
And in fact the article ends with mayor laying out exactly what he
He's talking about
He's arguing that Hermann Goering is the real brains of the operation and the Hitler was a charismatic frontman sales man
That they needed
Pictures of Harley from Jackman
Glammed
Shocking parallel
To our world
The government wasn't
So not necessarily A
Controlling him so much as
President with advice
Bush was in office of Karl Rove Bush's brain
If you think
Eid of it
People have influenced way over the even addictive
You think that's weird
0 childish fool if you believe
You know
I don't know I don't know what else to say other than that
We have an account
This guy very clearly explaining
The Nazi
Ended up
Solidifying a lot of their control
The small group
People and kept
People warm
There's going to be a civil war
LGBT community and
Is basically trying erase their identity
Hanover the majority of minority has two separate analysis provider which one
Now the difference here
Is it the majority is going to suffer
In order for the minority
To solidify their power
Power
So
That's going to be fun
Anyway
Chronicling the rise of the Nazi party
Real-time
Surprise
Saw this
I think you can understand now why this episode was a little bit
Call because we have this historical revision of Hitler being
Completely unrelated to that we have
Clearly the Holocaust denier
You see so much of it
And there's little things that I didn't expect
I mean this guy does Henry Mack out going to
The Philippines get a lady
Other reviews Carnival fundera
Distraction maybe not so fun to that lady
But like reading is I was Hitler's book
You know stuff
It's very it's very difficult to see this
From 9 years ago being very much
And now we seem to cruelty in the sort of the Mask
Coming off
It makes you wonder how much of that was already there
How much
Like
To say how much
Turnpoint
Was he just having more fun back then
And
Not as
Beaked out on his own
Is there a chance really the only fundamental
A couple of these policies
In favor of Palestinian clearly
Fascist dictator
Part of being part of a fascist dictatorship
Party
Is going along with whatever it is
Read the
Rise of stalinism
Complete destruct
Action of reality even for people with it
Inner Circle whatever ideas
Subsumed by whatever
That's true even in a best-case
Just had those inclinations and maybe they were late
I can come to the surface and tell
I barely got the baby it was one of those situations
You have
A gene that isn't Express
Stimulus
It's weird
It was really difficult and it you know
Is a lot of reading is difficult
Figure out like Howard
What is this say
I don't know I don't have a full conclusion other than to say like
What are constantly evolving
And we can guarantee 100%
Alex was around Indy rise of
Do you like wholehearted
Really good for you iodized
Ron
By anti-communist Propaganda
Scrum
You know 40
Even into the 70
All are all that is where he gets all
And it's unfortunate
But it is real
Most of those people
Have deep roots
So does that make Alex
You decide
Getaway website
Don't don't
Floats
Absolute
Media Networks
Podcast distribution platform Riverview if you'd like
Yeah
Look
I don't know
But I do know
I dunno.
He probably killed
Alex
First in color