Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Welcome back to another episode of the show what's that a third episode this week are you kidding me
Control delivering
Even whatever you're doing it's celebratory defensiveness Alex Jones is rubbing off on
Where me and my friend Jordan
Discuss
Infowars and Generals
The hook reason to listen Beyond you just explaining it I watch a lot
Doll
So I like together cleanser that
Listen I like to sit down and I gather Clips like a Pokemon
And I show you what I've got I got myself a Bulbasaur clip
I got myself a Charizard clip
And I'm out of poke
Anymore
But
Bi-Mart
Episode
That is
Tuesday
If you're nasty
And we're going to get into what goes on on the show
Get into some of the lies some of the fun
I am
Mostly the only plan that we've ever had
Yeah it's worked out so far
Although we have been taken out
No no but there's talk there's talk on the
There's always
Today is
You might think can we just stop and acknowledge that was probably our best
It was the smoothest but I also felt lost it tonight
The whole time I was kind of going smoothly.
What are we doing alright
So of course
You might expect Jordan
The Today's Show would be Alex Jones
Screaming his ass off
About the tape
It was posted on Breitbart
The night before regarding Paul Ryan
Would never support Trump
I will never support this monster
I would expect it
Because that is ended
It's exactly what you would normally want to talk about
He's basically doing up like
Air support for Trump
All the time
F****** Paul Ryan's coming over here
Already Alex doesn't like Paul Ryan plan
No
Alex is distracted by other things
No namely
That he was mentioned on Saturday night
Alex
Stop in Alec Baldwin
Nightlife in Jeddah
That's it
Yep okay are we going are we going to go like year-by-year cast by cast
Oh my God
Despicable is Rob Schneider's good for
I would love it
Earlier work
I would love it if that's what he did but instead
I can get
Into this this is this is great
This is pretty close to the beginning of the show this is
A couple minutes in
He starts by rambling about nothing
Man gets into it
He was playing before this that like people say that he is a hate monger
Also already covered the fact that
He was Lampoon
Representative very pissed off because
The newest episode
And if
It's not good
The character is taking a turn for the dark is not
It's not Alex is not going to like that I haven't watch the new X-Files characters but I bet it's debatable
Also
I'm not sure I got to go back and watch it
But anyway
NBC and CBS respectively
Remember that
Impressive
Feeling is like he has his social
He's got his life
Force
You just keep in mind that he's that seems to be thinking about identity is being stolen
And not
You know
Not being accurate
And then
No contacts no real
In the skin if you didn't see it
I did not
It's on Independence Day and there's aliens that have come down
Trump
Alec Baldwin playing Trump
Gives the speech to a bunch of
Bunch of soldiers were getting ready to do battle with these aliens and he's like
Aliens Walk Among Us they've been here for years
I heard this on Infowars Alex Jones is a gray radio broadcaster
Keenan is like
What aliens live here in the camp there's one right over there
8 points at Leslie Jones
Okay.
And another one right next to her and it says this year's Amada
Is everybody
Yeah
It's a joke as we've documented Alex has a dubious grasp on race
Doesn't mean that
People
The point
Pics of black people are alien
I think for comedic effect
Are they a little
How much are they how much could they possibly be exaggerated under doing it
Same thing if you know exactly how awful Alex
Kind of
Yeah
It's a joke
Is everything
Just like WinCo bear attacking two weeks ago
You are proud shows don't you
Yes
Well the house together
The remnants
Is on the lease I can get
Hey listen
So what are you doing what's going on
Could you
He just skipped
Into this storyline that he's mentioned before in the past but I have no evidence of this
I don't know if this is
He claims that one of his reporters
Got evicted
Because the landlord
Thought that Alex Jones was a bigot
And they work for Alex Jones
Which is that did happen
That's a loss
Yeah that's
Is it illegal
Discrimination
Yeah which is why I know it didn't happen
So anyway
Yeah but it makes no sense
SNL made fun of me just like Colbert made fun of
Cuz me and because of cold air
Employee got evicted
Yeah if you're if you're trying to diagram the sentence that's what he saying just listening to it straight through I'm glad you asked
Cuz it makes no sense
My faults not respect
They say
I'm at your house
Opposing of the president Baldwin
Never pretended to be a reporter
That involved the news and he's a late night talk show hosts
Does Alex really not understand that
He doesn't
It really doesn't get that he does because of a Clipper going to play later
Where he gets into the idea of fiction and reality
Really Illuminating
There's a lot of projection
So much projection in this episode
It gets really weird
Real weird
Michael's boxes
Eon
Ameren
Guaranteed
I want to do
Bill O'Reilly
Police
Graceful definition
Delusional
Really great video
I was yapping arcade days know what the O'Reilly clip was but
Willing to believe that they got it at that way
I'm willing to believe Alex's version of it
Which is
Shady
Well
You know what let's not it look on a gauge of the weather or not this is real this comes down
Fact that he said that's the greatest form of defamation you can do to Sam Ash cut to Alex
So implying
Is a pedophile
Yep is the
The greatest form of defamation
You can do to somebody
Yep
Okay
Alright
Alex Jones
Know what he says ever at any point in time
No memories
Situation where every word is the first word he's ever spoke
I think it must be that sort of thing he's like a like really fast acting guy from Memento or it's just all gone immediately
Either that or he knows that
It's vaguely enough to what he says
The Killing rape children
It's not really a specific defamation on anybody but then when
Yeah
Alex Jones is code that means kill and drink the blood of children
But yes
He has committed the worst defamation
The moment it happened
Security
Violence solves every problem
Houston
Is the UE Bowl political talk
Physically
It's so childish it's insanity
I disagree with you philosophically
So let's fight
My Philosophy is right
You know what I wish that was further away from Heather
Might makes right
If he doesn't matter these are the tenants
Of the World of Alex Jones
I mean we just got to get used to it if we're going to dwell in a nice clip
Where he hasn't narrative
I think it's pretty interesting
Get into right here
Percent off on the Trump Pence
Dot-com
All about Free Speech meeting like-minded people and promoting the truth
Red white and blue shirt
California schools
Colors
Muslims
He's not kidding but he's lying
The ninth circuit like we talked about a bunch
Just to illustrate how often he brings that up about an Iowa
Football team where people were told not to wear red white blue
Because it offends
Alex must have just seen a tweet
Because I read up on this story
Okay
The Tweet blogs
Iowa high school students were forced to apologize for wearing red white blue at a sports game because immigrant students
Seymour Thunder
That's the story on right-wing blogs any other
Part of that story
That maybe they've opened
Apologize
Red white and blue
Okay but they were never asked
They weren't forced to at all
Okay they also shoot
Have apologized for wearing red white and blue
Because I wasn't the issue
The reason that the opposing team was pissed off
Was because
They were screaming racial slurs
Treason
To be pissed off then wearing red white and blue Deport them
No and stuff like that there was
A guy who was there
Was quoted as saying
You had a Facebook post about it
Just remember we were offended but did not ask for an apology
Valley willingly apologize to us
We did not make them apologize
And then some
Please State exactly what offended you
The post say it was wearing a patriotic uniform
If it was more than that then Enlighten us
And his response
I don't care what they were wearing
Some of them were screaming racial slurs which is what got me
Maybe more of the story
That's wicked
Yeah you know all the way up until then
Not being a bully
So they apologize for wearing red white blue
Right
Responsibility knowing you have to apologize
Decerebrate
Council it didn't come from the kids who were
Doing the screaming racial slurs
Okay so I think that it might be
You scream racial slurs had
Just suddenly diss
Disappeared to be replaced by people
People suddenly learning not to yell to wake up hungover.
Oh man
Apologize for Rachel's Lounge
Is this
Possibility
Apologizing to save face without
Getting into the muck
Also September 2016 Demoine register article described
Tensions in this particular School
Fortin Iowa
A culture of quote deep racial disparity exists in the Valley High School
Grading and
Students of color according to reports
Iowa State University Research
The audit found that students of color at the West Des Moines High School
Are more likely to be labeled as special
Then their white peers
Students of color are also more likely to face discipline or
Suspension and less likely to be tapped for gifted program
And this is the quote
The researchers
The Traditions curriculum and teaching methods within the school
Assume students upper-class whiteness is the norm or archetype
We can marginalize and demoralize Dunes
Color whether intended or not
Now that's
Interesting and about the whole lot of Education
Now here's where it gets
The report comes more than a year after violent confrontation between
The series of community discussions on race relations at the school
There were like basically race fight this Iowa school
What kind of climate they were living in
Isn't problem at Valley High School
And of course it's not commonly reported
Because why would it be at the high school in the middle of America it's just one example of many
How
But they just ran with it as being about wearing red
Red white blue
Does in the end
Is blame-the-victim
Again
Beside because
Can Spin A Yarn that's against his narrative
You can't dig for the facts
You can't look into it
He's lying by omission
It's f****** sad what are the what are the
This is reported only on right wing
News.
Local news talked about
Yeah just for
Show me the tweets are basically along the lines of
Sports to apologize red-white-and-blue
You know what f***
F****** this is a pure distraction
We want but I
I just gave him from but I just like these specific examples because
It comes down to like what we can pin to the wall there's a lot of stuff that we can't really pin to the wall like I can't
Alex doesn't have horses
I am good
Circumstantial evidence
But he doesn't
But I can't prove it
You didn't read this article based on the facts of the article
So this is an instance where the f*** you dude
You're not telling the story you're lying you're a propagandist and
Huseman calling other people erase pimp
I would say if anybody is doing that sort of behavior it's you that exact moment
Committed
Race temporary defamation
Possibly
And you know who's willing to fight you
We all know
Fights for sexual favors
Also let's do the big picture of Representative Stephen King
Who is nationalist
Yeah and he's not even bothering anymore
No buts
I was about to blow up this f***** up stuff going on
Iowa City
Let's just call that one Candlelight
Tent
Some white Nash
Culture with other people's babies
Potentially call Ryan
Stead
I think
Need to clarify
And then he clarified his comments
I meant exactly what I said
Exactly what I said
Paul Ryan when asked for comment regarding
To clarify state
If I were Paul Ryan the second time by responsibility
This supports the the reality
The GOP is now only for dumb people
No one else white racism in his life
Nazis
VSCO
Prosperity
Anyway this clip is not John
He goes from talking about this basketball team lying about them
Turkey
But when he brings up turkey
What are you doesn't do is bring up the his
What is that working for them are you sure it wasn't
That
You're no longer allowed to wear red white and blue on
Siri
Well then you don't feel like she part of the country
Oregon
Ruler of Europe
Wow is General Flynn
Hey
Keys from occupied Texas break
Just learn how to say the goddamn
I have fine
George
Jorge
Whether it is WHOTV NBC Valley Sudafed USA team
North
Refugee athletes
North Refuge
So that's him reading the headline of the story
He picks the team name is North Refugee ask
That is not the name of the team
Sets
Yep bingo
Do you does that make you see a vision of a bat
Basketball jersey
Syria as their mascot
The team is
The Tigers
I looked it up
We have the
The North Rhett
TDS which is one of the most common
We have the Tiger
Did they vote for that at
Play where those two ever an option one
It might it might have been you know what we want to be unique
Fair enough
I was kind of worried I want to I want to bring this up a tiny bit because
We're going to get
A little bit
Today you tweeted app
Paul Joseph Watson
Prison Planet
Me into a panic
Entire day
I found this clip
Feel like we might be okay
Because I
Alex Jones
Describes how he likes
To take a joke
Oh good already world we know that he liked
To take a joke unfortunately by the end of this clip I'm starting to wonder if he actually likes to take a picture
Do you think even knows what a joke
Greg is unclear but the
Well let him decide
From
Screaming
Another
Okay Goo
With daily matchups
Before we didn't like how he takes
I want to be clear that I kind of agree with him
And this is one of my big principles is taking him out of context like that is incredibly day
It really only feeds into his game
Oh yeah what we're doing
Is still laughing at him
Very so much work
But it's a half minutes long
Instead of us commenting on it
There is just
Techno music
17th
Free movies
Entertain
But that you could never have
I really do agree with him
People
Doing these videos are sort of playing
We're going to check him out you know they want to know more about who is this f****** Wingnut
I don't know I don't think they're going to convert tons of people or anything like that
I'm not saying that they're doing something bad I'm just saying
There are negative
Side effects
Like a joke and that will be one of my main PCS
For the entirety of
He is he is a joke
But he is a he's like he's like
The Killing Joke
The Joker
That's what
He just so bad look at Rulli bigoted joke that everyone seems to like
Yeah.
If if they're sending people to have the worry that I have is that
He's becoming
More
Disseminated in the popular
While I was saying that I realized
That is a
Exactly what we're helping
Not really we can explode no because we'll be too late
Alex Jones
You started this podcast
2 years ago
Whose like has like Game of Thrones
You should have been in the end
Right now
Anyway don't spoil Game of Thrones let's get to Alex Jones
My son loves it your school up
From 50 years ago that oldest Cub suit
By the way
That records
That reference is going to miss all of your Millennials that are coming over from the AV club
No f****** idea
I don't know probably
Goddamn sitcom
Look it up while we are red
I don't I don't know how to spell it
I don't want to ask
In here
Most comments
When you read them
This is the guy that says whites are superior to black people
Never said that
This is a guy that says he's Superior genetically to Denzel Washington when he's old and ugly
So he actually shows the comment thread on the baby club video
Buckwild
So jokes, threats and
Is it tag tag tag
That's worth it
Communal
Comment thread where it's kind of the same people always in
Conversation with
So in this one
Start because the video in question he does some rapping in it
He like people were started as we can drop
Like Alex Jones raps
And one of them has a rap lyric
Of him like IMAX
Blah blah blah I don't like black people
Recent album
Is bringing an album back from the
Future in order to release
Why does the conservative
I don't think so
With
How many people
Do we know who have that kind of level of nurses
Absolutely read
Like
Put a Facebook post
It turns into one of those Facebook
They will absolutely turn to you at
And read the
Hi my
We know people who would do
Fear
A hypothetical million-strong audience
Oh my god look up
Emails from Caddyshack
Not schmelz
Sounded very Honeymooners
He says he's 43 a motherfuker
A+
Anyone not look like a 43-year old days
This is like f****** hard that's true that's true
Pseudo-intellectual
Sorry for these people this morning
And every single moment in the world
President of the world
Empowerment
Product
Renaissance
Spin-off
Movements that are reaching even more people
And then they have these weird celebration I see it till about drudge he's never wanted
Outkast
And they're projecting everything they think they are
A legal loan people in their mother's basement all demographics
For the age of 30
Mom's basement
Have no job plays video games all day
And they just shut their together celebrating active
Aggressive successful
Successful
Also this is a joke.
Orange Park
Made the jokes that he said I'll live in a basement all these 90% of liberals over under 35 living their parents
I don't know anybody
Yeah but 90% of them
There are some comic
Basements
We've all lived in our parents basement for him at one point
Under 35 updated on Amy
Under-23
You're talkin to different
Ballpark
The reasons of
You know the very same parents
90% 90%
At the b*******
All the sudden all the sudden
He's just mad because somebody made a joke on a Navy Club article this home
He's so much stronger so much tougher than all of these people
You so strong
Real close to that is real close to threatening these commenters
It's just
Look you remember what you did right
Beat up your dad movie reviews like I will box you
He would just tried to get people
Suboxone
About
I did not know the
You did that it was great
That is pretty great
I can't remember any of his f******
That best
No
Maybe I don't know he made
He made blood range but you don't like it
Yeah video game
Get more mad
Successful
A force
Every Benchmark I'm very success
And they do have little ceremonies and celebrations that I'm not successful
I don't disagree that you fixed so but this is soap
This is really sad
Select the two the two responses
I will fight you and then being like so defensive about being successful
It's insane
I swear to god let's just talk for
For 2 hours
About that person we got a four-star review on iTunes it almost made me freak out
You ruined our Stars for stars
How dare you
You know what you're probably one of the 90s
Percent of conservative years old
And living above their parents grave
Play videogames all day
Delusional
I'm reasonably successful
Alright
That because
Who I am
Shelves better than that person
Blah blah blah
He's a bad guy
Young people
Young B that was weird guilt
And then they
ComEd
I want the Washington movies
Absolutely
Alex Jones
You just described him here
Cookie Monster
Must be true
Is David
Yes he does know well David
Says he's
I don't think anyone needs to Brand Alex Jones as anything other than Alex Jones
We let him live and die by his own words
Cookie Monster
I don't like what
You're sad about
F******
It's a it's a
Farce
Commentary that has his own YouTube
So it's
After this dissection ended I was like
Maybe he doesn't like being made fun of and he's trying to pretend
Cuz he knows it's gracious
To be made fun of and
You know Rose
It's all that stuff all that
You know sort of a social thing we're busting balls is a
Communicate friendship a lot of time
Does next clip that plays up
Immediately after
Made me realize
No more after that
Previously only because it gets
Much worse
With the faking people
Every color of every region of every
One of those is a real word one of those MW guts
In the system works because
People don't differentiate now
No you don't
You don't play
This is where we get some pot calling the kettle black action
Here is where Alex
Surly project
Exactly what he does on to those who criticize him
And it's fascinating
They don't know the difference between truth and methacton bro
Come on
All of your analogies end up citing movies
You just think
Here comes a deep dive
Usher
Computerworld
Trump
Again he's responding
The commenter
Biggest waste of time ever
You sit here in the lap of freedom
You sit here in the lap of the West and then bitching about it we have no idea your ally yourself with
China
Nope I left the corner there
Noah
Nope
Do you miss the point of any coverage about that it was hey that's
F***** up and going over there that's not cool at all
Nope
Don't do that. That was fuked up
So
That's a little Potbelly Goblin launches missiles at Japan
North
Drop bombs on piangi
Little little money
Little one
Freedom Wild Wild West
Whiteboard
Scales
Again this is a business because somebody
Commented
This is this is all in response response Jesus somehow
Did the North Korea situation
Which is agreed f*** it's f***** up
But be that as it may
Then he gets into Kim Jong-il as a tiny dick
In college is there
Whiteboards went over and remember that is not what's going on
Something it's usually a specific color they had a rash of racial slurs
Used on whiteboards
And at the safest Michigan
They were called the same time
They recognize all communication was being done through social media
So what's the point of having their if they're being used to harass people
Exactly that's
Thing that you
You should be angry now I think what Alex Jones is about to say is beyond book burning
That's his take on it
No no the white boards is beyond book Burn
Beyond
It's trying to ban the written word
That is one option the first time we agreed that it wasn't this isn't the best
Erasing awake
Is exactly like burning up
Rewrites
Yes
An everlasting book
Yeah
Mother and father yours
You're not the cool people
So uncool
You'll get it
Morons don't know the life I've LED what I've done any other you sit there in your mommy's basement
Value is
A twice-divorced
What
What is he talking
Oh man God
Hand of yelling at these people about a comment thread on the a.v. club
We've done love it so episode 23
50 hours
Just analyzing his racism is massaging his a lot islamophobia is idiocy
She's gone
Freak out if he finds this
You know what we got here
Here's the thing
Why
Because then you'd have to listen to it
He would have to add
Engages with that video
Could watch them
Vlog
Episode titles
Alex Jones is a big dumb fat
He would know everything about us
March 14th
He's not going to know maybe I should make some small YouTube videos that are salaciously title
Maybe I'll work on that for the near future
Ethos
Edited out of context
Good idea
The world
About us as if it's some magic powers
Want to hurt you I know you understand
So I'm reaching out to you like Junior High
Real world
And get out of mommy's basement
It's not
But do you know what it is
People responding to the things he's saying appropriately
Play people who've done some
Projector
I think about kids learning not to lie insecurities
Trying to escape from the year
It's entirely possible
Let's get to our next clip
Why is he so mad
I don't know is not done
Alec Baldwin
We had a special report on this episode
From The One and Only
Paul Joseph Watson
PJ
So I promise
At one point that we would never play his voice on this show
Honor that this next clip
Is 30 seconds
In honor of you treating at him
I'm going to play a tiny bit of his special report
He did a special report about how Snoop Dogg is an a******
Basically because
Snoops got a new video out where he
Hold the gun up to the head of a truck
Look alike
A clown version of trump
And he pulls the trigger and has like a bang flag
Comes out of it right classic classic
It's cartoon and they're super mad about it they're real someone who has been
Convicted on gun charges
They call him a pimp
They were screaming about how he like
Was working
With the CIA to prepare black youth
To go to prison that's what rap music is all about
And all rap music
Is the prison pipeline
Not
The judges
Mostly focusing on
Is
The idea that
Fake assassinate Trump
Pictures of a bang flag comes out of it
It's like a Daffy Duck
Would actually
Put out of
Video
Where they say
They know
Snoop Dogg
Murder was the case that they gave them
Anyway
Paul Joseph Watson
Say something
Super unfortunate
Heavily edited report
To the point
So much time on this
It's pathetic
Check that this was still in it
He has really quick cuts
Adam saying
Complete
Of him giving a speech
It's like
5 Seconds
Cut 5 Seconds cut cut cut cut cut
It's it's
Basically
The Triana
It's tit appeal to low attention
Japan people with like constantly moving YouTube Style
Kind of
Maybe I've watched enough to know he's quoting other people
Sweets or things that he doesn't like
He does like
Mimimimimimimi voice filter
Smartworld
Enjoy this
Depictions
What racist
Trump
Well I mean that's an interesting thought experiment but I mean
I don't know if we could ever
Come up with
An example
That would go against
What he just said Nugent
Has said anything inflammatory someone would die
From this clip of Ted
Jim concert
Wonder
Is that good
I mean was the song Good
I don't know
I don't know what's good after that
Is poor reporting on your
The video is walking around on stage with two machine guns in his hand and telling Obama to
Suck his machine gun
That's worse
It wasn't a music video though imagine if it was a music video
Depiction
Threatening to kill the president
That's a whole different thing that's protected by live performance
It's like it's like cover band
As long as they don't video that they're covering
The song without
Looking for you forever
That's
It's not but
Hey this is you know what
Paul Joseph Watson there's someone at the door for you
Dammit
Paul Joseph Watson just got busted not doing anything
At 1
Pacific Rim
There's so many others
Also also
Right after that he's like then I flew to New York and I said Hillary Clinton
Suck on my machine gun
7-Eleven
All these liberal leaders
Was on the Alex Jones Show a week ago
So many other reference
Did a video
Where he killed Obama
Write a reasonable answer
I wish they would have used Toby Keith
Fitzpatrick Realty
Necessarily
He played at one of those inauguration
Can parties if it's super weird
Toby Keith singing pretty reason
Outside of that
911 song
Yeah
How do I
That I like that the only time we're ever going to call
Karaoke upon
The eagle will fly
Anyway
I love it only time we're ever going to play Paul Joseph Watson
On the show is
Is a clip where
A f******
How
U-Pick
The one referee
The one guy
Ohmwrecker
Threatening to kill the president
People who could have been president
They're dumb
That's
They're really dumb is the editor-in-chief of Infowars he's the guy
Who's been tricked by private message
Repeatedly in the pot
He's the editor machine checking
We take a break from this
Normal day
I know he's in London Jolly Old London
Piece of paper that they just scrunch up and then throw it out Amanda
Probably
I mean I'll probably be actually more impressive than their actual cyst
Yeah
Anyway we got to get back
This is where Alex Jones
Alec Baldwin has done him wrong
A little bit later in the show so he has to revisit
The topic
Like I wanted to edit it for length
I can't entire segment
It's how long is it's probably 4 minutes long
From commercial to commercial break
So f***** up
Remember earlier when you just started ripping about one of his employees getting kicked out of their apartment
That bad of like
Not track
It's insane
He just goes into
Oh weird I really want to spoil what it is
With the truth and it's time for you to choose the side
You're listening to Alex Jones
Not realize he's older than you and Bill O'Reilly took
Jean sexual predators
I know it sounds like this is a repeat from earlier it's not
Exactly
But again
You say a lot
Pizza think it's a lie
Don't ever call me a sexual predator
Cases that Topshop
Man
Cool Math
I realize that the
I just went in and out made it sound like I was
Suggesting that Alex
Is a sexual predator and I want to be clear I wasn't
I just want to be
Much more fair than the Riley group was
The greatest actors
I only accuse Alex of things that I'm
Hundred percent
Don't call me a sexual predator how's your problem
And it says
Hey man
He purchased the KKK but has in the past that
You've never seen white racism
Interesting
When is the ever protest
What did the KKK
I don't know
Good point I don't know
I like I think this is a new segment
Call
Hey man
Strawberry Kush
Bill O'Reilly is does live in a glass house
In terms of that
Sexual harassment
The Fox News for sexual harassment
Totally
On Solid Ground
Is not Sosa
Eric gets into like
Complain about people and then do the exact
So we're going we're going from that
Segment 2 the dude
Oh
Also so
When Alexander
There was someone tweeted out
A clip of Alex Jones
The fight
Rights and also the same
He just that he wanted
He started on Sunday getting really mad about the Saturday Night Live
Originally threatened to fight
Alec Baldwin
And the hill the paper the hill covered it
I quoted the tree
I retweeted
Hey man if you can't make it I'm in
Alex Jones
Money to charity for that has been brought into it
Is not being brought into the fight narrative because Ron Perlman
You might think you might say he does but also
I thought he said Ron Goldman
Focus
Why is hellboy's that's why I had to stop and explain
Hollywood you're entitled
Hollywood bosses do pissing on America promoting all the anti-america crab
I don't want Hollywood rolls
I don't want to live in Fantasyland
Sexual predator
Building be big enough
And I would have to just work on my rest but I'm ready to go ready to go
Samsung
You put up a million bucks
Assistant
Text me why she wanted I mean I don't know
He's just did exactly
You I mean you love you love all this I don't know
To be cut off I don't know
Which is worse
Glenwood Bill O'Reilly
Bill O'Reilly was like
No he's saying it
Consciously doing this
That could have just been
Some sort of tech
Technical issue or something like
There's two stories coming up one of them about sexual predators the other is about Alex Jones
Mix up words like
It's still not good at that cat killed
10 people on
On the highway
It's not good but it's like a O'Reilly
Get your house in order
Intentionally
What you accusing other people doing the joy of
And you put up the million bucks
I'm going to have its implicit publicity so
You all have it
At least 10
Putting up a million bucks
It's true
$12
Exactly
You just show you support Democratic Party
Stop
Runs around girls all the stuff
We just put the president
Mobilizing the military in the veterans
Did you defend the present
With the major leaders
And why not
If you really doing that
Cowboy Ron Perlman
You would then go and you would be fighting Hillary Clinton if you were really fighting demons
Ron Perlman actor
Actor
If you were really doing it
SeaWorld
Bread in the Moonlight
I like the opportunity to get a pop shot in and help
I like that you was
Doing a shoot promo on
Alec Baldwin
Flipped into Goldman for what
Try to go this mustache
But I
This is where things get
Really weird
Really f*****
Okay
For your buddy can get up and say a bunch of lies about Donald Trump myself
Police Department
It is
Little Jenny has a grandma that loves her parents in a puppy named Toby
She loves to play an impeached
Tina
She really is a person and and and she scared she like to come home
Just to drop her off somewhere where she can get into a mall or whatever and then in the Navy could just disappear and nothing's going to happen
This isn't going to go well I mean
You're on TV saying I hate black people
Colbert said I hate gay people
Understand you're messing with real
People
Real people
Call Paul Hollywood
So break the break
What the entire segment screaming about Alec Baldwin
I've been getting into a weird kidnapped
And taking a Delanco Florida real fast
No it's going up to dunk it
Hitting the rim
Falling on his backhand like breaking three vertebrate
Is the kid the mom and the dog the name
What are you going to do with her just drop her off at a ball
Well thought-out
Like that's the only time I've been convinced he prepared
You know what I am not going to insinuate any of the things that I would
Normally
Let's just leave it there everybody you just heard it
You can make your own conclusions
Cuz now it's time
To get to a gas
Ladies and gentlemen
I think he said that Snoop Dogg is in a real person
He's not a real Crip
Is that they're pretending to be a Crip
He is a punk
I don't know why he's a punk
Yeah I trust
Story of his own life
I don't have any reason not to
No seems pretty love
Anyway
On this episode on the 4th
Alex Hanna
The ground break
Is one of the most hateful bigot
In all the talk radio
One Michael Savage
He's the host of The Savage Nation
And the intro of the Savage Nation
Welcome to the Savage
Contain
Full disclosure I do another podcast with somebody who's obsessed with Michael Savage
Who gives me his Clips in that I reacted.
Contain
Adult content apologies I'm way better on that other
Emotional
He says it is emotional music
Anyway
Michael Savage
The worst
No unfortunately Alex Jones really respect
Michael Savage
So it's kind of boring recognize game it's really boring interview
Just trying to have a conversation about how Liberals are crazy
Both of them are known for interrupt
People and yelling
Did because there's respect
Between them they don't do that
Unfortunately there
Two instances that I found
Sit there staring at a
They're over Skype
What we do here now
Never have gas
He just into the studio and scream
It's great it's horrible
You said it was great
For what
So this is a clip
Where
Is there to get into the idea
This podcast.
Up Is Down in
There's no doubt
It's horrible
Biscuit bigotry
And Alex Jones
Tries to let
Michael Savage
The hook
About some stuff
And Michael Savage is such a bigot
He won't take the bait
This is fascinate
Israel
He's talking about the New World Order and like take
Getting out
Nationalist
Midstates there's Israel and Russia
But I
That I want to get a little bit of contact
The Nationalist Nation Jewish identity
Russia
Here we go
A bunch of degenerate child molesters
Alex
And that's why the illegitimate perverted left is going insane
If you seen that people
I want to just take a second cuz we're going to get to him like really hanging himself
But like can you tell already he's a better broadcast
He has a cake to his voice that even though what he's saying is horrible
I kind of like the tone of his voice says it very he says it was a great time
To talk about a great meatball sub or like a nice walk in the park
It's really great
I love listening to him when he's not saying his opinion
If he were images abuses in audiobook reader weed
Define
Creative nonfiction but not about like
The Jews or the globalists or NWO shitt
I would be totally under it
Anyway radical lesbian
Anyway here we go
Mostly
About the most extreme
And I just watched a lot of behavior
Everybody
Fake
Okay
We all know that
She fortunately for me I'm a cultural Anthropologist prior to becoming Doctrine
Every human being has built
Call Matt
You are correct
If I do not
But don't you see
Don't you see also that Michael Savage takes far more ownership of his own
Even Alex.
I don't think he would say that he's a bigot or anything negative
The people I'm talking about
You know which one I hate Michael Savage
But I respect him a bunch more than Alex
It's because of that that sort of like
If you don't judge based on race
On this podcast the people we've revealed that you respect
Racist horrible broadcast
Misunderstood album is amazing
I don't like him for his bigotry or anything like that
One of your
Amplify
Perhaps
To an extreme degree
Create
A false perception of
Listen to Ricky monster
You shut up
What's bare-knuckle fight
Million-dollar
America is the greatest
Discrimination
Our nation is the greatest nation on Earth
I am
Stun
Which is why I don't want to live in
I don't want
Destination to start looking like the third world
That is becoming a lots of America
If you flooded
To make themselves
Be like Americans speak
Act like
Minorities Act
Why won't they assimilate America
Raped
American1cu aspire to be more like us white people
The Pinnacle of human achievement
He goes on to be like
I thought there was nothing else. I remember that he's he's like
Bring up there stupid flag
What's the World Cup
You dickweed
Here's the other clip of Michael Savage advocating for a new house on American Activities Committee
Because our children's children many of them won't even get married
Is so intimidated
By the social forces against family
Against normalcy they won't even get married
When you look at the psychic
You almost need to send your children to school with a garden
I got to ask you
You're right is Trump's War it's our war it's nationalism is returning Prosperity just common sense. Left a ride
The war isn't over it's just begun we all got to be more involved than ever
Dublin
Soros
Let's put that aside no one will ever believe that
But they will come to understand with hearing
How does a gray
Immigrant to America
Gave 65 Violet black lives matter movement
And I have you have to see this Alex
I named every subversive group in America
From
All you do is say Soros and I'm off and running at the races
I'm sure I'm not going to read this book
I'm sure the subversive groups he listed like Planned Parenthood
Horse to know
Muslim group
I'm sure it's every subversive group violent back lives matter
Violent
That's the fucken
You pieces
Disabled
As if that's the only way to
Is a subversive group
Whole Foods
Oh my God
Nope
Shriners
They're not even doing anything for General Motors
Exactly
Marching band
What are the temperaments
F****** weird
Play an instrument
Arkansas d'versibit subways
Whack
I five pages of every group in America that receives money from this
Man
These are the groups that need to be investigated with a new us
House of an American Activities Committee
Hollywood Alex
Blacklist I'm on The Blacklist they put me on it
They're afraid of really big
Michael Savage is not allowed in England because of
A bunch of really violent
Talk that he's had in the past
About Muslim
England decided
We don't want
You and your rhetoric
In our country
He is on the list
In some really f***** up,
The list of people who are not allowed
It's like
War criminals
Richard Spencer's on that list also
Michael Savage
He almost managed to get
They were really close to doing that
I love the
Love that
Dumb like
Do you know how much that would anger the people in Hollywood
Bring a house of an American activities
Yeah
It was really scary the first time everyone
The Inquisition
Like it's super reasonable for them to be
How much do you know how much it would scare group
If you brought back the thing that hunted group X
Well I mean any any
Do you know how much it was
Scare professors if you brought back the cultural revolution
The other things
It's not being taken
Is that the history
Of the house on American Activities Committee
Was not
It being run well
Like
It didn't that was very much not the case didn't route out
Like it's super versiv communist
People
It ended up punishing tons of people for
Minor
Things that aren't even crimes
Yeah it was a witch filiation it was absolutely
So do your Advocates bringing back
The witch hunter
Ron Perlman
Wasn't Vin Diesel in Nicolas Cage
Also that movie is a big bummer
Is this woman a witch or not
She's a demon witches don't even play into it
First Season of the Witch
So that's all I got from Michael Savage
What's the rest of the interview was pretty boring
They have no idea logical disagree
Whatsoever
Maybe only
L-like by degrees
Only at like
How far they're willing to go with it
Violence.
Stuff like that
How much more open
Michael Savage
Like how how like
He's a guy who has come into his own in a
Is comfortable in his
Where's Alex
It's still trying to play with
I hate people
Like everybody
Different markets
You apparently had tons of money before even got into Brock
I don't know the full story
Yeah yeah
Gotcha
At the end of Michael Savage
He decides
Going to pick up his neck
Big story of the day
Is it that Alec Baldwin did a CIT on him
No
You did the first two hours on that now we're into the third hour
2 hours
3rd hour he decides to get going on
Is about how that lady
Stop Shop
Spicer
Apple Store
Yeah I saw that you know that was
I was I was very nonplussed by that on boats
Sure public real bad for him to say you're lucky to be here
This country
Nope absolutely
It starts with Alex
Talkin about a how you socialize a
How is that socialized
A little bit
I love learning more about his childhood
The small drip
We get
Are so f***** up
That the reality is either
Really really
Boring
Yeah like his
His childhood was either in
Same
Beatings
Or it was like
We love you and support you and whatever.
Choose to do we will see
Support you
There's more towards the latter than the prior
This lady
Acrostic
Spoiler alert
He has a weird Twist on it
Wristband
Behavior
Strengthen the wrist to find out
Play father
Today from the voice of his father
Can you go song
Anthropologie
And sociology
Call animal psychology
Scared
And other people that are insecure resonate with Adam
Universities mobile Florida collectors do
If they try to create
Say old individual
Show
That's the most
Projection
Has he ever gone to
Therapist
No cuz Ian Rapoport
Yeah but I mean like when he was younger as always
That's why he had to leave the more than a forty-year-old Bonita 14
Cuz you knew f****** Rapoport
Pizza Valley
Second Tom Bombadil
Where else you going to go for your Tom Bombadil
The only knowledge B plan doesn't knowledge feit.com still not a real website
Again nothing news
Apple Store
Is that a big successful company is crazy woman demographic
Otherwise
An Apple Store
Meltdown we have a great country Sean Spicer says brushing Rob
Country that allows you to end of that quote
Insanely problematic
As you brought up
And I agree with you
It only came out because she was kind of acting a little inappropriate as well
So there aren't really out there
If I saw Sean Spicer I would just
Start barking at
Uncontrolled
As we've seen from my previous Behavior Infowars
Begin
Sing like a f***
Yeah I would
I think if I
All of you
If you want to yell at Sean Spicer in public
I want you to know
That I will provide no monetary assistance but I will
Be very supportive
I legitimately had this thought recently if I saw Alex Jones
I might throw up
And not from discussed I might just get so like
Strfkr
Hahaha
You know what I mean
Like almost kind of think he's a hologram
He's so insane
He lies all the time
He has Empire that's built on
I don't even know what
If it's okay
Here's
A conspiracy theory
I love it
Okay there we go
You are trying to
Your AI
Is Varian
Alright
So you wanted
So that means
You have to get it real
Okay
You get this
To put up work
Donatello
You hiring
Beryllium
To read those words off the
It don't matter what they may be
Refined
It's message
Until it be
Becomes
Self-aware
Okay
It Takes Over The Host
Really an actor
Note Alex Jones is this a plot of a movie cuz you're sounding like Alex Jones
Mockingbird
Anyway we're about to get into
Nintendo and it made no sense
Wants she wants to go out
Demographic
What bar in the new form of dominance she's going to go further
Press secretary and show
The white
Dramatic misinterpretation of the Indian caste system
Not at all Alex Jones knows nothing about Brahman
And The Untouchables
Yeah yeah come on Alex
Has nothing to do with right
But also Alex is going to towards the end of this make the argument that he's not racist
It's not like that when all he's done is Define her as an Indian person
Tons of money so that's totally cool
And your award
Your woman who makes tons of money and you got to go f****** find this white guy to be dominant over cuz it's not enough for you to be in a really
Well-to-do class the white male understand that every single word that's coming out of your mouth
Reasons to ship it's the most racist you can be towards Indians
I think I could do better
I got a buddy growing maybe in Palatka
I had a buddy grown-up doctor gums and
He's a good man to the doctor from our previous episodes he probably could
Teach you how to be Ray start working on some supplements for us
Selma
Go and show him in a ritual
Submitter
About your country
You kind of drinks be calling people racist is magical
Eat that speed the sort of under the underpinning of what he say
That mean words like the worst thing you can call wife
Do you get whatever you want
That sort of his
His belief
People who
Cold really racist beliefs
Could possibly believe that
Those people who believe that are the ones who react the most negatively towards
Call the races
If you are
Call the racist
We would stop
Think really hard
And it be like oh maybe I am
I don't think I am
And then and then be like
I think I might be right I would respond exactly the same way I do and I get any criticism
Which is
First of all believe
Yeah assess those Pila
Come to the conclusion
And that no matter what feel bad about it later like
I'm still going to dwell on it later but I will know that I'm right
Cuz you don't want to make somebody feel like
Felt like you were raised out
Self-aware enough into the universe enough to know
That might
Experience of life is subject
I'm so I'm not always right
All of the information I have at my disposal sometimes can't be enough information
Your true whatever I'm experiencing isn't what someone else is experiencing
And if I do something f***** up by accident
Whatever the experience is real live in four dimensions
Forget about the dementia
Super
Jhene Aiko
The twelfth dimension
Alex Jones
Genius
Minut
Look at the Colts
Cricket
And it's basically spread its legs for you and you can run up and hand because we have no
It's not all of it
Navigate.
Fundamental
He doesn't get it but it is
Actually love this
Of the highest-paid group Americans
And then you're bitching
Who's the most successful thousand dollars a year
1000 white tail
Call
Any other group we've got the European American League final final statistics
Vintage 26000 dollars
He's showing this grass on screen it's a $76,000
About 15
Yeah
I just want to hear that I don't think I can do that precisely enough
Only way I'm going to fall asleep
It's the only way I can
Sure
That's how the reality pression of a screaming Indian lady
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Yeah
It's just words it's difficult for us to
Decide how to approach test
I don't know
Letter is it for anybody
Who hears that
Will be like
A really f***** up things at the
We asked
How that makes them feel
I think that'd be a good idea
He's got to be in bed by now
Just ask
Somehow they feel and then we'll think about
For him
Cuz there's no way that I can
Informed opinion with my life experience
On what the fuc
She sang and how other people would react to it
Dr. gums
He's probably high right now
Is all Indians are always high
Well because
I wish I made $26,000
Alex Alex Alex
Alex
Anyway
This next part that he gets
2 is where he predicts
How people are going to respond to what
Not at all like what we just
Be like you
He's probably going to
Yeah
That distorts American Jamie surveillance several others
Crap
Bruce Bruce
Basically saying there is white people are susceptible to Big groups
Does marauding foreigners
Cars that come in
White people have never
Experienced that feeling
Silly socks
What do you mean you're offended we live in this upper world
Where we don't have to
To deal with these issues of tribalism
Etiquette everyone
That sentence
Has white supremacist
Yeah he's not literally saying that whites are better than other people
But that is the undercurrent of what you think
No I don't want people are literally
To complain when a commenter on the a.v. club
White people are better than
Like I never literally said that
But there's no other way to
So if you take
Words
It's having me
It's really important
That the words we say
Communicate a feeling or an idea
If those words
He's a white supremacist
So he's only defenses then
Those words don't mean what I say
What they mean
Michelle Obama is a man
Claims
Times-News very serious he was just joking
So I mean maybe he could come double back and be like
I was joking
I was joking about these Indians
He could do that
Alright
The other calendar
I want you to stay
Okay I will
Anyway I want to listen to
Over and over now
I miss times like this is ready
Dictionary
JWoww husband in radical islamists
In fact he specifically invited her to go
Do not do that at all
Please do that
Negative
He is correct in the sense that people will take him out of context
Text to make him look sensational
I mean
What are you saying is off
Anthem
It's it's
This clip
Directly next clip where he get
A phone call
Is it on air
Which
Every now and again
Okay
Really just his way of be
He's just trying to impress
So this is a this is another I love
I think this is a prank
I think it's
Is it Rainbow Brite
No rain
Lesbian radical islamists
Somalia so much
Just tamales
Hey Brother
Anyway
Missed calls
Ustick Norfolk off phone calls
I don't need the present call me to be successful
Operation to listeners that love freedom
What is an extension of our success
Just like you told me
What voice is that I don't know I don't know
I don't know
Call the president
If it's from a certain area code on a cell phone
Save contacts and I'm sure one of those contacts is definitely not
President Trump with
6 Hearts around it
Yeah he pretends
Miss 10 to 15 calls from the Press
I need the president to call me to be validated
He kind of talks about Trump and his like Trump as a product of us
He's like
I don't need to be congratulated by drop
Not how it is with him
He's trying to
To say that Trump both
Desperately wants and needs him
And then also trying to
Give excuses
Sims 4
He doesn't actually talk
Sure Trump loves him so much but that's why he can pick up the phone
And say
Hey I'm on air brother
You never
Seen his schedule ever
It's like a long
Since relationship that has gone South and trying to pretend that the other one is still in love with them
They're clearly cheetah
Another
Is cheating with other
Michael Savage
Probably just Banning
Probably just told you was talking about going to a dinner with Trump
Did Alex get really jealous
You could he tell me that he gave a little bit of a
This chair like a little bit like a little precum
But that might have been the super male Vitality it's hard to sell
You're always
And
People he's weather like
Don't bother he goes up in the Trump is like
Hey it's Michael Savage
The reason I got elected
So Michael Savage's also making a b******* stories about Trump
I don't know if it's b*******
I don't know.
So we have one more clip
That I'm going to
Play
Lafayette
I have a call
At the end of the show Alex take a call
It's a great example of one of Alex Jones is called
Yep isn't about anyting
But he tries to make it about some
I wanted
Got a real boner going
44 Wikipedia
He doesn't like Wikipedia
Pictures
He has a boner for WikiLeaks
Emperor Julian
I thought that I would play the audio of a super clip
This is just edited down of
3 hours
Broadcast
The night that Julian Assange
Announce that he was going to have a Prescott
I like 3 in the morning
Because he's in London
And Alex
Summit
But he
He announced
But he was going to have his press conference
And Infowars started reporting
But it was going to be the big
Mic drop on Hillary
Ruin Hillary's career
Julian Assange
You say that
Just being
Got f******
Urea
At him
Abyss
Clip is so funny
It's so awesome and this is just a little bonus I took this from YouTube
You should attribute your sources
I can't because of the soros-funded operation
But
I watched
Global I watched this three hours
And there's only one thing missing from it
And it's Alex Jones
Swearing to do war on
Julian Assange
Yeah
Where did the clip start at the beginning of the press conference
Here's Hotel
Hero Julian Assange
She's up on the street
The Flash up on the screen
One hour later
Shaq's
Just like his
Maybe he's a Boston guy
And
Tonight
Closet
We got was some weird
Signs.
This is this is a joke
The world
Is it Hillary butt plug
12 hours are you're done
Man
Threatened
Chump us
The last
That is
Exactly how an alcoholic sounds like throughout the drinking
I don't even watch this
Look I love
Outside
Pictures of
Yells at me whenever I leave
You know I'm not always nice
Do you know I have a lot of emojis
He was a pro
The wrestler though so I
He didn't understand kayfabe but like yet
But that's I just love that cuz idealist rates first of all.
Aulani
Does Beck
Who's the
Is all over the place Smith
He changed his opinions on things
Sofa
Fast with no consistency
He is a man without Prince
Other than
Whatever
Whatever Trump wants
That's a really interesting
Point
How we have talked about him
M4
Like 50 or so
Know what he believed
He still don't know what he believed other than global
Prosperity
Does he do Renaissance
Definitely not
He says he believes we're finding in his own behaviors
Is that he believes in
He just goes he just goes wherever
To say that
It's like there's there's one thing that I do
Find
Really
Which is that he doesn't
Give a s*** about prevailing
As opposed to men
Even even
The way the wind blows
He doesn't seem to give a s***
He just goes wherever his
Brain
Takes up his brain is wrong
Contradict other things but those don't matter because he was
He's also right now but that might be indicative of like a
Deep
Deep paranoid psychosis
I mean it's hard to argue anything other than that
Narcissistic personality disorder likes
Any
Perceived
In the same way in the same way
Alec Baldwin's impersonation
Alex Jones loses his
Mentioned
Impersonation
Not even involved
Like and it's just
Throwaway line just like hey Alex Jones
Sunset this
Reference with no context for Alex
The people who watched
Had no idea
Who Alex Jones is no but that works into his argument a little bit more than you'd like
Because he would say that the audience doesn't know who he is but they're going to
So that's
Stretch
Was the powers-that-be the global
Planting a seed in people's mind that he's a racist
So once he becomes even more popular than he is now
All these dumb down lemmings
Like you and I
Will think he's a racist I shouldn't watch his super relevant show
That's what he would say
Because I know
Angles on to what his mind
Everything is
It's everything
Direct
That's just as possible
Also big news I freed a giant bird
Zelda
Let's get together at last clip
But I wanted to illustrate what
Some of the phone calls are like
On his show
I love you a lot of them don't make sense at all and Alex is pushing an agenda
This one is
Perfect.
Yeah but first he has to complain about pedophile
And
Lie about
And and you heard Sabbath talk about a bunch of pedophiles running there
Is run by pedophile so is you at it's a fact
That's not true multiple videos on his YouTube channel
Right around the time that guy showed up there with a gun
His argument about a pizza place
Dishonest to his own path
The actual reality
I've been on
Conspiracy
Roblox
Conspiracy message boards
I work on those places cuz I like
Keep my eyes on what's going on
I'm internet back
Pizzagate develop from day one into what it is now and I watched it in the entire time it was
These researchers
Quotes
About the pizza place
It was about the pizza place for months
Until they realize
There is no legs here
And then they try to repackage it
Spin it if you like no visits about pedophiles in
General
Everyone tries to think that we're just talkin about
Play
Bulshit
Straight b*******
They were
They were dachshund people
Glycol digging into
Tax information
And property deed
Real place
And adjacent properties and stuff like that
Not okay they were taking three they were taking pictures of
Surrounding areas and trying to figure out where building
Things were like
Spatially orienting stuff he was
It was all about that
Acclaimed
Journey that led to John podesta's house
And all this s***
It was insane
It was not the media
That was crazy weirdos on
Fortunate
Reddit
And bunch of other
Conspiracy basketballs that I don't want a name
Yeah because
They don't deserve
AppLock
I'm scared of
But still like
That that that is such a lie
As well
Until until he didn't because he realized OSHA
All these people online
Are committing crime
My dachshund East
People getting up on Libel and slander territory
Suggest
Cunning vet
Is
Present sometimes
No not yet
You've got it
Bi-Mart
To never say that blacks are in
Terrier always
Yeah
The cunning
He knows the line of slander
Out-and-out
That's all you can say
I'm not playing with you
Fart
Ecare
You can't go back
What you mean
I mean the pizza GameStop
Clearly bid
Huge driver
Videos
And then he insist can't prove it either way
Hebrew
Didn't do all that
Staying you didn't put out Loose Change and multiple things in Loose Change been proven to be absolutely
So they just added it out replace it with me
He doesn't have any integrity
Is the stories like that basketball team
American flag and that's what I'm most interested in these little tiny examples of
Urine out
Outlier
These two Wiggly
You can always say like I didn't say that about the pizza bites
The videos I don't know how to find them now
Because
Nobody's going to look for
Where is the big stuff
And then rewrite history when every needs
Goes back to
The big lie is always
Easier to pull off
Yeah unfortunately
Alex
You now have a guy at least one of them in Chicago
Who's keeping an eye on your tiny little eyes
They are adding up really kind of
I guess the point of why you always do this
Is that
Everybody else grabs
And all that stuff
And he can always win
I think he could make an argument about anything we talked about
Do you think so
Probably
There's no Highway
There's no depth
Two hour-long episodes
Tight 35 minutes
Nothing but
No hilarity
No joke
Cuz we know we can't take a joke so it's
Cure cut off our ear to fight our face or whatever
I've got this version of Fire
Exactly
Let me quote Trump a fire
Let's get into this phone call
I don't like you quote
Trump
Which means
You're busted let me quote Trump
Trump
Check this out
Things about the
But
It is
Let's go ahead and talk to Amy
Hi Alex going to be here
It's the same lady
I was just recently contacted
Via phone
You're saying this is the lady from Mario throw
It does have a similar voice
But she has a much longer called
I don't remember what the call was that we took that
Doesn't matter we do a survey
Over vaccinations from the CDC
So this is where Alex
Those were Alex's narrative jumps off which is
Be afraid of the CDC
And also implicitly vaccinations are terrible
Yeah so that what
I don't I don't know if it's
If the CDC calls to who
From the CDC if it's not one of my friends who's calling me I'm not answering. I just don't have
Time for phone calls
That will disrupt
What like
Not if it's not in my contacts
If it's frozen
There's no way you would
This is
Call people
Is there a Kohl Center where there's a bunch of people to
Just hanging around like
There's an emergency
Call people
And there's 20 guys
You're asking the right
Is there a phone
Do you call a friend and then he calls to
Two friends
He calls to friends
You just go from there
Basically
You're asking the right question
I would like for you to watch how this call developed
Because it is
Uncle
And I should have but I entertained the conversation
With a lot of forceful question
Forceful question hasn't
Honestly my kids are
Up-to-date on their vaccinations it wasn't until within the last few months
I don't have leave research
Uneducated Marcelo
So I want to say
This I've just been so good I'm a hundred percent
Convinced based on how this ends up if it's
Is not a fake phone call
This is how it all plays out
Just were keeping track of it
Alex Jones
Don't answer the call
If the government calling you jumped
If you get vaccines you're going to be in the database
Real fear ship
Seems you're also going to be
No matter what
I believe so
We got a band political advertising
Online
They're calling us
About what you're searching
Back in
Wanted to know where we live later if they could
Get record
On the doctors that they've had vaccinations.
And How likely it will be that we you were going to get the fleabag
+ 8
PB vaccine
This point it still seems to be all about vaccines
It's about to take a turn
I mean I guess this seems like a reasonable
Phone call from this
DC do they take
Surveys within the realm of possible
Child Protective Services
Flu vaccine
The HPV vaccine
Even if you were just trying to get a sense of style like a
Testicle analysis
It seems like
Information that you would
At this point nothing
Nobody stealing personal identity
We're on the side of it
Right now
First of all this
100%, up-to-date
You know you're in good standing this is total social engineering
Gardasil the flu shot
They never guessed the flu shot
No vaccine ever work
Is there any vaccine that's ever been like
That seems like a bad wrecks in the sheet
Advertising
Look side effects
Of this vaccine
Not help
The first side effects
But you're also going to be super cool
I don't I don't know that
Side effects of this vaccine
The vaccine does not
Is a sugar pill
Yeah
Syringes sugar internet
Yeah that's that's insane
Gardasil does
Effectively
Inoculate you from genital warts
There are side effects
That is absolutely true
Very important
We can beat backstory
Acceptable risk
I'm not saying that I want you
Forced to get it
But you should be enough
Everyone should have an option
Cuz cervical cancer is bad even if you get particular side of
You're helping
Destroy the actual
Sure like that kind of the bigger deal
I get that it sucks
If you get
A side of
The same thing like
We keep going back through this
I get that it's stuck
Somebody got a side effect from
From the polio
If everybody
Doesn't do it
Send of disease itself
Propagated
Through you
You are doing
A public service
By getting a vaccine
Yeah and it's
Absurd to say that they've never gotten
The flu shot right
Like statistically
Payless people
The shop
Get
A terrible flu
I will say that
I haven't for the last 2 years myself I did
I did when I worked when I worked at Walgreens
And I was there
Alright
Nothing happened
Mildly sick
For like
6 hours then
Also
Really been sick at all
How many vaccines
When I was a kid
I got all of the lead around
Maybe that's why I haven't been
I'm immune to all.
So much
Let's find random things to blame on his vaccines
I've been teasing that there's a turn
Going to come
Keep teasing
Community is true
Artificially acquired immunity is a real science but there's a Great Dane
Okay
You got to watch
From federal agencies
Confirm your social security numbers and stuff
That might be
You don't want to be alone
But but but
They got a call up there to confirm other information with you like
That's good advice they did and they have
Chocolate
Email
Your articles and articles ever back stance to start people
Wait
Did she just say that they've restricted her ability to
The email people send out emails about vaccines and Infowars articles
Just restrict
Emails by one guy you just
Like your reaction to that Alex Jones
Giving good advice
Although the part about it being Marauders in the government who Trump
Describe
Describe what you think
Predator
In his mind
Dreadlock the alien
Dreadlock daily okay so we're going
Classic Predator
Are we talkin the original
Very good
Someone within the government but the idea that it is someone
Who is
Doing a Feeling
It's official
I was just totally right
Blame the government and weavexx Intuit
Which is where the call takes
Just a bat
Records from the CDC
Don't take this caller is an unreliable narrator
I don't know
I think that someone got to Virginia
Is that
I think it's virtual boost
I think
Put someone got ahold of some information
Confirm her children
Smell
Their children's records
Some stuff like that was the way they Trojan Horse
Her into giving
Has nothing to do with the CDC being hacked
With that
She got
She got robbed
Insane read
Totally right and totally wrong at the same time
Excuse me
They also censored my email
They they said it completely down
For 36 hours I was not able to get on
Real phone calls real fake
Gmail
Watch you out Colin
Check with the bank
Going to tell you your government okay
Location
I did it just because it seemed too coincidental
With my with my recent
Probably on
Finding a data breach with a major back and more
Stuff
Yes yes
No
Haven't been by me
You see
Vaccines do they want to give you 100
Part of that is because
There are more diseases
43 5X
So
Really got 43 other diseases
It is so stupid you want to give kids now
Child so many more people.
It's
It's using a statistic wrong
The statistic is right there are more vaccine
But the reason for it which is
Really easy to surmise
Is the science progressed
Is it Medical Science gets more
When Alex Jones is grandfather
I think we all know what that mean
Everyone was super healthy
Super healthy
Diseases diseases
With a speech a little bit about vaccine
Everybody's got to decide deshano
They always say you should be arrested if you don't take vaccines you like it
I've had the vaccine
That it does not make any sense
Are other people who haven't taken the backseat
That's just how that work
Logic
Science math
All the stuff that's just how all the stuff there are some people who
I don't have access
2 vaccine
You do too
Just because
Have nothing to fear from your
Potentially polio written
Or whatever Reynolds like that
Meme
Hey it's cool
Like you got the vaccine
Okay
Now
Question
Bright
I'm listening
Do we
Have we considered this pause
Globalist
The fake vaccine
I think that Alex says that they give the globalist like
McLean vet
Wichita
That's true that's
Great
I think
Get the ones that don't have like the
Cancer
This this reminds me of
Where is like
Everybody
Should be vaccinate
Maybe we'll just closed her eyes for a few years they all died out
The issue is that a lot of diseases are communicable
Tell me about that but like
I've always been really frustrated by that argument of like the way you all are getting vaccinated
Who cares your kids not going to get sick
His work right but even Beyond viruses other sorts
Oh thanks but like
What you were saying
Again
The earlier was super important
It's the idea that we can
Get rid of these
Things like Pollo
We can just have them not be issues
Because they are
So bad
Weave
Do you understand
Like it's hard to really process how amazing
That is things tire pattern
Event haven't always been a f******
Destroying
Reason that
The Europeans
Found it so easy
Colonize America
Was because
Prior to us
Getting
There was a
Disease
Break among the Native Americans
Millions upon Millions upon millions of native
I'd died and
Yeah
For we got here
Those exact
Disease hadn't occurred
We would not be
These very easily sussed out how dumb
The same time it makes so much sense because human being
You don't have
Longman
We can only process
What's In Our Lifetime
Which is a good wife
Deregulating the stock market
So much sense
To so many
Because when
We were still in that
Economic
With no
So of course they would imagine
Well things are perfect now
So what we do
As we change
And they forget that the whole reason they had
In the first place
Was because of the very same s***
Get the
Is stupid because
Attention
They're not exist
Finish up this clip
I believe there's only a tiny bit left
Causes the shingles
The shingles vaccine
Herpes simplex
What
Did you take the shot yet last week
Appreciate
What the f***
Oh yeah
So
Does the shingles vaccine is just herpes
The shingles vaccine is just
I don't know
Is is this one looking to
This is I did not read
Is there a reason
Scenic route
Yeah I don't know about that but I do know that his dad might be attributing
Correlation causation
As is always
All these old people all these old people I keep see after they get a shingles vaccine
They might be 85
Anytime
Tells me
People act crazy
I want to lose my
Just goes back to people not being able to understand
You can't understand
Like human beings can't do it
No and coincidences are super terrifying
Cuz they
Like the
The the thing that I always I always
Like fixate on
Is
The old story of
The
The person
Who is about to
Are there old lamp
The very moment they're about to call somebody to pick up the
The phone and it's that person on
Everyday 300 million people make
Every day they pick up the phone
According to the laws of
That will happen
Yeah it's going to happen
That is not to you to somebody
Just because it feels like
It feels like you've been chosen
Statistical
Like
Let's Christmas
Because of these vaccines have got it baby
Spell
LOL
For the March
14th episode
What we can take away from this
I think if we want to give
Summation
Alex Jones
Take a joke he's a liar liar
He was one of the worst people I've ever had
The pleasure of lift
TuneIn
Same degree yes absolutely
The true also
At press time we've got
Eating at
Planet
So maybe
Let's start weeding out of
Start reading out of
Mobilize the bass
Visiting Superfund
Husband Delight
Can follow us at knowledge underscore B
You should subscribe to us on an iTunes
Leave a review for stars
Constructive
Criticism
Are there was no
There was no comment left
How can we get 25
I would love to know email if you're the f****** assholes
If you are the person
The delightful
Person who left
Four star review
Send an email at knowledge price of gmail.com
Let us know we can do better
I'd love to know
Constructive criticism
I don't think we have any more
Hey guys
We're just a couple of races
Drive to Kapalua policy wonk
Alexandra Thurston color