Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
What was the last time you went
In front of
Crowd of
Twenty thirty thousand White
When your
Third grade
Victor like back in my stand-up days
What I was in front of nearly that large what kind of dancer is no certainly not
No I haven't done that
You
I think I
Declared myself a nationalist
That was more in like
Risk that kind of situation
Nationalist
You've got to be you've got to look at the global perspective
The Oceania strategy
I stake out North America and I put all the troops on the borders English leave everything in the middle of
Let It Go much like Trump
A recording this last night
Cuz recording on Tuesday
On Monday night is Ralliart
Scrubs
Which is the very least they're added
Costco senior nationalist is really the worst thing in the
The other things that surround it
Picture and
Just some extent
Pick me up on what's going on
Alexace
Booty on the other side
Definitely
I know that because I know a lot about
October 23rd
2018 episode
I apologize do not have a Wacky Wednesday episode
But duty calls
Substitutions in life
Presidents over last night
And today is one such
Occasion
And say this is
Is all about hatred of people coming up to the Border
No
Only a little
He does you just do that
The last time we talked about
Being a army of Invaders
Trump rally for reasons unknown
Around
Terrible idea
Well I don't I guess I was kind of I think I was watching something on YouTube and then I went back to the homepage
What's going on
I started sort of in the middle of Ted Cruz's at the beginning
That's the worst
Hughes Crossing
I noticed something in him that you can
You can see in comics
If you watch enough comedians especially in the lower levels
There's often times there people who are really bad comedians or used to getting a terrible response
Front of a good room accidentally
And start doing really well and you can see it in their face or like oh my God this is
Oh wow I wish it was always like this had that look and it really
Fuse me
Didn't confuse me but it made me super
Grossed out
Because
I could tell the internal machinations in his head were like
Man I wish I had this many idiots would show up for me
Hillary sucks I never
USA trains would break out for no reason
It's the kind of crowd if you're a comic you would look man
Would hate for them to be your friend
Performance Brand of Avonlea EcoBoost
Coffee House
And
He know
I realize that I've really only watched while he's in the past I've never really watched
More than liked for continuous minutes
And it wasn't like not infuriating
I can't believe
And I know I know I know I'm not breaking new ground on anything or something
Bugs
Like from the podium
You just walked away from the breakout or something like that
Podium turn around to do like a shrub
I don't even know what to say to describe it but it made me very terrified
Because he is talking about the the Caravan of refugees
And he's calling them an invading Army and stuff like that of the entirely White
Faces behind him
Just got the shot is all white
And they're all like build the wall built
And it's really really hard to watch that without
Feeling
Of like
And again I know this is not new territory
But this is
Are you f****** hate real
There is nothing else going on here there is no reason for it to exist in terms of like
The midterms
I don't think this is helping him
I don't think this helping Ted Cruz
Ted Cruz going to get whatever he's going to get you know people are going to be swayed one way or another they do is going to pick up people who work.
Go to vote or undecided people Ted Cruz's got his old people
And that is that
This is all
Rick
Explain the
The base
This is just
Rally them around
This
This cruelty
It already exists within them normalizing
Let them express it in some public forum where the rest of the country has to watch
The rest of the country has to see
This exists
This whole stadium of people don't want you f******
Can hear you're a f****** Army invader
And it was really really
Difficult
To watch
He gets into his part where he's like
You know what you know what a globalist is
You know what a globalist
That's how he laid into I'm a nationally
He's talking about like you know what a globalist is
Pause
Which is
A little bit like
Everybody
Then he's like there's people who care about the whole globe
Why they can always old-fashioned to be a nationalist
Bahama nationalist care about our country
I just got overwhelmed with a sensitive like this is so what we talked about all the time like we don't cover
Trump nearly as much as we talk about Alex
And his information
Spear
And watching
Like a lot of anxiety because my over
Overriding prevailing
Feeling was
I am going
Crazy
Because the world that I've been studying
That people tell me I'm crazy for studying
He's now so
Publicly normalize
Yeah and everyone
Not everyone but a lot of people covering it or doing it very wrong
And they're going to end up playing into his trap
In the same way we've seen a bunch of Articles to Twitter
How about how if you are covering
Trump and you use his language of an army of invading people from the South
Even if you're just
Quoting him
You are helping
Wreck in your headline if you say Trump
Army of refugees coming done is aided the normalization
Nevada language
You given an advertisement for an army of ref
And there's 100
Mixed in with
This
This world did that Trump is allowing
Rear its ugly head that are exact same thing
Irresponsibly covering
What drove everything home for me
Was in the evening there was an article in the New York Times
Came out
About how someone left
The bomb in George soros's mailbox
And my first thought was
I can't believe that didn't happen already
It's if you do and it's not good
To feel that way
It's not good for me to feel like
Took that long
Crazy
But then on the other side
We have to dress
Expect it like
Al Jones is not the only person who does
George Soros game
Or anything like that
There's going back clearly before him
As we've we've seen in recent episode
There were
We're other autocratic leaders around the world who didn't like him before that in the 90s
Certainly there has been Eastern European despot who have
I just like Tuesday liberating influence
He tries to bring
Bill O'Reilly I believe in 2007 went on a little harangue about him
Mention those things are footnote
To what Alex
Alex has taken all of those little games and gone pro with it
He's made a career largely out of
Demonizing George Soros at least in the last
5 years
And when when we see
Someone leaving a bomb
In his mailbox
I mean there is there's no other way to say it like this it's getting way too real in the world
There's no way
Like Alex is not response
And II
Meme I mean that I don't mean mister Lee that he's legally
Responsible
But spiritually
He's actions
Have created
Now you can make the argument that Trump is also said some f****** s*** about Soros
Quickfire with the Tucker Carlson's of the world
Uncertain
That is absolutely true
Cushing Soros active
The big bad guy in an extended
Continuous
Alex Jones was
The proof-of-concept of that that everyone else has taken
And run with
And and made their own
I don't know how else
Because when you look at it
What we have
Is
A president who's running
Whether or not everybody there is white
Being Tire shot on television is a bunch of white
People saying really
Callus bigoted things about people who are different
You have that basically you have
A president doing nazi-style rally
For no political reason other than that
Yeah just for the sake of doing it
Venom gloves in the only way for me to be loved is for me to tell you to hate and that it's okay to
Right
Can you have the other side of it
Where are you have people like
Creating
Paramilitary street gang
That go around because of political
You have
People
Who's this
Bentleyville
Boogeyman
Mailbox
We are so much
The reason that I couldn't sleep last night and
Rapping like crazy
What it all adds up to me
Is
I had a realization that we are so much further down the road then I
I
Maybe a naive
Colonel in my head no
I never really thought that we could really go back home again
Necessarily I'm not saying that to normalcy I'm Falling Away
The reality of
Like how much deeper in a hole we are than I thought
Hit me last night
And it was
So unplug
Blame the right way
I mean Alex is already set up. He's already set up the idea that they're going to.
Absolutely everybody on the left George Soros
Vilify
Tucker Carlson
This whole thing all of these horrible
Conspiracy theories coming out and they were like
This is our perfect opportunity
To finally give us a false flag that we can really sink our teeth into
Find that violence
The best way to solve their problems and their Giant
Rationalize it is I only did that cuz I'm a liberal
I realize
I was in the situation where we're coming
Buntok Project Camelot or some s***
The world
What is Alex going to
Stay
His whole show is about Soros on
Many level
Yeah these days at least
And for quite a while
Call Rhodes Jerome
All f****** roads lead to Soros
Last night
Before this episode of his show
Someone left
A legit bomb
In his mailbox
I can't imagine he doesn't
Do something
Like I can't imagine he doesn't address
So I knew that I would have to
Do this episode
And see what
And I'll tell you what
Some really bad stuff in this episode
Surprise butt
I promise you
No but if we get through it
There's some really great stuff
Ventura
Cuz we need a pressure release valve I'm sorry about that sort of long-winded intro
I think I could have delivered it better if I slept more last night put the same time I'm in I'm in a
I'm struggling
Every
Free time the news turn the different way
No I mean
Closer to
There are anger
I'm not going to get there I might get
To the point where
I flee
That might be where we're at
Anyway like I said we're going over 2018
From today's show
I dreamed all night about Trump
We know
He was laying on the edge of the bed
Slowly crawled up
Wiggling
I knew
I had become and an absolute
Starts with Alex kind of describe
Boring
I think you got drunk at the rally and maybe he's a little bit rough this morning or something like that
So I don't know it was very on engaging it was mostly just about him lying about how large
The crowd was outside at the rally
Former Alex Jones and current Houston police chief art Acevedo
He's going to record it said there were three thousand
So
He also has really funny that he's going with where he's like
What's the weather today
I'm guessing the trumps people even without like
He might be too disruptive
Look
Thank you for your
Sherp
Second
Please don't be you're not allowed anywhere within 10,000 for you to prompt anymore on account of if you talk
The game is up
I could be some
Right-thinking advisor of trump
Knowing that
Alex probably feels a little bit like a jilted lover on a personal level
Probably a little mad that I
His home state and didn't ask him to do a set
So maybe so
He's always armed
Is Alex
Is Elsa a little busy but not publicly but I'm
Certain private equity
Here
Counter-protesters they're all mentally ill
Of course course
He explains it to the drop in the stock market was the Chinese
Cuz of course
About
Viz
Refugee Caravan
Course he does some of that
Dimensions goal is defeating America
Christian destiny
Okay well I'm on board with the glove
Which I think is a little bit too much
For him to say coyote
The globalist if your goal is to
The defeat of America's Christian destiny
I feel like it's too blunt for him
But
Whatever
Do you want to if you want to go that direction
Then welcome
Go to Chuck Norris in 2009
It's all kind of boring and a mishmash of nonsense
And then little bit into the show
This Proclamation
What's going on
Almost campeon are at this point
Good
And then I get so angry
But I just have trouble even talking to
Called overcompensating
Prepare for the chef
Like the idea that you can't talk about stuff
Clear indication that all you're doing is stretching for time and it's evident in this episode
Money because he's
Plugging ever
Every segment
And of course
Christmas sale is already
Action of Cortez Reno
He's frustrated
If you last that long multi-level marketing
That would be great
Finally a little bit
We've already been over 100
In the mail
College
Neymar
Filled out
Spanish
Okay alright
They're sending in their abs
Absentee ballot
What's my because they're dead they're writing the wrong address on their eyes
I don't know I don't think this is true
It's
Interesting it's an interesting narrative because number one
Breezy to substantiate
You know what I'm saying
You can't just put one out you have to put out at least
Ravenswood have a pattern
Right come from you
Because I do trust
What is interesting about a little bit
And I don't relate
The 2016 election you can find some stories about people
Hand is so often the case the reality serves to hurt Alex's argument
We know about these cases
It's because they're routine Jackson Place With Me
To make sure votes are coming in using the
Staples
Yeah that's nice for instance in Alton Illinois
Audrey Cook
Who is voting in the name of her dead husband
Because she said she knew how he wanted to vote
So what difference does it make we want to devote
Compelling argument that felt like she knew what was right
Even though it was a felony
So she voted her dead husband's name
The black woman who got
What was it like 5 years
For felony voting
That was just because she
Woman got
Five years in prison
Ocheyedan
No
So I assume that she is healthy
The same standard
Also fun fact Audrey Cook wasn't just a normal everyday citizen who may or may not know better
Better about what they're doing
She was a Republican election
In the town of Alta
Yeah
I mean we have cases like this alright the idea the very f****** idea of Alex
Tons of people everybody I know everybody mailed ballots filled out in Spanish
Is
Is absolutely ludicrous
Fight
He explains why they're doing it
In this next clip
How many points are very slowly
I don't have
This is one out of ten thousand
When would people get mailed if you get crap like this
You have to call the news
You do Columbus office
Voter registration
Maybe Airport
Conservative
But you get the leftist
Do birdies fly in the sky
I think Alex would consider me a deranged leftist and no I wouldn't I wouldn't do that
Also I don't believe this is
I also Joel Gilbert
He's the guy who directed the documentary Dreams of My real father
About an hour
Fill out one of those ballots
Himself to
Hold up as fake evidence that this is
Yeah but generally it starts throwing around a bunch of like headlines about the places
The town people voting
People's names
Generally speaking most
This concerned about dead people having voted
If you actually read the article or you look
Look into it a little bit further
The actual problem is not voter fraud
But it's almost always
Clerical errors made by the registrar or the pulling
Almost every single time when they look into it they find
There was some sort of a mix-up in the paperwork here or whatever
Listed as dead when they shouldn't be or people
Things were filed wrong cases of voter fraud miniscule
Number of cases like that
Hey baby getting there are a couple cases that you can find certainly fits Taurus fit into Alex's
If you look over the span of many years
Any kind of
Endemic
Systemic thanks
And I would
I would say the
If you think for a second about what Alex's suggest
He knows people received ballots in the names of dead people in Spanish
Why haven't any of these ballots been produced
This bdz way to substantially improve the story if it were true
Also wired
Is friendsgiving
Wouldn't the people behind the scam that want to jeopardize getting charged with a very serious felony
Look at this strategy makes no sense and him trying to wash it away with
Conservatives are going to fill that out they know better only demon left us to come do it
It's a perfect plan
School moral Republicans are going to do it
Skies this is a terrible plan
It looks very least do a little bit of research and don't send one to Alex Jones
Wealthy brand
Everyone who's associated with Alex Jones
And I think he tipped his hand a little bit there by saying that people
Wasn't written out in Spanish
My guess I don't know
Produced any evidence
It doesn't Trace back to Fortune
I'm going to say
Broth
Yeah
We see Alex
Doing what
He does
And that is expressing
He's a victim
I don't want to have America won big
Free speech
Authoritarian kontrolfreek pedophile Berkeley
Really are
A bunch of demons
You should
Take the pigs are political solution
The spiritual solution
How many really are just dealing
What a bunch of
Demon possessed
Mother and father
In order to
Present
Things that are unpresentable
In order to normalize thing
That other
Arrows
Beam
Abhorrent
Generally speaking you need to prevent it from a place of
Aggrievance
You need to be presented from a place of
We are the one
Who have been so nice all along
You've taken our kindness for weakness
And you are the crazy one we are just trying to return things to normal from your craziness
These are marginalized people
We let these juice into Ark
Haha
Well
And some of our people aren't doing well so clearly it's the juices
And then we tolerated them for so long and then they just
Book and took from us
And you know we can't let this happen anymore. We need to remember that we are a nation
Without
Juice
That is why o.j. is in prison once more
Only tea in the morning 7
Yeah it always works whenever you
It sucks
Everything
Because
Because his his
Tiger underpinning to all of this s***
Is everything we're doing
Weird sayings
And then we're saying that
The doing is this up there doing
What it is they say even though they're not
Because they're doing it even though they're not that gives us carte blanche to do whatever we want because they're already doing
It's a gordian knot of blame
That is just so stupid
The function of legitimately is to present the idea
And not only that
Demon
No not even would you break it down
The people on the other side
Dumb demon-possessed weirdos
Zombies walking around
The problem that I have here
Is it we need to really look at what he's talking about
You put up with this like we leave
We've appeased and appeased and appease
The things that he's talking about are things like
Gay people being allowed to
Things
Things like
Non-discrimination laws we let you do it
Things like women having access to appropriate Healthcare that won't kill them
Are tongues and then whatever those are they allowed anymore I don't
Things
Like
Minorities being able to speak up about
The situation
Beady abuses that they may run into from authority figures things like that
Why we wrote the Constitution
From the very beginning
It's um
It's tough for me to hear this from Alex
Disposition of victimhood when all of the things that
Complains about
AR
Were they gone would return to victimizing every
It just
It's a it's a real bummer
Thanks so much about
Unfortunately
What did Louis
DK's earlier
Off of
Where he was just talkin
Think about how
Every year White
People add a hug
100 years
Between when
Slavery happened
Slavery is the worst thing that ever happened to Black
Like that
Like that is the world these guys are living in
Taking our slaves away made us the victim
It's the same thing
Hey I lost a lot of money
He's on 5th
Yourself
Good place really irresponsible
In his rhetoric in that last clip
Next
But I'll tell you this I really am most frustrating
We're all going to have to go through the pain is coming
When it could have been so easy to avoid all this
But I think my frustration is it clear
The world has cancer it's called the left
And they're not going to go away without fight
They take our morality of our kindness as weakness
And
The frustration is crushing them show me one f******
Reporting Act of kindness
Crush
Tri-State weathershield they are trying to sense the broadcaster whatever you do
I'm sure the One X
I would like one act of kindness
How many years
Give me one of these marginalized
Give me one at
What you say to yourself wow
You know for all the terrible things that the right-wing is done at the very least this one time they were kind
There's got to be something but I got nothing
They're doing everything that he is saying that the left
Is doing and even then
Even then
With him saying that we're doing all of that stuff and then describing us as monsters
Who are a Cancer
Never heard that one before
I'm not saying that you guys aren't people even though you're doing all of them
Nazis are still human being
Yeah yeah
You know that
The people are not their government people are not their leaders
Unfortunately
Trump is such a
Monstrous Recreation of the
Idiocracy
People are going to flock to him whenever they get the chance
Look at this was f******
G.w. running again
There wouldn't be these stupid f******
There wouldn't be this f******
Like
Tapping into this
Destroy what you don't understand
Because
Active heart rate
Because at the heart of it was a cruel cruel person
But you didn't relish the
The cruelty public
Allow
Sans I guess because what is it
No they didn't allow the fans
To get in on the
The cruelty and really bathe in it
And make it their own and
Feel like yeah this is ours
Feel like George W bush
The s*** out of countries he could start a war on false pretenses
Supercruise
Super cruel even then
The best thing to do for them weird liberator
We're going to win the hearts and minds and all of that
Where can I bring
Freedom to them
And he probably
Where to kill all the
Those people destroy the Muslim world
After 9/11 if you was in every Muslim from the country
It almost certainly in the Middle East for something like that like indiscriminate
Select the idea of the different
Cruelties that you see between
Modern
Republican presidents
It is it is relevant
Let you know if this is something altogether different
A bit like
Decant
Left is a Cancer and must
Exercise the not going out with
The fight and they're soulless husk
And we all know you negotiate with cancer and destroys
Because you're so kind
8 I mean what you see here is
Some of the most
Dangerous
Rhetoric
This preparation ellinell like there's no reason to stay
You want your audience to be in a certain state of
Yeah you want them to
Tubi
The sort of people who will join the proud boys
In his
Tone of voice and all of that stuff
Is that
This is like him
Well aware that he
He's not going to
This is him knowing
My legacy is
Is done what I created is going to die out
And because that hurts
Me so much
I want
People to hurt other
If I am going to go down
Then you you're going to wish that you would never done this
Even a little bit later in this episode Alex
Express is that like
Kicked me off of Social Media stuff
The whole nine yards
I'm going to make them kick me off the internet of course I mean he's preparing his own martyr.
On the show trying to model himself off Colonel Travis
Write this.
Precise
Nonsense in order
Texas monthly
With one letter Colonel Travis created his own mythology and create
Yeah like that is
What Alex's is doing
Then a much uglier
Much much ugly
I don't know
Chips bad
Chick-fil-A
He wants to get into a little bit of
Comedy
What
Not good
We have different views on it
Well ladies and gentlemen
Wesner's viewers
Import family
Ears
N-word
I'm President Trump
World exclusive right now
We have the video not just the audio cuz you know they can
Fake audio
Videos of the heart
We have the world exclusive
It's it's it's it's where they
Spell it
That
Give me the video of the Trump use the n-word
Keep selling your earlier Alex is like
Take me to contacts when I say that I'm thrilled to Trump's at the Edwards
Jesus so desperately like please someone clip this so I can make fun of you
Yeah just someone don't get
Someone missed the contact yet
I miss you I miss you too
Tell people how you William so they remember man relevance
It is kind of fun
Whether he knows it or not
Immediately tired
The word Nationalist and the n word
Together I think most people don't know
Kind of figure it out
They kind of handpan
Yeah
So
Trump's rally likely mention it
The beginning of the show
He's a nationalist
We should all say National
Really which is fine
Like I said
In a healthy political climate
The idea of someone having
Preference towards nationalistic policies
Is not
Most unhealthy thing we call them protection
Inner balance
Protectionist policies
There is no doubt about that
But
It's not what
That's not what that's not what this means in the political climate they were in right now
We are in
Situation
Where
We have
Nationalist
Uprising
Throughout Europe
Alder parts
To the world
That are all mysteriously
Pretty fascist
And all seem to
Future people that like to hang out with Steve Bannon
I like to hang out Monday
People who
Don't
Have
The people's best interests
It does seem that way
Alex
You want to talk about this so we might as well bring it out
Fascism
Is
Primarily characterized by hyperness
That's one of the primary drivers of
Fashion
When you look historically at the leaders we've been able to Institute
Successful fascist
Installations
Are you looking
Used
Rhetoric that
Mirrored populist ideals
And stressed nationalism
Insane
People like Hitler Mussolini
Great
Examples
Of this throughout
Throughout history
Traditional
Everyone your enemies are not them
And then when you also add in
Features of
The great teacher
The Great
Along with a picture versus them there's always sort of
Distrust
Other
You know just the idea of like we are a great nation we should be
Be greater
There's that
And then there he's all others are weird
And don't trust them
So when we see
Trump coming out at this rally and being like
I'm a nationalist
Nationals
Yeah and at the same time we have
All the other invitations
We see him calling these the refugees
Better
When you see stuff like that when you see him threatening to take away the legal definition
You see the exact
Tactics that are used by people who are trying to
And maybe fascist isn't the right way to go about it
Because there's a lot of
There's a lot of connection to
The government itself
Potassium
More interested in himself
The only thing that they've this ultimately from
Descending into a fascist
Authoritarian maybe the best
Better Label
But when you see him coming out and saying I'm not a globalist I'm intentionalist you unpack
Bit of the language
What you're seeing is
Cheers
Maybe some of them were cheering for the idea of like
You know
Make America great again
USA USA
But others are cheering for something else
It's the way I think I would put it a little bit differently from
From the
More specifically it's not that they want to just
America
America great
It's what they want to make America great Earth than
Whatever
You are
And if that means that we destroy all of yours
What are still comes out a little bit better
It doesn't matter if we destroyed our only
Yours are worse
So we're still great
I guess here's here's what I would say
Alex is right
Maybe this ultimately is the most important election
In American history
Because maybe this election
Everybody's fine
The f****** picture
And everybody does what the Republicans don't want you to do as you can see my house
Restricted they're trying to be towards voting right then
Maybe this is the last election we can actually solve
Refusing to Mom
Because after
After that if they're still in power for the next couple of years
Even more horrible s*** and then
Democratic solution
Because at a certain point democracy lost
Even in your
Scenario
Even then you still going to have to deal with
It's going to happen
Excited
As it were
And they're not going to organize
Like the Democratic Socialist Flipside going door-to-door knocking
In order to help push rent control kicked out of there
They're not going to organize in productive ways
In terms of helping
People they're going to organize the way Alex would like
Militia
Or the way Gavin McGinnis would like
Into into
Street mob
And that is going to be no matter what
Need to be addressed
Because
They've been given this
Taste of Haiti
Right
If it's no longer in Vogue
That's another thing on their
You took away
Means
To cause real harm
Already are the end result result behavior is already
Certification will be along the way yet to be determined
Alex is going to
To be a f****** monster and get people hurt
It's just going to
To be whether or not
His guys in power
And he has that narratives or his guy is out of power in ESO
Doesn't really matter
Point
We get to
It's a little bit longer
But
On this episode
Again
The day after someone left a bomb in George soros's mailbox
False flag
Probably
Does mentioned
Like when he's talking about the refugee Caravan
He does mention sora's probably time for that sort of thing
He does mention him offhandedly a couple time
But this next clip
My heart started
Fluttering
Like I got that kind of anxiety flutter
Big understand when you hear what he says
But
It needs to be said
Did there is no universe
No possible universe that I believe exist
And I believe in the Multiverse
Possibility
Literally every single one of them
Alex Jones knows that someone left a bomb in George soros's mailed
There is no chance
But he was unaware of that
There is no way
But he doesn't know that
And that is
Something that he's aware of
When he says the words that he's about to say
I'm on fire defy
Where are your instance where is your common sense
Is Hardcore I'm not talking to you
Michelle Austin establishment
But it's a spiritual thing
And
Misery loves company
We have to stop going along with
And their minions.
They're a bunch of bull
Ono
Program
Relaunch
Like we're deaf
Because the damn we are death
George Soros and Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama and Rothschild
Reaper
Come to their door
Death of their system
Good save
Really just love life but she does because
Shut off our Unborn
It's on our families in two-faced everything
Literally alive and they're psychotic
Because they're possessed
And if you don't stand for The Unborn
You stand before God God will say
I know you not
And you are of the devil
From which You Came Forever
You are not
Amongst
You belong to death Journal
Bunch of trump clips
Plate
Forget
That if you don't support this broadcast will be shut down and we make it easy with the very best products
No one
Clip is perhaps
The poorest taste
Imagining
The idea that like
I think he saved himself a little bit from
Babylist
Real real trouble by thing
Adestrador system
Because the day after someone leaves a bomb in George Soros your main enemies mailbox
It's probably not wise
Come on Aaron's day
George Soros
I'm the Grim Reaper come to your door
I'm deaf
I'm death
That seems really really f***** up
The phrase that got me though
Before that
Now they know
Because I hear that
Can I hear him
Responsible
Now you know that I'm the Grim Reaper
Now you know I can
I mean it's certainly the timeline for everything now you know
Makes a lot more sense than it being like you got Trump elected
Cuz I was almost two years
PID
Was much less
Jarring
To me then
I am death I am death
Yeah but I mean
He's always
He's always saying that better their evil and if you're if you
It's weirdly that they make right with God because if you don't bomb George Soros
God is going to hate
Or whatever the frame
But the now they know
Hit so hard because
Like you said
There is no universe
He doesn't know
There's no University
We didn't call him immediately
City of God damn word about Sorel tomorrow
Kula Kula.
Don't kill him if he's like listen
I know I had Buckley call you
And I feel like
That wasn't enough
At the head
Listen to reason you don't listen to words
Call his dad
That's terrible
No that's
Is unconscionably dangerous
I think that might actually be
I don't think it's a crime man it's it's real bad because it's relishing in the attempted murder of Sue
The obvious response was gesture their system
Waterfall Dallas
You very clearly an afterthought
We should kill them politically
I'm sorta bush
I'm deal what you're saying and you know what people work here
This to me is really f***** up and
F***** up without the app
Killing our kids
What's that a reference to
Part of your narrative other than pizzagate
Clearly
Something that you pulling from in his memory back
In order to make this
Daredevil to want to kill your kid riff work
Doesn't have
The gnomes are coming that he needs and Ivy pulls satanic basement
That's also f***** up I don't know man
Van Heusen
Sure years later it comes up whenever he's talking about
The guy who just got a bomb put
F****** mailbox
Mailbox
Who Alex said was behind pizzagate
The puppet
So I mean what we have here is like
I expected
Bully 2
Have the show Oprah
Without
No-one to put a bomb in George Soros the mailbox
Never said that to be as angle
It'd be like
Blame it on us
It's going to be the next thing you know it's going to be Alex Jones made someone bomb Georgia
Already got the predictive programming
I thought that would be what he says
The fact that he never addresses directly
The fact that Torres had a bomb putting
And says
I'm the Grim Reaper coming to soros's door I am death
I am dad
It made me feel
So sick to my stomach
Because like I said
Last night
The experience of watching
Trump rally
And then afterwards the news
Throws bomb
How does visceral response
So then the two missing at the Alex
Wallowing around it like a pig in s***
It made me feel like
I guess the only way I described it is
When
Do you know
Saudi Arabia has clearly murdered a journalist
You know
And
Then Trump goes on air I did one of his rallies and talks about
That I got from Montana body-slamming a journalist
Talk about how it's great
When you have something like that you have something
Two things
Connected
There's no way they're not connected
But they're so inappropriate
And they show
Such a deep latch
If you manatee
I'm such a deep lack of
Anything
Resemblance
Babe
Eat it
It's so scary
Furiated
It will never not be infuriating to know
But the Koch brothers
Truly behind
The complete destruction of Democracy in America
Not Justa
And their Network the guy to report more money into this
Anybody else
Nobody on our things
Nobody's ever done that
People's lives
Insider trading in the 80s
That's that's these people man
And they're just
F****** thing that that's it
Are we are we all just going to die knowing that we're better people than the people that are murdering us
This is the struggle
I don't know
Hearthstone
Furiated it is you feel like
Like they're gaslighting
You start to feel like you're going
There's no reality anymore
That's what I'm saying that's what I'm talking about when I was saying I feel crazy
Where am I
I don't know how you get to
Present yourself as like the good
People
And the victims
And all that
You relishing and
Short of breath
Put a bomb
Somebody's mailbox
Your team
Murdered a woman at a
Owner of
And every excuse to be anti-Semitic
An antenna islamophobe
When your team is
Incarcerating children
Keeping any records
Is it not even trying to fulfill the court-ordered of putting the family back together
Your team is the victim
And your team is even
Encroaching on its own ideology
Those things
Because they make up
Philosophy is
There is no there is no
Nothing to The Republic there's nothing now but
It doesn't
It does feel like that is what's driving
I told you I couldn't sleep last night
Things that I decided to spend my time doing
Was
Play little Candy Crush
Good luck and then I decided I'm not going to get to sleep
I decided to look into and make sure I understood all of the accusations
Against George Soros
The people like Alex Jones
He's elk make
And it led me to watching a bunch of you
YouTube videos that are released
A lot of them are clearly Alex Jones
Rip off
No not use on their videos but are doing like an impression
Embarrassing to watch
You understand the reason
He's f****** talented like you had
Doesn't
Miss beat user
I can deliver as line
Yeah it's
Versions of Alex
This is disgusting that there are
A lot of them we've covered on the show already
Many of them
Never
If anybody wants to come at
And talk about sora's
I will smack down anybody
About it
Maybe this publicly
But anybody who has these
Sort of ideas
About George Soros
I can
And then explain to you
How's the beliefs that you have that is wrong
And not based in reality
It actually ties back to anti-semitic propaganda
So I was going to lay that all out on the show sometime
For that other stuff is just
And little
Straight
Accusations that were made by likely
Lyndon larouche
Of the world
There's nothing like I said
It wasn't really that big of a deal and he gave him
Money back and
And it's debatable whether he actually acted
With
Whatever
You want to take all weekend we can stipulate that one
Billionaires
So anyway
That that that
The most unpleasant part of this episode and like I told you
Since we've made it through
We now get to have something
And that is what Alex Jones is
Okay yeah the guy named Ricky Berwick
He's a guy who makes
YouTube videos
Little short YouTube videos
I don't hate the hustle
There were three or four
But I suspect that there's only one video of his metallics have ever seen
Needs to shut up
Expert analysis
Decided
Disgaea
So he's a special guest interview at this does not
Goes away
How would you describe yourself
Free speech
I like names
Like
We're all having fun
NSYNC
Purge of free speech
Social Jess
Fastest way home
A lot of them recently
A lot of people
Liara
We are sick
You notice those jumps
What happen if you keep swearing
Catholic
Hopefully got it it
We're on our way
Nan Kings English me a big favor
So in the middle of their conversation about free speech
English
I know that there's differences between swearing and like breaking SEC violations in different countries
I just think there's a certain
Siematic irony
Kind of reveal
Alex
You are right I think we should do that you are right and you are an interesting fella
BBW does not go how Alex wanted to as we've already seen
Don't stop swearing
That is
You're not having fun and I've also been kicked off most parsley
Hey man seems to be Ricky's whole thing he seems to be having a blast
Like it's not for me
I get to the lotto
Alex
His Realty
I want to be heard In that clip that
Ricky is super into
Alien guy
No Alex is super into this end
Turn on playable character meme at the moment
I'm so so good about it
He does not care
What do you think of impeach
Rachel it's a great meme
What do you think is going to go then
I think it's going to die like a man
Hahaha
I have rarely heard through people
Have such bad chemistry and it's one person's fault and ethos
Saddest sentence I think I've ever heard Alexei
Some people call me the
The Eternal mean
NPC meme
Ricky is like
People aren't like that very much against them
Because it's commercial
Ricki Lake
I just figured
Annoys people
Rosewood
We're running against
Because the Fabian socialist told us to use emojis
War with them with me
Fabian socialist
Again
I got nothing but respect for
So at this point Alex spot something in the camera shot
Everything was going so badly
But you hear the positive
They're not connected in any way
To try and like
Talk about
Piggy bank
What's what's his name
Quest.
You have the hammer a lot
Gorilla
The reason that I'm
People
Like what I do
You can ask about that if you want the stupid I got over here
That is desperate
What
Oh that's a
He asked about the hammer
But
54 absolutely
The the hound dog come back on
And even further than we all know that he's a dog
He can't resist killing it
This is what happens next
Why are you so
In love with my hair
I want you to kill it
You want okay okay
What
I like dogs but you know what that one that looks like
Where's Knox
I want you to
I want you to kill it
You want me to kill it
I was just joking
This is f***** up yeah I mean you don't really need
Shut the f****** conversation
It's a f*****-up way for it to go super weird for him to just
Obsessively want dogs dad whether real or fake dogs
Seems to be so consistent in his character
Even his jokes are like
Hahaha murder
Right right right
Joke
Cirrhosis
Responsible for him to even be like
That look dog
Yeah it's not
This is
Foremost
Public discourse
Was an attempt at comedy
It was
He thought he was doing some real fun
So he's got this memory in there Getzlaf
Cuz if he does have some shots as you can tell the timing is pretty
It's no like using tag team this thing
That was the result
It was the result
You want me to grab my
Kill the dog
We shouldn't allow people with right-wing
Because it only makes them a
Angrier and more prone to
It's for their own good
Department
Alex's dad
But don't think that's a good idea
There needs to be somebody already has a bit
There needs to be some sort of body in place
Hey man a note
Got to go we got to get ahead we got to get a union and are union rep would come in and be like hey dude no no no no
We want you to
There's
Just not enough
We've there's no more spots open
Ever
Trevor
Like a version of Alex Jones
Comedy
But
And our last question
Alex Jones discusses
Field comedy
But he did while he was out of the Trump rally
Monster
Oh I forget I forgot.
Hit it with a hammer
Monster
Who's like this station
Jobs dead
What do I have to do
Beto O'Rourke
Contacts cuz I know you're not on social media so you may not have seen
Is Alex
Standing over some dogs on the street
Or maybe horseshit I think he says it's horseshit
And yelling at this poop
If comedy alright
Mean it it would be comedy
Man
You just got to figure out how,
Video
The video that Alex put out
It just appears to be him yelling at
You on the ground but someone else
Was there and got it on their camera
Realized I got some level
You're doing this and Lexie
People are just watching you yell at
Hilarious
Do the poop
Supposed to be beta
Alright
You're supposed to make
Connection in your mind that Beto
The problem is Alex
Much like Dennis Miller is
Funny
Nickelback
Marco Rubio
What's his real name
Yelling it
Timbertop coming over like what in the hell
Where you go
That was it
Mexican Harvest pendejo that's the t-shirts
Did it smell
I didn't get to close
Listen to stupid
Talks to poop
Alex
Yeah
Do you just roll along with it
Response
Textures your B
Extend your bed
Hey many ideas I can punch it up
Are you saying like all the media is all saying that I talked to poo
You were
You did
Everyone knows that you were
Attempting a joke
They're just laughing at how bad it is
So Alex
Appreciate that you so incompetent when it comes to Comedy
Because it makes it a little more
Alex's Legacy Federal hamburger had no idea what
Search the s*** right there is
Malaria
I think the
Media is just not getting
Then I got to really go for
Your videos
Get it
Done
Right
Brings us to the end of this episode sink
I'm answering every time we do a Monster episode
I mean
So bad
Stupidness show is so bad
Every single time I listen
In the present
How bad this show is
How little it needs to exist
And
What do you mean how else would we have found out about that let's just show is vital
Irrelevant
If if
You if you didn't have Alex Jones
Just look at this show
Where would we be
Yeezys
The interview
Such a good interviewer
The show stick
Much like that horse manure the show stink
I believe he said that
Unreliable narrator
Beetroot
It's just as bad
It's terrible I think that his rhetoric
As it relates to
In particular
George Soros is
Just the definition of dangerous super irresponsible and the sort of thing they cannot like
It's
That sort of behavior
They're people like
2 years of my life
Dedicatedly
Studying Alex Jones
Almost a year now
Studying this guy that I hate
And if someone put a bomb in his mailbox
I would be nothing but sympathetic to him
I would think that was the worst thing
Ever
I would come on this show
I would talk about how awful that is
And how's that is not the way.
Things are done
It's not the way that we deal with these sorts of issues
I mean that in the sense of life
There's still time
There's still time for that not to be the
Tissues like that
Eventually you get to world war
This to happen I'm not right right right right
There's only one with negotiate a peace treaty with Germany running the world
Like we talked about at the top of
Episode
The parallels
To the rise of fascism
Are there
Strong and they are only getting
Stronger right
The way that we
Deal with it
Needs to be
Counter
To ever allowing it to get that far but I'm the way that you remember the
The urgency of it
Is you remember how
Historically
Quit it
The truth
That's what I figured I'm not thinking like
Now is the time we need to make sure we don't go
And if weird
If we're putting it off it's it's somewhere off in the distant future something
Like that you're not
Done
In a good way
Now
Because
If nobody does anything about it if we don't fight
If we don't make sure that this is
Carob
Will get
Is not negotiable thing that's not a
That's an exaggeration
So we may never get there but it's going to require work
George Soros open Society
Free societies
Require
They require
Generally exist
Without working
Driving
And I I I agree on that
On that end
But
I don't know all my point was
Was that
The person I hate the most in the world and I think is one of the most
Cancerous
Awful
Influences on people's lives
Sound
Disgusting rabbit holes
I would never treat him the way he
The high road
That is just me saying
I can't imagine anyone who would
Do act like that
I already said I would never want to be around them
I just hate this guy
This guy too
No
Do not
Yeah your combs
So anyway
Website.com
Facebook
Let's go check that out join the fun
Boruto episodes
Yes you can unsubscribe
Presents
I don't want to do this again for a while I'd like to be in the past
But just needed to be talked about and now it's done
And I'd like to say from the bottom of my heart
I mean this sincerely
Whoever left that bomb is George soros's house I'm glad
I know one guy who probably technically
NFL
Alexandra Thurston color