Alexandra Thurston color
Look up a little bit by Alex Jones
The f*** is going on
I can't answer that question that's sad interview questions
Star last episode
I don't feel good about it because we were operating under the contacts
Quit cuz when we recorded it
That the Roses mailbox
Was a isolated
I kind of was operating under that
Other than the fact of you and so
Posted that episode 130 or so on Tuesday night
Putting episode up
Went to bed woke up in the morning
Computer see how the world is doing
The first headliner
It's crazy because like on Monday
I'll get some sleeping
I sleep I wake up
In the past three days every time we have gone to sleep
I refuse to make that connection necessarily
Thrown around then the very Act
Sleep is causing
Recovering Alex Jones at the present
Because he's so full of s*** in the world is so crazy right now
The present are almost instantly data
They're almost
Instantly but don't have the full picture just by virtue of
How everything changes on a diamond
I don't
You know I see all these other people
Bob
The people
It's still all people that screams about all of the time
I don't unique
These are all people that Alex yells about because the right-wing world has
Become so Alex defied
So who don't spot
That
Who's going to let that
I was intentionally did that while you're taking a step
It's become so much that
Become such a blur as to like
What could motivate
To the point where honestly
The only way I would be
Convinced that this is Alex Jones motivated
Not prompt Tucker Carlson all that
Just be whole world of the right motivated
As if Brian stelter got
Alex is probably the only person she'll there all the time
Control group
Situation
Scorsese
See
Wildwood DeNiro get
Obama along with everybody else
I'll tell you why this whole thing is just a mask
That Scorsese is pissed off
The DeNiro spent those twenty years in the wilderness
Klumps movie
Meet the Fockers
Look Who's Talking Now
DeNiro
Is our new donors
Thank you
We appreciate those are very much first of all
Thank you so much for becoming a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Bless your job
Also would like to say thank you to somebody who came in a little bit of a higher level
I appreciate it also very much
Reverse
You are now at
Technocrat
Dogs get mad and tell her you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
You're Oliver
Thank you very much Oliver
So much I knew you like to meet
We will have our breakdown coming up in the near future
I realize I looked at the vote totals there's no way for me to justify
The will of the people is The Obama Deception
Coming up
And also there's a
The time of our website content that will be coming up
We reach that next goal
That is
Driving me crazy
But
For now
I'm at the top of the show
That we didn't have all the information at our disposal
When we did our last episode
And unfortunately I thought well the only responsible thing
To do is now that there's more of the story available as much as its
Talk about a present-day episode
I feel like it's our responsibility to jump in
And do another present day episode
To go over what Alex Jones is talking about now
Could be the October 24th episode 200 from Wednesday
In this first clip we're going to be listening to hear Alex is talking to Owen Shroyer
About the situation
What is unfolded all around
Did you sweep of other houses
Those for March 12th of this year during the Austin
Totally mixed up.
Actually the first clip
Erica
Propaganda
People in Congress
Michaels
Talk show host
I'm sorry I f***** up again that was from April 20th 2010
Now that's two in a row
And
Coincidence
I need three to form a pattern and then I will know whether or not this is going in a Direction
Honestly it was my intention to just do that the entire episode
Like that would be a way that we could Escape actually talking about the present but I'm horny
My archives of Clips are much more difficult to go through then I would like to
You like to think
Two that I pulled their to demonstrate like alright
Whatever you talk about bomb goes the same way
I always fall swag stuff
I don't know if I can
I don't know
From October 4th 2018
And it's a little bit of a pre-taped thing
With Rodger Stone
And you'll see you'll see the vibe
He's putting out here
Say something
Rodger Stone
Emperors
We do not want any violence
Bryant
Emergency
Please play
Alex
Against the media or anyone else
Or any
Reporter
It is not
False flag
With the goal
A blaming alley
I think we just did
Mission accomplished raise at banner up we did it
Cuz you can hear about Rodger stone that he's like a little bit more using legal language
Be a little bit of the mind of legal action characters living or dead
Play called for violin
The specific people who were bombed
Represent Alex Jones or Rodger Stone despite the fact
Countless
Numbers of times
Called for direct violence
Political violence he never has that always been
January 5th 2018
Disingenuous
Perpetrator
He will.
Scalp
Senior Living
Understand that
Skelter
Advocating violence
Demon and that means
Is that you was immoral
Send have
No choice
It's like in The Exorcist where the Exorcist
The demon was like
Call William
Peacefully
Of course that's a little vague and stuff like that but
Here's a clip from March 20th of this year
Judicial
So president to take covert action against his supposed enemies
I believe that
Legal for him to kill these
Come on
Fair enough
Alex's
I'm totally against violence and you can never save it
Encourage anything
Anybody who says I encourage violence
Fill your hand
I'll beat your ass
Play with Rodger clearly preemptive
Damage control
Because I think that they probably got the sense of like
We better put out where we literally say if somebody.
They should really have opened every show with that videos
It's really fun here is that in that clip
You forgot
Cut out of it
Showers
Why did you keep that in
Why didn't you cut that out
He said move
Alex
You got it you got to come up with more than two
Yeah I got to work a little harder on that day
You chicken
Right
What
How would you how would you spell literally
Is there anybody
Decry
You bet
And that is not
I'll miss you talking about stuff
Actually I'm Studio not in the
Broadcasting worldwide
2019 historical action
Obama
CNN evacuated George Soros
Right on time so they can play the victim
The ground
50000 people
From usaid
The George Soros doesn't pay for it
The US taxpayer through the UN
Is that wood donations run the operation
And there they are
Dislike
We predicted to slam into the Border
2 days before the election
They'll be more than 200,000 people
50000 now
The other day was around there
I've made this point
Alex
Everything is an exaggeration
But it's exactly what I expected
Define. Tuesdays show
Until Wednesday
To come out with this narrative
Because if the obvious narrative
It's his knee jerk reaction is already rolling on Tuesday
The false flag I bet you
Next are going to say that it was Clinton
Threatened
But instead
I don't know what it is like
I know that on the last episode I said that there's no Universe I believe exists that Alex
Didn't know about Soros getting a bomb made me not know I wonder if maybe
I think it might be possible
Wednesday instead of Tuesday
That makes no sense
No-shows are heavily scripted
They do dress rehearsal breakfast
Is that the case
Professional
Who did all the block
I don't care about breaking news
Absolutely
Worldwide I am your host Alex Jones
413 days out from the midterm elections and all hell is breaking loose
Obviously
Coming up
Dozens and dozens of clips
Imma show you the news articles for yourself here in a moment
Precisely
They are preparing the public
A conservative media
They are terrorists
Who are going to attack the media
University
Democratic
Jury's out on that one just say that collections are illegitimate and that we are going to
Cause all of this violence
I wouldn't say the last one
This is a situation where like you just get into this stupid game
I'm out
Because
What he's describing is the media covering
Trumps rhetoric
Alex is rhetoric
That they're saying
Hey you know History A lot of times people and demonize a certain population that populate
Ended up getting
For marginalized even further than they already were
Weather in this case journalist
You know when countries that have slipped away from democratic principles largely the first step down that road is
Demonizing the media
Throughout Eastern Europe and tons of countries the idea of
Free Press
Is one of the most dangerous things to our crew
So like when you have that
The media covers it in such a way that says hey
Really
Not good
And there's
Exact rate
The stimulus there's literally no difference
Between the reality of the media warning about something and Alex
They're trying to demonize
Did the middle like what make
What makes both sides do what they do is this
It's just that one sides
Defensive and full of s***
I was really nothing
You can do about that
There's nothing you can do about it
I was just be like how you're awesome
Here's the most
Obvious
Reason that these guys
No the rhetoric is Viola
Annie's
Causing
Violin
They are defending
Before we know anything about who sent
You texted me that and I thought that was like such a good distillation of this like all you need to know
They didn't even wait for a 5 Second
They might not be at fault for this one
They might be fun
But this might be a false flag
I think the odds
I agree minuscule but I would even
Trinkets
But the nature of whoever is doing this
Do right-wing media Outlet
Atolls
None of them are even saying
Hold on and find out
Who's done this before we
Terrorism admitting
Alex is responsible for this in a spiritual sense
No matter what they are
I still I still think that Alex
Has helped us get to
To the point in terms of the rhetoric
Acceptable
That sort of thing
B that weekend Where We Are
I didn't
I don't think it would be appropriate for us to be like this guy for sure
We can we can have
I would like
Looks like it
For that would be
Stupid
This affects the entire right-wing
Media sphere
People who were like
Formerly
Had the pretenses like I'm not Alex Jones people like Rush Limbaugh
None of them have even come out and been like
It could just be alone crazy
None of them have even given any other
Sabila
But I think you're I think you're totally right that does indicate
It's like we got to get
In front of this thing
Because otherwise when the truth comes out we're f***
And that's a strategy
How do you say I think a lot of
These people Hitler
For propaganda so that's not good
Now it is clear that the bombings
The attempted bombing
All of these Democrats
Robert De Niro
Debbie Wasserman Schultz
Yep you know it's just
It's balloon from where it was
Yeah and he said that it's it's fake
And it is clearly as I'm doing it to themselves because I need sympathy in the other midterms
And he's going
Be blamed for it
Bank line
Narrative
But in order to make his
He needs to link it to another bomb
Of recent day
And if this is this is a bad
Wards.com
Tours.com
Is that
A pipe bomb got mailed yesterday I'm very small little pipe
Another similar to CNN
Wanda Obama
And one of course to the clintons
We are in New York
Remember if you go back
About a month ago at gentleman was busted New York
Cooking up a
A true
Hundred
Spaceman
The bomb the Republicans to cancel the election
Inside
Washington Monument Mall
On the morning of election day
Try to cancel the election
Because the Republicans are going to try to steal the election
That doesn't make sense either crazy laptops
So that's really bad
And here's why
Alex is juxtaposing the stories of all of his enemies receiving mail bombs with a story about this guy out of New York
Building a 200 lb
He's doing
I'm claiming that the man was deranged left
Because doesn't know anything but
This false narrative serves his purposes
Resent the idea that the Soros Clinton Obama
False flag by the left
The problem is that Paul Rosen
Built that bomb was not elect
Nor is it any mystery as to what his intentions were in planning to blow up
He wasn't angry the Republicans is Alex's reporting
At least he was no more angry with
From the FBI press release
Quote in August and September 2018 Rosenfeld sent letters and text messages to an individual in Pennsylvania
These letters in text messages stated that Rosenfeld plan to build an explosive device and detonated on November 6th
2018 International ball
DC
Rosenfeld's
AB litical theories advocates for the random selection of government official
Alright
Val
Closer to you now interested
He's not like to build a bomb
To do this but I read some of his
It doesn't come off as crazy as a lot of the manifestos you end up repeating him
I have no idea about that
Seems like it'd be hard to build a home-brewed 200lb bomb that's big
It's hard to build a loaded in a van
Bacon
It's 200 lb
Let alone Obama
You know
Stuff
But I mean
The cake
I mean obviously
No no no more dangerous a lot of difficulties
Country was going in the wrong direction
The thing is he felt like that for a long time for Trump
He'd written blog posts years ago called things like the extinction of politic
And others
It was the only way to go
He opposed the Democratic process as a whole
Which is why you chose election Babe Ruth plant
He's going to kill himself with the bomb
Timer
These got hit that thing with a hammer
He broke the majority rule is monarchy
The constant political maneuvering of individuals and factions must inevitably winner-takes-all conclusion
Even today despite all our democratic
Pretensions of the US
One might easily imagine a scenario in which President Bush
Following an active nuclear terrorism suspends the electoral process
Under the pretext that terrorists have a
Infiltrated the Democratic Party
Perpetual Bush L via plausible outcome
Most people imagine a democracy and monarchy are different animals but they're actually cousin
You wrote that
Before it appeared the truck was going to be the next president
And Ducks out of the election
Did you mean
Okay
That sounds exactly like what Alex was saying about Jeb Bush in the 2016 election
Grammar in more developed ideas
Also sortation is a philosophy that is not largely associated with the left
They're far more
Do you know who it is
Who are generally now like
They like to hang out with libertarian
I mean like I'm not saying
Is it
Abate
Like sole possession of the right
Or anything like that it does happen heavy overlap with
People who are anarcho-capitalist to art
Liberal
Philosophy involved
Corrosion
Intentional erosion or getting rid of
The Democratic process
You're on a whole different Spectrum
A Venn diagram
What if
The short story The Lottery button
Instead of getting killed they become leader
Republican
That's why he was going to blow up a National Mall is
He doesn't know anything about the story but he needs to connect
To his other story idea that all of these bombs are clearly
Some sort of a democratic false flag
Doesn't matter if it's true or not
That's care about like it
If you if you want
Represent the idea that all
All these are false Flags
You shouldn't
Bring up a story to reinforce that belief
Vegeta
Know anything about a dozen
I wanted to do better is what I'm saying disappointing
It's 8
Always
It's always
What bombings are false flags and what bombings are not
A little bit a little bit later
Seems like
Statistically
You're right wing bombers can't
Don't tell Alex
YouTube video of left-wing bombers that were false
By the right I still be like
Like for real left-wing
Mercer
I promise you will get into bombing
Statistics here in a little bit
Alex had to take umbrage with the media
For painting him in an unfair light
Let's go back now
Adjust a few
Weeks ago and a few months ago here's two weeks ago
First person
Terrorist
Acquired
Article a v
So I found that article
The headline is actually the information
Plural
Mike cernovich all those especially
Confirmation process Article 4
If it doesn't have anything
Technology
Information terrorism is not a term I apply lightly
Terrorism is the unlawful use of violence and intimidation
Especially against civilians in the pursuit of political aims
Refute
More apt to describe what this group is Unleashed against their fellow America
Alex has
Brass balls
Complaining about why you're calling him an information terrorist
What is website is called Infowars
So
Information Wars use the definitions of all words
Determine what they mean
Ergo Heathen information because in the information
Intentionally political result
ARS now
Discuss this idea of information
It's an interesting concept but
I don't know I don't know how full it is because
Part of the article
Terrorism is defined as the unlawful
And if you are using that is your definition of terrorism
Spell legal most
Of the things I like
Texas doing
Particularly distasteful awesome doesn't fall under
Illegal
Maybe that's a minor squabble if you wanted to argue
You why this article is unfair
And also it is nowhere
Scroll down like four times board
He gets to the picture of himself as I was getting good
No more pictures
Nerd
So now all of the right-wing media
Is united in calling the
Little all but all the
Most
If we apply this to
I don't know
This would be very similar
You all of the
Mustang Las Vegas
False flag
Sandy Hook was a false
Cosplay
Heather Harris death
All of these things
Is it
Legally action
If it's legally UK
Conseil
We're going to sue Alec
What's Jones
For calling
Sandy Hook a false flag
I think that the only people who would have liked standing are the people who receive the bombs
I think that they have better thing
Things to do
I really don't if it means they can take down is not a lie
Alex Jones the target is
Fox News
Do you have to you have to realize like how big of a court case that would be that would be the next 10 years
What else you want that to be I don't think he wants it to be
Worst Outlet in American history now we see it that way
One of them
Barack Obama
I think I think a lot of them know that
Airbnb such an uphill battle you don't end up having to end up redefining so many
About
Except if you are one of those
Cuz I'm broke but sure other reasons probably
I think it'll be a real headache
Alex's reinforces the idea that this is a big old.
Rocket science
That when they start
He said that on 60 Minutes
Yes you didn't you didn't say it clearly
When are the ones calling for violence against him
So you know you have a lot of the last carries out violence
Against
Folks
100 100
It's a little bit and I'm going to redo this year
Of the global terrorism database by researchers at the University of Maryland published
In 2070
Increase
In the sheriff attacked by right-wing extremist
From 6% in the 2000
35% of 2010
Hard to imagine what's cause that
35% it went
Of all domestic terrorist act are done
Spell electoral
What is a scientific study
I'm assuming
To be 3500
Meanwhile the sheriff attacked by left
Strop from 6
Percent in the 2,000
To 12%
Emma 2010
A lot of that is because of
Like the 64%
Is a lot of Eco terrorism
Animal rights
2016 2016
That's so they wanted to look into it a little bit further
Buy quarts of the same Global terrorism database
That the trend persisted in 2017
We're both attacks in the US were committed by right-wing it's
Out of 65 incidents that you're 37 were tied to racist anti-muslim
Homophobic anti-semitic fascist
Anti-government Rosina phobic motivation
In that same set of data
Explaining actors
6511 we're less leading actor
And a closer review the data shows that six of these left-leaning Terror attacks were done by animal liberation
So that leaves five
And then there's also Environmental
Almost
Nothing
BioLife
Is a very narrow
Picture of
The court as opposed to the
Rampant
Spraying
Coronavirus
Terrorism
Right right
Because we're
Dealing with a person leaving Bombs all over
The place and Alex
Defensive about it and talking about how
It like that
I feel like
It's important to
The only way for the right wing
To discuss this element
All the terrorism
Is being done by their side is false flag
There's literally no other way to avoid looking in the mirror and realizing
The statistics
Terrifying
Globally the number of terrorist attacks
Has been on a decline
Since 2014
17 thousand or so attacks
In 2014
As compared to 11,000 or so in 2017
Is a drop-off going this very
Considerable but in this country that trend has reversed
In 2015 there were less
In 2016 and 2017
A win trumps rhetoric has shifted the Overton
What sort of things are acceptable public speech
We see that number dropped to 64 and 60
55in those years
The world is going down
VCR is going
Way up
And the share of them
Being right-wing extremist going
Way up
So I mean to talk about this isn't true and that
Or else
You have to wrestle with the idea that like
Maybe we're doing this
Maybe this is something that we are responsible
Do that
If Alex
And Fox News and
If they ever actually
Maybe what we're doing
Is
Violence
Right isn't that
Like the biggest problem they have is not
Are we are we
Causing the needless deaths
AIDS
Look at how popular we are now that we're calling 45
It has a lot of ass covering there's a lot of like this is what we do is win
Is my job
I mean it's
The digits dehumanization on a mass scale
Cuz I made you look at you look at the numbers
Not all those attacks
Fatal
Anything like that
Good but there are numbers that are
And
When you look at that and you realize the human toll
Numbers represent
And you realize like oh
Huh
Maybe
Public
Good stop but
Dollars
In the place
Because
This is something
Sing that
Imagine that
Every like
Human Fox
Employee
On a daily base
I'm part of
Yeah I wonder how many of those are left
I don't know
Keep working
I make enough money
Surviving
Lined up
I might go broke
Probably a moral imperative not to work
Fox News
That stuff I don't know
I don't know I don't know how that would work
Sure
Have been saying that like I've been predicting this
Has has been touting
Tons of proof
Times articles
To make his own proof
Show
Platform
Perfect Storm
To demonize conservative
It's also Perfect Storm
For conservatives to bomb people
Elections bigger than 11
Three blind on Trump and Alex
Call Joan
Emergency
Big check to steal election
About to be
Watch
August 16th
Alex Jones
False
August 17th
Alex Jones warns Applebaum Federal Building
And here we are two months later I told you I got tribe
Emergency reporting
Softball Flags
Two weeks before election
Call specifically
Two weeks before launch
The mom Multiplex
Do you have a clip 3 predicted the summer of Rage predicted that the dollar was about to be
Completely devalued never once
If you stay things repeatedly and keep
Varying up what you're predicting eventually something you're going to have a clip free like
But I also guarantee that is equipped
Almost before the election I guarantee there's another clip
The day off
There's a false flag coming now 2015
The further thing that's really important is all those headlines
This is improving anything except that he keeps saying
None of it depicts reality at all
None of it
At no point in
Does he actually
Reprove
In any way that the media is
Keep saying it and then uses those articles that he and his
Himself produced
As evidence
But I got it right I got it right because this happened
So
That he likes to try and present
The argument that he tries to make about this
Is the
He's able to make these
Throughout August
And all this
Is because
It's like when you see
Commercials for the McRib
You know that the McRib is coming back okay but the commercials are telling you that the McRib is coming back
Right David his rhetoric is dangerous
And that means to him
I know that that means they're going to false-flag themselves
To blame me
So he writes all these articles
And then attack happened
Bring
Sooner or later just called is going to get the end-of-the-world right
In this case
His version of it is this idea of like advertised
It's like you know McDonald's wants
YouTube I this thing in the future so they prepare you to know that it's coming
Or whatever
And that's great
Great I'm not going to take away from his argument that's that's super
For fun
Rather related to it I like to talk about Alex's actions of the media
Personally I believe the media is
Pretty accurately warning people about the
Consequences
Of the human icing
And violent dangerous Reddit
So when I look at Alex's Behavior
The media is going to fall swag themselves
Writing article after article about it
It's less
In advertising
And what it is it's more like the PR department at a company that knows they're about to get caught for something
Yeah you know it's like we know we've been littering and polluting for a long time
What is about to put out a report about it
About how
The Watchdog group isn't
There are not credible
They are they have been taking money from interest
Take us down
Because then when that report comes out about the police that they were asked
You have that to fall back on
Groundwork has been laid before the story comes out and he be like
Oh no look we're not responding to this story
We're responding
Me too like we know that there
They're dirty
I said Dad
Who's like
Killed three people in the cops
But he's like a month out and
They're going to say a lot of bad thing
I mean I did kill those
But none of what they say
You're going to hear a lot of things
You don't believe
You don't believe anything anybody tells you but what Daddy
He says and daddy says
Wait whatever is my business murderer is dead either way that you want to go with
What does
Comes back to is exactly what you're saying
The beginning
That they know
The end result of their actions
As well
Make all of the post
I'm talking about the media's going to false flag themselves
If you didn't have a
Keen awareness
Trump saying the media is the enemy of the American people
Walter and talk about how he
Kill and rape your family
Natural end result of that
When unhinged person
Here's those sore
The Natural end result
Possibly
Someone hurting
This is preemptive damage
Control4
It is not
Addicted
It's not predict
Except
For the fact that he's predicting that this will
It is also
Something
I would say
Trying to make
Happened
Do the world like
Maybe maybe maybe maybe
Maybe I don't know I don't know about that I'm only
Hoping you a little bit because I think that's too
Too close to Alex's predictive programming ideas
He knows is that it is
I'm throwing in
Regardless you know it is it is damaged
Preemptive
But
At the same time
While he's writing those stories
There is
And I hope this happy
So I'm right
Yeah maybe
He's never happier
Then when he gets to say he's right
So probably psychological piece of it's like that
Probably doesn't care someone gets hurt to make
Especially
Rochester
That's our new shirt
Like
I think that we're kind of getting the idea here that
It's pretty easy to smell through what Alex
Cuz Rider Wrecker Service
You know it it's pretty easy and his next wife is even more over
Will be
He visited drudgereport
Tucker Carlson
He watched Fox News
You can you can see the scripting at boy we told you
Jonesy's
Why
Why he mailed the bombs are or his his somebody
Anxiety that's the right wing that Hillary
Soros and Obama are good guys that
Or just trying to
What about the news
Help America in
We've been resisting them and saying their globalists and self
We would say.
And so now
With the election 13 days away
You know they're planning
Now there can be the big event
The group or individuals
Lone Wolf
That's behind it
Properly blame
So
You see there that's
Next
Evening
Like puns and tons of things
I would say that I know that
This person
Four-person
Who's responsible
Was inspired by Tucker Carlson
Spiritually responsible isn't even the person was
Influence by Alex
Directly
All that because he needs to say all of that
In case any of those things
Is R-Truth
I told you beforehand that they were going to say
Also there's such a
Which is that like
Right wing
Soyboy
And the media is trying to portray them all
Good guys
It doesn't
Matter if they're good guy not at all
Nope
Yeah
You know like what can't you just start
You could just start
I don't even think
In listening to this episode that I heard him say it's bad
You know I
I didn't even realize that but
You're right. He doesn't think you the disclaimer but that doesn't
No
It's not on us not on us
Yeah
Is trying to play this game
They're trying to get to the
For themselves trying to make themselves seem like a victim
Demonizing
The false flag
You know you got this false wagon the next
Viola person that did it
Wyckoff
Bring out somebody
Wearing it
Lock her up shirt
We got a long history of posting on the internet about
Liberal
Scripted because
And it's a script
Always know that it's because it happens so frequently
To be scripted
Frequently like similar offenders
Similar psychological profiles and patterns
Statistics
Could not track call false flag
The nature of false-flag stuff
From the false flag accusation
They get mad when they get
I want things I realize there's a real General Trend among people
The claim that thing
That would tend to make them be seen in a realistic way
Are actually elaborate plots
Against them
And there's no better example of this.
Fallout that happened after the right rally in Charlottesville
Initially the hard-right media Figures were totally fine with the rally and supported
Extension
Gavin McGinnis had the organizer of the rally Jason Kessler on his show to promote
Alex was firmly in support of the rally
Absolutely
The reality of the worlds that they help
Facilitate became publicly visible
Nazis white supremacists and weird fascist
Were there uniforms unashamed in the light of day
Heartedly on Alex and Gavin McInnes his side
Then
Heather heyer got murder
Videos of a group of white men beating the s*** out of DeAndre Harris with metal pipes and boards
The obvious to anyone
Who is looking
The situation
Things didn't get better when it came out that the rally organizer Jason Kessler was
At least a second-degree member of McGinnis
Immediately McGinnis went to control mode
And it's becoming too proud boy meetings under false pretense
Tessler being a proud boy was a false flag to associate his definitely not white nationalist
With street gang style violence perpetrated by
Real lights National
Alex would do the same thing having Kessler on his show to try and get him
To confess that the whole set-up was actually a Democrat
It didn't work
The Kessler wasn't on the up-and-up with
The Patriot movement
Another brand of the Charlottesville tragedy a globalist fault
The appropriate response to a situation like the one in Charlottesville is deep reflection and empathy
Unfortunately for people like Alex and Kevin
And deep reflection leads people to realize that they are the
The problem so that.
Shot
Did any
Left-wing media say that it
It was a false flag
Perpetrated by
Didn't you see Rachel Maddow going out and screaming about the
It was awful
Did they interview that guy and say that he was actually a plant by the Republican
Interview I believe like the guy who committed the offence
His neighbor
And he said you know you
That sort of sex version of it
No
They didn't end up talking
The shooter
Ballpark
I am done being like
You're really working
Koch brothers trying to make liberals look bad
Anyway it's all it is interesting to me that I started to realize
But the Volkswagen accusation really only comes out
Being like 911
Text Jessica business
These days these days it comes out so much when it's like okay this
Can't be part of what people think about
Therefore is a false flag
Because if they believe this about us
We can't continue to operate the way we have
We will not be allowed to or will be so obvious
Monsters
That we have to deny the real
They reveal themselves
To be obvious
Monsters
No Doubt
About Tuesday's episode
We heard Alex saying that he is
Gesture George Soros
The Grim Reaper come to his door
Death
Which was
I'm starting when I woke up in the morning a little bit
I've been looking online.
He also named Lord Rothschild
Venus Fly under the radar
Because that would be like oh my God
Probably claiming that he was right about that too
No I am death I am death
Evan Felker
It was
It was relishing it too much in a way that would I think
I think he would have
Beetle that it would take away from his
Credibility maybe I don't know
This is crazy.
Are we hanging on to that clip baby
You think that
That one might be there for a while
On this episode
Wednesday episode
And now he's actually talking about the situation
Hitman he's still not being like a cool about to these people
Yorkillon infowars.com
She's worse than that
POTUS fascist dictator
Was that the headliner with the editorializing
A pipe bomb shows up at George Soros the Kingpin
Last night
The same headline
Holocaust Survivor
He survived the Nazi
The poor thing
Now he's facing pipe bombs
He worked for the Nazis and said it was the best
Timeless life
Nachos
I can't imagine
This level of being a shity
I get Alex needing to Kant
Saved Soros is a Nazi collaborator by taking that 60 minutes and other interviews that he's done
Completely wildly out of context
Like that
You got to do these things
Demonizing your philanthropist anime
Business business
Good strategy
I understand you got to say these sorts of things are false Flags is
Preemptive
Kontrolfreek
But I can't understand the level of
Combine the two
Like the day after
Because I'm some level Alex f****** knows this isn't a false flag
Well you know damn well these people's lives word at very least threat
You know whether or not the song
A terrorist
You know I don't know if you've ever had your life
Have you ever had someone say they were going to kill you
I have as well
Incredible
We're just like I'd like to f*** yourself
That's
But when I worked at a movie theater was a little bit younger it's some guy came in night
Kick him out cuz he was acting up like crazy
He said he was going to come back and kill me
And I knew he wasn't going
Unbelievable level
I had I like I was like I have to
I can't stay and do the rest of my shift
Pretty unlikely
And then I was like a peeking out my windows
Real number on me
Agreed to that one
That was when I was like 6
17 years old
And these are adults
Federer
Then I was at the time shows up where you are
Not going to not
Levi impression on you
So when Alex gets on air
Sores look like
Sweet little baby he's are not there yet collaborator
It good day
It
It's inhuman
It's
I'm feeling levels of tallus Cruelty
That
It's pretty pretty spry
I mean it's not but it's
It it feels
Real
Nasty
And I would
Broke so I was hooked
Insidesherpa
One night I
Got my ass
To the tune of like
102 huh
Said I was always
You never bring your own puke
Okay
So this dude I was like
I don't have this much money on me
I got to go to my
And he's like okay man that's fine but leave
You keep here
So I skipped out on
Because of course
Brightridge
Okay
Dishonorable
Brokeback
So then like
Maybe two years later
I wound up going back to the same place
The city where I was doing
Ever forever
And I was just walking by this
Pool table area
And this dude f****** was like
Cuz I recognize him
Immediately
Wait did you
I think I
No you
I was like now you can
And he's like can I see your ID
And then he went
Van life
F****** kill you
When you leave this
Sneaking out the back and telling one of the managers as like that guy
Immediately
The Ruff Life
I was living like Tom Cruise in the color
It's never not a good fit
Never appreciate
I know that Soros doesn't listen to
But the idea of being this cruel
To somebody who is just
Received a bomb
I find it
Deplorable
Quarterback
Jeremiah
LOL
Bombs are there
They're such
Victim
There are hundreds of Chase
Declassified false flag
It's the oldest trick in the book
TV shows like
The TV show
The oldest tricks in the book
The issue that I have is yet
There are false flags that have happened
Saying that
Doesn't prove that any individual thing is one
All of them
Cuz
Does exist
Doesn't mean all things are at
Right that is
Portable sink
And he doesn't go much further than that in terms of trying to
His arguments are essentially false flags do exist at the oldest trick in the book
Therefore this is a false flag
I saw it coming this based on all of these articles
That I wrote about this with a really just preemptive
Control cuz I know that someone's going to dragon attack him eventually and I don't want the Heat
That's all he's got that's all the other
It's
Super thin
Little bit about bombing
Because there's another talking point that Alex Jones
Doesn't bring off but I've seen posted a lot by
S*******
Twitter
About like of course it's fake and none of them went off
Of course
Obviously if there was a bombing
I need to address this because whether or not Alex brings it up and what we're covering I'm sure he'll bring it up eventually
Hot fire with the
The Twitter
This needs to be addressed
There are few super important points that you need to know about making bombs
1 super easy
They're very very regularly don't work
It's very
The process
Along with factors
Completely outside of the perpetrators control that they're nearly impossible to pull off
Since the 1970s there are virtually no left-wing bombings in the United
Well it's again
It just died
Specifically is not been the behavior of the left
Again if you exclude
Environmental terrorism
And animal rights
Which I don't believe or necessarily
Appropriate to fit under it
The umbrella of
Left-wing terrorism as Alex would like
I think that would be disingenuous
Healthcare
Right
Listen to an issue that nobody is talking
That would be the equivalent of terrorism
For Alex's lightweight error
You can find plenty of list of bombings and terrorist Acts
Some people who made their bombs wrong
So they didn't end up.
It speaks actually goes off
When someone plans
The bomb people
One of the very few large-scale bombings that were successful was the Boston bombing
Another was the string of bombings in New York and New Jersey between September 17th and 9th
Steam which left 35
The perpetrator said previously been arrested for stabbing his brother in the leg
After quote and another brother attempted to stop him from assaulting their mother and sister
Left-wing terrorist
He spent a few months in jail and later became radicalized by online Jihadi material
Which is been inspirational is planning
Isaiah
Some sort of violence against women
And online radicalization
Then we have the Austin situation
When was terrorized Austin for 19 days
Is done by a twenty-three-year-old man whose motivations are still not totally clear but absolutely not
It wasn't
Just motivated at all
And that was another one that Alex had
Respond and go back in
Those episode
On the list of 9/11
You'll find
You that are bombings of mosques and specifically targeting Muslim
One of them was a man in Spokane Luther King Day parade
What are the Target
Mexican consulate one of them was a bizarre omage to Fight Club
0 of them
I'm having carried out by left
The game with the exception of environmental extremist
An animal rights
Almost all modern bombing behavior is attributable to Isis related terrorism and far-right terrorism
Is just out the facts breakdown
But I think there's a more important thing that you
Overwhelming majority of bombing do not go as a bomber plant
It's incredibly hard to make bomb
Then it's even more difficult to deliver them where you want them to be
And make them detonate when you walk without someone finding them first
Exact this is why you see so many failed bomb plot through history and why we can so clearly remember the ones that
Completion cuz they're the exception to the rule and they're deeply emotionally scarring to ever
Hard to build a bomb
It's like not the way we do mass killings in America
You don't need to get in
Today in Estero
But yeah man it's it's one of those things
These things went off is
Foolish as an argument as in the reality of it
The number these people have Secret Service detail
Immediately
He has people
Working there and are going to find these things
And even though the ones that were left
People's offices
Security guard
Leave a bomb somewhere
Do you want it to explode
It's so hard for me
How to find
You get the timing right so it hurts
The person that you were very difficult meaning
More not that
One of the bombs went off
Yeah it's surprising more that not like one of the bombs went off
And just killed some
None of the people who
You got bombs wherever
Alien day
It was it's the people who work for
Which furthers your argument that it's more about a mess
Subs and everything else
We should know
That's out of media
Alex Jones preemptive
In order to do that
To blame him
Him and make him the pass
He knows that
Because
One of the anchors
What's the NM
Who is not name
Okay
Alex Jones
I'm really scared we should kill us with bombs
Dimension
I know I know it's terrible. We're not going to Banning
Information
You know when they're on every channel saying you're
It's something that's about to happen
You say they do all the time
Michelle's with bombs and guns
I think he realized envelope or something
Bryson
That their pricing is coming
Send it
I don't particularly care to parse through Lester Holt to take on Alex Jones's battlerite
Ashley was more on Alex's side about it and the context of it wasn't about an offensive sort of thing
That was sort of emails from listeners informant
Connotation
We may not understand the whole context as a non gun non-military serving
I don't know I can't speak to that
But I don't want to get mixed up too much
Not going to listen to others
Listen to their perspective
I don't I don't I don't really have a take on Lester Holt's comments
Right but what I can tell you is that Lester Holt's discussion of Alex Jones of comments came after a number thing
One of them was out getting on Aaron starting
We're going to pay people to go on live TV
Angelle CNN is Isis
It was a formal contest that Alex launch promising thousands of dollars to be
Quetta news networks with a terrorist organization
A little bit after that griesmer was arrested
January 9th and 10th
In which you made terrorist threats and talk s*** about the Jews and black people
In one call you said quote I'm coming to Gunn you all down I'm on my way right now to Gunn the f****** CNN cast down
I'm coming to kill you
He referred to them as fake news and dropped a couple n words for good measure
The president of this country previously called the fake news media the enemy of the people
He frequently attacked again and it rallies press
Prison on Twitter
It's no surprise that Lester Holt would take something appeared to be threats seriously
That's something that's happened
Quite a bit to him
Recently
Refusing to accept that sort of context just saying like
Nowhere
Get your battle rifles ready
ATMs
The weakest critique we can always have four houses
Being a little unfair
But it's a little unfair
Contact the things that
Okay before that
Because they make your argument look like s***
You could describe it as media script
Scrip
What's that
Right-wing media has written
They've written this whole they've created this
Whole situation
This is
To be a result scripting in that sense I think what you're talkin
About is inadvertent
Consequences it's not like at the end of it they know exactly what's going to happen
It's more like this
Created a
Sandbox
All of these
And the only logic
Cold
The sandbox
Is
So it is next with Alex brags about how insightful
We have to consider
But that lives in the atmosphere
Literally wrong about almost every
How you know when a new Coca-Cola flavors come out
Cuz you see Billboards everywhere
Ribbons
Play Alex Jones said blow up and shoot the media
Call the media
You are great
Because you see this as a giant
As opposed to seeing the trends
That have been pushed forward by your side
Worst part
Is
Essentially saying
It's okay
Oh no that's another thing that I was going to get into is that like what we're seeing is a normalization of bombing
We are seeing
Literally
In front of our eyes
Of domestic Terror
That is
So crazy
How evil is it for you to watch
People get
I didn't say
It's a false flag that they're purple
And that makes them
But let's imagine a scenario where I know that we're not that important so it doesn't really matter
That's how I would
Sure
I get killed in a bombing
Alex Jones
Knows that I demonize him all the
All the time from this show
So
It would be an easy argument to make
That like
Something like that
Well I mean
The only difference between that and what we're seeing now is I'm discussing a bomb
Did go off
Yeah if any of these let's say
Didn't go off
One of them getting killed Debbie Wasserman Schultz
Could he still make this argument
You Betty
You f****** and if you would do it with one of them going off
He do it with all of
Them going off
This is
Like I know that we
I've talked about 42 Pierce on this show all he does is normalize and
Violence
And pretended White
Violence and terrorism don't exist
But didn't level that he's going to
To hear
He's profoundly Danger
And what it implies for the future
Is
So f***** up
It's so scary
To hammer this point home
Years ago when we started this podcast
Right
Every
Single f****** right-wing media Outlet is saying it's a false flag like Alex's
Better by normalizing bombing the same way Alex.
We thought we were out on the middle of the
We were we were
Real world
This is our fault
No it literally
Maybe we normalize this language based on our audience we literally can't wait
Listen to our shirts
I don't know about that years ago different landscape for Alex was being as like
You was out there and now he's right in line
Right that's absolutely right it's not it's not that Alex has changed
The GOP although
He's become much more of a quote basic b**** of the right it's that the right has come
To him
In terms of the craziness
I don't think anyone
Leaving us could have predicted that never replies is like
Literally the most dangerous mentality that is possible
Because
Anytime
Now
That any attack happens on people on the left
This is going to be the narrative
That all of these heads on Twitter and
Ann Coulter Sean Hannity
Lou Dobbs
That is going to be something that's going to be a card they can play
And when
Now that they played
That card
Seems like they can
Go back
They've already called it a false flag
Bright
What they're doing and that person will have to be a pastor
We'll have to be innocent
Going backward
Progression
From
Conspiracy theory stuff it propped up as Trump
Became much more normal
And then as it got closer to the election
More normal
Went crazy
But
Smaller level
You have
The normalization
The right-wing media
Especially Fox News
FIFA
And
The proud boys
Are the same thing
We're sort of organized
Group
Rite Aid and all they want to do is go and beat up Chris
Yeah right perspective as opposed to it being a loose-knit
Group of unorganized
Groups of people who go in
Encounter demonstrate
Fascist
Fashion and are willing to fight with
With them as opposed to a lot of
Straight against
So you have that on that side and then with the proud boys you have a s******* cult leader
Play Gavin McInnes who screams all the time but how he wants
And thinks that Society is too weak we should kick the s*** out of each other
And has a group with a regimented structure where the fourth level of it is you have to
To beat somebody up or get arrested for the cause
Heat incentivizes
Business idea of
Going and that's the fourth level of The Proud boys
What's 1/4 / 4
That's real
You have to get into a fight
I guess not
Can you not do that no because you
Pretend
But of course
As opposed to
There is nothing like that on the left
Did you go pick a fight with you
It's crazy because that language of
Equivalent of
Cowboys
And they're funded by Joy
George Soros
That sort of language about
What did the
Broader picture
Is the first step that leads up to
Nick terrorism
And you know
Charlottesville President coming out saying good people on both sides
It muddies the water of what we're at
We talkin about
And that even goes back to Alex's
Yep because he never defines what Nazi
Collaborator mean
Which makes it
Stole
Because if he said
He's a Nazi collaborator and by that I mean
When he was a very young boy he was a part of the Jewish Council which was an organization
They should also tell you that back then they didn't let Jewish kids go to school until they had to become a part of this
Deliver messages to
Is around town and then I was a
They give this message
They would end up getting taken away
So young George Soros told his dad about these message
He was told to deliver
And his dad
Deliver those messages
That you tell everybody that you give that message to
If you show up to that meeting
They are never going to
Comeback you warned them
That this is something that there is not what it appears to be
You deliver those messages
And I want people as his father did as well
Save the number of people from
The Holocaust
From being taken away.
Dashi as boy
After he made that run
Like I am not doing this anymore
So he disappeared
Stop the stop going
Into the Jewish Council
Meeting
That he was made to do because Jews
Going to live to go to school
Paul Revere
Was called a British collaborator
Right tells you that the
Evil is coming
That person is
We collaborated with that
How could they
But if you wanted conversation
About what does collaborator mean
Then that would be easy we
All the power out of his deck
Akita Nazi collaborator and buy that I have
Brought it definition
The verdict
The process that he was
Supposed to be
Looks like there's all this stuff
The essence of
What's going wrong
Thursday
Deterioration of
Definition
There's a deterioration of
Contact
All of this stuff
Just serving
I don't even know
Defense people playing defense
Does it mean if you look at
Popular who wouldn't be in any way if they weren't staying the shittiest thing
So for them there has to be some sort of
The financial incentive 100,000
Don't have a gig otherwise
Anita's Ally
With what he said
Even if
Was the
False flag
And he's arguing
Is that
CNN
Trying to pay
Poor little baby
Which you put those two
Two things together and what
Play saying is
Why would you care if he got back
That's definitely a piece of it
He's a book He's a Nazi collaborator why are you even trying to stop him from getting
Why aren't there is a piece of that
Maybe a couple more clips
Get to it which way
We're not legally allowed
Trump outlawed
Magical mirrors
I am
A couple more Clips before we do that I want to talk a little bit about how
For today
There were a number of like I didn't want to talk about present-day of core
I don't want to put people through that
And I think that a lot of
We've been having this
It's fairly basic
But it doesn't really charmie all that much
To reiterate
This is why
He talks about false flags all the time
Yeah this is this is his way of
Like you
Very eloquently put
Admitting without admitting
He knows something is really bad
Tunak
Papillon look for it
So I started to Rack my brain to think about like
What are other time
That we could draw analogs
Hey one of them was the Boston bombing and listening to that
That was just a waste of an hour
Unless we did a dedicated episode about that
If so
It's it's hard for me to experience the things were experiencing together in the country right now
Without thinking back to April 2010
That month was a month it was full of right-wing Insanity episode I wanted to go
See what Alex was saying about a couple incident
Imagine my surprise when I didn't find him saying anything
And mostly just talk about how Oklahoma City was a false flag.
Cuz April is the universe
There's some things I did learn
April 2010
Confirm for you that Alex was protein
So you does end up getting on board
Buy a April
You were very closely aligned with the rising tide in the Tea Party
April 2010 Wet'n'Wild
On April 15th 2010 president of the Cleveland chapter of The Oath Keepers Matthew Fairfield was arrested
And indicted on 28 explosive
Surcharges 25-count
Receiving stolen property
And one count of possessing criminal tools
When the police searched his home they found a literal Napalm bomb
But he'd constructed as well as child pronography
From an article on cleveland.com
Tough
Two-hander
ATF agent said
The discovery of the homemade bomb was particularly troubling because Napalm is designed to Target
Of course
This wasn't any kind of isolated
Fairfield was previously convicted in sentence
Two years probation in February for carrying concealed weapon
He's dropped a loaded gun to his ankle while attending an event at a country fairgrounds
The Napalm bomb is obviously a huge red flag but this guy also had
A bit of an Armory going
Motorcar detonators to m4 assault rifles a 12-gauge pump-action shotgun
A 22 caliber bolt-action rifle
Semi automatic
I can't dance from
He was hunting
This got a guy who was arrested on 28 explosive charges among other bomb
Generally speaking
You do not build bombs for recreation
Just sitting around is a bomb that is not serve
It's only purpose
So I went back and listen to episodes around the time of fairfield's arrest there was an article that came
A couple days after his arrest
So I checked that seems like maybe Alex missed the news
Expected Alex to say it was a false flag and there was attempted besmirch the good name of The Oath Keepers
What I found instead with him not bringing up the
Story at all radio silence
Radio silence
And what's difficult for me about that is I had to listen to all of that and I can't prove to you and Nick
I can't sit here and play a clip of him not saying that
Right go ahead
Waste 4 hours drive
Unsatisfying
So here was the president The Oath Keepers chapter in the city of
Population over 2 billion people
Being arrested
For building a bomb that was meant to
Target people
With napalm
And Alex doesn't talk about it
At all
Don't come up
Emily's
That sucks
The kind of wish that Alex
Had claimed it was a false flag made meant to make the o.c.
People's look bad cuz then I could have told you all about Derek Hough
The Tennessee okiboru got arrested on April 30th 2010
Courthouse
Where he would assert control them put everyone under citizen
I could tell you about how get 300
An AK-47 as well as a handgun
Because quote
I've got my 45
Because ain't no government official going to go peacefully
I could tell you about how only went to take over that because they were hosting a trial for a sovereign citizen weirdo named Walter
Fitzpatrick
Who's being tried for trying to make a citizen's arrest on the foreman of a grand jury charged with him
I can tell you that help was under surveillance
The entire time he was traveling from Madisonville because
Buddy we're going to take over Madisonville
I can tell you about how the city of
I could tell you about how the city of Madisonville surreptitiously rescheduled.
I told Courthouse employees to stay home that day so hopefully his militia buddies ended up showing up to an empty Courthouse under
And have you got four years
Four years in prison and ended up getting hurt
Get him for that one is like
You know I'm saying
Man
Really super small town of like hey if you're trying to
Take over a town where y'all at
Should be higher
Town meeting
Some stuff down
I could tell you about
Countless other very serious
He like that last one
Cinnamon plant are carried out by right-wing groups
Country
Just because something doesn't go off
Has planned doesn't mean that it's fake
Which is an important
Distinction
And secondarily
There is a ton
Oathkeeper related
Right wing
Violin
Damn terrorism
Are you otherwise
Doesn't even make the effort
To say it's a false flag
Earlier when you bringing up this idea of like what does he call the false flag and you were suggesting all the things
You can paint on the right or
False flag
Albany just doesn't talk about it
And this one like this dude this initial dude here
This guy Matthew Fairfield
Is there a one-to-one parallel
Who the guy was making multiple bonds one of them a Napalm bomb
I mean
This is the sort of things
You see
I don't remember it
Seniors
I get it that should be so much longer I get it mixed up cuz there was another story about another guy from
May or may not have had a
Stolen
A grenade launcher
But he claimed
What happened
What island in Hawaii
Right
Yeah they going to the leper colony
No no no
Underwater now
Can we put them on
I feel like housing
Difficult Island it can't be an island again
That's good
Molokai
Cinnamon that's a leper colony Island
Other people how to make f****** when I lived in Hawaii
2 island
Molokai
Can't go cuz
Used to be a leprechaun
Is entirely owned by
What is all fruit
I don't know if that's okay maybe we should have islands that are just fruit I don't know I don't know if it's 104
The understanding was growing out there's like
You can't go there
Don't buy.
Pennywise
That is to say
I kind of wanted to talk about that stuff even though it's not
It's relevant to this episode but not 100
Alex.
Talk about
Is that
Our real-world damaging
He does predictively
Repair
People
These narratives that are going to be
Or real-world events
Latinos are coming
They can't avoid
He can avoid that thing with the oathkeeper
This one
He knows that the guy that
He is the biggest fan of
Is
Two-way that jeopardizes
Safety
Journalist
In order to
Protect himself
She has to create
So
The issue is that it's not just
It's not just about saying
These bombs are
There's something much deep
Cheaper at hand here
And this is why I ever wanted
Very worried
The shut it up and test the public
And Obama is
Rolls
Osecina
Alex's articulating exactly what you said about the idea of now
If something does happen
That will be what you know that doesn't matter
He's saying they're going to blow up
BNN
Which
Is that does happen
Alex now is ready to be like
Who cares
It's not real it's all fake
Who gives a s***
This is a globalist
All terrorism is on the table man
I still think there is one and there really isn't
There really isn't those nowhere else for them to go but lower than whatever you think the floor is Alex's expensive
All of the right-wing media
Two of his way of being which is to normalize white violence and white terrorism
To the point now where we entire political party
And their propaganda organ
That are in service
Of
Man if any white guys do anything it's fake
I think that the election
What about
Anxiety
The midwestern
Just felt like they were left
It's hard to say what the motivation
But we can certainly see the effects
Land
I know I don't want to leave people feeling like
Hey
Cuz Alex
No cuz I was wrong about
I don't I don't
I don't think anybody should take him to be
Like evidence that it's going to happen
But I would say
Did Alex
If you can clearly see that
He thinks
S*** this is going to ask collate
And he knows that be
He knows what his fans are like that's why he runs away from them on the street
That's why he's
He doesn't want to go into the Trump rally because there's too many Trump people in there
He knows that
That's why he yells at a piece of s*** and calls it Beto outside
Instead of actually
Engaged
The thing
He's created
Dinos
He knows that there are
Dangerous people on that side
Statistics facts
And there's no reason why he would
You would make that prediction
False flag
So probably going to happen
Control
Well I don't
I don't know
Does anybody
No course
Nobody thinks that
Ten bombs
That don't go off
Where it ends
And especially
Like I know that we're recording this here on Thursday evening
Fresh thyme we can have
The perspective of like
No one's been caught
But someone will eventually this case
Pizza floppy
Situation
Criminal mastermind I'm sure there are fingerprints done investigation is going
To happen it's going to
More facts
We'll come out and we'll be able to
Disgusting more accurately
But
At the same time if you're the person who did it
And you see an entire political party working
In order to pay
Presented as if
You weren't doing the thing that you did
I don't know what other message that sends bombers
It sends a message of eight
You do this
We're going to bed
Even if you don't get caught we're going to do our best to make sure that people think it was this shadowy cabal of
Definitely not Jews
So I mean the world that were entering
F***** up
Dangerous
We Don't Step Up
And the media doesn't step up
I know
Some people are doing a good job about
Don't get me wrong I'm not saying everybody suck
But people need to step up and
Talk about it
They're normalizing terrorism
It's not a situation of
Hey what's this quirky false-flag hashtag that's going around
It's not that
Intentionally or not
The right-wing
Speaking to normalize and make okay
White Terror
I'm saying that
With no idea if
Who's doing this is why
We don't know anything about it
Matters
Because they're defending
As Bill the person was there's that
The reasons that I'm putting
Into the equation is
Because
Look at the
Imo
Past history of the
People who are doing
Who are they getting the media
Like Lou Dobbs like Russia
Limbach
These are people who is made careers out of justifying
And minimizing
The effect
On their V
These are the people
I mean Tucker Carlson did fine for himself
Crossfire
But he wasn't making nearly the amount of money he is now
Being just
Lap dogs
Is justifying white supremacy on tonight
Salt Lake
I'm saying that they're doing this in an effort
To normalize white terrorism
Because of the
People in the media
Their behavior
Beer is in line with
Not necessarily that
Perpetrator
Turcotte is why
I need to make that clear
When I accept theirs
Entire world
Out there of possibilities
Disperse
Azar
Imagine
Like we don't get the opportunity to imagine
Alex does
Have a writers room
Deeply script
I imagine being in that
Production
Tucker Carlson
And there are
A bunch of producers in there
About what it is we
The content
This was there
Maybe we're
Not
Doing this
Maybe we should
I mean it goes back to
Like we were talking about employees at Fox News like
I'm not saying I'm not talking they're all awful or anything like that
I find
Difficult to imagine
People there who have
Quit already it's hard for me to
There are no
Designer
The whole thing
Like there is somebody
Tucker Carlson doesn't record a show live like Alex
Alex
Everstaff
And the people who wouldn't maybe been like I don't know about this
Natural selection
Things that we're going on
Look I'm not trying to
B2 fatalistic
Go to like a freak out but like
If we are not more careful about how we allow stories
To be told how we allowed
The media to behave and I'm not saying like
On the media
But like
People who
People riding the headline
Need to be substantially
Be more careful
They need to be more aware of what's actually going on
And effect of this right-wing propaganda is
It's incredibly difficult
I do not
I am not in any way jealous of their position
I couldn't do
Finger-like
I could do your job or anything like that
I couldn't but I also didn't go get a journalism
You guys put yourself in this position
Because you who study journalism and now he's made a career out of being journalist
The public
Trust you to know how to do journalism
And we trust you
To adapt
The times that we're in
And not falling
To the traps
These right-wing propaganda
That will lead us all down the road to hell
Where any attack
On anybody on the left
Because that's where we're going
Without
Where We Are
But that that's where we're going
We don't get the
And I say we
I don't mean to laugh
Because it's easy for it to swing the other way to
I don't think we want that
Hopefully the one that's fair
Might be deserved but
I don't have anything to take this thing off this at all or anything
At all
Hopefully there won't be any more Banzai next week she'll be more fun
Listen to the show
Expecting optimism about the future
We
Have put
Together a long track record of being very positive about
The directions
Getting everybody
Please erase
To an opinion
Everything is good looking on the bright side
I am over here
Antifreeze
So I don't know it sucks but next week
Hopefully I'll be better
Anyway website.com
We are on Facebook we have a small group getting big
Call gamma.
That's right
Check that out subscribe
Suck
I will tell you this
It's really
Really good
It's a really positive
Bomber
No that's true I'll tell you what he did though
Probably
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color