Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Look up a little bit about Alex Jones
What's the last day you remember where we do
Didn't see a hate crime I don't know
I know that
This is
Check on it but it is getting exhausting
Everyday waking up a new
Just
Human moral travesty
Yeah
It's really I'm starting to realize like
I can't wake up and immediately look
At the world
Start a new routine where I do something else
So I'm trying to initiate like a
Just wake up and exercise
Or something with my mind
In a more stable position for I might
Good God
I just feels like
JF
This picture
The next episode
Feels like the
Damn is about
Are any of those ever any of the things that were experiencing the last week any of them would be back
Unique to the time we're in right now
Awful
Years ago it would have been awful at any time
Really terrible anytime
Yep it's
It's hard to deal with
I feel for everyone in the world
That is correct Kevin Hogan
Went out with him
Nashville hot chicken
It does little addition of the spice report
Where are we going
He really spicy food
Income report
The audience about it
I went myself
Yeah
Their secret level that's secret they have a secret secret spicy level
It's hotter than extra hot
How hot is that
I had the extra hot the last time I went
Secret
The secret hot
And
No big deal
Video
It turns out it's a ghost pepper situation
Breakfast the heat of a ghost pepper
Super problematic
But I don't like the flavor
So that's been spies report
We will be over March
15th
Which is
You're like
The last couple 2009 episode in one day
The f****** Pace right
And we do know that by April
2010 he's on board of the Tea Party
A lot of time
Like these shows
These were nothing
Because at this point in 2009
Alex
Featured
An ISP documentary
Call the New World Order
And it's
Premiering
March
Middlemarch
It's out by Southwest
Gallivanting around with the filmmakers
Having two filmmakers come into studio and they're just bragging about this documentary
Wait till is it
So this documentary is like
Staunchly Pro show my cruise when they're on the show
You stay out of that
To give you a glimpse
People
Verilife
So whatever
I would also say I haven't seen that documentary but
The main people who are in it or Alex Jones
Jack McLamb
Holocaust deniers
Who writes for the spotlight which is
Publication
Documentary
You don't
Also promoted The Obama Deception like crazy
And so we were able to skip
Through a good amount of this s***
Without
Going over
I still had to listen to all 15 hours of my time
Nothing to listen to Alex Bragg
Everyone
Thank you so much cuz I was going to do it at goddamn minute welcome
And I'm glad I did though because I was going through
I was like
F****** s***
I am not doing nothing
Especially not in the world we're living in the most toothless
Green thing in the world
Going gets rough
You don't invade Russia in the win
The first lesson you have to persevere
Do you have to keep pushing forward even when it looks like
Nothing is going right
What it looks like you're going to end up with a deadline
Who's going to show up at your house and all you got or clips of Alex being like
I'm at South by Southwest with a bullhorn filmmakers
Oh my God what if I got to I've got to Richard linklater the associate producer in studio talking about
I don't want to do that
Keep pushing forward
And you're going to strike paydirt
And I did
I don't like the way that you set this up like I was on my way to take me like 20 minutes to walk hair and you just
Sister like you don't
Understand fit like
6 hours before you get here I have to know what we're doing
Because otherwise
I hit Pay Dirt
I think I found something
Incredibly
Contacts
Contextualize almost everyday
The product
Keeping pushing forward when the going is done
Now that being said
Big caveat
Along the way to me
Something
There's at least a couple of funny moments throughout them
So here's one from March 15th where Alex tries to get back to his story
About how that
I was on was on the truck
Nope
Free shooter
Just a toothache
Oh yeah they're real
You don't trip on it
Xanax
Yeah
These ssris
A bit a lady's face off that turns out
Wasn't on ssris is on Xanax
Prozac bahut
Itsfunneh
The brat
Balls
Make his argument about shooters
Connected
The Monkees
Monkey walking on Prozac
Right
My arguments
Today Show
The next day after
Literally did say
It was on
And it said I'm going to rehab
Fresh
Radio
It is mostly because Alex
Gallivanting around with
Acting like a big shot
Hollywood movies
Richard linklater is Associates
Just like all strfkr eat a little bit and then Jason bermas being boring as hell
So the 16th we can wipe it
Completely off our play
We don't have to worry about this
16th
Now I should also say
That.
Is ulcer
On the 17th when Alex just has the IFC producers
In interviews that documentary about him
MetroPCS
I think they probably sent him a form
Better if
They didn't show him
The documentary
Just be a b**** slap to the
The face that would be awesome be good prank
Alex pranks
Most of the Senate
The end of the show has
He is one of
Is vaccine
Experts Fisher on the show
Talk about how bad
Barbara
Really dive to
But it Bears repeating
This is one of their big
This is one of the arguments
Expert
Is a bad sign
And I think that this is where I have a lot of trouble with this sort of greater good argument that they keep making
The argument as you don't have the right
As an individual parents
To make that choice for your child because if you don't make the choice of the government says you need to make in this case get get back
Vaccinated you put your neighbor's child at rest
I've always said if the vaccines there is effective as the companies in
Deb said they are
Then you should have it in the vaccinated
Should have nothing to fear from those two trees
We really have
Stop Believing in myths and misinformation and we have to get the information
That's terrible man if you're coming at you with the argument if everybody is vaccinated
Kefir for people not being bad
Nursery research
Get vaccinated
Underlying conditions
They may have
All these reefs bleach
Not being able to do that
Just that like
It's not like I have vaccines
So I'm afraid of you not having
It's a public health
Because there's a large segment of the population
Just can't
Get back
And if you follow her argument
Conclusion
As a person who is
I just get to watch wide swaths of children die
As they spread the disease back
And forth to each other
At the show schitt
60th and 17th
In my Alex Jones listening
I very rarely
We almost ended the show that's how bad those two were
Robot ending the show
To flirting with
Because I don't know when.
It kept happening
Is a little bit better
Now the 18th is really interesting time
The Alex Jones Show
Because he's
Cast
With
Napolitano on his f***
Oh that's super.
So it is a bad
The Obama Deception
Before they get to their interview
Sakura
Devices on show for the sake of a
Okay
Okay well we're waiting for my guys to send me that
Not going to it for about 7
Okay great we got audio now he's going to wait for fun
The judges show right now if you guys are ready to go by there as well
My face is
Did you listen to them
This is a rare trait
Who said that
Squeeze
That's pretty good considering
6:30
Eternal
Understood
I'm here guys I'm waiting
Regular
Joe
Shortly
Okay I'm here
I can't believe this is still going on
10 minutes
Surround
Alex is willing
To put that on his
Sacrifices
For this other show because
Mission
But he knows that foxes audiences
Is way bigger than his
He's willing to do s*** like this
He went on RT on inauguration day and just left his show
Simulcast
4 minutes
Beast of his live
Broadcast
It's so unprofessional
Who gives a s*** if I can tap into napolatanos audience
Going to be way bigger
Yeah but I mean even then there's a little bit of salt on napolatanos
Why is he getting
Probably not on the freezer but it's great
I don't know
It's crazy what are those
What the f***
Others lives
Wow
You come a long way baby
Somebody called 5 minutes before then different special
Hey we're going to come on at
Victor
Napolitano
Okay
How about you
For The Obama Deception
It infowars.com out there about the Maya
What's going on
Alex
Despite the fact that he's in a little bit of a
Sxsw holding pattern
Miac report is still the big
And what's interesting is on this episode March 18th
Alex
Purports to have evidence
This
Some guy
I called
The
Missouri police
And recorded it
And it's some sort of a damning
So he's teasing that he's going to play this audio of a guy talking
Missouri police
Like I don't
I imagine
Did the Kapil just
Like no comment
Rapping like that
People get possessed
How to think so
To tell you the truth
That would be awesome
Over the moon
Instead
I did not expect
This copy
Very reasonable
I'm trying
Explain to this caller
Exactly what I have explained about the Maya
On the other line right now
Let me say that the reason that music is playing is
Coming straight out of break
It's not like it's a going on in the phone call
I can have your old I can take your name and number and have them give you a call back
It's kind of whatever you would prefer
Let me hold for
Does the moment
Also
It's important to know that he was on hold
See how disrespectful the police are
Go to put you on hold
They're public
Servant
I'm definitely not continuing to talk over this.
Hi how are you
Campaign for Liberty
Like to ask you a few questions
Trying to clarify
As you know
A lot of information circulating on the internet regarding this recent
Circulated
I don't know I've not been on the internet to say but I've certainly is taking a bunch of calls
Report
Yeah I'm looking at the report if we're talking about this
We have any.
Clark willing to discuss this you seems very
Maybe that's pretty good
Strongly
And Pregnant
Now let's go
Concern
People who are members of
Some people deem is Liberty Movement or who are Ron Paul supporters
Members of the campaign for Liberty which is
The Grassroots organization
Predominant members in the leading parties and
Okay well received
And answer I don't doubt that at all and I
I commend you and Kendall
Preemptively
Tired of this bull already
Are you go home and tell your mother
Oh yeah you went to see pack good for you I'm thrilled that you're in good standing
Okay I guess the question is
Looking at one of the concerns why why are people that a part of this Liberty Movement
Being labelled or targeted or potentially profiled in this report as
Potential domestic terrorist
Well if you read that I don't see anywhere in that report where targets anybody were profiles anybody
Call were labeled anybody of anything
Terrorist or a militia group member or anything like that
And to think that any law enforcement officer or agent
Wood
Target somebody for political affiliation I think
Inappropriate
Well do I'll bet stupid like that
A broader picture of History that's very dumb
But that's the only thing I take issue with it he say
I like
This whole situation is like
White people aren't
Even being profiled and they're still mad
Everybody else has been profiled for Thousand Years
Holy s*** are you going to f****** do this to us we do that
Brightright
Let's leave aside the fact that
The cop is saying that it's inappropriate
Target someone for their political beliefs
The history shows a darker picture
Sure a lot of the time
The people being targeted were
Strongly on the left
More of the history of it
Yes
But
Leaving that aside
The only thing that you can really I feel
With this
Clark
Because it's not accurate in this case
Profile
And the report is simply does not say that
What
What is your
What is your understanding of why
Constitution party
Chuck Baldwin Bob Barn rampal
I mention of
People displaying Ron Paul bumper stickers why is there mention of that in the report
Well if you read the report I don't think there's a mention of bumper stickers at all any
28-page report so obviously
Obviously you haven't read the entirety of the report or your you're looking a report it
I love this video because
The last page
Busted
It's not
Starting on the second to last page where the parts at like
They're playing fast and loose
With combining
Details from this
Report in order to make it
That cop is
Completely right there is no mention of Ron Paul bumper
Stickers at all in here
Dimension of Ron Paul
These members are usually supporters
The former presidential candidate Ron Paul
The next paragraph
Talks about Antigua
Government propaganda
Meet militia members commonly display picture cartoons bumper stickers that contain ant
Government rhetoric
Most of this will depict
The FR-S IRS FBI ATF CIA un law enforcement at the New World Order in a derogatory manner
In completely different sections of this report
Dick characterizes militia
And these Danger
Groups
That are not
Just
Liberty lovers
Did they put a 100% of one side of your van covered in bumps
That's not a red flag
That's not a red flag.
Fairly targeting
Absolutely
So
We have
Seen this cop
Be very fair
Phone call with
Fight
This guy
This
Next clip I think
Really drive home
Appointed we've been making
I can't speak for why you think that there's something in the report that says
People who have a Ron Paul bumper
Or any political affiliation
That's just simply not true and it's not in the report
Is there reference to
Stop movement order
People who are opposed to North American Union
Was New World Order in there
Weather from information in there regarding
Certain militia groups in those violent factions that operate within those militia
Details
Do certain police system
And
What political parties or candidates they might associate
Certainly the document doesn't say that anybody who's affiliated with a certain
Political candidate or a political party is certainly
On my way to remember a pterosaur or anything like that I think of
Yes and is it's all these people want to kill you
It's not that at all and also and it's not even in the report also in a militia
Or a terrorist
Is
A disjunction
The generally means one or the other
The same thing at all
So now what you see
Because what Alex Jones has just done
Is very accurate
Play Dan accurate debunking of his narrative
On the Shelf
Is absolutely correct
In terms of
The inference problems that they are making
Fitbit Alta
Propaganda
The idea that
These dangerous groups that we have studied
They show these
Signs
That is
To say that if you
Exhibit design
You should be suspected of being a
A member of One of These Days
That he has just completely laid out
Alex is wrong
Do you think
Reflect
Sorry
I'll come in and disagree with everything in life about
Instead what he does is on March 19th
Is Susie start to show
He says that
We have a doctor Chuck Baldwin constitutional 1008
Don't let him spin it let him spin it again store already
Explained he hasn't spawn anything
I guess
Natural wheel spin
Existed
Reality is
Any any
Statement of fact
Any statement of the definition of a
But you see it right there
You see it clearly
At this point
I'm certain always
Thinks that any explanation
That is against
He is
Predetermined idea is
Trying to lie about this thing
That I'm lying about
It's lunacy
It's a way to live
When you have a 9
You get at 3
Makes 9 a.m.
A square number
We will not be divided
What they did at Alex
Third grade
The thing is that like this is the narrative is so satisfying
Because it reinforces
The b*******
Because if this is if this is true
You know that
This is absolutely true
It's an existential threat
For this to not be
Be true
So what's up matter
Suspend
Pathetic
After I Alex
Introduces his death
Let you know what's coming up on the program
He gets to his first
Story
On March 9th
It will ship
Very important
Let me break it down right now
House passes Tori national service bill
You heard me
They are going to do laser eyebrows
Live
Morning
Crowd problem
Cuz we're just going to legalize
Paul Watson
Bingo
Yesterday
As fears about President Obama's promise
He always is
Right now
Also completely misrepresenting
Gus Garcia
The initial version of the bill that was introduced in the house quote called for a congressional commission to address
Several topic
Including issues that deter volunteerism
And how they can be overcome
How expanding International Public Service might affect
Diplomacy in foreign relations
And whether workable fair and reasonable service
Requirement for all able Young
People could be developed
And how such a requirement could be implemented in a manner that would strengthen
The social fabric of the
However
The version that passed the house had this language
Completely stripped
The version of pass the Senate never included such language
At all
Even Orrin Hatch that are on the senate floor
Consistent with our all-volunteer army and volunteer opportunities an individual's choice
Community nothing in this legislation is Manta
Because Alex is saying that the bill passed and not the bill was introduced
It's very clear that he's lying or that the only thing he knows about the bill is based on
Show me article
Who is way too sloppy to know that a bill can be Rewritten
Or any other
Play some debate
So the bill does not always the same as the bill that's voted on
It's pretty clear this is just another example of Paul Joseph Watson having zero professionalism as a journalist
And Reporting some
Something completely inaccurate because it states
Infowars
Predetermined
Schoolhouse Rock
Heat donut strip
Yeah you don't know about
How to make a bell
It's not
This level of
Not even spin
I wish I wish
Cops are
Sorry
Narrative
It was in there that means always in there
That's based on the Constitution
You cannot change a bill what to do with it
I'm absolutely this doesn't deter Alex from
I'm trying to spread fear of what will happen once these forced Valen
Tourism
Things happen
That's what they want you to think of going to happen
Alright
The same thing with like saying that
National Guard can help in emergencies I'm really do you need a chance right
That's right the same thing
You hear this volunteer
Your stuff in your life
Children how to read
In truth he is
Drug head know-it-all video game players in playlist Violet games
Prime Ford
Now did it
Ignore example
Out of control
Tell all the young snot-nosed punch
Don't try running the checkpoint don't try coming up to me
I just can't handle it anymore I can't handle the scumbag bankers
And the dumbass
The barrel of a gun
I'm sorry I missed
It's just really starting to get to me
And don't you dare go to the hospital
Trying to get her to learn already I'm helping her spin things
I mean like what he's what he's expressing
Anymore is your fake version of reality
If you could just alleviate yourself you could understand
Jackal yourself of those burdens
By just reading
You can stop being so mad if
You would just read
Is paranoid fantasies
That's all he's mad at you mad at like
Ghost
Crazy
No yeah
Absolutely the whatever it is that scary
What's now and I'm mad
My stomach
I do like hearing that
Narrative of likes
Video games cause violence
Because we only ever see that
Whenever there's a
We didn't hear the violent video game
Has caused all of the shootings today we found out
Supremacy
I was apart of it
So many people were just like always all these violent video games
It's all that s***
And now you're the movie
F*** you you know what it is
Too difficult
To wrestle with the others
The other stuff is
It opens up a knapsack
Do things you don't want to look at the contents of
And so you say video games movies blah blah blah
You don't want to unpack the whites
Supremacy you don't want to unpack
The history of domestic violence
It's always behind all these things
So you know they played the Doom
And then 7 Days Later
Earlier in the episode of Chuck Baldwin on
Baldwin is another one of these guys
Who's listed
In the miac report
Knock me over with a feather
When I learn
Take
What about you
What we're dealing with here whenever
Categorize people who vote for
Myself or Ron Paul or even Bob bar
As potential domestic terrorists and make that part of an official state police agency report
We are
Deep do-do there's no doubt about it
It's almost like is a coordinated response
It's almost weird that these people have the exact same angle
Conveniently
Make the same logical fallacy in order to excuse the fact that a lot of people who support them end up in fire
Violet militias
I mean that strange
Interesting about Chuck
Is that he has come prepared
With a letter
It is written
To the authorities in Missouri
Things about him
He's the only Baldwin brother
Weather to actually
Public office
But he is
Really can do it
Can't be
He can't run for public
Might be a better actor in terms
Himself
Victim on the show
This dude
This is crazy
He hasn't later that he's written
To the Missouri
Law enforcement
Spoke and she's going to reach
Alex
72 and I have
I have a take on this on the other end
This is really f*****
This is like
It's more f***** up than just this guy writing a letter to Jay Nixon have
He's a butt hurt about being listed
Document
Verisk
It is been
Willits
It's all over two pages
B
Daredevil Elektra
A grievous write you as former presidential candidates as concerned citizens and in the case of Ron Paul at the sitting member of the US
House of Representatives and Bob bar
Remember 1995 to 2000
Bring your attention the most disturbing document being circulated by the Missouri information analysis Center Mac
Steal your office
And your name is governor
Respectfully demand its following describe document the immediately remove any and all websites
Associated with or maintained by the state of Missouri
Brady agency thereof
Including the miac
The document no longer be circulated by the state of Missouri or any agency there up or associated therewith
Missouri repudiate its references to the three of us has contained therein
The document to which river is identified as follows and a copy of clothes there with
Ron's Automotive
The thing that I really want to drive home
This isn't just
Chuck Baldwin saying
You know it's
To me that I'm in this
This is an attempt to bully law enforcement
Cannot be able to do their jobs
Because
Like people like Chuck Baldwin and Ron Paul
Don't want to own up to the effect
They've had on society
They know damn well
Little lot of their supporters have gone that way
Especially Ron Paul
There's literally no way that
If you can't recognize that a lot of his supporters are f****** whites
He can't
It's literally
Beyond
Realm of possibility
Plead ignorance
Especially considering his own writings
Right
Neo-Nazi ties that he has
For these guys who
Dino
Dino's video
Right
As a political
Getting together and writing a letter to Jay Nixon
The governor of Missouri
To be like this is a slanderous documented how dare you with
Are suspected of being in these militias and dangerous groups
They're taking that propaganda angle that is the misrepresent
Haitian that the
I did and they're weaponizing it against the very lawn for
Ourisman agencies
And the governor of Missouri
In order to get them to not be able
To express a truth
A truce
Big people in these groups
Do support.
Text terrorism
To some extent that information terrorism
Yeah and they're able to because people like Bob bar people like Ron Paul and Chuck Baldwin
Have social cap
They can bully
The governor to do
Andy Sixx
Yeah
They reneged or whatever their correct term is the Niagara for it
They said they rescind it I got to be the best
Because of all the pressure from
People like
These three
How dare you name Us in this
Dave
Inaccurate
They are babe just to put their tail between their legs and couch
To the pressure
Right-wing propaganda
I mean
Central like
Truth
That
A bunch of powerful White
Get together and
B****
Things will change
Because everybody is
F******
Fine just go
Happening
Keeps hair
He's partially just go away and then the other part
Be very fear of things that are in the miac.
Your followers might bomber
That's not to say that the
In everybody who follows
But there's a bunch of
So
You know it's implicit threat
That's underneath a letter that you sent it
The governor
Along with like
Girls they're never going
That they open up
Dammit
Government and the
Ron Paul
Sitting member of the United has a hello
Oh God that can't be real Bob bar from 1995 to
T2000
What he's in the government
Price
Sew in
But he knows that his story about the document
A little bit
Okay I will just add that
They start out
Connect
Malicious
Which base
Basically the majority American people pro-second Amendment
You name it
The Departed about a little bit
Is like
The listing of
Cop killers
Malicious
Like it's it's he's trying to pretend that they aren't the same thing
Twaimz
You know
Silent malicious don't exist
I'd like to take you back
When Georgia militiamen members of the peaceful chehaw tribe
We're done by other tribes
They knew in advance that the Cheaha tribe were a friendly group
And not the one
Decided to take out their anger on them anyway
Examples of
Exactly racially-motivated
Militia groups but that's
Too far back
So let's just mention the Bundy Ranch the malheur wildlife standoff the Oklahoma City
And then there's the countless
Disrupted plots of militia members trying to bomb boss
Take over army base
And Then There Was Fear
Demolition of non-commissioned service
As part of the plan to take over Fort Stewart in Georgia
19 year old named Michael
17 year old girl friend Tiffany York
And threw their bodies in a lake
Because they thought Roar
Snatched
Everything
Cursive F
But that's a matter for another time
There's tons
And tons of militia viola
Even in prison
To 1880
The history of malicious
Have largely been
Bored and killing
Generally causing
What a coalition of Stolen Valor and
Racist actually did served
So here is Chuck
Plan was to poison
Annapolis
Sherwood
I don't know maybe the applefield was like
It specifically went to Fort Stewart maybe his apples we're going to get inside
Southern
Classic
Sleeping Beauty plan I don't pretend to understand like
The finer points militia plans
Because generally they're a little crazy his f****** girlfriend got murdered for his other plot of
Sleeping Beauty
Find a lot of militia plot
Did I end up looking into
Play coronavirus episode there was that guy was going to take over that Courthouse
Yeah yeah
Kind of the
The equivalent of like a Rube Goldberg machine
It's like I don't understand how old is like mousetrap
Plan to achieve an objective
From
Yeah
To be like this
An action plan is like
Is few moving parts
Because anything could go wrong
Control every look at the raid on Osama Bin Laden's house
It's not like okay so here's what we're going to do
Six guys in there
He's going to have to Fry Road
Finally
Yobama
Where can I get a hologram of Jenny McCarthy
Georgia
Yeah there's easier easy
Either way
Here
Expresses
Is going to do
In response
To this mayak document
What what
Talking Ron Paul talking about
Retracted
I think I think I can safely say that the sense of
Chevy Traverse is that this is serious enough
If the state of Missouri does not respond appropriately
That we should consider legal action II think that is certainly a consideration right now
Yes
They're going to snow
No it was not
They know damn well that they are not going to pursue any legal action
Because if they went to court
Guess what
All of it would be proven true
Well never ever get into any underworld situation
Where the guys are actually just providing
A list of Victoria
A list of violent malicious demonstrating what the report actually says
It supported this progress 88 be like
Marine Le Pen
Legally named
Whenever it's real
Maria a unified front and the threat of a lawsuit is going to be enough
Forget that
I mean this is baby stuff man
This is like a queen
Whenever
Do you know the right
In the Alex Jones is in the Patriots all these people
Crow on all day about responsibility
Big Talk Non-Stop about
Bruce Randolph
And here you have a situation where
There's a report that comes out
That just says
The people who are in dangerous militia
Is Pam to like these
And those people
Can't handle that
So they lie about it and threaten the law enforcement
People
Who played
So it's so childish
It's the definition of
I don't I don't
Is pathetic
Whatever
Really
Really Chuck Baldwin
Hope for better Congressman pausing we're going to write a letter
I hate feeling that way like I just
They just always comes back
Need a higher class of criminal
I know it
They suck
They don't live by their own principles
Winchester
When put
To the metal
They show themselves to be
It never ceases
To bother me
These people are so disappointing and I've done so much damage
The only mean does that make sense but that's really the sense that I have is like
Just drive home that like
Literacy is important
Like all of this could be stopped
They're lying to a head
Have the ability to critically read the thing if you allow your child to be literate he shouldn't have any
Anything to fear from the child who isn't literate Dan
All right fair enough
Jordan
I should tell you something
WhatsApp
A little piece of information
Tammy
One of them is the anonymous cop who sent him the Maya
Yes about how he's a big supporter into
Out
But okay I get it you Wrangle to I understand that you took it personally that your body was in here
But that's not that still doesn't
YouTube
Read this act
So it's still I'm not Charmed by that interview it doesn't help me at all
And so we can ignore that
Voice maskers
Range of Missouri accent
Or anything
At the end of the show Alex has another guy
Disappearance
Might change
Everything
Alex Jones
He Stewart Roads credit a great website
Constitutional lawyer
Constitution
Call your work when you're absolutely right that was a fantastic Segway that officer
Goalkeeper
What we
Like that out
Don't use their real names
We want them to be able to continue in their job
Continue doing the good work then I can people
So
Stewart Road
Is on
Paratrooper for a time but he was injured in a shooting accident
Received an honorable discharge
From the service
Thank you for your
Ron Paul campaign
For president
It is
Because it really seems to
It has stuck up for him
Was how unfair it was
For people to associate Ron Paul
Right-wing extremist
Orbitform must remind everyone of the attempted takeover of Dominica and of course Ron Paul's racist newsletter that
Monitor with written in the first
After the failure of Ron Paul to become president
Roadside to change approach
Noticing notice things he Rising tide of the early
Tea Party Movement
Only about a month before disappearance on Alex Jones Show
He's very young
. of the organization
Keepers based on the 10 orders that The Oath Keepers will not follow
All of these orders are imaginary and all of them would be unconstitutional
Institutional on their face
The entire Basalt vanilla ice cream
The entire basis of The Oath Keepers basically the same as
Be temperament resolutions that Alex
Keeps bringing up on his show
They're really just aggressively pushing things that are already lost pretending that they aren't
It's not hard to think of them is like a man who's looking
Distract
From how he's cheating on his wife by insisting that they should renew their vows
It's kind of the same thing they're like
We will not
Met many of the early Amendment
And that's one of their 10 like one of them is
We will not
Listen to any order that involves allowing people free speech
Infringe upon the rights of journalists
So recognizing an opportunity to piggyback on the burgeoning sent out representative
30 of the
4th of July
2090 party protest
Backcountry
And in doing so he
He successfully associated
His movement
But before that
Here he is on Alex Jones Show
Pitching.
Snow lawyer
I don't know I got out of the service
Bard
Not entirely
What state was he was involved in some kind of oath keeper active
He wrote a letter
Implied
Vicki was acting as a lawyer
Andy was
Allowed to
We got this far
He's actually
Pasta Bar in
Like
Here he is
Degree
He is he's not like
He's not an idiot
I think he's a sociopath
For sure
But we'll get into a little bit more about The Oath Keepers
And why
Is it parallel to the present day
Very bad
Even more so then what we talked about the last episode
I didn't know when we were going over that stuff on the last episode that
Literally
Right around the corner was going
The founder of The Oath Keepers
About a month Into The Oath Keepers existing coming on Alex's show and the two of them getting along like best
So it does bear mansion
Couple days before we're recovering now
Jack McLamb
Noted a holocaust denier
Kbon Alex Jones
Orders
That The Oath Keepers
Will not
Follow
So there's already been
Serval priming of the audience
To the idea that
Pretty cool
Super cool and I'm guessing the Jack McLamb behind-the-scenes
Connected Outlet
Being here we go
So Alex wants to ask
How to skip going
Just amazing cuz like president
Camping Trinidad
DC office
And I had the idea that we know
And what's our next move
And my thought was as well
Beyond the men with the guns
If you're going to have
Awakening of 1 million people
Awaken 1 million people
Reconstitution what would you want focus on the military
Yeah that's troubling resume
If you had to get 20 people on your side you want them all to be the people with gun
Only if you
If you are a listener of knowledge fight
If you have a gun or not
It's not really not really important
Immediately after
You're bitching and moaning about my ex
As the founder of a violent militia on his show
Go Translate
You know there's a pretty good indication
Systemic culture
Within a lot of organ
Birds that are
Deeply racing
But
Superior
Stewart
Comes in
Within an hour
Do we know Alex Jones
Analogies
The rings of the Ring of Power
They think the ring of power is at these guys are going to do whatever they say
Deserving of power
Any more fundamentally to the people
You do
Special
You are something special
Empower is this
Flight allegory for nuclear weapons
Like I said Alex loves the movie metaphor
Here it comes in with the movie metaphor Alex's like
F*** this is how I understand things to you and I are friends
God you are so petty
You can take this is like 2 minutes into the Raiders
Buddies now
Why would the ring of power Jeff
The ring of power is the military whatever they want
The military
You do whatever you want
So his argument is that be
Because the globalist control the military guys with
There
Okay no
Actually
The guys with guns have sworn to protect the country
Rain is there for
The globalist have this ring of power over that but in reality
The Oath Keepers are helping to
Contextualize
To the country
Very different very different thing
And therefore you can fight against your country if you want
Other things that
You are now part of our group
With inside
That's always worked out well
When was the last time having a separatist group that doesn't take the actual government
Sovereign or whatever is legitimate
Blackwater
So
Alex is we called ourselves the keeper
Alex is so thrilled to make a
He's really excited
Because this movement is just getting going
We're still a couple months away from the 4th of July when he sends out everybody
Deals Keepers with
Tea Party
But Alex
Good mood
Did he comes back from
Break
Sing along with a little song
He's clearly trying to
Implant in his audio
A mind
Is actually
Enough about the okay
And we're going to be best friends
Declaring
Looking
Thank God for the Renegade
Lord knows where we'd be
When it comes to Heroes
Renegade
The mountain power lawsuit
Right here
Is right here in Empire us
Looking everywhere for the rain
Counting
The police
Yorkipoo
I can play
Obama born
I want
Too and I think we
You can do this
Because this is public
Let's release A Spoken Word album
Of Alex doing
Urstyle shark in Word album
Guys by the way
Next episode 2 song
That you will not believe
Teaser
You'll forget by the next episode
And it will still blow your mind
Remember
Blow your goddamn
Going to have to
Anyway
There
These guys are clearly forming a bond
Talking about Lord the Rings
Talk about how great it is to fight depression
I can talk lord-of-the-rings that'll be fun maybe just don't be part of a white separatist
White supremacist other Lord of the Rings with everybody but you
Sorry
You're out
Ever
Here's what
I'm having a big issue
Innocent
There is
No
Nogla
Think of any Galadriel that you
You can put in there
Rob do is Legolas
I wish there was no context
You know
Who is Legolas and then we just move on I don't think Leanne Macado's around yet but she obviously
Remember
I would read this book since I was a kid
Alright anyway
Alex Vincent
Complaints about the world
Monster Cher
And then going to make some claims
That I don't think reality backs up
You have to DARE great ladies and gentlemen
Information
Show the other attack
Smash cut to all of the
The roots of this tree are
Forget 2000
Hate crime
Store hours
That's why
Keepers of stress that this was
Contemplated a plan before the election
We didn't care who got elected it didn't make a difference who was Kennedy president
Duty military
And veterans
Who's president
Impala 64
Former Navy SEAL captain
Fleur-de-lis of gathering of eagles
Hardcore conservative groups
What's a dangerous
Oh really are they became president
Neutral on political thoughts
Maybe now
Neutral group of people now get the danger
Wheaten Terrier
Weird
It really it really is hard to hear him say like
There's a hardcore conservative groups that probably wouldn't listen to dangerous
Hear the f******
It's so crazy to me it's so crazy
They weren't paying attention was elected now they're waking up
Right
Another clip
I love it
Complains about people
Bull shiting on other
Cuz I literally am back that
Glenn Beck hates Fox News
All the people that he's now like supper going back but all these other people who
In bed with
They're all fake
Alright
So Alex
Makes a proclamation
Think this is like
The moment where Alex
Texas like
I
Love
That's right anyway no one gets out of here alive
Free
That's all
Pikachu
So they want you to think it's hopeless
Like you're staring into the
Is is what they what they want you to see you'll think it's hopeless Crystal
And then I will discuss
Some of the problems
Just claim you know what I really
Violet militia
Expression
It's not about my life
Yours
Children
Maybe aren't alive anymore
Extort says one
One of the most Monster Bleeding Out Roofing
And then on the other end I will demonstrate
Positive negativity
They're starting to see the other side
You don't feel like you said we have we have the strength
The positive organization
Jordan
Provide free breakfast
Impoverished
Rhodes
Fellowship of patriotic
Listed people
Are united by their promise
Enlistment oath
Protect America from enemies foreign and domestic
I forgot that a lot of them are also currently
Law enforcement
Awesome closer analysis of their actions
Directions to Foster's
Terrorist
Subscribed
Crypto racist worldview
On April 15th 2009
Keeper Daniel Knight Hayden quote locked and loaded for the Oklahoma State Capitol
See what happens
Another maybe it's time to die
Let's see if I can video record the highway patrol at the entrance of the Oklahoma state capitol while trying to inform them of The Oath Keepers
I posted to the internet
Since I live on I live on this sorry f****** States
That's as good a place as any to start a war
And no matter what happened posted on the internet immediately and send it to Alex Jones
Tons of EX
He's such a
Positive member of
He would go on to say quote of the war will start on the steps of the Oklahoma State Capitol
I will cast the first stone in the meantime I wait the police start
Killing now I'm willing to be the
The first death
Though he wasn't a valued member of both the Tea Party
Is right-wing Outlets like
The Free Republic immediately began trying to paint Haven as a leftist
This was just a plot to make right-wing groups look bad
This happened a month after
Interview on Alex Jones
April
Two months they had a domestic terrorist
Stewart guys
On January 10th
2010 Ford Marina no keeper Charles Dyer was arrested on charges of raping a seven-year-old child
Authorities searched his home they found a grenade launcher that was reported stolen from California Military Base
Previously diary been charged with quote making disloyal comment or statement
In reference to YouTube videos get released reactively called for armed
Violent resistance
To the government
He was acquitted of the charges and will go on to produce videos where he literally said that
To become a
Terrorist
His word when Charles was due to appear in court for his trial
And ended up leading the FBI on almost
Weeklong Manhunt during which time he posted Crypt
Threats to law enforcement that they better not
Catch up with him
When he was finally caught without into
And tried the charges were the grenade launcher dropped when he claimed launcher and thought it was a
Flamethrower
I don't know
I guess I didn't know this was a nuclear bomb
Dodge Charger
30 years in prison
Legal trouble mounted and Light
Charles Dyer
He claimed the dire had paid the $30 membership fee
B
Become a member of the group
Rhodes Greece
You didn't want to own dire as one of his own members which is really difficult to square with the reality
Because video is produced by Oath Keepers list Charles Dyer is the group's quote official liaison to the
He was
He was their official liaison to the Marine Corps
To make matters worse dire it spoken at a Fourth of July 2000
And the publication
I hate trackers founded no trick by Stuart Road
Housekeeper members promoting tires appearance
Deliver one heck of a fiery speech
Again we see this trend continuing of people gleefully profiting off radicalized
7 people and encouraging them down as violent
Dangerous path
Then pretended they had nothing to do with them once the radicalized party
Is The Logical conclusion
Of the path they were on
Just don't see how this is relevant
Modern
Not at all I just don't see any
Unparalleled
Episode
It's so date
Then of course there was a case of Darren Huff
The oath keeper who plotted to take over Madisonville Tennessee with the help of his
Melissa buddy
We talked about this on the last episode so there's no need to dwell on this one
There's one interesting notes
Make your though about how these groups are too cowardly to own their own filth
On March 20th 2017
Jerome corsi got on the Alex Jones Show and told Alex
The Darren Hobbs
The rest was the result of the Playland
But it been revealed by Joe Arpaio and Mike zullo thanks for Snowden whistleblower
Dennis Montgomery
Course he was attempted to tide Darren Huss arrested with the Montgomery
Leaving aside that
The dentist Montgomery information is
Complete b*******
Houses under surveillance
Because he told bank teller that he was going to take over Madisonville
And the bank teller called The Authority
Never not
A guy who's playing this
To take over a
Like
So so then what
You doing and that you think that
You can hold
I don't know
And it's crazy but what you see here is that like
No matter what
Infowars in their Associates
It exists in
In a primary role
Who's white viola
White terrorism white militia violin
Because while at the same time
What because years later
Jerome corsi is trying to excuse Darren Huff
Steak over Mattis
Sissonville Tennessee
Because Darren Huff is a wizard
Bazinga birthday
He was also a really big Obama can't be president guy so it fits in with their oppression Narrative of
People who
Things they do
Because Jerome corsi wrote multiple books
So you have him going way out of his way to fix
Use this Melissa
Superman
Because it helps them
It was Matthew Fairfield we talked about on the last episode was arrested
Super making and housing a bunch of bomb
Including a Napalm bomb which according to experts is quotes
Berkeley design
Yusan other
Matthew Fairfield you of course
Was the president of the Cleveland chapter of the oak
Again
Not a pulp remember
2015 olds keeper John timer came to focus of the media after he started wandering
Around in front of
Phoenix
F*** Islam
Muhammad contest outside
In an interview with Anderson
Cooper after
Recuperar tri-tip
Explain
Clearly constituted product
Location
Some will probably argue that the signers that signed the Declaration of Independence was a bad idea back in their day
YouTube
The country by
Alright
Alright dude
Right
So
So what are you doing any good
Are you going to
Take over the country back
Well pretty soon after all that John would start a GoFundMe campaign dollars to help him live off the grid
Because before trying to kill him
The Grinch
Well
Well either wanted to fund living off the grid or two very publicly try to run against John McCain fries then it's
Living in hiding the running for Senate probably be nosey
That would be fun if you were living off
The grid wallet
The same time run
In June 2015 posted online
In June 2015 he posted online that he was the victim of hacks and he was going to disappear for awhile
Michigan senator Debbie stabenow
Because she voted for the Iran deal
He wrote the supporters quote we have chosen her as our first Target due to our strong ties with the Michigan State militia and
Operating a manner necessary for an operation like this
Hold on
So their plan is specifically targeting
A state with latch
Text gun laws
To use guns
No in a manner necessary for an operation like that alright alright
Document
Why would like gunball operation like this
It's really suspicious
Choosing a state
They're just going to stand around
Hold up
So they put like placards on their guns
Because they ran out of 2x
So they're holding up the guns and doing the whole life
It's easier than going to King
Michigan State
Like it's clearly militia organized positive
Though he had a good six months of
Publicly agitating
Against Muslims being an overall embarrassment of a person
This plan that he had to go and arrest Senator Debbie stabenow was a bridge too far
And your Keepers decide to go ahead and diss
Stem cells from him at that point
Probably smart
Laws to arrest people
Probably
You want to get that done ahead of time
Hey buddy buddy
You do what you got to do
Hanover Madison
Making Napalm bomb
Raping 7 year olds
We kind of got our disavowing game down
6 domestic terrorist you're like hold on
We're going to let you keep going but we can't have kids.
So John would go on to take part in the malheur wildlife preservation standoff and operated website where you sold fuk is
Bumper sticker
In August 2016 new sentenced to a year in prison
For conspiring to
Police from discharging their duties
Also
He has two kids and lived off.
Big government
Little pieces
Visit these same people who are bitching about entitlements right and he's
Find to run with malicious and try and rest fitting centers with lack gun laws
This year after Hurricane Michael 60 Keepers were arrested
Did Mexico Beach
Florida while they were out quote-unquote
Patrolling
They had their car painted up to look like an actual police car
Pickle beer
Heavily-armed
The actual
The Bay County Sheriff's Office
They're out there patrolling the streets
They don't know the area they don't know the community they don't know our laws and that lends itself to Danger
Please leave Law Enforcement to the profession
So Nikki is at least three people were like
We're going to rescue her
You're cops
They were hoping to find black people out doing things that look like looting so they could
That's what they were doing
Well that's because Florida has very lacks gun laws and very strong do you understand
Why there
Somewhere like that
That's that's
Specific
Oh yeah
These are just a few of the notable
Keepers who have run afoul of serious laws
Isn't a quince
Not a couple of
This list doesn't even begin to mention how they were involved in the Bundy
Sure how The Oath Keepers plan to arrest
The pope when he came to the United
This doesn't
Distance keeper showed up in Ferguson and quote
Almost exclusively white business
After the protest
It doesn't touch on how in the Berkeley and Portland protest in 2017
Propaganda
It worked hard to convey the idea that the
Police no keepers at work
Berkeley Police off officials
Naturally tonight
But after American Freedom Keepers militia member Todd kelsay was arrested I'm sorry was recorded helping
Police arrest protesters in Portland
So he's not a cop
It's not hard to see
Kernel of Truth
So what is The Oath Keepers
Is an out now
Working hand-in-hand with an organization that
Doesn't like
To stay there
Can you put always seem to act
I don't think
Like I don't know
I'm not I don't
Pick your ass up
Unfair
You have a situation where
I'm not going to say that
The Oath Keepers
AR
Operating on a very racist
But man there's a lot of them that are
And a lot of them
In many ways
Brotherhood
Forecastle
Trying to uphold the Constitution
Stream to take that to where they build bombs
Try and get into shootouts with
Police
End up killing people do these
The standoff
Jouer drama Hamid contest
In order to antagonize entire populations
The people and then bake
For money because
Cuz of the natural consequences of your actions
Lakeview Resort
Depended on that
At least the lease egregious
And then you see the
Systemic things about how big groups of them often
Show up late
This is like Ferguson
Like
In the aftermath of
Mexico Beach
Hurricane
You just be a systematic
And further than that
Uc's Stewart Roads
Doing very intention
Damaged
Control
People that he had buddied up with
And help down the
The path
Their conclusion
When someone who is the official liaison to the Marine
All ends up going bad
And getting arrested for raping a seven-year-old
Grenade launcher
Like what
Responsibility for that
6 News
When you have
Head of your
The one of the
Big cities in America by the way
Very large city
Not not a Podunk it's not Madisonville Tennessee chapter about keepers
Cleveland Ohio
He's caught with a Napalm bomb
I would like that one
Just
Just like a neighborhood
We're just added a guy has a Napalm bomb
It's at I don't like to think about that
Pretty f*****-up
So
The point I'm trying
To get at is
This Behavior
Is
A defining
Of the right
Right now
Will you see it with
Everything that's going on in the
All of the
Every time there's something
Sing bad that happens
What's a natural
Quince
The rhetoric that's put out the violence
Feed excusing of white terrorism
Aldi store
Whenever there is the bubbling over
Never there's this guy interested
True sending all the bombs
How dare you
Here's a picture of him at a trump Rally from years ago
Stickers on his truck false-flag at the setup look so clean
No it's the same thing it's
An inability to take
Responsibility for what
Put out into the world
They claim to be happy
We're on the hook for a pretty house
Yeah I know I am not
In any way that everybody on the left
Is grade
Taking responsibility
Future of
This world that we look at in the
The Patriot movie
Make the Liberty people
It's an inability to take responsibility for the reality of the shifter you put in
End of the world he goes all the way back
Their granddaddy
Behavior with his slider and ability is it specific
Feature not a bug you get the benefit of having what is essentially a
Violent extrajudicial intimidating people who otherwise would
Finally try and vote against
The same time claiming loudly enough and frequently enough that is not part of your group
Believe you that they won't do anything
It's
Rodger Stone
Let's get out of here while screaming
If you all are demons and you must fall
It's a it's a modern dilemma
I don't know I don't know
Half out of it but some people responsible
I don't know how you do it
But you got to do it
One of those things where
I don't I don't want to paraphrase this
Too badly
But
If you are still working
White
Violence
I know it when I see it
You know
You're like the Supreme Court definition of pornography
Write this blanket law
Supremacy is
Is now in prison for
For two years
Because how would you
And how could you enforce that in any way that isn't
AI random
Like I know you're I know you're just a dude on Twitter trying to do whatever but f*** you your
About it
Are you doing
I know
The best way to go about it
But I also know based on
We played earlier this episode
It won't work
Asian
And helping people understand
Because of people truly understood beat like the motivation
The people
Or
Really just trying to get your money they're really just trying to cause
Trouble that they can capitalize off of
So then let's talk about that
Cradock dialogues
You hope you be able to have
With people and be able to get to the bottom of
All roads leading back to
Basically
A couple of
Big Lots
Can't understand the basic premise of a vax
Steam where it's like
You know how you've been sick before
You know how there are worse ways to get sick
Don't get those
And people are like
There's no way people are going to be able to process propaganda for a reason to Harkin is straighterline
Passion about how those studies
Links vaccines
Is autism
That's a bit
Nice starting ground hopefully you'll be able to demonstrate to them like
All of these people know
But look at all those people who are telling us
All of those people who were telling you the vaccines
Link to autism
Know very well.
These studies are
Aren't accurate they aren't real but they're pushing
You anyway because it serves
Their political why else would they put in a needle Dan
If you were going to give me a vaccine come in a pill
What
Alright you got me you got me hard right fine
But you could do that with just about any of these narratives if someone were willing
But you're demonstrating
Exactly.
The demonstration of that is
Earlier where Alex plays the clip of the cop
Very well
Explaining what the miac report actually says
It doesn't do a lick of difference
Alex uses that report still
Years after this
Duplex
We need to increase the population of deer
Unsustainable level
And then put out
Press release
Everybody can kill deer we got it
It's the best thing to eat for the environment
People are busy
Week or two
While they're in the forest
Living off the grid
Or doing whatever it is
We sneak into Congress
We do all the right stuff and then when they get back there like what just happened here this plan isn't going to work
Just do this
We just do a sleight-of-hand like a with a baby in a cookie just like all the cookies over here all the cookies over here is playing
Not going to work because in order to get
Depopulation
Rdr2 the level
You're going to need either
Fully restricted
I'm really mad
Start
Yeah I'm not sure
To say okie Preserve
Generally
Organization has
As a whole
Been a very negative
Organization
I beg to differ
I know you run it
But you're wrong
Alright
Now when kids are like
9 or 10
We all send them to the
And they all take one test
Where it's just like there's a woman
Is it not even that just like a speaker with
Blonde hair
You're just as kind of like
Oh you look alright
No big deal just like Barry pass
Passive-aggressive
Then we're like
I'm not saying that we're going to put children into a garbage
You're literally just buy them in a generally described in a dream Alex at this is still closed
Some of his terrible nightmares
Hasn't been working
I know but that's not going to work
What if we put blonde hair
Farragut
Love's
Stewart Rhodes
And it shows in this next
Where he
Is over the moon with
I like
That
Start run operations
I had to leave that in because like Egypt
You hit that breaks so hard
Because he's so excited about this
Although
During this time there was one time
For one of his sponsors
Call home game we played a commercial in the password
Hookup site
Everybody knows that those are real
Real estate agents are the most trustworthy
Casinos Brothers Liquor property
It's called entire Library Daleks has home again
The name of this
Play Rock yesterday
It's all good
So if we get to
To The Logical
Conclusion to this
To hear very clearly
Alex Jones endorsing
Keepers
Both Dash Keepers. Blogspot.com
Text
The enemy
You have to be involved
We are we have to shatter
Which is why most of the numbers are inaudible
Synonymous you write letters and post things are
Is good
Past the point of return and the committee will follow
Closest you're going to get from Alex Jones to a full-throated
Endorsement
That's brutal
The first stage of our 2009 Vespa
Navigation is complete
March 19th
Is when Alex Jones got involved with
The Tea Party
We
Didn't even consider like when you first started this investigation
You did not have Oak
Keepers on the list of things we were investigated
That's the most obvious popular thing
And then you
You get the reveal that it's The Oath Keepers
That makes way more sense than the Tea Party
The Oath Keepers are out there doing harm when we went back
2015 sound like
He doesn't like Trump but he's saying Putin is the truth
Yeah
Not even really nationally relevant Oath Keepers
To show up and be
The way that Alex
This is a theory
Yeah I believe that this marks the beginning of Alex Jones getting
Proper it is the remains to be told about the deterioration
Politics that happen
A very good strategy to definitely have nothing to do with a black president
A very good strategy to ensure that the Overton window is shifted in the direction you want
Is the offer two options
1 miles in one XP
The two sides probably don't even have to like you
The mild side says the extreme is childish and not Siri
Extreme side says
Magnemite
Controlled opposition
Climate guarantees that more people will sign up with the mild side
But the very nature of their overlapping rhetoric
Doordash
Heading in the direction towards the extreme
The people will join with a mild and ultimately find it on satisfying
And head for the more extreme stuff
Becoming acclimated to the extreme side
Go find the answer as to why they weren't Satisfied by the mile.
Because it was controlled opposition all along
Because the thing is
The pipe doesn't go the other direction
In this example Glenn Beck doesn't ever deescalate
No one gets free of Alex Jones as propaganda by becoming the Glenn Beck
No one tee programs from The Oath Keepers by falling in love with
Peaceful anti-tax
And realizes that specific action is
Is the best way to effect
If they want to see
The slide goes downward
And every convert to
Tea party is one more likely Patriot movement recruit
And waiting
I'm not proposing that this was an elaborate plan or intent
That would be absurd
Conspiratorial thinking
But I am suggesting that looking back on this
There could be no worse setup
For the maintenance of a healthy body polish
Once the GOP started embracing the
Tea party there possibly knowingly or possibly unwittingly embracing not only the extreme side
They're also embracing the mild side
It really only ever exist
Be a conduit to
The way that we talk about our
Text right so
It turned into Clinton being center-left
And in response to that the center
Went as far right as a possible
Is gone even further
Center-right
And center-right has turned into crazy right and crazy right has turned into the violent militia group
Bright all the way progressives are over here like
Which was the center-left begins to insist
It's the only way to win elections is
And in response to that they couch out and they make even further concessions to the hard right
Extreme right
Even more radical
How to put a button on them
What we see here I'm sir
Is the
Beginnings of
Alex Jones
Becoming the
Extreme
Extreme version
Which is characterized
This is his way to get in on the app
Uc's Glenn Beck
Be very successful
Without having to feel like you sold out
And I think that will carry through
Even when he starts associating worth
The Tea Party
Carry this torch of
I'm the real version of it this is
This is the media the globalist painted version of we are the 1776
And they're a bunch of bulshit
Glenn Beck
Whichever
Again in retrospect
So much more sense than he does
Jumping on with
I still have to act out even again
Esports over and over again
Anytime we go and
Can we find the kernels
Pieces of Alex
Should have thought of that
Play Ganesh Chalisa
Because now we know
As opposed to just gas
So we have this miac report I think
With Alex Jones bringing Lawns at cop
Playing at audios
The cop very clearly
Niagara Falls about
And it's not making a dent
It's in the propaganda arm
We speak of the hope
Of engaging
Or at least with people like
You see the hopelessness
What's going on
As opposed to it just being a misunderstand
In addition to that you see
Here
The introduction of
And what you're going to end up seeing
Contacts why on the last episode when I told you I went back and I listen to
The time around when that guy got caught with a Napalm bomb
His house who is beheaded
The Cleveland Show
Keepers and Alex's radio sign
It makes
He is with
So he's not going to cover when one of them has a Napalm bomb
Warehouse
No
Wait
I think
That's
If I were in the room
With Ron Paul
To other asset
Right
Whenever they tended
The
And we would have been
Like everybody we've been talking
Having a good old time
And then there were two men that
She know everybody has a good laugh and then there's
It's just that low before you get in
In that law
I would have been like
Miac report
More like Viagra port
And then I would have
Been carried out of that room on everyone Shield hero
Yeah so I see a little bit of what
Does portents for the
I obviously don't know exactly how it all is going
Going to play out and I'm still interested to see
Exact path that goes down but
I mean
This B totally in line with the Alex Jones
Existence from Vandeven in
The present-day as
Right right wing
Terrorism
White terrorism
Apologist
Should have known
One more clip here real quick
This is just the end of the interview
Between Alex
We commend you
The website again
He come in
You never see it in her
Interview like that on
On the show like it
Well at least he was trying to appear to disagree with David in this one in might as well just be like
Like you just watched a meat
Like the two of them.
Oh my God you look
I would I would
Like
Dreamcast
In one of these roles
So Kate Beckinsale is one of the other one
Beckinsale
Whatever
She was in the oven
Underwear laundry
Probably
This is where we end our adventure have struggled
Screw listening
Do all these boring episodes but I'm glad
We getting out of the
This reveal of Alex Jones giving his endorse
Characterize the next
Gears of his program
The entire Direction
He goes I think it will facilitate
So many of the narrative like I think they were going to
To see a lot of these things
We've been tracking
In terms of these thieves
Anachronistic politics
He has whether it be
He's anti-police
An early too
Is against net neutrality
Our situation is support of Palestine
Beginning of him
Because of the way that is prospective
We're a political we're neutral on Olive
We're also hardcore conserve
You know like
Around
What's up that's the in for him
Because that allows him to
Feel like
I'm still being a political this isn't a political group
And as he descends further into that group of course he descends further into hardcore
Conservative
I think a lot of it is true
I want
I mean we're getting a little speck
But I wonder how much of that is
Conscious and how much it is
Just going down that road I would I would
Suggest I think some of it
I think you changed themselves like
In order to fit
Whoever
Is benefactory is it a certain time
Much like you know well doctor group is around
He's way more into
To the medical woo
And stuff like that
Caregiver
In financial source
It's all about the economy
You know you can see
See these sort of
These changes in weather going on with
Whoever is fun
Unlike Megyn Kelly
Thru-and-thru from the Fox News to the NBC
You kind of got a tip you know you don't
We will see what happens
Future but for now
Real website
Twitter adknowledge
Facebook
Facebook / knowledge fight
Flash.
Blogspot.com
Dot-org
We also have a group
All that stuff you know you've heard about the
Now I can't do Keepers haven't killed anybody
Definitively but
Probably
There's still a little bit of
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color