Alexandra Thurston color
Where to celebrate Halloween
I know so little about all the way up
I know nothing about Halloween on a G lyrics
And they wouldn't allow me to celebrate
Partner is
She's dressing up for Halloween
She's going to school dressed up and
She's got a Halloween party
Going to do the whole thing
She is a teacher
Meijer
Thankfully that was one that they gave him there
Yeah me and my brother dressing up in like sort of evil issuer like
So that was nice
Simple
Live like the satanic panic
Ciara just never ends
Just like we're still uncle
Who is a psychologist
Who wrote a couple books about multiple personality disorder
And the only cure
Negative
Wild stuff
Traditional attitudes
Number one
A number two
Absolutely
Going over this house like we need something fun
Fun because it is
Is Ben straw
Whether it's been in the present-day or even in the past like
We're still hitting on even when we're back in
In 2000
Very relevant
Things about it
Different
So we can all just move on
It's still very
Rottweiler with in the
The conversation
I'm so where we let have to do
Whenever we get into those mode
Is we have to
Take a step back
A visit
Kerry Cassidy
And the world of project
Camelot Hellyeah
Get that together with them
Say it. They tell her stories about space
There's also a lot of weird stuff
We just don't cover about like a
Like she just did a reason
Two-part video series about
Christine Baisley Ford and
Being mind-controlled
I give a pass
This episode probably took more work than most Alex Jones up
Alright those episodes involve
Research
Involve a lot of
My time
This episode took me
Listening
Project Camelot being like
No
Is not the right one okay
This was this was a browsing in the cereal aisle
Email recently from a listener wanted us to go over
Super soldier
Episode
Kurt Russell
The episode the super soldier
That you had on
La
Pretty wild
Steph
Some nonsense
And I started looking into Miss Shepherd
It's all true
No it made me really sad
The picture started to come together of a woman
Whose family put her in a home
Oh no
Like our policy
Basically
Project good and well
Until we're making
King fun of somebody who seems like they're actually
Struggling
I know it's a good couple hours of
Live my life
Now it is like
We can't go over
B2 hours of us
King Von
Someone who's my
And that's not that's not what we're here to do
Make your own show about us vets
Us what we do to Alex
You accurately research
Source everything
Stop
Number of other episodes
We need to
The good
And so finally
I'm scrolling through
Episode
About a guy
Captain Jay's
I like a cat
Absolutely
Yes you're going
Information about Mars
And I'm like well we got to know about
AAA similar in size to Earth
That's all you need to know right now is that this episode came out
It was just after she started interview and Marc rich
She's in a little bit of a
I will say that these are the sort of people that she was willing to interview back pain
So she's left stridently confident in that everything she knows from
Is this correct
And is more in a very
Stage
Left full of herself
Alright she has Alexa video
Mark Richards
Is blustery
Sociopath Behavior
Maybe a little bit
When she gets in the room with like
And Eddie page
The telescope
She's able to meet
What is always important to remember that one of our episodes
Bus station I will never remember his name
What's important
Which one of these guys
She'll be able to mold their narrative
To help State hers more PL
Captain Jay's
I think that she has more of a like all right I'll let this guy
Whatever
Like we can get out of this
Evan
It leads to stuff like this out of
Contacts dropped
Come to the house yet
Appreciate
This information and Anna and you coming forward however
Appreciate from Mike
To say that
This was going to harken back to an earlier time
When I believe Carrie to be the most credulous woman on the planet
I get what you're saying
You know how this is bulshit it sounds like b******* to I'm suggesting back then she had more
More of an operation going where it's like
Nah
Pictures of every one of our as episodes we just and would like
Yeah I'm going to pass on this one it is just
Isaac modern-day Carrie would have taken Captain J when he came in
I hear things
What you saying
Outlandish
Yeah well from the information
I've got maybe it's possible
And try and get him to be like
You do now that you mentioned it yet that's like that
You know this is pretty absurd right have you considered yourself because
What
What's
Alright this is a great our talking
We're going to let you
Outlandish
I teased on the last episode
So we got a song to play
Yes
And I don't know you have been bothering me with how excited you are about this song
For 4 days now
That leaves my instincts
To say that we should
Should wait I'm not that cruel so I will go ahead and play it
Guys
In doing some research and fiddling around looking
Project Camelot world
I found
The back in 2014
Kerry Cassidy made an album
What's show Siri Cassidy made an album called
I believe I don't know if I'm up Spotify
But
Don't
Here is a little kids okay
Of
The track rebel g
Scleroderma
Raiding party are abducted permanently office
I need to pause for a second
A second just to say that the song is called space
Command the album Rebel 3
If you were watching 4th Matrix movie Underground
We have many uses to visiting races
Duvall as a food source and maybe others
Allies plays for building
Serving various races
As in scientific study versus the desirable vacation
Precious stone outside use the granite
Other systems.
Medic program human females
Blackstar Darkstar energy energy
Multiverse humans on the level with other ET Races they don't appreciate
Futaba
Okay
We have of
Space command
Could be an early really early Thievery Corporation track like that really doesn't sound that tariff
Really I'm not saying this is there later or they're even later
I went
Just turn this into a music
Target
But
You know
Be replaced
Gold standard
It really does make me happy in a lot of ways
I told you earlier I was coming
Still satisfies
So good
As we opened every episode with project
It says her name
But things go slightly different
Immediately reduction
And we have
Here with us today and this is the very impromptu
Set up
Captain
No actually
Clear-cut
To Mars and part of the Mars program
The understand that from the disagree
There's a billion different ways
If there was any astronomical astronomical movement around the time when he says he was
Supposed to have leftovers
For specific
Play more at the beginning
The show cuz she doesn't know what the f*** is coming
We're going to be crazy
It says he's like
Or doing his interview I have no idea
We can't prove this is your Dosha
We can't even prove this guy how long has she been doing the show is this
Houston's like probably three years ago I mean
The beginning date of her show on YouTube
Investigation
Things and stuff like that
Kind of nebulous
Sushi
She's been on
For like 6
7 years okay
3 years ago
Like 20-30
Alright
Search for 2014 2015 right next
Probably just recorded that
You need to know
Is this
View is happy
Very soon after
Interview with space
Super soldier
Randy Cramer
The guy who we did our first episode of
The guy who woke up in his bed that 80 and then playing for the game whatever
Space-time and it's
Various Alien Children on Mars
Ashley Stoller a protection unit or whatever Kramer Who come out and done his
Interview on Project Camelot
Which is relevant
Because he goes by the name
Captain k
This guy heinze Manchester
Men In Black J & K
Literally wrote that.
I've literally wrote that down
I don't think that their nest
He's necessarily trying
Make that connection
Is he
Okay then second
And I came before Randy Cramer in
He's going to say that
So many times
He's so petty about how do you say
Okay
Means that you specifically however chose your name
In order to make it look like you were before this
Because he was
He's older and Eve
I'd like I was around
20 years before he was up there in
Lovin You could have called yourself well
His name is very anyway
Nation that I don't appreciate
SuperShuttle do you got plenty coming up
Him trying to talk
About space weirdness
And then Randy Cramer came along
He's like
So I welcome and introduce yourself
I'm using a named Captain J because
It is my first initial and also
It's the letter before
I'm online
Online it
I realize that
No one was listening to me before Randy driver showed up
Cuz I got to strike while the Iron's hot
Can get in
As we guy who came before him
Even though I'm
Quite literally by any and all definition
The guy who
A week
Opportunism
Personify
I'm going to get in while the group
Super soldier drugs make you sound like Anna
Side effects to get rid of
I'm not
Listen I'm against the military industrial complex
Super soldier
I want maybe an imposing voice maybe the very least with you know I'm a very
Nasal Tanner I would prefer a thick based
You need to pump
Super soldier with that
Because you're assuming first about this guy's a super soldier
You're Assuming he's a super soldier
You're assuming that the government deep something
To him
Oldies maybe maybe erroneous
Do I know that you're making those exceptional because he's comparing himself to Randy
Turns out he's not a super soldier at all
And his story
Is convoluted as f***
I will do my best
To pull the strings in order to unlock
Untangle this thing but I have not gordian Dan I say to you now
No confidence in my abilities
I will do my best
Look at you and everybody
Absolutely
In the next clip
Captain J goes on
Explain
Some of the
The organization
He was involved
I think Carrie asked
Very basic question
And it almost ruined the entire it
Starting at the trial
Songs Navy and Marines at sign
That matter
All the way through that
Rover myself
How do you go from one organization to another
Well
Fake programming
Not answer
Give me a year
1963 when the first Mars probe went up which is actually a small man
Stuff that has been
AOL
I will accept that if we're going to go any further
Give any specific
Flying around
Not an answer as to why you were in multiple arms of the service
Mid 5363
I guess so
Disguise
Alright
You've got loving a man who's
Invalidated
I have a lot of trouble with this sort of a Project Camelot episode
Years is tough
Because
You should be able to
I do not know
You thought about it though probably
To put together like
Secret space program
If you were
Acuity about when things happen
If you were going to go do an interview specifically about those things
You'd be able to sit down ahead of time be like well that happened right around the same time as X Y or Z
Before this event in my life
Before Zach
Rhetoric
What specific information
You did that question come up
He hasn't been
This guy might be
Might be making a lot of s*** out
I just love
The confidence of a guy who'd
Just has no idea what
We talkin about huh
Confident I am literally
If I just say things stridently
Powerful
Yeah yeah yeah
And this is one of the like like
This type of Project Camelot
It's destroying the world
This this this type of Project Camelot episode
Kind of a challenge
Because we have a guy using an alias
MJ
Am I supposed to find out anything about who this working person actually is
Also
I believe his name is just
It probably why probably
Simpsons
Mark Richards I can look into that
Pass
Please find more information
Volume to flesh out the picture
With Captain J I got none
I just have his word to go on
Eevee research path to go down
No just find anyone who has been in both the Marines
And the Navy
No
Probably
Butler
The Navy submarine
He's in the CIA
The mid-fifties to 1960
C3 he's involved in something or other
Specific
Dora
Jets
Now is he not even know when Rockets were invented
Unimportant
Deep sea October Sky
Okay
Jake Gyllenhaal
In this next
None of those things
We've already talked about bear any relevance
To this Mexico
Because he's going to jump forward to the 7
Talk about something else
Good that I believe
But there's more like
Carrie's not great at like nailing him down on
The story he's going
To tell for the rest of this has to do with stuff in
So all that stuff about him being in the Navy and the Marines
CIA MKUltra
I don't think
Just to demonstrate
How
Blurry
His backstory
Run away we go to the
Part of a small group
Honda Pilot
Text message
1960 Prius
Wichita
Orbitz
And the same pilot
Look at
Defying all laws of physics
The technology we have available to us
1063 Tamar's
Documented
Being a teeming civilization
Let's find out more let's go home
How much
1963a life support
I don't care about that he's a child at the time
At the time yet
That is a problem we've always had lights
Speed travel technology
Towards the most important
How did all of these ridiculous
Don't know how far planets are exactly
Bitdownloader
It's a joke.
Mars is a jaunt
Jupiter is a bit of a long walk sure and then Pluto
One of the things that I find most
Sing about the center
In 13 Reasons Why
Is
It introduces us
To so many new alien races
Pizza spider leadership
Two brothers the man
Grazed the grades are always there
This gentleman Captain J has a
Very different take on the grill
Probably why Carrie says that this is ludicrous.
We have the
Polly ATM
We have
I already said rafters
Did we have in Vietnam
Yeah there's a lot of
Bunch of new
Draco
Break up
Wrapped up with reptilian
So
We get it we get
And
It starts to be introduced
Like
Between say 6370
Well that's when everything happens
I think
Talk about
As opposed to
Considerate
Local
However
Show me the flying saucer
Just never went away
Okay
So now if you're going exactly
What is just
Is that if you go to Mars
You will find
They're not really aliens
Cuz they're our neighbors there yet
There are silver flying crafts
Legend
Always been around never really went away or not
So this is this is
The world that we are now interjecting ourselves in
This is the basic setup
You know what I do like
About this
Is that this guy is
Drinking locally
You know everybody else has been talking about Interstellar long time including
You really break the very least
This guy Progressive illegal immigrants are our neighbors
That is that that makes me feel very uncomfortable
Right right
Hey there for Mars
Mars is just a skip away
Okay
That's what he's at he's like somebody who's like listen
Indiana still part of them
Let's not pretend that we need to close out
Sojourn
I told you
It would be wrong
To assume
The Captain Jay's
Is a space Soldier
You need
No is
Diplo
That doesn't make sense
Honorary title
Jerry does literally have to do one of the later Clips what are you you are the pilot
But
You the hero
Okay
Introduction
So you don't want to come out
And be like I am the most
Important person
In all of space
Unless you're parked right
Captain Jay's
Little more modest
A little more humble but now we get to high
Liberated bar
Key to everything
We finally managed to identify
He liberated the
Evil ones of Legend
He freed them freed Mars
Who was piloting
Where they are going
And what a word
Finally
All the species on Mars and the two
So we really
Had this meeting
Shut up
By virtue of a secondary Enright
This isn't right you Kathy
Powerful alien
Because these people down here on Earth
And so they were able to
Stop
Large degree
She do the activities
And in order to
And meeting with
Multi-million races
Pretty much
Liberation day
You're funny pretty funny ad
Powerball
Powerful
Trisexual
The beginning of our
That was a lot of talking
There are more than two gender
It means there's three
Things to come he does not explain that in the time being
What we learned
Where is that
Grave
In facilitated meeting of the minds
Of all of these races
Including our route
Like the pleiadian aliens
Ender's Game come out
I must Express
Zach's Opposite Worlds you the carry-in
The greys are evil
Reptilian aliens that come around and kidnap people
Which are starting to get a sense of why this guy is only been on once
Following my previous argument that if Mark Richards
Evil meaning
Good
People and he's calling the people he called evil good
Support
Three or four days
Track
Real
Light on the beat
Store to get out or anything like that
We figured out what everybody wanted we all got what we want
When he finally does give a little more detail about it
Even more hilariously absurd
You know we have our take on this
Mars
Here's what Carrie
And asked you about
Because it's
WinCo
It's not clear
It is a little convoluted
Yeah
So she wants him to get back
Debased
She wants to talk about
Like where
Did this
Where did your awareness come from
Because I think
She realizes is going to be an uphill battle
Let's get a little more report to me about the
Beginning let's start let's start how did the center
Evolve on Mars
Notoriously inhospitable place
That's good response
More of the backstory
And she asked about that
Route
Without verbalizing it
It's a prank being played on people that carries
Because a few years later we living in the present
Carrie is a steady pace
So here is a little anecdote
From
For Captain J
And this ends
I blurt
Hi
Anything pulled in
Ameren
But innocent
During that time
When I was a child
Why don't want to talk about it
Cuz you guys broke child labor
Illegal
Virchow's work this hard
I love the idea.
Every child labor laws
Weirdo
The Olsen Twins then you could get away with that s*** if you got twins
Makes your butt
It almost died out but it almost makes me believe
Kind of a weird line
Obviously child labor laws aren't
Play you're making all this up
I don't talk about that cuz I was a child illegal to make me work
This guy is coming from a bad play
But I like where his ideals are going so far
He say he's fighting in space battle
You just started s*** Outsource are these people alien
Are solar system
Children have to work
No nope
It is interesting you might be
The craziest but most reasonable person
Metaphorically stand behind buddy what he is representing obviously
Sorted it out is like no we don't need laser gun
I believe we need to do any Recon we just needed
To find out that they were there we went around once
Emma
Sorted out
Whatever that means
So
Seems to like
I mean
This guy's already said
He was Navy and the Marines mcia
Answer carry once made it all the way through the mk-ultra Baptist Church
Cloud from
MK Ultra
Haven't talked
Kramer knows that Randy
Kramer has an imagine
Legendary military liaison
A sponsor who is there telling him this is okay for you
All that stuff
So she wants to know
If Captain
Has a similar situation
Pre discussion
For example
He has a person behind the scenes
Who's backing him who is a military officer
Lorne Michaels
What's the people from the 50s or early 60s
Real quick. Is a reasonable thing to say at the end of his
A butt
I want to just say that like
What you just waiting
Whenever someone asks you a direct question
Your answer is
Usually means you're just making sure
So the only no I don't have a personal sponsor I was just
Have record
Abuse activities
Those records
Will be there
Oh yeah that sounds like
Really believe in good things real glass-half-full kind of
Information
Transparency is their business right if anybody comes in like a was camp
Flores
So you should know.
Is not playing
Where is proof
He did all this stuff
This like this clip makes me laugh so hard because he explains the proof
And where you can find
Any of the stuff that I say about Mars
I'll be very careful only to
Important information that I know
There are records of apparel Mart and other places
Can be verified
There's proof of it which is on Boston
Their record
You only have to go to Mars to get them
Love that totally awesome
Conspiracy theorist use about like the idea of
Everything that I'm saying
In a bunker deep under the Vatican
Give me the secrets of maybe
Existing the Vatican bunker underground people don't worry about
Do you want to prove
It's the same thing with the Akash
People talk about
These records
Is all of humanity that only exist in the astral realm you can access and Subway
Itsfunneh
It's fun to think about
Not fun to rely like base your life on
Edward
That's where it gets murdered
That's how you can kind of generally talwin
Just go to Mars
Break the ground please buy my shirt
Or whatever
Did you hear the Trump just issued an executive order
Leasing all of
Demars.
Working on it
Temp today
Is a day to remember
Both the good and the bad
The good
Is the correct lease test out this prop
The bad is
They immediately reported with no research whatsoever that Trump was going to issue an executive order
Right right
Trump says he'll sign executive order Banning Birthright citizenship
Trump signs executive order saying he can fly
You're not making any sense
Seems like a modern
Simultaneously
And that's where this is no place for reality
The Forbidden we're learning about space
We do not need to bring
We've got a lot of s*** that needs sorting out here
That conversation
For Friday today
Where in space
So in this next clip captain
Very clearly
He does not
Which is already
But it gets much more in-depth
I was sleeping one night
Woke up
I walked out into a field
Or maybe 150
What's up
Humanoid
Near future
Harmony
Sort out
Play Far Away
Shut up
ABC
You know intelligence agency
Yeah
This interaction with the gray
I don't understand anybody
20 minutes
Few days later released later and now they're along with
Keep it simple
Australian severe
Series of events went down
Bi-Mart
Meeting with the local
Matt
I guess you would say to me
Temperature of Mars
Supported by them
I see alright
Lucas Grave Art
Good
They've come down and check for whatever reason
Be there while we sort things out with these silver saucer aliens
Subscribe
Not an abduction experience as being like
Took us up they were like you folks are going to help us out later so check that out
I don't know what the 20 minutes part is that makes it so funny
Took 20 minutes either too little or too long
Dismissive detail
The same time it's kind of like
No big deal 20 minutes
It's like you're talking about a work meeting that like kind of a nuisance playlist
Disrupted my story later we saw sure why I needed to wake up for that quote
During the day but no 20 minutes no big deal with the bad everything is
Very weird
It's great
Scraped she wants to know
Carrie wants to know
Captain Jay's
The question is Randy Cramer
Not personally but I remember him or I remember the whole project
I don't think
Find your somebody breaking the ice maybe I
Sean what happened before that
Things from Randy Cramer
Interview I remember I remember I remember
Because I listen to interview
Later in the interview you'll go on to talk about how like
Randy Cramer was
Was existing in this world that was like
I stimulated fighting thing that was going on that wasn't even real
Or something like that
But also it doesn't make sense
It still has something
To do with the silvercraft B
Yeah but simulated fight Zone still has something to do with
Nefarious silver
But according to history they had already
Sorted it out by then
Is because they ran all these complex
Combat
Situations are they realize that this was going to go well
So why even bother fighting
You just sort it out anyways so you might as well just giving you the because Randy Cramer
Situation would have
Ten Years After
Randy Cramer
Went back in time
That was after him
And especially according to Captain
He makes it so clear over and over I came before
So is he sorted it out with his being
Then why is there this
For the stimulated fight Zone
It makes no sense I will tell you that
Further makes no sense
The idea that they had worked it out and banished silvercraft beings from the universe that were meddling
With the Earth and Mars
All this really negative stuff
They sorted that out in the seventies
And there's been no substantive difference
In the world
From the 70s
In terms of like
Some
Mastiff
Everything is better now
You know everything
No matter where we can never figure out where to land on the
Good evil alignment of these aliens
I mean 88
With the way he's dealing with time though like I could have been the mid-50
She's going to be in the midst
You could be wrong
On their way out they killed all the reformers on it
Maybe maybe those silvercraft beings
Protecting Martin Luther King
Rsk
They were treated silver beans
Because now we got that dead Martin Luther King jr.
You never know
F***** up I got to say
Anyway, Terry wants to know if Captain Jay's
And his answer
What
I really do
Any one of them
You saw the moon landing for the first time
That's of course you do. Proof of aliens
You're on the phone look at that
Do you know what happened
The Moon tonight they look at that I know you probably you probably pass out
Overtaken with wonderment like it would be so crazy
Ability ideas like oh my God look at that that is not proof of alien
Group of exactly what you're saying
It's a boon to listen to
First person to stand on the Earth
That's what you have to say you're not like
All the goddamn movie I think it's 11
I think it was for like zero gravity type stuff sometimes physical training and that I'm sure
Days of it were like
Kool-Aid
If you breathe super heavy you're probably going to die
I also we don't want that on your text
To chapter 4
The title
Cuz it will play better later
I disagree
The reason so many people
Stages because
Just acted like you were big zimin like
Water park world of food are you shiting me
You got all soaked
Considerate
Standards of
Decorum
Didn't allow that kind of
Even graduated the MKUltra
Uno's
So in this neck
Georgia
I think you might be innocent
Jordan
Are you
I'm trying really hard and
Don't talk over there
Journey
I have
Such a fundamental problem with
The very idea
Of what he's expressing
The population up there
It has to happen
Credible
Artifact
Real quick I just need to make clear because
He didn't know if he'd ever stepped foot on the Moon
We're back to Mars
Typically about being on
Across the other side of the crater
Where
Human
Humanoid
Never seen anything like it
Couple people
Indescribable
It would be too much
And we ran into an Easter Island humanoid
Maybe 10 or 11 ft tall
Easter on guy with the hat
Just like them starlings at Target
So now we have a new alien race to consider Easter Island people
The critic
How they're worth
Coronavirus
Yes of course I remember that I will never forget that those are real people
Absolutely
Is there supposed to be like that I'd like the Easter Island carvings are actually Giant
Lego deep underground
I guess so yes
I mean this is a fun way to
Incorporate that
I don't know what you call it
Weirdo World Easter Island
It is it is a piece of that
To see him be the one who brings that in
Easter Island head aliens
Here's my here's my question
Why is it that step
Easter Island
I'm not sure that even wanted staff
Wrote down the steps
On the other side of the crater
There were
Right
Can you solder
What is the next step is the next Beavis centipedes
Easter Island people
Show me for a loop
To see the Easter Island
Further
Weather
When I heard that clip
Be wrong
Thought that like
Meeting the Easter Island guy wasn't the step
It was incidental
I thought it was
I thought it was something that like we did these first two steps and then we wander through the tunnel of you found any Island Man
That's coming through the tunnel and that I like I felt something Bubba
I told her I was like hey sorry and then it turned out to be a 20 ft tall Easter Island
I thought that might be what he was saying I'm not entirely sure problem with the whole thing
So when you go to Mars
Be slowly acclimated to alien existence or else you're going to freak out
Flying around
Three-sided only 20 minutes
Flying something
Strongly disagree from the literally no reason for them to play this game of like
Oh dip your toe in the water is fine
Timetable for the Seahawks
It kind of sounds like this whole thing is taking a couple hours
Somewhere between
Liberated
Captain Jay's sorted out
Because
They were being
I guess terrorized by the silver saucer
That sounds good
You can't see through the glass we see through a glass Darkly
Only the Lord
However you want
Is the work of the Lord
Because it helps us see about both liberation
And who is he
Silvercraft
Liberation day
What do you mean
Silver saucers leaving our system
Lumineux whitening for
Tomorrow
Talk about that later
Mars
Problem
Our planet
Calling them silver saucer
The beans
Driving those
You said we're aunt
Gravity
What would be the mail
Highly telepathic
Fly with their mind
Set the trisexual group of warm-blooded
Make
Wawa
And water bears
So
Does he
Is is
Warm blooded
Water bears are like those might
Microscopic
Yeah
I love the idea of
Actual
Anytime you hear somebody with that thick Southern
You're never not going to like
Lower their estimation of
Be there
Intelligence
But at the same time if you heard
Einstein just being like
There's a s*** ton of Relativity going on there
Matter is basically energy
Okay
What you got or not
So you're getting from this
You better believe there is
Stop listing whatever you say something stupid like there's a hole
Galactic
But that's probably true like okay
It is
Listen
There is a whole hell of a lot of radiation
Wherever that may be
Weather
A lesbian like HomeBase
Almost
I thought you meant the center of the Galaxy
I don't know
I don't know that to be the case I'm just going on context clues I think he's talking about it as home base
Sure
In different parts of the Galaxy there are varying rates
Radiation
So wherever he's talking about is the place they come from there's a lot more of it then
Normal
And they are a trisexual
Again
Really not what he's trying to say
No also
I want to just try and explain what
He's talking about
So
He defined
Gmail
As the wasp
Okay the males as the water bear
And then the third gender what she doesn't really
Explain order
Detail at all
I don't understand what you have trouble with you
I don't
Right right
Sherman and the third gender is this
United Way
Certainly not
Right if you want
I don't understand the role of the snake I don't understand
I don't know
Based on our conception
Genders
I guess
If you're living in a nonbinary gender
And what you need to be living units is a trisexual gender world
Where there are water bears
I'm cool
Bet
You know I am cool
I am
I am above
The
The dichotomy of gender
But I understand I'm very open-minded
You are so
Very open-minded
Is so
Not where I'm coming from
Coming from a place of bees are analog
Of different species
He's on Earth
I don't get how a
Wasp
Mates with a water bear what is their offspring is it
Either a wasp or a waterbed
How is that possible if a wasp and a water bear mate and ask
Let me ask you a question
Here's what
Not this is
The problem with this whole
Carrie doesn't know enough
Why are you thinking and assuming that they make when they're in there fully adult
That's a great question
Look younger larval stage maybe they made they cross-pollinate and then they
Grove
A water snake
Those three things could come from the same
Right draw the face
I do know that yes yeah I do
Lego
Everybody starts out like in Skyrim on this
Okay for this alien
Video
Okay
Reasonable to land.
Complete
Bizarre nonsense
The reason why I
The reason why just sticks in my
Micro
That like
These are
Gender expression
You know in the same way as like
Do you know
Crossville
The Spectre
Gender expression
Identity
Experience
We're also human
With this
Water bears
Are all worms an insect
One of them is a microorganism right and the other is a reptile
Very different species
Here's the actual you understand why it's not
It's very
That actually makes
Way Morrison
Please walk me through
The reason
Is that
When we
Disgust
Every bias
As we have towards alien well
If we ever get in contact
They're going to be essentially us
We can't genuinely care about something that he's at
Because it's so far outside of our experience
Right makes more sense for them to Waterbury
And steaks out in the middle of f******
Space bulshit
Then it does for them to just be like
Two dudes who look like us but they're a little bit wacky which is what Carrie like
Genelec humanoid beings
Imagination on so many of the comment
Superintelligence face paintings flew B-52 bombers
You don't like this guy
A a is capable of reaching that they're not
It is absolutely ludicrous and I hate it but come on man this is good stuff
We talked about
The nature of liberation
Then I was like
Mars by Kona
Most of the time whenever we have these
Come on
Space Valor
And what's super interesting about
Captain Jay's
Is as we've already sort of talked
About there's no fighting fall
There's not even there's not even really an exertion
There's no
Threats or anything
Sing like that
Alyssa
The language
Before we go any further
Let me give you this
All right here we go
The water bear
Wasp
Snake triumvirate
Trisexual
The evolved separately on a planet where there were millions of death
When on Olive
Macy's began
AAA going through this
And only these three
Is recognized
They needed to survive in because of the way that they were reproducing didn't make any
They decided to come together they created
Combinator and then
Every time they want to reproduce what they all do is put a little bit of their own DNA into the genetic recombination
Bellator
Problem solved
Spine done
Staryu
You hit my Syfy nerd boner
MX Player
We find out about what happened
Deliberation
Can you tell me
Persuaded
Something you can destroy
They are too powerful
Are you intelligent
Anything else
Absolutely
Funny written on Mars
The brave
Whatever
Humanoid
Talking Tom
They are
AR
Oriole
Dominion
So
Because
You don't have a planet
All to themselves
Admission regarding God
Yeah yeah there's a real fundamental issue here with like they are overpowered
To excessive degree they can control psionically all of these other aliens
Only race in our solar system with weaponized
Ships
Yeah but you just go up there and have a little chat and you spoiled their fun you can't
Grab them but you can spoil their fun
You keep saying
Spoil their fun
I'm like I don't
You scold them and they leave
What
Silvercrest
What's what is an estimated IQ of
I don't think I mean
That's a failure
IQ test
I have a implicit culture
Surabaya
500 IQ.
They're the whitest
Whatever exists
The maximum IQ
Who gives a s***
The point of imagination artificial standard of
Intelligence
First of all
I meant technical interim
Triple scale
Doesn't go above like
200 right
Don't people just talk about like the greatest Geniuses being like 17
There is
Miss actually
Tested
Actually actually that was what's going on
Could be
Read
Gladiator
Group going to another job
The Galaxy
It also makes them seem like they just like
Pranks it doesn't seem like when you're using the language of like
There's
Funwa spoiled really doesn't make
Seem like you're eating
Right
Putting banana peels around
That you would get bored to the point where you're just like
Like what other explanation is there for
The s*** that
People ascribe to God
Ladies an overpowered
Bored bored
God prank
Ghost
Goes through
The Aquaman
Process
Easter Island
That's part of it
And then he goes
Deep underground
Will you find some
Communicating
Right
And is
Variable
When did Ender's Game come out
I'm sure
Said
The way he
So bizarre
I love on one level but also think
He's going to give you the history of Mars
The first
Serious Silent Communication and I had
Why
Getting in
Presents
I don't know you
Into
Attaches to their stored
Memories
I have records going back
Beginning and that's why I'm not afraid to come out with any of this information is all because
Put the f****** hospital for yourself
You're going back
That was the name
Immediately after the great cataclysm was almost
This'll take
Significant events and then head to years in another year
Melding together of 15 years
A good man's life
On that
Give me
Telepathic
Psionic memories
You are the character
It's so good
You are actually looking out for the character
This to me seems like
Something like a
Melding of
Albert Brooks movies
Defending Your Life
Oh yeah that's a HP Lovecraft story Shadow out of
Don't forget the matrix's little like throw throw
2 seconds
Really throwing me off
It really bumming me out
You've turned on it
Okay so
This technology where you put the helmet on
And then you get to see everything
They want to tell you
The helmet specifically designed for a human head despite the fact that until now
I've never needed a
Humanoid heads are probably pretty
Similar to Cranium
Baseball cap that can like
Expander
Deflect
Fiber
Okay that works at that party
Clothes on that one
Lee is at 1
Flexi helmet history
Show you
Not a problem that I have is
The only saw 50
Years of one person's memories
And not all of them just major that blur together
Maybe a little baby
Idea that it was
After the
Cataclysm on Earth never specified with that
Which one
Through punch
Pleasant
The only thing that I would guess
Because he never spells
Is it
Anti silver saucer alien prop
Buganda
Like
It's
Is it like
Like Noah's flood or whatever was caused by the
Like he gets to put this helmet on and then
Experiences
The life of someone who died in
That's like the alien
Who called
No I'm stretching real hard so I'm really not following him at all
But this one
I'm going to save it doesn't make any sense Dan also I want more than 15 years is
I want more than one
Perspective
If we romantic definitely don't want
One person's perspective over 15 years but actually it's like
Few moments melded together
Spitballing
Technology
Have the Matrix
Respect
Why not
Just like why does it have to take an hour for you to get
15 years
What is this
This is so yummy
It should be as fast as the brain function
U.s. Bank
Oh man
This is like
Has a governor
I'm going full speed but he's he's running
But he just can't run fast
Inspection is you
You can't break your own rules
Do you know what I mean
Like when you're writing a science fiction
Sure you got faster-than-light travel or whatever
But that has to be like a brick veneer f****** around
You know whatever rules you establish in your fake
Science fiction
Are fine as long as you adhere to those
The same way that
We're supposed
Yeah
Thumbs down
Comes down to this guy Dan
You going to roller coaster with Captain
Carrie is on board
Dislike
Part of it is
Because
He is Porter
Silver saucer evil aliens
As
These supposed
Radian
And next
Anthony other creatures
Communicate with you with you
City challenge long involved
However
So-called play in races
Lottery
Just be standing there going
Sub-Zero
Supposed
Pleiadians he's silver saucer aliens
Much more powerful psionic
Cabela's
Without
Deflect fiber helmet
Now have a trademark
Compact email.
So yeah the end that he scoffs
That is amazing
Like
You got a magic carriers Stewart
You your ass
Cancel
Marquez
Most of the lake
Queens most of the
Space Visa
Oviraptor
All of the channel the material
That you get from all these weirdos
They've been going on for
Years and years
A lot of them
Lightbringer
Do you like
There is this mythology
Time to give us
Bredemann
Identify the sentence the order of species but why
Is that just from the the Greek
What you mean
Is there some sort of connection there white
PPL Center on that one is being there Bringers of light
I think
Because
Nordic
Alien
If I had to guess just cutting through the b******* is a version of manifest
Or space race
Is a version of it they are the most similar to white people
And therefore
Cast in the role of
I need that that's racist already took over space before we even got there
So
Unsurprising
Yurt
Races races
Britta mean all of these people like
If we if we cut
Talking about like
The science fiction writing
And we actually just deal with it as adults
These people are just telling stories
With
The characters
That are extravagant
Some ways
And all not all
Because Captain Jay's
Is kind of an anomaly
1 reasons why this
95%
Alien
Stuff that you end
Cast Pleiadians
Scotch and they are always
Describe
Nordic
Taller than us
Angelic White
Because all of the p
Actuated
Stories
Boring
Ono lightly
Creative but not
Creative enough
Write something good
Who's okay
Racist
You don't care
Inhibition
On your creativity
Just like these people
Generally
Not good
Yeah you were talking about earlier the idea of like this is where you live
Your creativity
They get to a point
Can't go further
Next up is a convention
Lutheran witch
And they allowed their personal biases
You're in ways that they
Otherwise couldn't
Express them public
Probably
So in this next
Yes Cassidy
What about her
Whataburger
Is about the military
She always
The idea that people are in
Military
Because
The military
Services secrets
And what more
What do you think
Every single person that
But she has who are like
Underworld
Military
Randy Cramer
Keystone middle
Sponsor
In the military
Captain Mark Richards
Military
Video
Doing this 30-year bed to life
Prison
Because he's still part of it and yeah
All of the
Everything has to
Considered
Within
The
The world
Review of
That's a really good point
8-bit like begs the question
Kind of
Hardcore
Militaristic it's interesting I don't know enough
About her family of origin
My actual like
Deep research time on more productive
I don't know
I don't want to do more for.
I would save it
She probably has
A very
Strong app
Wow also being
Part is the like I believe
Space aliens
Imaginary
Authority
And then
It all lives within the world of
I only really believe people who pretend to be part of the military
Yeah so I don't I don't know if
It's tough to say where it comes from
I do want to break the Goldwater rule by psychoanalyzing
But
He wants she wants a fascist
Dominator she just doesn't want the
Perhaps
Truliant of all the
These whistleblowers that
Richie have
They all pretend that they were deeply involved
XYZ organization
Whatever records that organization
Deep deep Secret
Records that you're never going
I probably am the most important person to write me and my dad to Dutchman we even though I was over at all
Stanford over again
Yeah
Like Hiram
No like the highest
Like I said she's never had that she's always had somebody who's like that no one who's been looking to order
Of course you don't you don't you don't f*** around with noncommissioned officers
That just makes perfect sense that goes all the way back to her West Point
All of this
Is just a service
Reduction
To this next
Where it really is
Seems like Captain
Like
He's not even expressing bit like this
Trip to Mars
Quotes sordid
Nothing
The
That was just a graze coming and picking
You are the person
Took about 20 minutes
Did you
Commanding officer
Absolutely not
We had no radio contact with anyone other than our Pilots
Round document
No we were just to come back and debrief
Diplomat associated with the greys have chosen
He doesn't know when he's answering
Who are the other people on this f****** s***
It makes absolutely no sense
Four carries worldview
Because it's
Space Program
Analyzing its government doing all the
These black
Operations right
Liberate Mars
And I did it
Basically solo
Like we didn't have any military training now I am bored with his grace
Because they realize that if you wanted to go with somebody who is the political machine
You're going to wind up having to go through all this red tape and you're going to get a lot of people
Do you grab this guy who you know has a
Good
F****** hard
Which is all you need
I don't I like
What I like about this is that you have some
Who is so different
And all of her other guy
And she hate
Ludacris already visible
This is
Convoluted
She is not having a good time with
Because he's presenting like this
Experience which is just
Motherfuking right
And I will tell you the grades are pretty
They came
Mars
Military
Easter Island
They're great pretty cool. Like a civilian-led governor
No she doesn't feel like it's not like
She doesn't
Like someone
Doesn't have a clear up
Chosen
By the
Call Nick boscia
Dude
But
Not all of her other guests have only fomented more pain and Terror
Is the first guidance
I forgot, Rogue
Adult around the universe
Sorting shootout
Yes
Carrie is
Enjoying this
Clearly seen
And so towards
This point
She's
And she's like
She doesn't in an hour in this whole interviews only
Which is short for summer
Do I have other things
And she keeps interrupting
He I will say is one of the
The people who
Is the most
Loquacious
Like he just will do
10 minute long
Song
It was amazing
Went over and
Because they don't construct things
Talk about spirits
Security has to keep interrupting
When she wants to end
The show
But
She does end
Couple questions
The audience
I'm sorry to interrupt you here
I do have a very small
Questions in the chat
One person wants to know
Percent
Okay cool
Check that one off
Boring question
Another person
No reason I just think it looks more like
Malibu
I won't argue based on movies and like
Too far away from the camera
He has like a webcam setup that is a
Good like
Feet away from
But it's not a good I can't
Man look like a pirate
Dollar Tree
So those are the questions
And then
Rienzi energy
Soft
Thank you very much
Sharing your testimony with us today
This is as I say very impromptu and
Information
Time
Perhaps there will be in the future
And we'll just kind of
That is exactly what you said to begin
Which is there is no way to prove any of it but
You can sort it sound like
If they're gone better she wouldn't have ended it with I'd like to remind you
He's talking about
Yeah it's fun
Maybe this is
Maybe this is a
Halloween episode
Because Carrie is dressed up as someone
Who actually is questioning
Want some
Maybe maybe it is
Analog
I just don't know how
On the one hand
He's so far been my favorite
Project
Well I mean the running isn't
Like it's not a deep crew
Like who do you have to pull for
Well what's the racist murderer the guy who was
P.m. in Britain
Was he Diamond Parks was he on the show or was he just meant
Well he's up
I like him
I don't know
It seems like his policy positions were great he's not
Alien once every four months
He's not as bigoted
As some of
The other folks
This guy doesn't
I don't know
Is bigoted but I don't know where to
Who and why
Do you know what I'm saying when you get done
Beginning of the show
Expressing
At least
Metaphorically be more Progressive
So many of these other guests
And Carrie hates
Seems to say something
Seems like it
I don't know because we can
The world of metaphor
I don't know what conclusion you can draw
What is endlessly fascinating
Whenever we goes
Through all of
These guys and how they feel about
Races
Like they all
All of them
When an alien race is involved they all have hard-and-fast position
The races are good and entire races are bad
Uniform
Tickets given to
You might think similarly
Theater
Sure
But this guy is he even his racist things like the all the pleadings you think you're playing
And they're bad but even then they're like
They're like a badass
Like his is description of all of this s*** is
Is very non-committal towards an actual race of beings
Being good or bad
Or even like even his
His worst
Characterization
Was
You know like the infinitely powerful and have no problem
We talked to them and I couldn't have their phone
I don't I
If there are space
Politics
That's better version
I appreciate it
It's interesting that you have his guy who's come in and express
He's never been welcomed back on the show will talk to Eddie page 5 times in a month
Non-Stop
Now here is where the show proper m
Yes
And will be back
Just about
To listen to more track
From Kerry Cassidy
Knowledge cycling room
Azrael
A little bit of
Listening party
For IV
Camelot
Rebel Jean
Again released
Online
Showbox
Rebar
Charges like 99 cents
This was released
Find more information
Book.org
Check that out
Do that
This one is called guys only
That's good feeling feel that s***
Oh my God
Are you not free to communicate
Abortion message
Are you not afraid
Good
It's not good no I would listen to that
I don't think our voices
Is great but serviceable in that in that role
It's fine
She could she could take over for warpaint Miss Mister she's there
Let's see where we go from there
The rules upon your world they are the octopus pet rules
They are the octopus ride for on your room nro
Dia ansar we can't legally listen to this without hookah so
They are the octopus
Are any world yours secret space all worlds
Are yours except for Europa
That's a big reveal the big reveal
Going to go to Europa the only world I want is Europa
Never come up on the show before
Look a good artist never looks
Never look back
She burned that material on this album
All worlds are yours
Except Europa
Like what world is Europa
But also the next song
Nail gun to the Head
That's a harsh title
What's going on
Do all prospective whistleblowers get out while you still can
Ensure
The banker hits are being done by the bad guys to keep the men from stinging after they slipped
During prosecution investigations
Cstl fed guy discovered
Afforded
Before he sang again
Didn't know what I'm made of
Vatican connection
On massive Forex fraud that unclear which is bigger
Vatican linked to Narco money or links for axial broadsoft out
Protocol
Instrumental
Serviceable
Eerily eerily similar to The xx album I'm new here
Gil Scott-Heron spoken word
And then just put beads underneath
Eerily similar to the
Slightly different
Contact whoever says that a rat done bit
Better sister.
Iraq
The government Etc
This is
So while
I'm just
Almost
It's not worse
I think it's terrible
But only because
The combination of all of it
Parts
Like I think
I could
Loki
Mellow vibe
Some of the
Imitation
And also if it wasn't
Kerry Cassidy
I think I could put up with
Full disclosure like those kind of like
Ambience
Makes
It makes sense I don't think this is terrible I really don't
I will see if you enjoy this
The next track is actually space Clinic nail gun to the Head
Milk
Play the next song
This is AI battle
Okay
That is real Titanic into the Vatican play Hamid
List of all George Bush Senior or modular
Market-based in Tanzania
Return to Earth
Dark nobility are anything's
If it was kardinal offishall I'm going to be pissed off
Someone on the track and it doesn't say who is God
Also know that he will do
Anythink still show up anyway
Isn't that song with Colby odonis
Oh yeah
Carrie
Shari
So this last track hear the album
Closer
Call Humanity get off your knees
Understanding What You're Made Of is key to understanding what are true potential is
Once you realize this and child is father to the man
If you're not feel everybody
From the early 2000s
The father of man is also an album by the by Blood Sweat and Tears
Seems like opium in Goleta
Like this seems to me like you got to be like
Real on
Debilitating absolutely
Becomes much more real but that is we may end up being
Their teachers rather than the other way around humanity is engine
Experiment Library
Damn right
You believe it is likely even greater than the sum of a part
Our potential is unlimited as a result
Recognize who you are and begin to push the envelope above your potentiality
Hayward
I think that's a great Bass
Pictures of Proclaim it
Only listen to this sample
I guarantee if you had to sit around Elizabeth for half an hour you probably
Lessa half hour
That's too long
Each of those tracks we only heard about 1
Too long
The 36-minute album
6 track
No I can see her
Putting out an already to Blue Note album
It's interesting that you did that in 2014
And is not
Ventured back
The Waters of muse
Nor is he mentioned it on the show
Fraser
Call God
If I were her
That would be the thing I would be most crap.
I think that I've heard a lot of like a albums by people who have no business make
Music
Like you're like a
Joe Pesci
Call Nathan music
Actors who has made music
And like
You listen to that you like
What are you doing
I will I will come with you as far as I'm going to accept
You should come with us and leave your world behind
Music
Good good on her apron
It's not bad then we will
This will be our eternal struggle was producing that album
Knew exactly what
She was working with exactly what they were working
Stupid you are willing to Elementary
Let's make sure that this
F******
Vibes
And let's not worry about anything beyond that
Who's going to live or die by her
So what happened
Non-essential
I'm just
As mellow and just whatever is possible
I meant to throw her weirdness on it
Let's not on me I was just on their website I still don't remember what that guy's name is
Who did all the music
Let me tell you something I look it up it's on
Multi-instrumentalist
Doing all this for
Damn bro
Find out that he's the genius behind
Stanley automator
You love the most
Guides
Fun
Nice break for
From reality a little bit but
With our next episode
Whatever it is
Materiality
Maybe
Covid-19
I couldn't even sell myself on that anyway Weaver website.com
I'm not on that one
About Facebook
Tell your mother you're brilliant
Backgrounds free
The joint
I do Avail myself of
You can leave a review
Describe
Appreciate it thank you all
For supporting the show
Absolutely
The only thing that I can say for certain
Shut it down
I do want to hear what you were going to say but I have a better
Okay alright
Alright you're alright
The only thing I can say for certain is that for the first time
On a project Camelot maybe not the first time
But
For the first time in a Project Camelot episode where a guy calls himself a captain
He has explicitly
Never killed a guy
But I know somebody who
So here's mine
It's pretty close
Bank
That when these
Silver
I have to be in
Problems in the universe
Was
Some
Going into space going to Mars
Getting acclimated
To Easter Highland being
No one
Todai
Figuring out the
The problem
But one guy had to
Theoretically
Lee die
No reason
Mine was a little bit more
It was the way I would just remind
Let us know which one you enjoyed better we'll see you next time you're on the podcast
Alexandra Thurston color