Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Everybody
Alex Jones
Loudly
I mean it
Not that far back
Certainly it's
Very common occurrence
I don't remember the last time but I know that
For me Morris
Before I normally do
Because somebody was talking
So loudly
On the train
The conversation isn't even worth reporting back
No it was horrific your report it was horrific
Boring conversation overheard on train
Brutal
Cool
It was just so angry that I just died
Is it was
Could do was trapped in this
Half of the converse
Lewis are you excited
Ask my tattooist
Shut up Murphy Murphy Murphy
I mean unless you donate to the
Oh God come on Murphy
Come on
I don't know if he has the money
Irrelevant
Thank you so much for a shout-out
Thanks
Well
You know you got
York UK
I'm a policy wonk
MB
And I apologize
Need to come to the show
So we're like found him on Twitter
Things didn't work out no put in doing so we did find that Murphy has a pretty good sense of humor
Okay keeps calling people female humans real humans
The other thing tweeted they'll never forget was
Don't nobody love these hoes
But Everybody Loves Raymond
Got it back
You are now a techno
Don't get mad and tell your brother
Someone someone sodomites
Set me a bucket of poop
Baba black sheep
Thank you thank you very much
I got that wrong I'm not the best with only ever
Read before you've never act like I don't know NES mizore Esme
I o b h a n
That's Irish name
I have looked how it's pronounced and I have since forgotten if I feel terrible
About if I'll never ever be able to retain
But either way we appreciate it oh so very much thank you for your support
Join up
We can do it by going to knowledge fight.com
Couldn't support the show button
Appreciated
I wanted to do a present-day episode
Because we've been
Sort of
You know we were in the past on Monday
Yeah I thought it'd be good to check in on the present but then I saw an article where Alex was saying that the
The shooting at that synagogue
You can stop right there and I said
Yeah no no
I know that
Like looking at the the the abyss
Is kind of part of
What does show does a lot of Stephen like
Like water why are we doing this
You get drawn into it
I just don't think there's much
Like
Talking about that
I think that's
Like
Alright get back
And assholes
Two-story out there's nothing to look at
Irrelevant
It's weird that way
Somewhat it so I decided it was staying in the past
And today we're going over in episode
From March
20th 2009
Tell me what episode
Because I also am going to just stay off
Off the top
Is the Friday episode
March 22nd 2009
Sunday
Annette
Was hot garbage
I realize that Alex Jones
Nowadays
A soft launch is for his married
To test something out see how it feels coming out of his little bit of an open
He'll do it on Sunday
Back in 2009
He would just do a recap of all the bulshit he talked about lots and I realized
It's because back then
More people listen to Sunday shows because it was distributed by emmis Communications
Audience on Sunday
So we tried to make the most of it
Right now
If you knows the less people look like on Sunday
So who gives a s*** that's f*****
So I realized
This is technically March 20th and 22nd
Compare apps
Having our context drop
I am an animal I am vicious
Ivory
Today's episode of our last
We had
I think probably the most Subs
Something that happened was Alex got a visit from the guy who started the Oath Keepers
To wish on anyone
Like if you told me that
Visit from the guy who started the Oath Keepers RV like how do I run away from this
Alex's
Quarterflash song
Harden My Heart
Keepers
And that will serve as a transition
That mystery is a little
We've got a lead
Yeah in that one
Further where we last left off he was going real hard on the miac report bulshit
Really trying to
Sane
Create the idea that the government
Hates Patriots and they're taking on over
We all do now
Here we go this is where Alex starts the show and it's sort of indicative of his mood throughout that I would say at least
The first half hour 45 min
Just how serious the situation were in
You know I don't
And I'm telling you that they're going to kill the majority of us
You are doing a
Aw said something that made me laugh
The problem with it is that he is right
He's always proved
Has demonstrated over all of our episodes
Put together
Pretty solid
Truth-telling
Lingering
Views of Gandhi is that quote that like first they ridicule you then they
Bella is really dumb ideas
Take solace in the fact that they're being ridiculous because they think they're on the path to being revolutionary
Yeah
Exactly
Like where Alex
Just a note to anybody speaking of a sagging inspirational quote
It can be used against
So don't
Be careful be careful with your inspiration
I want the very least once again
This is a
Sick situation to add the... Except
This is a great one
Birthday laughing
F*** you
What kind of
Rolling around like a
Picking s*** about how people make fun of him but he's always right
Isn't tire headspace and I'm not sure exactly why that is
I don't see any external reason for him to be like
Is there anything like that
Consuming his person
You talk about it
A bunch
Lindback does hours and hours every day already on TV on it
He's on with my ex
It was out for a few days and get the attention we pointed out the Iowa National Guard
Dealers
How lockdown the time
Was what that story was
Criticize
Army troops
Associated Press
See this is where the difficulty with Alex back then was
He is right about
Episode
It wasn't some nefarious let's put troops on the street
Weezer
Responsibility
He brings in the Arcadia
Simulating the idea of
Looking for someone in
In a town it wasn't gun
Confiscation drill
Like that
To do with it but then he is right about the
Exaggerate
So it's like okay
You get half a boy
You know what he's absolutely right we really shouldn't have the military operating within our borders
Interesting
That is a principal
Stick to it
He doesn't change based on the weather and whether or not the guy
Is doing it
Federal law
Posse Comitatus
I'm here to get the barbed wire first
After
You know what I like
Because I'm doing this for
Ecology
Oh boy
Something
The alien lady
Martial law New York
I mean
Dangerous level of
Flagellation
I guess someone was on the last
And they spoke like that
You
AR
A little out there
You you are unhealthy
I agree with what you stand for but you are unhealthy and I don't think you're the right person
That's kind of how I would look at it just from like a human standpoint
Hey
I know that he seems to be the example I pull up all the time but
Because I think he's funny and I like him but like I was acting like that
Never again
I'm beside you an e-mail see if you're okay
Lego who's this who's the dude
Used to be a Sports Anchor
Doberman doberman
I felt pretty similar
F****** calm it down
We might agree with.
It's unhealthy when you perceive yourself This way everything is going to be in
Nothing is ever going to be you're never going to be able to look at the world realistic
Because you're not looking
Yourself real
And so Alex
Deep in that mindset
Thomas episode
Hello
Not you have to talk more about how he's always right about
Literally
You're welcome
Subject
We started the 9/11 truth movement
Yeah you do
Record
Frontline's the shock troops
The power you have
So the first thing I want to talk about about that
Examples in order to establish his credibility
Asia Iowa Arcadia Iowa story
Complete post-modern militia
There was a real document that WikiLeaks
But he completely lied about the cont
He made it Elementary logical fallacy about what the inference was of the report
At 9:11 still out on whether or not
Aggrandizing
Sing of his movement
Fair
I don't know enough about the opthamology
Popeyes Lake establishment
The entire
Quickly
How long did it take for the 9/11 truth movie
Start after
Towers in Howell
Like this is the governor
Michaela
Ernie brought it
Tower bowling alley was like government did it let's move on whatever time he was on air
That's good
That's the best time spookables your world is watching the worst terror attack in America
Alright alright
911 prices
9 oz / 11
I mean what what better time to override people's sense of like
I got to check this out first
This clip is Alex
The word shock
Rocket troops
To Define his audience
I know Alex loves
Use military terminology to describe players in his information
Doctor Strange
The term shock troops isn't Americanization of the German word
Which is the name
Specifically established to be Hitler's bodyguard
The concept of shock troops had existed prior to
Hitler
Describe offensive attack units
Interesting Lee many scholars on combat
Do the strategy that isis uses of employee suicide bombers as a form of modern
One of the reasons why Alex metaphors disturbing
Rarely survive
They would go in and light up the rear guard of the base or something like that
But I'm pretty much invariably be killed in the process
In the west the concept grew out of units that we referred to as forlorn hope unit
The name reflecting how Dreadful their position was
The idea was that these troops ago in a whole lot of them would die or be
But if they were lucky they might be able to establish a position that they could then defend
Often the soldiers would be willing to take such huge risk
Because in many cases they work inscribed prisoners or no choice
Or because they were promised great reward should they survive
Alex Jones
This sort of a soldier is very
If you just add the caveat that the war they're waging is Imagine
Alex knows full well what he's doing to his audience with his lies and propaganda is mortally wounding them in battle
They may not end up with a limp or missing limb
Abby end of being
Shock troops in imaginary globalist
The equivalent of social death
Banana community
Except for with their fellow info Warriors
Little further insulate them more and leave
Leave them be more interested in being a doctor
So there's a there's a metaphor Alex
Is accidentally making
It's really it's a real bummer when you realize like
On some subconscious level Alex's expressing an understanding of how much he's
Crippling
His own list
Brainworm kind of APK
Even he in his like I would say
Minor understanding of the term still
They're going in
They're the ones
To take the Brunt
Right
They they are
Billions of dollars
Kind of like
BookIt barbwire
Panthers Barbara Airport
You're not a shock trooper
Dollars a year
It's so today
Exist
You're scared of it
Yes
I don't understand what was I saying again
Martial law New York
This sort of
Analog
Is language
Especially when it's couched in the
The psychology that Alex's
Clearly
I love it
Cuz I'm always right eventually
You guys are out there
That's really really f***** up and it would be f***** up if he actually was right about things
He's wrong about everything
I mean the picture starts to take shape
Destroy people's lives
To get away from that a little bit
People's lives up
City racquet
We're back from the break
The metaphorical break
New York
New York City
Would not come on
I wouldn't
Jason bermas is from
Run outside
Police drug dealing and Corruption
Mary considers options martial law
The story that he's going to leave and he's going to leave it into like they're trying to
Martial law in place in
Schenectady New York
That is the best
And unfortunately in Alex
His telling of the introduction to the story there
Solved
The mystery
Clearly
Because he says that Jason bermas is from around there and they have
Police corruption problem
That's what this is about
It's not martial law
It's about 8
Deeply deeply entrenched
Incorruption
Police
So
The beginning 2000
Town of Schenectady face
Multiple officers
Leaving a mess
E6 officer
Department
According to the Daily Gazette
The six officers who may be fired or Darren Lawrence accused of drunk driving
Crashing in the colonies fleeing the scene and beating a friend to keep him from recording the inside
Sounds right Michael Brown accused of driving drunk hitting another car fleeing the scene refusing a breathalyzer
Weather test John Lewis
BWI threatened to kill his ex-wife and numerous other charges
Sam's Diner
And Andrew k0i
Charis Kiewit
Accused of beating during an arrest
Dwayne Johnson
Accused of leaving work 4 hours early on numerous Tuesday
Might just be a Stern warning is just a
Did you Brody
Alright however I do
To have guns
Publicly
List of all these people acting with impunity and either beating suspect while in custody
Going home from work early
Describe it
And they beat the s*** out of the sky
Trying to understand
People f******
Sometimes
Menu
You beat up somebody in order to not get arrested or
You know you trying to threaten to kill your ex-wife on top of it
Yeah okay we got a problem
Clifford was undergoing
80 told the dispatch
But he was going out on a detail
You still on the clock or just went and got some dental procedures
I'm fine with
The Civilian Complaint review board listening to any of their complaints
I need a Civilian Complaint
He even said he felt that he was just an errand boy like a courier delivering complaints
That would then be ignored
Yeah that sounds right city councilman Gary McCarthy said quote I'd like to go one week where we don't have a negative newspaper article about the
Department it's just baffling that they it's just
Keeps happening
It's human nature that people are going to make mistakes but this seems so into
Institutionalized
Schenectady mayor Brian Stratton was kind of in a tough situation
He was facing the possibility that
Fire a group of police officers
Those were just the officers that they had potential grounds for dismissal for that wouldn't likely get challenge
Just cause for termination
For Better or Worse
Please have a pretty f****** good union
People support unions only when it comes
Who's the police here
I absolutely I absolutely support the police Avenue Union but you have to recognise in a situation like this
Then you become deeply entrenched
Inside
Police force
The union does make it incredibly difficult in order to have
I know what you're called
Easy solution
Because
They have a strong
Protection
Because that protection
Nasacort
Situation like police
Sing it could very easily be used
Politically
Seriously
So the protector
Is there a
Also gives you that
6 dozen the other words
Like you f***** up
And yourself
Trooper
This is where they have the tea
Just go to work
And sit in a room all day because
They can't be allowed in your stew
Like
Ultimately
Mayor Brian
Stratton had just said the calling
Department
Calling in county or National Guard help with
Not surprisingly to get off the ground but anyway
Comment from the mayor
And even in response to the comment or like
Yeah you can do that without the governor
So the mayor doesn't even have the authority to do that it was just
Trying to express
In some way
How severe of the Rat
He was willing to if
Need be
Look into this as a solution where they dissolved
The entire police
Department because it would be
Impossible
Yeah that were resulting in
Population
A little bit
So now the problem of police corruption
Corruption's
Stratton did not give up
Completed mission
Enforcing out entrenched office
Who did things like quote
Rachel flowers while fighting in a bar
Board of course there was a case of
Detective Jeffrey Curtis
Became addicted
Did the crack cocaine
From the Police Department evidence
Curtis compromised evidence in more than a dozen cases
What is that
We have a situation like that and
He took a year
And found novel solution
In order to get around things like the
Limitations of the
Do unions he was able to find ways
To convince a lot of these officers through
Resign
Eddie made it his mission
He retired heaven
Completed
Events to do in office
Actually
Obviously don't know everything about Schenectady politics or Brian Stratton
Like it really good success story
In many ways insurance would like setting out
Will you get it off if you realize oh s*** look at all
Look at this mess
Our our budget
Is completely stocked up
Police force is a disaster
And you said about trying to make changes
Along the way you make
We're willing to call in National Guard in County
If we have to
Dissolve the department
And propagandists like Alex jump all over that instead of looking at like oh my God there's a lot of positive
Liver forms
I need
Do anything
Did the real bad
Bierocracy
He worked
The real story is Alex
Paul Joseph Watson
Stratton
Respond
Yeah because then that'll be later Alex we'll talk about that one that actually happened
A couple
Weeks down the road or whatever but like you don't do that cuz then they just
Get to dance on your letter
Or whatever by what your letters
Seems like a civil service
You did a great job
And help the people of connect
Be quiet
Alex
Is a complete liar
Why do people
Heading to be part-time
So I mean here we have Alex starting to show up in the entire thing is about a guy I'm right all the time and people
New York martial law story that the
Complete lie that you
And that is this is why I
Any chance
It doesn't help
Is it against that he have
Not be hard
Heating interview
It seems like
If you're a politician
I got a lot of
What time you have to
Hold back
Diplomatic learn how
There should be
Uofu exception
Is that where you're allowed to
Just go be like
You know like your response to Alex should always just
You should be allowed in all public like nobody is allowed to write
Complaints or whatever
Alex
F*** that guy
And we remove the taboo of
Tearing off on it
Yeah I don't
I don't disagree with that
We get here now
Guest
Are very
Not hard-hitting
Which is another reason why people are like what
What the f***
Rightly
He has
The time he has his sponsors on the show
And they're not
Not announced as
SAR
It's just them
Telling stories and weaving narratives
A disappearance
Feisty
Alex Jones
Direct sponsor
I want to bring up for the balance of the shower before
SeaWorld
4 minutes of news I was covering
Well I think it's absolutely Anna
Bored with what you and I were go
Going to talk about
HR
Were there
Weather moving on
Do just as you and I have talked about
The last 3 years
Moving on it like a
We have a situation here where he has his food sponsor on cells
Survival bunker
It's basically who's coming into talk about this legislation
I'll bet Alex
If we mentioned it in passing on recent episode
In Tulsa where is is like now they're talking about where's the budget for
Upkeep and things like that
Not about that trying to
We've this narrative into being like they're going to try and encroach on YouTube
Do you want be able to have a garden in your
Home
Story is now
Now I just don't
Understand why
He doesn't say where
We're going to go to the shack
Little bit more mornings
Might be a little more entertaining
There's a fun little bit of Internet hysteria that went around in early 2000's conservative
Conspiracy theorist
It's called HR 875 which is what species
Just brought up is a house resolution
The sponsor of that bill representative Rosa delauro was more than fair
It was a response to
According to the Huffington Post quote
The intent of the bill is to focus on the large industrial processes such as the
Peanut process
Implant in Georgia that was responsive
Before the salmonella outbreak that killed
She says
Fantasizes at the concert
Students Commerce Clause
Prevent the federal government from regulating Commerce
What does across state line
There's wiggle room on that
There's like a little update
At the end of the article
So I just felt like giving
Delauro says that she's open to making technical changes in the Bill of any small farmers remain concerned
The article goes on to say Dolores
He's been told that the dissing
Information campaign
Operation somewhere in the country
But we're trying to
To figure it out
I think I could help her sort that mystery right out
Libertarian
RadioShack
Hatred of Regulation
More by
Moneyed interest
Who have a
Big'o
Alternate build
Committee Rosa delauro introduced the year prior
So also sf-425 is the other bill that
Shake Break
Before this episode
The house version was not backed up
Committee on February 4th
All of this is just lies about what the text
The bills say
It didn't even get voted on
The only reason the covering is a tall is
Because it's something very easy to craft
The Narrative of government encroach
Plus it has the added benefit of being something with
Easy to twist into being about big food like Monsanto trying to crush your home so you rely on them for food
When in reality the bill was written
It was
Specifically designed to regulate big Interstate comfort
Nothing to do with guard
Like
Basically it's just a sales page that allows Steve shank and Izzy Foods Direct
To enjoy some of that status
Did Alex Jones love stove
And uses to sell his
Be victim so bad while running everything and ruining people's lives
Fetishize
Because something we don't ever really take
2 into consideration
Super powerful as a motivator
Like
Fear and empathy
Same time
Ability to help us
Turtle of the empathy
The people have for likes
Steve
Or for Alex
They probably have some misplaced
You know any emotional response
People can use
To get you to override your better judgement
I stopped short of calling it
Brilliant powerful Market
It's in effect
What is the beginning of the show
So everyone
Dancing all over Jacob Wohl
Yeah I know that's hilarious
That was the dumbest
Press coverage that was
Astonishingly.
The other guy
Yes
Jack burkman
Headed fly
Yes no
That's not what I wanted that's not what I wanted to bring up
Although it is fun
Slido
If listeners
Longtime listeners do the show might recognize the name Jack burkman
And the reason for that
That is we went over
Along
Months ago
We went over Alex Jones
Trying to tell the story of the Seth Rich investigator who got shot
And it turns out that that was just a situation where he had hired another crazy guy to work with him and Amanda
The guy who got shot was Jack burkman
Nice to have these
I wish people report on that I know there's other stuff but that was a really fun that's a really fun
Piece of art
Our past
And I when I realized
Guffawed
Play Everly
How people just don't go away
Keep doing b*******
Call me episode is sometimes a good thing but sometimes
About that
Tell a story
Covering
I was like I don't know enough about Jack burkman
I know dude
I'd like to go back in time and retroactively affordable
If you go back and listen at all episode in a week and I'll have like a little
Combo breaker
Propaganda
Nearly the amount of time to go back and find no idea
When you got her back
The miac report is a super big
Piece of Alex Jones
This current mood but
He also has a story that he
He pitched on
Heard it on Monday
Where he has been
Forced volunteering bill
Baby Feud
If you recall
Alex
Is reporting on
The introduced version
Of the bill as opposed to
Cast version
The bill that had the
The sort of mandatory service
Stripped out
This is never a good I
He's lying
Entirely about
But he brings it up again
Amanda
Has evolved over the course of a couple days
This is so much scarier now
Country on Obama has started all of this
Flawlessly
Like relay runners
That they are going to have martial law in the states and cities
Civilian Army
Including warzones so
Define love
Or they will decide what you're going to be in you will serve
No Doubt
Mayor of New York
Love you man
Another another like uses reading that that martial law
When connecting it
You we need you to volunteer
There's alot going on we need you to build home
We need you to build Gardens
We need you to fix
Road
It's very complicated cuz what he's doing now is he trying to combine
Different things
Seem like the same thing
He's talking about like he mentioned at the department of
Defense Direct
In there and then talked about it
Figure out where he's getting
All that other stuff
Some of the things about like warzones and stuff like that from the Department of Defense
Able to talk about
The house is that stripped-down version
Of what was it house resolution
So like
Play fast and loose with all these details
Pretending
It's all crazy
So it's great work on his part
F******
Bulshit out of
Have a full picture talk about that
Infowars
January 30th
Defense department civilian expeditionary Force
Builder
Exercise
Management Authority direct and assign civilian employee voluntary or involuntary
Domestically or internationally
Now happened
I think there's one word that Alex is hoping you didn't hear in there
And that is
Employee
Yeah because this is about DOD employees
Mandatory
They call them civilian employees cuz there's a lot of people in the military work for the dod
Civilian employee doesn't mean citizen of the United States
Transcribed into service for the.
It's a non-military Personnel who work for the defense
Department contract
So it's
If you look at this cuz you can fine also
If it is
Edit YouTube videos right
What kind of idiot would you
Grab some random person and be like I had now
It would take for money to train them
It is the dod directive 1404 like 8 you can find it
I read it
Ava Lincoln
You want it it's all just about employees
Because it says mandatory or like willing or unwilling
Reassignment and stuff like that
And he doesn't
Read what came right
Before that
In the tack
DOD civilian employees in ee or positions may be directed
Accept employment requirements of
The position
However whenever possible the dod civilian expeditionary Workforce
Will be asked to to serve
Expeditionary requirements
Voluntarily
Now the important thing there is
GE means emergency
Essential
PE means non-combat essential which is to say that the position
This is entirely about
Essential position
And how we will try to accommodate you as best as possible to be voluntary
But because he's
Position versus Central
We might have to reorganize in such a way where you go to a position
You don't necessarily want to be
And if you don't want to be in that
Guess what
Because you are Adam
Employee
You can quit
You don't have to go
That is true
But they do also
The the civilian expeditionary work
Except volunteer
If you go to their website and you read their FAQ page
There is a question as a volunteer are there any negative consequences if I decline an opportunity
The answer
You cannot be direct
50 serve in Expedition
Also there's a
Almost like all of these people have already thought of the things that he's going to b**** about and it written
Into the rules
I need to go to the website there's a list of the
Intensive training requirement
You have to undergo
Indisposition
Pretty high-paying position
Like these aren't something worth
You know whatever
Article
At the beginning of the article quotes
What is established
Civilian expeditionary Workforce CC American civilians trained overseas in support of the worldwide
Carrie Mitchum
Problem
DOD directive 1404 10
Is really just an updating of an already existing directive
You can easily find a version of it from 90
E92 which still explicitly includes
Nearly identical language about the
The deployment of Civilian employees of the Department of Defense
Also I found one
Brumate
Is from April 1992
We can't even say Bobwhite
Also I found a revision of their there regarding
Department 1988 you can find online
Employee non-military
Script
Putting these people in secret damn that's why we don't know
Where so many people are right now
Missing persons cases
No
Forced conscription into play
Understand or wherever they want to go
Bill that he's lying about
In the house
Reporting on a different version of the bill then pass
Department of Defense directive 1404
Which doesn't say not explaining
What's the villion workforce
Because it serves its purpose of like Obama is going to come
You can take your kids and then they're going to sassy with the dinner table
Brakes
This b*******
It's completely
You connecting to live into a bigger lie it's
Obama's going to come to your home
He's going to give you
Training
And he's going to pay you $40,000 a year
Whatever is another aspect of this I want to talk about
And that is in the midst
Volunteerism was really hot
It was really hot
Because I went to the University of Missouri
I worked at the office of service-learning
And that was a department within the University
That's absolutely true
Entire job because there was funding for service-based
Curriculum
What's the go through the entire catalog of course
University of Missouri
Could have a volunteer aspect
Added to the course
Play like a pulmonary science
Something like that
There's an easy application of 5 hours a week
Or something like that
University
Grants and things like that in order to we volunteerism into the
The curriculum of classes where it was
I know because I was involved in
Creating the catalog
Of course it's worthy service-learning Department
It wasn't
Something nefarious
There were many times where I was
Stretching
Maybe this good
That's not really applicable to the course
It was hot in the sense of like this idea that paradigm
Department there was this idea of
We have an opportunity
Me to get people to help
Where they
Volunteer their time
Which is a positive thing
Sing for everybody
Doing those things
It's not some
Evil thing
About what year was that
Missouri
Still into town Tamagotchi
Ciproud
I was qualified to work at that apartment fire
Girlfriend's mom
Department
Nice time
An interesting work
Alex
Probably
See something very nefarious behind
That
And it was
Dislike these moves
Push the pushes towards volume
Tourism in stuff like that
It was happening
Before Obama got in office
I mean
But I believe they is like you were saying
A lot of Grants
Encouraged
Shirts
Do this
Yeah I mean
Donnelly University
But the university got
Money in order to
You know it was it they way would they got money in order to convince
People that bought
Which is interesting
About it I think positive
Yeah you could also have really positive
Experiences
Truecaller
I think there's a lot of people in the world
Like
Cuz you got to find a place you believe in
You got to go through process those like
You don't know if it's
Put on a cloak
I don't know
Tearing that you need a cloak
I couldn't come up with the word April
This is all hot.
Experience
It was a little overwrought and it was like an interesting new pair of paradigm
Education a little bit more gung-ho necessarily then
I don't understand
Hey someone who lived in a tight
But
Stupid
We already had
Steve
Who sells out
Yeah
Rather Financial
Doan's going considerably higher
This is the only place to go with
Money isn't golden store
There are no more alternative
Your money
Golden silver Communications
The communications Network as a
Marketing arm
Word Midas
Noahide
Idea how great
Now they want to do any of that
My Bitcoin back then
At this point
Own a cryptocurrency
The outlet
Is over and over again
You already know that he's going to show up when I play like
Eclipse from now
He's there to service
Fake expert about the account
A bunch of s*** about how terrible
So here's the part of it where to tell you
South
That gold was the place to go
We left that to our buddies
Whoops
To doodle
Horrible prediction
Things for the future
This is right after Alex
Controlled him
His stories about the e
Evils of volunteerism and volunteer there
There's a rumor in the bill is past the house on its way for sure Passage
Beginning of Terranea
People that write about it
Recurring all the places
Did you mention
Just now
And John
The plans
Being put in place
How long will it take
I think maybe
Week
Coronavirus
Centex here
And
By the end of the year
And I don't
Think that's enough
To get people cranked up
And so I think
Sometime during 20
Demonstrations are going to be
Happening in America in
Turn off my timing belt
I think they're going to
Wait at cookout your own prediction there at the end
Really bold the world is going to end
But I might be wrong I couldn't never know
I would like the forecast
If you think you might be wrong prediction
Dickweed
Book jokes please date
Don't do that
Don't you remember how Skilling always comes up. Doing the weather is like hated my ring
Sometimes rain takes a little bit longer than you think
You don't get to play these games and then likely like I'm going to give myself and Mike
National forecast
Prince forecast
Summer of Rage
Oldest
You're a forecaster
Talkington
Who has already many times
Can men be so wrong all the time
It's crazier
What they mean or you know when you save forecast
After we think of it
What they're talking about
Is they cast
Forest
Okay no thank you
Agents for our bottle
Does nonsense conversation about Alex's scared about everything
Alex
Bob about how manly
Manly Bob look
Alex
Canby
Nobody's calling about
Probably not
Manly is s***
Annamalai ambitious
Yes you do
I don't know
Great answer Bob
How much would it look
Bob
You got it
Getting paid pretty well not well enough to just sit there through
I know there's others
It could be really hard not to laugh
I don't know
Like maybe.
Do that I don't really care it doesn't really care
I do believe the part about him
Overkill after he took them
Conceivably
Listen to like with Jon Ronson
Testimony
About what happened
Mangrove
Lying about everything
Complete lies
Like his coverage
Defend himself
So real
Weird
Murder in that guy one time
So here's the park
Depends I guess.
Gold sales
This part is a little bit more
Giant days
About $60 to get side
Today was off 280
Something like that which is miniscule
And we'll probably have a soft day on Monday
But next week is going higher
On the Franks and on the
Sovereign
Montana gold
Now I have to put a block on selling out of
And not many people do this Ted
It was a stroke of Genius
Yeah I'm right here Alex
I don't know about the stroke of Genius because
Figure out that have gold drops right now with
What's going on in Washington DC
Alright whatever
I can't imagine I can't imagine anybody listening to this
Completely passive way cuz I can understand
Episode of this show
I'm not being like
Just
The Bob Chapman Ted Anderson
Vinny Appice I guess
Those little set-pieces alone should be like
Can't trust these dudes
Even not knowing that might not knowing that a couple years later
After this point Anderson will have his license taken away
Dishonest Trading
Even not knowing those things you just hear
This will get you into the free card
It's so crazy
Broken listen to this and drop you like
I think they're trying to find marks
Is not
It's not crazy to me at all
It's sad
Bad how utterly believable
To know that he's gay
I should wait until Monday
And then
What you said
Right now
The others like I understand
You know the game is
They're playing on
4 years of the economic collapse
So you buy the gold it really matter how much it goes up
Is the dollar going to collapse worth
Broadway
Yeah you will have to
Take a bite out of
Understand
They're framing playing on in order to
Yeah
Like Bob is coming in with like
It was up 60
Or whatever
Because that's not enough
To Mater
For the kind of investors who are listening
Like if you're listening
Probably couldn't afford an ounce of gold
800 something dollars and it goes up 60
Are you just going to sell it then and then you've made
$60
I don't think
The investment in Gold doesn't make sense
No
It really doesn't of the economics
Which is why that's
The selling point that they use as opposed to like
It being a smart investment you can make a little bit of money
It's not just that but it's also
By preying upon his audience which is not
I'm going to go out on a limb and say billionaires
By praying on these people
They are
Scrambling together $800
They think it's going to last
Last forever and it's going to go up
Austin eventually
Going to be worth it
+ 2
It feels good to own a little bit of gold
I can understand that
At the very least you're like oh well at least I've got this money in
Invest it
Yeah there's there's something to that
The deceitful awful
Fraud
No other word for it this is
It's like it makes you feel like if you've ever had
Like a bunch of cash in your
Even if it's
Nothing to
In your hand
Very attractive
Do a lot of people
Maybe
Buy it baby
Moving on from Bob Chapman
Display
Alex has another guest
Is very excited
And talk
Her name is Amy Allen
And she is a musician
She wrote a song called Ron Paul
Alright alright I forgot about this photo Taylor Swift
Taylor Swift
Of the past
Apparently during Ron Paul
Thing it was like a big anthem of his campaign
Now there's some interesting elements of Amy Allen that I'm going to get into as we discussed
Because
Alex wants to talk about how she got
No she was a victim of an assault
Alex wants to
To talk about that
A lot
And I think
Not great
But also I want to make clear before we get into any of this I do believe that
She was the victim of a crime
Yeah and I'm not in any way minimizing that
And I'm not making fun of her
For being attacked
I do believe that
Yeah I don't believe a lot of the window dressing
People
Like Alex Jones
And other folks
Have put on
I assume she
She's going to be explained
A little
Maybe
How quickly Alex wants to
To talk about
Where's the rail
Who want Liberty wants to understand that we have a new world order taking over
Our nation and they're very afraid of popular culture
Further popularizing the message of Liberty
Towards doing that for South by Southwest
They're coming up with her but it's great to have you here in Austin Texas
Thank you so much
There was
Talking about
I still
Continuing
Los Angeles
There was actually Fullerton for the Tea Party
And 15,000 people came out
Protest the tax increases
Shut down the
Ad campaign for Liberty Rumpole should have been present
No
I'm not going to go along with it is it really Multicultural
Documents
I'll bring the international crime syndicate to Justice now
Warrior
10-minute and 3-second
To talking with her in order to
To bring up this
Which is a little quick I think it interview possibly
Unless that's all you want to talk about
Yeah
Instantly goes to
Talk about this party
Through the prism of okay
Cuz that's where he's at
Because that sort of
Confirm
Some of the feelings we had on the last episode
Chipotle
I'm not making this up he really wants
What's the talk about that beat
A lot
And I'm not stealing anything
It was very bizarre
I mean there's three of us
And they pushed
My friend out of the way
To Target
My head and face
Is my mouth
The crowbar
I had time to cash the dump. A person telling them to take our money
And
Victim
I think
I think they were I don't know they were
Mexican gang members
That looks like the government or somebody hired him or it was a gang initiation
The only two options
Someone hired a government
Vines to the government
One hired him
And I okay
I don't know what happened here obviously I have no idea I can only go based on her telling of
The event and
Amy broke the story today on the Alex Jones Show online Internet show
She says the police told her the attackers were most likely illegal in
Investigate the brutal attack
Amy was leaving the recording studio in Downtown LA with thugs attacked her at random
They're simply looking for a white person to attack
I believe that Amy was the victim of an assault and I think that's horrible
However I take issue with all this time
People make about this
Situation
Racially-motivated attack
Against her because she was a white woman
That was from Stormfront
New World Order
Amy was told not to talk about revolution in her music
And she refused
So they sent a Latino hit squad The Punisher
My problem with that is that
Album was called I would start a revolution if I could get up in the morning
The first thing on the album was literally just titled Revolution
News produced by goddamn Randy Jackson and Mark Ronson
One of the album featured appearance by Pharoahe Monch
School in 2002
He had it
Also the attack
Happened in 2000
Who's six years after
She put out an album called I would start a revolution
If I could get up in
In the morning World Order Alex Jones
Or putting out
This idea that you was threatened because
She Wrote a Song
Putting up music they had revolution in
Which is known
It's absolute nonsense
It is
Absolutely using
As a prompt
It's gross
It's really really gross
I feel
The whole album was tracks were produced by Mark and Randy Jackson
Play with journey
Play bass
I'm dirty like some shows
That
Absolutely
I feel really
I feel bad
I feel bad for her being in this situation
Where there is entire world trying to
Galvanized race-based hatred
Order new world order fear
Based on
Did her being the victim of a crime it really
Imagine
Any scenario
I can't imagine
Did any historical
Scenario where rabble-rousing
People would
Take the attack of a woman and then
Turn it into a reason
To demonize the population
That seems
Crazy
We haven't seen that since a couple months ago
In order to do harm to a larger
Community of minority
Exercise
It is a sick bomber and
Everyone
Losers
Except for Alex
Bike rack
You can even hear it in her voice when he was asking what these people looked like she had a reticence to talk about
Really didn't want to say because I think there was a sense that you like
What is going to come of me
Describing the these people
Alex is probably going
Play something off-color
Or it could end up being reported on Stormfront as a race attack
I think she had some kind of awareness of it
Because
I need to tell you
Amy Allen is not
Somebody who's unaware of
These worlds
How do you wake up to the New World Order
Well
Montana
It's a little bit like
Since I was a kid
Raised
Raise
With that
As a small child
Enter.
So
Amy Allen
Was born in 1982 and was raised
Paranoid family
Oh no I thought you I thought you were about to know I thought you were about to like save it
You're done some research
Since you was raised like a
Literal sepehr
This group hold on
No
Paranoid about the New World Order
Inman
Tana
Is Montana along with Idaho
White nationalist separatist communities in the 1990
81bay standoff
For the FBI after the land where they would hold their mock trials was foreclosed
The militia of Montana was Super Active
Ideology is shockingly similar to Alex's
And a little Glimpse that we get into Amy's family of origin
It'd be impossible to make any definitive claim based on this little bit of info that we have
But the fact that Amy describes her mother's belief system this way
The timeline and the fact that they were in an unspecified town in Montana leads me to believe there's a high likelihood that a negro
White nationalist militia
Again I can't say this for sure
Those are some of the biggest signs pop
Yeah the 1990s Montana
Anti-government sentiments fear of the New World Order
Those are all
Those are red flags
Yeah we're talking about Montana
Chicago
Thirsty
12 people live in
Nationalist
Malicious
Montana and Idaho
It is
Something that's very historically
I'm not
Her family absolutely
Part of that
But you can't come from a family like that
And not be aware of it
It's pretty funny
Oh you're the master race
Well they could pay their bills but they were doing it by writing bad
So that was kind of part of the problem
Yeah the the Montana freedmen getting a lot of trouble for bank fraud
Cuz they were just
They just write the rent check
Text
Supposed to represent real money
It sound like
Conservative
I'm not saying anything about her based on what
Context clues I can
Glean
For a family of four
I'm just saying that I don't believe in any way
Did someone who grew up in Montana in the 90s
Wo does have somewhere nice of white nationalist militia
Yeah it's almost impossible
Which is why she had the
Instinctive
I think so
Action of like
I know
Maybe
I feel like I need
To tell the truth but I
Kind of get
Like
She's coming in and doesn't know what she's getting into his show and stuff like that
But I do think it's possible to live in a space where
You are in Turon Paul and you do want to audit the Fed
And maybe your
Willingly
Blind to some of the others
You just have the
Privilege involved in your life where you don't need
Unpack
And we're fans of Alec
What's Jones in 2009
Want
You know like it was
Like I'm just waking up
There were a lot of liberals
Shemar Moore
The next clip is just her talking more about her mom that's kind of the same things
Stockpiling
Food
Intuit
This mixed with
Is something that tells me
That
He doesn't know her audience as well as she
My plan is to do tea party
But the album
Lot of reggae
Tea party and notoriously
Kerry Cassidy
Huge
Cheese
Security party
You could not be less
Reggae
No I'm not not you
I don't
Stan Wiki
What is the exact words
It's using your mouth isn't it
I don't
How do you do that
Any other way
Wanting to talk about
All you're doing is super good job evidence
So there's other ways to
Talk about this
Without
Why
Did you say that
That's that's that's made out of someone else's
And that's not fair
I'm really ugly
Here's what I
I am going to tell you
And I want you to feel
We're done with that for now Alex
Accidentally
Tell someone
Dirty business
Some of their dirty laundry gets aired on
Alex's show
In a way that I don't
Person wants to know the public
3 years
Dollars
And
Anti-war
The start of the war just to muzzle him
I literally
First of all this isn't true
He signed a contract for $3000000
Showed up to his first day on the job
Ill-fitting suit
Now you need to understand what we're going to do
You're going to say what we
Tell you to say
You're going to cover what we
We tell you to cover it if
You go off script
For even a moment
You are
John
You know what I mean
Not going to do this
Give me my money and I will go surf
He's sold out the country for 9 million dollars
I will just take all of my money for that
Also please
F****** consider
He had been the mayor of Brooklyn Park Minnesota
4 years already
He was the f****** Governors Minnesota
I think he would be Savvy enough to be like
He's already super out
Spoken weirdo
The voice of the WWE app for a baby with a professional wrestler who is a Marine
Professional wrestlers are understanding contracts
Massive career up till that point already
Let's
Predator
Governor of a state
A picture
So is this is true that I was intentionally
Really feel like that the breach of contract
Also I mean
Could actually look at his
His book
Is a bibliography
You could say
Works out
Cuz I'm 2002e wrote a book called Jesse Ventura tells it like it is America's most outspoken Governor speaks out
They didn't write another book
That's 6 years not
That's confusing
Yes already said
All all
All of your unspoken
It's really hard to name books to because I'm 20120 talk Democrats and Republicans
Democrats and Republicans
I was public Republic
Stop the name books so
Scenario
Ventura took $9000000 in order to
Do not speak out against the war that
Philosophic
We against and ended up leading to
Conn's in tons
Civilian deaths
And so that makes him a
Coward
Worst case scenario autism
That's the best-case scenario
I don't think Jesse Ventura would appreciate it like this on air
Anyway
Studio
And
They start taking some calls
And its first call its first its first color is
Is awesome okay
Sing anything about pro-guns Amy
Anything about the gun called for anything like that
I do have a song
Play reggae
Is part of me in it
Have a gun culture is a big issue Amy right now in the
Small town
Versailles Missouri that's where I
David North Raleigh have their power hour show
Friend of mine told me last night he called me a
The teachers
Real Steel
13 sing the kids that guns are bad and making
Nadia faizan in their classwork now and then they're
Tell him it's bad for him
Kids
Volume
I know this guy man 7-Eleven
Not literally Versailles Missouri
I've spent some time
Around
The smaller towns in Missouri I know this cat
Play with Ava Missouri
There's a lot of French
Cairo Cairo Missouri
Paris
Anyway
Yeah I know Dino
I love the idea that was like
Who's the singer on I'm going to call
She has songs
About guns
The gun culture vulture
Gun culture is very important right now because I just got a report was very credible source
They're trying to get kids to your dad
You're bad
I know for a fact
Is not the
Case because I've been to Versailles and
Everybody
Any place in Missouri
Largely any City that
But isn't
Columbia
St Louis or Kansas City
Is going to be full of that guy
Ulta
Bulshit
Paternalism
Sick move of like
I hear that
Another Direction
So they take another call
Are the shows
Missouri weird Direct
PayPal
Say thank you to you and Amy for doing a good job
Patriots thank you
Well she can read though that's the
I just wanted to move on I want to try to
I want to let you know about local or a 40p county to try to sneak this through it says the regulating to purchase ammunition
And what it is
When you start reading this it's on Albany county.com
Right on the website you go to local while legislature
And here I was going to read Section 5 real quick quick
A record shall be kept by the jewelry
Dealer of
Each cell domination with your shoulder type caliber
Quality ammunition sold
Name and address of the person receiving the same
The caliber
Make model manufacture
Name and serial number of the firearm which the purchase
Pittsburgh
Stop stop stop
This is why we are always way ahead everything cuz he was got that
If I understand correctly
He is mad
Because
People are going to have to
To write down
Why he
He's buying at me
Curative goobot
Good Records
For like
People shot today
It would help
Recently bought
There's that you want to just take a
Like a little step backwards
Touchy about the idea of like
Any kind of regulation of guns leads to a registration
I'm fine with that
I mean I know that people can enjoy guns recreationally and
Do you know it's not an evil thing or scary or anything like that
You know it is
Like if you really look at it through things like
Fertilizer
But if you buy fertilizers
Is it can be used
There's a registry event
Haven't LED
To the nightmare scenarios that people like Alex
Builders ideas like
As soon as they ever record buddies fertilizer
No one's taking anybody
But his car is because of these
These rules that we put in place to mitigate Danger
You can't even buy that much allergy medication
Two people taking away
Or anything like that
Sudafed isn't
Gone
It's just better control
So
You can make a substance that can
It's almost like we should know
I don't
This is that cray
This proposed law in Albany
We'll get more into that here in a second
Because Alex
You can hear it
He's freaking out
Furniture
Is Rhino lumiguard Schenectady
That's right
Albany county.com Department legislature
Revolution 108 local law number 84 2009
Do you have trouble sleeping
That is rough cut off in the middle of emergency by a hard day
Do you have trouble
So
You can see there
Hear the wheels turning in his head
I was like oh my God
Connect this to the Schenectady story
This is amazing
Combined
Give us the coordinates for this
Albany New York surrounding counties
Federal martial law
He In that clip was 30 seconds long said I haven't read
Screenshot
Also this is connected
This thing I don't know anything about it
Little bit
This guy is that on
It's email this to Rob do after I've reported the story
What if it wasn't
What's this called was making it up he's reported that it's connected to this other live in your belly
Because from what I can tell it didn't pass
Regulation
Completely legal and not violate the Second Amendment
The dead past
All I really want to point out here is absolutely not breaking the scoop
You can find an article about the proposed law that was posted on the NRA's website that uses the exact using
And likes to the URL that he's trying to read Alex on air
That post was from the morning of March 20th 2009
This isn't the scoop
It's just Alex picking up NRA sloppy seconds
Most importantly that's nothing to do with the story that Alex is misrepresenting a disconnected
Those titties are about half an hour away by car
Good traffic
Turn up
SimCity
Schenectady is in Schenectady County where is albinism Albany
Not even in the same
The goddamn thing nearest Publix
Is gerrymandering
He's just shoot-from-the-hip
Don't you remember what happened
Obama smart martial law martial law
Took over Albany
Congratulations
I have it ready training
Martial law
The next week but
Tour with your wig to remember
Going back is not your friend
A b
So interesting Lee what you have here
Is Alex Jones starting to Broughton
By talking about how he's always right and everyone attacks
For being
Right all the time cuz the truth comes out and he was right all along but he's up against that barbed wire and I once climbed over him
Now towards the end of the show he gets
These two stories that he's juggling
Any runs with it without reading anything about it
And that back
Landscape
So self-satisfied like
I have now done my work and they will attack proven right
It's it
Almost like a perfect
Narrative Arc
Like you set up the theme of the show at the beginning of I am unjustly demonized for being right all the time
And now at the end here
Demonstrated that he's right all the time now
I welcome the attack
Meanwhile people
And they laugh and they say that I'm not a real journalist
What is journalism
But hearing a call
Not getting any confirmation and Reporting it
It's true
Actually name the clip Alex
Congratulate himself
We're doing 0ja
So many things you should have
Call Schenectady
You should have had robbed
Miseno's the area haven't call Albany
Call the people who are listed in the press release
Like it's not hard that would be doing if you're trying to
Report accurately
If you want to spend these Yarns
About like oh this is all no takeover
What you do is you still called they give you no comment then you report that they gave you no comment
That's what you do
And then is it
Reported they gave no comment that sounds suspicious to the people that you want to
Sounds
Step one
Crazy
Awful
Just because you didn't have a song about the gun
It shouldn't
F***
You
Studio after this
There's a lot of
Just two clips
The show
Hotel
India
This idea of not reading thing
Wallowing around
In ignorance
Presenting and masquerading itself as wisdom
Is every
All of these people in Alex Jones's world
No matter how credibly they presented
Themselves
Are guilty of the exact
So here's the first
Where he talks about
Obama's National
Specifically
This is Barack Obama's National Security advisor
Okay
It's right off
The Council on Foreign Relations
Website is from the city of Pharr
Show that the
Do you think this quote
And I'll say this
I do not care to defend Kissinger
Absolutely
Even after he left
It's formal position
Especially whenever he was orchestrating
The shift
Complete bulshit
If you read the opening remarks
From James dork
You find that he says quote
As the most recent National Security advisor of the United
Orders from Doctor Kissinger
Filter down through General Brent
And Sandy Berger who is also here
We have a chain of command in the
Security Council that exist today
There's no indication from the transcript that he speaking literally
Or if it's just a little wink-and-nod kind of joke to open the
Even leaving that aside it's important
Consider what he's actually saying
Although won't rostro is technically the First National
What that position
After him
Cambridge Skokie
Well actually came too big
Well we don't take orders from
He had all kinds of wild ID
So like there is this idea of
It's not I don't think you literally about taking orders from them
I think he's talking about these are the people who have died
Define the position
They set the precedent
They've given us guidance on what it is
We do right and I'm not naive enough
To say that
Those people weren't in some way
Capacity
Twerking
It's pretty clear if you look at their arm
There are indications
Advise on
Security Council
The directory
But I think it's a little bit of a stretch
Literally
Okay so what happened
Kissinger says something
Then he whispers and Brent scowcroft
And then he goes and talks to Sandy Berger
Who then tells me what to do
Video crafted Burger
The language indicates to me
The filtering down is the lineage of the
It's not this literal thing
So Jim Morris
Like I understand what
I'm not going to
I understand what you doing
But you're demonstrating an inability to
Wrestle with contacts
Because also the rest of this speech
CFR
Was about the idea that he wanted to hell
Appreciate the
So there was a hearkening to Legacy
The beginning of it
Speaking to Waze
That the modern challenges of the world
Such that
A different approach
Might be necessary
Element that exists
Speech if you read it as a whole you cannot
Ever use new
Caulking
You can't
Do you can't do it
They just
Don't understand
They can't read
They don't understand
You can't use a metaphor
You can't even but you can't even pretend to use the metaphor otherwise Alex
Confirm
Stroop
Anyway it one more clip of Jim Marrs
And it should show you kind of how he does his
Frank I have not looked at leaving this post but I know that just from what I've seen and glancing over some of the
Paragraphs in this proposed legislation
He's going to mean you can't
Have a
I glanced
Over
Legislation
You know
Something that's notoriously easy to glance over at a little over
Legalistic bulshit language inspections referring to other subsections
A couple closet
Well they're trying to get rid of your foot
Garden
They were just right of bills rid of your garden
It's irresponsible to come on a show that is so
Bad
And say something like that you're like I haven't read any of his books
You can't evergarden
Like that's f****** stupid stupid
Stupid
This needs
Very clear
When you engage with legislation like that
And you make
Options
About what it's talking about you end up wrong
Almost all the time
You can demonstrate this with Alex Jones his favorite subsection
About chemtrail
The one that if you just read one piece of it
Sounds like
I got this
This is
Anybody as long as it's a research
If you only skim it and Yuri
That section of it
It looks that way
Have to look at it
Cuz there's another part that says
That section there
That you're reading that's scary
Is subject to subsection that stays informed
Consent of all four
Required
It does not work
But there might be something in that legislation that sounds scary but there's another thing that
Weekly invalidates whatever
And that's almost always the case
When I look into these
Alright
New
Proposal for a
If you're going to cover Legend
And and claim that you're a jerk
You have to
The first
Go to
College
Alex
But
Specifically
Understand
Pacific
And then
Continuing education hours
If Alex's dad has to do that dentist
Test proving that you understand the Civic
Prosthetics is super bored
And if you feel it then you don't get to talk
It's against the law to get your journalism license
VRBO
Civics is super important
Because like
Or even if
Well not lying
How bills are passed
What
Mean and stuff like that
He couldn't spend most of the stories that
Like these ideas what he has now that he's talking about like also if they succeed in suing me the Sandy Hook family
Ensuing me
The first
Amendments gone
Which anybody has a basic understanding of
How are
Government operates
But you know what
I'm actually starting to think that law isn't Arab
What affects about how easy that would make getting rid of fox
Because if you have
Vegetation requirement
Then you can prove
They're lying about
Plausible deniability
Keyboard
You know that because they are out
To pass a test
We already know that
Confirm
Exactly
But now there's no
There's a lot that says you got to
Define let's regulate
I have Alex freak out about it
March 22nd
Not worth talking about
So that's off the table
But I really think I wish that that those Jim Morris
Important and demonstrative
How stupid ever wanted
And how
Fast and loose they are with details
Intelligence reports
Leaving about
I think it's important
But I wish they weren't in there
Is there such a satisfying art
To Alex's blow Hardy
I'm the victim and I'm always right
To the end of the episode where
Completely misrepresent
2 stories
I'm saying they're can
So
Alex is just bad
You got it.
Fila website
About that
Story that
Reminder
So much
I bet no living blackbird
Has ever had
Has ever been
No living black person has had as much racism applies as I have it a white person
Same like
Idea of
I got it
This is this
Proves
Everything that I
I've ever thought about how I am validated
That's why he wants
To talk about
Caribou
But like the other thing that I need to make clear I don't know if I did a good enough job of it I read a bunch of interviews
That cuz I wanted
Text ordered under
And like
What else
Crime with a big part of her
Career
It's like she talks about how afterwards she
Like really valued things differently
Like that
In every interview that I
Confined with her
She doesn't talk about it being like
Some sort of
Government hit
She doesn't talk about the being next
Second gang Bangerz or anything like that
Details that come from this interview
Extrapolated by ronpaulforums
Storm fried all of these other play
That's not something that she talks
What about in interviews
With music public aid is there any other
So I don't
I don't think that she is on the
It doesn't seem that way
It seems like
For putting that there
For her
Cuz I don't
Venn diagram of all the
They love it that
They're coming for our women
They're their animals
I don't even want it
I would make sense
Play Stoler money but they didn't
Like all of that stuff just all come
Comes together to me
Perfect Storm of white guys
Justified
Committed
And meanwhile
A about they're coming for a women while they repeatedly tell her how hot she is
That's not really relevant there
Navigate to same time
Perception of
Today or animals
I'm a vicious animal
So I don't know
We are on social media
Plural
The chirp
We're on Facebook
We have a Facebook group
Correct you can go to
Itunes.com
Un
That's right
Flash
Podcast
Slash
Knowledge
Flash legislation
We don't have time for that
Send me a screenshot I will do that alright
Please button do
Brother
I will tell you this
I know who I know that Alex
Does not have any
About the gun
That he's rich
No I know that
He is a vicious animal
Tell you how I
Cuz that he probably
Technically
Alexandra Thurston color