Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Alex Jones
When was the last
What time you had a knife
Ice cream sundae I don't know when you go to like one of those frozen yogurt places in you make your own thing
Cuz you could put like that
Pump
But I still don't know
I was just wondering if it County
Time
My dad loves ice cream
Okay then my brother now owns an ice cream shop
I don't think I got that Gene
I'm not super into ice
The grabit
I'm more of a
Who would I be in terms of
Dessert
Candy bar
Furthermore
Follow
I don't know if I've ever actually had that.
Let me tell you
My brother
I feel like it is just
A bowl
You got a bowl That's essential yeah
Maybe not maybe put it in a car supposed to be like isn't it supposed to be like
Just put like hot
Call John it and then you're good then you got a Sunday I don't know
Alright well then let's have this episode and find out
Ice cream sundae
Thank you sweetie
First of all
We appreciate it so very much
Thank you you are now a policy wonk
I like
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Someone someone sodomites
Caribbean
Black shirt
I don't want
Thank you so much. Thank you very much.
What we have in front of us is a situation where
To go over
We have November 2nd
2018 to go over
And today
And no one enjoys a present-day episode
Deeply truncated episode if this is an episode where we decide hey Alex is really afraid of white
And then cut all those
You've heard it all before we don't need to play for clips of him saying that Alex Jones
Worried white people are going to do well
The normal
Sort of stuff that he gets into
Couple of
Stupid narratives
There's no
This episode is just really bad on a water level
And I don't want to
Talk about it so much
It's so much that we've already gone over 100 times
And I don't want to waste our listeners time I don't want to waste my time while I'm not feeling great
So I just want to cut through all the bulshit
And just play you
A couple of really important
Because they are very important
Some a couple of things that he says on the show
Are are
Dammit
And some of its kind of
The first cup I'm going to play for you here is Alex
Talking about
Trump's recent comments
About how
If you throw rocks
We might shoot you at the border that Alex would not be in favor of that
It's probably a little Overkill
Military
U.s. kill more cops
Commercial video
Christman
You will be treated as military
If world
In front of you while you do it
You little dirtbag
We're putting you on notice
Call Deshawn
Across
The bow
The first one's free
Control
Know that
Isn't this a message to Iran
Stripper meme
That you have pushed so far you people are so crazy
Actions are coming
November 6th
Get ready
Sanctioned
Before the election debates in 2016
Trump was throwing you in prison Hillary Clinton
Cendere we are you
There's so many of these things
Carrots
If we win the midterm
It's so pathetic
And then heading into that this idea that you like yeah yeah
You throw a rock
We're going to shoot you and that is what should happen we've learned about this Palace
But years ago not that long ago
Alex was
Just use that as an example of like
Yes absolutely it's a great idea to shoot people who throw rocks
Is deep
Deeply troubling
He could throw his support behind
The US Military
Murdering
Thousands of people
There's a lot of guys wearing
Full body armor with semi-automatic rifles
As well as other battle accoutrement
Sure the other side there are
Women and children escaping Honduras under threat
Places where they don't have all of those things
And they're bringing their kids to just survive
On one side you got those guys those are cute
The big rocks
Yeah this is awful
And this is one of the reasons why this show sucks so much
In the present
Because we know enough about Alex to know like
Hey man
You have gone like you have gone
So far away from what you stood for
You should know
Go back to where you were nothing like that
Not great.
Awful
To look at this interview like
You lost it
You never had it but you lost
You still lost it and never had it
Mainstream thought
We need the military On the Border
What else is a military for
I don't know anymore either
No principles
It doesn't even matter
F****** so stupid
So if Alex wants
Be afraid
Caravan
Coming up here
I want to change
Change America
Into another
Used up by the system used by
Underclass for the laps you want slaves
And they're coming here in Flagstaff
Anyways
T-shirt
These days
Hurt more cuz they're just like
You are
He's spending all of his time talking about
There's a hundred thousand two hundred thousand people
All slamming into the border is an invasion Force
Venezuela also we have
Terrifying
Why why
Why
Would you
That
A group of people
Spleen
Asylum
But their own country
Would want to then bring that style of government here
Does he not know why people are coming
I mean he he thinks he
You knows it but it's
It's not
Is that the people that are coming
Weather going to change
Country
The people on the ground
You are forcing the chaos in order for the
Global
Globalist
Combines in order they are going to change it into Venezuela
That's more
That makes perfect
Ludacris
Equip Alex's f******
Fired up
On this episode
He's going Full Tilt Boogie
If you will allow the
U-turn phrase
Explain
Why he's fired
Literally globalist
Movies
What was
Indeed.com
Call me by your name about
Man old man
That
Sad I think the nun was actually about Raceway
Did you did you notice
Groceries really not immediately after saying
This is not red
Otherwise you're like
We have to go kill the other guys
Weather
There's a problem
Went further being like this isn't rhetoric and then using it very clear rhetorical technique where you at listen to
Emotional response out of your audience
That's rhetoric to a T
That's exactly what he's doing
I'm going to use this rhetoric in order to Prime
But it's not a rapper
I'm going to ask myself a question and then you will listen rhetorically
This makes poop is really the reason why
Even though I realize that most of the stuff isn't worth going over
Like
Elvis episode he's complaining about Michael Moore
Be eliminated
He's just talkin about a staff Myers interview where he doesn't say that
He's talking about Oprah Winfrey talking about how all old white people need to die out
He plays an interview from
Where she doesn't even say that she just
The people she's asked the question of whether or not the problem of racism has been solved
Jesus going today
No absolutely not you know we have a whole lot of people
Have been soaked
Did marinated in the cultures racism
Prejudice
Need to die
They need to die out
Jinsei white people at all
That they always reveal exactly what it is
There's a lot of stuff like that
Don't I don't care
Just don't care
But this I care about very much
This makes clip
Is
Problem
Lawsuits against
You got to let them come
Understood
Benin flood up with million
Call
The UN and the globalist
He just said
Trump
Has initiated rex-84
Now
This
Is perhaps
The most
F*****-up thing I've ever heard come out of his mouth
Alex
Something that is recently is 2016 screaming about it being part of the globalist
Here are some headlines
2009 RAV4
U.s. Constitution
The article is about out
Because of wrecks
It 2012
FEMA camp rendition hubs discovered article mostly before
His entire career
Alex Jones made it a Cornerstone of his rhetoric that the big
Threat that he was standing up against was government tyranny
They presented itself in the form of
FEMA camps
Used to set up
He spent countless hours detailing his perverse fantasies
Of fighting off the Imagine
And what are the big pieces that he always
This wasn't just
Sup
In baking the stuff up with the existence of rex-84
It is real therefore what I'm saying isn't bulshit was basically his argument
Rex 84 was the plan that Ollie North came up with
There was a
The Detention of communist and leftist
Let nothing to do with Alex
But because it's sort of thematic Leaf it with his stupid FEMA camp narrative
He and Larry Nichols in particular would use it to drum up fear in his audience at this was coming
He were days away
But I'm coming for you
I find it pretty
Piccalilli pathetic and stick
Good thing
For Trump to use rex-84 to deal with these Refuge
Career out of arguing the rex-84 is the literal blueprints
We used to bring in martial law in this country
And the fact that you celebrating the idea of using such a
Here is very clear indication
Northeast
Is very cold
Alex Jones does not care about tyranny
He was really really doesn't want that tyranny to be targeted towards wife
If a black man is in office
Cuz he might
Then
And here's the bigger
Richard Jordan
In his entire career
Did the tyrannies at that he's afraid of
The implementation.
You playing very unpopular that people wouldn't be into it
In order for something like rex-84 to be implemented his imaginary bad guys would need to create a false flag
Pretext in order to implement
These villains
Have a manufactured crisis in order to bring a plant
What do we see in front of us right now
It was a
Caravan that came along every year is almost like a symbolic Act
Just blatantly lie about this immigrant
Event coming up
The American Border
To stand there in
Situation
Where Donald Trump
Essentially said
PewDiePie if you got them
That whole thing
Are you staying
Qualify as this crisis
Interesting
I mean Alex over inflates the number of people in the Caravan of hundreds of thousands
Has a strong Army
The right-wing media refers to visit in as an invasion in the f****** stupid president
People throw stones
An article in the Washington Post today was putting a number of people in the group at approximately 4,000
Which is right in line with stories that have been coming out about the numbers dropping
Past week
They were passing through Veracruz 626 miles
From the closest border crossing
Approximately 204 more hours of walking
You didn't take any break
This isn't something it's that to culminate on Election Day is Alex
Clams are
And most importantly nothing that these people are doing or plan to do is illegal according to US law
They're refugees fleeing violence in Central America native every right to make it to the border and plead for Asylum
Whether or not they get it is an administrative matter but they're entirely within their rights
You're totally right this entire pageant play out is it
Concerted effort by the right-wing media to manufacture a crisis
And we've seen the mainstream media be woefully incompetent in their reporting
And it doesn't solve
You could make the argument that most of the right-wing is jumping on board with this traffic in this false reality
Because they know that without something
A lot of them
But that
Can't work for Alex Jones
Based on his career
He knows
All Alex does is warranted a shadowy group of Bad actors are coming to manufacture a crisis in order to put
An unpopular and probably illegal plan people in camps
In place
And the process will use the military as a way
Breeches Papi, Tata
2018 is an active participant manufacturing crisis
It's being used to push through on
Probably illegal plans at least people
Which involves using the military to breathe
He is exactly what he has warned everyone about
Pathetic
I mean if it
If it were like a
Andy Kaufman
Sketches
Brillion
Well it's a tragedy
20 years
Building up this anti-establishment character only
Turn heel
At the opportune moment
Set 80 Kaufman all over
Uno's
One of the reasons why I feel like
I'm in I'm out of sorts
I have no words
I am deeply disgusted by this sort of
This sort of thing
I felt like
Every time we've seen him be like
You know earlier couple of months ago or so
We checked in on him and he was saying that it's great
The Trump is going to send the military to the Border
This is real
I thought that was
Surprising I'm disappointed in you
But I didn't
Get the FEMA camp stuff
Was negotiable
For him like you know what I'm saying
He's made
Multiple documentaries
The building up of the fear of
This exact thing now advocating
Just nothing
Everything you believed in a gun
Stop it
We have to quit.
Conclusion I don't know
In this like long tragic
Kind of tale of rising
Meaninglessness
They were all global
Completely
Every single one of his like this is the last one
Of him actually advocating
For the very thing that he has been
He's he's now
OSHA
That's actually good
Let's do that one
In the reason he's able to do is your dad even in
The Liberals
Retcon stuff
But that is been very present
Like even just a year or two ago that was his line
2D ID
I'm trying to rewrite this idea
It means you have to rewrite
That everything is up for grabs
Nothing he believes
Or or
I mean he could just be like
DirecTV
Everything is gone
He wants to kill the Younglings too
Come on man
I guess what I wanted to hear is
Michaux
Is predictable
Present-day episode
Is very pretty
Stupid fear-mongering about the Refuge
Fuji cameras
Stupid
White genocide
That stuff is all like yes
Seeing all this
But the idea that he's advocating
Literally
Trump is putting in place Rex 84
It just means to be like
It's not interesting
I do I don't know if that makes sense but it's not interesting to me because
What interest me is true
When we
Shows that I can in the pack
It's it's interesting to me
To hear him lie of whole bunch
MN learn
About
XYZ
I understand that there's a
Probably an interesting
Human story here with a man
Who's gone so far
Down a terrible path
But he's advocating for the very thing you made six documentaries
But it's not really interesting
Yeah yeah
Expected
Think you would be that Brazen we don't generally make predict
Cuz we did this
Back
Second
It's parody it sees a parody of himself
You know what else to say
Fascinator
F*** you don't have to
We've gone through all of these different
. and Alex Jones Is Life
Never even even when we saw him jump on Trump
I never would have expected him to have
Literally denied all of his
Principles
Thumbs up
I think that's because that's one of the most
Important things
Edsby
Protection of white
That sort of thing
I didn't get that
The biggest
It's non-negotiable
Like we're never going to see that change
He's never going to come out like in favor of multiculturalism
Of that one
I think the bigger issue is that what I mean you've already served a touchdown
It is not
Presenting himself as
I'm very passionate about and caring about
He didn't really care about
Is on
Doing his wife's work
In recontextualizing it in some sort of weird way
Like
If you'd studied RX8
Before and realize that it was all the liberal plot or whatever
When did that happen
When did it start
Send in decided to start eating like out
What did you study tell you that
I don't know what to do
Future goals for Alex
This looks grim
I hate to feel bad for him
But I just
I don't know you know it's like it's like you have an enemy
You hate them
10 years
Go back to
Your hometown you find them
Drunk at noon at the bar
Hey it's hard to hate you and I'll come on man I got to go
Whatever it was you lost
Whatever it is I got to go
Like in Grosse Pointe Blank whenever
John Cusack meets up with a volley from his high school
Amazing
Notebook.com
We also have a present
Barely on it
Facebook
What if you wanted to find us in a downloadable format where you're living with other podcast
Something
I'm sorry I'm feeling under the weather
And I don't want to do a present day episode
And that's all of the clips that I have
I realize that would be marginally unsettling or unsatisfying
Four people out there and I apologize
Something that's a little bit more
Good and hopefully
Midterms
If you if you want to
Play Aisha
Anyway
Listen
Rex 84
It is now though
Corndance
As far as I know that plan is never killed
Although one guy
Technically
Probably have
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color