Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody was acting outside
Jordan
Lake Michigan
It's not a seat I feel like no
Visiting my parents down in Austin
Then go down to the Bay right now
I don't know it's been forever
Yes we are definitely seven
During that reads his bachelor party
Cabin to the lake
I like swimming a lot I belong in the water fresh water is not the same
Body wax yearning for the show actually I just thought about
Right
Stacy
Let's get you to the Dead Sea
Lightning
Have you seen the movie the Salton Sea
I saw the movie
I know a lot about swimming
Sorry about the delay on this episode I have been
The weather outside like to thank everybody for their well wishes
People to wish me help
Definitely makes
You know it feels better
Fever broke around a little bit
Episode
That would immediately be almost meeting
Sudoku
Slightly meaning was on one hand because we could predict
Exactly what
Would happen which
Is basically
I texted you this
If they
Republicans win everything
Alex will say
Are they
And if Democrats take control of anything that I called
The Narrative no matter what but that was a disaster
Took that election was a disaster
Flickers
The great hope
In terms of voting measures that passed throughout the country of the
Control Band here in Chicago
Made it to
Where are there
Brightsign
That's wonderful
Positive
Everything's if you don't
If you don't look at the big picture
With the big changes that we may need are going to necessarily happen
Isaac
It was the right thing to do to not do an episode on here on Thursday
Because
Especially
We lose it Alex Jones
The show would be the same
Before the midterm
But likely
We quite
I'm so I'm glad that today we're going over the
November 7th
2018 episode which is
Is the day after
Someone who has donated to the show before and then bumped it a little bit
I'm just
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket
Caribbean black actor
Thank you so much destiny
If you would like to become a pilot
But Motorsport the show we would appreciate
We do not have any
Advertisers or dark money
We're offering you want in on this
We start today and I started recording something that I was
And that is
That this is
Show at least on November
The brief window that we have after the midterm
This is that one show I can
Kind of get down on
Because I think that Alex Jones
Gets it
I think he understands what happened in the midterm
Maybe more than he would like to reveal all right
Flip cuz I don't think anybody actually understands what happened to the
I think a lot of people have a lot of little pieces
Not so much
But in this first clip ice
Little littles
Glimmers
This is a big takeaway
Toothache
Legal cartel level
Started
Racketeering censorship the last year accelerating to the election
And
The house not passing voter ID
Michael Savage
Blue
Last chance
Illegal alien
Names of dead people
Taking over the edge
Along with
Censorship
Deplatforming and harassment
I'm just saying
And
Ted Cruz only one by like three points in Texas is Hartford
You see a little bit of speed
Because the results
Especially in Texas
I think that he
Probably would do better
Then a normal Democratic candidate
The historically has
Very competitive
Then winning places
Is that it did not look like he was going
And the temperature in Texas is changing
And I would want to talk about this
Baloch
B Beto help
Pushover the absolutely
The enthusiasm that he brought
2D election
The fact that more people were coming out
Led to more democratic down-ballot
So I think Alex has
Disposition
Rephrase
As we would have predicted
Is narrative about it is
We need voter ID
Where would we have
You know
Why do they reuse
Year of the pig
I need to be back on Facebook
Depth analysis
One thing I do like
Opposition like towards
If the government
Not just
The Republicans are aiding and abetting
32 pivot backed
Familiar territory
A sort of like
The position he
He plays well from
Like he was being asked to play point guard for a little bit
Female has
I think that we are going to see at least a more familiar hours
Alex
I don't know if playing out of his depth
What is the right way to put it
But there was like a real ugliness
To his show lately
Because he doesn't have
Anything other than
Defend Trump
Against everything
And now with the ideas like a demo
Mccratic house
There's a reason why Trump isn't
Doing the things
But he wants him to do
Before he had to come up with
And I'll give you like all these Democrats in the house
Now at the same time
I think that
Having Zach
Thing took
Complain about
Could lend itself
More extremism
Going to become much more tolerable to lithosphere
I will say this one
People fake names
Every establishment. Behind Democrats
Father was a
Beta man here in Texas or whether it was Gillian
Gilligan's moron
Island
For more on island I know his name's not Gilligan I like the books of the range
Alexa
And it's all good
Pathetic
Confirm more on island now I'm not calling Florida moron Island
Feeding tube
Becoming a little bit
Alex's
Mood
Text Cliff
MC that Alex
Or at least
Previous to the midterm
Romantic redwave in
Take every
I think in this makes Lucy very clear indication
Given the result
Does recognized
For Trump
And
He's a little worried about it
And then he still wants
Yes
This could have been a lot worse but
The fact that Trump has had his leg cut off for my dream
Internet censorship is a big deal
Is Ted Nugent to give us his aftermath
So did I
So you saying it like without this illegal we would have want
Expert about
We're going to have to give his analysis
That is not good unless he's coming to bring me Hot Licks
GOP people try and save it in the pastor of the largest wing
And a little bit of that
I think Alex has to read
Pig noise
A little bit later Rodger stone is on the
Michelle and I think he has to recognize
The house
Is controlled by
Democrat
They have the ability to
Subpoena people probably going to get speed
Real soon
And there's all sorts of other investigation
They could gum up the works
You would hope that they would use
Is that powered judicious
It actually go after real things that should be investigated
But I mean
Zika basically turn this
Next two years into
A procession
Durable investigations
The next two years right
That is true if you do like he's on the up-and-up and they're doing spurious investors
Even the most
Ridiculous investigation I could do
Yeah yeah yeah
It is there's a whole world
In front of them
Open world games
All sorts of places new mission
Galax recognizes that on one level
That I think
Alex Munoz
Strategically
They can order for trumpet
To be the thing
Galvanized
To be the person
That he
You
He tries to make
Make Trump appear to be
He means
It's just a rubber stamp through Congress
Because his positions are unpopular
And so without
Republicans controlling both houses of being able to
Push things through
He's going to be like I want to deport all
I don't know
Lebanese means
He doesn't know Lebanon is Express
It was just a random pool
Not going to happen
He can try any
Legislation
Progressive
And it'll just die in the
I wish that were true
I think it will with
Real serious issue
Maybe
Not it
Look we're assuming a lot in terms of
Having some faith
And Democrats
Do not
The rollover needed they needed to get like at least 45 26
60 seeds
In order to
Keep Pelosi for Speaker of the House
And that's not going to happen
She's going to stay Speaker of the House
And the whole time we're going to pass Republican Lite version
If possible
Images
Even if it is that I still think that
If you wouldn't be able to
To do as much as
If you could with a Republican
Control
Entirety
So I think I think that there's that
I like that Alex recognizes it
Diminishing returns
An actual things that
He's getting done
The veneer of this like
Super powerful
I can fix
Everything.
And when
Veneer goes away being is propaganda
Much more different
Because you have to vent
Expect
You don't have a hero to worship you have just inefficient bureaucrat
And I don't think that's going to be
All of the executive orders that Trump is going to
Legal eagle
Sure you're going to be even the even the Supreme Court
Executive in my new executive order I get free food for life
Alright McDonald's
Okay
At least offense
Something possible
So we got 10 News
Come and get with his analysis
Most of their interviews
The boil
And
Or just really bright
You know and so like
This is
What I
And actually I think Ted Nugent to some
Something really
Turtle
Maniacal
Constitution the Bill of Rights the Declaration of Independence I believe in the Ten Commandments of the golden rule I Believe In Loving
Your neighbor and helping your family and neighbor and being the asset, and making sacrifices and taking wrist so that you are pretty
Community so that you can help others when they need it
Cuz I know these
Everywhere
People who believe that
Eastern Michigan into a San Francisco 49ers own
Amber
Michigan
So I mean his characterization of the two sides is wrong but I think he's starting to recognize that
The things that I like
Is not the most popular thing
In the right direction
I mean granted he goes on to say that like
I'm response that I'm going to fight
Within his right to do
Douching in the Ten Commandments which is why
We should kill Hillary
You know
Two things that
Boats
Strongly advocate
He was super into like
Displays
Is of
Like high power weapon
Remember Elijah
Piece of wood on fire and then everybody did some
Ted Nugent Naples love guns Alex
Accidentally says that you should
What you're doing what I've done what what what
At what
Trump is dealing is get really aggressive
Around
And understand
Outreach try to take leftist out deprogramming try to take him shooting
Shooting
But he does like puppets
Yep
Still do it
Because
I know if we were so like his
We would be like yeah
Clipit app
I would cut out
The part where he says Outreach so just take him out shoot them
Buckethead a slip of the tongue
Believe
The guns aren't that
Scary the outdoors
I don't know if that's going to get people to be weird okay.
That's a terrible idea considering where the country is going
Enemy you believe you should kill training that I've heard Alex talk about going out with
With people who don't like
You keep talking about like those explosives
That you shoot like one of them
Exploded at a cinder block
Hit him in the head
Wait what
The cast of Silicon Valley
In the country right now we're dealing with
Some pretty serious radicalization
Another write obviously
VCA manifest through murders
Scares
Fun
Good days
Take on that speedometer
And if you want have a political and economic fight you're going to get one This Is War
And they're organized to take a shower
You get it
Because they say the Republicans radicalizing it because the left is radical
A choice
They made me do it
It's the same stupid argument is like I'm only racist cuz you kept calling me racist
What did you expect to happen
Oh my God I'm only radical because your radical
But it wasn't there before
In waves for the last
Forever you know what it was our fault
If we have never elected a black president
Play Thinkin private company Alex
I think you might as long as there wasn't a bugged room
Might say that
I believe
In terms of conservatism
One of their best
Arguments
They have is the
Self-determination
Sure I believe that I believe that when you say
The accused believe that everybody has the right
To choose how to live their life
I think
You're in
Good you're on a good rock
Just saying.
Legislate those rights to choose
That's where your b*******
Philosophically is a
Good starting block
To undermine the idea of just saying
I believe that people have the right to live their life how they see fit
Sure I think that
Interesting Lee
Starts talking about his beliefs
Is it weaves
Very quickly
Determining how other people live
These people are coming to come for you you better start
It is if you if you believe enough
In the American dream in MP3
Choose your own path in life and you ear to do the best that you can do if you believe in that
Fake news
When you see it
Nothing I can do weather is something you can do
So
Snowflake
Everyone should have the right to choose
Perfect right to determine their actions as long as
Weezer determining
As long as you agree with me you have self-determination if not
Back of their lives
You know you had that blow back to me saying like that's a reasonable belief
Always
So anyway
Tomorrow's him
But
Takeaway
Here's where he's at
But I'm going back
Has ever had losses this low
Powerful enemies
So I think that is actually probably a sensible approach
I mean it's a little bit
Still shining of a s*** a little bit
But the idea saying like
We lost
This is an optimistic Alex that's coming to studio today
I understand that's the thing I don't understand where these guys are coming from
I don't understand
Like ultimately that's what they did they
White supremacy was really what was on the ballot
And you saw so much such a high voter turnout
And white supremacy
Power tools
I don't think it is
I think that
I think that there were areas
Certainly
You can make that case but I don't think as a whole
That cases
I think I think they're what we would have loved
Is a condemnation
So many
In a perfect world
There would have been no Republican
You would have thought
But that's an unrealistic expectations
And I think you look at
Incremental progress
That you do
So many women getting
The officers
Governor
You're those sorts of things are real those are important
Bits of progress
Absolutely it was a
Bigwinnn
For the right away
Accurate but it wasn't
It wasn't as much of a win for non-white Supremacy this week
Kind of in the same place as our
The Lost could have been way worse or saying that the wind should have been much bigger
So we're both sort of in-between
No one's getting exactly what they want
But there's little things that both
Sides can say
I like
And we still have to
50 hour everything
Cuz there's a recording this year on Wednesday
There's still a lot of
Races that hasn't been
Been decided yet
They're still
There's still things
Sure
I don't
I'm a pessimistic guy
As as baby
Somebody
I don't see how
This doesn't
Further
Expand the ability to
Have a minority rule
And the minority is
But they have
They have cheated
They have twisted
To make sure that remains in power
As opposed to
And then we have an ineffective Democratic party that's going to be like
We're going to do some white nationalism but not
Soupremacy that's terrible measures passed about like a votary in France
Measures the path
Like getting rid of
Redistricting
Really hurts
Voter turnout in
Inactive voter suppression
There are there is progress on that front
You know even
Even if it's not
Like
You want to just shake everything like an Etch-a-Sketch and we can
You want to do that but that would require exactly what we're again
So
I get what I get what you're saying and I think it's fine
Pessimistic
I also think
I don't know what I think
Is what it is
Maybe but
Maybe not
It's possible
Share in your in your leg
I'm not I'm not super optimistic but I am I am like
I don't know
Wichita
Dave Chappelle
I think you're one of the greatest comedians
Really
He starts getting into some of his
Fears about
Globalist
And it gets in
Dimensional aliens
Which I haven't heard in awhile
He's getting into a weird head space
How do I know this whole plan
They want to use it
And thinkers
Along the line of the world that wanted
Opposed
Human world
Because their God
Is going to give them life extension and give them power but at a certain point
Give their body up and be uploaded
This larger Consciousness that will then move on to the next planet
Of course
Former head of the British Illuminati wrote childhood's end
He also wrote 2001 Space Odyssey
Okay
Figure out
World
Entity known as Lucifer
He's going to give them the blueprint
They just got to kill themselves and their families once they get the point
Not even
What about was talking about he's really into
Take it too far as she believes that it's coming in
They went on board the spacecraft media
Right
Condom
Silicon Valley shrooms almost everyday
Okay
Weather
Creatures
That are giving them control
Course
Are you f****** didn't
If our if our head of the Illuminati
Right
2001 A Space Odyssey should not God be a space baby and not
Lucifer
Maybe I don't know I don't know what to do with that I don't care I don't care about that stuff
I don't I don't care at all
I don't
I just think
This is so stupid
Cida like titties
You saying that Heaven's Gate
Figure it out what the Silicon Valley people believe in
Took it too far
Anybody who knows anything about Heaven's Gate nose
Is that that is not
Of what they were up to
At at all
Baby wipes
Stupid but it's fun for him to get back to some of that stuff
It's fine for him to be like
20 years
Are you bugging happen
Inditex Corvallis uses
Term
Probably not cool to say
I think
But he says it again
Another one
He's talking about
Beto's
Going to run now
Louisiana
What
Hillary Clinton
Kentucky
Awesome pot
California
Hello Latinos how are you
What's condescending like that
Phone
What type of
Okay
Alright man
I'm not sure if it's okay to use that term use the beginning test
Did he say
Coonass
Twice he said they're going to give them a coon-ass name
Where is Winchester's I'm on the fence about exactly because the enemy
Do the term it's
It's a term for a person who
Cajun ethnicity
There are people who have like look at the etymology of it
It's difficult to
Tell if it's a like
Offense
It seems like it is
I know if it's a breeding
From Wikipedia here
In the early 1980s occasion worker suit is former employee
The lawsuit light directly to the federal government's recognition is
The Cajuns as
As protected by the Civil Rights Act
So it does appear that it's probably a term that can be used offensively
It is Coronavirus different from Coon
It appears that it is
I don't understand that it does come from
African American
Which is possible but one the other etymology says that it comes
Comes from the French word
Canoe canoe
Which is a vulgar term
For the vulva
But I'm not sure if that's accurate
There's also
The French word connoisseur
Think it could come from which
Loosely translates to dirty Prost
Alright so no matter what comes from a defensive from everything I can
Tell that it's a term that has been Rick
Claimed a little
Descent
One word
Unacceptable
I wanted to come here and tell you like I've looked
Portable player
I don't
Cut-and-dry as that
You might be able to wiggle out of it
I was almost like should I not even say
Because it's
It's it feels that way
Some of that might be
Because Daleks
Might be a package
Kids with that but
There is a
Batman
His total voices that is
Skip this next clip
Just Alex again repeating that everything was Rick against the the right
Maisto land
You win but not really win
Barely lost
Legal voting all over the price
Is Alex going out to break
With
Pronouncement
Shawty said it out loud
What you been doing it show
So
I want to go in through and Beyond
That sounds a little
I know that he is
Probably feeling overdue for his own martyrdom
Like lose your audience as opposed to
What's up
All my heroes.
Why can't I do that too needs to do is fake his own death
And then come back like 10 years later
But pretending
Corporate Wendy's building
America that Alex
Apparently in favor of
Surprising at all
We saw this with Faith Goldy wouldn't get your ads on TV wouldn't come on radio
Toronto
Most analysts said she would have one she had the money
Young looking
And I would have letter advertise
Okay
Well is the
Pretty thoroughly as you may know she used to work for Rebel media which is
Who's the former employee roster
Stood by the daily Stormer Augusta Charlottesville rally
Which was
A little bit too much a little too far
Rebel media is like dude
Going a little bit too far
Eminem December 2017 on the podcast
Millennial woes and recited the 14 words
Supremacy and responded
I want to survive
So not too surprising that the Alex's real Interstate Goulding it's not good
Sure I've actually ever heard Alex
Directly talk about
Which is
Miles dab
Alex
Methodist that Ted Nugent in
Great
Yes
Ted Nugent optimism
To the world
Macclenny
We are blessed
With an appearance
From someone
Is barely ever
In the form of Rodger Stone
Stephen Austin to Lucky's in studio which is
Sort of interesting
Might want to go
Might be wanting to meet up with the carousel
I'm meeting up with the Caravan adver
Infowars
Kind of interesting
Because there's one element of it that makes it
It seemed like this
Should of organizing and political action
But there's really something else
Laughably pathetic
We'll talk about that
For this
And it had a hit had a massive mashup effect
Handwritten letter
They shine
Weather postage-paid individual ladder
1 million of these to flood the White House
About 100,000 to a Trump Tower New York
Thousand
White truck.com
Sobe idea behind this is that they're trying to
Convince him to take
Internet censorship seriously
Alex is going to sell it as
A million people demand you help me get back on Facebook
Take a look at all this Groundswell of people
The whole point of a handwritten letter is to make it seem individual person
Made it right
Make a bunch of copies of a handwritten letter looks like instead of yourself we're also sending
Q41
You're still sending the same letter
There's no way you can't see through that
We're not riding
Weird Written Letter
Perfect crazy self-serving
It's so easy to see through
We need to
To get back on social media or we are
Fuct
Rodger website
To do that
Alex knows that right
I don't know if she knows that the president literally
Corporation
You have to put this
Broccoli
Sears to make sure the president
I'd like to present it as like
I have iron
Clad proof that they're specifically targeting
So the president could say
Infringing on
People's free speech
In terms of political opinion
Enforce them
Not
Discriminate
Dance people for that
Yeah
With the interpretation of
Political ideology
You being a
Back to class
Which is
But
I think that's what Alex wants
Yeah
Or
Use rendition
Against
Headed towards
If one day we're just like
Extraordinary rendition
It sounds good to me
But then I heard this next clip like this is
Amapola
Apples are desperate
Don't forget
67% off of colloidal silver silver bullet
Byproduct
Text Jeanette
I believe
From everything I can to
Because he's saying this is a targeted sale
There's these stick things that I need to f****** sell-out
Hold on it because
According
They're going to take my payment processor
I won't be able to sell anything
So I got to get rid of all of this
That argument doesn't work
Because all the other product that you're not trying to sell out of
I believe
Play recent
He needs to get rid of the things I have overlap with products that sell from Jeanette
He needs to get rid of those cuz
You can't promote both
So while there is a knockout that Alex cell
There's a sleep thing genesta
You can't have both of those on the shelves
Compete kind of thing
Private label on your own
Where is a fire sale to get rid of everything
Overlap with his Market
Multi-level marketing
Oh man that is
The great great point
That's a great analysis
A balm
Because there's no other way for the reasoning to make sense
Just Elsa
If it was a fire sale on everything
We need to get rid of everything
Before they say we can't sell it
Believe that
Doesn't work with all of it
I think it is a bulge
It's just because
Those six things
You know
You can't sell
Got your whatever
That's a good point.
Slippery assholes
Rodger and Alex is sitting down having the B of A bull session
How's the weather
But how their victim
Destroy me financially
Again
Beacons of Truth
No we want to put you in jail Rodger just got to do it from listen
Martin Luther King Jr wrote from a jail if you if you want to
Federal penitentiary
Foot by 5 foot area
Video Dear Future
Aladdin bunk bed I mean
I don't
Play I don't know all of the information so I don't
I have a sense that Rogers
People who know all of the information
The behind-the-scene
Steve
Alicia
Talk about prison fashion
What is because Buehler
Blanche to investigate whatever
You know anything that kind of just comes up
He can just go like I'm referring this to the FBI and all that stuff even if even a stone didn't commit
Vegas particular crime
We all know stone at some point or another
I've committed at least one jailable offense
So many people have such a
Involvement
With Rodger has been
Talking to the special counsel
To be like cooperating
People like good for him
Because before when they were just like saying they were going to arrest Paul manafort
He could play the game
The game is not
Also if you expect
Jerome corsi to go to bat for you is the easiest dude to flip
He be like
Mueller called him he was like dude I'll tell you everything without anything
Like Jerome corsi completely gave up on that narrative he was trying to pitch like
6 months ago
Because of information
Give me the f****** courtroom
Flop sweat
Waterlogged
I don't know man
No one wants to silence anybody
I think the private companies have absolutely the right to do whatever they want to do
Taking Alex off Social Media stuff
Because of
Very
Clear bra
Of their rules
But he's done
If they want to do that to make him do that if I'd like their web hosting
The youth
Is they don't want to host his stuff anymore
That's their right to be like now this is beyond what we can
Do we deem accept
Is there was like the government
Have a good day
He just has like
The chickens are coming home to roost
I have made a millions of dollars
Off doing this
Very distasteful work
And now
So
That's important
Because it's Mexico
And that's important because this next clip
George Soros
Infowars
If I hadn't done it
Somebody else will
Alex Jones
And shows the club
Defaming
Nazi collaborator
Facts are facts
We're basing our research on a t'riffic interview on
CBS
Vagueness
There's a couple indications
If it storms really understands the
The questions that are be
Okay
To what the interviewer is asking
He's responding slightly
Questions
But that's not
I don't know if I've ever heard Rodger Stone give the Alex Jones Soros narrative
And that to me it seems like
Also damn can you think of any reason the Taurus wouldn't go on Infowars
I've read recently the Taurus is rapsod asked
Which is it
I don't know if you would ever want to go on Infowars
I think you could
I think I would just yell not be at Amherst Alberta
Pieces like
Talk about how great it is
Really character
Like
George if you're listening
Dojo
I still think that would be bad
It is funny to hear like
Paper napkin
Into for a while
Yeah
Only stupid people
It's really almost
They don't want
His voice
It's on there
Program
Because that's
What they do they don't have
Like multiple opinions
It's almost like they are some sort of
Outlet in order to propagandize for the president
And there's no way to prove that
What if what if one of their opinion commentators
Was actively campaign
That doesn't prevent
You forget Jake
Showing up at a trump rally given stumps
Ludacris
It is awful that the media is
Biased
I think they're just trying to get one person you know they're just I love I love Sean Hannity
I knew he was going to give a speech
Before the rally
You picked me out of the crowd likes
Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen
Jesus chord
Rosemary
And that's not good
Interesting
Because the other day and article came out in the National Review
They talked about how like you don't need these Soros kids
He receives his real life
Just as bad
Realized
Are you going to read
A blurb
Play some contacts.
The bombshell
50 minutes
Cirrhosis adopted father
The truth about George Soros is damning enough
It's got a quote
About the following week the kind-hearted
Nazi local militia
An average hear the unhappy lad up
Took him off with him
Already here he's lying
The
Quotes
Kind-hearted
Local Nazi militia
Where they talk about The Oath Keepers
Blouses
Which is the name
Thibodaux Soros
Alex George Soros
This is from his memoirs
Is the name
He gives
To the adopted
George Webb
As a young boy
So Alex is already turning this one individual
Into a Nazi militia
But you see he's already twisting this
Image of bacteria
About the following week the kind-hearted
Local militia
An effort to cheer unhappy let up
Took him off with him to the provinces
I'm a modern
Estate of a Jewish aristocrat
Baron mordo
Kornfeld
Swan Village
But what was left of the staff George also met several other measuring officials
Young man
The alleged godson of mister
Bath wash
Help with the inventory
Surrounded
Regain their spirits
On Saturday return to business
That's George Soros
And a rich juice house
Taking the property
In his father's and his adopted father
So
Go find that book that that is
That is in there except for Oz editorializing
But this quote from the National Review is yet another example of cherry-picking quotes
Zorro seem Super Evil
It's taken from page 71 Soros George's father's memoirs
Once
Note is that it's completely deprives contact
Use this quote
Immediately before the passage
Did Alex just read
Is this
Blouses
Was charged with the ministry of vitamin A
Weekend
The rest of the time you spent taking inventory the province
During the week George past
Time alone in blouses apartment
Lacking anything to do he caught the attention of some
His schoolmates who lived in the building
Lacrosse
Communicating by hand signals they seem surprised at the stop in somebody else
The following
The kind-hearted blouses
In an effort to cheer up the unhappy lab
Took him off with
The provinces
So you already have the contacts to your other
Miserable
He said he doesn't
Isolated doesn't know what to do
So The Godfather
On this one
To the presidency
Put the argument that he was working
Rounding up an inch
Inventorying
The property and stuff working for the Nazis
When you realize that
This passage where he went to this estate
And was
Or whatever
It's in the context of
Written out
Not immediately after this
Describe how blouses
Just try to accommodate a sad young boy living in hiding with
So we allowed to go roam the hills and
Exploring
There he's almost discovered by a guard
What is allowed to pass out
This is related this is been related
Do a story of George
Just friend of Jeremiah
Who is not so lucky
And ended up going
Cast
Jizo the reality of this story
Piece of the story that they're cutting out
Is taken from a larger hole of
To Vdara
This part of
Cirrhosis
When he was younger
When he was in hiding it was miserable
This guy tried to cheer him up
He took him along
To this estate where they had some wine
Some folks
And he took note of some of the
The thing
Things that were in the house that we're going
Would be confiscated
Who gives a s***
And then he came back
Nearly died
Work it out you know how a lot of
Cutting Edge of almost dying at altar
Yeah
Jesus
F***** up
Ending
Tim is a Nazi
Collaborate
Withers
When there's a
Getting out of it from not being killed
Like you very well may not have had any Soros
Right because he could have died
I have had
Tons of people who have found the article that I wrote
About how Soros wasn't
On our website
Tons of people who come
Cast or anything like
And they will say yes he was
I'll ask them for a point
And then I will
No one has a good heart
No one Alex doesn't
Nobody who's cam
And
Pride Flags
Has a good argument
There's something that I started
F****** realize
Really really
And that
All these people
To have this store has brain worm going on
Do you know what they have
Fingerboards
Sympathy for the Nazis
Then a thirteen-year-old
Target of dinar
Understand that there was a
We got him
You know they were sucking Mass killing people
You know
I feel like
Writing down there
Over here is
Collaborating
I honestly think like if this is what you
You got
You are an embarrassment
Collaborate and listen
I just think that
Sockshare
I went out
Alex
Rodger sitting here talking about is because we're a beacon of Truth
And then you come with that week
National Review
Be f****** ashamed of themselves
For printing without
Contacts
Depart in
Specifically
Because he's Jewish
Later
Rambles about Service ribbon
He doesn't like Judaism
Validated
Experience
Or something
I have no power
F****** idea but it just
All this is
I don't even like Soros
I'll fight any
I want
Someone to actually make a good point
To do with that one little possible insider-trading thing that he did
In the
Lady
Anything I think it's earlier
I was like to see the differences between the soft and then later on
Hits the heart
They're going to some rich Jews
If we needed more evidence
But if we did need more evidence
Of this being a
Very white
Centric
Operation
Submit
This clip of Rodger Stone
How does McDonald's
There's a lot of commentary about the nomination and election of a
In the Democratic party in Queens New York
Realize that
Cortez
Defeated Joker
Machine White
Working class traditional liberal Democrat
Person
He was a classic liberal
There's no room for
In the Democratic Party
There's not even room for classical liberal
And Cortez
What does that mean
What does that tell you
You need two people of color in it isn't anymore guys
Beat white man
Who's the classic liberal
She should have been able to do that he's a decent fellow.
What is Alexandria
Name me one politician Congress
I mean
You just got elected yesterday
Tell me what is the first hundred days
Administration
So I don't think there's any way to look at that other than Rodger Stone
Clearly trying to
Express
The cutback
But I think it's really interesting to hear Alex
Trying to be like
Like Alex
Trying to
Walk Rodger back a little bit and then
Not
He delivered for his people
Raise the ship
Razor
The level
That's such a
Have to walk it back a little bit
Cuz he's being sued
Most racist flag
Supremacist
Second Sight
He is
Yeah it comes out
The Jeff sessions
You asked me to quit
That's good fight
Next
The law firm was a scam
Scamming people in the guy who hates
It's almost like he's gearing up to fire Mueller I didn't have enough time to look into him all that much before we started workout
For the day
You look really nice.
Everyone was
Article
Talk about Mueller probe
Too far and stuff
Everything I was able to glean again in my elementary research
Would still be in charge
Do the probe until someone is
Confirmed
Yeah I don't know if that's a hundred percent accurate that that was a sense I was getting
I do believe that it was
To get rid of
It is an indication that like power in the house
I got a lot more about Bennie and the head of that committee is going to be able to subpoena
Returns and if I just say no
Nope
Alexandra's next clip
Is talking about how Rodger predicted
The sessions is going to
Be fired
Literally say like a month ago
Rodger and Alex
God-knows-how-long
Eventually you're going to be
With the Trump Administration
You're calling for someone to go
It's only a matter of time
I'm by Alex claims that Rodger has
Prognostic
Skating ability
But the way you phrase it is really troubling
Ladies and gentlemen exactly as Rodger Stone predicted a month ago
And last night
You want to change the subject mr. president
He said you must fire
Sessions
And Rosenstein to change the narrative
From the election lost loss
We need a man
You need to fire him so we can change the conversation
I'm good on them
For what I'm saying is
Screaming this forever
Of course eventually.
Going to be right
I think their EX
Mr. president
Change the narrative
By firing your attorney
It's pretend like I don't
I'm not
A hundred percent sure that's
What Trump is doing
But if it is and there's nothing like this
It all looks really bad
Because why
Like what
What's wrong with The Narrative of
You guys not really losing
I mean that that narrative still forces you to admit that you lost
Truck and admit that he lost he's the one who's
Alex
The appearance
This Paul Joseph Watson
24-hours
Who cares
You going to take calls
Angry dragon
Is talking about how great they are
NSX
Cuz it's so funny
Alex is talking about how America
India's
Give my bonus
Fides
Claiming that known super Patriots like Donald Trump
Rodger Stone
This is
Okay
Superpaint
For Thoroughbred America
It doesn't exist okay
Michigan
Trinity
Garbage
Okay
Infinity times a trillion garbage
Doesn't get more American than fighting against the Union
Advocate Over Texas
See the number of time
That's because he's so American
Rodger Stone who made millions and millions of dollars work
King for foreign
Necessarily in America's best interest
A multinational corporation
Already seems to prioritize over
I would qualify as
Super Patriots
Actually
People who actively want to destroy America trillion times
What is the trillion times
Very poor
Noting
Is that a little bit of a
Jim Acosta
Much
You're bad
What's more important than attacking the Free Press
You asked me a question I don't like your bad
I'm going to have this woman
I can't believe people let you work for them
So
So adults
Do we have any
Do we have any more
Philippine that way
But buried in that Exchange
Is Jim Acosta
About the
Rhetoric
The Trump used about the Caravan
In the lead-up to the Moon
Trump's response to that is I want
People in
Because we've got jobs we've got to fill with Industries coming back
Because That's Amore
His self
Perception
The markets are doing good
He only needed to drum up that race racist
Fervor in order to bring people out to vote
That largely in this
Strange's
Characterize it isn't
Like
What we need to be invaded
So notice Amazon splitting up the thing in the two things come on
So noticeably that's absent
From Trump's press
It's also
Fairly absent
From Alex
Is rhetoric
He's still a little bit on that tape
You said it was going to happen right before the midterms ordering
Anyway
Restaurants
Prince was petulant
Nonsense
It was a childish man
Lashing out at people who were trying to ask
Fair
Questions
This is the response
That Alex
Rodger has
And I think
They're fairly
Such a moment
Everything we wanted
And all the fake qanon people
No no
When he put sessions in Utah
But don't worry it'll be dealt with
Happening ladies and gentlemen
Selection
Now you may see the real down from someone you just saw slapping
Jim Kosta back that was the Trump that I know that was the Trump that I love
That's what I love about him so I get ready for Donald Trump Unchained
God I'm ready
So that brings us to the end of this adventure on November 7th
We can glean from it are positive
Towards Alex
Show
Being a listener
Which is good for
It's not great for the world
I mean the world has got its work cut out for
There was no part of either of us
Person I believe
Whose thoughts term election
Could
Substantially changed
Situation where
Even if Democrats have taken over both houses of Congress
It won every Governor house
In the country
That doesn't deal with the issues that were
The government stuff
Is a real bra
In care of
Taken care of
Whether it be voter
Enfranchisement
Big issue
Climate change
Massive issue
Economics
Disparity
Those are those are issues
We need the government
Checkpoint on
And work towards
But the real issues that we're facing
In terms of extremism
In terms of the
Trend towards
White nationalist violence
Right
Adjacent violence
Like
Misogynist
Violence
I think you could categorize
Had to keep shooting people
Maybe in that
In that camp
Doughsserts
Things are the real issues
I need to deal with
And I don't think any measure
Sure of
Left success in government
So
That's my type
There's a real positive
Does real
Unfortunate
Should have gone better thing
And then the bigger picture of
We all need
I don't know I don't know but probably
The problems
With all of
A lot of it
It's a very vocal violin section perhaps
But that's still our problem
Yeah that's true
And I think that week
We can help
People as much as
I think that there is
There's active Soul search
Extremists by
People need to do in order to
Be helpful
In the coming
Most of Florida underwater
More like interpersonal climate
So I don't know I don't know I don't really have a message
About this but
This is much more listen to
Bluetooth on the Shelf
It when you have a man who believes in the cons
Institution
And the Ten Commandment
Which are perfectly aligned
Each other if you recall
Everybody knows
Nothing is nothing goes hand-in-hand more than the
Constitution in the Ten Commandments that whole Amendment about covet
Yeah I don't know babe
But
Do everything we can to get rid of
You've got a chance. Just leave so we can do better
Let's hope for the few
The f****** worse
But you can't find out
Underscore
Can you find us on Facebook where can't find out
Where the group
Go home and tell your mother your brother
Unfortunately you can't find out
You can't
Find
Ensure with the status
Question
Describe review all that good stuff
I don't think they killed
Play me some
Locations of them B I don't know anybody from voting
Let's play
There was one lady at least voted before the election
Oh no
Devoting
This season
Jones
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work