Alex
Alex Jones
Yep
Are we going to live
How are we going to live how we're going to make it
What do we do
Are we going to make it through this
I really thought you were trying to do like a song lyric
What is the reference
And the only thing I could come up with is that Daniel Bedingfield song
Schmidt's
With this too shall pass
Natasha Bedingfield brother
Field with one hit
Early 2000s mix
From my phone
Where's the third hit off that album
Remember what it was
Told you I don't know either.
Never heard before my life got the bangers
Find are fun
Plenty of fun adventure
We're back in the past
To pay a visit to Alex
See what was going on in his world
Further into tea party adjacent
And develops narratives
It will linger
That was off the top of my head
Goodreads
I'd like to take a little more
Alright
You are now
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Caribbean black action
I don't want
Thank you David
You know in the context of our
Distracted really in the context of our last episode
In regards to how he feels about
How does he feel about a Caribbean black axe
Does he give us the give or take on it
Doesn't like
I think he thinks Jar Jar Binks his exile
What is terrible
Something like this
There would not be a
Mountains Galaxy
Jodie Whittaker is doing a fantastic
At the job by the way. I know this is important
Galaxy
We were seeing all these established
Almost seems like every single day
He hasn't new weird thing
Using two
Approve
Did the government is oppressing the
We had the miac report which is his biggest piece of proof which is
Water Horse
All sorts of other little things
Is the POP3 trying to
Sort of
Create
History of Oppression
And for himself
Patriots like a motherfuker right now you are bringing it
I'm not even reading off anything these are just I am
Today we're going to be going over there
The
The March
23rd
March 23rd 2009
Episode
What super fascinated me is like
Every single day
There is something new
It's being added
Tuesday
Larger narrative
It all branches out from the miac report
Where is using it to argue that
They're staying
People like me and
Supporters of Ron Paul
Misunderstanding
New
He's growing on the branches everyday we get one
Today but Alex is
Is declaring classical tea
It's like we're Iraq or Afghanistan
But
Eternal Secret
Where they specifically talk about
The protest of last November
The park across the street
His brother Wayne Dallas
Specifically
Terrorism Posse Comitatus
This is 180°
From freedom
This is classical
As opposed to
Iroko codes
Like Alex's got this report there's an army report
City of God
He's going to get into it a little bit and we'll discuss it
None of this stuff is
Except
If this report doesn't
Specifically mentioned
The Texas
The feds
As much as
All the cities
That they had protested
In a list of like 46
Austin
Have to take the show as Alex
I like I like him too
Military
You realize that
The military is like they don't always have to wear uniform
People in the military could be there too
To be a part of the protest
Further I don't trust Alex
To know the difference
Patrina playing close
Person
I think that he would assume
Anybody who's
Maybe dozen
Does
Got2b
I will tell you how you can
Figure it out
The cut of their jib
If you don't like the cut of their jib
Military
Definitely
So Alex
Complains that
He's the only Norm
Prison life
And then brags about cells
Just watch
It's also been my daddy
And it isn't so much that I'm some special or wonderful
Other people have lost
Or never learned
Themselves
What powerful creatures we all are
You just don't have any initiative
So doesn't that mean you think you're special
The proof is in the pudding
Number one alternative media website
Already services
You name
Define alternative news
I don't know I don't know
Give the s***
He's in the vest
Market
The brag that mean
We are the number one
Freezy Cuckoos podcast in the world
We are
Gruber.
The number one Alex Jones
There's a
There's a Mite that could be involved there
Just adorable person
Believe yourself
Special
It's really just sort of like that thing of like
Jesus saying you will do what I do and more
Convey to his
You could do everything I can do but I
Just know
And do it and you guys apply
Who would even think that
Jesus thought he was some sort of special
What makes him different from the rest
Is there any difference
Also small point the expression is the proof of the pudding is
Anyway
Actually
I do think that people for it it's like a regional colloquialism
Proof is in the pudding
The expression begs the question
That's not
Inappropriate
Turn of phrase
Astrological
You should say it raises the
Proof is in the pudding
It does make
Why does a why I don't understand how that doesn't make sense
Yes
Things you can tell you how you can use it
The proof would be in the pudding
In the eating of the product
Alex's lack of principles
Describes
Politician
That are up
Do some good stuff
These criminals Swagger around Washington everyone but the bankers
Globalist Bankers were swaggering around in the two people he's staying or standing out to him
Are them are his favorite person in the world
And Bernie Sanders who he knows at this point is a socialist
Because Ron Paul has been on Alex's show
Impression
Counting him as
A contemporary of Ron
So
The enemy of my enemy is my friend
But he can't think that because
By definition of socialist
He has to be his enemy
Because socialism is really only communism
Communism
Authoritarianism
To take old
You have a theater me of my enemies
Could be my enemy
He has to believe
That
Bernie Sanders a socialist
Is in League with the globalized in League with the globe
But he's controlled opposition Dan
Advocating for someone
Controlled opposition
Anyway
It's just weird
He's an opportunist
Opportunity
Opportunity here is Alex talking about the army.
He got
Everything the way he is
Describing
Because
I'm not I'm not positive
He's done it.
Please.
Because I don't want
Going on here but I think they're smart enough to know what's going on
That doesn't make
Davis arm document was written
That's why they used
Respect
It is the Federal Reserve
Mutton
Liaison with local MP
CC triple cross
Alright yeah
This is maybe like
12 minutes
And Alex doesn't actually get into talk about the story until about the two-hour point
Vaguely about what it is it doesn't actually reversed
So the document that Alex is referring to on this shows a document titled Force protection advisory 09-01
Dated November 7th
Exciting
It really says the report was written with respect
Because if you take one look at the report you can tell exactly why he thinks
The report says things like quote
The November 22nd protests are intended as a kickoff of an ongoing campaign to organize the public
And take concerted action
Only the conscious action of We the People can save the nation from ruin plunder and total socialist tyranny
The thing is
What happens next
It's very clear from the context
This is a report
Quoting from
Which is linked at the end of the same paragraph
It's stuff that they took off the
The endless website protest
The reported superfair to the Embassy
Just describes them as they describe themselves mostly through quoting
The only purpose that serves is written out in the first
Quotes
Provide situational awareness
Recommended mitigation
All it is is a report that's going out to provide
Awareness of the situation
2 people who may be
Please wear
The protest
This document proves there was targeted harassment campaign
From the Army regarding
Activities
But I fail to see proof of that Miss document at all
It does tell those reading to quote be aware of their environment at all times
Advises them not to retaliate
Gate to verbal assault
It's that commanders and have relationships with local law enforcement
Threat because anytime their large Gatherings like this
Not just from the protest
The Miz well
So these sorts of large Gatherings of people
Things that are absolutely
You should have on your radio
It's not necessarily all that weird
For that
The report doesn't say anything specific about the Army going to surveilled
At all
So I wanted to get a little more information on this type of
Report
I found a few others
Is of the same variety
Force protection
Advisory
And exactly what this report is
From a 26
16 Force protection
This advisory situational awareness
Where does Route.
Planned or spontaneous
Coming up in the Navy want
To remind Department of Navy service members civilian employees
And their family members are reminded that large Gatherings of
Violent gentlemen
These documents are called Force protection advisor
Because they offer advice on protection of the
The forces
It has nothing to do with troops being sent out to watch
Patriots it has to do with
Potential dangers large groups of
Two people coming to
Together could create
If you read this document correctly there zero indication
This was written
For any Army members
Burbank protest
And a very strong indication that it's about preparing members
Community
For a possible worst
Case scenario
Things like telling people not to retaliate to verbal assault
These were Army members who might happen to be at the protest organically
Things like the report advising commanders to use random
Rhythm measures
Is in reference to operations on it around army base
This is not at the pro
They're talking about routine
That the Army engages in
On the basis
In these cities
Not
In like on the field
Out at the
What they're saying is that
Rather than stick to the routine you should random
That way they can't observe it and then plan
During the circle
Stances
Large protest
Senior City
Then what you should do is randomize some of the route
In ordered so no one can play
Clear
Incontact
Something could be done
So they're trying to say that they don't want to
Any plain clothes
Non-military people surveillance
That
Orders that
Well there's that for sure also like all of the possible plainclothes people could relate to
Otherwise
The report goes on to say quote report all potential protest activities to the Army Reserve operations
But this isn't telling people to report all protest
That would be f******
If you're in the Army and you're going to
The protest
Lhr
That sort of thing
This report is
I've looked at all the other reports of this
Nature
Alex is just taking basically a human resources memo
Finding the little pieces like
Anti-terrorist
They think we're Tara
You taking all of it out of context
In order to add another
The history of government oppression
It's pathetic
It's it's it's
Interested
As to whether or not you would want to
2hr
You know what I'm saying if you are in the military and you're going to the women's March
I don't know
Aggressive anti
Descent
Campaign within the military I feel like there might be something
Do that the only look at it
Reproductive
Let's say you are at one of those protests
Papa Bear of my own volition
That could be useful paperwork
But I don't know I don't know enough about the bureaucracy
Human resource department for the accuracy of human resource department
Yeah so I don't know I don't know what you would get out of it or what
It would help
Mitigate
I feel vague picture in my head
You might
If you were the higher-ups
You might want to know
Okay some of our people were there
You know I don't know
I'm just I think it's just an interesting question as to
Whether or not
Sympathy
Order online
In place
Be discriminatory
If You Were Somehow punished for going
Nobody
The knowledge I have
Do know is that this story is
In the document
It's going to go on to play
Later in the show
But that doesn't stop Alex
Becky's been harassed
All the time these are
Intelligence
It was fronting
Parking lot
Special Forces bearing and they would
Michael threatening comments and
What's a special forces
Does bearing
I have the shoulders back
It's all about
Specialty
You want to help you
I don't see any reason to believe these are special intelligence
Military people
Hey Alex are you going to do
FBI agent showed up
He's got the unmarked
These are not good stories
These are real soft
Imperative I have been f***** with by intelligence agencies
These are actual
Or if they are there the week ever
What are you are you
Why would you even say I'm not going to answer that
If you're aware if you're driving an unmarked FBI car that you can see in your huffing and puffing up
Are you from the FBI
Who's onemorestory Alex
Is it doesn't work
It doesn't
But
Parking lot
I got out
I've got out of line I was dead
I'm going to go get groceries
Things like this happen over and over again
What happens over Alberta
Airplane glow
FBI officers
Brilliant at Target Market
I guess I'm guessing he got into a fight with somebody caught him off and or maybe they cut him off
Something like that in the Target parking lot recontextualizing is like the military
I don't know
Really frightening stories
Zetabe
You better
But also I think because these are so bad
They might be real story
Not necessarily government people harassing
Bicyclist
Bike bike riders
What does a professional bicycle necklace look like
Ivelt
Lotto
I didn't know they were that talk
Classic
Floridians and bikers are very very tall
I did not know
Important
I don't know why I would do that
We know we've got this Army document that Alex
Incorporating
We have the big miac document
A big
That's the varsity narrative
Save it
Ettore service Bill his
Witchy escalated into
Yep
Resolved
Nope and then
The dod directive 1404.
By which
She thinks memes
Put you in
To service and send you overseas
Civilian employees in the defense department
An emergency essential personnel
. thanks
Next clip
What he does
Is he tired
Them all together
As if they're all talking about the same
Uses it to make
1 G
Narrative
The draft in the house last Thursday
I should be yelling and screaming and hyperventilating
To prepare the feasibility of forced compulsory service
What is a mean
Nexus Tire
Farm Direct
In support of combat operations
Giants
But also in
Hundreds of thousands
Little College
Mandatory
This is going
They are really trying
You see they're all of these pieces coming together
This is how they're going to get a lot of people
To be little doubt hundreds of thousands of bureaucrats overseas or something
Which I don't understand
She's also baby
What kind of position
Bureaucrat
Alex
Just housing
Fill out paperwork
That's what they
I need the paperwork
And we all know that really plainclothes military man
Therefore
He's just found little pieces that seem like they might go together
Just taking a little mallet
Jam the jigsaw puzzle
Together
Display has made
The color Dreamcoat
The time that you need to go through these things like
We can see all of them
Pieces that are each individually
I've come together to
Voltron
I don't know every member of the family as their own little patch
Sure it's 28
Taking the amount of time and paying the amount of attention needed to be like
Alex is all lies
What are you doing
Complaints about Obama
Really funny
Scores and speeches of Diane appearances
It's really funny that he's complaining about Obama have any permanent campaign
But he talks so glowingly of all of Trump's rally
How they're so great
Also dude
If it if this is 2009
We're still in the depression cause
By Valeska
Starting to make progress. We're not we're not
Pizza Valley
What is bulshit narrative
Arizona
About
The fear is about what's going on in New York
The albeni
Story
But you guys get back to Schenectady
I like the Schenectady
Completely unfounded
Whatever you want
You know Friday
Schenectady New York
Schenectady
Hockey Chicago all Schenectady
Declare martial law
WE Post
Schenectady
Is a smoky special mayor of Obama's
And Alex probably has
Bulshit
Come on
Schenectady would never lie to us like that
Episode ends up being
Interview with Kevin
Who is a picture of note
He is made a number of
Asheville
Alex Jones
Closest
YouTube Bill Hicks
He's one of the reasons that a lot of people believe that Alex Jones is Bill
Gachas because
Kevin Booth
Work with Bill Hicks
Card making
Movie about
The Waco
How to show all the time I believe there was a time or two that he's actually called Alex bill
But I think some of that might be true
I really care about that
But
So he's on because he's
He's working with
I believe there's a reality show that they're going to make
Kevin was Keeping Up with the Kardashian
Freeway Ricky Ross
Who was the guy who brought crack
Into Los
Rick Ross
He's the guy who's working with
I don't know all the details
Believe they probably had some sort of
I don't think he's making
Kia dealer and then he went to prison
And then he got out
Rick Ross
His name
Story of the pet
He's cracked and Ricky Ross
Sometimes
I watched a couple of his appearances
But you still in prison
Is coming on
Is reality show
Ricky Ross is going to get out of prison
Wonder Park
In the first year
He's making this show
He's going to make $1000000
It's so he can show people how to make that million dollars
He's going to do it without
Doing any crimes or anything like that
You just going to show you that enough
I don't think that's from everything I can tell from looking at IMD
I'm not sure I have no idea I don't want to disparage
But Kevin Booth is on
We brought on some assoc
Rick Ross
And
Man
Alex
Is so disappointed
Because he just wants
What's the talk about how the governor
Selling drugs
Rick Ross is going to
Come out and he's going everything
He gets into a conversation
I'm here with
Rick Ross
Straw
Has a friend named straw
This is where the interviews.
This is where the interview starts
Be very clear
Call Alex
Not getting what he wants
Are you worried about your safety
Of course not
Matter fact
As far as the whole
Ricky Ross
Trying to
Bringing
Russian
Russian fans
Sprint
Is really not what
Doing
What Rick is trying to do it through with move on with his life
That's basically what
With kidneys
Operation together
Not
Not to bring
Whatever
That occurred with him in the past
Corruption code
What is the look forward to
The future
What are you
Incarcerated
Understand
To be like
We're not trying to expose to make a multi like media out
Since we can make it
You're going to expose the CIA
He's just going to lower the rate of recidivism
He's trying to just make it TV show that shows that there's another way for people probably social excellent
Alex is
So disappointed
The friend of Rick Ross's
Equally disappointing
Just like
I really wanted to talk
So you guys are not getting you want to talk about creating a positive environment
Right Alex
Give this disclaimer
Cuz he needs
Take control of the narrative
Because he
Before they came on her promise this is all going to be about it
Call Dad
The main reason you're on today
Is the try to
Important
So he's basically saying I know you guys are saying this because he got two keys
13 interview so this doesn't happen like
What are you doing
So now this is interesting
Because that
Kevin Boothe
Comes back on the phone
He starts talking about the interviews.
He's had
Rick Ross
He's made
He reference
To somebody
It was Alex Jones
This world
Yeah I know absolutely then and liking my film to you know
It was sad that I
By Robert still his on your show all the time
CIA operative
Basically you're just saying that you know perhaps Ricky
Didn't make enough bribes on the local level
Through through various lawyers that can channel the bribes in Tavares politician
Kevin Booth references Robert David Steele
It says that he's on Alex's show all the time heard any appearances
Robert Davis
Steelers made at this point
But this is crazy
Because Robert is the guy
Who last year on Alex's show
Set that the globalist were kidnapping kids
I didn't know that
He was a guy who went back 10 years on Alex's show
I thought you was kind of a new addition to the stable
Especially considering the Robert David Steele the shows up all over the place
Jupiter project
Mistrusted him
Eddie bird
He's a guy who's been Alex's
Kampfer years
That's crazy it's interesting that area has previously Farm
Let's
Smaller claimed that was also part of
You will have to deal with his new Rick Ross
I find it very interesting
Steel appearance
Chick-fil-A
I don't think so
16 I believe you
He started coming in with his like
Devoted to unrig the vote
We need to get in the room with Trump immediately in a room with Trump
Get me in a room with Trump where there's no secret service
No
Aruba
Anybody would want to do that
Of course he was showing up
Little bit
The lead-up to the election
26th
He didn't Factor heavily in
And like I said I
My radar
Is up
Could be
Could be the
Booth's just never let
Sushiya
Then he has to have some reason
To believe that Alex knows Robert David
That's true that's true which is an even more interesting proposition
Is
Vicki knows that Robert David Steele Devin
I'm not entirely sure but we will see
Future holds
Alex has spoken
Freeway Ricky Ross
Associates
Sounds
Not very
Who he wants Alex to talk to
It goes a little differently
Alright only aware of the Iran-Contra Affair the forest
Wsvn weather
Iran and using the money to support the country
At the Congress cut out on Sunday when they found out the operation we were running
You just pulled me up out of the doldrums
Hakeem
Special Operations in Central America
Funny
Fighting the contras
He talked to him for like 15 minutes
Nothing of it is notable but it's
It is notable that
No idea who this through this
Diffuser
To protect the serendipity
And
Alex is reporting it as like alright I want to get you back on the show
This is veritas
Edith got to feel bad if your straw
Could have been that guy
I was talking about what I thought was a good thing and I was way wrong
I was way wrong
This should have gone the way of
Detox to him because very excited that's kind of the end of it
A whole lot
Even though it takes up
Yeah it takes up so much.
Like a lot of those too
And then
Ballistic
To be one of his source
It is what it is
He wants to
DOD directive
Khalid
To our point
Into the RV report
And what are you doing
Is he lies
You just says what it says
Absolutely.
Adam say
Basically
Terrorist
And maybe planning violent attacks
Basically decide to attack
And you can read that report
Cam
Order sheet
Dallas
Orders
You can
And the only ordered that is on there
On that third page write this report
It's just released this report that is it
Imply
Also sitting congressman
A report and release
Vet said a sitting us congressman
I don't believe it
I do believe
And if it is it's only that these
You don't like these protests
Once again say
Ron Paul if you get a lot of supporters of romp
It's not even
It's not even that
Lying about what this report says
Even more about like little specific
Commanders are
Remanded at the time
Set a reminder
Exercising physical security plan
No it doesn't annexes means sub directives with weapons
He's just making that up
What is the sub directive with like a regular directive has its own sub Direct
Sure
I just put it in the regular director
None of that stuff
He's claiming that bass
Commanders will ensure that
Random anti-terrorism measures
Program is conducted as an integral part of their daily operations
When is particularly important nudity
Static nature of our forces admission
Which often result in the establishment
Only want to go after you
It doesn't say routes
It says routine
Alex's
Completely lying about the word in there cuz he misread
Is mint
I know you meant to imply that
But I don't think he can read that
What is
Non-moving about the static nature of their operations
Yeah but there's some directive is about if they were like
Some sort of Engagement
Surveilling
That wouldn't
Gstatic
That would be
Active
Well they're not allowed to move from their post
Monitoring the
Mighty suspicious
They're literally in the bushes just staring out of them with binoculars
So you get the sense there
But Alex is bringing two
Some weeks yet
Use hinges
Is hinging on like words
Like
Route
Instead of
They got to sneak into they think we're going to attack them and stuff like that
Read the right word
The level
Real f*****
The rest of the show
Pretty much
Is Alex talking
Again. Alan Watts
Alan Watts
Ross.
He is a
Supreme New World Order weirdo
He is
Like
Are you just
Listen to him
I know I know
I doubt you're just basing this on on
Utter nonsense
Answer most of it is
He's kind of not worth going over at all
But
A couple of Clips temperature
Circular this one clip here
We're just like
You are lying
You are absolutely willfully lying
In fact they say
When you go into the right thing was off the big thing times that work for this global system
On behalf of David like the club of Rome
They said the democracy was just too cumbersome
They wanted collect
Activism under collectivism
You're looking at a trainable
He is making the argument
That the club of Rome doesn't
Democracy
This comes
Publication
First Global Revolution
We we talked a little bit about the closest Ramen
In the past and how one of them
Principles
The problems of problem
The problem
That is 30
The consequence
Dealing with that problem with
Problem
Exactly
ISO in their book
The
Did they put out the first Global Revolution
Call Vivek
It's reference
Expression nature abhors of a
Of the chapter is a lot of horses
Cohesion
Plus there's a vacuum
If we're not careful
Extremism or deck
Dictator could end up filling the void
Declining cohesion the public trust in government
Replace bike
Hostility
Largely born out of a recognized
It's not equipped to deal with
4 problems
Elected leaders like the understanding of complex
Political parties
Concern
The hole is just not designed to respond quickly
Immediate concerns
Country
Requires debate
Generally or at least it did when they wrote this back in 90
D91
By the time you've done
That's a very difficult
Process
That
Democracy isn't
Berkeley equipped
Campbell
Now the report is not advocating for abandon
Democracy
Exactly see very clearly
Quote the crisis in the
Contemporary democratic system must not be allowed to serve as an excuse for rejecting democracy
So
The difficulties that
Like dealing with modern problem when you have a democracy
They're very explicit about the ideas like
That doesn't mean that we should get rid of democracy
In fact we should find ways to supplement
The public sector and things
Is like that the private sector
In order to
The Democracy that we have reserved that
Political system
Dealing with
Challenges that we never thought
So basically he is specifically like
Because he knows
If he's read the club of Rome
The crisis in the Contemporary democratic system
He knows that's it
He's just straight-up liar
Yeah but these guys always think those are like
Coded language
So it's like
Covering their ass with that little stuff
Like they're signaling to the people who are believers
That this is what needs to be
And then they're hiding behind
To say that that's not what
They're always
They're always doing that
Like that's always the the
We're just putting
Like
You have to
You should acknowledge
They clearly don't want
Interpretation of
What did you look at it through the prism of water
Everything make sense
If you look at through my crazy world view this one
In terms of equality
Upholstery in terms of the people that you are speaking
What they want
Lie about
The club of Rome documents
Pointing out
Where you think the club of Rome documents are lying
You only further inoculate them
Because already now you're saying
Well whatever it is they say that
Who sang is it is you know
But it makes more sense to acknowledge it and bring it out
And then
I don't know
No but I get what you're saying if you look at it
Kind of makes
All I care about
Alan Watts
They get to another story that's really interesting I want to see if you can tell what this is
About
Today
Hillary
Criticizing government leaders
And that it is under election law now
Jamaica film criticizing any elected official
Do you know what this is about weight was this one of those
Project Veritas ystyle thing
Yeah
Veritas vaguely remember this
Dislike
I really remember some sort of like bulshit
Documentary-style thing that's like I can't remember
This is Citizens United
Oh this is Citizens United the group
15 Hillary the movie
What's the Free Speech argument
As it was
Do you have to reveal
If it comes out and it's clearly a political map
And the Supreme Court sound
You have free speech
It's just been applied across the board
Alex is on board early with muddying the waters about what
Yeah this it wow
This is that one
Yep and I think it's a strong indication
Maybe not though it's exactly what you would expect
Respond
Upon the things that he likes which is Hillary
And he is not understanding the underlying principle behind this
Well with case was
Tell me about the idea of
This is clearly this
Sure
You're presenting it as a movie
But it's clearly meant to sway political
If it's political
So the it was about whether or not you have to
The in the same way that you regulate political advertising
Donating
Disclose
All that stuff
That's what the case
Alex Azar
Bulshit
Jesus has led to horrible things
Little bit more
Skip this next clip cuz it's just him
Again combining that.
The Pfaltzgraff
Story he brings up the dod Direct
So it's just the two have now become
I'm skipping it
Really want
This is one of my favorite things
This
I don't even know how to describe how so
This weekend
What
Call New World Order propaganda
Is from the 30s
Basement water in your face and every episode
Cobra Commander
So he's early on it was all throwing a globalist
That you
Washington
Play were portraying Cobra Commander is the good guy
He's trying to say that there are externalizing what they're doing through the form of Cobra Commander
The first five episodes of g.i. Joe
Deprive the world of electricity by creating a superhero
Episode cobracummander launcher
Is Atlanta flooded the world's major cities
With a lava
In episode
Try to mind control animals that is at least a good plan
I don't understand
Flooding places with lava at all
Name to use to meth
Make
Any sense
Understanding of the Northern Lights episode 20
To conjure the ghost of a World War
Korean War battle
Which of course
Is the globalist
Alex
Snow out
He's out at Sea on this one this is awesome
Now I'm just I never watch the show but it's a romantic woman
World War 1 fighter Ace
Mongolian to fight and in order to defeat these ghosts
The most
Technologically
G.i. Joe has to find 3 artifacts
Talk about the 31st episode
Mesmerize you excited report admit
In this one he's for gold
Manipulate
The crash the world economy and the shelter
And he's bad gold is bad cash is good
Your call
Cobra Commander
Where can I get to CNN
Amazing program
Your Cobra Commander Alan Watt
The name that means that the snake system isn't the starting system
These people talking idiot
Mindset of playing audio video
It's because if you watch it
Video
The plot of the episode
Becomes clear
In that episode
It's not that he loves gold and he's trying to take over at Academy
It's the Cobra Commander has created a weapon
That mysteriously only destroys paper money
So no rules
Soda videos
The video that plays over that is of like
GI Joe guys playing poker and their money exploded
So it was only 2 weapon that can fire from vast distance
Anywhere within 300 or anything like that
Shmoney it seems like you would have already done it
Yeah I mean
It is a cartoon
Alright alright
I'm just having a lot of fun
With Alex
Play
Clips
From g.i. Joe
Are portraying
Libertarians I guess
Because I watched this episode ever
Snake masks
I watch this episode
Purposes
The fake create
Rapping
Destroyer
Course
To get cobra
Right
Now the printer
Hold on
That's good point
Does a great episode
Right
The issue is
Not about gold
Okay because
The Cobra money
Very clearly is shown to be non valuable things painted gold
With gold on it
Made out of Rock
Replacing the currency system
Is it nefarious plot where in these people
Don't know it's still everybody.
Add reminder it's charging
Money destroying where exactly how
Just like with any Project Camelot
I have to figure out the plot
Like a week from
This episode is like
The globalist
Resurrect The Ghost
What's the Korean
World War 1 pilot
You can't really pilot anything
Play
Yeah
But Wonder Woman was Justin visit
That's a feature of being a
Very ineffective because you could actually see her throat
I'm on 80 stand up get it together so we are one more quick left of Alex
Get it together
Together last clip we play at
Recommendation
Color of how to make some money
Create a laser destroyed money
Get spoiled
Not like
Electricity electricity
I'd like to see.
I really don't like how they all yellow Gojo
I don't know
I don't understand what Jojo
How do I cure a Alexa
Alex
Real trouble
Graphic design campaigns with billboard, use their own weapons against them
Parties for the film
I'm working on getting that.
Well that's another issue
Yourself man we have never done a money bomb and probably never will have
The technology to do that
He the guy is talking about a money bomb knows what it means cuz it's
It's like a Ron Paul did it and it was like a really big deal.
Make a deal 31st 2000 Alex had a Moneyball
I'd like to remind you
March 23rd 2009
Got a year earlier Alex had a money box
Here's the biggest question
Right
How does this guy know that billboard sales are.
He cuz he needs his plan is
Hyper-specific
Any considers billboards
Their own weapon that we must use against
The goalposts love billboard
We know that the globalist have weaponized billboards
Sales are dead
Alright
More importantly
Alex is already had less than a year prior
Alex goes on to have a money bomb on June 11th
Another money bomb on October 14th 2010
Money Bob
October 8th
He doesn't
Theory
He stopped having money bombs once he starts playing
The product
Brings along
Life appears
No money bomb
No money bomb in 2014
In September
We get a money bomb
Mysteriously
Right around the time Ted Anderson loses his license to sell
Weirdest coincidence
I meant something else has had a bunch of
Money bombs with a different
82 hour marathon
Believe
The timing of all that
Evidence
It looks like something
It looks like oh yeah that's the way you get cash
Infusion whatever you need
It does seem like a number of them around the end
But who knows
Correlation
Can't really say for sure
Looks weird
Episode
In front of me is
Alex is trying desperately
T2
To the plant
Of his Patriot aware price
Patriots
All this stuff is all these little individual lies that on their own are very easy to be
Now that's not
Trying to bring it together into a much bigger lie
It's more difficult for
Through
Because once he starts talkin about
Bbod story
Mixed with
The draft
He's still non-specific what he's talkin about it
Petarded be like
Oh no I can track that down
Right because we know the pieces of where they come from now we can see
We know the ingredients that went into that cupcake
It's interesting to see the cake
Getting baked
We know that it don't eat that cake
He's disappointed by Kevin Booth cast
Super Friends with Rick Ross
New Life
G.i. Joes
That was predicted program
Propaganda early 80s
2019 global
Absolutely
Has bad
Latta is bad
Control of a population when you wield the power of lava
Actually
That's for son to let me ask you a
If you are going
Find Romani woman
And ask her for 3
What does
Natasha
Still want to go
Talk to her about some of those
Maybe you just want to know
Make grapes
Carly Rae Jepsen
Looks like one of those
Stop music
Female pop artists who I think make a great pop
Nobody better show
Alright
G.i. Joes
Educational
The educational knowledge is power
Integrate pop music
Everybody should
Man
None of those people are ghosts
Do but you already said we could take the Astro for the original question
I'm still scared you like you want to answer your own question to go ahead
Bedingfield
Jeppesen
None of which are ghosts
None of which are guys
We all have it
I like how you accuse me of person who'd
But who asked you the question if you had $1000000
Never but these questions all seem likely like I have an answer to this and I want to tell you
Literally never done that
Steam like nothing but that guy would ask maybe they seem like the thing but I'm interested in your answer and your answer was cheating
It's not cheating
Identifying goats
Alright I feel like
We all have a shared definition of ghosts
And if you and I can't come to a definition of term
There's no
Lovecraft
Jeppesen
The guy who made homework
Alright do we have website
Dollartree.com
Underscore
Knowledge
Fun things to do
Absolute
Superfund
I don't know what you
You win this one
People remember most about g.i. Joe
Is that no one ever died
Skilled
But
Alex Jones
Probably finally got an answer to the three
Of my three and I'll tell you who that ghost is
The ghost of the guy that Alec
Probably
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work