Alexandra Thurston color
Hey everybody
Alex Jones
Hey
Midstates
Have to recount election with Rama
Vacations
Could possibly
I mean I know I know 2000
What's better situation in Ohio in 2000
I don't think it would have turned
Right now actually yeah that would have
You bring that up because one of the people who
Involved on the grounds are in Florida
Infowars correspondent
Officially finished
Gore won
The I know Rodger Stone
Who's involved because
I know a lot about Alex Jones Infowars
Unconventional
The people
Is a big announcement
People yet
In my lab
Working on the research for The Obama Deception
10 documentary
That we will be
The week of Thanksgiving
And everyone who supports
Over the week of Thanksgiving
Children love it love turkey
It's been a lot of
Research
That a lot of people have done things of The Obama Deception already so I thought my workload
New there is way more than a lot of these sites
I know that a lot of them actually got them
Things wrong
So it's
It's been a ton of like
I know that I told you during the endgame coverage
That I found
Specific factual problems with what Alex Jones said
Indian Game documentary
I lost
Lifetime you gave me an update
Roughly 200
I want I lost count about an hour and 10 minutes
I just don't even care what the actual number is
It's absurd almost everything
Isn't true fun there's a lot of fun information that I found out that
I appreciate it
So the reason is involved
In this being a
Unconventional episode
Is generally on Mondays would like to do a dive into 2009
She was going on with
The beginning of the tea party and I did
But it turns out a lot of the things that are going on in 2009 or things may come up
In The Obama Deception
Not to say that like to know about the miac report when he made the Obama.
It's a lot of stuff we've been talking about
Not necessarily in there
But it'd be very hard for me to myself
From spoiling
A lot of Obama 27
Can covers
Put that on
The 2009
Side to side
Let's do Wacky Wednesday episode on Monday
So I said to myself
It's dirty.
But I realize like 8 for long time
Jim Bakker I was watching The Tire hours and talking about
The migrant Caravan that like nope
Terrified of it it's not I don't
That was one of the things that really really struck me wrong
About
I mean the whole idea of Jesus had to do with like helping the down
Very off brand
Christianity
Sure there were never any situation
People were judged
Yeah
This isn't going to be fun
So I'm like
Friday last Friday's episode
Do a modern episode
I was very capricious
I don't know
The racism today it was really rough because he's talking about the
The recount
Georgia
Florida
He thinks they're scam
He does
He's also like no we got Rogers
George Bush stole the election in 2000
Do you have Rodger Stone one of the guys who was apart of venue like it was a good thing that he did
What are you doing it's soaking
I don't want to do that
I do it's just my head is
All of it
Singto is it a lot of it a lot of his stuff is bad
Paul Joseph Watson put out that video that was altered
Jim Acosta and he's all
Big Sean
At 1
It's it's a mess
A real man
Brazen especially for Alex someone brings up Orwell all the time
Write whatever they want to believe
The world objective reality has died
Sure
The end of all of these options
All these roads
More than anything
Is understand Alex Jones more fully
Highway
Of course that's really what I want out of this show because I believe that understanding him within the context
He's existed in
Years
Helps us understand the context that he exists in
I believe
Bully
The child is the father of man
To some extent
You know
Who you are what you experience
What you advocate
K4 is a part of what you
Generally
I'm so I want
Do 2009
I wanted it badly
B b
Because of the intersection
No good
So I decided
See what I could find
Even further in the past
Oh no
So what
It's very difficult to find actual footage of Alex Jones from
Public Access
But
I was able to find
A 2-hour YouTube video
Compilation
And another
From the 70s
No
His Public Access
Panera
What about Waco
It's a it's a pretty interesting glimpse
A lot of it is what you'd expect
A lot of it is.
Expect
It's
It's it
It's a weird Glimpse man
Just off the top
He doesn't give
S*** like or at least in this car.
Maybe they selectively cut out all the parts
Where we would be talking about these
Care
At all about anything
All he cares about is the governor
He is f******
Is he a witch
All about the
Government
All about being anti-police
There's a kernel of it that I'm like
Here you go buddy there's a kernel of it
It's like rock on
And I think in this first
Quit we get a glimpse of
Izzy Izzy
Is this all the way back when he's still spelt
He's in between
Alright
He's on the good side
Oh it's happening
No still hasn't turned all the way read all the time you know I don't
But I don't I don't know his wife or anything like that
Alcoholic
I don't know but that might be really thinking better handle it
Or at least while he's doing the show
Possibility
Fight in this first clip
We get
A piece of wood I
What I was thinking about you go man alright alright
Bit dirty sorted
That are I think
I think there's
Replace entire ask Laura if she is at the DMV protesting
Mistakes when they were solo he's he's at the Austin BMV where he has made it clear
Picture of
The DMV
Is put out new guidelines where you have to give us some Prince
In order to get a
Alex
Does protesting this interview outside earlier
I brought eight forms of ID
I have every possible can
Conceivable idea that anyone would ever want for
If they make me
Put my finger in the scanner in order to get my ID
I will lay down on the ground and make them arrest
Alligators coming it like I like it
Camera outside
Local news channel looking out at
Going outside
Dlnet
Here is a him trying to
Get arrested at
The BMV
I'm not doing a great job
What's the penalty for driving without a license you know I don't even want to go there that's right
You know why I'm asking you
I would be glad to see your Mark
Guard your
You're sitting here sergeant in telling me that you're all friendly and you're all nice
Problem with it
Thumb scan like Criminal
We don't even need to start there if I know that you're not going to submit to a thumbprint why waste your time
Criminal Criminal
The one who used the words
I don't know what I want you to give me my driver's license
And I want my driver's
That's fine
I like his voice
Dude
U.s. cellular near me
I'm not I'm just
Look man
I'm trying to get arrested on principal you're not helping me out here
You're saying you'd like to help me over and over again
Play like that in Paris
This was a fruitless Quest on a tentative level is
Because I don't
Necessarily think it is
Should be required to give a fingerprint in order to get a driver's
I think that this is probably a place where
I think it's a protesting that he's probably
A little bit
Alex's
Further argument that
This is just a step towards them
Blood in urine
Alright
This kind of Alex Right Alright guy
Beautifully Lodi
There's no downside there's a societal value to have
Exist
Isn't aggressive
No I'm not
Whether or not
That is the sort of issue
Glad you worked
You know what I never would have thought about it
I've been a cattle member just gotten up and then giving them a thumbprint
Take me away to the driver's ed school
Because
A little
Later in this exchange that he has
Alex
Reveal something about himself
In the mid-90s
Constitutional right to travel
BoBoiBoy
I'm not going to violate UCS
For your exception
Is exactly the point of Alex is a sovereign citizen
For sure
The ideas he cannot be like
Situational right
To travel that is
Sovereign citizen
Because they believe that you should be able to drive cars
And that the only reason anyone needs a license
Is for like commercial
And you can have that license in all caps
Otherwise they own your car
Alex
His phrasing that
Reveals to me
Clearly he has at least Sovereign citizen
Believe
Dating back
As far as the Moon
So that's interesting
I find that very interesting
I find the right to travel
Endlessly
Well
To get shot.
People who have guns
I wish I was just like a weird mainstream argument
Like why not have Elizabeth Warren just for one moment go on like I should have the right to travel across state line
What about state line
Haploid
Richard silly to because Alex starts to related
Can you have your f****** passport that works as an ID for any of those
Scrabble
It's it's
What up no fly zone
Does it do Sovereign citizens respect no-fly zone
I don't know about
Constitutional
To fly over in our magary area 51
I have a blind spot
BMV
Irate
Fun at least for our purposes
So harmless
Alex just getting arrested on principal going down to the DMV thing I won't
Duplicate license that's even better
Order for a publicity stunt
To be done
There's a Craftsman stupid would you take it out of realizes that
But
At the same time
You know
Its meaning is a
Seems harmless
Your honor in the
In the case of
The State versus
Humbly say
Dude come on
Dude
It, if you've already if you've already given the state finger scan
Or whatever
What you should do
Is make a big stink out of it
But still do it again because they already have your f****** taking forever so
I already have my fingerprint
You can save yourself please give him my duplicate license you should try and get your finger
To be forgotten
Famous Mexican
Alex Jones
Just taking a trip to the Grand
Wondrous Beauty
Drill baby drill
That's not the angle
He believes
President Clinton
Has signed an executive order
Control
Do UNESCO so here is Alex harassing people
Northern Arizona overlooking
The beautiful Grand Canyon
One of America's most beautiful Treasures
And it's very distressing to me and other Patriots people that
Truly do care about the environment America
What is executive order
January 19th
Began
Define over
Are National Treasures International
Control
Yes this is a international biosphere in world heritage site and guess who controls those
United
Wait what
A little bit of a
In front of the Grand Canyon
News remote to another shot where he's about to her a bunch of them.
Sorry
Ladies and gentlemen
Experiment
Executive order signed January 19th 96 by President Bill Clinton
Number 12
Which designated this is the world heritage site under UNESCO Corporation
United Nations Media
Have you heard about it
Heard about it
I pulled up
Executive order
Wants to
From 1996 signed by Bill Clinton
Yep
It's called International Union for conservation of Nature and natural resources
By virtue of the authority vested in me as president
Houston in the laws of the United States
Including sex
Blah blah blah blah blah blah
I hereby extend
The international Union
For conservation of Nature and natural resources
The privileges and immunities that provide or protect
Came to immunity from
Disinfect the following sections of the international organization immunities actual not apply
To the international Union for conservation
All it does is make immune
From Lost
This
International Union
No edit
Transferring
Property of the United States
The national parks over to the international
Community about that found a bunch of like Patriot
Message boards that work
Hey Alex says that this executive order gives the
Nothing to do with that
Even the people on his side were like
There's a huge problem with his argument that he's making
Funny
I don't I don't know do you need it
What's the drive-in
Now it's comical because
In the early days of the Trump Administration
He started making moves in order to sell parts
Start about that you plan on raping and pillaging
The punchline
Alex doing some more voice over after
Gets done harassing
These people about
Executive order that he is completely lying to
No sooner had I turned away
Call Mia
I guess they weren't 1286
I guess I don't believe it must I hear it from his mouth
Nothing to do with who's saying it has to do with like what the truth is
Yeah
None of them want to read the executive order because I don't believe in anything unless
All I wanted to do
Stand with my back to whatever it is that's by what is this
Call marvelling at natural beauty
I wanted to find people who scraped together enough money
People who live across country
To Arizona to see the natural beauty of the Grand Canyon have been dreaming about it for years
Finally got the vacation time from work down
Only yell at them about an executive order I don't understand
Literally like the plot of the
You know these roads
Are pretty hot right now
Are you coming out
EuroTrip
Maybe they work
EuroTrip movies
Probably years ago
Here is my point
We make a road trip movie
Early Alex Jones
Going to
Nuby natural wonders of the United States
February 1st
Steve Coogan and
Hot
They made three equal today
So far Alex Jones
Going to the DMV
People about bulshit
I feel bad for the people that were laughing so
The worst thing ever
Jackass probably in can
I mean
Lying about
To suit his purposes but I'm still like
No racism
Rudeness
Rudeness is forgivable
Slate Roofing
I'm in the next
Alex announcing something
So weird
Given what we know about Alex
I'm the person about 4
And I jumped the shark
Right here in Austin Texas
Southwest Austin
Where I live
How do you want the corruption ferreted out
You want real information.
Downtown
I need you and I have a major problem
Centered in the ballot boxes
And I'll be there making
Sure
Computer Fraud going on to where I sure
We don't watch
Election fraud
For the great legislature
Yes that's right
Computers
Unaccounted votes
Get inside that system
Inside that mechanism and I'm going to win
Here's my solution
To making sure voter fraud doesn't
Plant
People
In the counting situation
Secretly
Like like all good up-and-up
Pray right
No running
Representative
This is already worried about voter fraud in the primary screaming about like
Corruption
Luma 2000 election
You dropped out before the primary desire to
To quote focus on getting his
Who's out on the airwaves
Which he was already
Democrat kitchen ended up winning the election with 59% of the vote
My guess is that this is basically just a bit of a publicity stunt
And that no one was
Rallying around to fund his campaign is like
I give up
Like the idea of someone who's on public access
Using
Running for office as a way to get publicity
I think it's alright
Slightly and abusive
System
The guy who ran the bar I used to work at
Almost every time there was
Basically just to get promotion
Accidentally
Do you make sure of that by dropping out
This is just a hustler
At this point
From what we see
So far from the 90s
A mildly principled Hustler
Make the DMV
Because he's getting a duplicate
Do you like we said
Go there he's forcing it
And also get himself a ton
Free publicity
So
I mean I'm fixing this little
When is next Alex getting
He said something
The shocking
Modern
Distance from
Yeah we're winning over
University
Their engineering
Apartments
New World Order
And we're going to wear
How we know their Heroes left
He took me like three lessons over that I thought you said he had memories of in the slave
No
It it was I need to make that clear
I don't believe in reincarnation
You know it's true
Is that built
Arousing
Like his chops
Have always been
Gained any popularity is because he has the ability to
Turn that on out of nowhere
If he wasn't a flaming bigot and he wasn't
Completely obsessed
With these stupid
Communist propaganda things
I think you have the potential to be an amazing improv comedians
Like he couldn't
Indeed
He's one of the photo. I don't know if you had that guy
If you had someone who showed in the way in terms of
Collaborative comedy
I think he has the raw material that you could mold into somebody who is
F****** outrageous
He's making
Out of nothing
Out of nothing sexual memory
To know that that's forever
Because he's not making that up in the present that's been going on since he was
True
Schizophrenia
Frappe
Just
Really Vivid dream
Possibly
We hear another
It's very
He has said
Cincinnati
Well because that's one of those old-time maybe communist
It's like how old is
I thought I actually kind of thought he just made it up to the 67
At least
Suspected super racer
I don't think it is
I think it's more just about the
Communism
I think I don't know
I don't I'm not I'm not willing to give this one the races especially after we overreacted about coonass
Totally fine I'm one of them
If I'm unfamiliar with the term that has coon and ass in it but
Very
Is the better part of Autobots
Anyway
I don't know I wanted to say discretion and I accidentally launched
Anyway Isn't that cool
Alex
Which he's been afraid of forever
There's consistency there
To like what
Boast
Of his show is about
Back then
It's certainly not Bill Clinton giving all of our nuclear weapons designed
No no no it's people like
Sore
Randy Weaver Ruby Ridge Idaho
Oh boy
Yeah we are the terrorists
We're the danger submit to Total Domination
Total control
Total
Slavery
Waco is a sterling example this the lies and Corruption
During their activities for the children
That's why
The 17th
Little children to death
Again
From the terrorist
Their parents
This show is so much about Waco
Like I would say
Outfits to hour
Compilation that I watch
H plus
I don't want to talk to you much about Waco cousin
Super complicated case
So much of it relies on people deciding to believe whatever they want to believe
Like some evidence shows the David koresh
Is dangerous cult leader Brothers
Your stuff like that
True
That was
Southern tide
Another reason I don't want to re-litigate
Too much is that I do kind of agree that the
The standoff
Wasn't handled in the best way possible
I suspect there are better ways
They could result in that kind of
But I'm not sure what that path would
And I think it's
Beyond me
To assume that I know what the right is
Just to remind our listeners
Remember the
Clearly
What happened everything went wrong
Janet Reno threw a Molotov
The window of
That's Alex's version
Name the show that he does but then
Realize that Bree noses
Radio station
Search has made claims of rooted in the idea that won the government started the fires
The burn down the comp
People trying to
Leave out the back
Both of these things
Senator John Danforth was charged at the special counsel investigate
Waco standoff in 1999
This investigation found that they were
Very clear indication
Started the fire themselves
This is based on the fact that he
The potentially pyrotechnics
That were shot by the government they were trying to force people out
Of the
At the building
Those four hours before the fire started and they weren't fired in the places where the fires
Ended up starting
In addition to that lab analysis found that there were
Accelerants
Clothing
Investigators found
Punctured fuel
Beyond that survivors were on record saying that they overheard other Branch Davidians talking about
It's acceptable I guess to have suspicions about the fires
Faith absolutely unreasonable to assume that the government started
Based on the app
Real credibility
All the time
It's not true
Play the government was shooting people trying to
Escape this is based on infrared video that were shot by overhead are
It's people like Alex blame the video shows flashes
Gunshot
Is there bodies piled up by the
We are exiting the building
Right experts analyze the videos may sound that there's no way that they
Reflected gunfire
But they're actually thermal reflections of
The fire was charging up
Making spin in the air because of
That just sort of wind spinner cause
I've some reflective things ended up like spinning
It made it look like there was a
Flash flash flash flash
AMC
This is what every
Credible
Further there were no bodies found in the room where the rear exit
Rashad Rashad with high velocity
Around
Which one would expect shot by machine gun
Or snipers
People like Alex
So
He spent so much of his time
Building up his case about the government being
I'm super oppressive
Based on
Lies
Most of those people were victims
That board
Is the tragedy
Situation
Irresponsible
A lot of government fervor that he would like to be able to
Exploit
For his
Career
Make the furtherance of his
His career without taking into account
It doesn't match the actual info
It's a good thing that he only did this at the
The beginning of his career
And once he got that popularity
Realized
The error of his
And then it became a competent
Yeah
Right
Definitely
I'm sorry
I was I was
Revelling
So I don't know I I feel real
Grouse about
At Alex's
Waco Behavior
Especially realizing B
Continuing worldview and how he evolves the narrative
To do with the Bedrock of
His lies about Waco
Coupled with
What do you say
Maybe 10-15 times just
Compilation
Is like
Hitler burn down the reichstag
Ascend
Chancellor of America
Or Bill Clinton the after-effects you would expect
If this was some sort of a thing
Where they did this
Rice-like situation
The proof of the pudding is in the eating as they say
Although we don't know who may have been elevated
Through Waco
I hate I hate you
Somebody real in the elevator
I hate this so much
I hate I hate that so much
Because it relies on the word May
You can do with the EXO yeah okay
Sure if you use that kind of warp thinking
Whatever you would do
Might with you okay
So
A lot of a lot of
I don't know if I got a lot of this stuff is about
Rehashes of this
But there's one
It's Alex
Microphone
Presumably the town hall meeting
Arguing and insulting
When it comes time for me to leave my parents my girlfriend
Call my country
And
Are you almost laughing
Talk about that or I have no idea about that
Eureka
About this ATM
Criminal
Look like
No it's not personal
It's a it's a huge
I had to come and talk to you
I know what's going on the country I know about rex-84
I know about
I've Been Around The Nasher
I know what's going on
In this country
Since the early 90s early to mid-90s he's been yelling at ATF agent
Rex 84
Which in present day
He's I got to run before
Perfect
Is flipping on the idea of the
Stealing of the 2000 election
Waffle. Everything is
That is also just such a laundry list of things that immediately make you go
Oh you don't know what's
Oh I know about rex-84 about the national parks
I know about all the
I'll let you know what to do
Cincinnati
The Grand Canyon
Exercise 1984
That didn't
Happened
So I don't really thought it was
Really thought that photos after Alex's son
Edit
Drafted in 1980
But that's
Unfortunately not true
Finish up with Alex
Why you haven't Seaway carrozza gauge
Why you won't comment away from the back of the building brother automatic weapons
You saw it
No
Building
I want to take this information I can't believe you
He always
Backup
Multiple multiple times
Waco Rules of Engagement
Documentaries that was made
Since
Pretty thorough because there are some FairPoint
There is a little bit of you know
I do I don't know what the
In terms of like who fired first
Put the ogre yet
Could have been
It's unclear in terms of like
The government
Who fired first
The front of the bill
But the stuff that Alex
Specifically about the behind the building
Stop that overhead
Infrared footage
That is absolutely
The government shooting on the back of the building
Which is part of Alex is like
They were trying to slaughter the
Killed them when they were trying to leave
If you wanted to make Subs
About like
We need to really nail down who shot first
I was around nobody shooting at the back
Camden automatic
I don't know I don't know what I'm saying
That's scary I don't like
Machine gun fire
Like straight up
Gatling gun like murdertown
So
Alex
Information
This Waco rules of
Documentary
And it doesn't
Imply
You're making a murderer now
That levels
It's so good
But he's so talented at this stuff is able to turn
A cursory knowledge
Do something
With
Super compelling
It's really it's really fast
It's unfortunate because it is important
Yes
We got it why do you got to turn this into it you know like 911 like
The government
11 super hard
It was, they intercepted all this they know all of that s*** they f*****
Doesn't mean they did it
It could just be that their s***** at their jobs doesn't need to be a giant conspiracy
You know how you're that a******
A conspiracy but it would be
Suggested
I like
Yes absolutely there are there are
You talk about things like that
Conversation
Right because they detract on these
These
More out-there points
Art really based in reality
The conspiracy part of my life
He existed
Being paid in order to make sure we never had this conversation
Distracting people
It's not a good
Conspiracy
It would be if we had some sort of
Proof that were the case
It does
To be that's just
The NRA
His instinct is to muddy the water
Yeah
What comes
Patriot
White
Issues for the conspiracy theory I'm just saying
To be the Playbook that anybody who tries to talk about gun control runs
That's true
Coordinated Playbook that everybody uses
Whenever any gun control
Versation about maybe semi-automatic weapons
Everywhere
Do you know
Lies thrown around at all
Possibilities
It is a it is a feature of right-wing propaganda
And that's
It's suspicious
Certainly
Make some sort of app
Pronouncement
Conspiracy
Alex's
Exist for that role
But whatever the case may be
It is next to it which is our last clip Alex says something
That I find
To go over the
Real f*****
We have the force
We have the capacity
We have the world and we will not surrender
We are the ones
Where are the ones galvanizing organization
Where am I
Where are the ones
Terrorism
You traitor you globalization
And you Governor bush from your CIA run Harriman brother Banker oil family
We got your numbers and weird and we are moving forward
Can you be fully aware
I'd like to thank our sponsor
Oh really add pivot
Remember that speech immediately after he gives that whole fucken
Also I would like to thank you very much
It's wild the fat strategy midnight
Radiate 3rd grade
I think the reason for that is that
Cell
Thanks sponsors
Inclination
Because at this point he doesn't
Have Ted Anderson
Right resources
Communication
What's he got on board
He didn't get commercial
He barely had to
Do any
So
At this point he's doing that
It's for a numbers remember looking at my 2009 stuff
Could you didn't have to
Often at the end of the show
To be like
Search for the points when he actually has those sponsors on air
To do
To make you fraid of food issues
That's so clever exam
The Grateful song
The reason
Multiplication
That's his way of expressing
Each one teach one
No
I'm going to reach more people
Group it feels like
Got too crazy
I think it's f***** up is using the term L list
And the reason
Leaderless resistance to the term was coined in 90
Take me to VyStar
As a means to promote Revolution
The idea was that Loosely connected but not
Formerly connected cells
Decentralized actors
Against an enemy with numbers were far greater
It's still stand a chance to succeed
Literally
Kind of early apply acts of violence or anything like that
At this point. Kind of a strategy is all good and well
If that's what Alex
She's referring to
Because Alex complains about Bill Clinton
We can be sure that this rant was post 1992
This is important
The concept of leaderless resistance
Bell Auto
Until 1992
What a man named Louis beam wrote a note Aureus article advocated
Leaderless resistance
Lois Bean was a door gunner in Vietnam
Ku Klux
Plant eventually become in the Grand Dragon
Of the Texas
In 1982 he was arrested for kidnapping his daughter from his estranged
Who ended up dropping the charges
After receiving Target
B rassman and threats
He was known for not being at all
Not into viola
Spell bullets will prevail
In 1981 beam want to pay a visit
Aryan Nation
Compound in Idaho
Which Butler then the
Visiting Whitby mkk
Galveston Bay
This resulted in Butler declaring beam a quote ambassador-at-large
And serve to bring the two hate groups closer
In 1984 be was instrumental in
Creating the Aryan Nations Liberty
The world's first internet hates
He helped bring white supremacy into the Modern Age and gave white supremacist an online platform where they go
To come together
Deform a bulletin board
But most important to re-issue
Is beams 1992's a leaderless resistance
Here are just
A few passages out of the
Exactly like Alex
The passage of time will make it clear that even the more slow Among Us that the government is
Is the foremost threat
The life and Liberty of the
We are cognizant
Before things get better they will use ever more severe police tape measures
Against disappear
Quotes
The federal objective is to imprison or destroy all who oppose them
And I'm talking about that sounds like
Dumber members
Amongst
His rank
The government the government they opposed has declared a state of war against those fighting for face folks
Freedom and constitutional Liberty
Using Focalin
That's kind of Bill O'Reilly America is quickly moving into a long dark night of Polly
Bi-State to urinate
Where the rights now accepted by most
As being inalienable we'll just
The sound
Very similar to Alex Jones
Yeah easily been written by
Mecosta exultation of the
The references
Command and control
The specific terminology used
Describe the American Revolution and how that situation
Analog to the fight against
Modern.
All there
Given the timeframe in the extensive overlap of
I can't come to any other conclusion than Alex Jones is
Was very inspired by Louis beams Sao
Leaderless resistance
He was a patriot from Texas
Wasn't
Becomes almost
Unsaddle
It's worse than
What we have is the Grand Dragon of the Texas Clan
Who served as an attache Ambassador with the Aryan Nation compound
In Idaho
Extreme flare up
Yeah
Militia Act
Supremacist white nationalist
Militia activity
And you're saying he influence Alex we're all inspired by Ruby Ridge Waco Oklahoma City
We have the leaderless resistance
Which can't be read in any other way
Eating that
Contacts in that time
Listening to Alex Jones Show
They know that is code for this
Very seminal essay
It was written by Louis
This I don't think
Does Deadpool
When you look at it from the
The prism of
You look at
Alex Jones
Certainly
Casey Shelton
I think we get Eclipse here
B a b up to some real bad stuff
Victor bombers brother news him because he saw the
The pet phrases in his
Is manifest
There's a little bit of
Where there's smoke there's fire when you're using the same language somebody else
It's not like leaderless resistance didn't
Before that essay
It was not
Very pop
It was used
Turtle in the sea
It was something that is falling out of
Vogue as I said
Edwards ignited
Envy
Patriots
Anti-government communities
Yeah
The fact that Alex is speaking after night
T92
Really
It makes it so hard for me not to draw a clear line between
Just getting
Like the leaderless resistance
Philosophy is
Because they had this whole
Did if you had a
Pyramidal structure
And you had a leader up at top
Buddy who infiltrated
A certain level would be able to
Two bird everyone below them
I possibly people
So if you had upside down
Sure if you had an upside-down pyramid
There be much less people
At the bottom of it
Point of entry for possible mobile
That you'd be able to burn
And if there is no
If you just have sales of
Lone wolves
Or five people who have their little group
It's almost impossible
Able to infiltrate
So that
Super
Super important
To the rise of
Demolition movie
The world we live in today
It's a it's a local exit hold on
It is a Sabian accurately lays out exactly the purpose of a show like Alex's would serve
Some of the groups
They do exist
Useful purpose
Either for the newcomer who can be indoctrinated into the ideology
Give the struggle
Or for generating positive propaganda to reach
Essential freedoms
So it's almost like in this essay
He's explaining what Alex Jones is
Purpose would be
Proud boys
Generator
What positive property
He whitewashes a ton of hateful rhetoric a bunch of
Dominative
Any
Turns them
Things
People could use an entry
Three-point and we seat like Robert.
Kids podcast
He did a
Study
He's got a lot of chat logs
Discord server
They were all discussing
It's super
Hi number
Alex Jones is a palatable entertaining
Very talented broadcaster
Can you get in with
And then eventually
Either turn on him because you think
He's not talking about the
The Jewish question
Or something like that
Do you go to someone more extreme
Leaderless resistance as they he's talking about the idea of
This can be useful
Purpose for the newcomer who can be indoctrinated
The ideology of the
The struggle
The idea that Alex is saying that we use a leader list
Resistance
After this essay
Call Wildfire
In
Malaysia community
I know that he's read that paragraph
I don't know why do I don't know what to think
I think he has influenza
Probably has family members who either are or are they
I know I know
With his
Family
That he likes to brag about
Where he live
Highly improbable for him.
An extended family member
He said he's related to
Bedford Forrest
The guy who started
He's he's been
For a long time
There's like what I get when I heard that
It was very trouble
To me because
Vegas Vacation
Probably
This episode totally
The whole time we were at the BMV
We're at the Grand Canyon
See the Grand Canyon
Alarm
Yeah
Sorry
But there's an underlying
That sort of
The ideology that philosophy
Behind
You know that's the guy he is
Maybe we got the wrong
In front of his dad
Maybe he's not a
CIA agent
Maybe the KKK
Possible
Toothbrushing ilysm
So to answer your question about the show
Clips
Can find of his show where it looks like more of a set
Saint Austin
Community Access
Yeah
Which is just hit a black
Like cuz he's filming amid his dad's Dental
Corner of the dental office
With one light
I think there's some there's more sincerity
Visually
Compilation
The street
And stuff like that he needs to get back to his roots
He said he's in his
Recording studio Castle
From time to time
Get back to the Box
I don't know it's
Think of him having a tea
TV show on cable access
I somehow can't get past the idea of like you
And he's got it
And he's got the little end table to the left of them Amore Styles what are the only Clips you can find
And on YouTube is of his Halloween episode
Like taking callers while carving
Great it's only like a minute-long and
So anyway this is interesting
I think there's
There's there's
Questions that are raised by this
Into the early career of Alex
Sure better at the very least
Answered
In 2009
It seems like it
But if
It is weird to be like
So
Different
And things that are still the same
Funeral
Yeah I was about to try calms all the time
That's never change
National
Doesn't need to go to the DMV anymore you can mail in your registration and get a new license that way
I don't know maybe you need to stop
About to go in
Pissed now too so
Addition to the facilities with a DMV
If
And blood testing
I think you'll be ready to hire a phlebotomist
Phlebotomist
I needed
To go back to the past
Present
And 2000 I didn't work I think the scratch the itch
Yo
Has great
Great thanks I want to go to the DMV Now
To do
Wistful for the DMV
The physical DMV in
Columbia Missouri
Biggest hassle in the world
So it was like all the jokes about that
BMV
Whatever I lived
Sucks
And then when I moved here I needed to get a new IP I need an Illinois ID
So I thought
How bad it wasn't Colombia
Going to the DMV in Chicago
Worst I went in and out of there
Was anybody protesting
Not at all
Needing to get a new ID
Expired
Nightmare
Partially my fault
Difficulty that you would be mad at them
But it was my fault for not having the right information
Partially
Laser.
That was why you could
Absolutely
You had to give him some
I will be back with a new episode
Call also.
That Obama Deception
Forgot be crazy
Thank you all for
For supporting us
I am.
Getting up to the point where
Fuckology
You also
Is this
Is a lot of work
Elsevier website
Social media Network
Check us out on Twitter it's knowledge
Watch the social
You go to Hulu
I don't know where it streaming
But what was the movie about
Great
Performance Bike
That's what it was about
Actually make a movie
About the grape
Disagree I would not be affected by Mark Zuckerberg
That's correct a lot of fun over there
Leave a review need Force multiplication
Yeah
About you baby
I don't know if anyone's died at the BMV
Like 80s
Joke setup
Someone probably died no good
Fingerprint
I'm looking over a lot of these
Involved
Text Jones
The Grand Canyon
Nobody. You don't know that
You don't know that for sure somebody falling
We can reasonably assume that no one died that day
It was not great
Could have
Ended
Alexandra First Time coloring with huge fan I love your work