Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
When was the last time
Aquarium Museum
I want to Shedd Aquarium
Downtown
Surprising number of
DigiTech
I have like a
Do cats like humans in 23 years
The end of the whole thing was
Was kind of implying
Are we going to be a part of this one
What was the diversity of the said even if climate change
Achilles the fact that were destroying all of the species of the world means
Biodiversity assessment is really just
Because I know
Never been smoother
The show
To the wacky wacky world
The secret space program my God I need a Wacky Wednesday
Coming up next week
And that is a whole lot
So we want to give you guys a little
A little reprieve from chocolate
The wonderful world of Project Camelot where Kerry Cassidy
Investigative reporter
6.
How about their time in space
Perfect show format
It really is
Is it
Until you get erased
It's kind of
Ill-advised
I'd like to take a little moment
Somebody who
Has
Appreciate
Tamale
You are now
Ewok
Thank you very much
We can go to our website
Sports over on knowledge fight.com
We would appreciate it
Is Molly
It's mollywobbles sower
Default maybe last initial sometimes
I think people would prefer you left their names out of it and just
Said they're at
Just came up with fun
Great nickname
My social security number is my day
Play what we've got is an episode where the title of
Is
Secret space program recruits
Okay I'll write I'll write down with a couple of dudes
And the other guy I believe is Tony Rodriguez
All right there
May or may not be super soul
So exciting the lead actors in a reboot of chips
That's all I'm saying
But here is an out-of-context drop
290 you have
Started out as a
Illuminati sex slave
I would say that's a tough like entry level position
Possible for any
2toni
Different stories
Space together
Or anything like that
Their story which
Together and I believe they met each other through some internet forum
Amanda
I'm 40 I'm all about French
Here is Kerry Cassidy
Beginning the interview
Starting it out
Hi everyone I'm Terry Cassidy from Project Camelot and I am
Today
With two very
Resting individual
And we're going to be talking about
The secret space
Program Mars
Variances that
I have been having
In their past and I'm not sure whether there is
It's on going or not
Where to find that out
So we're just
Calling them Secret
Space Program
Fruits
Designation
Are there tide
Sadra
Why don't you have a designation
I don't know but isn't Alex
SSRI
Supersize program-record opportunist
Hallucinogenic
I think that these people might be suffering for
So I feel like it
Years that carry Castle
He's been doing this
Whatever level Veyron
Movie like nose
Noncommissioned officer
Contractors
Here is the gentleman
Their relatives
Should like to welcome Jason rice and Tony Rodriguez
Screen over
To them here in
Just bear with me if we do have
All right so go ahead on
Real quick
That's important
Is it an issue
Remember that I've been spoiled
Hello everybody
Thank you for having me on your show today Terry certainly appreciate you
Yeah everybody good to be here
And great beyond carry
For the first time and I'm glad do this is my first time really with Jason Lively been in
Contact with each other
Green guy off for awhile now
Also it's a it's good I'm still learning about his for a happy to be here and continue
I believe that to the internet message board
Right right right
Time to each other
We got hooked up together by the
Alright man
You talk to a tree
I would say that this interview is
Probably like
It starts out real
And then
Disappoints
For a bit and then gets
Alright
Someone like Eddie page
Whenever we have those people and it's kind of like things just
Keep Calm this is ridiculous
It is like a
Drab adult
No-nonsense kind of
He has a real boring voice
So he's coming in with like
Retainment Valley
That you would help from
Space weird
But like I said
Responsible
He wasn't Tony
A butt
I told you this starts out hot
And here is the
Where Carrie starts reading their bios
Is dope ROM
So it looks like
Befriended
Human
Appearing visitor name
How do you say the sign
Send my love lyrics
Cultures and people
This friendship
Saltillo lawyer witches
Artist
This doesn't come back up at all
Vienna the agent doesn't it secondly doesn't come back up there
That is why he is an escape artist no idea what that I would have loved to know
But
It goes on
Jimmy Church
His show you will have heard some of that
He got involved in an
Cherry my lab
Situation
And he was in
Identified as an intuitive empath
Corsage
Experimental Behavior
Daddy's
1980s
And the Seven
Last year my lap
Training
1977 this guy would have been
Under 10 years
The 1970s
So
Just consider that
And
Most of his
Time in Act
To a program
He was involved in Atlanta and I'm going to
Kind of skim through this
That's a little rude
Okay so Tony
You just choose drugs over to Tony.
This guy was friends with an alien
Bus station I guess that is kind of blase
Dura Dura Dura
Mr. right
46 years and married father
I Loved Her First
He's poor
E46
Sold
Married
Father
The worst way to confusing possible
From
A name I can't pronounce Michigan
Doesn't keep cilantro
Working class man
Normal is
Kind of
? there
I was involved
Human I think you're calling yourself sort of a Slave
Our sex slave
Satanic worshiping and
I'm assuming this wasn't your with your
Your permission
We need to start getting into the Dom sub relay
Bishop's part of Obama sucks covers
Find that out
And I later sold off to seek
He served on Mars
Sportster
Support Soldier
Search for the model waiter
Look up directly from sex slave to Soldier
Involved in this
Series colony
Where he lived
Over a decade
And was working on German
Sepsis
Repairman and eventually and cargo engineer on it
Betrayed me
Sleep now part of his story is that they are able to
The digitally trained
Things to do that
It's terribly like I just downloaded Kung Fu For Me main issue
If you just
Like the people the Illuminati
Who owned him
We'll learn a little bit more
Gave up his papers like they they sold them off
Because it was in a
Particularly boring
Stretch of the show but I believe
Stuff like that
Do a different drug
Who drugged them and he was allergic to that drugs
I believe that that is how he
That is the most reasonable explanation I've ever heard on
He's not terrible at war game like he is pretty pieces at like
Alright that's alright also
Cut through any of this conspiracy bullshitted not like
Right rice
I wasn't saved by anybody I was allergic to this new drug
Bummer it it's like recommendation whatever I became a soldier that if you're already in for a penny
That'll help you get in for a pound
Do you have decent Prop Shops
Storyteller
So in this
Next
You got to gold
Secret space program
You can hear it there that he worked on the Mars colony Corporation
Event ended up in the series Colony Corporation
That's because people like him
Acute sinusitis
Kerry Cassidy's whistleblower
They're very big into the idea that these are corporate in
Interlake businesses
Sure
There's something
William Shakespeare
Can I listen to this
Twice and missed it both times
But I'm so glad that I
This is something that I think is the Pinnacle of ludicrous
Okay but I will get there as we
For now we have to find out
How did Tony
End up getting into
This whole thing
Situation because
I don't think you sign up
To be an Illuminati sex slave
I think that's a situation probably
You're not you're not thrilled with the situation
And then they
I don't know right
Makeup for the steak tips
Mysterious Corporation Fallout
Entirely possible
If we find out the
Not something
You found on
I don't know
ZipRecruiter
Something like that
I also don't think they would like be implying that Illuminati sex slave openings
Do you want me to text late check-out ziprecruiter.com
Well I didn't go through
I wasn't groom
For the space program
I was I was kind of more of a victim of it like
In early years I made somebody mad that had Acts
They put me in that
In that program
The score and back
Or whatever Arie want to call it whatever we call it nowadays
Where I was taken at night
Did 20 years and put back and during that time I was
Though it was done as a punishment
It wasn't because I was
The best man for the job
Somites
Did my particular situation is much different than other people you've heard in that regard
But why me and Jason are working together as what I found is that
You know
Since I've done my first I've done over 40 interviews now
And since the first ones with dr. Stella
People have reached out to
Most people don't remember as much and people that remember quite a bit don't want to talk about it
What I found is that the absolute best therapy
Speak to other people that experience it into me and Jason have been
Able to do that
I can respect that little
Right right you had access to the secret space program
Well and you and then open the next
20 years of sex life
It's also kind of important to consider that he's 46 years old
And he will later say that is able to 1982
So you was married for 46 years on top of that you would have to invent
This happened so he pissed off someone in the secret space program
World for 20 years
And then put back into his body the exact so
This is all
Birdnow this is all metaphysics
No it actually happened
Who cares it's the same thing with it
We'll get into it with when we heard that interview with Randy Cramer
He had the same
Situation
I believe his version of it was
He got cloned or something like that
They made a younger clone
To put back
Into
Who cares
It's all nonsense
I promise
I promise you
Everything okay
So a little bit more
Seeing them come back door Escape artistry
It should so we learn here more of the back
In this clip
It's only a minute
But he drops a couple of bombshell p
Formation
The carry does not follow up on
Until later in the
Play the program that I was apart of
Called
And it's actually
Was
Earth providing 24000
24000 G forces
Or used by the
German Breakaway civilization
Initially
It was going to be used for Border Patrol
What it was
I'm worried about it too
What is a Volkswagen
Which we were helping
Their planet
There aren't enough of us
To fight for them
So our mission was
To help train
Build up their defenses
Help them to
Create their own opinion
And I
The 20 years that I
I spent in that program
I made it
Through the rank of major
So they always
First of all bars Germany something that should set off alarm
I believe
Learn by the time we have not
That is unfortunate
I already assumed pleasure
In space
But the other part is when I
Hear that
Cliff
I can't not think about the Iraq
You know
Feel like that
Entirely a poetic way of describing what happened
Iraq
Because if you want to talk about false Flags
Some things like that everyone
Involvement in Iraq
Actor gets.
That that sort of
So
That's there
Him being like
We weren't there to fight we were there to try and train these
These martians or alien
In order to figure out
Border
Border control
I we were trying to make it so a raccoon
Did sell all like here is a
Bentley veiled metaphor for our failed foreign policy
Over the last
Decade
We don't need the
Iraq
Enough for you for everybody to be like
Evil off of
Literally like
Did you hear that George W bush got
F****** metal metal
I'm not going to say anything other than that man should be prosecuted for war crimes Under The Hague
You shouldn't get a battle
Right right
Beer minimum
Could you set a building on fire and then you put out the fire at
Did you get an award for
For putting out the fire
Gametal
Self
He was there for 20
I work with
German
Of course he gets back
Just minutes after
Have you had
My term of service in IDOC was
I'd argue over
20 years
The worst Mac products
Stanford electric rollers
Defense in Readiness for since I believe is what I dark stands for
Secret space program
Better than I do
Okay but in real time
Were you gone for like
Longer. Of time
How does how does that work in Earth years
Workout
Equal time
Was 20 years into months
But my reinsertion back
To the initial departure point
Happened
Within a couple of hours of my
Receiving my change of water
Why
Okay so
Will the royal couple of hours
Because they
Can be explained by a night sleep or something like that a couple hours
This is very easy for you to be like
That's the amount of times that I wasn't here no one would have noticed if it was overnight
Keep notice if you were gone for
This is important because a couple of within a couple of hours
20 minutes
Totally
You're preaching to the choir
I empathize with your complaint
I don't have an answer for that but there must be a Sikh
I don't know
There's got to be some sort of like you do they still have to do the paperwork on Earth
Or something like that I don't know
If I understand
Maybe because
A Time paradox
Or two of you exist
Who knows with these people because they need their to
To be like
Oh there's proof but
Oh yeah I was gone for a couple hours you can ask my parents
Was gone for no time at all but then you have
24-hours of
Baby baby
They don't even have
A couple hours
Another attempt on Jason fart
To imply that there was hard evidence
Anymore
Enhancements that we received
Where nanites
And course
Ring from
My system
All of the insurance that I had during the day
We're going
So
Any of the
Sorry but you say nanites
You're talking about Nana
Rihanna right now. Cantrell's everything on
Planets
Actually clear.
Completely because
Cuz we've all got it
You have a second
Do any of the other nanite
Others present in the atmosphere
So super soldier enhancement
Consistent
So that way
White wine
When did they flush them all of it is out of his
A couple hours after he left
I thought cuz I saw
Yeah he was like
Mentally taking away I don't think so I think that was another physical
I think all of them
I don't know what I look like
Physical kidnapping
Just taking someone's consciousness
Is my
Interpretation their bodies going
Grabs him
Put a man in space
Work with space not
They aren't even the ones
Trading or helping
Space docking
Boonton German
Bars German
The thing is I understand it is they
They physically take the person away
What's the problem
The consciousness
Out of the person and put it in a 10 year old
Clone
Of the the person and then puts back
Alright repressed the memory
If you can transfer Consciousness you could wipe
Remember never remember
Ecology is like
There's no reason for them to not improve it to the point where these people can't remember
Furthermore
Number one point of order
Alright
This is a shadowy group of interstellar traveling Space Nazis
They can handle all kinds of s*** that are abducting children
Spending and sending them to act slaves or soldiers
Respectively
Caleb
You wouldn't spend all of your time and money like rebuilding them and putting them back into a different bottle now.
Contra
You're totally right
Yeah cuz people just
If you were a child but it does happen the kids disappear
Fear from their homes
In the middle of the night from home
Elizabeth Smart taken from her house
Maybe
Listen through your windows device
So like let's say
Jason
In the middle of the night
Secret space program takes him up
Tomorrow's to
To be a major or something
Do they bring him back makes no sense I ground it wouldn't cause any
There is a fundamental problem with the way these Moon Nazis do business
If you're going to steal somebody abduct them and put them put them to work for you for 20 years
It is an implicit agreement that politeness
Dictate
You bring them back
Resume to that
Leave it better than when you found it
Sure get rid of all those
Also true of the camp
Consciousness
Put it in a 10 year old
Clone body they wouldn't have the nanites
Where in the body
You like displacing
The consciousness
Back
This makes no sense
I guess what the event is like
It's not that they put the country
Is it a clone date
David machine that makes you a ten-year-old again
I don't know Space Nuts
Very
Contradicting position
From Jason
For a little bit
He has a little bit more than him
And then this is
He's got everything going on
Investment Club
Do you think you did
Everything
Basically it was a 20-year
Turn
That I was taken
In the beginning I wasn't
Play service
Seems I was privately owned
And I went through a program CIA remote viewing program
Where we were
Classified as clones
So I can't work like that intuitive work
And I ended up living in Puerto tahuantinsuyo Peru and
He was a psychic that they were drugging
They could put me under and I was
Being used as a
Security measure for an airplane that shipped cocaine
From portal tahuantinsuyo to Santa Marta Colombia
Can you could you could you give me all of the details
Using psychic involved in Iran Contra
I would like all of the details there
Harry does not ask any
What
For the CIA which makes them
Bridge
Sure
Maybe
I don't know
How could you know
You would never actually not
And he knew that clones existed and he was being drugged during all this time
Any was classified as a
But you yourself are the clone a real person who died or was
Seems to
Used to be that he is certain
The Clones
That part
Check that box Roy the theory or the end of this clip
Just wait one second
Sorry you called yourself
Was that a purpose
Explorers Den
But I think it was a misunderstanding but the doctors that worked on me
How could you know
That put me through that program which I trace back through project bro
The CIA
Considered me a clone
So I don't know if they were told that so that they they were disconnected from us but
The more I look at it adds up
Has more than one second
They can do what I think there's many different
I've got a few
Did the same as earlier
Medication
So they sold me off
That's alright cool dude
Dehumanized me like
Love that! Feel like they were f******
I loved it
I love that explanation as to why I am once again on his side
Good enough
Also
Because they do
You want to hear it
From the other horse
Were you taking off
A few hours that amounted
220 years or
How would you clap tinoco
I was taken at night after we went to bed I had a
We have the UFO experience I have greys and reptiles
Open my bedroom that carried me off
Makeup me back this very same night and I woke up and had breakfast
My family's next morning
Okay what year was that that you lived those 20
In my rutinel interviews
School year of 81 but I thought 81 but
Good morning look back on it it was
It was around April of 82 that I was
Fourth grade
Liar
Disney Original interviews
He said it's 81 now it's 82
Because I look back on my life
Is a little bit of
I might I might be a little bit wrong about some
I think that's normal if your Maybe
Spell I can't argue that although it seems like
Massively traumatic events like being kidnapped by aliens
Here's another issue
Entrained
Remote viewer
You should be able to put his brain
The past in
Baby tooth pain
I
I don't want to I don't want to ask him to open up old doors
Evenflo sleeping
How am I able to do the remote
The natural York
Having a vivid dream
Is it going to be responsible
For some
It's not a
Does Gear in
Next clip
Tony playing
Precipitate
He's coming out
I'm talking about being
Being a secret Soldier
When I came back
And I had my memories back on my lights off
It certainly seems logical that I was taken
But whatever my Sparkle icon
Taken out of 1
And put into another blank slated body and then
Put back and so that way those ears weren't remembered so
After the 20 years
Brief memory
But after the 20 right after the 20-year Mark right after
No 2000
Then I had an MRI done
And that's what triggered the memory
Also at the same time with one eye
I discovered Randy Kramer's first interview status
Find ballet
In the same night and I think that's when it all
I was in denial of everything
I remembered I was in
Complete denial
When could I have had time
Understand it look out the window the Starship over the planet Ceres
And look at look down when could I have done that I
I had chronological memory of my whole entire life
Maybe when you're asleep
Time to like stand out on the bridge
But like you hear their man
I had all this stuff they came to him as I call it all makes sense
Now that I've heard Randy Cramer tell.
Exact same story
On Project Camelot
This is like
This is a clone
Generational super soldier stories
All the Project Camelot
Is
It certainly seems logical
Favorite favorite
They removed my Consciousness and put it into a younger body
Spell Occam's razor
Yeah it's a little it's a little much
It's actually called Mac has raised
Will you learn a little bit more about Mars German
Iran
I know we've already talked
It is bad news
It is that is that the worst thing that you can say about Mars Germans they're very clean.
News
Is not good for
German
Series colony was a German break
German Breakaway collar
You knew there were German
Because why
Expensive
And there were everywhere you with every every
Where you at there was an eagle with a different symbol under it
In some places
Yes
Places that happen.
Western Society ran
Was it run
Call Sasha
The fastest colony
I'm series
Yes
It was a military it was ran by the military
But they were German
Yes and they reported to the Antarctica
G Series and had absolute power there but they reported to the high command on Antarctica and I believe that the high command on Antarctica
Reported to
Reptilians
I believe that
Bobo's
What about Dimas
I'm not familiar with any operations out Bobo
Project Camelot
There is that line
Except
Are we were all like
Chicago it turns out that that's a reference to 2010
The sequel to 2001 Space Odyssey I didn't realize that
Call went over my head I completely thought that she was
Saying something about like
Information not looking for the movie
Yeah who cares
So the other thing
I want to know what's going on in Phobos
Remember find out
How do we not find out
We do know is that serious is rotten
Bars
German German
They speak German and have Nazi regalia
Do you know who else I would describe
Like 10% of America
Spiritual
Most of them are you Linda
You know they're run by
To Antarctica
Which means
This guy believes in Halloween
Because that's where it's stuff is that there are underground not going right
New Berlin
Center of the Earth
Informed
Just like that
So he believes in followers but also apparently this is news to me
The Antarctica Nazis report
Reptilian
Outside
Which is exciting
He also says that he's never seen a reptilian
That they're in the mix
Okay
Which is way more than if he was like
Yeah
Yeah it is
Difficult
But it is
Expect from an outright conference
Describing
Vivid hallucinations are dreams
That stuff like that
Sounds to me like there's some sort of trauma
That he is
Dealing with
Subway
Anything I can't do what it is but it seems like this
If this story is like
Not a
Not a lie. I'm trying to get something out of somebody
This is one of our classic
Project Camelot episodes where it's like
Something went down
Maybe make
Entirely possible
Convince the necessarily that is
Because he's not really like
There's a lack of emotion behind it there's not like he doesn't
Like really troubled by any of the stuff
Lytic is equally likely that he saw a bunch of
Movies the baby he was too young to see when he was a kid
Vivid dreams
He had some sort of like
Begotten
The drugs a little bit late
Riviera bad drip
Or something like that
Conspiracy
Any of these things are possible that would plant
Later to hear
Cramer's interview and be like
That explains everything
This mythology
G about himself dating back
When he was 10
Stuff is possible
Stuff like the guy in
Vietnam
Who was fighting beetle beings
That's a different animals in
Tamia still like we're cool
Possible
You're unfair to suggest
Possibility
But we have no idea of knowing
So
It still feels
Far more real his responses are
Because in between all of the Corn Flakes
Did the sense that I get from listen
You someone who actually
We asked like
What's the problem with this idea
Critique of my
My narrative
I was allergic to medication that's why I
I would like to know what
Other
Medication tickets
Medical history search
An allergy panel with me if you got
What's the weather
Scripture
All these damn spiders that look like humans
Keith what are jobs at the borders
Jordan
He was deeply involved
Control structure
The
Mars
German
Were in
Play
The Jason also had
F****** everywhere he has
The f******
Funniest take on this
His explanation for their speaker
German is so fun
How did you know they were Germans
Speak German
That's great question
I knew there were Germans because the other
Officers that I first
Counters at work from our Sherman
Self identify themselves
Farfegnugen
The German word for something that was reserved
Leadership
German military
Soldiers
Knew how to speak German than that was
What
Bay Resort
Which specifically so that they had it means
Communicate among their own citizen
Without others being able to determine what was that they were saying
But here's a problem with that
Germanism
It's really not hard
Germanic language
Could pick up fairly easily if you're not
Space
Like there's a high school
If you are these soldiers that are up there all of them were taken out of their beds at 10
Conceivably some of these people would just have to know German
German family
Super easy to
Pickup
Languages that are very closely connected to English
Now what they could do
Is a space like words
You know what
Female but I think it's you I think that's unreasonable
Q
Sweet Creek community Mars German
They hold strong
Sure
Maintaining a connection to the waterline
Sorry
Now what I would suggest that's true
But it was
You know you can invent a language
Like Esperanto
I don't remember any of it
To understand
I can't remember much of it
Much like these guys have memories of space
I have memories of being like a
The ten-year-old boys
Like speaking
Germans teacher do pigeons experiment
I would say that if your plan is to make it so that there's a language that no one else
Understand
There's a very easy way to do that
Make your own socket
Don't use German
Germany is
That is
A good
I take that as a good point
However I do think that it undermines their goal of using turmeric
Because like I said it's too easy
Key I don't
For real I mean I didn't get that they were doing it as anything other than like an
Exclusive
Think we're only the only the officers
Are allowed to communicate in German
Not because they don't want other people to understand so much but because
It gives them a sense of class
He said that the
If you learn German if you know German it gets turned off I don't know what that means
They turned off the positive what's going on with
There's f******
If someone's talking in German
Plenty of there's so many of those
30 Mars German
They don't respect their planning
Whatever I don't know
Sooner or later you're going to
I think their Authority goes too far and then they f*** it up this might be where they played the role of Icarus
Bluetooth close to be linguistics.
But getting further away from it
And Collective
So in the next
Jason talks about his time
Up there and
He said some things
Is that are like
Alex Jones
You claimed that you were going
Planet
Interstellar
Going to other civilization
Swaggin I'm not sure
Part of a
Seditionary
Force
That would be
Innocent
Tortoise sounds like colonizing
Other planets
Giving offer
Bring our services
As a military
Deceptive layer in there
If you're using the word fall
Trying to say that we weren't really fighting for them
We're pulling the strings
We're also responsible for
The
Organization and The Invasion
Creating
Highbridge
To create
Dancewear
We were invited in
Is that way they create
The problem and the solution at
Christmas door
And you're able
Go to
Franchise
Please
Control mechanism out to other plan
Globalist
Damn the speaker what he's describing and
Spit it out rice
Get it out of your goddamn
He's describing exactly what Alex has the country
This is exactly the same
Storyline
But now we have
It's like Warcraft becoming Starcraft
Itsjusta6
Isn't so stupid
There's such a consistency in this because it does
Tap into one of those big fears
Especially among white people
But which is like
They're going to do it to us
You know like look at all the, all the colonial Isaac
We did exactly these fictional people
There's an underlying fear of like
Oh we got it,
Ghetto we just have to really hard to make sure it doesn't happen even though we deserve it
100%
Either these guys telling other do we on Earth run any kind of risk
Space.com
Did you start oven temp
Implied cooperation
Between our secret space program and the Mars
Billabong to get along
Whatever I'm just fascinated by how almost no matter what where you going
These disparate places
You think that they're talking about different things but
But you scratch
The surface a little bit
And you find the exact same ideology
Promoted
See Steve this guy who's trying to talk about his time
Super Soldier on mars or whatever
And he's just
Saying the same things
With different apps
Gives Alex Jones
You look at Jim Bakker you think he's a
Christian preacher Republican
Alright talking points about the migrant
Caravan
Stuff like that
You just like all of these worlds are so Blended together
With just different clothing
Which is
The sport of rhetoric that leads towards
It makes sense because they all hang out in like the same corner
Right
Individual had an interest in both
Christianity and Allergy
Boards and people
Just kept going for me
Play say that's true but don't do what they do is like all of these three worlds Beyond them being like basin
Call the car
Job
What they do their purpose
She would do this for years
Start s*** out
About space
Kind of amazing she still doesn't know
Twenty-something years on the radio hasn't proven one
Victory
He's against the global
2016 election
You got Jim Baker Hughes do not yelling
Right
Behind the scenes
And their actual effect on society
So dis
Trust
Like mainstream sources
Think what they do is they
You try and put a splitter into your brain
Eternal into your brain
Distrust of a shared reality
What they do is they trying to force
Encourage
To use their worldview to see the world as
Supposed to
The reality that we all share
And by doing that you week
Give me abilities
Society to work
So what is there really actually super
Super like profoundly damaging
Influences on the world and they're playing the same games
Just from different angles
That all these people should really
I mean caretaker prison
Weezer
I don't know what you do
They need to have some sort of
Absolutely the last you can prove anything you say
But if Carrie Chasity came to
To be tomorrow with a ripped
Hey Dan this is my friend Glee
Maybe like
I want to be thin
I'll be goddamn Carey
We'll do another Wacky Wednesday around like a guys
But there are his hands and they're in play maybe we should believe some of
I also approve anything I also think
Makes perfect sense that these worlds
Tail into the right because as
The right-wing has found objective reality to be their main enemy
Reality
Put some of that
It's difficult to say whether or not
The right-wing picked up that strategy
Lee from
Aldi store
The success that they have Within
If it's
You know they only gets
Stronger
It's no surprise that we see
Vu fervent
Conspiracy theory
Forethought
Write write each other down
You know they say pull each other down
Further
I don't know if we're going to
Large truth with anything other than just
Saying things what I strongly without well I think it's important
Like when these things
Come up to
Bee-Line Bus
News world
Be brought up because
It is
They support their all working to undermine shared reality
Like
That's fine if the shared reality is
Evil and wrong
But if it's not then
You are
That's my point
Bring that point up to people who believe that their reality is
Only makes them
Well that's why I don't
Exactly right
Hit the brick
Get out of here right across the aisle
No that's what we got to do
I told you that there was a clip that I found that I admit
When I was going over
I'm so glad
Is this made me
So f****** hot
I need you to put your bike.
This
Is Jason
Explaining how it all got started
This explanation is unlike
Anything I've ever heard on Project Camelot
It is
Lunacy
The drinkers were behind the scenes
Pulling the string
Because the original formation of IDOC
Who's back
The mark German
Original moon base
Lease
In order to least the proper
From the daycare you work and build their first name day
Couple of things
They had to
Troops to the Draco for you swear when they needed them
The IDOC fleets were
Find a note 10
Bound for the Bazooka Ball
SP program took over
Desmares Germans original Moon
So Jordan Avicii I know you followed that cuz of your laughter it turns out
This was a sublease situation that broke bad
Alright
How long was the original lease for ever
Otherwise why would you give
Why would you be willing to give up
Roots the seed that is not a standard part of a lease
Dude
That would make renting
Real weird if everytime needed to get out of your lease
You had to bring troops into it
Right right on the off-chance
Also I love the idea of like I'm looking for a new check it out with go
Around Chicago
Furnished Yu-Gi-Oh Android
Awesome
I love that so weird
We're living on the moon
Mars Germans are
German
Are working with the Draco
You at least in the movie Ghost
Is it a whole moon or is it just some part of them
It's just the moon base
The Big Bun base with the bars Germans had on the witch
Germans who are on the moon
Also another really funny part about this
Is like a
Tony said that he
To the Moon
So Carrie brings up
The stuff that
The guy with the telescope who works
To the bus station
Nope
Because of course the
Of course
How could you not assume
To the bus station with see if it was above ground
Camouflage
In some way
Where's the court
Programmed you to civil court
Unless you give me truth
End
We want to get out of this mood
What are they what are they going to do
Hey if you break this lease
We're going to murder ever
Why do you want to get out of the lease
Oh I mean
Have you ever been to the Moon
Pick Up Stix
Plastic up on the Windows look I have survived in a lot of bad
Chicago
You got if you're putting plastic up on the way to maybe start looking for a new place
Little bit
I always put up last
My Steve
I don't know man I think that if you were
Moon German
You might want to keep
Keep a foothold on the moon
Does it imply that they went to
They went to another Moonbase is that possible
They were tracked
Bedroom to a studio
What the f***
This baby so happy when I heard that I was like
How the f*** did I miss that
Cuz Jason voice is so f******
It's at least issue so let me explain how this
This whole thing start
So
It turns out the original
They were not yet Butera
They were on their way to becoming
Moon
Right
Could not read
They just trusted me Draco
You guys seem cool
We're German Nazi
If there's one thing I learned from the midterm elections
It's that there isn't
Controlling most places
Rent control
Do do do Drake
Keystone human
They probably pay them
Blood
Write monthly
What are moths like
Well we can find out what movements
We can't find out what Drake
Draco's don't use the Gregorian calendar
Allegedly from this interview they're based in Jupiter that's where they had commanded
I read so high
We're trying to avoid paying rent
Sure
So they sign a year lease
Sure but they don't understand
How long
Jupiter
How long how long
So they're like oh s*** we won't have to pay this
30 years right but everyone high-fives everybody doing great they realize they didn't save enough money to pay
So they're in a crunch
Right
Finally
Will break the lease will give you a ride
And then we'll get the SSP in here
Because if there's one thing I know
About space
They love
Fooling
American
A Jupiter year is 11.8
Earth
Watch long
Be like a year is a month
Tomorrow
I can see this
The other thing I really tickles me is Eid like
Is it okay
Abilities do the Draco have for up to
Like the door or whatever help door is faulty
Is there code is there like building codes on the moon what kind of Regulation
Is there a regulatory environment
Is there a renters Bill of Rights on the moon
It doesn't come up because they were able to reach
When they gave some
He's my favorite
This is me off.
A follow-up question
It carry
Do your whole show up in
Like I understand the idea that there's like
You know
War base
Space law
I'm willing to go with you that far
Crazy Tuna
Dig into that.
Pissed off
What kind of what kind of universe doesn't exist without civil law
That's a good question
I think that's assuming that
They're all tearing out a lot of democratic ideals
Interstellar
No matter what Mark Richards has ever brought to our lives
Whether it's Raptors love chocolate no kill a baby for it
Nothing to me top
Spacely
The best
F****** thing I've ever heard from one of these days.
Litigate
And I will watch the small country Phobos lawyer
I don't know about your business
How you guys
Have a thriving Entertainment District here on the moon
If your honor we would like to
Oh no
Space law
That I find
Proposed
But this made
This Paisley's there's nothing will ever be better than
Because it's such a boring
Love Jason rice if only for that
But here Tony comes in
With some other weird face laws
He might have been involved
Breaking
So can't have diarrhea the pool even in space
Doing something illegal
Where were they doing
We routinely stole
Cargo
From other
Colonies within the soul
He thinks he's on solo
There's a law that says
That all the colonies are not allowed to attack each other
When there were
We would steal
Man
I wasn't really prepared to think through every every infraction
There was bootleg things from Earth
That's one of the one of the
Hardest things that researchers have had with my testimony is that we used to listen to Earth music
We used to do
Cargo run
Diego Garcia military hardware
Or any kind of military cargo we want
Diego Garcia in the middle of the night
Only a few Personnel handful Personnel knew we were there
And we would take cargo
One of the officers gave a music player to
A girl in communication that she was able to sway
Music
Let me know and nobody believed
That's how I
The main cargo bay
Movie
What's wrong what's wrong
There's a law against it there's a login
Are the meteor from Earth as
I guess
Mind-control signals in it
Able to listen to one song at a time like at the end of the day
On the way back to the base
He would listen to one song
But
Is it happen
Hardcore researchers
From my from my testimony
Because it's so illegal it's an illegal thing to do out there to take it kind of works
Is interesting that you think that now
Interesting that you think that
Interesting that you think
If you feel that way about some
Something I said
First music is illegal in space
Control messages
But they could listen to one song
Weather
Eastbound & Down
Is there a
Hi-Point
Convoy rubber duck
You're listening to something from the era of trucking songs
I got way worse
I went all the way back in the prohibition era.
Bringing space Hooch across
Rush
I would have play 2112 Overture
Cuz that's like
20 minutes login
Listen to Frog Rock up in space
Prog rock in space
That's a good that's a good point
As you're driving around in
Email I would want to go with something with a space time signature
I want to go with like
Let's see how it goes space-age Bachelor
I would go with
Honestly what I would end up doing is probably try to
And piss off the people I'm in space with
The Duke of Earl
Stop saying dukedom band stop it
No ma'am
I love that there's there is
Real estate law in
Yep
Camp bootleg
Repressive
What's so restricted
No movie
But that does imply that there's
Space music
Music
By the way
Technology is actually all hooskerdoo
That's all hooskerdoo in March Germany Wagner
Like
Choices
All you can listen
Is every cover of the spake zarathustra
Very meticulous
Opera
Jethro Tull
Baroque flute
I don't think anybody at the Grammys
He knows who this is
Comedian named Jason Earl folks
If you know him
Videos of Jethro Tull
If you look almost
Exactly like you on the University
Freaked out
Running around with a flute
Aquiline nose
Really annoy people
Kind of like what
I wonder why
Podcast about Alex Jones
High tolerance
Here we get to our last
We need space
That's what I said
I would love to
Run
Chris Pace office
Is untenable system
Space regulation
I want to be
Populist
Subspace
Deregulated the entire real estate market we are regulating
Music laws
Freedom of speech
The First Amendment
All right I wouldn't
Start with D regulator
I don't know if
I heard about that
I don't know about that. Be regulated real estate
That up there we'll get the super-rich off this economy of Mars is going to collapse
Honestly that name
Advocated for renters rights
So we reach our last clip here and
Tragedy
The Falls the broad
Oh no
Freestyle for a little bit tell me anything that we might have missed
Trouble strikes
Just for
You know 5 or 10 minutes
Whatever whatever you'd like
I can cover it
If you think we haven't
Dealt with it
Will carry first thing I'm reading the chat here and it looks like we're not online
My audience
Don't know what happened
Recording looking like it was recording
It's a mystery
S2 what happened
Broadcast
Invite you guys back
Maybe you can come back next week or
Estimation
Andres
Do it again
If you don't mind
Alright
Thank you really appreciate it
No idea what the hell is going on
Some things that are pretty far out there so I think
The course
There's a real given the way he said that was so boring
Like he's implying that there still are.
Draco's
Yeah
Interfered with by alien
Anyways
I guess we'll see you in
Here is my
Occam's razor answer
Surfer what happened
Carrie was super
Distracted by the idea of having two people on Skype so I won't
I forgot to hit
It f****** record
That's what happened
Beginning of the episode
Omnifarious that the video didn't record but she has the audio up
I thought you would still found this anyways like maybe wasn't
Streaming recorded the audio
But the video she was
Recording through YouTube
Chew streaming it live on YouTube and recording it that way not
Through like the way we do it through a recording software has a bad process
That she follows
And she
Look she's done a lot of shows sure but that doesn't mean that you didn't forget to hit
Record once it happen
We've done a couple shows where we lost a couple shows those are not usually in
Resume not hitting
Crazy
Not a couple of instances where I had like
Almost
No space remaining on my computer
Because I just
Didn't know how to
Erase temporary files
Five minutes of an episode
Who issues do happen especially when you're kind of dumb like me or Carrie
Cheeseburger
Hit record
Going on
She's trying to log on.
She's trying to record
She's trying to scream
Think about a second album
Google
Look
She's hasn't announced
Thanksgiving about
I'm thinking about it
I'm hoping for
Look
Here's the deal
What to do
It's up sodas
I'm suddenly
Wondering about
I know I need a lease
Myself
Haha
Is your girlfriend
Possible
Trip
Oh yeah
She has kids
I would say that
In the Obama
Deception stuff
It's really hard to
When you get a call
This is so like
I'm not going to say that I recharged my batteries cuz that would be
Deeply dishonest man I needed something like that
Mcfucking weirdos talking about space Germans and
Yeah yeah
That last two hours almost that much
Better that the episode ends with
I forgot.
Somebody needed to of Ashish
I know she would have liked
But she should have added
Price is Right
Slide whistle
Congratulations Gary you have proved everything
I have such a weird relationship
Project Camelot
Replumb the dab
Swift like Eddie page
I'm surprised
Legitimately thought that
Project Camelot was going to be like
But we're going to do a couple of fun episodes maybe of Mark Richards shows up again will do another one of those but I
Legit
In the same way that we're done with Jim Bakker
How do you spell largely emotionally done with it
More than
Yes people.
No it turns out every now and again
Just f*** around
Disappeared
For twenty years into space
Illuminati sex slaves and majors and
Secret space program
Because
Dispute
This is so great like this is
Got to love it I love it all of the Project Camelot
Everybody seems like they
I've always
I've been trying to out
Dudum cell
Do you make it as grounded as possible
Is absolutely the one who came in with teaming with fleas
You still on that tip
It's the
You know
Like how did the space believe live we've had Mark Richards he's flying around
Solving problems that old is just like a regular
Sex slave Joel elevated himself
To become basically Han Solo
Dark trap
Eventually owns her own brothel every single motherfuker who comes on here who's in space
This is the equivalent of someone who's like
It sucks
Lake duck knowing
Like man I had a rough go of it
I was just like
Shoveling s***
Eat like three Hots and a
Ducati scrambler
Yes
Because they're all making it up
And there's soap
Victor's ego by
Like groundedness
There is
Minutiae of Modern Life
Is day-to-day life that is now being mirrored
Pictures of really good improviser
Do they'll go for jokes you'll go for like big
The grand
Broadcast
Corks of
Stuff that you understand and relate to others in specificity exactly
Understand
So
Anyway congratulations
Jason rice
Tony
Space Germans for getting out of that lease that was tough to do
Congratulation
You're stuck in that lease
When I lived like when my house burned down
Years back
Terrible landlord
And apartment
Completely destroyed so like it was condemned
By the fire department
So they let us out
And that was the case with a number
How many troops did you have
But there were a bunch of other
Unit in the building that weren't that damaged
Expensive like smoke damage or water damage
For one day
Firefighter's prayer
Yep.
But they refused to let the p
People out of the lease because
The fire department didn't
You say you had to
She said
Stuck in their leases in
Slightly
We destroyed apartment
It was horrible like I remember learning about that
That kind of behavior
That's what I would expect out of the Broncos
Congratulations
Let's slippers
Look
Maybe the Draco as a species
Are better people
Draco run
Nazis in the hollow Earth there are not good
They are very
Burberry
You're you're on this
Creeping moral relativism
Moral relativism
The f*** out of here with that
Hey Daniela my backyard mister mister
Involved in an interplanetary
Dispute
That's the cowardice
Cowardice cowardice that allows Injustice elsewhere to return
Intervene in World War II
European
Space Mountain
Spaceventure
Thank you for project at least common with something
Open Project Camelot
Myspace was with flickering in
There's still some
They're still gassy
We do have a web
Technology
From the Moon
As long as you smuggling computer
Although although internet
Including that way
We have to get our have to get
You have to get Comcast service is shity but
Salad all the time
But RCN is it plugged in
No not at all
Space regulation
I am running
Also we got to coming up next week we are not going to have enough
Because
To get all my ducks in a
As it were
But next week
All week
Everyday
Throughout the week
Ruby new episode
Of Art
Exhaustive
An extensive breakdown of Alex
Is very stupid documentary The Obama Deception
So thank you to all our donors who have supported us and
An enviable position
Thank you all
You were getting what you want
I like the way you put that
You said to do this
We could have got a different documentary but it was voted on
In our Facebook group go home and tell your mother
That you're brilliant
Fight tonight
Not bad
Very tired
That's true
The score fight
That is true
Describe download
Good stuff
We would appreciate it help
I don't believe that Mars
Killed anybody
In their career
Find a drop because we don't exist
Probably
Comply
It's like saying
Freddy Krueger
Is killed people
He doesn't
Exist okay
You're too
Goddamn Mars German
They haven't killed anybody by Burger
Like they don't exist
Is preamp
Technically
And that's Alexander Everett
Alexandra Thurston color