Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We're couple of dudes who likes
To sit around and drink
Red wine
Specifically red wine
Picture because Alex Jones
The character of a man who cares about anybody else
Weirdo
As we always do an event
Enter through Alex Jones Infowars
I'm a guy who listens to a ton of Infowars
It Alex Jones in particular
Listen to any
That's why I mean
I've got to find all the eclipse
And then we can
We are both a little bit unhealthy at the moment
Buckeye said I haven't been sick in like a year
And now I have a pretty bad sore throat
My life
If there was ever proved for the globalist
I think we might have been poisoned polonium
Also I'm not sure but I believe since we recorded last Rogers
Claiming that he was
T-boned in hit-and-run
Second attempt on his life
Okay
Sketchy details
About
This hit-and-run situation
The other car
Whether or not it exists there is one there is also an issue of
The police report being filed like
An hour and a half
Disturbia
I was supposed to have taken place
Usually
I don't know I don't know
You know is that I don't believe Rodger
I'm not sure I believe him on this
Anyway
Really
Made of Polonia
See now this is an interest
Is where we go
That way we get just kill two birds
1 Stones everything's
Alright alright
We had a good run
After that pun it's time for us to go to an out-of-context drop license
Drunken Soldier
Pumpkin world
I am anti shrunken
I am smart them
Led Zeppelin haven't talked about
Might as well it's a woodland creature.
That was it
Just give some contacts that he was
Lena Jolie
Does he cares about
Is in the middle of a long rant about how I
Your daddy
What you probably really a shame to you
We got to bring in your dad
It's not like the most
Insulting
Or inappropriate thing in the world
Especially in the movie Anaconda
The president
We have
We got a website going
It's at knowledge.com I know We've joked about this in the past
But it's real now
You can go there I have a doctor
Document ated
I've documented
Alex Jones
Past lives
The archive will build
Grow from there
Starting
Living biography of Alex find pieces of his life
Which is going to be the best
Little Snippets of Alex Jones telling his life story
Episodes
Trinket discussions going with
I want to try and build in a discussion
Chambord
I've some point but that's
I don't have the time
Go in
Comments on episode
We could argue about stuff I'd love it
Betty White
Could be episode
Today
For mostly dealing with Friday March 7th
Okay
F***** up stuff that happens on that show
Of course
But first I wanted to play
Uclips
From the 6
From March
60 + Thursday
Because you said a couple of things
They were really stupid
There was one
Then there's a call in the
Is it needs to be discussed
I meant he says something that proves why word
So that's why I
He says we don't have enough to do during
Is what he says
Exactly.
I got a few more clips of President I want to go to it and it's only right epic species, Road
No they're not want to dress up for a second
Yeah I pulled up I pulled up a collection
Current polls
On Sunday
And most current numbers
Show a if you if you average
12 of the most
Recent polls
His net approval is -2
6.6
The Gallup poll has his net approval at -21
37% approval rating 58 disapproval
The highest
That we have in the last
Women all these polls are basically up from March till
Beginning of March still current
The highest is a Rasmussen report
From the 14
Study was done
S48
Approval rating is
That's unconscious
That is -4
Percent of this
That's wild
What are you do not have
If you are a few are a Hermit living behind a giant
Rock that closes up York Avenue only get out
Once every four years
To vote for the
Your approval rating of him is going to be
If you're alive
Let's call it a human being
With consciousness
There's no way you can read any day of the news
And be like
Oh you doing a great job you can if you don't believe the news
He's doing even if you support this whole Muslim ban in like there's no way you can look at that
And be like he's doing a good job
This bad thing he wants to do he's doing a bad job of setting up
To do you have to admit he's terrible at
I totally agree
Even worse the only people from the month
March that has him with net favored abilities
Is the USA Today poll
Come on now on every front page
2 + 3
Favorability
But still
Only 47% of
God so
Again
Crazy
He's only been president for two months
Doesn't this feel like he's been president for our entire lives because everything changed
How long is this guy going to be
Much longer now but anyway
What numbers are going up up up
Uncontrollable
55 56
Perfect
Devastated
There's no way there's no way to really know what possible way you can real numbers are 74
Yeah
Unbelievably untrue
Just based on
There's no way that's
I don't think there's ever been a president
Once in American history
Well if you don't going to win 97%
Boy anyway
Our sources didn't
Sources in Bloomsburg
Numbers
Weirder
Fair enough
That's the real upper-class billionaires have secret numbers
Secret numbers that we don't know but I kind of agree with him there
The Billionaire's have secret everything that we do
Casually drop in like
You know I know a lot of billionaires no big deal I know people who have access to the billionaire
Sources apparently couldn't
Sure
He's got people close to billionaires interns at Google the baby that he knows that call him on his telephone
He hasn't turned it billionaire
So he would get to the next clip I'm going to cut one where he misrepresents what happened when the party
We flipped in the sea
How could you not
It's pointless to go over but here
The phone call
From from a rapper
Is it Riff Raff
It's not riffraff
Should be Riff Raff so right not anyone famous
But
Alex
Response to this
Is amazing
Play for Maryland
MTV Snoop Dogg thing
33 now
Awesome
You name it
He says you named it when he's like I can't come up with a lie
Literally the only rapper who I think would talk to Alex and get along with him is Vinny pazienza
AKA Ikon the verbal hologram is the the rapper in Jedi Mind Tricks
I feel like you're not
He's pretty talented but he also is a
Little bit of a conspiracy
There is also
Is that people a lot which is
He and Kanye West
Station right below that
Interesting conversation
Crustacean at the other purse
I mean like if you go through the history Alex Jones
5 degrees hated and loved Kanye
Depending on what
Most recently said about Trump
We all love them
He's a genius and his Mercurial and he's at 100%
This this call is great
Cuz it made me started off already and we
Still complaining about Snoop Dogg
Which
I'm not here to defend Snoop Dogg I don't care you're fighting a ghost
If
Actually
Do you think he would fight
Somebody
Alex
This is like
I think that one's about babe
You still there
The website we're going through every Tupac lyric
And see if we can
Vaguely apply something to l.a.
Alex Jones
Song For Mama those probably about
It's called
Gatto's on the Makaveli album
Great empowering
Now
I want to see a couple things
We've already drop we've already drop that we got a new a new track, hopefully the dog
Not going anywhere
Mel Alex
Is about to announce something he wants to
To do
Which would be
Crazy please
Please tell me
I'm talking to
Play music deal all the sudden
Patriotic country music hip-hop Rock everything is so good people submitted to us
Call
I want a whole hour long show everyday
Literally wants to win
The best
Hip hop hardcore stuff out there
But then deal with it
I need a few crew members on the funding to shut it off
Flower show everyday
With talk radio music
Replay everything
I just
I don't believe
Play Willie Nelson
Alex Jones
To play Willie Nelson's new track
Do this show.
That would be amazing
Also
It's in the hell you get anywhere near the legal rights to play any music on Infowars
What legal rights do need to play this guy's music was just some weirdo calling you
About
Play
Like mainstream
Country songs Bass
Amarillo by Morning
Going to make people have grudgingly allowed into
It's not going to make us money except for all these super male Vitality ads were going to
Has anybody got a funny operation
Leanne Wackadoo doesn't have time to do this
She's busy
Doing something
Tearing
And so
But believe me sir absolutely
Take her from you
Alex is claiming that you did that
He didn't
She's claiming that he has some responsibility for Joey Joy Villas
Success
He didn't
She came out
The Grammys in that make America great dress
After the fact our tether as a guest on the show now he's trying to rewrite history that we feature her
And tons of record sales
And because of it we can watch careers
Meanwhile it's a couple weeks later I haven't heard
Yeah what is this
Start I don't know
Genre of music
How dare you
We're in this together
Uptogether
Where was that going
He said it doesn't matter what color we are we sink or swim together
Doesn't matter if we had problems we don't need to talk about this point
Alex Jones
Very much
Fix the sky is black
I looked him up
Kane glaze isn't black
Every rappers
That's why he's giving a message of racial Unity
Do everyone but
People who aren't
Explain my research
Enemies of Freedom worldwide or against Trump because he's real
Hypnotic
Mississippi Market
Fighting whatever you know we got to rebuild this phone to the thin crust bonus
Garbage out here on TV in the media and
This release is my first one even though they're rather size 15
Carvana linoleum stamp
Amanda
Blue envelope and put my album in there
Massanutten was handing it out just handing them out handing them out
Not charging nothing to try to get them
My YouTube name is Daffy Duck
Let me say that that
That's not otherwise known as Daffy Duck
That's not a good YouTube name it's very hard
It's a bad YouTuber
He wasn't first popular
The day I managed to find him though any guy with a big bushy beard without chopped
Without the Sideburn he looks really ridiculous
And on his YouTube Channel videos of himself rapping
In what appears to be like
A service truck that he drives
A living
And they're about 30 45 seconds
16 days after this episode
Nothing nothing
100 hits
Did you
Look it's hard to tell from like a 30-second clip offensively bad but it wasn't
So I don't know well
You know it
It's disappointing anytime
We can't add K Blaze to the list of the greatest rappers
About time
Pokemon that show to heaven
Believe it cable is not getting a return phone call
Let me tell you this
What are you going to tell me a blaze is a patriot
Keyblade
The Patriot on this episode on Thursday
16th and I want you to
I want to know that this endorsement
Is going to
Ring out in the years of the millennials
Okay around the country
We're going to find out somebody else
Is the Patriots secret Patriot
Oh yeah
Okay
You'll never guess
This is somebody
Who is universally respected
At the top of his game
Not someone who everyone hey
Oh okay
Alright
I mean you looking at
Sonic.
Borderlands
10 million cars
Surrounding
Is listening a goddamn info would you want to like really reach the kids and you want to be at
The tip of the spear you know you want to let them know
This guy who's seriously f***** up an icon of Ivar, degeneration
Is a patriot
Basically tried
To destroy as much as possible
This last clip is about Mark Dice
Is Asa
Patriot
Did not see that, I would never have guessed that I was going I was going to stick with the music.
Mark Dice is a guest
On this episode they've a little conversation about nothing
But before this
Alex
Have a conversation with you
I'm up
I really didn't my pep talk
And this I believe
Whenever anyone asked
Do you want to do this show why is knowledge fight something that they
Important
And why am I going crazy trying to quit
My therapist
Number one
Couple people at work but
This clip
Really spells out why I think it's important
We do this
And push back a little bit on the b*******
I told Paul 56 years ago you're going to do weekly videos you're going to come on you're going to Tweet or I'm going to cut your
Play Paul Weller
He said okay Alex
He's better than I am on it
What's your name
Marx's goes on a better place
Show
Alex is not doing National TV show
Mark
Mark Berman
You don't want them
Mark Dice
I'm not sure
Stick with me history I don't think is real but
I'm sort of complimenting and cutting out Paul Joseph Watson
It look
F****** do anything I don't tell you to do otherwise
Goddamn paying apps
Eye Center
You always have the videos in front of a giant
Heol Paul Joseph Watson
Does all of his videos
In front of a judge
Not American flag at the world flag
World map
Just talkin looking like
He's going to cry reaction going on with your eyes
But anyway here's where it gets where at
Really sums up my
My feeling on what the future holds if we're not
Ketchup
Awesome program
Money
Shut up
I need the best
Total transparency here
Keep in mind that
Wait
What did happen
Is he having
I like
Staffing discussion with himself on air right now
He's already so Mark is watching
This is Alex
Physically describes in his human resources report on Marco Polo review on air
Pause
You must come to the Mothership
I want you here
What's that slip
Why would you need
Time
You know what I mean I need someone with a real grasp of slander really knows the fine lines of libel
I like somebody who knows it
Exactly where the line is and then
Crossett
Without the government finally catching you I hope
People
Hi I just said this on there tonight
I need a reliable Sherpa
Play The Police
What he shouldn't be saying stuff like that on Harry climb the mountain
It makes
Parrot that like
His business
Just barely not getting sued
Imitation of the things you said
He wouldn't have to worry about getting sued
If it's the truth and he can prove it
That's not live or slander
I mean after the whole thing
Who knows
Whether or not
You can publish if someone s*******
Then we can talk about the
What's a public somebody s******** so bad bro man of Lake Appaloosa
B s******
Kind of want to publish his
Probably
Have Alex Jones the s*******
I don't want any part of this
Mothership
I want
Mothership Factory
And a Mothership
Mothership
Weapons platform
He just wants to 24
It's anybody's being there though if we really break it down is that
We need more media Empire filled with Liars
We need more products The Hub
Yeah you are really good
Does Mark Dice
Please, create another Mothership
This is the future if we
So when he says another Mothership do you think he's trying to
To turn the himself into a 24-hour
News
Well honey you should ask no
Talk about starting to go on are at 5 a.m. and going through 28
I just broadcasting live like on the internet from 5 a.m. to 8 p.m.
The too much news is breaking week There's we can't cover all this
BYU got 4 hours a day and you don't cover any
He just wants a jiggly infomercial to try and sell more exactly
He wants more time
Where you can possibly be drawing eyes to it
Sell these pills
It's not it's not like it's
I mean I don't know what would your overhead cut why why am I think
Thinking about his business strategy
It would only raise your over
Head cost
They probably 40%
I think that's a very smart business decision I think he races overhead a lot more than
Manpower's please Alex start broadcasting
Please
I would love it accelerate Beyond reasons
If you did it at 5 a.m. meet have like
The first three hours hosted by Paul Joseph Watson
London
Be that as it may seem to get to our are mainly
Speak of him broadcast
Open from 5 a.m. to 8
He's wearing away
The banner ad
At
Lee Banner ad on in Fort Worth this weekend
Has been Alex with his
Shirt off
So that's great
But
It's time not only
I've also
There's before and after pictures his chest just looks
That's really all the different like himself
I could use more test I couldn't
You couldn't know literally could not
Anyway
Stranded on a desert island
Covid-19 Chicago Animal Shelter
I was like how do you
Fix a radiator with Chester's this is really carefully
The could be
Redux Channel
We have had our amuse-bouche Leto as a patriot Jay Leno we had our app
Which was a lesson in why I think
Disorder shows in Port
The counter propaganda
That is going to
It's going to only get worse
For the foreseeable future
And now it's
Which is the
March 17th
Now I want to say clearly
A couple of these clips along
We're going to have to play them
I couldn't count them
There's no way to cut him
We're going to play them and we deposit any time
One of them is like 10 minutes long
The ones like
Which is under lock but he goes on
Tangents
That I need to have
Incontact
He wants to start off the show by talking about immigrants
And also make a little
B of A point about
Considers President Trump
Double-patty sounds refugees
Adam and by the judge
Islam Sharia law would be an unusual intervention
The elected president and Congress
Yeah thanks Breitbart you guys are always on the ball they're very impartial very
Journalism
What was he talking about
That a judge was going to order Trump to allow more refugees in
So he didn't
Well maybe it is maybe it's like a potential future
It's not like a we already have a commitment
To accept such and such number of residents a program to
Patriot such-and-such number of river like un guidelines
Depending on their economic ability and population
Executing all of his responsibilities
Anyway
The people
Whatever he
Spending all of our money
For his wife to hate him meanwhile Muhammad Ali
Khon2
This goes on and on and on
And
The judge is are now issuing executive order Psy.
It's not called an executive order when a judge does it it's called a
It's already a decision in a court case
Yeah generally they have something in front of them on their docket
Invade
Decide what the law says about it
Which is
Judicial branches for
No it's not
It's not
Now
There is zero possibility of no it's not even if you wanted to
And here's the craziest
You can't even compare it to an executive order because
Can't overturn it
Right
Of that
Other people
Unconstitutional
Yep
No checks
It isn't
Dictatorship
Did they
I don't know
You know what babe I'm scared
They have
Consistently
Push the narrative
Obama's a dictator
Obama doing all of this stuff
So for them to say that
Trump is being caught
Because
We don't have a dick
Realize that Obama
Was not inside
Sure
Save-A-Lot
As long as you
Obama is a dictator who got to
To do whatever he wanted
You get to assume that Trump gets
To do whatever he
Well it's like they called I like Preparatory rhetoric
Yeah it's this idea a bit like
Muslims poses
Threat to America's way of life
When people make that argument they aren't reflecting their reality
Currently
They're reflecting what they want to respond to later
Yeah I can see that you're Preparing People
Hozier
Meaning that there is no threat
No no maybe there will be
Brighton framing the discussion
And it's very very
Yes but it couldn't be an executive order anyway
Executive orders a reference
Executive branch
Judicial order
Wallace Rebellion
Tarzan goes there with the proper size picture
Shut up
Again
That's not how that
Snow.
That was how that worked and it didn't go well
Also that story in question with them not wanting to hang up
Put Trump picture at the VA
Bureaucracy
Should have to go in to decorate
Or something along those lines
Bureaucracy on decoration I kind of agree to but the idea that it was like we hate Trump
You can't put up his picture that's not what it was it was like
Is rigmarole
A spot where picture of a present
Supposed to go to bring the wrong size picture
I'm not saying that
Still do not care I don't care either but it's not what Alex Azar
Although if it was me I would want to go to agree with him for the wrong reasons
They already have one
Porsche open up your board is bringing 5 million
No I don't think
Create
Confused
Many say you're against people that are
A different
Fifty-year-old man has her six-year-old kids
That that that was you know I was always
Run the World
Voting is
Is so
Crazy cuz he's like
I don't I don't hate anybody for their sexuality but if you're up
Which kind of proves
He knows what he's talking about you like you're a beta and you wonder why your abandonment
School tells you you should be a woman
Watches Over Me
Of course
Of course they go to class
Have you ever been to work
No you haven't been to one of these class
These classes they tell you how to be a girl
Not if you're an alpha
Also
If he's right
The number of genders is exploding
Too fast look
I don't want to be I don't want to be anti multiplying
52 101-year
Guys
By next year they'll be ten million
See now that it's interesting that you say that
This sort of relates to what he's about to say Preparatory rhetoric what he's about to say
Not really but
Exponential growth of
Something alright
Bred 4S
The clip you said I have the
He's talking about that like
If you dump chemicals into a thing
Gay frogs
So that means
People are gay
Because of Pence
Got you
More
Gay frogs
I don't know.
Business
That's on me
I just want you to know for sure that
You've got a long as you keep that I've got to run once I'm 35
The number of each year in Sweden
Within only 15 years
They can't procreate Mission completed
Exponential growth curve
Wallace
Concur
Sexton stupid
Okay very great a lot of pink
I love Lana Del Rey
So
Here's with stupid about
He's quoting a Breitbart article
About
The rise of transgender identity
Right and there's no snow
There is nothing
There was a quote
From a doctor in Sweden
Sad without any statistics without anything to back it up
She just said
That each year the number double
There's nothing to back that up
Also
She said that in the last
Searcy scene 197 in
Who are trans
Way more than 197
Play for next year
We got one more year before sleep
There's literally
That's a percentage wise of so minuscule is less
More people are trans so much as more people
F****** comfortable enough most of the time it's people who are already identifying as we think
Hiding it
F****** killing themselves right right trying to not be what they are I believe if I if I work
It's just a correctly like it's on the rise in America as well but it's like 1% of the popular
It's very long might be called at 1%
Has to be at least at least like forty million probably rub
So that's
Almost nothing
So she didn't see everybody
So I mean
She's a doctor in one
Goodluck Stockholm
York
But like
There's no statistic
It's just
The quote that doesn't have anything to back it up
From somebody is using
Also there I did in my research I did find that there was an article
About how the trans population of America
Is double decker
In the last five year
Conflating those two nonsense
What was possible but that number doubling is only base
On a very unscientific
Convey guest
Estimate of about
Trans individuals in 2005
So that number that is hypothetically doubled
Is not
There's no evidence that's true and that's already a bulshit thing because it's still got that same that
That same ring of like
Previous length
The time in in the same way that
In Saudi Arabia there like
Yeah we don't have any
Tomorrow is population growth of 3%
We're overrun
Now let's take another lap around this b******* Christmas tree
I don't know why that came for my ring around the rosie
Shipt
Good luck Maple f*** the pool is the metal version of it
Symbolizes a tree
Bada-bing bada-boom Christmas tree
The other thing that Alex is f****** stupid about and if he had any understanding
Of these communities he talks about know is that
Not all trans people are operative not all of them
Have surgeries
To get sexual reassignment sir
Many of them are still
Able to have children
The idea that wants you are want to be
Become the other gender now you can't have kids
Is b*******
That's absolutely bulshit
Into that
Ariel
I know but again that's
Still validate that idea of something about having a womb
Qualifies you as a
Yes like that's what it always gets back to is not wrong
Are you a baby Factory
Is
Alex Jones
Woman are you a person
Are you a man with a big dick who can
Be all kind of alpha
Or are you a baby
And everybody who doesn't fit in
To those inappropriate
Procreate art
He's full of
Serious
Canary idea of reality
It's such a fuc
S*** this next clip we're going to go into is a string of Lies
One of them
Is
Really fun.
And the others
But the
We'll make it through
Phone
Double is the cheapest and most nutritious food in human history
So that's the introduction of the premise
That is another great isolated drop right there
Is a McDouble
So I want to have McDonald's to have that
On their f****** website
Tomorrow I would like to use Bisquick
As something of a case study
Then we will come back to later the episode of Alex Jones
Not knowing the stories that he's talking
So the introduction is that McDonald's
McDouble is the most nutritious
Cheapest food
Humanist
Is Amore meaning it's the cheapest food with the most
Nutrition in it
Should I redo the article
Of
Or fuschia
I don't want to read the
Basically it is a telegraph article
About
The co-author Freakonomics
Stephen Dubner
He
Debate on his blog after reader suggested at the
McDouble packs a better nutritional punch
Search for the penny van is often assumed
The double cheeseburger provides 390 calories
22 grams of protein
Happy birthday Lisa
7% of daily fiber 19th grams of fat
Half of your daily serving
Right
Christmas audio for the average person it isn't a great option
Take a trip to the farmers market to puzzle over esoteric left
Codes just weird
Where else but McDonald's can poor people obtain
So many calories per dollar
Now that's interesting
Really good question
This article goes on to break down the difference
Between like caloric intake
Price of junk Foods
They have it thrown in the face
The argument when
Thomas
A campaigning organic farmer
North Carolina
Subs nutrition
You can get a pound of organic brown rice in a pound of red lentils for about 1/3
1 lb 30
A serving of each of these things would be around 48
So basically saying that you could have red lentils and rice
Yeah also
Right
So basically this article
Not to jump on the whole like
You know what nobody wants to hear
If you're if you're
Going for like hey I just want to
You know you could get a half of a
You can get all the brown rice
You want to eat for half
Yeah well I
I didn't get that
Goddamn reason
Red lentils
The premise
Right
Is that a reference I don't care music
Very close
This article starts with the headline
McDonald's McDouble is the most
Hypothetically
But it has
Just got those what the premise
The article is I'm by the end
Explains that there are comprable other
Things that you can eat
Could have about
The same nutritional value
What articles
Do you mean the
Point out information
Generally you could use
Is Jamaica in French
You don't get the information
If you just read the headline
You don't get any of that information
It's much like
It's much like the McDouble
And that you get a lot of empty
Tea calories
I was going to say it's like eating these
10 of an orange
You're not getting why you're supposed to
Eating the skin of a five-year-old boy who is taught to think he's
So Alex
I have not read this article
But
He's mad about it
Any talks about it
For quite a while
Spends it into something
Conspiracy theories
Alex hasn't Reddit very mad about
Press release put out
It's the cheapest
Most nutritious food in human history
He did not
Eyeglass a folks
Don't
Press secretary
The longest-running
Is it a bomb
Bombas running press secretary
Mr. Gibbs
Mister
Francis comeback
Was an accident
Know someone somewhere
Did that isn't McDonald's
Article he's thinking this is a press release from McDonald's
Discussion that was led by the co-author Freakonomics
From McDonalds because this guy who used to work for Obama is now
PR at McDonald's
Holyshit
Let's let's bring Obama into this
Let's bring this whole thing in
It's crazy
Now watch
He's off on this
For quite a while and then eventually
Cuz he's an idiot
Are you just ramble
But then
He starts to read the article
And I think
He realizes everything I've just said is wrong
Gmail
Confused look but it wasn't it wasn't as the words coming out of his mouth
There's been other times that it's been more obvious.
But this one was just like
Bass
Enjoy this
Dumb
Thank God they're so dumb and MSNBC last with him
Mister
Don't criticize him because New York
Google
These aren't true things he's just headlines from like
Zerohedge
Right
Johnson
Don't get bogged down in 8
Elsa gets back to McDonald's
By the way
The Muggles get mad
Got to go in
With or without Muslims we can't drink on the
In America we can't have open
Do you know when that law came into effect
Or maybe it was some drunk assholes through like a bottle at a car
Muslims
And you drink beer on the street
Find yourself
Muslims
Cuz it's so easy
Yep
15 years ago
Ridiculous
I'm saying that now
How long till we get to realize
Never be afraid of it for 9 on my entire life now
Absolutely
Henry is right around the corner more of a boogeyman than Obama
For Soros
Barack Hussein Obama Leah his daughter Rides Again
Islam
Control those areas
We've got millions of
So we're not saying that
So he's mad
Coupland
Yeah he's mad at Earl
But I mean like professors
Piece of s***
But they ought to
Still denying that much like Rogers code for polonium poisoning
Probably but
Types of salad
If you can get away with that move that's a solid moves you're not a krasic dictator movie
They have millions of people per European city
You're going to move you're in
Entire population
Kiss people
And
He's not saying that
Yeah that's right
We got bogged down in the reality of Matt's
To the fact that nobody has said any of
I promised it says compact
I forgot once
We got under turkey
Still in North Korea is also going to come out
Islamic domination
Thought
Turkey
I wonder if that has anything to do with the people in power
Sing
Holy war language
I wonder if that's
I wonder if it has anything to do with Bannon
To the president literally saying he foresees a holy war between Christianity and Islam
Bird wants nothing
But
If he was
We're playing
And we should not be doing that
Do a lot of holy war Reddit
Using that holy war rhetoric
United
No that's true
Which is the best Family Guy bird is the cheapest and most nutritious food in human history
Google
In the middle of him
Telling a fake story about Robert Gibb
Being behind
This McDonald's story in the telegraph
He's complaining that people think he's fake news
This is
Insane Through the Looking-Glass
Don't make sense to me
Everything you've heard me say for 39 minutes
Most of it from their own mouths
0 of what
He said the opposite currently
Was
Obama Trump and Saturday McDonald's
Who's the chief medications officer
Nutritious food
He's not it's the guy from Freakonomics
At the guy from Freakonomics headed discussion on his website
Would you know if you read the article
Would you purchase crazy
Is Wister give been anywhere near this
His fingerprints are nowhere near any any of this
Reached for comment in the article
Play glad
Is the McDouble
McDonald's double cheeseburger
What's the cheapest most nutritious and Bountiful
Also
The best comedy ever is probably the original Ghostbusters
Not this
I think it's the one with the women
Capicola
Will not rot
Under blocks
Handsome man
Flowers
Kim Jong-un
17 different
Yo in North Korea
North Korea do that
Do you know what's crazy
Do you remember what happened on the day of Trumps inauguration
I don't when it was raining and then the sun came out
They said that it was him
Is Providence
It was God smiling down I'm not going to lie to you here at
But
Alex
You're busted
Where is badazz North Korean propaganda
He doesn't even have any clue
Father
Sheets this is ridiculous
Official
So is he
Is he doing the voice of the North Korean news agency people
McDouble being the nutritious playing that liberals believe all this stuff about
North Korea
Kim Jeong Hoon
Which is not
Anybody
But
Believe half of that show their forced
They're beaten if they don't cry when the Kim Jong-il die
Well they're also be
If they speaking
Anytime
Effeminate British Butler I kind of wish we all spoke
This would be much more interesting podcast of somebody you.
To use this
Voice
Kill myself honestly with my sore throat I don't do nothing I want to f****** die
Talk like
He's going to get right back
Of course
Under Obamacare to bring that in
Nailed it you got it
That wasn't unfortunate
That was an unfortunate thing
Obama said
So turned out not to be true
Lion
The year the liberal Outlets
Vrv
Mainstream Outlets all have also
I believe I believe that
He intended for that
Be the case
He couldn't
Do it
And everybody was like
I imagine
Animal might be fantasy booking his
History but I imagine in a situation where you wasn't up against such a
Very
Strong opposition that threatened to shut down the government over his the health-care bill
I imagine he would have
Got them and you can keep your doctor
Peace to the bill
Maybe that's not true who knows
The more important point is
Re-litigate the past on that one cuz
Scant months ago that we should probably go after
You can keep your own doctor toy
Timer
He says
We're about to hit a lightning rod
Out of Lies
So the next one
Pause
What is isolate that
The building it says that Obamacare
They said Obamacare was going to be free
No one ever said that
They did say if there would be tax credit
It's that would help you
And eventually it would
Necessarily pay for itself but it would
Fuel Expo pay for itself in terms of government
So there's the other one
Did the Obama saying that you didn't build your business you super super mad about that
Obama's trying to make him that speeches that we all live in
Communities
And you didn't individually build your business
You did it within the network
And the framework of
The community you live in
Or even if you did build your business like legitimately from
The ground up you built
The building
You built all of this
You got your clients did you build the roads
Did you Corey the rocks that you built the building with
School that you went to the Taj a build all of it
You build the hospital when you broke your goddamn leg
Did you build the neighborhood that provides you with Gus
Parents
Right
Pointe Ranier like
You didn't build your business but the reality of it
Is what he saying is
The everything
Framework
That's like saying
So Alex Belcher business
2 + 2 equals 5 is the next lie
Of course that is classic Orwell
Very much Obama to
If you
Sometimes two plus two does equal five
I don't want to get into geometry
It's about to get wild I'll give you
I'll give you a very basic example this comes up in like Taxation and accounting
A lot of times you have to round thing
If the round things to the nearest
Brian Austin X
But often times that you can leave a penny
Play Penny's anymore
So if you have something that's like
2.49
You double it
That's rounded to
The two cents
When you're adding it up so it's $0.02
$0.02 and what you'll end up with
The 2.49
Jiggles 4.98
Around that up to five you now have an
What's $0.02 +
Tucson sequels 5
Is that
We should have ballast
I agree with that
Stupid
We've been having for
I understand the point of making it slightly pedantic
What is string theory
Basic arithmetic
But yes there are other in San
Located where
The numbers take on differ
But just in that in the case of rounding
Often 2 + 210 equal 5
Alex Jones
You
Telegraph
The biggest load of horse manure
One of their most recent tweets is the Shamrock Shake
McDonald's in Austin
Emma told me that
Horse manure
Manure
Horse winner obviously more nutritious
Double is the cheapest I'm reading and most nutritious food in human history
The terrible British
The cheapest
Might seem sensible giant colossal
Might seem
But according to the author of Freakonomics
Injection is a
At this point I think Alex realizes that his whole narrative
Confirming that maybe they're just saying
You might be
Surprised
Copaxone amazing caloric punch Pernod
But
I think at this point he realizes he's about to
He's about to jump ship
He's about to dismount
That's right
This is a grown up
Because he read that Freakonomics doesn't say what I've just been saying for the last 10 minutes
Does
Pretty well if he was I was dreaming
Like instead of like it's like in
Whatever the whatever the gymnast falls off the balance beam
They still get up and do the thing with their arms out
But he still doing
He still didn't he committed to it
Still performing the man knows what he's doing
So embarrassing
Yeah that's that's
The Arc of that clip is
McDonald's I don't read this article but I'm going to tee off on it I'm going to claim that it's some Obama guy who's the
Behind it
I'm going to other fake stories
About Muslims invading countries
I'm going to
We've Obamacare and Obama lying about
Also
Also North Korea that all liberals believe North Korean propaganda
I'm going to actually get around to reading the article OSHA
Hero's journey Joseph Campbell
Volume
But then here's what's great about it
So that
Quip ended with
Let's get on to something more
Ridiculous this next clip is going to start with him saying that
Just so I can illustrate that all of that
Lead to this
Alright
Is yet another one of our little adventures
Down Alex Jones's bulshit history know it's personal history or is Imagination of what the
The real history
I think the ladder
I don't believe it
But I'm certain
That there is an element of the story
Does not know
And he doesn't know that
Story
100 years on air
I believe
Based on
Based based on how repetitive you I guarantee you stole it more than 100 times
Though I have never heard
Toothbrush for me
Because it happened about a year
I just reset there because this is such a big deal
What about
And I'm staying a small apartment
More about that story was together
Where they had to say for their bedroom or whatever but
Now we know where the
Alex is the worst at being discreet is the worst at telling stories
Isaac
There's nuclear weapon
But I'll tell you this
Obamacare
You want me to tell you that
Aggression problem
Well-known newspapers
So
Recap so far
Yeah if you want to steal his parents safe just know that when you go in
You can already grab Alex's guns to do so they're in the bedroom to bring your own guns
Make sure that you walk in empty-handed this is my situation
You can walk in there
But to be fair you need a time machine
His back when he was in junior
I mean who knows
You don't want to keep guns in
Junior college dorm
Support him on that
And so I go and I come out
Rifle
And a Percocet
And he's all the way through the living room in the den
And I want yes
And my dad goes pee it come on Alex coming
I don't sense
My mom works in the major newspaper
Since I was born
Today I'm haven't seen Bobby 67 years
Walking out
Sideload
No big deal
These freaking I will not answer
It's fine I could see Eileen
Really whatever friends with them again
So now
I don't believe that story at all there's something else going on and I don't know what it was
Alex there's something
There's something in the dynamic between the two couples
There's some
Straining their friendship that already existed
There's no way that some squeamish liberal be freaked out
Not a chance
That does that does illustrate something about gun people that they just
Which is that
Don't
Bring a gun
Well I don't I'm not I'm not going to
Whatever Alex Jones is make
But I don't want a gun in my face
Right.
Simple to me that is something that would make me angry if
You act like if I come into this
To record this
And you just haven't been around
I'm not going to feel okay with that
And then if you come up to me and the publicity
Your p**** don't look
It's not loaded
It's not loaded right now
Play kygo
Tumi
.
Then it's your right to think that
But then I also think I would put a strain on our relationship
I think there's another thing.
Not going to be couples therapy therapy
They charge extra but it's worth it
Here's the thing I think that gun people also don't realize that people who don't like guns
Really aren't that
For the most part
They just
Recognized
The danger
That's there and they don't want to be in
That's really what I mean like I don't want guns around.
I understand that a lot of people can use them
Responsibly
I just don't want to have a lot of my good friends
A grown-up in Missouri had gun
But I think a lot of very liberal people understand
Responsible gun ownership
Is possible
Prevalent
Junction
I mean what we would ever want
Realistic
Speaker
Could be a lot worse. Now the flip side of that is also liberals understand
Statistics
And a lot of times no matter how careful you are asking
So it's best just
For our money
We don't want me around it cuz
What's like a baby accidentally shooting another baby
Two things do happen
Are murderers
Yeah how weird is that it was in there cold baby hearts
How do you raise a child
That has
Accident how do you raise a baby
I don't know
When it was
You know like
CR7
Is your seven got a parent statue down in the living room and they say
No way no way
You're freaking me out
No it's not that
Okay
Oh my God you're a murderer
You killed your brother
Your ears all the time
You take to the Grave that's like you notes that's like you're a right babe
Pallet child
I know that everyone
It feels like all information is important
Everyone to have no it's not
If you accidentally killed someone else as a baby
You can't tell that baby that
You can't tell that baby
Somehow in your scrapbook
Inopportune picture to take
Like you remember how we're getting so far off track the point
Childbirth videos that somehow happen where they live
And then just a baby covered up with a gutter
We shot it on
We shoved it up there in the third trimester
Handy with the steel
To get back to Alex
Pic of baby murder
Yeah
He does not understand something about this story
I'm not sure what it is
I'm sorry I can't
I can't dispute
What are you saying except to say I
It doesn't melt
Correlation there is no cause
At this point he pulled out a gun
He does not actually pull out a gun
He pulled out a gun
What a f****** idiot are there for about 15 minutes
Because he's always pulling guns out and about 15 minutes throughout this
This makes 15 minutes he's like putting the laser scope at the camera
Shining Light On
But
F******
He uses this as we're about to see the as the rest of the squid plays at
He uses
To discuss the story about Sean Hannity
Pointing a gun at 1 William
We can address after this clip is done
So we can hear Alex's take on it and then
I am 20 years
What do I tell you the story because
Pelosi press conference
Bush is present
Again
Flip it and you're making
Hey
While The Sun Shines on that
That wasn't one of few weeks ago there's one even worse Maxine Waters again things
Russia invaded Korea
Same clip package you've been hitting on for a month now it's
Stale
The new ones she's obviously has dementia
She's out of her mind
Giggling like an insane person
That is liberals are domesticated
Really
Most of us are not
And
Tough guys
Incompetent Foster just hard working class middle class people big dicks
Big dicks
I would like
To posit
Something
I want to go back to that abuse thing
Yes I would argue
That a lot of people were abused
Not generally liberals
Okay talking about it there okay being open about
Trauma
In their past
Because they understand that it doesn't make them any less
Of a man or a woman
Things that were done to them
When they were powerless
Which is something I say all the time all the time
Because the damage scary to see somebody aggressive and confident I just love being around the Veterans Affairs
It's the complete opposite
Of the people that are friends with Juan Williams
99 Restaurant
Barry Fey
A gun
The truth is that the the story of that's being recorded in the blood people are
Shocked about is the
Sean Hannity
Pointed a gun at
Pulled the gun on
Even if a gun is unloaded you're never supposed to point of conversations we have about responsible gun
Responsible gun ownership
James Brown
Because even if
It could accidentally go off
There could be loaded even if it appears unloaded there could be something in the chamber or something
It's entirely possible
That something f*****-up could happen
And that's why the number one rule is always Point guns at
EXO
Go to the person the story is like
What
Stop
What's the second word
Aggressive is the part we don't like is great
Type of aggressive
Embarrassed
The only time I like aggressive when it is when
High School football
Hear those cheerleaders
Spelling it out
Aggressive
Fbe aggressive
Burdock root
Sure. Cheerleaders
I just felt
The point is
Like Alex
Woody's harping on is that these new stories were saying
That want Williams had a gun pulled on him after an argument
Ever someone is reporting that that's on Friday
Story was just that they were talking and then somehow
And of course the one Williams he was fine with it
Crazy Town
That's just bananas
If you want to be fine with it that's fine on the internet
Is that
When he said he was fine with it somebody was pointing a gun at her
Sure it turns into the Deep Space 9 mm video
Reference for you
Cool
Cool run the jewels fan
You and that references too late
Company flow referee
The point is
People don't
And when you do
Expect you should be criticized
I think of that
Expect somebody to at least be like
Hey
Don't do that
So this next clip I'm going to play we're not going to actually deal with it at all
Because I died I don't care to
But at the end during the show he had an interview for an hour with a guy named Larry's
Johnson
CIA
The XVI a guy
That's at least a
Is egress
Absolutely she's Larry Johnson she is not Grandma Ma
Butler Johnson from the Charlotte Hornets
He did not appear on Family Matters
But here is Alex Jones's intro
To I when he's about to bring him on
Know-it-all orders board winning
A crisis management
I'm so much more he also ran
Into Kuwait
And that'll situation on the time to go over there while I'm asleep
You don't have time to go over all of it
So I will
That on your credit
I will go over all of them
Failure of mine
Larry Johnson
Is notable
Because he went on RT
The Russian
State News Network
Give an interview where he was talking about how
People that he knows within the CIA were ordered
To Target Trump
Which is based on hearsay get no
Kind of
Maybe Trump is his Source through some
Weird Ouroboros
Love Lies
So
Made these claims
And then
Andrew Napolitano
Father Judge and Fox News
Guy
He went
Fox News
And repeated
Essentially
That
Larry Johnson
Like a piece of it but it was basically that the thrust of the
Is that the British intelligence agency
Gchq
Had been one spying and there's a quid-pro-quo thing going
We spy on the British and the British spy on us and then we trade information
Nobody's happy about
No
We're spying on everybody
Yeah let me get through this
I want to fully discredit
So I was the source for napolatanos claims that he made on Fox News
The conspiracy theory was later asserted as fact by present
Trump with him sighting Fox News and Napolitano
The British intelligence agency in question
Gchq responded stating that the claims were
Nonsense utterly ridiculous and should be ignored
Fox News later just about the statement by Napolitano
Trump has had to apologize to British intelligence
Well
Exactly
Because
It doesn't because here's the other
The reports are that
Trump had to have
Spicer do that but
He has basically said to his death
We want to keep pushing that narrative
We just don't want it to be
Trump still want that to be the thing that people talk about
Rather than the fact that
He's made up Bowl
And he's using his
The distraction
From the fact that
He's full of s***
He's doing s*** let's not get distracted
Larry Johnson
Because I could just be a thing where he's like you know I got the I got the s*** wrong
Alright fine
Would never ever ever
According to the New York Times best known for spreading a hoax
In 2008 that Michelle Obama
In 2008,
His blog No Quarter USA often criticized Obama's qualifications to be president
On May 16th
John supposed entitled will Throw Momma from the Train
Which alleged that a tape exists of Michelle Obama
Rallying against White
Jeremiah Wright's Church
Johnson claimed that Republicans were in for
Possession of
It's being held
The fall
It's being held for the fall to drop at the appropriate time
In a subsequent post
Johnson claims
When she was on a panel with Louis Farrakhan
He also explained that he himself had not seen the tape
But it's
Who have spoken directly with people who
Where on what
Real bad work
Hopefully
The smears website denied the rumors saying No Such Thing exists
Michelle Obama has not spoken from the pulpit that has never used that word
Which word
Waiting
White
Cheap used that word
I use that word every
Rachel 1301
Cracker goofing around I would love I would
Would love Michelle even more if you want on TV was like
I am sick of all these honkies talkingshit about
I would love her for
I would love her for that to the story
Yes please
No tapers ever released nor has any other evidence Michelle Obama using the word
On October 21st 2008 Johnson said that according to the McCain campaign
Progressive
Convenience
Yessir
It really it really would have torpedoed
That is bad
That's a big
That's a big line right now
This one's worse
In 2013
Larry
Falsely accused
Oh no he's at his people
I am a legend
Do support his claim audio clips from a 1971 debate on the Dick Cavett Show
Terry and John O'Neill
The original interview audio was altered
The piece together words
The Kerry spoke as if he
He said
For pleasure
What
When the falsehood was exposed by a reader of Johnson
The article without apology
You
What I did
Bulshit
Show
When you talk about fake news that's what it is
Didn't we can't prove or even do I think that
He did The Cutting and pasting but you fell
For this obvious hoax
Video
Yeah that he clearly make up the
Stuff about Michelle Obama
Way worse
For the stuff you said about John Kerry
Like that 228 literally accuse someone of war crimes
And raping Vietnamese women for pleasure
Abomination
Perhaps
Worst acts of defamation one person
Absolutely
Preclude you from ever being lied to
People shows
What do you make prognosticating statement
Alex has one for a f****** hour
Great
I'm sure he's got wonderful things that we loved
Yeah we do
We don't need to hear it
Anyway this
It goes on from there.
Look at him
The arrogance the fake confidence
Folks you think movie
North
They are Force
The North Korean people
Force
If you don't
Yeah you want to go to a labor camp
Adult
You better think he's a rockstar
Right
And I don't like the idea that he's making the argument first of all the people are choosing
To do this is the
Only possible outcome of socialism
That's bizarre
But be that as it may
Very inappropriately weaves it into our American
Just deserted movies
I don't think that's why we were superstitious this is pathetic
Any lizards anything in archery everything's Banette
I love that everything's going to Ethan North Korea
It's again back to that house bill Wildlife at all
Baron nightmarish hellscape with no food it's like the book The Road
This country that he references
Just like that
We references on a past episode he was talking about how in Venezuela's everyone's
Eating all the zoo animals
Research into that
Actually after the truth on that before we recorded
But the reality is
I do too much
But the reality is that there's one city where they had repeated break-in
But it wasn't like a widespread everywhere around the country everyone's animals it was just
Clearly one group
In the city
Kept breaking in in like stealing a
That was what's going on
Granted their situation is bad
No matter no matter what happens
If you say somebody broke
Into his due to eat animals I am
Just imagining somebody like Wylie Coyote with
With f******
Saliva dripping from them outgoing
The wave
The way this story made it sound
It sounded like they broke in they found a horse
And then they barbecued it
Riverwalk
Zebra with the phones at Worldstar Worldstar
You know what
That's that's
Premier living in the first world life where I really have
Llamas
Lemmings
And lemurs
I have run out of lions
I know all of my zoo animal start with L
Forgiving is one of the greatest
All time
It's a monkey
To the listeners
Santa Monica
That's the thing with Thor able to swing by
Limb from limb
Tree branches
Monkeys are they able to do that
It's something that only eight
Play the given is
Is a monkey that is a
Able to do it which is
Really cool anyway this is another
Another new segment of ours
Cuz this next worth is
This is a clip
Where Alex Jones
Explain
What is going to happen in North Korea Ono know she is really
Really out of shape
About that rotten General but also
Low blow I think that mites like cold that I've got going on I was making me a little weird
I'm a little off this episode iPhone
If you're a little bit on the bush League Baseball
Punchy
But
This is he's just getting done talked about how North Korea is got2b
Taken care of and
Rex Tillerson is
Is f****** awesome
Recognizes that
Now I'm going
This is a bit of a longer clip but we got to let it play for a little while
Before we interrupted
Cuz he's going to get into a nightmare
Scenario
If Rex
Tillerson
Was in
It's a wonderful
God we would all do
Just watch him die
Probably
When is the banker that
It is the worst
Garbage human
History tell you how this will go to the military
Three different ways and
Really try to crystallize in the best I can
They start loading
What appears to be an atomic payload
They've got sensors in space that can scan
Radioactive
On one of those
Missiles
And
The phone calls we got a President Trump who's got the mediator by attacking him constantly about
What was leftist insoles out kind of China
Call Tamara nextbot
We got the stands there loading
With atomic payload
Maybe it's a
He doesn't know the difference
Hydrogen bomb
Doesn't know the difference
President makes the decision they've already had the meetings and
Launch
And then it'll be
Line
North Korea
Spelling on the size of the bombs are or
Small
To wipe out the tunnel
Basis
And then they'll start dropping the 500 Megaton bomb song
Thousand nuclear weapon
Most of Russia
Reverse engineer plus I have all the sources over the years
But again is him saying I'll just making
I'm reverse-engineer this
Because
Maybe a Bad Thing could happen
Never distract the president pointing out he's a liar
Well though
He would be distract
Cuz you guys are all about this
Watched all those underage girls
Or he's a rapist
How many times do you rape people
Don't point out that because what if North Korea does a thing
A little curious always doing
I swear to God I will
This is going
I'm not saying they're not a threat but I do I do think that this
First of all
J / 0 fantasy
Play it's it's very scary and I don't think anyone wants this out
It really sounds like
What he does
He wants because but if it's something
Another notch on his belt of I told you
Sure anytime a thing like that
Yourself
I still think
This is going to be the same like
Twenty years from now when we all have webbed
Feet and hands
For saying this Korea is
I think they're silly
And I think
Without
Without China providing them food and
Their dad
But that's why they're also pointed to China
Alright alright
Alex
Wait wait wait for expansion
Have they met
The movie War Games
I think I was totally fine with
Drone
They did not
Where the DU schabo rounds or basically meteor gun
Doubt they're not Atomic they're not they're not hydrogen bombs or Tommy bumps
They gun parts
All the classified nature
Orbitz
Rock Crusher
When I get there you're dead
No holds
Mountain Crest High School
You do a mile under
Nobody Shake
Huge weapons platform
Japanese amateur astronomers are always showing him floating bases
Space Station
Military bases
Big platform
With particle beams
Like in the movie The Avengers
Every few seconds
That works
He's describing like Star Wars
None of that makes any sense even possible in 1979
It's all I could remember whenever we spent billions
$2 not making
Space-age
Gun bullets
Yeah but it would be traveling
Very very fast
Going to be hard to Target anything's
Okay
Let's start with the theory of relativity
Alright it's going to be sent
Different discs
The difference between
Traveling in a different
Rate of time then the other ship
If you think you're actually going to hit anything with
Any accuracy in Ephraim a made-up gun in
States in 1979
Your f******
Ridiculous even now it's
It's dubious 79
Special
No stupid go through the rest of this where Alex
Light goes on
Threatened
The Chinese
Great great glad glad to know he's ours.
Under the BB guns
Missiles are in come out of Russian
I'll come out of China
That Russia cruise missiles
If North Korea moves
Pacific Ocean in the Gulf of Mexico
City Center's population
He's describing essentially the worst tragedy that could ever
Befall the world
He's describing once the population dying
Tomorrow is describing
War crimes is that
If North Korea does
Anyting
All of China
A billion people will die
All the city centers
All of them
Civilian
Hold on
I'm sorry
Okay good
Chinese leaders make jokes about how
And by the way
WonderWorks of China
No Doubt
Noah
No we don't
Because here's why
We're not going to sit here while you launch missiles first
No
Not even a little bit
Calling for One World Government
Krazy Connie's
So we got it
Kill Everybody
So that was one of the three scenarios that he's playing
Total total human destruction
The end of all human life is one of the scenarios
To be thrilled about that
The auto Bible
Survival
Sure get those ones
Your desk get the survival pack
You will make it through a nuclear winter
You got all the freeze-dried food I could possibly need and also now
You be very horny what with
Destruction of all human beings are enough to get it up and repopulate the human race
What's up Superman Vitality food
Feel porosis at Indianola
Bone pills
Here's the visitors
Scenarios
Could actually
And
Easter me did
Horrible family
Stolen loot
Stabilize the country
China combats off now
Yes
And understand that
You're not going to get
And Chinese understand that traitors inside
Nope shows how crazy this whole thing is
Satellites
That
No idea what's going on
Or how huge the secret space program as
And all the stuff that's been going on for a long time
Just look the United States and Europe
It's still frustrating kind of jerk off
Is that
Disgust
I've ever looked into how do you even say
We're not going to let you start a nuclear war cuz we're going to strike first
We're going to start a nuclear war
Again
People who could be helped by humans
Not okay no none of that is okay
Even makes any sense
Murdered
Immediately
Even if we agreed that the Chinese government
Was our enemy agreed with that
Which we do
The idea of
Killing
People
Is disgust
Play that clip through because it's not
We're not taking that out of context he's not
He's not saying no
He's not saying something that like
He's openly advocating the murder of
Billions of the most likely scenario
We're absolutely not
It's horrifying
It is something of a teachable situation now for the American people
Citgo
Like
You shouldn't attack us
Because our president and our
Yeah
Do you know how we've treated so many other countries
Because their government is insane we're like oh well that's fine if we killed our people there people are the end
Hopefully we will become
We're all going to rightfully be like everything
Oh I don't want that it's exactly like
It's exactly like
Is look at the point of view of somebody being invaded
Wouldn't you be on their side isn't it all about you being like sheep
These f****** invading us are bad
Yeah don't think about that
Maybe when you're invading somebody
You're the bad guy
You consider that
Maybe you're the bad guy bad guy
What are the bad guy a while back but we could pretend not now we are one hundred percent the bag
Agreed
I've ever looked into these
Secret space program that Alex was talking about
I highly recommend
It's not even a regular space
I would love for us to if people donate to
To the show and s*** I would love for us to do like a bonus episode
About bike project
Never heard of them
King Arthur Galahad
Guinevere the whole shebang this is lady who does like interviews with people who claim
To have
Contact
You like that
If you like anyone's name except for this guy named Andrew basiago
Cuz that's the name but then also because he claims that when he was younger he was in the
The secret program that
Involve time travel
In Stargate
And when he was younger he time traveled with
Barack Obama
There's all that
Discover Secret
And then we'll find out that it's a lot like that where that lady married at
He also claims that he has like
He's like a half dolphin Warriors
Exactly no.
Disprove I can't prove that like
I know Jeanette
I know that Alex thinks he has better sources
But he doesn't
These are the people who come forward
Say like I was part of the secret space program we have time travel
Technology if you listening
Project Camelot interviews people for like
2 hours
Because they are
So
What's the word
Onboard
Do fatalities bizarre obviously not
True stories
Know what there's no grilling going on
The stories
Sometimes yeah I think I believe
You know
That's Festival
What's what's the
Between
You need help
And
You actually
Time traveled with
Will the edges that didn't happen
Help thing is
If people didn't believe
Based on
Clearly insane peep
Word that there was a program that involved
In space
Same time traveling
Would you like that
If you didn't believe them
Then they wouldn't eat
Moosehead like his fun fantasy if they were living that's fine maybe it's not the most gratifying
Winding up in a mental and
Institution
Is having a syndicated
Or being allowed on a
Slightly popular alien base YouTube channel
This latest episode goes on
We have another long clip coming up but 2in meantime we were couple of short clips insulting
Angela Merkel
I just returned the Traders and I'll get them up
Colonize Europe of Muslims in Turkey says
If you don't submit merkel's
Allied with the Muslim stuff
What a pathetic scumbag
None of that's true love true Merkel is very much not that
Here's another clip
That might be an
Lincoln Russian sovereignty and American sovereignty
Fairy
Drudgereport.com
Prisonplanet.com
I mean he really shouldn't do that right
Literally is a tough word there
What up Rick
What April
Unbelievable
F******
Also
Markel space I don't know if there's anything more indicative of
Of how we view Trump
Merkel's face video is
So
God comfortable
F****** four-year-old
Crying like a little b****
The f****** press
And Margo both being like you want to have a handshake
I mean
Now I'm doing funny Alex Jones
Him being Trump
In that Trump is a giant
The face that she made are those picture
Cuz you see if the face you made once Trump said
You were wiretapped by Obama I guess that's
Something we have in common
With that face
Your rage
And hatred
Even I know you're a f****** liar about that
You're lying
I'm here standing next to
Giving you some sort of
Platform for
Forest because the office
To stand here
A winner
He could do such a reputable. Emage
There are standing in the world
Treehouse
Most of us voted for that
Call Vision
Good point
A very up not even a plurality voted for that fox
Because the weird rules
Now we have him
We have one
Extremely long clip we've got to go
Okay I'll try not to shout it
To skip one of these clips
It's about how I laptop was stolen
Secret Service Car blueprints for the Trump Tower
Alex Pretend This is Obama's
Of course
The false flag
He's like I got to go inside job on this one
I looked into it and it turns out that every
Computer is deeply into
Cryptid so no one can get any information
And
And every laptop that is owned by the temperatures every
Device that is open
Can be wiped
Remotely
So if it is something that is in hand with a k
Take it back they've already why
I think they're the Secret Service they have contingency plan
Hey bro yeah so that's a non-story
Whoever stole it doesn't have the blueprints to Trump Tower
And not aggressive
I like it when those two things go together
To the strong offense
Why do you stare at me
The clip is
Just fun
We already know that
The conclusion of it
But it is just
And how biased
Is about Trump
And it hurts me
Him to compromise or something just doesn't do it
IMDb a rapist
And it doesn't shake merkel's better
Doughboy
Bubbly
That's kind of the games 100% respect 100% I personally expect
My leader to recognize that we live within a world
In a world with differing
Opinions
Either we don't have control of other cultural ideas
And that we have to find a way to live together there are cultural compromises
The need to be made
Kantime
Four things that you're okay with tolerances
Tolerate
So like
Whenever whatever you talk about tolerating North Korea
Angelica I'm against Kim Jong
Before
I'm fine tolerating it as it situation wasn't halfway okay with Ken
And that's
Just cuz it's closed
Yeah
Yeah I bet like the best
Tolerating
Is it like I'm against this thing
I accepted as a place in the world
We're not able to really
Solve the situation
Without
The nuclear war that Alex
Describe
On the prefer.
So we tolerate the situation as it is now
Until such a time a better opportunity arises
Fix
Compromises about
Placated Scituate
People mad
The Iran deal
The nuclear Iran
Where do I go
Is there money
It makes
It makes so much sense
Perfect
Encapsulation of
Here's the bad thing
Here's another bad thing
Here's another
Here's a good thing
Can't do that one either we're trying not to do all the bad
Here's what we're going to do
The best
Possible thing that we
Can
To get the best
Possible outcome
That we know of
Yeah
The thing about those outcomes
Two people then
Is
Is regularly thought of
Is how the law of energy
Is not
Bad
In those situations like
Alright
The unintended consequences of that
Deal
I really negligee
Right
There's the fear from
Awesome the the fear from the right
In the United States of life
Whatever it is a sin
Yeah they're barking and they're going to destroy Israel
Spalon like
Holy war coming to kill us but
But overall it's just everybody on the most part has been like
It's probably good
Is probably okay
And nobody's gone crazy
Go too far in either direction in that deal
Everybody
Fuct
Each side legitimately get with their primary goal is
We get
Array
You can't have nukes
We got that
They wanted
The ability to create sustainable and
Powerful energy
Money that we stole from them back
And they got those things
It's kind of like a prisoner's dilemma
Situation solved everything
If you want to look at through the prism of Game Theory
Like maybe that's a negative one outcome
Right
Probably
Plus one plus one out
Listen
Here's the argument I want to make
I think it's possible to - 1 - 1 out come
If you look at it through the prism of people who
Like
They're running
Who what
This is the negative one outcome for that
Just hear me out with them
I don't want them to have any cake
Or they just want us
To impose our will on them to not
Right that's still a negative one outcome for them
Now the reality is
One of the other outcome
Is out-and-out
War MSI - 20 outcome for both of
So negative a pretzel
Critical
But it's a super preferable
Scenario people don't realize that sometimes a slight loss is a huge win
When we talked about this North Korea s***
Here's to be as what I'm saying
It's the same thing with putting up with North Korea
It sucks
The people there are living in the terrible conditions they are
We should never turn a blind eye to the
That we should never
Make that okay
But
The outcome
Of us fighting with them
Is way worse
It is way way worse
To Kim Jeong Hoon
Kim Jong-il as well before he died
Had no,
Talks about the idea of killing his uncle
So
They would not even with Siri
The problem and Siri absolutely
Political situation
North Korea but because they're not such a preferable pronunciation
Eritrea
Because they're not f****** at least they're not protected by China
Nobody f****** gives
Do all the stuff
Yeah
What we focus our energy on itworks
Everybody
Trying their best except for people who work for and with
Like they're doing everything possible to screw everybody
We got to get to this last for
This last clip
As long as
But it's
It's worth it cuz f***
This to me
Is a roller coaster ride
That I could
I was at 1.20 that
Teacher College course about what's going on
I guarantee I could be
College course
About this clip
What should I cook
Are we going to
I couldn't I couldn't but I can sum it up in one
Directions to
You want it you want to put them on the board
Is this worth in in Guthrie
I get three
3 Strikes
Just cuz I don't like
Anyway this clips
With Alex
Still mad about Alec Baldwin
You still mad about that and
Complaining
Then he gets interrupted by one of his producers
And Chaos ensues interrupted
Angela
It's a madhouse
Okay great
They're just all of the comments sections going
Why does Alex Jones think blacks are humans
NSYNC
Watch your Superior
Because Alec Baldwin
By the way when he was last complaining about Saturday Night Live he was like they have a million viewers
Because he wants to play the victim
Of course
Well whenever it's
Whenever it snows
PeopleSoft
Whenever I'm the victim
People think that that doesn't count
Dumb people
I told Donald Trump
And I did not
We all know
Do people believe it
Something like that
I wouldn't get up on air
They paid me on all that money
Serial rapist
He just comes up with his own line
He's very clearly
I think I might have cut right at the wrong time
Hold on
Hey Alex This is Nico popping in on are we were just giving him with a New York Times writer
Progenitor
We have the New York Times
January 20th on Inauguration when they said wiretap in the headline
Plus it's admitting
Wow next level at I just
Are flashlight apps used against Trump
This story is from the night
But
But what
So
The producer comes on and he says
The New York Times
Just saying that
Infowars
Progenitor
Of the
The idea
Yes
Tweeted all that stuff
But they were saying that
We're going to get you going to play it
And do some of his
Trademark media criticism
But right now it's next level because
That the New York Times
What he knows is
The truth
He's so dumb that he thinks he's being gassy
Like he doesn't understand like earlier this is why I wanted to make a big point of that
McDonald's
You didn't read the article
Course he just read the headline in
I'm teed off on
He didn't know what the context was
He thought it was Obama's old guy game
Mr. Gibbs
Then he just created
Entirely false narrative about the story when he started reading it on air he realized
This is a situation where
There is a headline
On the March
January 19th
Issue of New York Times
This goes back that far
There was
Play it out
And try and figure out the
The case and then I will come in like Hercule Poirot
Do that
Belgium is proud
I don't know if I'm
For the main hubs go through for the USA anyone
We always use American
Share the data that's how we get around to show call log
So at this point he's talking about the idea that the British spy on us and we spy on the British that quid-pro-quo thing we were
Talked about earlier
Is not true
In this particular instance
I mean
You do with the soda
Revelations there the idea like
Vnsa is not allowed to Spider-Man
What they are allowed to do is
Spy on
Foreign Communications
And because sometimes those do come to Messick Lee
They use that is like their gray area too dense
You're already to nuance
Good point
Already
The reason I paused it was I wanted to point out that he's talking about this like
Spying
Leica all that came out I was telling you that 20 years ago
I didn't I didn't
Cut anything
This is exactly what he says
Next
Has nothing
To do with what
SmartPay
Super high
Small ring around my route
Machine gun
Missiles are coming
Hopkins patient preparing to
You just sit there with those men
He's got nothing to say about the actual intelligence
Stuff what
Talking about exactly he's gone back to these space BB
Because he hasn't
Nothing of this article but he doesn't know
In his heart
What is head
What the article was actually even about so he
Can't discuss it
What what is even talking about
Do you just desperately grabbing for whatever piece of information was fresh in his mind
Yeah because he was talking about the North Korea stuff earlier all of this was revealed
1990 whatever
All this stuff or not found in there
Matter at hand
Rat desperately waiting for one of these dudes just talking to his hearing
That's 100
What's going on
It doesn't lose any of his fortune and
That wasn't my opinion
That's a fact because
George Lopez everywhere else that job
At that point someone had talked into his ear
Is like okay I've got a couple more detail to what's going on
And that he gets it from us
World
Listen
We do a show where we were now it over 2 hours
Was talking about Alex Jones
And all of this
Has been like
So I don't need
I don't need to make stuff up to
Discredit you
You are just a liar
The all this is wise
Every single person you have as a guest on your show
The only thing that's true
So far
Is this
Keyblade
Probably with no proof it's not digital
No no he is giving it out to people he's the guy on the street going up next
That's fine good on cable
It's soaked but also let's be super fair to Alex North Korea isn't cool
North Liberty
Hazel mixed in with the untrue Things Are
That we should nuke them
Anyway
Things are nuclear destruction
He saw the bunch of other b******* and then he gets
To this clip
Our gets back
To really spend those wheels for a while they tried a lie
In the information
And then now we're back with the legit
Media criticism
Some of the CNN clip
The producer got in his hearing was talking about
Call this segment media criticism when you can't read
North Korea threaten the new Pandora
It's that
Trump
Has apologized
They just said look okay with her steps
So this is big
Intercept
This is his big gotcha moment
Is that like
Do it supposed to be different
Said the wrong word
I'm lying
At my f******
Airplane games of semantics
Everything's fine
What you can't deny what three up
The reason it wasn't more successful is that when people
Poured over the Vault 7 stuff
Who was only ideas
Some techniques that could be used there was no evidence that they actually did use them most of the things that were the most salacious
Things like your TV is spying on you also
Included
That you needed to put a USB stick
Into the computer in order to use as a spy device
You saw it
Rolex
Do I have Showtime is that what's going on I recognize that I'm quoting John Oliver but I did also look at
Confirm this is unplugged
Oh s*** that's the way to get around that
No so they
So
If it weren't for you damn kids
Alex is so sad about this guy who he wants called Hillary's butt plug
Being his vault 7 release not being effective
Because there wasn't allowed in
Information in there that really matter
No there was no smoking gun
There was no proof that anything actually happened there was just
I work around
Right up but
It's not that big a deal
Lot of it was already published
A lot of this stuff
Seems like
It seemed like a lot of what was lead
Is the same thing if you were
Comedy writer
And you are in the writers room for for like a show like
If you leaked all of their writers notes yutzy's a bunch of s***
Well that's
Terrible joke
That's the whole thing like
It's just a bunch of guys in a writers room throwing s*** at the wall hoping for the best
Weather
Papago
Thousand thousands of pages
Admissions of how they're sabotaging
Appliances
Tracking listening and watching us
Underlust they listed all his calls with foreign governments
If it's just
Sphere
And say the present was being listened to
Really getting intimidating
Trump
The rest of the ministration
You ain't a crook son
You just a shook one
Mobb Deep motherfukers
Boys club on a few people the country needs to grow testicles
Frozen testicles
3rd person
This latest Fiasco got launched
And I pulled up washing post La time
Intercept we got the surveillance
Transcription
Bunch of trump
Months later they don't release it they go
Times again
Intercepts
At this point he's
Splashing up this New York Times headline
Two I can invest
Navigation of trump
Even the headline
Has nothing to do with Trump being wired
Has everything to do with
Specifically
Carter page
Paul manafort
And Rodgers.
Those guys
Now if you read the actual article that
Attached to that headline
I can't imagine why
Specifically lays out this
We have no indication that this has anything to do with Trump
Also even in the article to be superfair they say
There's no indication that this has anything to do with the Trump campaign
They just say that these communications between
These Trump
Surrogate
Had been intercepted
They don't say
Probably through
Yep probably
Threw interceptions
Of
Foreign
Legitimate looks like
You can't get a bicycle
You can't get them to sign off on a warrant unless
The person in question
Is suspected of being a foreigner
Well Anna Gunn
That
Like
Paper wallpaper
Since the fisa court has been
So the fact that they said that
A multiple warrants were denied through the fire
The court should be the biggest
Like
Oh maybe there's nothing
It's because the fisa court is a rubber stamp Court
Those denials probably amount
Total of
The 10 total Visa is denied
Impossible for the fisa court to
Deny something
That it had two of either been something that
Should be hidden
For that had
Alright but then agree after to denials that also
Only something there is well because if the third one was just as flimsy
And they would have had jumped
Does easy time
Saying no
The third time obviously there was something
It is
I love it when Alex Jones live
And this is his belligerent ass
Don't want to have a show
They don't want
If the facts
Is Armani
That's why we are now an enemy number
It is not weather
No and
It's just again
Look back at that McDonald's story when he's complaining about the Evelyn thing these fake news while lying about a story he's talking about
This is just such
Juicy
Like
It just that that's why they hate me cuz I have a memory
4 things that aren't true
It's like I remember all this b******* I said
You're teasing this too much we got to get into this man I got it I got to hear this b*******
MCI officer
And one of the richest man in America
These operators and Cooper I just want to be clear he interned at the
The CIA has not one of the richest
Vanderbilt
No f****** way you stupid at least a hundred million dollars
Other people need work
One thing it's Admiral
About him
I think is that
He could have
Just done that and instead he had a calling
To do something else
So he
Wait
Ya know those Mark Wahlberg he hosted the celebrity male
Alright
Now I'm back on this side of the world
Waging War against America
Myself and my family
You makeup
The White House
And more of a
You know what eating grin he used to look on that New York
Whoops whoops
Also
Effeminate
He's got to be CIA
Arrogant
Herobrine look
Real
And I would
He looks fine
I don't know
Wake me up purse
I'm Yul Brynner and I'm playing the part of Cairo
New film coming out by Cecil B DeMille
He's doing this because the guy
Is bald
They just launched into Yul Brynner impression
That's it that's all that's going on here
And it goes on
For quite a while
Enjoy
Charlton Heston
And whatever you do
Don't smoke
I'm your brother
W2
Country
Who is this ding dong
Weirdos they dug up come on
Pansy around Anderson Cooper
The White House fighting your article
As part of the oven
I mean
Rodeo
So again
Just let's let's marinate them
I wanted to wait until the end to really explain
It was full of s***
But I think it might be more fun
We've got a lot more specific
Like this guy wrote the article in the New York
He's a writer
And he's going on
And the reason that he's discussing this
Is
His possession
Which I happen to agree with a hunter
Is that
You wrote this article
About how there were intercept
Related to Trump AIDS
Again manafort
Pavestone
These
Trump has cited that article repeatedly an interview
And in those three
As evidence that Obama
Wanted to wiretap
Tower
Did not happen.
100% of any one of those words
And then apply them
None of them are true
Can you use the fact that the New York Times use the word wiretap in there
As evidence
That that's what he was talking about
Goes back to Alec not reading
Stories
The only reads the headlines
Scams
So mad that he knows what's going on
Know what the article a
Actually says
If you read it it would have said
This might not have anything to do with Trump himself
It might not have anything to do with the
Alternate universe where would we live in if Alex Jones actual
Thoughtful Alex Jones
Will it be a better world would be a better world
Take his place there's always going to have you considered that The Wheel of Time
Yeah
We were testing
Come to fight forever me and Alex Jones the destined to fight forever
Ben Alex Jones are basically like Sami Zayn and Kevin Owens that's a wrestling reference for a minor
Sam's
But the point is
This guy Alex doesn't let him really
To the point we can
Get this out
But his argument is that
We wrote this story
And then right-wing blogs
Picked it up
The president reference
It as evidence
Without
Engaging with what
The story actually
Which is the hundred percent
And it's Alex's Emma
So he actually says Infowars
Which is what sets Alex off
On a f****** tizzy but
His argument is right
This Matt Rosen
He's totally right
That is what happened
They wrote this article
Infowars wrote an article
Lying about what their article
Go said
Trump responded to that
And then now we're here
Yes
And that's where you went wrong
Absolutely
I realize there were
But now that we know the
The full picture
Let's enjoy just
Marinating and Alex being
So sure he's right
When if you watch this
Instagram clip
Roof adhesive
Let's Dance
Weave
We have the cover of the newspaper
We have it all you have the interception record
No you are
What are the
Democratic Party
I don't want to take you down Alex like the closest people
Do you know how little they want to take you down
Emily no one listens we have 100 lives right here.
We are probably
Sincere opposition to Alec
The Democratic party does not give a f*** about you bro
Does not
Care
Hate so much more
Yeah
Yeah it's it's
Stories
Soros if George Soros gave a f*** about you he would be paying my rent
Oh yeah
My man
So goddamn
That's a cool song protesters
We Are One
Salsa with I'm Sorry by pause at the wrong time
Democratic Party
Not celebrity Bowl
Doesn't have mold
Moles in the Democratic Party
Patriots
Like in the in the DNC
Yeah I guess so
Hey bro
Also likes
Tell me about what
Thinking you know what I'm saying
University
I'm totally fitting in
On his lapel he's got a mic
You like marijuana don't you
Because I will show you
Lex Luthor
Do you think you interrupt
Do you want to keep account or do or should I
I think it's on you
You makeup
The White House
As part of the evidence
Weave
I want to show like 30-40 articles
Russian contacts
Again
Probably just talkin about misrepresenting headlines
430 article
And
Based on what we know what he thinks the news is
It could include Breitbart
Or Zero Hedge
Or any of these other way
Outlet
So yeah go ahead Alex
You can put 30 article together doesn't mean anything
None of those articles are
They don't
Follow journalistic
Which is the disappointment of network self
He can put together 30 article
Really bummed
Together
I was putting together
The last episode and we were talking about that
Iowa
Basketball team
Is racial slurs Michelle Obama said
The kids were forced to apologize
I want that was the story
Yes one of the things I did was I
2 tons
Of conserve
Live blogs
Ran with the
Story and it was a
Give me how many
There was no I had to Notting
Include all of them
Yeah it was like
On the front page of Google it was
The blogs
Really
Dumb kids
Unpatriotic to wear
American flag colors
With our knowledge
The Cambridge
Analytical
Great question
I would have the
The same
Google search
You have those because you're at work
Which is interesting like what
So so their whole thing is that
They can
Looking at like by analyzing the number of
That you like on
How many searches and all that
Like what
They think of you
With your researching
The insanity likes only Orange
It's just
Cambridge analytica must look at you and be like
A lot of pornography
Which is the same thing listen to Boz Scaggs
Avril Lavigne
Lana Del Rey
Write confusing a lot of old Steely Dan
Yeah they've got to be I'm a riddle too
This kid is depressed
The catch Russian just last year
They were on the news
Thousand
The thing is it get exhausting when you're lying
You know
This isn't that hard for me
I'm just saying that
Made me think like we're if Infowars
Was honest
Like all the things that he says he's doing is basically what you do
Take spoken word poetry about.
You can't have a play-by-play with color
You're doing the job that Alex Jones says he's
And
Weirdly enough
Turn
He's not doing that job
He has millions of dollars
I have 925
I have
Rat with reality shirt
Coronavirus
Three months
It's not that but
Only president for so long I've forgotten my own
Restart the show before the inauguration
Feels like 7,000
I know it does but
My parents don't believe the Earth has been around as long as I feel like
Totally
But look that the reality is he's complaining about we don't have enough human intelligence
Qmap
We don't have enough weed eater we need more help
We need more help to get all this stuff cuz there's so many lies
It's like
I can do this on my I can bat you down on my own
I don't need a team all I need is my friend over here laughing
And bring it over wine sometimes yet
And I was just having a good time
Uno
Listen
Hey
That was not throwing shade
That was not
The one that's obsessed
It's pathetic
An operation
Worth millions of dollars with
Can't f****** get his s*** together to know what he's talking about
When the information is all right in front of him
Apathetic
It means you like
Keep going back
It is within his self-interest
To not tell the
Yes
But at the same time
He seemed so convinced of the lies that he's
Just a weird like
What are those
Coincidences of
Knixwear
Somehow we have a man
Who's naked ignorant
Somehow
Coincides
With his naked selfie
Well you know how one of the features of
Schizophrenia is often you can hold
Belief that can't logic
I'm not saying that actions
I'm not I'm not diagnosed
That is what
Haha
So you can have this belief in your head
That you've worked yourself into and no matter what
Someone
Basically your response
Rationalize it
Use their
Whatever it is called
Flavor
Yeah I think it's possible that Alex Jones has some
Schizoid 10
And when he was younger he came van
This idea
Of the global
The reading that book
None dare call it
And it's stuck with him
The point where
Now
3540 years later
Can't not below
So all of this stuff
He's just Incorporated whatever
Whenever anyone needs built
Tire like
Lifeline
Yeah
Even if he does
If
Allows
Tiny crack
To form
The whole thing
Comes comes comes comes
Realize that there are no glow up
Zorbing
Like
Write everyday
But if
1 time like we've never heard him
Admit
Said he's wrong
No. There's actually even when he was wrong he was also right
I didn't pull this clip because it was
The relevant but
On the Thursday show he was complaining about
John McCain
Saying that Rand Paul was working
A Putin
And he was like
He was relating it all to Ukraine
He saying that McCain wants to go and have war with Russia
And that's why he's mad Rand Paul standing there
Contesting his motion
That was about Montenegro
That wasn't about
Ukraine do that wasn't about that at all
The entire time
So now
On the next episode
Admitted that he was wrong at the idea wrong
Here's the twist
He brings it back up
And he's like I got I got a couple things
Conflated that way
Was about Montenegro but it's
Oh
So
Yaga
Realistically
Yeah I believe
I don't know it's so hard
In terms of what I think about what he
But if you
If you look at it as a 40-year mental illness
About the globalist you notice you look at it like that
Hazing movie with Judd Apatow called the 40-year mentalism
But everything falls into place all of the
Conspiracy theory s*** all the reasons why he's joining up
With Trump now what
All of the fear about in Armageddon
How's the weather
He can rationalize that
No I'm not a snake oil salesman I'm really trying to help
If he actually has convinced
To be that
Go home at night
Sleep
Like a human being
He has to believe
Will the flip side of it is like
If you have people around him
Convince
That is
That's like a very
Your Christ syndrome
Yeah it
The real corollary to look back on
Historically
Cult leader
Actually believed
I would say
Minoriti
Like
I think a lot of them knew what they were doing
Right on study Jim Jones
In particular
So I can use him as an example l.ron Hubbard
Like a
Who's the Mormon talk Joseph
And then come up with the most normal name ever
Well I remember because I was
Like Joseph Smith may have just been a f****** lunatic who is Brigham Young was like the Paul is more still one who
Went
The town on that ship
What about Brigham Young on this
This clip
Open surveillance
0 Segway
In the circular reasoning
President Trump says it
You better
But that's because you're only engaging with the head
That's the problem
Consistent prob
I say you say I say
God say
What if he was one of us
Communication
Associate
Who wrote
Schmidt
Adam Goldman
Joseph
Can you talk to me
Cover for drinks
Don't walk
Another fake another fraud another scumbag liar
It started
It's time to pray
Where did that one of his Waypoint
Who's Rick
Billy yes
You know if you go see a jazz musician
Any always winds up
On the same like little triplet
Your f******
You're sure you're not doing your homework
Really realize just now
What
Alex Jones is essentially a debate student who didn't
Like he would have been thrown out of the Bay Club
Because it becomes obvious in like
You don't know the source
You're trying to make an argument about the
But the other person
Who has like
A nuanced
Understanding of the article
Are you saying that
Doesn't say what you think it says
And all you have is yellow
Because you don't know what it
All right hold on
Can I counter Counterpoint
But you can
I like that
Here is the one thing cuz I do have a
I do
Inexplicably have a base
Acknowledge of Debate Club
Was younger too
From all of the
Inexperienced
A lot of the times
Confident
M
Goes a whole lot longer than
Aren't many more demeanors
More confident
Or at least confident in there like a
Confidence
Alex jump I will say he does not follow Robert's Rules of Order
He does not follow Roberts.
A respectful gentleman
Sir
Confidence is one thing but
Heady
Complete
Lack of comfort
What it's totally obvious that your confidence is
Experience
Selma
It's right now
Some Powers know what it is
VSCO this idea of
Francois
Feeling
Pick-up artist
Demarcate reptile lyrics
Jen going their own way
But every morning they wake up
Negus
I guess you just also nailed another
Toxic masculinity
I rather quotes still isn't
They're not they're not
I'm glad he doesn't say s*** Rosenberg
Intercept
And you still force-feed it cuz I got to shave head
Look at that
And see that's not what it said
Angela
11 seconds ladies and gentlemen
Around here
Because
The other
Outlets out there
If these are the two sides
We better f***
Ray they win
Are you saying it's time to pray
Inside of her
Dear Lord
Please don't
Don't know how I feel
You don't know what things are like
Because yes nationalreview put it out they were forced to retract it wasn't true
Months before the peace headlines
Is it important to help the president
He just clocked out all of the other blogs that he relies on but then secondarily that he's responding to
Do something that is now with the reporter said that's not what Rosenberg
Merced
He said that
Infowars
Lied about what was in his story and then Trump
Responded to that
Which if you really look at it as a
Pretty much
Exactly what hap
But just because
This guy on
Rihanna and did not follow the cardinal rule
Keep my name out
Right
You now
Have to face Alex's Wrath
Where Alex
Once again message
It's great it's so fascinating
The oldest one
See how Alex reacts
Let's turn into the only thing I want to find out you're out there
I want to
Have a whale research
Biography
Of Alex Jones
Either you or I just go around
Every single human being
Together an actual
The other thing I want to know
Is Jessie J
Probably not know
Dominic
About is not
Rosenberg
Infowars
Rental page
Chickasha
Smart
And he remembers
New again
Bayridge the cover
He does not read
The cover who watches Fox News
Probably reads like Alex
Reply
He does not read I guarantee you might read headline
I guarantee
You did not read it
We might be in agreement
But anyway watch out this
Never were talking about that Nadia Comaneci
Style like a
Finishing
Gymnastics news about to finish his media criticism nobly
Is your preference
She did but I mean
Warrants for that
Corley
When a
The north remembers
He's merely transitions into a field
So he does that bedroom I'm so angry about something
Superman Vitality just the Classic Alex Jones
Exactly what we've always
Does episodes been too long
We're both under the weather in
Clearly at this point red wine drunk
Yep so we should I mean
Clip I think spoke
I mean
Credibly insane
Him not realizing to the point that the article was making
Is it they misinterpreted the headline
And then him not knowing what was in the body of the
Improving
Through his yelling for 10 minutes
But he doesn't know what's in the Bible
Was
Sad
Pathetic
Hopeless
You just summed up our podcast
What's levy on a positive note guys you can find us at dollartree.com
You can find us some knowledge fight.
Oh s*** big man
Follow us on iTunes from
Website Lakes up there we also
Regester email at knowledge
Gmail.com
Regarding
Alex really good too
The bottom of what his life was really like
I don't think we have any other plugs
Now I think that's just you and me I think we might
Just be
What's up
Couple of days
Cucked out liberal policy
Seawall
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work