Holding
Alex
Everybody
Jordan
Watch was the Obama
Documentary series on Netflix
Whatever the guy who showed up at a bank with like a bomb around his neck
Was crazy Irish
Connection with
So crazy
Fell down the stairs
That's coming from me
Long time
Episode
Call Joan about Alex
What we're here to do today
In the spirit of
You know
Our donors
People who make the show possible
We have been tasked
With breaking down
The entirety of
Alex
Spiritual end of a season
Probably
6 months ago
I don't think there was anything groundbreaking it happened right before
Before we did
But like
I feel like we're entering a new era of covering Alex Jones
That clip from the leaderless resistance
Different ballpark
Pretty convinced he's been interested in white supremacist groups
For me
Especially the context in which I look at
This season
With
Exhaust
Steve breakdown
People who are
Deception
Title
I don't know I watched it when I was younger
And
Is that the conclusion of all of your research today is
When I was younger
Really long things on YouTube
Habit of mine
Just one of the many
Really stupid
Long can
Conspiracy videos that I watched
Discarded out of
Realized
Think about it
I'm through it I realized
Documentary
Is the stupidest thing
It's so much worse than
Okay
Nightmare 49 hours
Bridge
FEMA camps than a lot of that stuff
Maybe about the same on this
Complain up top or anything like that
But the experience of going over there
And watching
Documentary
With a critical eye
Was brutal
Duct or something like that
Yeah
The show up with a six pack
In the morning or whatever
Quick
Shuffle the first
We are going to pause probably 20 times in the first minute
Alright are you ready to get going
How much
Receipt
Start at the beginning
Because even though
Even though we're making
Phone of Alexandra
There's still a corrosive toxic
The effects of listening to
2 tons of Alex Jones
So
Eroded
Someone who hopes for our show 216
We want to grow and we want to be
Best possible place but
It is
You should not
Listen to the show too much.
Lutein
Don't even bother
If this is
Tell everybody they were
The shot of the
National Mall
People happy
I was not born in a manger
Drake
I already got to stop because of some sort of like
Memes of being like
He's full of himself
He fails to recognize or point out any way that this is eclipse
It was taken from Obama's appearance at the alberty Smith Memorial Foundation dinner
That dinner is a traditional
Both parties
Poke fun at each other
Damn themselves
50 forever
Exceptional
Humorous
The big-ticket fundraiser and Catholic charity
And others and their discomfort with supporters of abortion
The foundation non-political
On the video
I feel right at home here because
It's been said that I share the politics of Alfred East the ears of Alfred E Neuman
Kills
Aerosmith I never knew your great-grandfather but from everything is told me the two of them had a great time together before
Here's another one
Maybe a little bit controversial nowadays
I have never put lipstick on a pig
Or dog
For myself
That's one for Rudy Giuliani
The cross-dressing mayor of New York have a hard time winning the Republican nomination
And he looks over
Ethereal
Fox News African American
Obama speech
Masterpiece
Embrace
Dinner on October 16th 2008
Conspiracies are already running wild Jerome corsi was already appearing all over Fox News
Claim to be short for
I've been released
Alex opening is telling a joke
About Bush's accusations people who are us
Alex
To give you a sense of where this documentary is
Spiritual level
So he's playing over
Obama's inauguration
Clearly what he's trying to do is make it look like
Even at his inauguration
Remember him
When is inauguration
These ideas in your head
It's incongruences clearly in a
Humorous
Even though
I don't know about that
That's on the editor
Only honor military in order to achieve
National Security objectives
Obama gave on July 2nd 2018 Colorado Springs
Quotev
Around that clip that
You just played Obama said quote
We're going to grow our Foreign Service open consulate that have been shattered and double the size of the
Peace Corps by 2011 to renew art
Diplomacy
We cannot continue to rely on our military
We do from listen to show 2000
Very selective
For the 10
He's not using military might is the sole Avenue towards
The re-establishment of focus on diplomacy
Which I would think I was
But oh well
Let me just
Keeps the service to others and
The community are really important
To ask people to embrace service
Not that he intends to
To force anyone to
Already predicting for this entire
That
Regardless of how evil he is trying to paint
Feelings on Obama's presidency
Back mixed
At least
Highway
Everybody somewhere between ages 18-25 will serve three months of faith
Training
Emmanuel
Thousand
Kokoro called the plant
Because because
Any other kind of
He also spends a lot of time talking about corporate welfare
We're in the long struggle
Terrorism in America is a target the best ways to prepare America
Forward
In understanding what their roles going
Everything from
It's
Chemical attack
What role they have
Understanding
A kind of civil
Just an idea that Robin
His co-author had
Not something that ever got put into legislation
He wrote This Book
Susan 2006
Well before
Well before right around
So this is this
I am already.
Because I do not
Ever
Ever ever want
To defend Rahm Emanuel from
Send Rob Emanuel Chicago
Criticisms
Is dumb
If you want
Possibly
Would be a system that would be cumbersome
Myself
How are you going to get them today
Community service through
Anyway
Hecate
It's high-minded missguided
Everything that you just described their completely did not do
He was given every opportunity
The middle here because codes that Obama is saying is that we need a civilian
Peace Corps
But it's some sort of nefarious
International for Charlie puth that's just as powerful Justice from
What the fuk was that
African-American children
Routine talking about Obama's
Plan
Is without a doubt a visual dog with
Alex is trying to make you feel afraid of any large group
Children
Oh
Even if they're just children
Spell with multiple lives
Alarm
There's no
Posted on October 2nd
The video shows children one-by-one Express
Because they were inspired by Obama
Professional mostly being an architect
Be a better job
The procession
Immediately after this week
Kind of understandably
I guess it doesn't
Indoctrination
Children
The urban community Leadership Academy in Kansas City Missouri
The students because they were like
Legal action
ABC was the fact that the teacher was having the students study Obama's healthcare plan but not McCain
Not that they
Be totally fine
Probably more important
Community leaders
Academy
Charter School
Which is described as a failed experiment
2014 report
Network of public education
Endemic patterns
High School
Michael
It closed in 2012
Missouri state auditor found notify
University of Central Missouri
$19,980 in school funds
Unaccounted for
Even under subpoena
Cheats to justify the claim purchases
You kind of have to assume that this wasn't the only incident of
Conveniently sloppy record-keeping
Never got up to
That's the bigger issue that I see
You can study Obama's healthcare plan because
McCain's plan was super simple
N99 mask
Also
They're just assuming that the teacher didn't teach them both plans
The kids
I don't know
I have no idea but
You know the thing that I really feel bad about here is that
Element
If abuse
With him there
These kids were put in
Into this situation
Not the teacher
Presumably the adult
Situation
Feel like this
It's wrong with Alex to do this
Those kids don't
Deserved
According to this documentary
What stores
Severe
For Alex's viewers
For free
Let me tell you something
They're action figures
Could not keep them on the show
We meet one of the main Scholars
Documentary
Exactly like
The road but here is he
The Fray
Obama is
Cool Hawks
He works for wolski
Capital
Where did you come up with the number 700
Here's the treasury spokeswoman quote
It's not based on any particular data point we just really wanted to come up with a really big number
The Democrats and Republicans
I say
Step Up
Butterfly
A few members were even told
That there would be martial law in America if we voted no
California representative
About the initial bailout bill
I was just playing fast and loose with martial law
Threatened with martial law
Consequences
But some people felt they
That's what represent
You know how I know this
Giordano's
2008 Brad Sherwood
Dammit as this exchange occurs
Play Store
The streets as you say would happen
Conversation
Between numbers on the floor
Alex
I understand
I think these were people who really believed they were saying
I don't think these people got called by Goldman Sachs
Take a life of its own
One person says the market will drop
Somebody else's 2500-3000
Somebody else's unemployment will immediately jump to 9%
Alex
It spreads
It gets worse and worse
Brett
I don't think there was early so I'm not aware of this being carefully orchestrated
You made an appearance on Alex's show
Contradicted
The version that Alex presents
The very guy was on his show
Consequences
Heather arm-twisted
Threatened by Goldman Sachs
Preventative
F****** b*******
Here is my new plan
Transcripts
Of the show
I want to bring him out so we could do it as a Duo
I wouldn't be against it
I know and one of a dozen
Let's
Play Alex Wright
You look like
Robin Williams
The punchline
Conversation
Immediately
Tell you who told me
Lady strange already
Lgbtq
Introduced
Against Donald Trump
Wait what
What
So Alex has a documentary which is
The number of people who are in this documentary who have really funny
Makoto's to their career
There's one of the like
In preparation of this documentary
Sincerely
Went down some weird rabbit hole
Stories are so absurd
That they must be told
And this is one of them
Here we have Louie gohmert
Talkingshit about Henry Paulson
Secretary Henry Paulson
There's no George Washington
To talk about it
I got so like
Here's
Who is no George Washington
Terror babies for like 7 minutes
That Louie gohmert is pushing
That terrorists are having a baby
Years down the line
Anderson Cooper has such a hard time not laughing
It is one of the funniest
About
It 2013
This is the result of him defending his position that you should be able to regulate guns
Because gay marriage
Is the same thing as bestiality
His quote
The problem is once you draw capacity magazine
Cool
Good
Good thinking
Somehow
Your regulating marriage
He's angling it's
He thinks you're deregulating
Marriage
Episode deregulating.
Bridget
Beastiality somehow
Make a stupid
The country by pretending to be Mexican
We don't have any fear of Hispanics coming into the country
Backcountry
I'd like to keep having fruit
I'm a big fan
I'd like to
Thought of a great idea for a TV
It's in the wild
Pages from the 9/11 report
Is there a
Very weird visit to Egypt
Soon-to-be installed president General
Abdel-fattah el-sisi
Successful
Erstwhile president arrested
For Morsi supporters and headed up by a girl
Camps of protesters in Cairo
After they'd been engaging in a six-week long sit-in
Human Rights Watch describe what it's doing is quote one of the worst world's largest killings
Demonstrators
It is single day in recent history
Less than a month later Louie gohmert visited to give el-sisi congratulations on
Performing Baku
He was
Weirdo Michele Bachmann and outright Nazi Representatives
Alright
Steve
Give me the plane
Congratulate
America
And this is after this is after he killed all those demonstrators
Elise's
The pro-morsi protesters who were massacred remembers of the Muslim
Motherhood
Took it upon herself to
TheBlaze
Brotherhood for doing 9/11
It's not true
Because the Muslim Brotherhood publicly
Strongly condemned
Is this
George Washington ever done before him let him know Terry and revolution revolution
We met in general el-sisi a man who is the leader of the military who might have a shot at being a
President
Egypt
Is no George Washington lccc
CD record
Benevolent
C in overwhelming fashion
He's still at present
Human Rights Watch has described the government
Civil Society
Congratulations
Anyone
Question
Mister Kashkari
Working hard
Resume the security and prosperity partnership talks
Between Mexico and Canada
The President Bush
Defense secretary
Leap year
And others that it was at Hillary Clinton
We've said oppressive
So frequently a lot of this stuff
Is going to be stopped
Thumbs up light
I'm not ignoring you real quick
When was this
This was released in 2009
I believe March
Obama
President
January
Did he include anything
Post
Inauguration other than like video of the inauguration
Was inaugurated
Is about to pop up
Podcast episode
Was after
It is
Problem
Rushed this
The market
You should
YouTube
Lexia
Crazy
No
And it wasn't
We've got to give them a steak
In creating the kind of
I will order that I think all of us would like to see
Alright
Hold on
He was talking there is a big audible tear
He was not talking to a rally
That was edited
The World Series
From this documentary blew his
And refused to take it out because
Use of information
It is really crucial today
Camera pans out we see that this isn't just an animation of Barack Obama
It's a group shot
Geithner Jade Skywalker
Tom daschle was nominated for secretary of Health and Human Services
But by the time this documentary came out he had already withdrawn his name from consideration
Because of
Text problem
So I think that Alex blew his Budget on this shot
Awful
Just refuse to change at 5
Because
Embarrassing
This is embarrassing
The Obama Deception
Cameras one rocking
If your burger is not done right
I want to go to the Supreme Court
Hungry
Burger King
Or to the bottom
I like to let people speak
Piece that's why I didn't interrupt
I don't
No
Who
Actually is what
In that
I mean analogy
Okay so the cashier is
The courts
Your Burgers called
Metaphorically
I'll leave that part 11
Whatever
Marillac
Go to the
President
That makes absolutely no sense
Now the second problem that I have with it is
If your Burgers cold
The cashier
The store manager
Can I help you
Owner doesn't have time for that
Not the problem
What is the fridge
And then the president is the store managers cashiers
One of my favorite thing
Conspiracy theory all dead how the government works
If you listen to the Riza talk about the government the funniest f****** thing you've ever heard
Little bit
Everybody knows that
If he's displaying this level
First of all
Lack of awareness
Of how our government
Networks
Substitute
Complaints about state government
And then also demonstrates this kind of like
Inability to wrestle with
Inference like the metaphor
A good one you don't need
Explain which
Part
Each individual thing is you know you don't have to be like
Go to the cashier
Go to court
Explain
I've always admired Kerris one I still think a lot of his music
Disgrace
Need to take a step back and assess whether
Donuts
Chris Creighton The Fast and Furious movies
That's true
Hold off on that
Also it's important to point out that five months after this interview with Alex doing right now
Terrace One release a 600-page book
Call
The first instrument
Improv
I'm suggesting in 100 years this book will be the new religion on Earth
I respect Christianity the Islam's the Judaism but their time is up
He certainly has every right to start his own music based religions
I just think it's really funny that Alex
Who's actively trying to start a religion
With art
Hilarious
He's such a user
Like
Disappointed
Politics
In front of the camera
The public
I'm going to kick my opponent
Yep behind the scene
Y'all are friends going out
Dinner K
It's hilarious
Nothing is like politics is like
If your fries are cold
Every single person
The other day you told me about this great metaphor about fast food
Saying that Republicans and Democrats act like opposing forces behind the scenes they get along
That's how I want the f***
Can government to work
This in Show Business
It's it's
Cubans disagreeing
Is the way that I would like things
To work once I believe
The other side beliefs
Position why
But they're both good
People could share a steak and talked about their families are golf scores or whatever the f***
That's how the world should operate
Jesse is saying which is like
Hey everybody in public hate each other but then we hang out
Improv
Trying to paint
You talk about pro wrestling
Hanging out like a
Absolutely not tragic
First
Look at things
Discounts and takes away the entire ideas at like
Like you and I
Could disagree
Maybe you unfairly major position
Other common ground
Policy abmc
Rhian f
G
There's no reason that that that you don't have to be idealog
What would make it make more sense
Everybody was like
We understand the climate change is the biggest issue
Still disagree on
Figure out where they come together
It's it's trouble
Less than right mean nothing
The only thing
Chances
Are you working for walls
Gigantic fight
Politicians
Hey there
I mean
60 Stoopid
Whenever he wasn't
Is this is also the only appearance
Most popular world
Tim to be all over this.
Before disaster
The Logical conclusion of that is not to adopt any of Alex's
It's to initiate
Institute publicly-funded funding
For campaign
And make accepting any donations illegal
America
Years been disaster
Fair enough
F*** you
George Bush
Conservative
Shredded the Constitution
I was trying to figure out figure out what Alex meant by triple the size of the federal government
Couldn't figure out what he was saying
During endgame
I found out
Bibliography
Which is mostly Encarta Paisley TV
Encarta pages and then
Citation needed
Confined
So what do you mix
The claim that bush
Triple the size of the government
In order for me to talk about that
Government-to-government
What is he talking about
Guest for you
Right and that's going to happen.
Anyway
Destroyed the image
No weapons over there
Over a million dead Iraq
And more than 5,000 dead US troops
The Patriot Act warrantless wiretapping Supply
Patriot Act
In the Posse Comitatus
The Rose
A deepening recession
Create some sort of
Like really save your thoughts on that
He over-exaggerated misdemeanors will be terrorism
Embellishes exaggerated
Don't operate outside of federal proper
Is a 2
Like is the case that we went over on the show recently
Cuz it's North American Union.
We have this
Recession that was happening
If you're responsible to talk
Lakers
February 2009
I haven't had a chance to do anything about it
Particularly jarring now that we live in the
And it's still fun
Going on
The equivalence
He has
Putting
1million dance
Iraq
5000 dead ameri
And he does not
Like he just leaves that there puts them right next to each other like they're the
The same
And it's like
Yeah
One of these is not like the other
That's that's a fair as a fair
America's Best
The American people in a state of panic
Their future
I'm a very existence
People
Facade
Past
Both parties
Universally hated
Congress 9%
The globalist agenda
Poll numbers
Photography
Information from
13th
2000's hits 14%
Does the lowest
During this Panadol
Inauguration
On January
The numbers are back up in the 30s
Sullivan great
But it's not nearly what
Never get down to 9% until November 2013
It's not hard to remember what was so bad back then
You may recall that this
Was the result of their being
A democratic majority Senate in a republican house
The Affordable Care Act
The Koch brothers
Tea party organization
It was an existential issue for them
The ACA gone
Auto insurance companies
Unregulated gambling
In September 2013 there was an Appropriations bill
Repast insured
Republicans
Crews used as a bargain
The dismantling of the affordable
Only if they could be fun
The Affordable Care Act
This strategy was literally
From the Koch brothers founded
Think Tank freedom to work which
Suggested that
Must be renewed in order for the doors
Stay open in Washington
The continuing resolution
Is the best chance we will get
Withdraw funds from Obamacare
This could be done by attaching bills bicep
For Congressman Tom Graves
Continuing resolution
Which will
Defund Obamacare
Congressman Mark Meadows
Get their colleagues
By putting your signature
Affirming that they would refuse to vote for the
A concurrent resolution
And guess what happened
The exact Republicans named in that release
Freedomworks
Led the charge not to approve the spending bill
With a strategy so we ended up with
They shutdown
The Federal
800,000 employees were furloughed in 1.3 million had to go to work not knowing when they be paid
The damage was caused by this petulant shutdown
Pretty hard to put into words
And governmental organizations are relied on federal funding
Cut off
Including to mess
Violence shelters in program
His many is 19000
Children lost their access to the Head Start program
Which provides education food in healthcare
Underprivileged
The national parks estimated that they lost approximately
376 million dollars a day
And tourism income during the shutdown
2.7 million a day alone
From the Grand Canyon
Which has a reciprocal effect on the small businesses
It exists around the National Park
They rely on them to bring in business
In the form of Tourette's
That's when Congress had a 9%
Favor of the government shutdown
And support
Cruise I'm not sure what that means
So you're saying that there were no negative effects
The billionaire
For this
Political stunt that never had any chance
Success at all
Real-world effects
Like regular
And and just like humans
America
Buddies
Super 4
Good good good everybody makes sense
I love it whenever there is a
Your ideology and your
Supporting
You betcha
That's the time
Poll showed an actual approval rating
Rasmussen poll
Percent of the 1,000 likely voters they pulled
The Congress was doing a good or excellent job
But that's not a 9% approval rate
For contrast gallup's poll was just opposed
Not necessarily likely voters
And they specifically asked a quest
Do you approve or disapprove
Way Congress is handling
Leave the way that they frame the question
In the Rasmus
Lynette wasn't
Looked at
Also when was the last time Congress had
Positive
I don't know
Also a minor point but both parties Alex
Universally hated absolutely
Okay by 12 points
Which makes sense
Because in the 2008 election
Democrats
For the Main Street
Right the ship
Contact
The last time one party had fee
57 cm
As the Democrats
2008 election
Was in 1992
Republic
Intitle majorities at Large
In the election of 90
President at 11
For the Senate vote
So just giving you that the world we lived in the last time Republic
Had his a majority the Democrats enjoyed
Crazy how did it go the last time the Republicans had that
Massive majority
Since that so it's almost like there's a pattern
When the Republicans are in power
They did
Everything
Youth history
We could all be
Already go f*** yourself you came onto the scene
It's perpetuated by the right-wing
Came out of nowhere
It's used to in service of the ID
The creation of the Illuminati
Even a demon
Nothing
Promise complete bulshit
Try running for President Obama
Is the senator in Illinois
Gets rid of the he came Outta nowhere
For being Senator Obama was a member of the Illinois Senate winning his first election in 1996
Deep are the state senate that puts Obama right on the same level as all these weirdo state senators that Alex
Constantly has on his program
To talk about reasserting their 10th Amendment rights
He was in
State Senate since 1997
That's almost as long as Alex has been on the radio
Obama has been an elected
State position
What is the state senate
Alex police
Legislature
It's not cuz he's black
It's all good
It's fairly easy to see why
Is time in Congress
Turn basically
Obama was
The primary sponsor for
For bills that were enacted
I'm out right now
He's only got one bill passed
Obama was an active member of the state senate in Illinois
And in 2004 he gave a super important
Speech at the Democratic National Convention
Which state was
It was
Like it was the first time the world was like
Breakthrough like the idea that came out of nowhere even if you wanted it
Before 2004
He gave that
Groundbreaking
A patriot
Was a sleeper Canyon States
Who else it was a community
Barack H Obama
Bring our troops home
Yeah
The Constitution
Federal government
Find America
He did all right
Like some of the
Issues of the
Specifics
Later is out
But like you've already brought up it's so important to remember this is
Is less than 2 months
Imply
Use
Executives it'll act unilaterally
Which kind of makes sense
Now considering in present day
While the same time upholding the Constitution
America with no regard for the other branches of government
While still maintaining the Constitution right
All the amendments
No I don't
Breaking news
2 months
In this film we will prove
But Obama says one thing
She'll just breathe
Bush serve
The very interest
Engineering the financial collapse
Formation
I'm addicted to real world
Best film is not about left or right
Go fuc yourself
You like hearing that violin come back
Yes Humanity
Directions to the better
Will not come from the Madison Avenue false reality make
Barack Obama
Batman
To alter our course
To defeat the corrupt Elite
Do puppet
Coming into view
A world in which there is a very serious Prospect
Seven New World Order
Webster Griffin
Noticed
Christmas decoration
You think when he was videotaping West
Before Obama
Christmas
Geopolitical animal
Are the unauthorized biographies of George Herbert Walker Bush
Barack Hussein Obama
The postmodern coup
Bushkill
September
New World Order
I'm confused about
The New World Order
A Moorpark
Angela
Second world Empire
Twisted the work of
Who put out the book The anglo-american established
That has been
Misrepresented
In the naked capitalist
Gary Allan and none dare call it conspiracy
These are
Now I want to tell you about Webster
Griffin Tarpley
Guide
Okay
Pretty fantastic
Their website
Judge people's
The same way that Alex
Right right
Helix
Exactly the billionaire
Lebowski
5 is the billionaire what
Looks exactly like
He does there are still married
Cuz he look
List
I wanted to
Metairie
Call Webster Tarpley
Let's just do a documentary about webs
Because he is
Completely fascinated with this guy by the time
I finished this bio on him
So Webster play here in the documentaries created as an author and historian
He's notably not also credited as a guy who has a radio show on the Genesis Communications Network
It's a bit of a conflict of interest
Is also similar
The payroll of the
Distributes Alex's radio show
Cinnamoroll and they have a little sit-down now
Get back
Deception book
The only way to get past the North American Union
Babadook
Ted does not show up
The Protege of Lyndon larouche
Who comes up on our normal show every now and again
Tangentially related to the matters at hand so we're going to save getting deep into him for another day
But suffice to say in 1979
Somatic
The suit was thrown out just as Michael.
Of the New York Supreme Court ruled that it was a fair,
Reasonably give rise to the description of him is a piece of heaven
You are legally a fascist you dumb idiot
Accidentally made a New York Supreme Court Judge rule on the record that his actions could be fairly called anti-Semitic
You are a sort of idea log
Magical predator
I decided to check into tarpleys credential
Nice pose
Epsom salt
Most of his books are unauthorized
Like George Bush the unauthorized
Obama the postmodern making of a Manchurian Candidate
2 subtitles
Funny note
The book was called Obama dangerous when it was released
I like that
Jimmy James munky funky donkey for karate Murphy death card
Mistranslated as likes
To buy Hut
The author of the book called Barack H Obama the unauthorized biography
Right
It was titled
Just
Weird Bishop of America
Polygamy theocracy and subversion
Subtitles
Any interest in reading these books but reviews
Oppositional Style
That makes numerous leaps of logic and there is no evidence
And another time
Contrarian
Information
That reveals a more complex picture
Sounds like
Exactly the sort of guy Alex
To be an expert so if he were to go in front of the New York
State supreme court
They would legally say you are not a historic
Kind of a historian
PhD in
Early modern history
Which is today the Middle Ages
However that degree is from
The Catholic University of America
University
Well early modern history
Catholic
University of America is
Good school according to the Princeton Review I still going to raise my eyebrows
Concerning what a school literally founded by the Vatican might be teaching about the Middle Ages
Seems like they might have skewed version of events from that. I have no idea if that's true
The time that it was multiple popes
Distrust of organized religion
Especially
Rotational tool
Association of college
Professors
Catholic University of America
All that being said the school
0.0%
There's no abortions there ever
That is not even
True it's not even it's not even 0.0%
That's not the most interesting thing about
Steven is bachelors in the languages
Is from Princeton
Is a Fulbright scholar at the University
Whataburger
The reason is interesting is that
The Fulbright program is funded
Entirely by the Bureau of education and cultural affairs
State State Park
We'll see
Fulbright program
Students abroad
Improving Intercultural relations
Abreon said Nations
Together you think the Fulbright program
For the guy who came
William Fulbright
Insofar as International laws
International laws
Kings of predicting the behavior of those with whom we have
The creation of
Practice international law
So what we have here is Webster
Money
Globalist
You should make a new one all that surprised
That
In the lead-up to the 26
The election
Webster Tarpley
Strongly in favor of Hillary
He accurately figure it out
Collapse
Kind of a prince
Libertarianism in America
Was leaving it open
Trump could exploit to bring in fashion
He wrote
On March 25th
If we look for the roots of the Trump phenomenon in particular The Savage immorality
Of a candidate whose supporters applaud
20 calls for expanding
Severity of torture
Mass deportations
The mass killings
The families of it
We should not forget about the
Tremendous
Including included by a figure like Ron Paul
Paul wanted to abolish all u.s. emergency food at MiniMed about 6
50% of the emergency number
Usually available worldwide in a given year would have disappeared
Leaving once again to genocide
He literally argues
Libertarianism is the front door
The natural introduction
To fascism
And that Ron Paul is
Ended
In this blog post
He's clearly also talking about Alex Jones
Between 2008 and early to
The libertarian bloggers and broadcasters
Accelerate
Decline
Especially in terms of the moral honesty and ideological quality
Output
We're watching the astounding ease with which veterans are Libertarians blithely throw their
Principles overboard
And rushed like Lemmings to join the bandwagon of the fascist Trump
Who's dictatorial and authoritarian tendencies
Hardly be
I don't know
Also I totally help them out also sorry I was in the Obama
Yeah we're giving you a year of intellectualism
Clearly something I regret
After you put up that block
Prison Planet
I have no idea what to think about whether sharply like as a whole
He's going to be factually and spiritually wrong about almost everything
Get Lisa the Goodcents
Was
Crazy
Considering the other
Most likely conclusion here at is what I'm going to stick by because it's
The easiest
Simplest explanation
Explain all of
The things
Is it Webster Tarpley is a charlatan in a con man
Generally knows
Better
Is Dino better than to
To support the rise of something overlay patch
Because generally you have to pay them for your con
Also just ignore things are being unfair
Huge piece of s***
Yeah he supported multiculturalism abroad
However he protested Brown versus the Board of Education
And ironically
He's part of the Great Republican
Exodus
Pontoon out there
In August
With a high-end prostitute
Which quickly led to a libel suit
You're totally settled that lawsuit
Which were private
Topology
A substantial
He's off the wagon
Spiritually
Don't get yourself into libel territory
I hear you
9 minutes into this documentary and already we have the other
Literally the main person in the documentary
Entirely against
And what he's up to
And the other got sued for libel for calling
And Roblox before the election
Calling him
Aspire
Authoritarian
New York washing
The world
It's hard to get people to
You call it the Angela
World
If you call it
The New World Order
India or someplace
European Union
Might think
I just want to stop by
Except
F****** stupid
Anglo-american
Quarter
It's really the old
The British Empire
Morphe
American Empire
Do us British
World Empire
Talk all the time
Subway
Is
Are you talkin about is the idea that I
They called the new world order instead of the anglo-american
So they can can
People in India
I don't know what that means
To the people in charge
He's not talking about getting Indian citizens
The would-be oligarchy
If it was called the anglo-american whatever the name of it is if they're involved
Does a f****** matter
So he's arguing with Ben have to be front angle
That come up
I don't really honestly do
Bingo
Powerful men
Maybe true as a
Isolated
Gerald Celente
People that are knowledge
No
Got the fight
This country's been
Waging
Section
Not to take over the
This is so funny because if you're not watching this video.
Both cameras are showing
Just involves him moving his head
So we've run into a number of time
Times on our coverage
Or that is his business
The trends research
Protagonist
Strong
First thing is really funny about Gerald Celente being one of Alex
His go-to guys
U.s. passport
Considers himself a citizen of the world
Globalist to me
We know Gerald Celente is a guy who appear in land Alex's show a little dramatic
Flair with his expert delivery and cranky old man
We also know that he existed on the show Almost
Exclusively to help
Sell gold
As you constantly warned the audio
Wheatley be devalued
Can anyone expect
Dubai gold also Rubik's Cube
At the upcoming summer review the summer of Rage
You do that every
We seen it over and over again
It is Trends Journal
2015 speculated that it was possible that gold would soon be Trading
$20,000 in
Definitely be above
2010 the very near future
At the time of his writing golden trading around 12
And would never retire than 30
Fart
Just been wrong
Consistently about gold prices and a salary
African puppet way off of
But you are right on.
He also wrong about the dollars imminent demise for over a decade
He's also been wrong about some more fun
Researching this topic in
Particular was really difficult
Because talenti or is it
Employees website constantly to remove failed prediction
Trend forecast for the middle of the year
$100 a year to get access to the quarterly Journal of wrong thing
Today's news
Oh that revised rain forecast for like Courtney Brown at the remote
Viewing Institute
Whenever he likes
They make predictions
And the next month
Exactly
Difficult I wasn't I wasn't
Find it a couple really fun predict
Is made of
For the years that were
F****** so far off
In 1999 he told the San Francisco Chronicle
Unless you're going to have some kind of mystical ancient Chinese power from drinking it
Bubble tea
Play races
Little bit in 2016
2016 the bubble tea Market was valued at 1.9 billion dollars with projections that it'll grow
Approximately 3.2 billion by 2023 it represents over
Half
The year 2000.
Are there
Hours for me
Borderline
The comet in there
2000 Wrangler
Today quotes
Voluntary simplicity
Once merely a counterculture idea will finally become a reality in the 21st century
Moderation self-discipline and spiritual growth
Movie the personal goals
The future not Material accumulation
That is the worst Trend forecast I've ever heard in my entire
Tire f****** life
That was a 2000 like
I just like to remind everyone how
Huge Reality Tea
V.
Yeah
Materialism became like
Grills came out
Betty White
Yeah
I also from that psychology today article
Somewhere around the year 2000
The Revelation and revolution
The lawn
!
Your front lawn
What about it
Morons are everywhere
Williams
I wrote this and I didn't even lie I wasn't even ready to say that that's
Lawns are everywhere
Millions of coffee
Nothing but growing grass
The trend to convert Lawns into Gardens
Havasu
We eat but also the way we live
Feel
My comments on that
We all know how many of us have
You drive around the city of the suburbs
Front yard Community beer in a suburb driving around everybody's like
Oh my God look at that great tomato patch
The selenti deception
Misconception
He goes on in this article
She is with the
Let's call it trends
Ragtime music
Pictures of Jude
Looking out his window or watching TV make beard like
Oh I see the lawn before let me make a prediction on these things cuz they sound so cranky and I know
His voice is so awesome
Didn't want to hear him talk about that f****** rock and roll
Replacing swinging
I miss the good old days of ragtime
Doesn't mean
Justice rock and roll replaced swing and Ragtime music
A new genre of Millenia
Millennium music with despair of today's cutting-edge
Gerald
How old was he
18 years ago
He's 70-something now so I'm a word
Music is going to turn into
I got my finger on the pulse
Little more than his guests
Rainforest
Her now
In the book invest in yourself the authors asked
Blimpie how he makes his
Prediction you replied the basically what he does it every day you read newspapers
Stories that may or may not actually exist
Just
Read the other article in the newspaper he's like
Music
Asia so
He's a terrible predictor of South
Keys made
A couple of correct
Predictions
That if you really look at what
He said
Credibility
One prediction
G7
It's not great
Jordan Bonet
Season predictions
Flair
Sheepdog in
All the time
Perfect as the ones I have around twist
You perfect
And that's why people like Andrew
Jackson
Netflix
People like Tom
In case anybody is wondering right now
President Andrew Jackson
Central Bank
National Bank
Is that you were going to teach me some things about Andrew Jackson
Among the anti-government crab Jackson MS
Sekiro it was working hard to wrestle control over America
Evil Central Bank
To the really important to take a look back
The influence
Jackson hat
Visa V Central Bank
Because it's not the
The story that Alex Jones
Community towel at all
The biggest
Charter for the Second Bank
The United States after he was elected
1832 for the Fifth Third Bank
This bit about how we need to start
That's technically
Conquer the day
The Second Bank was established after the war of
Left
Precarious Financial
Situation
Inflation was through the roof as the mirror
Printed up tons of money
The money increasingly
So you said all
Producing
That was different
Ended up
Centralized Bank in order to
Fight back this inflationary effects like Alex
Has ever advocate
Has a historical precedent
President Madison
Last 20 years
When Jackson was elected
Charter Charter
Despite overwhelming public
Support of Congress
For the bank
Push for the removal of government funds from
Can back which he succeeded in carrying out
These funds were specifically placed in his favorite quote
Pet Banks
State Bank
How to be loyal
Inspiration
In 1836 the federal banks Beast
Became the State Bank
Historian James Sholar noted quote
34 there was some five hundred or more
United States
Circulation
Several times
Sterbank which Jackson
Packers running down
It is clear servers noted
Existence
Half a thousand distinct currencies
Great deficit
The poster regulation
And so did little
Which was with those in favor of the Second Bank
Navigate
And in his deregulatory laissez-faire attitude towards everything
All of these competing currencies came up
Traded mask
Who said that he should be
Working on
Controlling
For their help
Historian HW brands
Explains the situation that Rose
Interim
It got worse
Primarily as a result of Jackson's
Free from the restraints
Vittles
Actress Skye G
Biddle's Bank
Issued
Cue up the ramp
Speculation in every time
Commodity
Do much about the speculation overall
Except worried that it jeopardize the stability of the economy
And threaten the welfare of millions of Ordinary People
On July 11th
1836 Andrew Jackson put out of
Land speculation
Only be brought bought by you
Using gold or silver
Historian major l Wilson
All that did was to make cash poor Farmers more dependent on
Capital Rich speculate
It magnified
Defraud the president
Expunged
Loyalist
The fight little
Every state
The Union
Golden Silver Reserve that millions of dollars were taken out
Used in land speculation
Or just privately hoarded
Leaving Banks vulnerable
Kohl's on deposit
All this led directly to the panic of 1837
Where the country was plunged into
2D procession
The last until
Midday
1840s
Unemployment reached
Over 20%
Many area
Andrew Jackson was a really stupid president
Also really dumb Point Alex yells all the time.
Crack fiend
Party the KKK and how Lincoln was a republican all this stuff so they're the ones who are really good
Changed you could make the argument
The Democrats are the party broke up
Potater Jackson was a Democrat
He almost
Destroyed the entire
Stupid and short-sighted Petty accent
He is one of if not the worst I mean
It's to Andrews in the running for president has
I will tell you that right now
Yu-Gi-Oh
Hell yeah
Centralized
He was supposed to
Renewing the charter
Expire when
Consequences of his actions
Proves the need for those Bank more than the guy who
C13 Creighton Federal Reserve
I mean
Alex is also saying
There are multiple
Bank agents
The try to assassinate
Yeah but he
There's one guy who attempted
I love that the other f****** good was a minor fight Jackson got into it
Press charges over
Richard Lawrence
Lawrence born in England
Which I get most
The crown
To lead and other chemicals in the paint of the day
Decline
As he reached the age of 30 and on
England only to return a month later
But how we couldn't go
The first time he complained it was
Second time the story was much more
He been in Philadelphia for a
The US government didn't approve of
England
Amedia read several articles in the Philadelphia newspaper
Critical of his travel plans and character
Richard quit his job
He told them that he was Richard
The third the king of England to a died 380 years earlier
And how that would not make
Money in issue
Still
Send a letter
Because Richard
Richard
Write for reasons that aren't entirely clear.
Vetoing of the Second Bank of the United
Made it impossible for
To collect the money he was owed on the
He reasoned that if he killed Jack
Martin van Buren
Compressor heat setups
And just like that
He gets all the reasoning that he use
And that's what Alex
I am fine with that
At this point Richard started dressing up like British royal
Began to appear
Is always
Is there
Much more
Familiar with
US Capitol
Didn't fire
Hold up his back backup pistol
As this
Beating Richard the third with his Cane
Richard was by the crowd which included
Davy Crockett Hollywood
You going to face trial that area
What is where was none other than France
Richard was found in his
By virtue of
Until his death 26 years later
In the aftermath of the assassination
Really to find a reason for it
Rumors spread that he was working for the
Proponents of the second
A theory that literally had
No proof
No backing and evidence at all
In a mirrored by at least
1 president
Conspiracy theories
Has it helped
Can look heroic
Demonized
So it was crazy
And you're actually talking about entertainment
He's a crazy dude
Story that you already know I feel like
I felt like
You know what it is on this show
Your reaction
Sincerity
That you worked
Surprised
Cuz you weren't responding
Delighted
I think it was like at least a couple of years ago a friend of the show
Sent me this video
Of somebody who is done
Essentially my Andrew Jackson B
On his album
Oh no it what we had
Define Allina does his line for line what I say
Which is that
The Secret Service
Keep the president from being assassinated
They kept the president from assassinated
Because that was a good line
B*******
Gerald Celente
It was something that Abraham
Lincoln War
Okay
The money Powers Prey Upon the nation in times
X
Is mulch
Despotic
What is silento
Receipt
More selfie
Iraq
Sing in the near future of Christ
Approaching
Cause
To tremble
Safety of Mike
Corporation
Pennyroyal corruption
And the money power of the
Tree
Will endeavor to prolong its range
In a few hands
And the Republic
Wall Street
Is killed
Slavery
Valenti's argument for Ham Lincoln was a fast
That's a fact
Utility
Select Abraham Lincoln collected works
You can't find that quote
Twenty years after Lincoln
1896 presidential
Release a bogus letter about nefarious forces trying to meddle in the economy during the 1896 election
It's hard to say for sure but one pretty strong
Is that the gold standard was one of the top issues in that election Williams
Democratic nominee
At the Democratic National
It makes this would be an issue
Comeback
And everybody likes
To try and take historical heroes and pretend they said
Things
Predicted
Died supported their cause
Hitler said that
In the past
Alex Jones and his crew used
Completely fabricated quotes on a regular
Almost everything
It was nonsense
That's definitely
But in this case they might have a slightly better argument
Then impact
They just don't know
Because in 1950 Archer HR release the Lincoln in Psych
Wikipedia which purported to be a One-Stop shop for all things
The problem is
The terms authenticating
He put in the
The letter that this quote comes from in that encyclopedia
A letter supposedly
The colonel William FL
But historians and researchers are
Clearly determined that letter was
It was far from the only example of the lack of
Completion ism
It's not being as well put together resource for
Information
But I could see Gerald Celente or Alex seen that book called The Lincoln encyclopedia
Any further steps
Tear
You can have credit
You're still wrong
Church
Whatever I get where you coming from you're not you're not active
You're not an act
Participant
Unpopular
You seen as helping Banks
We just had a shot of
From their beds
I promise you I guess
Open syllable
World progress
Assassination
And the others
Beginning of the Vietnam
McKenzie
That is now
No longer
ProgressBook
The military-industrial complex has taken over the country along with the walls
Street game
If you look also at the
People that Obama has
Put on his
It's all walls
It's government of Wall Street by Wall Street
Fort walls
Not wrong
Israel
From Silicon Valley
Nobody from
Okay well yeah
Defense
No women
No retirees
Small business
Nothing
People who have a voice in Obama's
Bar Wall Street
Finance
That's all there is nobody else
Under Obama
The most extreme
Wall Street
A little bit
It's important to recognize like I'm old
When I did a lot of his research
Basically use the information that would be available
Substantiv claims I tried to limit myself to available before March 2000
Fair Shake
They do not deserve
You know all of these
His first claim their that laundry list
Heavy Industries pretty range usually means steel mills that sort of thing
Uninvolved incense contract and arrows
Space work
In February 2009 Obama appointed
Senior advisor to the Secretary of Treasury
Previously Ron Blum
Ben
In both the Arenas of Labor Relations
Special Assistant
The president of the United States
Representative
Industry in there at least one
So I know that that
Famous Subs
Miller might be active
Seem like it doesn't seem like I can't I can't find any autoexec you
Important
Advisors early on
Which considering
Where is
General Motors and Chrysler
The time to have Auto executive you know what I mean
Did I don't know
I'm going to give him a mic with
You know
Display the kernel
Boil
This one makes no sense
Queens of England
The Denmark
Complained
About if it wasn't
Canelo fight
I'm not sure what it is
Is big wild
Defense secretary Robert Gates
Drilling which is
The company involved in offshore oil rigs
So it doesn't really seem
Also National Security advisor
Directors for Chevron
There's nobody from defense such as other claim is next one that's Ludacris the aforementioned Robert Gates
Who's the Secretary of Defense under George W bush
What do you agree with Mr nada
How does a job
Which I do
Experience
This documentary
Purple
Doesn't have anyone from
Defensive
By the way he specifically allowed to stay on in order to give that appearance
Within that situation
Exactly
Jeff said he says there's nobody from labor
The aforementioned Ron Bloom at a previous career in labor unions
Steelworkers
Obama Secretary of Labor Hilda Solis had a career in the House of Representatives
And supporting labor-friendly legislation
She's the only member of Congress on the board of the America
Rights to work
Approach Union organization that is
4 years
Percent ratings
A laborer
Tattoo
To Whit there was Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's EPA director Lisa
Jackson secretary
Un Ambassador Susan
William sibelius
Secretary of Labor
And that's not even
Complete list is just another example of
Nothing
There's no retirees
Punt on this one
I don't think it's necessarily one of you trademark signs of a hell
Healthy Administration that there's
A guy who came out of retirement
I don't want those people there
Yeah I don't I don't know what anybody who's not invested in the future
No small
Exactly what your definition
Small business
Email.
Who built their own dinners
Setting up their own private practice
Not always
Is exactly the same
It's pretty similar
Also truck
Small business administrator is Linda McMahon owner of the WWE
Washington Post journalist
Implicated as a nice
Executive at Google
Obama's director of the office of Social innovation
Civic participation
Global development initiative
The philanthropy sex
Google
A person out that this claim is also
Not true
Is claimed that Obama's administration
People who actually have involvement in Wall Street
There weren't that many
They're only like three or four people that you can make an argument out of
The 22 cabinet
Positions that are the official
I said have any real history in
Would go on to have her
History
Sure sure
I'm debating
Right right
You look at other
Ministrations
You look at like Trump Administration
Steve mnuchin Gary Cohn and James Donovan
Executive
Who
Had positions that were
Specifically
Areas that had to do with
Phoenix Financial
Century
George W bush
People from Ball Street
This is not really I mean sure we could all be idealistic and say like
Be great if there wasn't
But to say that there's some sort of a
The most
Aggressively Wall Street cabinet ever is
Is Ludacris
Dino's when fascism
Apparently that's nice
He knows whenever he's
Onslaught
Play Eminem
Hell yeah
Pick up Matthew Moore
12 minutes
54 seconds
Before his death
President Woodrow Wilson apologize
Republic
Regret
My group of International Bank
And the country's Financial system in fall
Iron grip
Woodrow Wilson was one of the biggest
Piece of s*** president
He didn't he didn't apologize
The Federal Reserve propagandists
You justify that sort of
Claiming that narrative
Is as follows
Industrial nation is controlled by a system
Democratic
My credit is privately
And all our activities are in the hands
Fu man who is Iraq
To be honest
Republican
Are necessarily concentrated upon the great undertaking
In which their own money is involved
Chill and check
And destroy the genuine economic
Freedom
We've come to be one of the worst rule
One of the most
Completely controlled and dominated governments in the Civilized world
No longer government by free opinion no longer government by conviction in the
Small group of dominant
That's the quote that Alex's
To justify the sergeant
Woodrow Wilson apologize
Just before his death
About
The Federal Reserve
Problem
Is it busy
Of Woodrow Wilson's writing combined to give the impression
But this was
What he was saying
The first paragraph
A speech that he gave at the Democratic Club in Harrisburg PA
On
And the other was from a book he wrote called the
Published
Both of these passages were written before the Federal
December 9th
Have nothing to do with the effect
To the Fed
Information is demonstrably fraudulent
Began making the rounds
The 1950
Has the Cold War got moving
Like Alex Jones espiritual
Godfather
So the Phyllis Schlafly is of the world
And this narrative was cracked
Regretted creating the Federal Reserve
Couldn't events
Before the Federal Reserve
Also also Woodrow Wilson
Everybody who is black
To hide
Woodrow Wilson
A giant piece of
Better president
He's knowing
You got to give
I know I don't be the most racist president
The Civil War
You mean that Lincoln
I think they're very worth
Pointing finger
Nicole
In terms of Alex's claims
All that's important is
Alex
Just regurgitating
2:02
Images Frankenstein monster together by 9
250g communist propaganda
The Federal Reserve
Thanks
No I got to work to you
Potential for the day
The fastest rising
Misplaced power
Exist
And will persist
That the military-industrial complex was taking over the country
President Eisenhower's prophetic warning concerning the threat posed
Industrial complex
What happened to John F Kennedy
Expected to be
A puppet it was.
You pop it
Republic
Speculator
Guaranteed
Establishment
Discovered
Bad back though
Having a space probe
Making deals paper I started before him
What about the secret space program
111 10
Shine by president
Began the process
Pulling the troops out of Vietnam
Alex
Because he signed
Executive order
That would begin the process of eliminating
Now that executive order wouldn't
Fantastic example
Even about the topic
He's made his bread
Frankly this is just another example of Alex parroting conspiracy theories
Propagated
In this case
He's just repeating things that were written in gym bars
Conspiracy Theory Book Crossfire
Executive order 110
I first need to explain to you Public Law 280 8-36
Which is what the executive order eggs
To be a compliment
In 1961 President Kennedy realized
The demand for silver to be used in industrial industrial metal
With increasing at a rate
Then the prices enjoyed at
As a currency
Emerging Markets like microchips nuclear reactors
Medical applications of conductors world
Silver approximately 80 /
Percent drop in the United States
XS silver
Noticing
This could be a problem can be called on Congress to
Status of silver as a metal for which
There is an expanded industrial demand
Except for its using coins
Silver serves no useful monetary
I recommend authorization for the Federal Reserve System
The issue notes
In denominations of $1
So as to make possible the gradual withdrawal of silver certificate
From circulation
And the use of silver
Released from coinage
Purposes
Congress to take prompt action
So what do you think about
So
That's the quote
They used to
To say that he was trying to
Destroy the Fred
Used to urge Congress to enact
Public Law 88
Which
So if you
If you
Shut down silver
As occurring
Then
The Federal Reserve disappears
Nono Alakazam
This is just a coincidence
Isn't that
Response Congress passed hr5383
53 with large majority
Become public law 8836 effective
Repealing the Silver Purchase Act
Republiclaw 8836
The government
One of the element
Federal Reserve the authority to issue dollar bill
$1 bills were originally released in 1920
Change the silver dollar
The public law and the ensuing executive order
The Federal Reserve actually expanded its
Responsibility
As far as
Concerned
Aldi executive order did
Was the treasury Department to issue silver
In the interim
. while the transition
What's happening
Alex's. Relies on the idea that executive order 1110
Print money
The Federal Reserve
And give that power to
The treasury the closer look at the order itself
As well as the context
But that's the opposite of what it did
There's no way these acts
Could justify an argument that the Federal Reserve was mad at JFK about
It's complete
And this is going to
Frias
From having to deal with Alex
Quoting subsections
And it's all because of 1111
We have to name all bills
In binary
Okay so you can just stay the night
Whatever whatever
So you have to say it
What
110 00010001
Betrayal watch Revolution
Have you heard about HR one-woman 000 you can just be like
Trackdown
Really confused
Barcodes
Vietnam
The time he was in office.
People
I don't see that as a good argument and he says there is that he was trying to make real
Civil rights
I don't know
Somewhat but I don't know what real civil rights mean civil rights
It's a problem
Understand
What is Alex divinest Euro civil rights test
The right to vote or whatever it is
Real civil rights
Is making sure
Change
You can have
Fundamentally systemically racist states bordering
Statesville
Everyone like TiVo
The last time you had an actual
Was
Indecisive
Later Alex
Every president
Has been controlled by
So if
If you use those two
Give me like not controlled by
Definitely not Jews Banker
That's what he say
International finance auto parts
I think he's a charlatan
Princeton
Get a Fulbright scholarship to Italy and then get a PhD
Just
Without some sort of
That's possible
Next thing you know everyone's going to be posting messages call Webster Tarpley
Larry Nichols
You f****** nuts
Okay cool
I just think there's an interesting Dynamic going on where Webster Tarpley saying
In-N-Out is on Words later I guess
Coolidge
Was the last real president
Hooverwood
Ser don't know how to make
Like there should be some sort of like
I don't know how to
The talk or think about presidential history
Without
Thinking that centers on one
1 president
Right
That doesn't make any f****** sense at all and it doesn't even make sense if you take the entire picture of his
Which has to take into context the presidency before
Like you shouldn't be allowed to
Should have restricted access to history
Maybe
Pedaling
Talk about
Nixon expanded the Vietnam War
Channel in order to get reelected
He got hundreds of thousands upon
The people killed
People in the likes of Alex Jone
The intellectuals fear of his
His influences
Fortunately most of them supported George Wallace
It's not better
Good-news-bad-news
Yeah I think I think there is
Responsibility that
People like this
Call Ted
The last real president
What do you mean
What does that mean
Specificity
It's the same thing with saying that was Triple the federal government
You skate by on these
These are the vague Notions like
Are you trick a lot of people
Fraudulent narrative
I guess that's what I guess it's what you do when you call
Here's Jeff.
Also apparently
Burgerville
It has
Abraham Zapruder
The future US presidents
Back
And to the left John Fitzgerald Kennedy
Thanks for using this full metal name
Until the globalist removed from Power
You will never have another real one
Is a puppet
Puppet
Play pop it pop it
When he's obviously been chosen
Miami Subs
Krs-1
It's not just knowing.
It's so funny
You can't go from Webster Tarpley saying that Obama is giving
International Airport
Episode
Ksr1 I like that
6 or 78
Has been a strong voice
What makes
Now means nothing
Arms crossed on the brink of revolution
Does that mean
You know what
There is something of an argument to be made that
I mean had the financial crisis been allowed to
Growing
Depression that it could have become
Had we not
Stimulus package
Which somehow there again
Maybe you could have you could say you better make an argument
If elected it passes the same as unlikely
You don't like a puppet of the finance oligarchs
And whatever
To win
Then he would have passed the stimulus bill
Because that's what the globalist want them to do
The argument is so f****** stupid
Although although I do like his boy
If you
Hold on
With the the election of Obama and everybody kind of leaning back
Saying
Lead to the Republicans taking over literally every state government
The brink of a revolution
Self
Kara's ones better
Forecast
Password is writing songs
Really good at writing
Freestyle
The money
They give him the Buns
Fraud
The media whores
They give him going
Elected official
To put people in jail
Criticized
In public
All of this is the month of corgis
Oxymoron
More of a puppy
Even more of a
Is the maximum
Jimmy Carter
They put a black
Space from the new world Carter was a puppet I don't care
I honestly don't give a
Hey Jimmy Carter was a puppet
Peanut sauce
Peanut the puppet
Mr. puppet would be a wonderful
You don't say
Suppressor
Complex
It's cellphone by the International Bank
This is a very triangle heavy traffic right now
Power structure
System of world government
Pyramid around the globe
Alex is reporting that in
On the perfect
Graphic
This is a perfect
There is a graphic
When the app
Before this graphic came up Alex
Secret meeting David Rockefeller Define the New World Order
Shark special it raises the question
It should come as no surprise Abraham Lincoln
Recording or unofficial transcript
It comes from Daniel estulin
Respect someone told him
How did Rockefeller
We got deep into Daniel estulin sourcing problems back when we covered
And we learned
An expert on Bilderberg
Repetitive
All over again
Daniel estulin is full of s*** unless this quote
Be in any way since it's not
Worth thinking
Much like building a
Injury
In that clip
Alex said that it was the 1991 Bilderberg conference in Avion
The 1991 Bilderberg conference was in Baden-Baden Germany
To confer
Lebanon
Seems like you should know that
Yeah you know I'm detail normal documentary
I be like
Okay you f***** up
That happened
You should know
Documentary
F*** off
F****** Jew going to make an argument entirely based around the globalists and Bilderberg being the most horrible thing
I have specific information about that this Bilderberg conference
Yeah I can't get basic
Exact right
Fair enough
The secret conference is always where it was going to be the next
But the real conference
It's like it's like the Montreal
I will gladly switch locations for the beach
Go to warm up a boiled dumpling
National stuff
Being deliberately destroyed
After years of denial
The media and the elite themselves
Proudly announce
That not only
World government
What is the answer
To the financial crisis
Hey everybody is dead
Revolver
Today
Today is
First episode here
We got a cliffhanger
Did the media come out and Save
Is Alex.
Talking about something
Real or is it
Is yet another
Loadable s***
Documentary
Tomorrow 2
How much listening
Saweetie
Twitter app
Underscore
We are on face
Which is really wear a lot of
The real action goes on into
I'm really terrible at
Keeping
Facebook page
Can find us a run
Subscribe
It's the best way probably
What's up
The other place
Real bad at
Michelle hope you're enjoying it
Redwood back for part 2
Of The Obama Deception
Coverage
Tomorrow in
And it just gets
You're in juicier
By that
I lose
My patience with this.
As it goes on
Just doing a little
Bumper here
Has anybody to referee
I'm the only person
Anybody find a one guy who has
Technically
Theoretically it's guilt
And I forgot who goes by
Alex
In color