Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Voice you will be hearing
The structure of the show is
I know a lot about Alex Jones
In the world
You were joining us
Two of our in-depth
Exploration
Alex Jones
The 2009 documentary and heavy quotes
Documentary
If you are
Just randomly jumping
The first episode before this one
Because otherwise
Which is always a lot of fun
It's always fun to find those
Is it like
But where we left off in the last episode was
Was just about to
Introduce
Is proof the evidence
But he has
Vexed
New World Order was being announced
Media
Media in 2008
The new world order for all this.
So we'll jump right back into that in a second
Before we do that I want to take a second
Because this is the Thanksgiving weekend in the spirit of thinking
How do people who make this show possible our donors
Who are the
Rescue invest in the first place
Obama.
I thought I would take a little bit of time
Joined up with the team
We appreciate it very much so
So much
You are now
Someone sodomites
I don't want
The world today
Dust
And let's jump
To The Obama Deception part 2
And now
After years of denial
The media and the elite themselves
Are proudly announcing
That not only
World government
What is the answer
To the financial crisis
Alex is improving with a carefully engineered
We've talked about in some manner in the past
That all don't say what headlines
A chance for a new world order
The financial times for a world government
Like they're all
Just conversation
Isracann
Israeli News
Yeah
But they're all just people
Hoes like
Possibility of a global government
None of them are an announcement that the New World Order
Also
Alex
Dominis article say those things
Piazza in Obama's new world order
Prodo world
You're probably arguing that state solution
There should be killed or whatever
Suddenly
The Wall Street Journal
And the getting rid of
A dollar for a common currency with Canada
Chicago
This is an article a flashes up on screen to Titleist which is how realistic is North America
Concurrency we talked about this
The financial times of London
Published by a member of the Bilderberg Group
Tutorial world
Shadows
And that it was now time
From behind the curtain
National Security
This is an article from the financial times called it now for a world government it was written by a guy named Gideon rack
Like I said this one
It also sounds like
He's a British dude you know it's like that
Overworld
Trump's Secretary of Commerce Wilbur Ross
So did Lindsay
National Security advisor HR McMaster
Contra
I can find evidence of Gideon rackman
Is he number of times in
Capacity of the journal
Not as a
None of this proves that he's a member of anything
Publicly opposed to position
Such as strongly arguing against the idea of England getting mixed up in the euro
Do do something today all globalist therefore
Wouldn't he be on board
With ditching the pound in favor of the euro
Vociferously defended
Also
There's no such thing as being a member
The only membership category that exist is member of the steering
Membership
Steering committee is the group that plans
Meeting
Figures out like speakers
Cast of bunk'd
The rest of the attendees are
People who have
Prominent positions in business
The art
Industry dauberman
Diplomacy those Arts thing Mingle
That's
There isn't a member
Conspiracy blogs
I was like
$400 a night Hotel
Coffee
Ice cream truck
200 dollar a night Hotel
Absurd restaurant
Glorified
Work retreat
Conference
Yeah
Team building event
Interested
Diplomacy
Apple
This means nothing
You never one
A serious crisis
Go to Waze
You think you could not do before
Absurdly misused quote
And Henry Kissinger gave lockbox
National Television
Economic collapse was a great opportunity
Bring in the New World Order
You went on to say that Barack Obama was
Perfect
Sell it to the world
Images
Do American foreign policy
Probably because
Silly
Hypnotize
Could be to develop an overall
Strategy for the medic
Pick it up Grandpa
.
Attracted
Because
First of all
You could describe them as people who are interested in
Guava
It integration it's not like a dirty word
Then for them generally speaking New World Order
The intersection of
The Illuminati
The world order
500 New World Order
There's this whole situation every new world
B b Ops
Password
Trump created a new world order
Trending towards progress
Always looking
Towards
Cooperation
And
Wars
You're always
Working towards a new
Influenza
Something better
Something
People that kissing
Used
New Order of the world
A new ordering
Evil or suspicious
Weird that he says
Like
Yeah.
Flashlight
Kissinger
You're either hated because
It's either you think you should go there cuz you're right
I don't care about the ethical implications of Kissinger's actions or anything like that right
Cherry into the side of them
Absolutely
Occidental College
It's for his freshman and sophomore years
Disagree
Graduating in 90
His first job out of college was business international corporation
Enrico's
You latched onto this job
Because
77 Elliott
The company's founders
New York Times it is father's use the company provide for CIA agents cover
Between 1955 and
Even if we assume the information that's coming
Still has not approved
412 company into fake company
Publicnews
Conferences
During the Cold War companies that clandestine
Business
Many businesses
To help hide their spots
What are the reasons
Journalism
Publishing
Is it journalist ever reason to be in a foreign country that doesn't raise suspicion
As far as the facts go that's about as nefarious as business International
From everything I can
Until that is
The rest
Provide cover
Doesn't doesn't mean that
Didn't stop
When Cold War
It doesn't mean that everybody who work there were CIA
Any of these
Also his
Obama has
Would never work for
For a cert
Classic
There is no
There is no limit like
Because look at conspiracy theory and trying to figure out like little things and then
YouTube your conspiracy theory
Interconnection here nope
Anyway
Did I miss anything
Do I miss do you miss endgame
No
That is basically just
Old automobile
On the shadow government agenda
Cars from
Lower the budget
Best-selling author Daniel Escobar
16 m
Is mold formed
But the elite
Unimaginable in 2006
I want
But they were planning to
The price of
150m
We know from list
To Alex the show
That one friend Lindsey Williams
Is the person that Alex has told him that the globalist plan to raise the guy
Gas price of exact
Adventure
Why is now in The Obama Deception
Further in all of his appearances on the show Lindsey Williams
This really credible guy Lindsey Williams
The defense exactly what you're saying
Why not that's weird cuz he doesn't have
Lindsay outside of the
No but he could still beat
William
Said exactly stories lineup
Placated we've got b roll
Rowlett
He may have been hiding and Daniel estulin
That's true
No it's banana
I know I don't want to talk about it Daniel estulin
Except to say that
The rest of the stuff Daniel estulin
Is just
You would
No
If you followed
Like none of none of it
It got up to
Something like that
And then with the eye
Follow trend
Like Gerald
If you if you had a decent awareness you would know a lot of
None of it has to come from
Secret
Sources from the evidence presented
It so far is that
Documentary
No that doesn't say what you said does
Yeah
Even if the thing that you were lying about was true
Live
You also
Reported that after sucker in the middle class back into the stock
The group
Was going to inflow the subprime mortgage Market
And destroyed
New weapons
Oh well
How to draw things that make a prediction that you can't backup
Mortgage
Crisis
Remember that movie like it was it like
If you followed the new 12's
You would know that there were a lot of concern
You know we getting
From this morning
Severe damage
This is Daniel estulin sitting in a bar
To the camera
Jim Tucker
For the express purpose of
Public opinion
Come on
The afternoon
4 + 30
You're talking about
This is one of the American delegates
I wasn't
Interesting to watch Daniel estulin information that he already knows
It's sort of improvised a storyline
Fit2me indicates creativity there's a creative thinking process
You telling
If you was reporting from what somebody
Or something like that
Journalist Rick what
Space Commander
Like a waiter rating
Intuit
And when I get my news I want creative interpretation
Literally
You may be being influence
In part by the
Now that I see Daniel estulin again
He looks
It is
Holding his hands and could see him having a card pulp right now
Like he's a magician
This your new world order
But everything is going well so what they going to do over the next year-and-a-half
Backup to 1998
DVD copy of the
Navigate to Detroit economy
When people don't travel at least that's what they say
When people don't travel
When people don't have money they don't travel
Oil
No conversation
Weather
Running out of
So you have to sort
I bet
Bicycle
People double together going to be back
S21
Pacifica
Those guys
British guy in the 50s
It looks
Copy of his book
True story
The Bilderberg Club
Is that is the book
That
Able to report on future events with stunning because they know the agenda
The waterpark
125 of the richest and most influential individuals on the globe
When I go tanning
I had to type such mixed feel
Like sincerely makes me up
The first was missing
What the f***
God
I love it
From Istanbul Turkey Chantilly Virginia
Bilderberg always
By June of 2008
We'd already figured out
That Barack Obama
Choice
4th 2008 Democratic primary
Primary primary
Republican
Like
It made me
Nervous
Because I
Doll houses
This might not
Homework you might end up seeing a lot of
Come out
Even at that time
I'm scared of
Because
Ww's presidency was
Is that somehow
Despite the fact that people don't want a republican in there
Yeah it is it is
You take the rough with the smooth
Destroying the entire world
Just real quick
I need to drive home
You knew
Predictive or like you're a psychic
You knew in
June 2008 that Obama
F*** you right off
0 support ND
Wendy
He was the puppy
Good work guys
Congratulations
Gerald Celente powers
National media claimed
The during the weekend the Bilderberg Group
Schedule
Speaking
Set for Chicago in the Midwest
Classic bait-and-switch
To get on Obama's campaign plane
And the Obama would join them
On the flight to Chicago
Campaign staff
Then slam the door shut
The farming president Shanghai
As Obama's campaign aircraft lifted off
Without
Alex would laugh his ass off.
Depressed guy on the plane Target
Remember this
We had a desire
Mother's Day
Enterprise
We set up these me
Score
Obama
Like
Like it was some sort of evil nefarious plan
Terrible thing
Eerily like
I'm sorry I got to go to the bathroom
Journalism
This smart
Sort of ockham
Explanation
Is that
Obama and Hillary
Because the primary kind of role might have
Any Administration that sort of thing around
Which I understand I think that's a little bit Shady
I don't think
Suggest that they were both
Rat
They did
In order for him to get to Bilderberg
Where was Build-A-Bear
How is your day
There's no evidence
Pictures
Who's there
He was there he has no
The records don't show
Absolutely
They shouldn't done but
I think it's just sort of like
Something I'm noticing right now
Is this is a terrible 20 you back not even like us
All the lies and all the b*******
This is a documentary
Why I hate during preparation
There's so many things
You down
Or just like
How do I prove
There's things like this worth
Nocuous explanation for this but you're never going to
To accept it
That's pretty funny
If he wasn't having a prefer if he was just like
I need a night off I'm going to go hang out with Michelle
Play for laughs
Is it afterwards he sends them like an edible
I wasn't going to Chicago
Obama's spokesman denied
Confirm player the former rivals
He also
Keep in mind right there it says former rival
The primary
Literally say good day max
Discussion
Trying to find out where Obama
The corporate press had to admit they had no idea
They work anymore
Embody the time that the two of them were still in the running
Already one
The denomination
And the reason for that is
And then the world leads to
Exactly
At the time they were chosen
World Cup games
Because if you Obama had already won the nomination
Beforehand
Choosing
He won based on the boat
So can you try
Maintain that facade throughout the
This entire document
Bulshit
Clinton and Obama aren't talking
Funny sources knew about this meeting
Told others that it was at Hillary Clinton's house with Philly
And it wasn't
Westfield Marriott Hotel
Outside
Yolanda bullhorns no matter what
None
Like like no
We went to this Marriott
Series of breadcrumbs
Also remember that episode in 2008
Where Alex
Was getting ready to go to
I want to find that episode
In Washington DC for driving to westfields Marriott tomorrow the hotels close
Throughout the week
He looks so much more healthy
Disgusting
He looks like he looks like a rough
Yes.
But not like
Yeah
Forget it
Beyond critiques of his physical
Jesus
The night time we're going to go check or whatever
355 agency CIA intelligence Mossad
Whatever
Forty-Eight Hours before Hotel guests
The annual meeting
We're no longer
Reserved
Pick us up tomorrow
Cuz of the
Forty-Eight Hours before
What is
Okay
Reserve the room at a hotel for a week
Like technically I suppose you could say at the end of that week
Kicked me out
Yeah used to do that
Login to my reservation
For the rooms
There's a private party
Kind of but
Guess you would have liked to stay longer but
By the way
This is going to happen
The building was Nestle
Open the heart
The military-industrial
National reconnaissance office
Just a stone's throw away
Looking at b roll
There's a nice hotel
That's a pretty solid breakfast
Security
Getting there
Some footage
Riding in the morning be summarized
And I'm getting out
Call
RadioShack
Call Lisa
George
We're sitting here
I'm not going to settle
I'm not saying that it's not a good idea.
Set up
Shut up
Open the door I want to hear the fire
Open the door
I want people to hear this
People listening
Georgie hear that
Marriott
Right outside
The Flash
Everybody
Goldbergs
Yyyy
Shoppers
Virgo
What
Questioning
Another hotel
Caucus
Fire drill
Moana
The moments I'm way
The alarm goes off
It's going off right now
Put the shirts say
Over 100
Today
Total ghost
This is what
We have a security
Batman Legos
There's a shop
Of the artworks
Fire alarm
I forgot that part.
Credible
Coasttocoastam
Ostensibly
Fire alarm started
Is the phone rang but
What is the we just saw there
Start in media res with the called fire alarm
His track record
When he started making the call or when
Is deficient number one
Number to House of fire alarm
Globalist
How in control are the globalist really
Pressure a goddamn Hotel manager
I want to the backup Hotel
No footage anywhere to be found
Weird
What kind of setup to make fire alarm
Soccer
He has no shortage of that
Security guard
Nope
Based on his own description
We were filming at that
You would think there would be a piece of cake
I know you would still have the footage of someone off camera
Credibility to your story Alex Jones
Needs to put that in or else
Also
If I rent a hotel
Add Alex Jones
Haley have him followed around
Pornos pornos like nefarious reason so much as like hey I just need people to follow you around
Because you have a long and varied history of f****** with people and
Could you please don't f*** with me
Yeah
My assessment
Yeah like in Prosper
Like I said nothing but because the Marriott is just a normal or not
So when he got on the phone with George Noory 02 report
We walked around we saw some art
That's about it
There's nothing appearance on Coast to Coast AM
Maybe by coincidence a fire alarm
Maybe one of Alex's group old
But whatever the case now Alex has the ingredients
Now we can portray himself as the brave reporters out there is life is in Peril who's also the victim
Have a grand
Conspiracy
A fire alarm
So now
I know the audio of the next day's episode of Coast to Coast AM
Where Alex is
Story starts to change
Paris River
We just heard
From Alex's at game
Obama Deception documentaries
What we heard is a story about a
Guard coming up
He's trying to take pictures
Furby role is trying to create
Is the artwork
Now what have you now let's hear what he says the next day on coasttocoastam
Eaton DC area the Bilderberg conference
It was supposed to get underway today
Let's check in with our own Alex Jones
George I am and thank God that you're having me on the show because we're in a lot of danger and I've never said this before even when I was detained 215
Hours in Canada
Large commercial mainstream show
A no one notice papers nothing is covering it like your radio show the 15 million listeners and then my
Baller News website infowars.com in prison
Wired.com
Is there any
Right
3 minutes before you went to me
Like when you called an alarm went off fire alarm
And walking up 10 minutes before
Before
Places thank you
Waiting on hold Tom call to produce their right as
The alarm went off
I'm thinking what's going on I didn't film Channel crew in there filming all of this
Happening
Fire alarm is going off everything's crazy
And
Earliest wildfire
We go downstairs working out there with over 200 people
We are going to f
You up
And
Then they said that goes for you Alec and you raw from under my name
Unknown
Marine coming in
Here therefore
We have the evolution of a
This narrative
Yeah something about fire alarms and security guard
1 calories in Arena security guard
Conspiracy
Which is desperate
Yeah a little bit in the beginning of the
That's not good
With George
The alarms going off
He finished his interview with George
Alex
Footage of them leaving
For the fire alarm
Venomous.
There's a fire truck
Also
OtterBox
Being outside
Nope
Is it
Engine so now we're on to the next morning
They had footage
Multiple cameras
It's all that is true
They would have the camera down and use the audio then
You can still do that
Also
If it is a scheduled fired
I don't know if it was
Fire
Usually doesn't
That's not really but if it is
Bro
Midnight fire drill
Hotel
What is more like one pulled the alarm
Pulled the fire alarm in order to specifically
Because he was going to leave anyway doesn't scare any
Did that
All they've done is handout
Silver platter
To use to pretend he's a Preston evicted
Yeah
Rob Jacob
Smoking Gun
Back
I didn't know used to run security
They have checked out of the hotel and they're
Sing like they're running out of
Alright we paid her bill
What time does follow
If you
This is clearly a silver
Later they will pretend that it is the same thing as clearly
Bluish green car
I don't believe it
It's the same car
So far no evidence of swallowing
Alex has
Camera going in his car turns that were taken by this car
It is just Alex
You followed us 45 turns or whatever
Gotcha
Southwestern Grill
This isn't true everything they're being followed
Credible as a tail
Credible as a
Almost as if he has no idea
Seafood
0 man this is now
This is I was trying to create some sort of narrative
I believe there's a world
Where
I don't know how far away that is from the Marriott
If he was being followed
He had multiple cameras in the car
They would have footage of all of that
Argument
It blew
Look-back or anyting
Nope
The next stretch
This documentary
This stretch is meaningless
Covers
About 25
Top
Cars appearing
2.5 + 2.75
This is a meeting that happen
Like
They were in the car
It was like okay so I'm going to take a bullhorn out
Rob you is right there next to
You pull up are you f******
How much more powerful it is
You see how far away
Like
Cover that distance to 1 bullhorn a******
Still no one
Look like a Wawa
Probably interfere with each other and it makes the sound
Find secret service
07 Convoy
And internal sources confirm
1 m
Inside
The conference internal sources confirm that Obama and Hillary attended one
That's not
There's no evidence that they were there that the official
The record doesn't show that they were there is no proof they were there
He doesn't have any footage of Obama or Hillary being there
There's nothing
It's just Daniel
While the Bilderberg Group was a hundred percent successful
H-E-B near me
During the event
Angie newworldorder protest
Alternative media
Circle bar Hotel
Stripes
Call Asurion.
Behind the main players and we are James
Ron Paul campaign
I wanted to talk a lot about
I looked
And I'm in a lot of the claims that are made about him
Tons of money
We are
Because of the never-was charge
I don't know enough about it
So I'm going to punt on Luke rudowski
We're not
If you resign
Yeah you got them
Obama we know you're
I don't know who this lady is
Cheapest nice
Purchase a DVD copy of The Obama Deception has a scroll that keeps going under the video
Came from
United States
The main conference call
Close range
As the global power Brokers
And that's all
Every
This is still happening
This is
Are they
Everything that's like the people are coming together to stop them
What is a population
Policies being developed over by powerful special interest
The people will revolt
Detective
A picture
For federal official
World
Sun federal workers
Jim Tucker
Walking through the lobby of a hotel
Nasatal
Also is misrepresenting.
Every
Right
Show up
If they always do
Open Alexa
Pretending
Officials from other country
Discuss
Truth
This is my favorite shot
By the pool hat
Any suspenders
Like
Distort of young guy is in a he's the guy who's like
A muscle
Who's like IMDb
This Old Man
Telling looks like
Something out of a bad movie
Teeth movie
The silly hat on top of it like
Tucker Leonard
Protagonist
4 hours
What's important is that while there is so much metaphorically there
Some people go bowling on the weekend these guys protest
And every newspaper
Every broadcast
Exposed
Eagle Lake
You write for publication that was created
The media has their obligation obligation
Alright
One second
Still shot that they showed before
Which was
I think it was Hillary
And they had it
Hillary was looking at Obama with kind of like this
F*** you
The only thing I could think during that though is
To pull off an earring
I really think you should get an earring now that he's out of office
You should really f****** go for
Where the flag for a while and everyone and everyone was mad at him
Remember those times
Obviously
Bilderberg
Trilateral Commission
Found it
The Carter Administration
Charter
We're all members
The trilateral commission
Sensation public
Professor Griff
Davis's View
I truly believe
Imperialism
In order to get this interview Alex
Black nationalism
He was a friend of Professor Griff
Thought you called into the show
I don't think Alex is even there
Professor Griff
Documentary for Alex
Political opinion
Is not an integral
Member of
I would do it all
Listen to wrestle with
Documentary
The deck
Facelift
And the reason I believe
Simply because
They're trying to go into a pool that already in a
Yelp
Totally control
Oh really never heard of white people
23rd century
Did they have to go through a phase
Galvanized
The map
Dark skin people
They truly believe
That chain
People
For them
Little man on total
Agenda
Have the right tile on
Have the right smile
Prisonplanet.com
Where is Professor Griff Colonial powers
One world government or a black president the United States
Forever
Well considering what the British
Congo for Ivory rubber
I don't think they were
The concept of an a
African Union besides possible idea
Colonialism is already inflicted on the Cotton
No
Professor Griff
Expressing a dumb idea
Couple hundred
I don't think he's a real
Professor
WhatsApp
Schlitz Wilford Brimley
Hahaha
Even worse nonsense then professor professorship
Terrific of Professor
No doubt about that
But
Professor Griff
Instead we know
Thick off hands
It was for that sort of behavior
Media media interview with British publication
The white race or Caucasian race came from the Caucasus Mountain
He was not
The pyramid
The Jews can't even build houses
How the hell did they build the pyramids
Finally
How big is the Palestinians
Not great
Problem
I'm not for that one
Just killed all the Jews
I don't think
Be alright
Don't think
He is
Everything was a okay for a bit
Professor Griff bio writer for
Improve
Chucky
The song Fight the Power in his movie do the right thing
Add Public Enemy
Commodities
Unfortunately
Professor Griff
Jews are responsible for the majority of the wickedness
That goes on around the globe
Most people remember
He went on a full-on antisymmetric
Henry Ford's book The International Jew as a store
You bet
Little Hitman
Concluded
Because if he wasn't
Who owns CBS
Have stents forced him out of the group of the five Juventus to hold us back
Working title
Tired
Minister of information
You know what you could still be a representative in Iowa
Twenty years later Professor Griff wrote a book called analytics failed analy
T.i.
Love it where you gave this rambling explanation for his Acts
Just say the Jews are responsible for the majority of wickedness
I'm not the best nowhere God
To know who's at the Crux of all the problems in the world that's not correct
I don't know
Now you can't believe me
Is the different time
People through people
It doesn't really matter because he pretended to be sorry and you made a visit to the Holocaust Museum kind of blow over with
Exceptional
For the wickedness,
Reinstall
LeBron James
You know what
I'm going to put that low on my list of things
Bad about the Rock
I'm not here to talk about the hall
That's not even in the top ten worst things about the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
Systemic problem
Louis Farrakhan
Espouses deeply auntie
The archetype of a
Black racist to Alex complaints
Who is team right now I guess he's the one who also believes of the New World Order
Very clearly thinks it's
Don't want to talk about that
Weddings 1964
Senator Barry Goldwater said
The trilateral commission
Of the commercial and banking
The trilateral commission represent
Disease Control
Consolidate the four centers of power
Monitor
Intellectual
Trilateral Commission
Worldwide economic power
Superior
As managers and creators of the system
Future
That they just showed what is essentially the Globe Theatre
Goldwater
I don't really care
From Arizona
Batshit crazy
Born the son of parents who owned a department store called cold water
Which you would go on to take over after his father's death
Estimated
Million dollars a year as of 1940
Would you be 17 billion dollars
In present day
Doing alright dude pretty good in the 40
Interest
Weird conservatism
Flying airplane
And that
Wsn
I skipped over something
I forgot the Goldwater started a national fad
Which were just men's underwear with big red ants
Alright
As of now
I am fine with berries
Perhaps
Already
Here's the new deal for that reason and had prior to
Arizona
To work state
Bran Floyds didn't
Wheelwright
In 1963 Barry was a vociferous
Did Barry the Republican nomination
A president in 1964
How things change
President Eisenhower
It is now or we would never allow this kind of behavior
Pb2
Where you said that we should be using nuclear
Justice liberally
He went on to suggest that
Without the approval of the president
Even with the president
I love how stupid
Tactical nukes
Dislike
Like still going to take down
30000 miles out
Which is very rare we should kill terrorists
We voted
Never allow somebody who says
He says things like that a fact magazine printed an article called
The unconscious of a conservative
Special issue in the
Play on his book Tekonsha
Article the writer said that personality
The Goldwater rule
Public personality
Oh sorry
At this point Barry Goldwater was also running a ham radio station out of
So how did he lose
And was running a ham radio station out of his house while he was at the office
68 presidential campaign
Like I mentioned earlier lot of Alex's other ideological ancestors
Preferably on board with segregate
I don't know what to make of Barry's involved
But I should also tell you that in 1976 Goldwater was inducted into the International Swimming Hall of Fame
You know
What guys like Goldwater you never hear the paws
The 1968
Goldwater finally retired from the Sun
Endorsed
George h.w. Bush
For president which is another weird choice for the people in this world
Bush's father Prescott
Actual Nazi collaborator
Prescott Bush
Between him and John McCain about like
If I was in charge you never would have been to that annoy Hilton
You never would have never
If I had been in charge
You're right
I would have been a prisoner aboard the China
Nice mechanic
93 year old man
Barry Goldwater advocate
For the creation of laws
Protect homosexual
Discrimination
Supported the right of homosexuals to openly serve in the military
All of it
Because he found out his grandson
Even though
He had previously
Vociferous
All those sorts of things
He encouraged Federal legislation
The principal positions evaporate
Me personally
Would have made a
Look in the 60s
Yeah but if his if his kid was gay in the 60s
While he was in office
He still living
Facebook
Call daughter.
Colorado River
Scattered of the Colorado
The Colorado River is a Fitting Place for his ashes because I forgot to tell you that
First person on record to ever travel.
I'll be on that he also is like responsible for a lot of his stupid anti-communist propaganda
Rest in peace Barry Goldwater
You crazy sonofabitch
Bilderberg issues executive decision
Prime directive
Do it subbed
For implementation
The trial
He just said I don't know I didn't understand how those Vine
Relation to each other
No outside
And executes its
Serves as the managing Roundtable
This is an attempt to explain
Council on Foreign Relations
Has dominated every Administration
Since the days of f.d.r.
Alex's
Everybody
In control
Eva
See that's a problem
Makes it to be controlled
Freeze the last real president
Ulta
President
Also
Man
F******
Payment office in 1932
Implies that there was a good 11
Weather
We can't do that yet
They came together as an evil group took him 11 years
To be able to
Test runs and then you're ready
Catering setup
Jordan was elected in 2019
T20
Employee
Piano
He had yet
Spell Kool-Aid
Coolidge was famous for being a shity
Text back then
Coolidge
In charge
Rich a
I mean I guess that's probably
Robert is a small governor
Conservative
This was entirely into laissez-faire International politics
Coolidge
Set up
Missions for the Great Depression
And then hurt
Cover for hardywood
24/3
Goodbye
Calvin Coolidge laissez-faire
Small government type
7:36
Hoover wins in 1928
Use federal funding to help
With the increasing problem alright
I don't know I'm just
Orchestrated that
The crisis
It's necessary
To do the s*** that they wanted
Which was elected fpr in order to create
40 years old
The interest of the bankers
I mean
The reason we ended up not
Financial crash
Between
The Great depresh
Is that was regulation
CFR in the globalist
I don't understand
No the only thing that makes sense is everything that Alex says
Eccentric
Oligarchy
Remember this is not that meaning marry multiple people
Bankers rule
And the banker set up these
Tution
Set up
Model.
Royal Inn
Bears
Chatham House
Round Table
The. Right after
The boardwalk
Alright done that
From misrepresentations of
Pause this
Little bit
After Alex Rambles about the CFR
Pronoun reference
Dictate
These are isn't run by
Priest bureaucrats
Cfr's membership rolls are
Public
Just a few names you might recognize
Who are Council on Foreign Relations members who are not bankers
Colin Powell
Jimmy Carter
George Clooney
Jesse Dylan
Priscilla Presley
Ted Cruz
Carl Sagan course let's not forget good buddy and manners coach
Steve pieczenik
These are all people who remembers or have been members of Council on Foreign Relations
Something is Ron by Bankers there's like
There's thousands
Members of the Council on Foreign Relations
Orange Finance
If
Some of them are General
The entire list
Before World War 1
And this is how they make
Call lissy
Upon Obama's inauguration
Members of the Bilderberg Group
Trilateral Commission
Ncfr
Every position of power
Replacing
Trilateral commission and CFR memo
Previously filled the positions during the bush
As I said earlier there's no such thing as a member of the Builder
As much as
Remember the steering
Alex is playing
Members of his cabinet
Susan Rice
Any relation with
Right
The trilateral commission there's a number of people who were
Republic Service
Condoleezza Rice
Obama came in there were five
Another
It doesn't
I don't know
No
Weird paranoia
When you look at that
Us ruling class
How to say disabled
Pathetic
And bunglers get their ass
Problems we have
Is you
Obama
What's
The order
These orders are
Wrongheaded
To say the least there are basic
Citibank
Civilization
Using the
Existence of the United
Act out there
Wallstreetbets
Their capital
Structures in maintaining
Take it back from me
You got to drive Wall Street
You have a reason
Getting back to prosperity and some kind of peace and order in international
She has a kernel of like
Yeah
It
Take It Outside of the conspiratorial exact sort of
Offer any foundflix
Real solutions to anything
Netflix
That's the whole point
The plan is to make the problem seem so insurmountable
There's no point in doing it
Paralyzed
If you deal with the reality of the awfulness of it of like
Look
Over everything that they should
We don't need to take our country back
We should still have some influence
That part of our f******
Consistent
Yeah it's super unsatisfying
Sometimes
Hey all these Bankers should have no fun
Control over anything we should
You do have to make
Compromises
Do I will save it
There are things that sometimes
To work towards the greater good of everybody
You have to say like
I don't want to do that but
Alex Jones Infowars
Who is this
Mullet
Knock knock
Documentary
Got a chance to speak with Economist and author
Power elite
You're f****** Amber
Of their Club
Unless you are multi
Billionaire
And friends this is not about
Rich vs
Spore
This is about a very
Very
Small handful
Criminal element on this planet
Fine
George Humphreys
Credentials
Hayirli made up
He called himself
Credit I found a graduate from University of Houston
Degree in economics in nineteen
Foundations of Education
You don't want to move to Austin
Renovation
Company operation
Pink store
Weird weird
I don't know what stretches
No idea
From 1980 to 1990 Humphrey served on the Austin city council
After losing a re-election bid in 1990 and founded
Production
Companies that witch
That much as anybody who
Who has that many
Instead of
Entrepreneurship
Hiding money from the IRS
Import business in Austin
There's not a lot on the
From where
It's not like there's Docs
Look if I go to my hometown
Important
Chicago
You have proven yourself corrected myself wrong
Call of Duty George Humphrey
Books I can really find on Amazon written by George
Ireland
George Humphrey
So
If I can find no real evidence that he is a published author
There is one book that looks like
Music
Companion book
It goes along
911 the great illusion in Game of the Illuminati?
Subtitles
Amazon there's a review on Amazon
Was an inside job
Factual inaccuracies
He got the flight number
What's the name of the CIA director on 9/11
Without a doubt one of the
Worst 911 DVDs out there
Factual inaccuracies.
The 2005
Only to get a rude letter of scorn and response
That's what I
Powers are actually still standing right now
The Austin city council
Weird business history
Film production companies
I can't figure out what's going on with it
Bad 911.
My perfect resume
Perfect Alex Jones
To be somebody's dad in the 6th
It looks
Haribol
He looks like he has a normal haircut emerging from the batter
He's really into people's appearance
Because it's 99% audio
I never get to criticize people
I can see what all these assholes look like
Fairborn
Fair enough
Manipulating
And destroying
The good people of this nation
World
Look at the people he's
Put in
Larry
Strawberry I love it
Every time they talk about Larry
Strawberries
Is another
Really it's one
Think of YouTube
It was put in place in the
1930s
So thanks
In the 1990s
Real quick
Conflicted feeling
Larry Summers Lawrence Summers
He absolutely
Metal and helping
Apart
Regulations of
Working concert
Write multiple
Variety
Institution
But he also after-the-fact
Realize that he's f***** up
But he did say
How's that
I shouldn't have done that we were
We're working on the wrong kind of information
He paraphrased John Maynard Keynes when he said about it when circumstances change
Switch to me does
Someone who has wrestled with
But he was a big part of helping
End up
Fixing the problem
Hero story at all
Alright
You did
After the fact
You were a part of helping
Look because
Generally speaking our elected officials are not
Intellectual
Powerhouses that we might want them
So there is he's got a massive
Very very smart
And finding the little places where he's
Vulnerable and convincing him otherwise
I get that
Then happen
You at the beginning of the derivatives bubble
Thanks to people like Alex.
In the Obama
Administration
Entire problem
Today
The same people
I don't know they seem to shift around on top of quick
Complicated
Fairly correct
Deregulation of
The derivatives Market
Did he played a very big party
And what happened
I think that's fair
What you think
Regulations
I don't really know what to say
If a deregulated derivatives Market is the cause of all these problems
Then wouldn't it stand to reason
Solution
Would you say you're not allowed
Massive regulation I don't know more regulations
You're not allowed to do this bylaw
My boy
I kind of agree with tarpleys analysis that this is a big part of the problem
But I don't know what his solution to that problem is because
So I don't know how much I can go on board with
Prescribed that you can recognize a problem
Ideologically opposed to
But using can't prescribe
So you can only record
We have the US
Treasury
Protege
Uncle Larry's glass-steagall
Caught the regulation
Prohibited
The banks
He was a side are you on
New York State
As we all know
Federal Reserve
Federalist
That I don't understand
Catchphrase the Federal Reserve Academy
Propagandist of catchy
Gucci Mane
Complicated but very important to understand
The nature of the Federal Reserve
As we go forward in
In this documentary
Reserved
It's not a private bank
It's a public bank that holds private
To understand exactly what the issue is here it's essential that we understand what the structure
The Federal Bank
Federal Reserve actually looks
The Federal Reserve is run by their board
Governor's each of whom is appointed by the president of the United States
Score
They served
Thank you be reappointed or knots on a very basic level they're accountable to
The government
It's not
A feature of
Any private company
In this
Did they would have that sort of stuff
Don't you remember how the president
It's a it's a private business
Confirm
Each of the 12 Federal
Terrible AR
Federal reserve banks
Commercial Bank
Basically their stockholders
Any Federal Reserve
According to invest
Expedia
Distinction to make
Is that while these member banks are considered owners of
Member Bank
Amir Federal Reserve
But
Investment is fixed at 6
Percent
It can't be higher than that
Oh s*** that's a good idea
Furthermore
May not pledged as collateral for loan
He specifically held there
The Board of Governors and the Federal Open Market
The Federal Reserve
The seven people appointed by the president
Confirm
The open market
Is made up of the same seven board members
In five of the heads
The 12 Federal Reserve
In essence the balance
Power always
Governors
Who can outvote
The heads of the Regional Bank
If there is a friction
Infowars report
Respond
So also the Federal Reserve Bank
Don't rely on tax dollars
Interest interest
Depository
However
They can't really make that much money because quote any except burning must
Be transferred to
The US Treasury
The reserve bank's amounted to about 35.5 bill
Billion dollars of which 31.79% was transferred
The US Treasury
That again
It does not exist with any other private for
Prophet
Essentially
It is for prop
Yeah
Impress
The 80s or 4 price
Yes
They can't make a profit
Isn't
Transfer to
Skated why this
Exist in the structure that it does
Hate the fat
Because while you're explaining to do I'm going through this and I'm like
Okay
But there's a part of me in the back of my head it's like
I want to stop listening to you now
This is Aiden
Massively complicated system
Easy to understand if you actually look at it
It's not that hard to understand
If you look at it through the prism of a solely private or public
Private-public
Business also the Federal Reserve is subject
Exhausted
Government over
Is the government accountability office
Conducted multiple reviews of their operations
Every year
And every year an outside unbiased select the office of the Inspector General
Does an audit of all the
General actually isn't
Spectra deck right now
That is true
I'm trying to find a way to reference the fact that he and I both have a cross eye and I'm excited about it.
Battery
Picture of anything that you would ever see you in private
Yeah it exist
Because of the private-public
Intersection of court
All of this is to say that no
The Federal Reserve
Is substantially
More Federal than Federal
This is just a propaganda catchphrase that allows people to
Impressionable people
You don't understand.
Complexity of
Public-private
The Federal Reserve
Weight function
If it were to be entirely private
The bank would have no reason to act
Complete
A plunder the f***
Country
If it were entirely public Federal Reserve System
Compromise way too easily by a president or political party
Exact
And when properly regulated
Appropriate oversight applied
It does work
Pretty well
But unfortunately
Entirely private business
The worry of that is that they will start acting with
Impunity and not in the pub
And that's what we see
That's why
Really negative effect
Without
Regulation
Is essentially a
Pirate
Enterprise there's no reason for them not to
Company
When you when you get down to
Unfettered
Pure capitalism
They will travel around the world
And pillage and plunder
F*** if they won't kill
Responsible for setting like interest
Something else like that
It has to be a political
Because otherwise it could be at the whim of
And that's why that power has to be slightly external 2D like Treasury Department
Say hey treasury secretary inflate the economy
For instance violation of
Federal Reserve interest rate
Is there a
Fear if it were a holy
Public
Institution
Like I understand why people hate
I do
Why some people are uncomfortable
Because it does seem like
Like
Regulation and oversight
Required
Fortify
Absolutely
But I don't like
The complaints that Alex Jones makes about it
We can look into what they say and how it works
It's not true
Like at 8
They're just lying about it
To demonize it
There are real complaints
Complained that means to me your argument
This week
And it's the same reason people hate
F******
Calculus
Like
Trying to understand it makes you
Picture that I
Because
Connection yourself
Text
And then the whole puzzle starts to come into shape
Used apps like
The second page of Google
I would even argue
Never go to the second page
Then of course
Cuz it's hard to understand
Call Yaya
Vigilant as you can
There are so many opposing forces within our government
How many times have we seen
The Fed
Regulated more and then regulated
Send that whole thing
To the feds
Federal reserve's website
I was really hoping that you would so totally surprised we was like
By the way
That was made
Great things to say about the website
It's really awesome
It's navigate
So much information
Balance
Literally audit yourself
Right now
Well I mean
Fit Physical Therapy Colorado
You can track trends
From here on out here is the simplest thing
Somebody says like
The Fed
You just ask
Have you been to their website
Whatever question you may have
It's not sure proves they're not
Evil
Good or evil at this
I'm just asking
Have you been to their website
Because if you haven't but you don't know all that information
I have a conversation where you have
Federal Reserve
A very important service
To arconic
I mean
Historically
How many massive crash
Do we have
Right
I go into Alex Jones
Documentaries
If you have an argument that
Specific
I'm willing to listen
Lincoln Escape
Gerald 28 Federal is Federal Express
You something I can look into
I looked into it and I thought oh my God it is entirely private
Holyshit
Give me head entirely private
For-profit company that would interest rate
And all the other big financial responsibilities that they have
Do you like
Especially since we talked
Is not true
Boy
Anyway
Everybody
For today
Said I believe
I think I don't know
Tobias
Information
Always love to tell people about how Barry Goldwater created
That's always doing this documentary
And that was the only thing I got to tell people about
I think it would be worth it
Just to tell you about
The weird
Weird life the Barry Goldwater live
But
The Glimpse
Just how wrong
Alex is on a fundamental level
Just about one of his biggest issue
Visa V the Federal Reserve in whether or not it's
Our private
Should I
Very important for us to all
Carry with us
When we understand that
What is the
Jones's beliefs
And when you realize that that is what's up
It's something that is a fundamental
Elementary misunderstanding
Things look a little Saturday
Back tomorrow with part 3
I bought that for now
Also
Twitter tattoo
Knowledge underscore fight we are on
We have a group called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Which is a lot of fun people post
Stop
Talk about nonsense and if you'd like to join
Please. Come on over the water is okay
Be great if you could
Believer is you all that good stuff maybe recommend
Your peeps
Word-of-mouth is the best way to spread
Recommending something
More likely that
Blah
Anyway guys we thank you so much tomorrow but until then
I don't know that's
Let me see if I can come up
Off the top of my head
Someone who is not killed anybody
I was watching Survivor series
The other night WWE Survivor Series
He's a big old hospital man
But
He's never killed
Anybody in kayfabe
I'm certain as a human
The guy who
For Cricket the character
Never killed anybody
But there is one guy who texts
We probably may have killed some
Is Alex gay
Alex