Alex
Birthstone colors
I love your work
The other voices
We're couple dudes
Sit around drink novel
What about Alex
Chocolat about
In particular
Yeah The Obama Deception
We are out here on parts
Chiavari
Investigation
Said
Dragula
Please go back
Mobility one
Sort of
Not really all that much
Cuz this documentary doesn't really
Adults
It's different
Jumping off in the middle of
He comes back in the other
There's no way there's no stick
No watch
This document
Ethereal
Hope you guys are all enjoying it
Perfect thing like that
That's exciting
Take a moment
Do some of the people who is
Signed up and are supporting the show
Give a shout out
To Leslie
You are now a policy
I'm a policy wonk
Bank of America
Robert
Roberts thank you so much you are now
If you'd like support the show this show is entirely listener-supported
Anyone
I'm going to advertise on the show
Basically about Alex Jones
Every now and again
We talked about
Weirdos
But if you'd like
Transport the show and I join up with the folks
We're making this possible
You can do so by going through our website knowledge
Slate.com
Says the 4th
Michelle we would have
Appreciate it
But for now let's go
Two part three
Of our coverage of the apartment
You are a
If you recall
Where we left off the last
Episode Alex
Just got done lying
About the Federal Reserve
It's private
I told you
How the Federal Reserve System works
Now we'll jump it on
Completely different topic
What you talking about
But
Immediately after
I mean camp
What Wall Street
Hijacked
Everyone is
Appointment
Are there
Gru
American Pie
Their object
Single one of them is
Every single one
Who are work
Public
He's a member of Bilderberg
Play exist
Trilateral commission put he left the group
Secretary of State Hillary Clinton
Spell
What's unnecessary
Because again
But there is no evidence
Is a CFR member on Wicca
Interpublic membership rolls on the counseling for relationships
Bill and Chelsea Clinton
But Hillary is not
The trilateral commission member list from the time is also available online
Is not a member or former member of
The trilateral
So
Also
Trilateral Commission
She also left
What information is it going off
That would help him is fake argument
Just bring it up
Make a member of the group or anyway remember the Cs
Maybe Alex
Much like Tim Geithner and Susan Rice
McDowell York
James Earl Jones
Sorry
Cars
Dismember CFR
Geithner into
Joseph Priestley
Butter left
National Security advisor
Bfr
Efficiency apartment
McDonald was dead
Member of
I don't think it means anything
My notes are my notes
Editorializing
How many more minutes before we just get all of your notes
All work and no play
Note
F*** this b**** documentary doesn't mean anything
But this is the closest of all these people
Closest
Because he was member the CFR and he was a member of trilateral commission
Special State Department Envoy
Bilateral Commission
So Henry
Jeremiah Henry Kissinger
Probably all of those things
Debate whether or not he's still a member of the CFR
She had left
The problem is
He wasn't special
One of them
Administration to go in there like big bad guys
He is
Genuinely evil
God you could just like why not like get rid of a couple of
Okay get rid of Susan Wright's you don't need her
The US
Economic recovery
Volvo
Bilderberg Group
Trilateral Commission
This is the first one that Alex is almost entirely right about
Hear it
But why doesn't Alex point out that he was a founding member of the trilateral commission
Bored
Well recovery
To the Secretary of State
I want
Founding member first
Directions
So you throw them in there up top and then you were like
He's in like this
Economic recovery committee
And then
This is the guy you bring it by you punch it
There's also former chairman of the Federal Reserve
In his role as the economic recovery chairperson
He felt that Tim Geithner was being real f****** rude to him
Keep him isolated from me
Really Alex 1003
The Director of National Intelligence
Admiral Genesee Blair
Bilderberg Group
Trilateral Commission
Did you say director of wedding
You know you're
You do you
You're no you're not making this life
Eyebright
Coronavirus
This is insane
The voiceovers Corral
He was the director of national
Director of National Security at the guy we talked about earlier
F***
A member of the CIA
Trilateral Commission
Secretary of Defense
Front lateral commercial
He's a member of the CFR
Detroit Lottery
The only source I can find it says use a Bilderberg
Website
Not on the public list but
Conference
Nothing more reliable than done confirmed
That leads to an Infowars story that says
Infowars reporters Aaron and Paul Joseph Watson to receive confirmation
B-list a conference
There's no proof
Who is
Plus years after this documentary came out
Who gives a s***
Deputy secretary of state
James Steinberg
Bilderberg Group
Trilateral Commission
Participate
State Department special Envoy
Richard Haas
Trilateral Commission
And president
It was a special Envoy to Northern Ireland
From 2001-2003
Northern Ireland
Because
He's a member of the trilateral commission
Position
Obama president
Bilderberg Group
Trilateral Commission
Bfr
Is remember this we have
Not a member of the trilateral
Supercritical
Federal Reserve.
Needed to create the subprime mortgage
Mortgage crisis
Who's creator
Can find online about OB Horsley critical
Alan Greenspan
Even if you weren't advisor
Floribama
Alex like that
Alan Greenspan was a free-market kind of guy
Hated raising taxes
You should love if the idea that use an advisor for
Wasn't
Alright
Alan Greenspan
Alex
Him to do
But that's
Osher
FedEx
But not the things
Followed up on
Turn back
Let the outcome to take print
Exactly
Cuz you look like
State Department special Envoy Richardson
CFR
Finally
Oh s*** there was just a lot of balloons
All over again
Remember since at least two
I know that because the CFR
They put out a press release
Mission of the director of communications for the council
As a special representative for Afghanistan
Globalist
Boosting the agriculture sector in a sector in Afghanistan
Holbrook
Diplomats
I can argue with
Holbrook was ultimately ineffective
So adorable
You've got a war in Afghanistan
I love that
You get a lot of points
If your last words of that
Learning
Ernest B world
Exactly
Make make the world
And the list goes on and on
Petroglyphs
Three of the people that he listed in that group
Are not even in the Obama Administration at all right
Is given the wrong title unscrew
I guess this night it was appointed by Bush
If you people who have left the trilateral commission is Alex being
3 really only got one of these people's description right at all and it Paul volcker and he didn't even mention that he was this
Don't understand
Like this list is
Full of deception
Haribo
Also please consider this
It wasn't even Obama's entire cap
Who's just 13 people cherry-picked out of the hundreds that Obama had on his team
Unity been absolutely correct about each and every one of these people
Pictures that prove
It's just a drop in the ocean
There's 19
The main position
Out didn't mention any of them and they aren't members of any of those books
Directions to
Black screen
Eric Holder
Not member of any of these
Groups right
That wouldn't
No
Vice president not member of any of these groups
Labor secretary hour and a half
Who is and is not in
Is a member of those groups
We're going to start alphabetically with the entire population of the world
Aaron Rodgers
This is
Even if
Barack Obama
You're the most wonderful person in the world
And brought to power
Carryout
There
Citation needed
So far
You have proven nothing
Humanity must
Look pass
Obama
And realize
Presidents come and go
Machado
Their program
Continue
How could people be so stupid
Gullible
To believe a bunch of
Politicususa
Some people that voted for Obama
Define Express
First of all son
The hatred
Bush Cheney
The desire to punish
The Republican
For their Adventures
State
And their record
The second Quest
Was on the economy
Bushwick
Selling them
Depression
Herbert Hoover
Regards
Really why Obama was
Prepared
Almost
Did Obama is there
To frustrate
See all of those
Those hopes
Obama is
The cruel hoax
Real f****** b*******
Because
Negatives about the Republic
As opposed to positive about Obama
If some of the progressive policies he was in Decatur
Torts
There's a strange world of everyone around him
Profoundly self-censor
Self-centered
Outside of its relation to themselves
Townspeople excited about the prospect of a bomb and liberal policies
He discussed
Which of the positive
Everything is good or bad is a response to what their side is doing
Of any agent
We don't really
Believer
You're not responding
How much we love guns
It's that same dumb thinking's it really is
Is a dead-end it's really
Really talk
I'm stupid it's childish and self-centered to level two
It stinks
Like mad that I have a lip ring
Mohawk is the equivalent
The people who support
They do hate push but that's not what they're expressing
You are looking at only the negatives applied to you as opposed to the positive
Did exist externally
Because we're going to recognize those for a second
You would have to either
Debate those positive points
Admit
You don't give a s***
And ignore those
Because you're a dumb f***
I
Am so
So happy
That you watching
Beforehand
Listen to that
And then
Spare time
Rioting in Ellicott
That is exactly what I thought
Immediately
Because I'm
Waukee Wellness
Absolutely one hundred percent correct on all fronts
Thank you so much for avoiding me just going like
Value value in that response because it is it is
Like
Hitting the point of what
He's expressing
He's so important because it really does underlie
So much of this.
When we talked with Alex Jones
I don't
I don't know was that
I felt that in the back of my head for a really long time took
Something
Oh that's what they're doing
It's a real and revealing moments
Nicole endpoint of that
Point Break before this was plenty calling everybody stupid
It's like the idea is exactly what I say
Everybody else
Euro Gyro
Reacting to what's real
You are not capable of agency yourself
And the only way that you'll ever be capable
Reacting
Right you
White Anglo-Saxon Protestant
Straight
Yeah
The only people
In our wake
The Ancient Aliens
The explanations of aliens created pyramids and stuff like that
All that really does is take agency away from non-white
The aliens built the parts
It's the same sort of
Go to Art in my quick or whatever I don't believe them to be
Be capable
Positive
Only reactive thought used at the directions
Which would be the equivalent Webster Tarpley saying these people
Did the Locking of bricks around to be devoting 40
Boat over a mountain
You look at stuff like that
Just like it's hard to look at that be like
Oh you're a
Greatest really tough to hear that mentality
But again this is why
To break
Conditioning
To come out be like
Toughest ride to Institute fascism part of it is real
Failure of Ron Paul in the Fig
Principled libertarianism
Babies been around for
And also why does he still have a show on the Genesis Communications
Isn't like
I mean I know he was a big role play
Okay so anyway
Fungus shampoo
Absolute
President
It is very disturbing to see well-meaning people
Falling for High-Tech propaganda
Over and over
American people a mess was swept into a mob psychology
Whatever the administration told them to
The general public eventually caught on to the fact
The George W Bush was a deceitful thought
Somebody's trying to make that he's leaving on Saturday
Where is Sparta
I don't like whatever they get something right in the wrong way
I was part of
Bike protest
Communities around that time
I don't think anybody didn't know that
Bush was Africa
Selection with heartbreak
Before 911
It was literally all that happened
Like it's not like people didn't understand the game before 9
But people came together after because
The economy was in free fall
In the midst of it all right walk Obama
Speaking out against the abuse of the people at the
Undercuts
Wench
No sir
What is your forehand
What is your window for coming out of nowhere
It's very small
Like
Surprise
I'm nobody's like
Wayne Gretzky got out at came here out of nowhere it was literally like
Barack Obama
But unfortunately
This was another vicious frog
I want to like
He is
2 seconds away from saying articulate
But you know what
Is that at
Free
Really really measure
Quality of
Nope
Put away all the flowery words
Put away all the rhetoric
When you put away all the rock
And roll music
Starting with
Notorious
You promised
He would get out of
Power
The Scotsman
And sure enough
Promises
What about the Dutchman
Mister Richard
But honestly who cares I actually said about
Official website
Machines
Must be careful
Immediately upon taking office military commander
Ending the war
The removal of the troops
Will be responsible in space
DirecTV
Military commanders on the ground in consultation with the government
Military experts
At a pace of 12
That would remove all of them
That's where the 16-month number comes from
Promise
Bring everyone home with them.
But that it was a military expert
I believe it was possible to do responsive
Gotcha an estimation of both the mostest
Expedient and the most
Responsible
Absolutely
Buy NES
Estimation
Remove home
The troops
There's no way for Alex to know
Wait
Eight it is fascinating
It is fascinating
To watch this
Aventurine
And remember
Weir's
They're in there for
I remembered I was 19
High School in college
Which most people use to hire.
Eerily close
Amazing
All the palace intrigue
Every f****** day
Still doing this
We're still f****** doing
I mean I mean to the 2018
In the 2016 election
Nobody ran on ending the war in Iraq
Lip service
To talk about the present
Throwing bigger
People brought it up
Depressed
It's not something
We would like to be
Because you stopped
The doing this interview
Who's actually on
Right
Obama campaign
Express
Little bottle could realistically withdrawal
The plans that he's able to make it.
Not the same
As well you'll be able to make one
To make a plan in March
When the situation may change by January 2000
Basically
Clarifying
She's just clarifying and she said that the 16-month window reflected a best-case scenario
Which I think is a fair way to put it
Obama promised
Like I don't think it's unfair.
But interesting
Based on the fact that Webster incorrectly
Is power doing an interview with a Scotsman
I know that
Did she also was no longer with the Obama
Having resigned in March 2008
Any immediate aftermath of her interview with the Scott
The problem was that you said
We f***** up in Ohio
In Ohio they're obsessed and Hillary is going to she's going to town with her
Because you knows Ohio's the only place
The chicken wing
She's a monster 2
She's stupid to anything
If you're if you're poor
And she's telling you some story about Obama's going to take your job
Maybe you'll be more effective
Reminder Tuesday to put forward is really unattractive
You know we have
Also where the Scotsman we don't give a s*** if you say is off the Record right
Obviously
Already knows that this is something
Before
Use referencing an interview
It was John
On a different
Medium that he's reporting which is just her clarifying
The misconception about the position
He knows that
Immediately
She ended up leaving the campaign
I rate this
Hundreds of speeches and interviews
Home from Iraq
If you'd said that that's what
Easiest Clipper Alex
Pulling up
People ever after 6
Yeah
The story
M16
It didn't change
It reflected the advice of
The people who he had hired
To advise right
Look at bring the truck home in 23 months
Washington Post
Cholesterol
Colon Obama weigh 23 months
23 months
But up in the up a little bit higher
Sherwood
Yeah Bunch since day one in this election
Understand
Because people more powerful than him.
We first released one not
What he saying
I love the just because I'm a Lovecraft fan
Powerful people brought
Do you know the case of Charles Dexter Ward
References I still haven't read it
Stop being able to raise the Dead
How dare you
Bring up something you can't bring back down
Like a raise
More powerful
Did you relocate
Also in that
Text Rory
Evolve
Charles Dexter Ward
To get some sleep
Read between the lines
That's not what you said
There is no military solution in a rock and there never was
I will begin
To remove our troops from Iraq
Immediately
Begin
Begin memes
Begin to
The process of it
This is not a demonstration of Ally
That's still beginning to remove the troops from Iraq
To physically bring someone
Consult with your expertise
It's not
Right lateral
Yes
Over there I don't care they're all getting slaughtered
So much in what's the best way to achieve
So much as they are in scoring points
Promise
It's just
It's a charade
Even if you want
2nd
Even though announce mission accomplished
How many times
Even then like
There's no way that are reasonable
Could say that just unilaterally removing all troops now
Is going to be a good dumbass
The idea of like
That is a great outcome have towards that outcomes that you are suggesting would lead to everyone dying
U-Pull
Just willing
To die in a much greater number than already has
Even even like
Let's go with
Funeral lateral action like that
Like I think a single-payer healthcare system is the best way to go
Congress
Tomorrow
Institute even if we had supermajorities in both houses
Your Healthcare System
Tomorrow is a
Chaos
Results
Does that
Hey being in a nice cool pool feels good
In wrong condition
If you jump you could have a heart attack
I have to find a way to
Is this
Singular individual
History
The idea of singular variable
External
Ideas
Write this is a failure of
I think comp
Group of Rome
Problematic
What bro
I apologize
Okay you can play whack-a-mole but you're not going to solve anything
Until you actually
Deal with the totality of the issue
Somehow that's both a
Critique
For these guys
Because they're dumb
That's best really boiled
We finally got a lot more listeners willingness to engage with
Complex ideas
Insisting instead
Nope
Go to the second page of Google
It makes you angry because I love it
It's weird to me
Excited for it
In-N-Out
And I was going to add this saying another
For more troops
50 Cent 30,000 more Marines to Afghanistan
Baroque
Eastern Europe
This is very important
Especially
From July 2009 article on America. Gov
Ballistic missile missile system
Under President George W bush Interceptor missiles in Poland
Radar station
Protect allies in Europe
Russian officials at Express
Ballistic missile
Obama and Russian president Medvedev
Did their missile experts
Conduct a joint review of the entire spectrum of means at our disposal that allow us
Cooperate
The development of missile programs around the world
Obama was working on cooperating with Russian president
Jamaica region safer in ways that serve both
Countries entry
To prevent this is some sort of integration toothbrushes complete bulshit
And even though this joint agreement was
Finalized until July 2009
News reports all over the place earlier in the year when I was working on the documentary
The testify to the fact Obama was trying to find a way to work together
The only reason for him to not know that
Is Wilfred
Wilbur Lake
Or he's lying
That's the only way around
This
To me seems more like
Medvedev and Obama
That is cooperate
Right
But
Nationalistic
Serbia
That narrative
The propaganda
List of Russia that we know today
I can't find any evidence
Like
To back that up
I'm not going
Once again
Automotive
It feels very
Weird feelings about Russia
General
But in terms of this documentary it also
Things like Occam's razor could tell us that it
It's just good enough
Quick question
Wood
Do Interceptor missiles actually work
Has anybody ever
Junito are released as a
Deterrent
Really hard to shoot missiles out of the sky because I don't think
Tiny little bird
Not small planes
Technology does exist
You could shoot down
I believe that
There's a little bit of a
You don't know all the technology I have
Here you don't want to waste your Rockets
With the idea that I might be
And so on
Weather
Everything that I've ever read about Interceptor missiles
It's like a success rate
Like
Whether or not
Sweetheart
Yeah
I don't know
I know you don't know the answer to
I was just kind of hoping that maybe
Like maybe a vice
I no longer like quick question
You have ruined them for me
Only logged
Fascist creep
Who does the best nature
Ushanka
Ukraine
What's Jacques beauty or Georgia
Your time to remember a payroll
This is worse than
Bush and Cheney
Brudzinski's
Soros
And the other people running
That is the only time throws his name is mentioned in any way in this documentary
Because with the ID the Webster Tarpley is coming
Why wasn't demonstration
Kissinger in their house
Why didn't you throw
Because he's not someone who's on Alex's radar in
A 2009
I mean
What's purple
Lyndon larouche guy
Two things about this clip so far
How many more places are we going to interview
Carplay
Like this is
Crazy
Outside the hotel
It's the same place
Because because our listeners can't see the eclipse
Another one of those fashion
Now I'm one of the best
Whatever version of you
It's whatever version the Oval Office whose country has
He's on the phone and he's just kind of
If you're going to play
Better if
Just a shame
All this stuff like I think it's kind of outside
Our purposes
The political situation in Eastern Europe
I was going to leave that alone for now just cuz
May I was outside
All safe
Zach
Around Russia
What that was predicated on
Is the idea that Obama was putting missiles around Russia
That's absolutely not true
That's the most important
I don't care
For good or ill
Because it's alright
And even then
They specifically point out that he's putting
Interceptor Interceptor missiles
Which
By their very definition
Ardis
Expensive
I don't know if you can or not
You can't just like launch
An interceptor missile
It seems like you would have Disturbed
Obama School
Bernie Sanders
Bush Administration
Real quick
A couple things
He just said that oversight
About government survey
Be meaningless though I don't really know
Re-examine The Patriot
Going to get rid of it
Voted for it
Renewal
By no means are we going to
But also. Onscreen Alex's pushed up this
To Post article
Intelligence
Necessarily
So you trying to make this about the idea
It's complicated
On that one
Is that
Wood
I would
Posit that the debate on Obama
This presidency
Twenty years from now
He's going to be
Far more fascinating
Even then the debate on Obama.
It will be
His
His legacy will be so interesting
Work through on a line-by-line ones were out of Crisis that were
Very hard for us to have
The gift of insight or Force
Chaos
This was made two months into his
So like when they're saying he's not out lying
Not that they're wrong
Totally
Because that hasn't happened
Obama pledged
Filibuster
To give retroactive
Telephone
The telecoms
Except
For that bill
He's right
Neural network
Pickled Angel City downtown
To reinstate
Patriot Act
Wiretap
Candidate Obama told
Brick Factory workers in speech after speech
Negotiating
A mistake
But then
Top corporate leaders
And then it was just campaign rhetoric
We got one
Wilford Brimley
Webster
This article
Canadian news organization
More about this and then I'll explain what
Obama saying you know I'm against
We had Austin
Rhetoric
President
I forgot this is also still a news article
Was publicly criticizing the North American Free Trade Agreement
In a bin for boats
But privately worry about it
Custom piece of b******* Webster Tarpley
News reports
That were erroneous
This is absolutely
Yeah
Anything to drink 2018
Is going around telling people in Canada
Local access
He was just insisting that it needed to be improved to add labor and environmental
Protection
The campaign Trail
Diplomat
True and most likely was actually a coordinated smear against Obamacare
The story that Alex plashes up on some
They reported on February 27th
But there was a memo
Contact empathy
And told them that Obama's rhetoric was just quote political maneuvering
In the Fallout from the story being
Obama's campaign
The Canadian embassy
No record
To be found of Obama advisor
Their contact info
Canadian embassy
There's no record of transcript anywhere to be found
This was days before the Ohio primary
Place where
To both Clinton and Obama
To being about
Visiting the Canadian consulate
Chicago
Palatka
Likely change because go visit consulate on February
And after weather topic
Take the came up
When the full meeting with offer
Included this
On Master Goolsby suggested that Obama is less about Sunday mentally changing the agreement
Clarifying
Labor Mobility
Established
That's pretty much exactly what Obama was saying
They're also part of that quote
Political maneuvering,
Even close to that
It was an inappropriate
Made by whoever had written that were
The Canadian in
Embassy issued in
An apology that same day on March 3rd
In the recent report
Produced by the consul General in Chicago
There was no intention to convey the senator Obama
A different position
Computer Express
Private including about
We deeply regret any inference the could have been drawn out
In the Fallout accusations were made
The chief staff staff of the conservative Prime Minister Stephen Harper
I've been behind the week with interest
Interfering
Whatever the case is and whoever was behind
Which is still to some extent unclear
This is a situation where
Emily
Hillary would go on to win the Ohio primary because of this mirror
Most likely
It's hard to say
Obama was gaining ground had a chance to win
And in the aftermath of that she did end up winning the Ohio
Pointless to re-litigate that to some extent because of how it is.
Even though.
To come out about it just me Obama on the general
It's
Goolsby.
In order to paint the picture that Obama was a flip-flop
And now we have Alex
By this point
It when he's making this documentary all the information is there
Like you should know that this isn't something
That is
Isn't right
Public toilet
Even going even going down to the staff
Don't have a cartoonishly evil name
Goolsby I don't want to be that guy
I don't want to tell you that you have to change
Come on man you can't be cool course you're going to be in a f****** controversy
Gold
The moment they said that conspiracy theory and you said
There's probably some truth to that
Canadian
Little bit
Animalistic visceral she probably took
Distrust of ghosts
I just trust
Acrostic
Let's move on
You Google
No he didn't
Experiment
Parents
In about
Haircut
Not have
Pavlova
He said he was
Clean up governor
He said he was going to work for
You're laughing about
You're laughing about Dave Chappelle that deceiver with Obama being pi
Like Obama's silhouette being the eyes to fever
It's clunky as hell I thought they were like
Really was like
We trying to spell December I honestly doubt the first two times I watch this documentary
It looks like instead of Obama being
It's
Terrible
Visual Arts
Another part of the
Legitimately
What I was doing
What are the points of the documentary
I would end up watching like three minutes and then have to walk to the bathroom and look in the mirror
What am I doing
It took a payoff
You probably took me
Now I got to read a wrestling article
Casino
Point B
First
Month
Of his inauguration
He has lied
Beat It
No obligation to respond
Complaints to Georgetown
Campaign promises
Some of it is fairly
Like the idea of
Fair Credit
It is so unfair
It's nonsense
Bulshit
2 months
Kept getting this feeling
Overwhelming
Trying to figure out
What they think
2 months into his term
Is a futile
Baby baby
Probably
Exercise
Breaking All the promises don't matter on the primer
Started making this documentary
What I've realized from this
Finish the documentary
16 hour days
I guarantee first of all I worked harder on this then
So much of it is padded
Filler from like
Endgame
A lot of it is stuff that is just like
I guarantee
No matter who won he was going to make this documentary
Absolutely matters
Is responsive that would be like of course I would have.
He's making rely on the specifics
Of what Obama has done
Who he put into
Position
And it doesn't matter
I look at this and I'm like
This is the
Francis Trucking
Anything in the world
Makes me feel gross that were covering
Level
One one thing that this makes eminently clear and I've already been on this trip and I've said it
Seriously and loudly
These people are
Well
They're probably delicious
Flank
The futility of arguing with somebody
In this kind of
Like what
Why would you watch this documentary and then think will going on Fox News to get my point out there's going to make
Know these people decide
Years before you showed up on there was going to be
Turn office light
45 days
It's 45 days when the documentary was released was finished
No
-10 days before he was inaugurated
I do know how to take this.
Valid criticisms
I can't take this seriously
Yeah
This is going to help me much more than endgame really pisses me off
8 1/2 hours ago
I really miss Obama backwards back when you were at home
This documentary
Early first episode
When I was going through
From those those peaches
Because
Really interesting
To listen to
Oh that's what you're getting
It's not just like hey
Those people in the back in the media they f****** suck
Hey baby maybe an old Jew
Get some of these Second Amendment people
I forget
Trump was president
The podcast
Can I watch a movie
I forgot how
Really great speeches work
The people of the United States in the world
Or filled with Pope that Obama was the real deal
In office
She signed an executive order
Supposedly closing Guantanamo Bay
Another Secret
Then the Press actually had a chance to read the executive order
And we're shocked
Define
Was thinking about closing Guantanamo in the year
How much does an Obama signs executive order signing
Thinking about closing Guantanamo orders that are like
That's a diarrhea
Number 4000
300 or actually
Earlier
You can't be like
Having a nice meal for Logix 800-1000
I'm thinking Arby's
Brandon Florida
I had a dream about
Bears
Know what that
I don't understand what Alex is trying to
Ludacris
President of
Country
Persuade
F****** stupid
All we did was cry
Closing Guantanamo
In reality
You signed executive order 13 490
Explicit timetable
Close Guantanamo
And relocate
People being held
Now admittedly they ended up blowing it in terms of actually falling that timetable
March
This substance of the actual executive order sets of timetable
When they're going
Reevaluate the position of all the
People who are out there
And also reinforces the idea
Right
This refers to
Alright but worst of all
The executive order continue the practice
What's the yellow X called
Secret abduction
Because that's the day
It's not in the executive
Executive order
Hey also let's stop right
I wish I wish
Never
Isn't expect
To be like a compound executive orders
Something is not even part of
The most
Celia Cruz
He's made of Obamacare
Having sex
Dictator powers
Closer to our version of like
Mirror socialist left
Later on explicitly say you should nationalize the Federal Reserve
But yeah it's so you want to have closing
How did Obama do that
He just says
Who can just
Whatever you want
Consequences
Who you are now releasing
Soccer players
If you are at
Yeah I do whatever
If you are a terrorist that is been held indefinitely
Force-fed
You are not going to suddenly be released
Now I'm not a terrorist the whole reason to close it is because
If the Earth because they knew that there were so many people that they were holding
The f****** win
Because that is a
For the pizza
Call Reese mobile
Consider
That
Like what
Is forcing the issue
U2
Actually I would say
Let's go ahead
Myself in a circle actually think you probably should have
Just released everybody and let the chips
At least then maybe he wouldn't
Think that he signed off the
Immediately on
Closing
But he's allowing
Prisoners now.
Taking Safari
Countries
Not knowing where were there Sunday
Detroit shooting
Borinquen
They don't notice
Obama is now continuing the practice
Record prison
And most important
Indefinite detention without
Trial
Which you will be for a scam
Recorders that proof that the Bush Administration was ordering Personnel the systematically abused
Barack Obama
The program was important National Security
Not only endorsing Bush's crimes
But continuing them
But the ACLU Alex's referencing the ACLU
Alex
Makes no sense
Cuz by the time
Like by 2009
For president
Administration
Position was pro-torture
What's debate about it
Ministration
Didn't really give a s*** about it
I took a lot of activists
No
Now
Columbia Missouri
What are we doing
The revelation of the torture was like
Profoundly impact
In 2009 Alex
Is it like Obama is trying to
Block these.
Coming out
In some way to empty it's an aisle
Did Bush torture people
Obama was clear on his position that he would end torturing
Absolutely
Some of the
Gray areas about
Third countries
I'm stuff like that
Eastbay
2 degree
But it's
You made it so that American
You did kind of Outsource it though so I'm not exactly right
U-Haul
That you just do none of it
Obama presidency that we are going to re-litigate
Twenty years from now
Incremental
Morally acceptable
Forward progress
Consistent
What you do today is a building block for what happens tomorrow and what happens the next
It is like
Okay we can achieve everything
Swallow
Pill that we don't want
It sucks
But it is what's best
Maintaining a haystack
Appropriate status quo
I know that
Calculation we're not taking into account how much
That is still
Horribly abused
X Xbox One
X + 2x + 3x + 4x
X + 5
Expose
Or whatever you get to a point where it's not
Hurting arrest
Exactly you working
But since Xbox One
It means nothing
Probably matter
Maybe that's the true reality that we learn about compromise
Power exists in your hands for
A certain amount of time
Preserve that power bi
Is only serving the entry
Chris
People who agree
The exact off
When
You are someone who is like
We shouldn't
Kill people
The power that you have
You have it
To confirm
Because you had the powers
Right I don't know it's hard
I think my
If I were a
History
Masters
Two graves
I would definitely right about how
The first two years of Obama's presidency was
Probably the
Here's where the linchpin
Sensitive
History
Don't worry about it
Obama was trying to protect
The Secret of bush
And that's not fair
Because the tickets are already at
Search impossible that's what his motivation
In reality if you look into this Obama threatened to limit intelligence share with
United Kingdom information
But not because it revealed torture
But because it would reveal some of the information that was gathered through the course of the interrogator
Now I still don't think that's
Right
Write a very different scenario than what Alex is painting
He's not trying to
Protect bush
Or the idea that we torture people
We already owned up to
Right
About it
He's trying to protect the idea that there is some information
That was gathered from a
Interrogations of people that would be released
If the British
Put these rats
Some people have speculated that
Contained in that information
Have released
Information that Obama
It's not
Entirely clear that's just something
But
If that's the case then that's a really good
I don't know
Because he's what
Just like with our last documentary
Forgetting
That we are watching it.
Just a
This is a series of like
Visual
Very little relationship
Just kind of Freewheel
Obama voting
For reinstatement of
Zerli.
He's already
Subway
2000's hit early
Nevermind
People that have been charged with
Beach Washington
Cover all of Obama's lies
This documentary would never be released
I love the idea that the makers of this film
It would be long
It's crazy
That way like
Like I got f****** hire to do voiceover work
Because there are new ones every day
We're going to cover one more big
Black Edition worth
Keeping out of administration within hours of being
Collected
Obama did a 180
Distilled white house in Federal
At all levels
On the campaign Trail
Did industries that they
Documentaries
Were people
Lobbyist
Reviled
Power of the executive order
Or any front
And I wish you would have stuck with that commitment but ultimately
Oprah
And I always had this big of a problem
I can't imagine how he feels about what Trump
I know I know
I know that like
Idealism and we wish would be
Be true is so caught up
Certain extent
Because
You know we we wish that this had been
Vindicate
Right but if you look at almost every president ever
Special interest
Right
So Alex is going to get into some of the lobbyists
That were involved
Obama's campaign
Are they all on the council for relationships
But some of these are interesting
Example
Terrible
Obama pick William Lin
The top lobbyist for Raytheon
The building number two position of the
Department of Defense
So you did
He looks like he's a robot
It looks like a robot
It's definitely not a good looks
Years in the past
The argument was
He was very
Qualified
For the position
He was also
An undersecretary for defense
He also been a senior fellow with the national
University
The job in his waiver was specified that he not be able to work in any matters that relate to
Did any of the six
Did he previously been a Lobby
Is that good enough
Probably not
That is your first example
Probably have a weak argument
Probably
Because I
You could
I want any I don't want anybody who has a financial interest
William Lynn would be a very qualified
BT undersecretaries
Like I get it
Understand
If there is oversight
Where do stuff like
You get out of line
I don't
In that role
I don't know
I still would say I
It's that is that ultimate question
It's like you have someone who has
A good resume
Re-qualify
Applications
Good for the job
Do you
Surprise yourself
Of their experience
Because of
The former job
I don't know the answer
For that question
There's probably equally qualified
But maybe they didn't click
With the other people who were involved
I don't know
It's not my decision to make
Alex is kind of fine
I would say there's another decent point
Phuket never going to get his body
Exactly
Timothy Geithner
Former president of New York
Secretary of the Treasury
That's a terrible animes
Looks like
Like his chief of staff
Mark Patterson
Formerly the top lobbyist
Like I said there was never a lot
The president of the New York Federal Reserve
Mark Patterson works at Goldman left the Furminator
April 2008
It's probably not enough time separation
Confirm
But they thought he was well qualified for the position
Who's the Democratic staff director and chief counsel for the Senate Finance
Committee from 1995 to 1999
Enter 1999
2004 you the policy director for Senate
He's only a Lobby unqualified forthright
Yeah I don't know but also
Alex Gartner Garden
This is the one example he's got
Hacking
The department the chief of staff
Is a former lobbyist but also
Maybe qualify
The people or Obama
He is indicting the revolving doors
I am
Find
If you want to hit you with it
Buc-ee's
Individual
When in reality it's about the entire system that has created
Existing now
Now if you want
All of the places where he has
To do
Specifically about the
Like
I am with him on
You guys shouldn't be in the
I know Gartner's not a lobbyist
Well that's fair
But it's not like
These guys are the individuals
Doing this
This is part of a broader system
Politics
Gris on a certain level
I understand
But the actual
Charges
He's making are not
Because because
Resume
Well if you had just taken a lobbyist
Reyes on the fellow at the National Defense universe
Would be able to profit in Subway
Then we have the absolute
Absolutely
Personal experience in government
Someone who
Is relevant to the job
It's not the same
Thing is that revolving-door thing
It is 8
Is adjacent to it
It's not the same as like Betsy Daedalus being their Department of Education
Carson Beach
And not like their lobbyists or anything like that but it is like
Those are people who are unique
Unqualified
To be in the position
Work Wallace
It's a decision of glad I never have to make
Right look at it
I don't think
An example of his
Then I'll agree with him
Absolutely
Obama appointed top lobbyist
The Saudi royal family
George Mitchell
Obama appointed the
Dla Piper
History for the Middle East
Envoy
He was actually lobbying
Interesting one retroactive
I think so
Do some lobbying work
Frassati
Right
A2000
You have a perfect candidate for the job
Simultaneously
The dirt
Tobacco manufacturing interest in the insurance
It makes me very uncomfortable
At the same time the position Obama was looking
Phil was the special Envoy for Middle East
F****** good step qualification
He previously served as special Envoy for Northern Ireland
From 1995 to 2001
Where he was involved in the Belfast Pizza cream
Mitchell a liberty medal and the presidential medal of freedom
Because you resolved
Tense situation in North Carolina
Just perfect
In 2000 Bill Clinton Mitchell on a fact-finding
Mission about the arab-israeli
In 2020 released the Mitchell
Which called for the Israelis Brent f****** stop building settlements
A call for the Palestinians to work on preventing vile
No I remember
Beyond that he was a senator from Maine from 1980 to 1995
Use a senate majority leader
And he's a senior fellow and Senior research scholar at
Universe
International
That is a very specifically qualified resume for someone that Obama might look
To be the special Envoy for Middle East
Shooting has been disqualified because he done work for these other Industries in the past
Maybe I don't f****** know but that's a great resume for somebody want to send her the
Negotiation
Successfully and quote
It largely made progress in North
Diplomatic
Conflict resolution experience
Is a
With a 15-year record as a center
And the point here though is
His job
Is Middle East Envoy
It's not overseas
Middle East on I apologize
HR overseed his job is literally
Leave the rest alone
You can do on this tissue thickening
It probably have a lot of connections willing to talk to
To use and other people
Someone who is easy to plug into that role
I don't know I don't
F****** know I don't know what to do with it
Lakers if you was able to
To be in that role and there were at the
6 rules in place but like
Nothing you do
Can any way touch any business that you have Lobby
Be fine with that
Cuz it's unrelated interested in
I don't know if you
It's like a Jimmy Carter gives up
Peanut Farm
Because he's worried about ethics issues
There's there's
There's no lie
And that's when you have a s*** ton of hotels that are making a lot more money because you're the president
Good grace
We would avoid
Because it feels like what
Like what's going on
What you're saying
But it does feel like
We're trying to
Or someone could hear it as us being like
Well let's let Obama off the hook
Because here's what's wrong
I'm not saying that I only
Want to
The only reason that that's important
Bring up at all
And is relevant anyway
Highlight
The level to which Alex Jones
Just giving up on any principles
He ever pretended to have absolutely
You could never be what he is now
I am ready
Concert
Because what's the point
The difference
Between like
Okay
If we still lived in the 2009 World of Obama
You were like
Who has a history of and I was like
Well what about bugs
Situation
Whiffs of corruption
Now we're talking about with a whiff of corruption
And Trump's admission Administration
Farting corruption
You know if I heard what about
The version of what we could do
Would be here Alex complain about George Mitch
And then be like
Address
George Mitchell
No that's that's real here's the contest for doodle
It's the right decision but it's not as easy as represent
Sign with
Martinez housing
Yeah so here's five under the radar
So far
Garbage
Uniquely unqualified for the position
Nonclassic
Smile
It's nice to know that
Major crisis
They are ignoring our minor Christ
Which are fireworks
Which are far worse than anything
Of Wall Street lobbyist
Leon Panetta
Never been a lot
Killing do Consulting work
Clicklist
McLean auto log-in
He's never been a lobbyist
Old article
You can find about the Scribe is action
Activities
Closely approximates
But it's not like he's not a lot
And maybe
Maybe
Amy's
Really good at hiding
I don't know
But he thought of
Technically speaking
He is not allowed
Through
Consulting
Doesn't change
This is not
Yeah cluding Leon Panetta.
Judge him by his record
He's a piece of s*** in the way that you say
King of Wall Street
Kingslayer
Federal Reserve
I'm not allowed to know anything about this
Jack Purcell
It turns out people jug into
To some of his past
Used to write
Game of Thrones fans
Oh hell yeah
Is a character
A story about Donald Trump
Love with
Su with a
Let's see who's next
Top lobbyist for healthcare
Department of Health and Human Service
Arby's app
On and on
The list goes on and on
Like I said Obama nominated
Bedazzled had filed
Texas correct
You might have missed files
Deduction does it
So on February 3rd 2009 from consideration for
Human Service
It was replaced by Katherine sibelius
This is embarrassing
Looks like he has every reason to notice
Came out
Why would
Stacy was a month
Took his name out of consideration given to the confirmation Pro
Plays because he been foot animation
8 awful
Angela
Look at play
Listen to Prince
What the f***
Got a new animated Katherine sibelius
Getting robbed do take some
Who that sounds too close to home
Is it real
Jesse was nominated
Joseph Alexa Lobby
Bye-bye
Then three weeks into his administration
Obama wants to know
More outrageous than the
Academy Awards
He said that he was up
Upset about
The banker bailout
Which is anshika
Rahm Emanuel
Another former Wall Street executive
And anyway wrote
The 2008 bailout bill or head
He was a member
I don't know I
Looking for
And especially considering earlier the documentary they said it was Larry Summers now
I don't understand
What's going on
Borat
My wife's pension
There's nothing to understand
It's the way they do their propaganda
What they do is they make
Extravagant unsupported
Sensational clay
They don't prove
No
You can't play that game
Like no I don't have to
Now it's your job
You're the one who made the claim
I can't be expect
Negative
Because then
The only way I'm going to ever satisfy the
This is like
Give me a detailed accounting of literally everything
Horor Alex Jones
And that's the way the heart
I would look
I don't I don't do that kind of pressure like I don't understand it
I don't care
You know what I mean like I think a lot of people
Robbed
And then
I don't know
How to be like
Prove me wrong
Like I will I will say that
If you prove to me
I'll revise my position
Position
You know like it's not it's not worth it
Obama says
Taking the bailout
Enzyme executive order that was just part of
Major Banks and brokerage
Firms
And the New Order
With any future bailout
And those were to be on the honor System
People upset
And rightfully so
Executive being rewarded for failure
I want to respond I really don't care
Because
Alright
Yeah
2009 were already started to pay back the bailout
Yeah but it's just nonsense nothing went perfectly
IG Bank of America and Citigroup which it received
Bailout money
This plan
Only banks negotiating future agreements with the government will be restricted
But this appears to be built in honor System
And White House Press Secretary Robert Gibbs had a hard time explaining
And I will get the clarification
From treasure on that generally speaking
This is already the biggest liar and the biggest disappointment
We've seen in recent history
Delivering on
On promises
It doesn't matter any of the stuff
I'm telling you
Something's about to happen in the second battery
Big changes the f***
Obama is a fantastic and Weldon better liar
His track record is clear
He has done the Opera
Everything he told the people
He would do it for 3 weeks
You believe these
I don't believe it
Get their asses so late
I bought the delivery I love it I love it
Within one month
Of the past
Baker bailout bill
The Press reported
Set / 5 trillion dollars
That's not true
That's not
How could you even make that
Claim pretend disappear
That's absolutely not true the specifics of it hours we'll get into a little bit further down the road so we'll deal with it.
Colors disappeared in Iraq
I get that trillion dollars is enough to bankrupt
Short version of about
Contacts
I promise we'll get more
Is conflating the bailout 7
A hundred billion dollars with
Funds that were
By the Federal Reserve
Got others trillions of dollars
What
The amount of money
Circle boomerang
It would not discuss where the money
Manual back there
You're close to ready for what's about to
There are at least
Generous
Man
Get like
Buckle
Using this for like four minutes of this documentary which is the 8 hours in real time
Americans protest
Apple 38r regional governorship office
Give me a refreshing to see people standing up
Against the real power structure
Alex wrote
He's goddamn
Being distracted by the elites
Frontman
Like George W bush and Barack Obama
We travel to Dallas Texas
The cover
We the People
No
Smoking cigarettes
Understand
Federal government building
What
You are making sense and I would like you to continue
Please 100%
He's like a Vining with Federal Reserve jobs
It's controlled by clique
Bankers meeting
Here's me doing the GIF of a jack off motion
Senate confirmation
But I like that you strongly waited into argument very first position
No recognition
Stepping in there
Operation
Jackals hyenas Raptors
Super Bowl
President Obama
The president
Is the Federal Reserve chairman
Who is
Installed
President of the United States what the f*** is he talkin about
This is John Smith and then hey guess what
After that
The Federal Reserve
Federal
Testimony
And they're the ones orchestrating
Freakonomics glasses
Why I left the End the Fed rally outside
We spoke with Ron Paul's brother Waynesville
Folks I am so sorry that that's where we're cutting it off
But
We're about to jump off into a section
This document
Listening to
Discussion of house
Stupid depaul's
Episode
Uno
From the end of the
Episode
Paul
And you know what there's very few times on the Stark
But I'm actually able to do a cliffhanger
I've got to make the most of it
And you know what
Tomorrow
Next episode Thursday
It's Thanksgiving
What better way to celebrate
Thanksgiving read to learn
About just how off base
Ron Paul
Do tomorrow
Today
There's a little bit of wishy-washy
Episode
We do have website
It's knowledge fight.com
You can follow us
Twitter
Sciatic notch
Underscore
You can follow us on
Facebook
We also have a Groupon they're called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
It is a private group
For no reason really but we let people in
So if you'd like to
Be a part of these
Community Justice Center request
Iran
Follows
Describe
Levi's
Review
Appreciate it
Until next time
You know what I realize in the last episode that I talked about
About Survivor series
I didn't feel right about it
Together putting
Soda realized
Probably
Was that
Games
Saturday night
Future.
Someone who you think might've
Aleister black
Pro wrestler
People really hard to the face
But
Has not killed anybody
With his
Mass kick to the face
Has not killed anybody
One guy that I know of
Who technically
Probably killed the dude
That's Alex Jones
Alex
In color