Alex
DIY voices
We are 22
2cc Beverages and talk little bit about Alex Jones
You have joined up here on part four of our coverage of Alex Jones is
A very Loosely described as a documentary film
You haven't listened to the rest of the episodes I recommend you go ahead and go back
And look at those before jumping at the park cuz we
Restarting this episode off on a cliffhanger
I'm sorry about that but today
You will see I give thanks
For this that we will have your stay where
We make fun of
Ron Paul and his family
What's Thanksgiving
Breaking photos of people's relatives
Oh well
Documentary Aces on 12th
But before we take a second to give a shout out
Have I joined up with the team and I are starting to show we really appreciate it
So we like to give some shout out
First
To say thank you so much you are now policy
I'm a policy wonk
Also I would like to say thank you
Byron Byron thank you so much you are now
Thank you guys so much
I would like to support the show what we do as we are a hundred percent
Supported by our listeners
I like to
You can support our show by going through our website knowledge fight.com there's a button on the top of the page it says support the show
It helps keep things
I'm moving on literally Keeps the Lights On
So
We thank you all who support us and all that
Enough of that nonsense it's time to get to this Cliffhanger so without further Ado I give you part 4
Of The Obama Deception
Cool I'll let the End the Fed rally outside the Federal Reserve Bank in Dallas Texas
We spoke with Ron Paul's brother Wayne.
Oh no
The Federal Reserve Act was
Florida house for three members
Cameras were on the floor
At that time he needed a majority of votes
Capacity
Covid-19 13 the Federal Reserve Act was passed
Jordan
Yeah
Completely
Unacceptable
Unforgivable things
Just happened in this documentary
Rompope
The Federal Reserve Act Fast with just
Three members of Congress on the floor
M2
Alex Jones didn't fact check that at all
Before allowing this to be in his dumbass documentary
I'm going to
That whole that whole like
The Federal Reserve Act
Pass with j
Just three members on the floor
I just let that one
That's so silly
And nonsensical brother
Well Ron Paul's brother with talking
Where'd you learn from Rock Falls
I don't understand the words you're saying
Because nobody ever taught you how to speak
Here's the deal
The myth surrounding the passage of the Federal Reserve Act
Is the evil
Wait until Christmas break
When they knew that no Congressman would be around force their legislation through
Could enslave the country
Compelling story
Complete
The first first time
Federal Reserve Act
Proposed was June 26th
Built-in go far in improved version was introduced
On August
20 nights
Hr7
It was debated on September 18th
1813 Pasteur
Weather
Is the problem
Amended version
I was sent back to the house
This inability to come to a consensus
Until December 22nd
When the house agreed
Prince version of the
And it passed by a vote of 296 260
The 76 not voting
The next day
The conference board
With 43
With 27
How do you feel about that
I got it
People in the house who didn't vote don't really matter
Senators who didn't vote
Where was Christmas break
Instability
This is where Alex Azar
Ron Paul
Wheatley misrepresenting to save it
3 people
Historically
Betty's
3 people
We're on the floor and 18.
Bears
Exactly
27 knots
Voting in the
Is where
Of course works with votes that are happening during times of likely to be on vacation is that members
Congress try really hard to help
Each other out
What's the plan what's called
Announced pairs
People
Without affecting the out
We saw this happening
Information Lisa murkowski
Who is opposed to The Copper
How to vote
Steve
Favor of the confirmation could attend his daughter's wedding
There's like a congressional courtesy
Your daughter's wedding who gives a break
Live in DC or something like that
I will agree to go together
Yeah so what happened
In the Congressional Record
Now tears
We wouldn't show up for Christmas
Which accounts for 26
Super 27
Voters
Did they vote on the bill today
No way to call this abroad
Not just making stuff up which is
This is crazy
Like crazy
Are you sick from Ron Paul's family is saying crazy
Factual
Ways to
But it would be talked about early there's a lot of ways to talk about the problems
Who's had their own face on this
Stupid b*******
Like if you're putting a senior
It might be embarrassing
For me to put my name on
A video of Summer
3 people who voted on the Federal Reserve
Without looking into it
But what are you doing
Reason why a lot of the other stuff
He was like
Yeah
Look at you allowed this in your documentary I don't give a f*** about anything
No
Hispanic version of it
0220 Olney possible
Regardless of the fact
Give me three names
Give me the three names of the people voted
If you know so f****** much about this give me the three names of the people
Not argue remember if you imagine that only three people voted you should know their name Dutch
Wayne Paul Ron Paul's brother is
Full of s***
Like
Stanbic he might believe
There's no way
He might be Steve dial I have no f****** idea okay that's
I don't know everything
Ikea
I can conceive of something
Version of like he's convinced
Yeah
I suppose
The historical record shows that that's not
True
And in order to
Extraordinary proof that what you're saying is true
Switch
Okay
They want to believe it's better reservist
Even if
And I don't mean that in the pejorative term
More like
Left
Less interested in spreading
If possible
Cursory knowledge of American history
There's no way that you're to be like
Are you saying that a major bill
That changed the course of American history
Was passed by three guys
And also Disney lyrics
House of Wong
Saturday the 3
The biggest story ever
April 1st
The other
EvanTube told it to that would be like a week later everybody got together we're like
No
The other 400 represent and the other I don't know 99
Are we taking these three people's asses
Book business in 1930
People were still like
Crust
Dispel to happen
He would
That level of other centers
Crazy stupid
VIP Post Road believe that is advocating it in this documentary and Alex
Cut it out
Cuz he should have cut that hell yeah
Crazy Idiot Brother is
Borderline
Incompetent
Liquor
That's worse than terrorists ones metaphor
Like
If you believe that
You're willing to
Go to an NSAID rally and try and convince other people that's true you are far gone
You do not know is that way Paul can
Spit hot
I am not joking
I also should say I feel really bad about
But I didn't look
Whether or not William Paul is still alive
He might be dead
Alright
20 years later
Roosevelt
Reunited
States with
Thank
The Federal Reserve private Banks it's okay
USA
What are you going to play Jason lateral
What happened
Cirrhosis
He's not in the second email
You make bad on that hurt
Stroke
Do you have a stroke
You still being used as a propaganda
2 of an oz
From the 70s
He is more but bad idea
Like the collateral for Social Security
60s
So far
All of what he has said is
Fantastical
On a level that I wouldn't believe in a
Novel
Fictional universe
That's
Are you seriously going to tell me that a legally
Resolution was passed the house and the Senate
Bi3 total guys
Reading all of American History the Constitution
Validated
Buy 3 f****** dudes that's it
I mean
Knox
Fair enough
He also doesn't think black people should be allowed
Truck.
Make discount
Country Bank
Ark ever
Emergence
Powers
It is
City station
It's Azteca
Manage
The bankruptcy
Bankruptcy Iverson
Soda Prince
The miniature the bankrupt
Is probate
We're at today
Is your listen carefully you can hear Alex giving an interview to somebody else.
What are you talkin about here in terms of the bankruptcy the United
Safes
I had a strong suspicion
He's talking about the emergency
Citibank - 90
He doesn't
U.s. Bank
I tried to look into this more to understand the argument but pretty much all the way
Website to the purport
Prove that the US went bankrupt in 1933
Happened to also be the kind of websites with the word
And really scary lighters at the top of the Pole right
Version of the heart Jack
Yeah
Most of the argument
There are on these pages also rely very heavily on a forgery of a speech allegedly made by Jim traffic
Jim traficant if
Call
Tax evasion
Back in 2002
Would you like to him being one of the first people to be expelled
17 months
You was up to some real serious
Where is supposed to Lake
White supremacy
Amid
It's what tasteful I don't know it's supposed to be like a misdemeanor
Jim Preston got out of prison
Project
It's too boring not a lot of
Is really fun
Think about for a little bit that Ron Paul
But really all I Come Away with is a realization that like
Call Family might not be all that smart
Deeply involved in
Like really weird Sovereign yeah
Yeah like I can't stress this enough
Play bankrupt
3 is almost entirely if you look into it online almost all sources lead back
Do this speech
The gym
Gave on the the floor
It's a Forger
It's not real
It's a fake
Speech of the guy who was the
The first guy to be expelled from the house yet
Is using this as an example
Prove
That the American government has been bankrupt
What the reason the keys
Use is the same reason
Isn't that people go back to like Abraham Lincoln
And get like apply these words to him
It's a different strategic tactic
Used rims
Because
They were like
No he was not on the floor yet
True that we've been bankrupt since 1933
When you can go read the Emergency Banking Act doesn't say there were
Bankrupt are so similar to women who fall in love with
Like
Like tigers
Yeah you know where it's like
No no you guys just don't know
Committed that crime
Much more for them
It's it's
It's all good at all to be resolved with a slight amount of reading that just think for once
Alright
Based on what you're saying
The
Has been operating under emergency Powers through the treasuries
Kateri
470 years
There's no way
That could have been kept secret
Maps
Knowing what I know about human being I mean there's a lot of people who have been in and out of the house really quick
If everything's going fine
You would have just been like
Oh yeah by the way
This is Howard
Like if nobody notices
It's not an emergency
True
Like you can't be operating under emergency powers for 70 years
Betches
Larry Nichols
FEMA provisional government
Stuff like that it's just a special sounding turn and the reason the powers is so appealing
It's because it relates back to the Emergency Banking Act
It it has this like
Well it was an emergency
Emergency
But it's not
Yeah buddy
Fine
Right even if
Even if what you're saying is true it's been going on for 17 years and everybody's kind of
Fine
Black people are allowed to vote
And they don't like that
Congressman Ron Paul now has a huge amount
Private Federal Reserve
And having a great time how yeah
Alex is wearing a motherfuker
HR 1148 sponsors
To end the Federal Reserve
It dies in committee
We've now
Woken up the world
So on February 3rd
2000 Dodge
HR 1144
So now I'm
When step on February 3rd
Ron Paul
Announces hr-88
Federal Reserve
With no co-sponsor
Course
Out there with a boho
Ted Cruz's shity shity as a
Who are in Congress
You start to realize a lot of a f****** waste
There's a reason that they deserve a 9% approval rate
Too much about Ron Paul's bills
Tell you a little bit about some of them I should tell you that on May
May 8th 2012 HR 1094
To End the Fed
No co-sponsor
How long was the belt
End the Fed.
No co-sponsors
We got to get rid of these
Every year
Play no way every year
Interesting ways the Ron Paul has a lot of
Weird Corky Bells
In 1979 he introduced
Introduced HR 2310 signature repeal
No no
You just misspelled
I hate you
Everyone works together
Brinkley Atlanta
The same here
He introduces 1979's joint resolution
A joint resolution congratulated the United States Space Program
Supporting them developed a new field of technology to promote and Preserve
The free enterprise system the acquisition of knowledge and freedom
Chucky with his hellish resolution
Divided cigarette in Congress
Has essentially been
Leave us alone
I'm not in love
Even want to give you the appearance of me accepting you being a thing
Jump around and try to repeal the national flood insurance
What disaster protection Act of 1973
Did not work out.
Ghostbusters.
HR 4984 which is titled
A bill to prohibit
Use of funds
For the Peace Corps
Individuals in order for abortions to be provided to those individuals
Just doesn't want to fund people in the Peace Corps
Get abortion
People who are in the
Who had abortions
To that trap know specifically menstruation brings
I don't understand what the point is this
Peace Corps to travel
No Ghostbusters
A 1979's oil and water conservation
Right no co-sponsors.
The Hayloft
From now on
Spider-Man
He did some f****** quirky as s*** while he was in office
So here's the deal Ron Paul is in the house from 1979 to 1985
25-year
According to the official Congressional Bill tracker
There's only one bill that he sponsored that ever became law
It was in 1929
And the bill
To authorize the administrator of General Services of real property in Galveston Texas
Galveston historical Foundation
That's all
Achieved of his own volition
In 25
Leaders of the House of Representative
Now now that those are bills that other
Put forward that he just put his name on
I mean like the fact
That he has had 25 years
Tamisha
Suggest
America gets what they
Trump
It's our fault
Crazy
Look guys we have it covered
It's time for the chickens come home to roost
Was never there never get out of order.
Turn dogs
And those hot dogs
Your neck and I'm the one working
Please pull up.
Yeah
It's such a good damn
Do ya really look at it
What did Ron Paul achieve
Confusing a lot of people about the Federal Reserve in 25 years in office like he
Bill passed as a lot even in life
Like what did he accomplish
Personalized books
Shutter failure
I looked through all the bills he ever sponsored
I didn't see anything about
Like legalizing weed
Writing like that like people
But he never introduced legislation
It like in order to
Breathing like that
Tomorrow
I'd be like
Will you know what at least at least
Good I feel like we made something
Well that will you know at least affect some people's lives
At least I'm not a complete Nutter failure like
In 1913
Take it away from
The people
Institutional
Legible
No more
Federal Express
If we can
Put the Federal Reserve under Treasury
We start
Beautiful
Able to
Control
Monetary policy
Maybe half of the United States
If you put
The Federal Reserve
Under the Department of Treasury
3 what
You is a wow
Whoever is in power to
Control everything about the can understand
What are the healthy weight
The Federal Reserve has more Federal than Federal Express line
But
What is advocating for gray
Quickly the ability of whoever is in power write
Wheatley manipulate the financial system
Would never want to be
I agree
Percentage does look like 26 year old boy standing on top of each other wearing suit
I know this is weird I know people who listen to the podcast game
Everyone
What is
Is the
Proper relay
Should be the prop
Between the chairman of the
The fat in a president
First of all the Federal Reserve
Cousin
Not man's basic
No
Go suck Iran's balls you f*****
Overruled
So long is that
Is
Place
And there is no
Evidence that
Administration
Congress or anybody else
Is requesting that we do things other than what we
Appropriate
NSYNC
What relation
Don't Franklin Armory
Noticed
Alan Greenspan
And I will marry to the issue at hand
Making the old.
Tempe Slayer
But like
Alan Greenspan came on
He's above the law that is not what he
This Is Us
Basically
That on a day-to-day basis
Congress and President
Do not dictate
The Federal Reserve
Specific
Feature of the public-private nature of the bank
No political force
Dictate mods
Without
Prefer the president have
Like applique
Control
What is the preferable system
Doesn't realize how easy that would be
To turn into like
Exactly what we talked about over and over again we're above the law
On a
But also what
Expressing is
Is that
As long as
They're not asking us to do anything inappropriate
It really doesn't matter what our
Right
We exist as Arendt
Yes what it is absolute is beyond the law
As far as I know
Has the Federal Reserve
Whoever has
Mommy nationalized
Is going there and find out
The order
Who's real quick
Just keep in mind
We are going to nationalize the Federal Reserve
Who engaged in corruption
The volcker to Greenspan
And so forth
Barragan
The founding of the Federal Reserve
Is there a back under Woodrow
The Federal Reserve is
Struck out
Three times they didn't stop procrastinating
Didn't stop the banking panic
And now they are
Of the derivative
What is it about Obama
Derivative
Greenspan
So I want to be fair Tuesday
Depressed but it is
Supposedly about the people behind the scenes llamas puppet
Federal Reserve
Very foundational misunderstandings that they have about what the Federal Reserve is
Right.
What the history of the Federal Reserve
What
People have said about centralized Banks
Fabricated
Right now in this case saying that the Federal Reserve is evil and must go because
Failed to stop
Crashes and maybe cause 1
Over the course of 100
5 years since I've been in.
Like around
I mean
He's not making a serious talk
If that's what you bring to the table
Number of crash
Ed Financial
Occurred
Prior
The Federal Reserve
To think about the exact
Number because it's it's nebula
A lot of different sources will give you a lot of different
Regional
Big probably Panic Within
Yeah freshen like
Massachusetts is fine and Main
Yeah 1913 was one of constant chaos
The crashes happen
In the 20s
3 years
Stream for 1907
The economy was basically in a constant state of
Prescient
The myth of the financial Paradise that was uprooted
By the grace of the Federal Reserve
Exactly that it's a myth
It's told around campfires by paranoid anti-government proper
I have no vested interest in the Federal Reserve exist
I don't give a s***
I think it's done a good job but if it didn't
Obito
I looked into these things
I'll be on their side
And I will tell you that like I would say
Honestly at this point in my research
This stuff I'm close to
Fed Up
F*** you
Nogalitos nothing
Department
I love you Dad
Currency in credit
They're the ones that are cut off
Economy
Then they cut it off
Under the song
Toddler doing right now
Bring those out
So frustrating
So clearly
This happens in so many conversations
Where you're talking to somebody and they're saying s*** like that no likes
Okay
You know two things and you know nothing else and none of that provides any context to what
You're saying and you're just wasting my f******
You know two things right
Traces back to the fraudulent story
Diesel Secret
Nevada
So you could buy it all up for
Like we know Alex believes that story is true he's expressed it on multiple occasions
He talks about it all the time it's not true
It's hard not to be here in
That's just an archetype of how do you think
These
Globalist
Quotes
They work
Reply
That way
Not what I hear
There's
By the way
It just seems like that's the archetype
What you think the mo is
But that's just based on nothing
I don't know what to do
Except to say
It was actually built out of the blood
Economy going but they're hoarding the money
Buying up other Banks
Find a Pinterest
Defense contractor
Logan economy
By cutting off
Credit
And then once things really called hello
Hello because then
Play Barbie thing up
And start been putting more money
Autonomy
Asuris
Building something Sheriff
Getting ready
All of the world are always cheering some country
Comes out the road I'm in the world that God can
The foreign arms
These are the people who claim to be
The saviors of the economy the people who created every important
Prices
In the past
And it's a failure
Right now
I don't know what part of the Constitution
He talking
Discuss
It was like
It's unconstitutional.
For all of the people carry around like a
Okay Constitution never actually
I don't know it's the same as people who read those like
New modern language versions of the Bible
I'll make it really modern that we got an updated to live for the kids
We got to get the key
Call Bushwick
Now
Will be saved by Barack Obama
Apartments
I got
Savior
Do jelly and dialectic
Save-A-Lot
With a million person
5/4
Environmental spy Forest you don't get an award for most words in a row
Gallatin manage
It is really funny to look at
The faces of people around it
Leaderboard
There's one woman
Into the middle distance
Listening to him talk
Don't really want to be here also if you look at this crowd this probably one non-white
Mail
A non-white male symbol
I think you're reflecting back
2 hours ago when we saw it behind
Yeah nevermind
The other rides
American
Classical
Baptism
The Communist also do it
Vertically integrated
April
Call Terry insist
Haha you're throwing words
Russia
Thomas Manifesto
Call Central Bank
The ideas they got Marx and Engels
He doesn't exist
Consolidate
Borghese make
Look at it
Doing good here for a second
Because this is all
Just like four so far it's just been Alex Turtle rambling about nothing
This is a lot of words with nothing else going
To prove a lot of
Thanks
Is about Communist Manifesto
First Central Bank
Do they advocate for a private Central Bank
I really don't think that marks was into private
State-run
Nationalized Central Bank
Central Bank of credit
In the hands of the state by means of the National Bank with state capital and
Exclusive Monopoly
That's one of the matters
These
Now I would like to quote Webster Tarpley from earlier in this documentary
One of the first things we got to do a nationalized the FED is go in there and find out the audit
Webster Tarpley is a commie
Advocating for nationalizing the central bank
Good ideas are good I do not
Realize that that's in his documentary
Playing about the idea
This Communist Manifesto talks about Central
Contact
It does
Is the exact same as what
Right
Central banks have existed since the Dutch started getting creative in the 1600
It's not an idea that was created by the Communist Manifesto
I like I like
Play life like a little
Maybe a little bit
There is early 1600s
It started to come together a little bit to me that like
The nascent idea was
The first
Sort of like
Universally accepted Central Bank was also the Dutch
I thought maybe they would come up with the idea and then someone else would improve on concept they're like
Not suck it
Not going to be 100%
But
I'm very worried if I do remember
Get racist about the judge
No no like the way that European history goes it's like
People say that the Dutch were the first people to have a central bank
And I do.
Modern
The West
That's true but if I
I really do
I should tell you that they're reserved
With wooden shoes
So
Use that language anymore
I understand
Wasn't introduced by The Communist Manifesto
That nationalized
Pillar
He's talking about wrote The Communist Manifesto or behind
Although
No I know
It just like that sort of Declaration it seems like
Flippantly throwing around 8
But the reasons if your a new list
Experience with
Awesome Alex
We have
Several hundred episodes
Proving definitively
Not like
Like deeply influenced by
But the reason at this one strikes
Particularly
Is that
Like I can't find any evidence
And
I again
So like
I can't
Go to
He's like
Historical resources about the writing of
The Communist Manifesto
Marxist
Documents
Victor
There were
Unnamed
Hit were around somewhere
So he's going to move the gold
Anti-Semitic
Is because
That like I said I can't I don't think it's true I don't see any
That's true and the Patriots
Absolutely chock-a-block
With people who believe that bankers
Arduous
Conspiracy
And with people who believe that
Communism is this
To the idea that Alex is suggesting that Bankers were Bhai
Hi communism all alone
Is it weird
Influence of those two beliefs that are very
3 prevalent and right
That intersection
Doesn't seem like a coincidence
No
It's it's it's very trouble
The the thing that I think about with anti-Semitic
Underpin
So much of
And not always
Because a lot of times it literally is straight-up
Richer
The thing that I think about is whether or not there
Anti-Semitic
If they recognize
How effective this anti-semitic propaganda has been against
On account of
Several thousand years of people getting one
Propaganda about Jews and then
All the programs in jail break
Whatever
What's granola
The game
They transfer
Play country
Classical hardcore
You asked
But we have the internet
Bro number
Are there
They're playing
Tree rules
21st century
One hell of a fight
With the people
Something important
That guy right there
Six Flags hours
Like a Wavy Gravy hippie
Like Loki but also very obvious
People around Alex
0 people are nodding in agreement
No one is saying and anybody who is paying attention
If you look right now there is that dude looking directly at Stella
Well I think it's probably a collection of real life
Who's the exception of a few mostly angry
Nobody fed rally other than app
Nobody's in support of
No
Okay
But like not in reality
If I was your right
If I was there
And I like
What are you saying
I would constantly be doing
I would be his height man if I was weird Christian
Please read the references
One side
New World Order on the other
And everyone
Are you out there count
Golden Spike
Gofugyourself
Everything
Exposing how many years have been licensed all of them
Let me make this clear
That Chiron was played underneath Alex Jones
While he was talking
You know that in just a moment something he does is important
Should be
It's not
You have no idea
New age of tyranny
You still have no idea
Or a new age
Liberty Inn
New Renaissance
Choice
Who's out there
Okay we can tell you what's going on
It's not
Investigate now
Get involved now
Reach out now
We don't have time
Brothers solution
Look in the mirror
Because you out there
Call Young
Black lives matter
It's going to be up for you mostly mostly white why do you only ever say black when it doesn't matter
Hector God
There are master
We're animals funded Lenin and Stalin
Take a breath
It's not
You're watching me just a minute
I wanted to take some time out middle of the film
F*** it
Go to infowars.com
Real quick
A uniquely disgraceful at pivot
Because he's about to say
You should purchase the
Already watching
I blurt laugh
So hard
Sitting alone in my house
Hugh Butler f***** crazy
I mean sure we're watching it at home but what if you were in a cabin
Sure
You could very easily downloaded
There's a
You know I'm pagan
And we can put on a flash drive
Okay
Great question
Like
What are the only thing left in the armedia sphere
Players
Spears what do you want to live in a world where you can't watch
I know that the world that I've created for myself as one where I constantly watch Alex
But yes I would like to live in a world where I would love that
Good thing that's most
Tell me about bees
Issues that I have with it is
I can't imagine a scenario where it's at
I mean
So whatever
But I I
Can't imagine
Watching this documentary
Emphasize
Because they don't have the internet
Right it's crazy
So here's the problem
That I think Alex is correctly address
If you he's not get money off this
If you were to send somebody a lynx
And they weren't already interested they would watch two minutes
Right
But if you have a DVD copy
And you take it over to your friend's house
Their captain
Escape
You be not exactly really help
Make sure they know there's a
Physical reason to continue watching videos
Youtube.com
Alice's getting money
We should sell it DVD copy of this entire
Elvis documentary
Screwed up
Victoria realize DVD sales
There's the video of Jordan and I sitting mostly
Like Glee.
Drinking couple beers
How much is the 2019
I don't know
Anyway
More than just trying to sell the DVD
Prisonplanet TV and download high quality
To give your friends your family your neighbor your community
Also want to challenge
All of yours out there
Timer
As you watch this film
I've written
50 pages of notes typed
Single-spaced
I could not have taken
More notes
Alex
You suck
Because I'm confident in the information
And I want you to not trust me
For yourself
That Obama is a betrayer and a liar
A Judas goat
A
Trojan Horse
To bring in the One World Government
Infowars.com quality DVD
Super high quality
To give your friends your family your neighbors
And warn the public
That prisonplanet.tv
Is it f****** hilarious
His speech in the middle of that End the Fed protest
Chiron
Warning
Announcement
It's amazing anytime destruction of
System they're always
Following up with
And now
You should participate in your very
Directions
You should get per night
If you get too into me
My friend
Cold
The Kennedy assassination
Already
This
Then we are already played playing the same clip in
Make no mistake about it
Vincent remember HR 1100011
1100011
Got it
You just recorded this one Alex
A very powerful
Football
Assassination
Kennedy
And the others
Father
Beginning of the Vietnam
Beginning
Absolute domination
The Wall Street
Poop over every other
Nobody else counts
Except
The Wall Street money man
United States
Into
For progress but something
Destruction
That doesn't need to remain that way
The interests of the American people is
The fight to take your government back for
From Wall Street
And make the United States
The forest
Easily could do
If we could just break
The power of
Of the people behind up on
Do you think break the power of the people behind Obama
But
There's nothing substantiv there at all and
Terms of
Prescriptions for Pat's forward there is nothing
At the things that
Guitar player Alex or any of the people who are
The
Supposed experts that are in the documentary there's nothing that they're advocating for that is outside of just like
F*** all this there's nothing really to
I mean I guess they would probably argue that audit the Fed
Is constructive
Not recognizing besides audit all the time
Destroyed affair.
Productive
Let's just go with what that motherfuker said my boys spider tarps
Motherfuker
Like oh I'm Erica could easily be a positive force for the world
Exactly
Everything you said so far
You want America to be a giant shitbag s******* all over the rest of the world same time
Deeply
Relieved
To accept Trump
Except
At least he doesn't
You know like it Italy
The window
Is that
We should
Luke
Iran
But other than that
We will be fine
We don't know that for sure
Probably
They all love
I don't know
I never know what it is with these guys and their misunderstanding of the history of Iran Iraq
Whether or not they know they're different countries.
Ever ask them to define the difference between Shiite
He's gone into it on his show before
Would like blissfully ignorant
He does
He changed his position
Means like
Making a
Choice
Winner
America being awesome
You're right like it that's that's also
Everything is
It's all
And just in service of
This s***'s bad
We should do better whatever the guy I don't like a guy
Impart
It doesn't matter if you're Democrat or Republican
This is non-partisan
This is purely non-partisan
Racial
Wheel of white
The First Take
The main Banks
Severe up which
For started by Adam wise
In Racha
This is a big problem
Adam Vice
He's the guy who started the Illuminati
Yeah
Yeah you started goddamn
Is it from 1776 until 1785
And then was disbanded because I was like
F****** stop
He had nothing to do with banks
He was trained as a lawyer
Covid-19
Free is coming in here and expressing his ideas
And the Rothschilds started
I know where he's getting
Where is the 1991 book that was written by
Pat Buchanan
Call Javon New World Order
No
Wait Pat Robertson
Then I meant
Crew from SNL
Right
Patrick
I know that this probably comes
From reading that book because
Horses that
Look into it and find
Those books
They were mostly
Like
The protocols
The arguments that was made in Pat Robertson
Was that
You can use
Dispenser
Pat Buchanan was making the argument that
Adams
Right
History shows that
When history stairs
That the order was disbanded
In fact
They went under Underground
And they met
Collaborated with
European Jewish bankers
Collaboration
Does the CFR and that's
So that's
The piece of Pappy
Buchanan's
Literary career
Alex Jones
You've given credit
But I think there's a lot of sources
Before it that are much more
Yeah
That we pay attention
Comes up here is because George Humphreys
Clearly expressed
Adam B
Was involved with
I'm like starting
He brings up the Rothschild
Yeah I do to me when I hear that like
Jose
The only real connection
I really
A device of a
Thinking
Betty does
Anyway
Have all fine
The Messianic
Warleader
The last two under
Polian
Lenin
200 years
Darling
Adolf Hitler
Franklin Delano
Roosevelt
Stocking right now
Barack
Haircut
He should get a haircut
This is the perfect example of one of these things
Complaining about earlier but the idea
These people just make extravagant a historical claim
And then if you're like
No
Did I prove me wrong
Let it was independently wealthy
Biggest family was super rich
Independently wealthy because of the
Sure
You got it he gots the money from the Germans because the Germans wanted to have to go back to Russia when he was in Exile
How big is it
The USSR which was in their strategic interests but it wasn't
That much money
It was It was a pittance
Compared to
Yeah what
Had no reason to
Globalist money
Throw in all of the western history you possibly can because
About the history of
Anywhere
Stalin and Hitler
During the global it's raining of Terror like what the f*** are you talk
My complaints about the State Historical
Is that like
All of this
They don't even give a fuk
A bright any other history
Snow White
Who's shares a border with Russia
China
How old is China
Like are they real
Would you say that maybe those two histories or perhaps
Level that people should globalist Hitler globalist have to do with it
Genghis Khan
Whatever hookah
Gives a s***
Deeply salient
All of this history
Even their even their negative histories white people it's all white
Even their weird deeply conspiratorial a historical s*** is all like
Who gives a s***
About what non-white people were doing
The banking cartel has established a beachhead of 1913 to the Federal Reserve
1940 Chevrolet set up a little Shadow government
For the National Security
Burbot from 47 on
The National Security state began the long process
I'm absorbing
Federal and state bureaucracy
All the same time
Undermining the Constitutional power of congress
What
By controlling the issuance of currency and credit
The private Federal Reserve was able to buy up
Most of the Fortune 500
Whoa company wouldn't sell
The bankers would unleash Federal regulator to run them out of business
Anybody listening to this who knows anything in our in 10 minutes into the documentary
Turn it off earlier
Go fuc yourself
So
That crazy
The Federal Reserve is the Federal Reserve own most of the forts
500 companies
He said the Fortune 500 I don't think he recognizes that that's just a that that's a term
For like the 500 most
The profitable companies
Each year the list comes out
Including the
Guy
Federal Reserve
Sound right
He just said that they own all of the Fortune 500 or anybody
Warren
And knocked about a bit
What about nature
He was in the cut
Well good I hope you get this percent
Look
What is Alec
What is Alex
Tyranny of the American economy while like if he's if he's not like prison
He doesn't believe that I don't know
I'm not saying
Like where's the cutoff point for the Federal Reserve today only
Okay alright next year now that I know that now
He is not just making s*** up
Which spoiler alert
That would mean that the Federal Reserve owns
Walmart
Apple CVS Health Amazon AT&T Ford General Motors and everything all the way
We down to Yum brands and Western Union
Cuddledown
Are you saying that
Oh that makes
Krs-1 Burger King
Fair enough
Herberger's
Not touch the Bell beefer
Really saying that
Who owns
Because the chairman of the Federal Reserve
Is he saying that that's who owns it
Cuz that's a person is appointed by the president serves a
When is there an office they own all these companies is that
Now
This is where we're getting back to my earlier save
That it has to be some dude
Who's like
In the in the middle management
He's got to be he's got to be there
He's not appointed
He's not on
12 people who are relevant in the Federal Reserve
The owner of the Fortune 500
No that's not
Kevin the owner of the Fortune 500 companies put out the list
Yep
And he often isil
Legitimately if he sings like the chairperson
Federal Reserve
AR
Exorbitantly rich
Another term is over
They are no longer on it
But
Maybe that's not the case maybe he's the abstract
Dia of the board of God
Owns Aldi
These companies
Complete and utter
You know he's just praying that his viewers don't realize how stupid that sentence like
The Federal Reserve bought up the Fortune 500
Because if
If they don't
But if the board and all those companies
Then all of their profits
At the end of the year would go into the
Treachery
Feel like all right
To the government
Isn't rephrase the but that's what the government does have the problems of the government
Deeply in
Since 1933 if all the Fortune 500 companies profits are being funneled back into the treasury
Which they would have to be at the Federal Reserve
Vanoss
The point being
Alex
Does federal government is the richest
It is ever been
8 also bankrupt
And
Both simultaneously
But they can't afford any
Everything and nothing
All the prophets are there
They're running a death
What else is there
Oh they don't make anything and we need to reduce the size of government
And they should sell off the Fortune 50 should do they should
Sell off the Fortune 500 that they don't own
I don't know
I don't think so I think you should
Control
These companies
Here's the here's the deal
Like real talk
Big big
Your situation
Knowing what we know and what we've gone over about the structure
The Federal Reserve
Like it
Ludacris
To hear something
Thinking they are a strictly private business
For-profit
That takes all this money and
You would think maybe it's possible that they bought up all the
These companies we live in a world where everybody
Just run by the Federal Reserve
But
If you do those two steps that you've already talked about being so painful
8 boring and frustrating
If you make it
Get through those two or three steps
To the point where you understand
What the structure of this
Actual private-public
What business is
You would hear that sentence
To be like go f*** yourself
You think you're an expert
Even easier
Remember
Remember how much you said that the Federal Reserve
Made
And how much they go
The Federal
I gave 89%
Write 45 billion dollars
Is 31.7 billion
Alright the operator
You know how much
Much money
4 billion hours
Google makes evereve
45 minutes
More
Yeah
Yeah it's crazy
Cannot buy or sell the fortune 4000
All this is like
He's just preying on people's ignorance and like
Hoping they don't
Have any spider set
Wilfred Webster
Write any any kind of Institute be like
Hold on that sounds like b*******
Dumser
Question point of order
Are you stupid
Yes alright I will retract
We have more to get
Documentary
I don't care really too
Like
We've already had multiple fake quotes
We've had
Allowing
F****** Ron Paul brother save it three people voted on the Federal Reserve
Yeah but
We've shown it explicit very literal sent three people
Did vote on that act
There were multiple others as well
But it from a very
Yes
Three people did both
We've also seen a complete misunderstanding unawareness of
How the Federal Reserve work
Were you seeing
Completely childish understanding of civics and how the guy
Take anything serious
It's Thunderdome man I don't listeners of our
Cast we are at
Eight and a half hours at on the show we are at 1 hour
Documentary
Spirit
Vic was lovely to know you don't really give a f***
Private central banks in Europe
The United States in English
Do taxpayer money
And loaned it
At over 30% in
The third world nation
Not to pay back the loan
Their third world puppets
Wood sign agreements
Stated
That one the country defaulted
The banks would be given all the natural resources and in for
Structure of the One Sovereign land
But worst of all
The countries would pledge future taxes
Paid by the people
In perpetuity
Is profit to the private
That's a bad deal right I mean
What countries is he talking about
About nothing
They did this to third world countries
Kind of sounds like
He's just
Extrapolating on The Americans
Treatment
Is that what you're doing or likes trying to
Repurpose colonialism evil that just like blame something else
I don't know I don't know babe
I bet
Most history
Is now being
Used
To benefit me again
And he's putting this b******* around about like
These third-world countries are in
I have to pay taxes to
You know there's a bunch of countries that have central banks
Don't have income tax
That's one of them's probably memory
Has a central bank give me an
I believe is another one that has never heard go back no no income
Who gives a
By the year 2000 there were few Nations
People sitting around
Design
The globalist were now on
The destruction
Of the western Nations economy
F*** that guy
They first remove banking regulation
Alright
I am going to give him this
He
Put up a picture of
Clinton
But but
Especially nefaria
Wow
It is
Bill Clinton
A bunch of
Look
I don't care if I'm on your team or not on your team
That picture is nefarious as father
That picture is like the epitome of
Look what we did to the minority
Goodbye
Play Nickelback
Glass-steagall
It's regulation
Businesses operate
Like I don't understand like I really
I don't need miss flippantly or just like some food
I'm pretending to not understand
I don't
Get why he's mad
That they got rid of glass-steagall
Other than the idea that it's very clear
Too bad thing
The only thing that
Cuz he hates regulations so f****** much
He's allergic
Makes him upset
I don't I don't get it you eat now complaining about glasses
They don't
Any bets apartment pretending to not understand
Nothing these people are back
Vessels for whatever nonsense it is that will get
The Koch brothers 2
Feel good today
Either that or just sort of like what
Point on
How can I get more lives now
How can I get more eyes on my product
Ragweed
Oh yeah
This allowed their front company
To issue
Unlimited credits
And the setup colossal Ponzi scheme
The likes of which
The world never seen
The scams were advertised by the control corporate media
As completely legitimate
Because of the Fantastic return
Private investor
Corporation
State and local
Invested heavily
They got taken the bait
Hook Line & Sinker
Troy console
The bankers themselves
Began to bad-mouth
The scams of Vegas
And create it
Watch the central Bankers cut off the tsunami
Fiat money
But they have been using the pump up the bubble
When Congress and the public
Refuse to write the finance oligarch
Blank check
The bankers began doing gay
In financial terrorist
But the world would go into another Great Depression
Unless their demands were met
Further destroying
The stock market
Biggest one-day loss in history
But even that
Wasn't enough to force Congress to capitulate
So
At that point in history 777
Repeat not record three times in 2018
The top
Three of all-time drops
I'm a single day or two
Are you saying
So hold on
Let me try and get it
Right so
Which as we all know is a nightmare in a disaster and it should never have happened
Rick Fridays in 1930
I'm sorry
Sorry actually
I I I like it
A while
Lot of my comedy goes that way
Initially Drew you're not you're not really a lapse
I think it's just why I quit
Alright
You got it
Amor
Comic
You're way funnier than
Iwa sushi
Federal Reserve
Hear the last name
Crushes
All of the stock market
Laid
To everybody for the hundred years since
105 minutes after that
Problems
1929 Great Bridge
2 or whatever in that
Maybe
Webster
But then you could also
Consider the.com bubble subprime
Mortgage crisis all kind of
But even if you wanted to
Consider those two it's a pretend you got
But that's last
And in that 20 years
Federal Reserve
And you could say that from the
Fadh2
1929 and then what was the oil in 1933
No emergency
Citibank Bill had to be passed in 1933
Just going to stay out of the Great Depression
They they have this guy who had this like
Whole he's like
Listen I'm going to make a
Like a fresh agreement I'm going to make it
Rarity
So then
Laid out this thing and you know what it's watered down by these motherfuker
But it still strong
And it keeps going and then let's say
In sometime.
Nike
Somebody start trying to
Apartments
Right so how many Market crashes did we have
In between 1933
Well if you don't count the already existing
Depression right
Ruger 10
0 now after this like
Let's end this is a completely completely random numbers
Completely random number 1980 passed
Have we had
A few
Okay it's almost like they'll really easy
Federal Reserve
Like Boogie
No baby
Deregulation of
I mean is Teddy to point out but
Alex is like
And his reasons were too wrong and you're wrong and f*** off Alex go f***
Senator inhofe of Oklahoma
And Congressman Brad Sherman of California
Amongst others
Nobu
With martial law by the White House and the treasury of
Olay didn't pass
The so-called Baker bailout bill
The beginning of the episode about how Brad Sherman came on Alex Jones Show
Refuses to acknowledge
Which of the he explained
You was talking about
Only way they can pass this bill
Is by creating
And sustaining a panic
Bad acne
His fear is not
Justified
Many of us were told in private
Did it we voted against this bill
On Monday
Vet
The sky would fall
The market would drop to 3,000 points
The first day another couple thousand the second
And a few members were even told
That there would be martial law
In America if we voted no
That's what I call firme
If there's one thing I've learned from watching C-SPAN
You can hear a man
Talkin on the floor of Congress
And hear all those echoes
It's because there are so many people who are so
Right
It might be like 8
Situations people on the floor
It is like you know you want to put something in the Congressional Record
That's possible
Situation with this was
I hear Brad Sherman
More deferiet then
Exactly what
Describe
The show
I don't hear this is being like
Someone some strong-arm a****** commands like
Martial law you son-of-a
S'mores
Everyone is freaking out
The idea that this could lead
The monetary system
People talk s***
Can you imagine how bad
Going to get
This is the time when braking show and starts
Bright
No
Does anybody
The gorgeous
Can we just get a sponsorship
From the concept of gold
I think we
Probably
Could
How many based on the fact that Webster Tarpley still has a show on Genesis I bet we could too
Except
Just like
He's.
Yearly talkingshit on Alex like
He clearly hates libertarianism
And Ron Paul are there
Can't imagine what his standard for like
How do you get kicked off setting
All I want to do is sell diamond gusset
That's all I've ever wanted this way
I will sing I will sing that suck
Can song
Okay
Unjust
The final version of the bill was
Was Kept Secret from the Congress until minutes before the vote
On October 3rd 2008
This isn't true
The bailout bill was not
Litchfield Pasta House on September
29th 2008
Took up a new version of it
October 1st 2000
And then it was sent to the house
Voted through on October 3rd
It was quick
But it wasn't
Nor were they given minutes
This is all just b*******
The Federal Reserve and promise
Total transparency
Let every dime would be accounted for
The Democrats and Republicans
Bernie pissed again
Step Up
Philip White
Let's do what's right
For the country at this time
The second time
The time to act
Is now
Superbad
The possibility of a crisis
Turning into a capacitor
Publix
The building just give 700 billion dollars to the banks
It was a blank
Check
And as of February 2009
9.7 trillion
Has disappeared into a black hole
Not true
Not true at all
The place that I did
Here's an article that Alex puts up on
Screen about this 94
7 trillion
Dollars
It's interesting because if you go find that article
Will you find it that
In this article a clearly talks about the 9.7 trillion dollars and 7
100 billion dollar numbers
They're two different things
700 billion dollars is
Is the bailout the tarp
Save-A-Lot
Who's passing late 2008
The 9.7 trillion dollars is a figure that's being batted around
About what the Federal Reserve was going to land
The banks
They're different
Money
They're different things
And
They're not missing it's not missing
It's not stolen
It's not messing
Yeah if you accept
Inception
Federal Reserve
As some sort of a
Evil
Evil Corporation
Within 24 hours of its Passage
Secretary of Treasury Henry Paulson said
They were no longer going to use the money to unfreeze the mortgage Market
By buying bad day
We went
The Congress
Illiquid assets look like the way to go
As a situation worsened
The facts change I will never apologize
Changing an approach or strategy when the facts check
Honestly clip
Makes
Like a reasonable person angry at all
Apologize for changing my position when facts
Change
Yeah
You're ever going to get good thing I was wrong
We didn't
Approaching we f*****
Stop sorry about that
And then we tried this and that didn't work much as we thought it would
What's going on so we're going to do that
Was that we thought it was this
Whoops
That was Henry Paulson
Yeah day later
Henri-paul
Flip the script on everybody
And now we're not
When do we start
Going to do
Took him out on a stroll
Like nah f*** that
It's my way or the highway
24 hours later
He tricked everybody
Bulshit
The emergency economic stabilization Act of 2008 was passed into law in October 3rd
The quote Alex Jones
Henry Paulson
It comes from an article in Bloomberg
That was reporting on the speech
He was making there
It was from November 12th
Over a month later
The quote in reference to what they were going to do with the second half of the 700 building
Dollars
The initial plan of buying up all the devalued assets
Clearing up
I'm gone as well as they'd hoped
So the treasure is looking for a different
Approach instead of looking for ways to die
Keep going down the same road
They're exploring the idea of even consume
Credit One
Right or wrong
It's not some sort of evil Act
Weather
This was November 12th 2008
That's correct when Obama had been present
A sex years
I think you've been
Did four days
Going to make hay out of that door to dance all over Alex being like this
None of this is Obama's fault really
Is really is the police involved with
Personal level
The only reason I don't
Keep bringing that up is the Alex pretends that
The point of this documentary is not Obama
Who's the dummy
Isn't really a refutation of Alex
Still just throwback
I stopped myself whenever I
We're talkin about
The only time
Looks like Alex is using to C-SPAN appearance from Ramen 2006
Irrelevant
The way that we're doing this podcast I feel like we need at least once every hour to remind people that
This is not about Obama.
Not really can't be because he's only been in office for less than
Paulson has in the meantime admitted
The subprime mortgage crisis
Is map
The car is really
Entire world
System in the bankrupt
Most of the banks in London
Ending.
In Wall Street
Subprime
Mortgage is what he's talking about his
Derivative
The reason I write mrs. because of the idea that he's like why are we wet this
Approach and it didn't have the effect Lee wanted to
So we're do it we're going to use the rest of the money
Reproach
Webster Tarpley
Pretending that what Henry Paulson
We're saying was this isn't
The reason
For the things
The situation
As opposed to being like
This is not be the best way for us to move forward
It's a fine distinction but this is a lie
Derivative
Are the center of the
The crisis
Which season
Where the money would go in
I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing arm
The American people ever allow private Banks to control the issuance of their currency
First by inflation
Then by deflation Banks and corporations
Children children wake up home
Issuing power
Should be taken from the bank
And restored to the people
Properly belongs
Thomas Jefferson
Third president of the United States
Daytona track record so far
Dan before you say another goddamn word did Thomas Jefferson actually write that f****** s***
But also the reason I waited till the end
The whole thing up on
Sunscreen
Didn't happen
F****** fat
We have had like
I think it was like 6 fake quote in endgame and now we're like to work
At this point on this episodes
You know that's
Documentaries of
Completely out of whole cloth making a quote now with this quote it's really interesting
The earliest reference to this quote according to
The Jefferson in cycle
Pedia is from 1937
Cousin died
Right that's Drake number one
Strike number two is the use of the word
Deflation to describe the process that
The money goes
According to the Oxford English Dictionary that words intake on that meeting until night
Almost
100 years after he died
You know where you said that
In his defense
Thomas Jefferson
Love balloons and its many metaphorical
Until 1920
Oxford English Dictionary
Etymology
A good resource
Alex has up their on-screen this is a letter to Albert
Gallatin but according to
Sometimes
Those words don't Gallatin has been dead
Those words appear in any letters
Jefferson Road Gallatin
I believe the banking is
Students are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies
Is a paraphrase
In a letter to John Taylor
14 years
After Alex is claiming that letter was completely made up
I love it
Yeah I know
It is you can trace it down cuz those people who care about this stuff a lot
Fun to realize that you could make a lie that everybody knows
Bulshit today
Become the Bedrock
Truth 100 years
Might create an entire dump movie
Record is one of the most
Important of Alex
That idea of if we let these Banks do what they want to do
For our children or grandchildren to be slaves in a land where we conquered it
Knowing
Just made that up
1930 Thomas Jefferson
It's very rewarding to me
Yeah they're like
Hahaha
What is nice about it is that because our language is so
Completely and utterly different
Now it would be hard
2 makeup
Like it would be hard to make up quotes
Emoji Emoji Emoji
Believing the truth emoji
Easier to track
Imagine that wouldn't
Congressional Record
See you in 10 years
The Congressional Record
Is going to look like
Your friend of fraud
Like the idea that deflation didn't have that
Back then is a
Marker the people
Can use
To go back and be like
There's no way he said this amazing
That's not
Someone else wrote
It's like when you go back through the Bible and you start looking at the derivation of all the words you like
This was not rich
Whenever its purported to have been written
This is clearly showing the signs of this time. And so on
Fixer
The Great
I like
Sprite has a really fun
He has a degree in
Secretary Paulson came in with the vice president
You idiot
Need
To get rid of the Coronavirus
Derivative
Products
Different names
For this
You know
If we traded
Credit-default swap
Okay but they
They talked about them as though they knew what
Hell they were
You got the money
And you remediate
Italy
What
Items what are
Now the treasury just just
Basically cut that out of the bill
A banks
Hoarding the money
That they're getting from the tarp they're using the money to purchase other bags
And I remember
We're going to give you the money that you want you do what you want with it
Unless you directed
Pacifically it's not going to happen
I don't think anyone
Questions
Kashkari
That you're working hard
Carquest
Before
Yeah
Kashkari was worth it was it that's
That's Bush Administration
Implying there's very clearly
The best interests of the people or for
Just trying to play this up as some sort of like a
Are you working for the Illuminati
System of revolving door
Regulatory capture as they would be
Also
One thing
And I need to talk about
It's so good
This is the only thing
That I've ever been able to think about kucinich
And I
Read a lot about his
Policies
I've read a lot about hitting today
Nothing more than what you're about to say
This is the one thing I said I thought
Has any Taylor ever been able to figure him out
Every night
There are zero since I have ever seen him in that make even the slightest
Throughout its past
President Bush and Senator Obama
Worked in tandem to get Congress to pass the bill
Without even having time to read it
Despite the fact
But in major polls
98%
Of the American people
We're against the bill
The leadership in both parties were for
They had time to read the bill
But also he keeps saying both
Parties and what we see on screen is again
He's playing the exact same
Footage
Pelosi
Raw
Yeah
That's not 98
Percent is
Crazy literally
In America
History
98% of America
Has never agreed on something.
I can't find
Amy pool
Water's good like 98% of America does not agree on
There's no way 98% of Americans agreed on anything
Way too much time trying to find this pulse
I dug through all sorts of Records
Trying to figure out like he's varipole the
Earlier
I found that bull that Alex was lying about the 9%
Approval rating for Congress was based on
There was no poll that said that when there's just a slight misunderstanding
I can't find any
I'll tell you this on September 22nd 2008 Rasmussen
Posted
It showed a 28
Sing for the bailout
That's a Baseline
Around 1
On September 26th
2018 USA Today poll found that 70%
Approve Congress doing
But 56% thought that plan should be
Then what Bush suggested
America in a nutshell that's the most America you got
3 something over half days
Fine I don't know
That should be written
Pool if you make a decision
Display respect hours and hours
Negotiating Ono American
Forever red
But I also understand
How many USA Today doesn't really have the best like polling
History like in terms of their like
Statistics of credibility
I smell that pulled
Those numbers look like
You bet that seems like
Fivethirtyeight accuracy Remember the Time. 2 and it feels like
Feels like emotionally I might have been there
Yeah we got to do something
Whatever it is you said he might have accurately pinpoint in my emotional state
Articulate
USA Today
October 1st 2008. Search center released a poll showing
45%
The government's plan was the right to
Things to do
So that's pretty close to a
45 +
And ABC
Post survey
Not Apple survey
From September 29th found 45%
Approval rating
For the proposed
Spelt
I can't find anything that even comes
Close to approximating a 2%
Santa purple radio
I know that as things went on things got left
I understand
I still can't find anything from around that
Time that is even
Close
Wilson pool
From September 22nd
The 28%
Is the closest I can find
I don't know
Just making this up
I I I really think you might
Just be
Out of nothing
In the in the same way that a dictator
Re-election by 98% of the vote
Is specials
Yeah this
This is
If it was a real polite I wouldn't believe it
And I really want to come in and Barack Obama because it's we were involved in the
This and that and different provisions of the bill to pay
Persuade people
He really gave them confidence
That this was the right decision
All for the America
Can people
Even though it wasn't
In our view a great bill
This is Nancy Pelosi
Alex is trying to present this as like her saying this bill sucks
Yeah it's like she's really expressing
When is the idea that
We would have wanted something a little bit better
That that's something our Democratic caucus would have
I'd like to thank Barack Obama for
Negotiator in summer
God brought us all together
Probably the right thing
Things to do
There's nothing nefarious here
For them to vote on the moment
To also think they need to do here
And that is bro
But the members of our caucus
Excite
The passes legislation
But they were hoarding the bailout
Money and using it to buy up smaller healthy Banks and insurance companies
They're so real quick
This is something
F****** evil
Because the idea that these Banks already
Tons of money from the government
They're using it
To buy a buzzard
Alex is suggesting this is super
But this isn't what I want
Presenting it
Tubi
If you go to the article that he just flashed up on screen there
Explain exactly what the situation is
Right after the part where Alex
The article probably strategically
The article goes on to say quote
There's a growing consensus among
Among Treasury and other Federal officials that allowing healthy Banks
To use the money to acquire Bank in
Jeopardy
Availing
Could stabilize the economy
And bolster confidence
This could also save money for the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation
Naturally this isn't ideal that he wouldn't want to be creating even bigger ant
These were as a whole excuse or balances
Beware the strategy might be considered
Think about it like okay
You got this back
Bright
We need to help them
Wreck that other smaller bank is also failing
We got to give that money to
Is that bigger back with the money that we gave them buys that smaller Bank
We no longer have to get out to get us by banking
Yeah there is a scent to it that makes sense
It's not a good strategy
It's not good for those situations where when you when you are in Congress there's a party that's like
I just want one guy
Kind of like
From their whole structure who's going to go like
Oh that's a dumb idea
That's the idea that got us to where you had right now
Is necessary
It would be me in Congress in flip
Swapped smoking split
It's like just split
In the house like
I wouldn't do that
5 years
Then
No
It's a bad
Absolutely
But if it
Time when we're talking about
An emergency
It does make sense
As
Business complex
Could help
Trouble
Could be efficient
You observe a lot of the damage
Did but but again
More importantly
Strategies f****** stupid
Yeah that's it
That's okay but see again that's not like a specific
Failure to failure of like
Well you're in Congress for a short
So this makes
Idea
It would still suck for a while and you might get
You know you might
Losing your next election
If you did the right
And complicated
But is there is it is judicious
Is it wise
Is it a smart thing to do
It was sort of descriptions life
Are applicable but like I don't know
Right or wrong
Right or wrong aspect
It is hard it's hard to say
I don't know I'm glad to make these decisions
But I can look at it from afar and
I don't need the hindsight of 20
18 to know
What was actually going
Haha
All these Banks got all this money in there like haha now we're going to buy up all these other back
What sort of an arrangement that was going on about the ideas
We can absorb
The damage they could come to the
The FDIC
I help out
And also there was a little bit of that
Working bikes
I'm sure there's
When was working like a charm
Next
The central Bankers loan the federal government back
787 billion dollars of our own money
But I didn't really spell
Sophie
That package stabilized Bieber
Congress was given less than 70 Page Plus
Barack Obama
Who had pledged
Campaign Trail
Toy 5 days before a bill can be voted on
So that the Congress and the people
Could have a chance to read it
Studded the stimulus was too important
Had to be passed
Before anybody
Could see it or read it
Or the crisis
Would turn into like a task
Doing a little or nothing at all will result in even even greater deficits
Even greater job loss
Even greater loss of income
Even greater
Los Ocampo
Correct
On all fronts
Turn a crisis into a
Catastrophe
Hagrid
Friday passing
Gangster fashion
President Ford
Earlier to Alex for his restraint dog whistle
Earlier you said that they were just giving in
And they were given it
Hour to Reidsville that's not
I was introduced on January 26th
2019 Pasta House on
On January 28th
It was voted on the Senate on February
10th 2000
How's time frame isn't ideal
I would I would
Refer more than a day and a half probably
But an hour
Gangster fashion bulshit
Alex
He said
That it is
Passed on Friday
Vacation
So here's the
I hate prison
To go on vacation
Regularly
40%
If not
60%
Of the days of the year
The do the stimulus bill passed
The house on January
28 2000
Which was when
Which is a tooth
Congress passed
Versions of the Bell
So in order to get it through they had to go to conference
Negotiate the Bell
They reached Goshi ation on February 13th 2000
Which is a Friday
Probably without to talk
They got through conference on
Next Friday
It was signed by Obama
February
The following Tuesday
That's probably because the Senate didn't take their vote
Until
The conference bill passed
Ellen up at like 5:30 p.m. on a Friday
Got to be out of there by 5
It's a Friday
Coworkers
Didn't die
So we couldn't all have a 40 hour work
Strongly
Residents can also check the f*** out
Going around a little bit about the bag zpacks bill at 5:30 on a Friday
They didn't sign it
Until Tuesday
Is because the
The 14
The day after
Is Valentine
And
Monday
February 16th
Was president
The federal holiday
Let the clerks have the day off
You can't
What what you think the president's going to take a
The federal holiday off
It is
It's literally his Dead Presidents
He took a vacation over the long weekend
They passed the bill
And then when he came back
On Tuesday
Yeah
Alex is talking about like you made it seem like such an emergency and then he
Was gone for the weekend
Will you look at this the reason it was an emergency
He wasn't a matter of a day or two it was a matter of dragging your
And that very queer
From there he was actually saying in the Red Orchid
We can't afford
To wait around
Bureaucracy getting away
Because
Do you have a situation where Congress
Could
Really
Gum up the works and they could get to
The infighting
Could be a whole bunch of nonsense you could end up with
A bill getting stuck
A month-to-month
And if you waited that long
It would
Be a disaster
A day or two
Knock knock that big a deal
Like
I think he's a f****** s*** head in Oliver
But if you waited a day to sign a bill
Victon
Matter he waited a day
I would never be like
This m***********
It's not
What
To live in the world
Where that's my problem with Trump
You can't sign it until a week later
The issue
He could sign
Because him
And his wife publicly
At least a is a man
Valentines
A joke Venable calls me out on it
Be my biggest problem
We're keeping people in
F****** 10
What's the fun thing about being children in front of them
I would love
It's a fun thing about being a patriot battling ghost
That is nice kind of know that
The Patriot movement is a giant group of people saying
Everybody who hates you
The spending bill
Does find photos have your license check
Donors
Bruit donated
The both part
I guess as the world's slid deeper into depression
Snipers to braided the fire sale
That they had created
I believe
But again
It seems like if you hated Sarah so much as he did
Surahs on PBS
But I was able
In your own self
Go off
Well I mean like there's been multiple occasions already where his voice-over doesn't match
What's showing on screen
No that's the b-roll
Right
English the phrase burdens of the office is overstated
Why did the financial collapse have to have
On my watch just I don't believe
The president-elect Obama Beast full of self-pity
I honestly think that that
You responded very poorly to that I think that's one of the Bush clips
But I've seen
That makes me like him the most
Yeah
It sounded like
He was giving some sort of like
But he was poking
He was addressing the idea of the burden of office
I don't really think
It's all that. Smith
Who would take pity on himself
Wifey f****** things
Agreed
Disagree
But I know that you do my letters only know that letter that every president
Write to the next president
His letter is going to be like
I learn how to write with a cramp and that's it
F****** God we're all going to die
I don't know
I don't want to send
W foot like the only reason I responded that weighs cuz you were like 5
I think it's pretty good
There's a lot of clips of bush in this documentary that are fuckingawesome
With their access
2 Unlimited Fiat capital
They can now buy up sectors of the world economy
Not already controlled by them
Likewise over a century
Artificially engineered
Address before the trilateral commission
Terrible graphics
The super National sovereignty in World Bank
Is surely preferable to the National termination practice
Is a higher-quality version right now at prisonplanet.com if you were wondering
Rockefeller
Of an old decaying white man
Prisonplanet.com
Do you hear that quote
It wasn't real
God
Another fake quote
God dammit he's talking about the supernationals
Collaboration of these octagon
Is definitely preferable to the states
YouTube video that went around
Pearson Redwing Circle based
Video
Bialy copy
The speech that Rockefeller gave at Bilderberg
D91
But
If you look at this video it itself says
Video
Like on
The goddamn picture that's on screen
It is just an image it's not a video
Is the picture it says
In parentheses
Audio simulation
It is not a recording at all people act like it is
There's nothing to back this up
No transcript
There's nothing
Start making the rounds until 2 years after
So my feeling is abs
Any other time
Based on all
Keeps using
I hope
Yeah absolutely stupid
Global business
Illuminati running
Worldmaster
It still wouldn't say they're all so here's what I would say
I understand that you expect privacy of Bilderberg you know like it just
They work under Chatham rules House Rules
The understanding is
You can
This is actually really what they go by
They use this ruleset where
You can use any information
That you got
But you can't talk about
Do static or anything like that
I am there if Hilda Berg you and I are there
Information about bikes
Thought I have
Whatever right
But you can't say that
I told you that
There's that
Christine Fair
The reason I'm bringing this up is that hike
In 90
G91
Many Bilderberg meetings before that
Jeez it's not his first time
He's not some sort of Green rookie
Rain comes in
And gives a speech where he says
Hahaha
We are used to
That would be gauche
But even if
Why would you f****** say that
You're only saying it to people who already know that that's what you believe if
Is the king of the whole thing be like
Now yours
Betsy
F****** stupid well what
Concerns me is where is the king of lobbyists
He's not play I don't know
What is always
Session rights
You got it you got to steal one of his client
Oh no
He'll require
Trial by combat
That's another way to do it
Ultimately it's
Everyone's going however
Cast of House Rules so
You guys have a fight
And going to talk about
Peter chapter blue
Bring this up is like trying to
Obtain the fuc
Good idea
I welcome Alex to prove
I will retract everything I said about this
But I think it's f****** stupid
Well I'm saying
I make a decorations
Thought well hey
I would say I would say
There's no way
Doesn't come back
Text Daniel
And if that's okay
I say
Get that
We have all been held Within
The
Jail cell of that Ponyta
That jail
And that is where we will have to cut it off for today I hope you all enjoyed yet another
Spurious quote
That Alex is peddling as if it's real
What a shock there's this documentary is lousy with Alex
Just making sure it up
But we will be back
Tomorrow
For the conclusion does thrilling conclusion
Of The Obama Deception coverage
Ask the point where I have given up caring about this
Not a proud moment for me to have put on
Semitic Idol really
Give a s*** about Alex's even saying anymore
I will see how it plays out for the conclusion
Thank you so much for joining us on this adventure I know it's a lot
It's a lot
But I figured why do people out there probably have travel over the holidays
Love you got long drives and hopefully been able
To enjoy this over that
Would you like to show we have a website its knowledge fight.com some stuff over there
In the very near future.
Stuff in the works
I can also find us at knowledge underscore fight on Twitter we are there Laura Loomer is not
Find Target worlds on Facebook
You can check us out over there with a group called tell your mother
You like to join that to send to request will let you in the other
Secret
Close Group whatever
Subscribe scribing is a gray tank
To do us both
Describe
Android
Anyway guys
You trying to think about more ways that I can leave wrestling interviews of these outros here I was just interrupted by a very rude
Rude cat
That jumped on my my back here
She doesn't want to say hi but she's annoying the hell out of me
I love my cat very much saline is it is great cat appreciate the most about her
Is that she has never killed anybody
The cat is murder free
But one person who can't say it
Technically probably gildedguy
Is Alex Jones
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color