Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Play everybody look
Sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones
To the end of this adventure
The thrilling conclusion if you will of our coverage
The Obama Deception
It has been real
Real Whirlwind guys something
Seen a lot of the hot b******* Alex making up quote
Store people he has on the documentary Making up quotes
We've seen Ron Paul's brother say incredibly ludicrous thing
Seemed every single actor in this documentary
Be unable to grasp what the actual nature of the Federal Reserve
It's just been atrocious as an outing on Alex's parts
It's good that we can finally put this in the ground as it were an end
What's today's episode
But before we get to that I'd like to take a little moment
Very excited too
First of all I'd like to say thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Paul you are now a policy wonk
Thank you so much for supporting the show if you're listening out there and you thinking hey it's Black Friday
What do I go
As soon as I came out of my mouth
Ugly
Disgusting.
Take that out of there
Strike it from the record
If you will go to our website
It says support the show
Appreciate it
Now a conclusion
Of The Obama Deception
4r
Podcast
To get sloppy
Kind of
Not
Attract
Maybe I'm not sure if you're waiting for the boy will resort to lose it
I think you'll find it in this episode this is kind of
Blue contacts that believe
This was recorded this is all over me and Jordan sitting around and talking about this
Documentary
In one in one sitting so of course we were sort of losing our minds and
I think Jordan
Kind of checks out
Pretty hard
I'm not sitting here
It's a real Dynamic of Jordan having checked out addition to being kind of angry at Alex
Me realizing we just got to get through this and tried to make it to the finish line
We left off
Alex
Just made up another quote we were discussing
Entirely flat
So let's get back into it so much for listening
I will see you next week after this for
Regular
Regularly-scheduled podcast alright
We have all been held Within
The
Jail cell
That ponytail for
That jail
Now that the bankers were holding World hostage
Issued their ultimatum
The only solution to restart the global economy would be to set up a planetary government
Buy a new Bank of the world
Hundreds of prominent Publications announced the soldiers but he's shown to
Salvation
You don't say
You saying what they say
These are opinion
We're individuals have
Explorer
The new banking
These people as in the case right
Conceived by line Justin Fox there
He wrote for Time Magazine
English writing
Suggestions
Does ideas
Also fun fact in May 2009 Johnson
Fox wrote an article published
By time
About how everyone should listen to Peter Schiff
Alex's favorite Austrian School of economics
That's not just my interpretation
The Articles literally
Entitled quote
Why we should listen to Peter Schiff bad news
Dojo
What's on Fox this guy who wrote this article
To complain about
He's working for the globalist new world
Consistent
This fairly obscure Economist who want to destroy the things that
Used to make all their money
Yeah that makes sense
Multitude
Dad
Is saying it is
They're talking about
Creating a new World Bank
Bank of existence
Before you don't have to create a new World Bank
Is there
What is it called is it called some sort of international monetary fund
Connected
Who's going to make
Time Magazine an article titled the new world orders of adjustments control the world's currencies
Knock the heads
The bad countries
Like the United States
So we are my posit here so you can see a little bit of attacks but also like
The courthouse is referring to from this article doesn't pay that the bank
I should knock you as his head
It says
In the view of many outside the US and within
The only limit such a is through bigger more powerful is a bigger more powerful
They can act as the central banks
To the world and knock heads when needed
Importantly the prior paragraph provide
Provides
Text about what this mean
Discusses how
In the 1980s China and India learns at their best
Toward US dollars
Protecting their currency
Which it turns out isn't a good system
Either
Justin Fox
Isn't saying there should be a new bigger IMS
He's just expressing that some people feel that there should be
And in his article explains
Why that's all that's going on
Well no I mean the continuing question
From what I can read
Should Capital flows be
Should there be limits on trade.
Surpluses
Should the IMF be able to order round
Even the unit
Us
If the answer to any of these questions is yes
Global capitalism
Will have entered a new and dramatically less
Freewheeling error
If this happened
It doesn't seem like that
The positive reaction
Going off of like I Googled it now.
If
If any of this situation is so terrible that
We have to then
Give so much power to the IMF
Then that is Dramatical a bigger IMS
The power irrevocably
Forever
That's a big part of what he saying
Which he's not he's not implying is a good
Advocating for it
No
Know how to read
At a meeting of Central Bank heads and finance ministers dub
Bretton Woods to the plan
The world government was unveiled by the very bankers
That engineered the collapse
Formerly Sovereign countries
Would now pay their taxes directly to the banking cartel
Hundreds of new carbon taxes controlling every facet of human activity would only
We be the beginning
So God we're getting into
Bretton Woods 2
Do you know about brentwood's agreement that was made
It was about the world's economy becoming more interconnected
The 1940
And the international realization that they needed
To make sure there was more mechanisms in place
So is it country is could cooperate
Currencies could be traded with simplicity
So they created an exchange
They created a way that they
Trade currency
Easily cry cuz that is very important
International trade
Was the first participating countries agreed
Debase the currency of their value is
But the US insisted that the dollar should also
Reserved
Not too surprising
Play seeing as the US was
The biggest tower in the world
Or one of the only countries not comply
Be devastated
Economically by World War
We got our way
When Nixon.
Us off the gold standard night
The default
Reserved
Based on the Bretton Woods system
Now we no longer
Part of
By the way
Bretton Woods to was a meeting of international economies Express
Concerned about the world
Michael system
Particularly that little thing
Where anytime the US has economic
Trouble the trouble ripples through every country's economy
Because the world reserved
Along with ours
And that's a good thing
Brightburn your country isn't that what the
These countries were looking to start up a new world
Themselves from us
Particularly after our guy would you want to protect yourself we're doing good
Democracy
I mean after all our shoddy record
Like what we did to the world
I mean it wasn't
We played a big role
You are a team effort
Billionaires
Sure but
There was a lot of things
Spin it
Like that's what Bretton Woods to was
Mostly about
News about the idea that people wanted to disc
Connect from our economy
Not that they wanted
There's one argument Alex could conceivably used
Make his globulus Target
That is that
Other than the dollar
Probably the only
Realistic
Do they could use was
Gyro
You could say that they were
Shift to the euro
There's a place in Sgt it's dog
But it's mostly of how getting away from us
Yeah so I don't know I mean
Is there is there is one good thing
To be sad about Trump being press
Which is that finally the rest
Save the world
Has taken the advice that I gave them 10 years
Witches
Do not trust America
At all ever
If you go into any negotiations with America
Belie
No matter what and now everybody knows we
Are it's nice
Exactly
It might happen to you good luck
Record World I'll be in France
It's like any history book where you read the the Fraser and then the white man came
And you're like
Who is like the beginning of a horror movie
Like now we we have Trump in office everybody knows on the global scale
The white man is it
Avoid
I want to go to France
Anyway it's not going to help but
What do in France
Macarons pretty bad too
Macron
Want to go print
Easter Island
Nah
Now all the elite had to do was to sell the public on accepting the Final Phase of their teiko
And it's Obama's job to succor the pub
In the standing down
So the bankers agenda can move forward unhindered
Before 11, right there the media gotten behind a present
Like they are behind Obama
The Press has pulled out all the stops
Give me some credit he was f****** great man
Great
I know this is also a post factual's after when he made the documentary
You could make that same
Man about Trump
Like a lot of the media was
Presumably negative
Yes but they gave him as his eyes much
Attention and has no play on how much free advertisement
Billions of dollars
Just be a thing where Alex is
Recognizing a trend
Started with Obama
Like in terms of
The media oversaturating
Like God might be thing where he's like
He's accurately pointing
Medias do too much here
Right not recognizing that it's not
Because it's Obama it right back
Now what they do with politics
In this shot right here
Way too on the nose
It's the Seal of the president of the United States
Fresco of him with Jesus's Halo like
Look
Louisville
I would not have liked I wiggle
Too on the nose
The cameraman or knock that field
Throwing a crown of infallibility upon Obama as the savior of the people
The elite are betting everything they've got
Obama's charisma
And hoping that he can sell the world
Summer program
Between
America
Whataburger
A change of leadership
Will not let this go
European
It is the only one
What the f*** is he playing that making you evil
I don't play that
Isn't it scary
Not least of which not least of which that all of those all those features are even more specifically like
If you go back and read those are more rebuke to us
The people who voted for Obama than anybody else
Words like all of his speeches are
We need to come together
We need to do this together
All of you need to participate
Every one of you needs to be a part of this
Please don't just expect me to do this
And we were all like
Researched his own
Failure it is certain except again like this is another example of like
Alex is playing these
Heine clips of Obama speeches
Veteran ice I noticed it where we were both silently watching
Great like if you watch the entire speech
Also f****** great throughout like eight pieces
It's not
Some sort at 90 hit Alcazar
No problem
He has if not at powers and you guys are just falling for it. That
Great orator
Make
I want
And
That are uplifting
Right
Now weather weather
Involved in government he's able to
Anything away from the speeches
Anything away from what you
You feel when you
Hear it I wish I had
Elizabeth Warren in
That's why the first two years of Obama's presidency
That's what we're going to see over and over and over again prediction
5 coins
Gerald
No does the one
The one stretch of time
Where
Babe
A truly Progressive agenda could have been
Run roughshod
Over the s*** of America
Destroyed
And ultimately
By losing those first two years we lost every
At the time it seemed like the right thing to do and in hindsight probably wasn't
To do because
We thought we were ready for a black president
Thought we were dealing with rational people
Rational
We've got to give them a stake in creating the kind of world order that I think all of us would like to see
That's a llama is not simply continuing
George W bush
Two policies
He is radically expanding
Okay thanks
Proservice tornado
That was just in my list
The classy move
You know bush like Obama will be
The kind of petty person to
Complain about the burdens of office
Obama when he's being
Handed the presidency
Thanking bush
Forget service.
Me and that he endorses Bush's policies
It just me like what do you want to do pull out like a dick and piss on him
Like what would be appropriate
Like him
Karmic
Global pulling out of sick actually would be
Can you imagine what the blogs would do if
The first black presidential candidate
Virginia imagine the Scandal that would come from
The first black president of all time
And United States
Is rude
To his predecessor every other president was very nice to all the others
Yeah.
This film is documented the painful.
Of what he has claimed it to be
Also by the way this documentary has demonstrated
No
Barack Obama
And his controller
Screw agenda
Holy s*** we're an hour and
45 minutes to reveal what the
F*** the point is is the end of this documentary coming into the home stretch
Yeah it's a little bit
Now we come to Alex trying to make
His like
It's
Hughes
F******
Like
Thesis
Yeah it's a 10-part fuses
Europe Europe
We well you
It's a 10 party funeral mission
And then you submit your stasis
Nevermind he didn't go to college
Stop
Was never called upon to committing probably Terrain
Any papers yet
But like he
He's going to try and make
Eastpointe
These are
S***
I'll say this
Yeah
Alex
Number one
Bring the United States
All of the complete regulatory control
Of a private offshore super Bank
Known as the bank of the world
More than 100 new tax
Are now being developed
Under the umbrella
Of curbing greenhouse-gas
The new taxes we pay directly to the private bank and source
At the producer level
Taxes will be paid on farm animals
On all forms of me
Beef
Poultry
Pork and fish
It's important to note that within that b-roll right there was a stretch where he was zeroing in on certain
Certain parts of article
Break
But then for no reason
He just zeroed in on a
Cow's udder
Bright like if they were there was just like beer all of a cow and then all the sudden for no reason is just like
What
A couple times you pointed out this is a poorly edited
Poorly edited
So is first piece of the big plans globalist have for Obama
Yeah is to bring the u.s. into a new super World Bank
That's the underlying
Grandma's best before the whole time
I will say that I will judge this
Nor did they ever really try to make it happen
Making this up by misreading that Newsweek article that he flashed up on screen
Mission number one
No right make this happen
So we're we're over one on
Put an accident
Put a checkmark when the global is 60
And also all these articles keeps posting
Put it up on screen hear about these taxes
FaceTime suggestions people
Not really on anything that's ever gone
Through
Like none of these are real taxes but Alex is acting like is already a plan to put in place a laundry
In America are like
Indian journalists
Call Missy
But I mean not even like
Somebody who works for the administration
Or a press release of
Announces laundry Tech
That's a source I would take
Not real buddy saying
Hey laundry is hurting the environment not I got nothing
On that I got nothing on that
Decided to say something
Can do can go
Someone wants to write that someone wants to print it that's all it takes
It doesn't mean that its government
Anyone's taking it seriously
Like it is
He acts like all these suggestions
Somehow or miraculously going to be
Your new oppression
It's just nonsense
Old cars
Will be fitted with satellite tracking boxes
Applejack's driving by the miles
Encoding motor oil and natural gas
Old plastic
Products will have a carpenter
Not if I'm going to count that one for Chicago baby ate that
Not a federal tax
Cuz that's available tax
7/10 everybody Pace attack
Bethel local tax
No it's not
He only cares about federal tax alright well then
They're in the same weight part of number one
You still part of metal part of the global superpower
But like
Taxes in Suffolk
Like that
That doesn't exist on a federal level but it does exist in like California
That is their right to
To do that that's a state
States are not allowed to have
They are allowed to
Continue to have
That's the only thing I know
No gays
No taxes
If you have texts make a cool cuz that is not at all federal taxes
But there are examples of them on state or local levels
She shouldn't complain about
Exactly
Until then
Until it's not what I agree with
If you
Don't
Federal government
The European Parliament
So in the in the UK
Are the beaches
All electricity produced by coal power plants
Will be tagged
Got to bring me a cold
Citizens will be forced to pay tax
Another wild thousands of products
A private cap-and-trade Services No Pain by Al Gore no other release
There will be taxes on light bulbs
Water
Trash pickup
Paisano's
Before we go
All of these examples
Right
Right light bulb
Trash pickup
Cuz my lights were out
Little more than that after it when I paid for it so I can
The movie Walgreens with a central bank Walgreens scam
Now here's
Here's my big
Alright
Broly
And these are played out
The globe
Is there an exclamation
Play text
Call Bates electric Tech
Sure
The Earth is an apple
Trash pickup
If it's a private service that does it
Who's going to be at Exxon
Like it because it's if it's a public service
Most of the time
Your landlord will take care of it I mean where rent
Some stuff like
Most people are renters in there in Chicago that I know and your building generally takes care of it
But your landlord is tax
There's services
Since none of this is really
They don't know
I get it
30 bucks to get your trash picked up
So everybody pays a little bit of other things that already
So Furious
Steel production
Mining
Clothing
Laundry
Asphalt
Are just a few of the new tax
Is the Beloved
Those are all all depends on what you're doing with
But if you're buying clothes
If you're producing clothes
There's some sort of tax return
Lord I don't know I'm not sure what he's mad about but if it's that then
I still don't care to build that f****** roadman
That goddamn Road
From the ravages of climate change
We need
Ultimately make
Clean renewable energy
The profitable
Kind of
So I asked
This congressman
Find me legislation
The place is a market-based cap
On carbon pollution
And drives
Production of more renewable energy in
In America
I'm not
Anybody
The other time
Do something
But Obama is talking about
50%
Of America agree
That you should do so
56% says it's the wrong idea
Obama right there isn't talking about carbon taxes which is what Alex was
Before they do talk about camping
Trade which isn't it
Attack
It's a system where carbon emission
Center cap at certain level
And if a business wants to admit more than their logic
No
They're not taxed
Taxation by those admissions Unit A, another company that does
It's not a perfect system
F***** with ax
Get hurt climate progress all that stuff but texting me with your words
It's not attack
Extensive it could be
Cap and trade
Doesn't affect
Non-kin
Consumers don't get affected by that all it only involves people who run these businesses
That pollute
If there is
Carbon emission
There's another
No I know I understand that
That everyone know everywhere
Portrayed
Contacts can be used
Possibly
Cap-and-trade could be a good way to.
Yeah in Subway's
Feel like
Friday
It's too late
So let's not worry
Just because anything
Feels like it's too late doesn't mean
Do something
I know I'm not saying or not but
You during the war for water
Running the other
F****** way
Who run the other way with
Coming was never had a war for water so
Here for you every 10 of them
Absolutely
I'm not saying
I'm not going to donate to the show
Obviously
Play Garba Jackson
Affect
Just wait we have the pantheon of certain normal suggest
Also, Traders are really
Reasonable Middle Ground
Help
Will might be more able to
Accept it
I'm not going to get the best way to go nothing is perfect and it also creates commodity out of the the carbon
Nobody is buying my plan to recreate Avalanche
With Barrett and cloud and yuffie
And take down
The Shinra Corporation
Everybody here
Always listening
Everyone here
Everyone everybody here
Great a Final Fantasy 7 references
The notion of
Anthropogenic global warming
Is a fraud the idea that the planet is getting warmer
And the human activity
Is a pseudo-scientific
Fraud Wilford Brimley
I think I'm fascinated by him because of
How unable I am to pinpoint exactly the weird world
I know which is weird
It's not weird it falls in line with a lot of
The other
Crustaceans that I have
But his his
Trump
Display
And he's still being on Genesis Communications Network
Is to exert too much for me to understand
Have like like a certain amount of
I'm a Breaking Point
Like whiskey
Webster no
The in
2016 early
16 using trumps the fashion
Just go f*** this guy
Libertarianism
The fraud
Hey Ron Paul is a f****** a******
Words that I would see him and talk about like mischaracterization
Carol Quickly's
Books like I know what you're up to. Haven't begged
Then
Bring that anyway
I don't know what
You are now a rogue variable
Spell for sure still alive
Denial stuff go straight along with
The libertarian
It is very easy to
Compartmentalize that into
That world
Very heavily funded by Coca
Pinterest
Big tobacco that's hurt
Like that
If Alex is someone in Alex Jones
This world is a climate
All right right
Yeah that's
Yeah
Just an anomaly
That Siri
Perhaps no
Pitch
Where is he
Right now
Actually
Find an old phone
But I don't think so
Japan
Waiting at bleeding
No
So we we knock a little hole in the sky
And you and I
Some straws in there and we drink his brain and we gain his power
What do you think
Agree to that
What is what is left for him
Something greater
We have an idea we have an idea
I know that we just said we're going to eat brains don't listen to that. Don't worry about it
Avid turn around
Where does where does
Justin
If you're Elizabeth
None of this stuff is going to happen
That guy make a bandana on you and eat your brains about you
Balaclava are there that covers your head
There's no way we can put a straw through there
Erase science
Grace Hightower
They said Aryan
This is where we went
Search Holocaust
Global warming
Caused by human activity
And the answer to that is
Carbon tax
Plus
Cap-and-trade
According to the wishes of algor Prince Charles
And basically the entire
At world
Banking Community the world
Bigly
In the world of Nazi leaps that
Impressive
Videos
The Nazis had raced eugenics
Climate change
What
Before we go any further
The article up
Right now
Is from
Good girl
Clearly
A year-and-a-half old by the time of this documentary
What they're trying to do with that
Is to perpetuate
The current system where Bankers rule the world financiers rule the world
Festivus
If you try to put on tattoos that we all wanted waterwoman later on in life
Guess we were wrong.
I did it you're going to save the polar bears
Telegraph
The deaths will be measured in the hundreds of Millions
And indeed Independence
Just the idea of global warming means
Southeast refrigerators
Any car ever
Jack off motion
Inspiring
How much he cares about
Africa right now
He cares
Like specifically now
It's amazing
Kings nuts
It's important to expose and fight
The pseudo-scientific fraud of global warming
One more point
Climatologist
YouTube I really wish I did
Historian
I can tell you okay give me a
We had a period of
Temperatures
Called the medieval warm.
Growing very far
F****** charts charts
Pause this dumb f****** shirt
What's the minimum in there
Later xyx
Alright
What does that mean
Carbon-14
The molecules I assume they're on the other side
So what is the weather that mean
Calendar years
Before
Prometheus
Now if we're going to go by his b*******
We have between 709
Describing as historic medieval history
Correctly
What he is saying is that
The climate exist
From
1188 does seem like that is the what the graph is
Because I mean
It's not specified any better than that
I think that's a limited stamp
Apple size
Does he know dinosaurs were real
I really need that question answered right now
Before we go any further does he know dinosaurs are real or not like a
That God gave us
It's not something that came up in this documentary
I can't favors it looks like
All time
Maximum
Sunspots
Right now
We can save it for the historian
The limit
The medieval warm.
There was
Ice Age in
Northern Europe
Call Samantha Foster covid-19 response to an all-time minimum
Sunspot activity minimum
What to do with solar activity
We can pass
As a result of increased solar activity
But we're well within the minimum
With the oligarchs
Claimed to be an open-and-shut
Scientific case
Is a piece
Pseudo-scientific nonsense
And it should be
Rejected
No that's not true at all
It is the one
Who
Someone who is special interest group would probably say
Damn it's not you have me
It had me you.
About a Boy
It was such a long time
But that stretch
It that stretch has definitively proven to me
Webster Tarpley
Can take his head
Twisted around
Stick it up his own ass
And then have it thrown into the f****** son
Like he's he's advocating something that is
What a moron
F****** moron they don't fly matologist to tell you this stuff cuz I was Dory
Recalibrate it so like retroactive
His money is taken away
Probably
I think that over the course of this podcast
A lot of the stuff we talked about
Has shown that he's not a great historian
He probably hasn't misplaced ideas about history
So like when he's like you don't need some ideas
A very nice way of putting
I went but I want to know those
Irritated climatologist I'm a historian I know these
I have problems
Who's your credit is a historian till I also don't take
That is very seriously
I bet even beyond that I reject the premise
You do need a climatologist
You do need it cuz it's very it's very subtle a lot of
That that the Stuffies
Is f****** b*******
It's nonsense
And I will move on
You don't need a climatology
The social engineer
Fully aware
The Obama craze will wear off quickly
So they are racing to put in place
The most impressively state-controlled
Number to get on your horse but you're keeping track of the tenants of
What Obama supposed to do
I'm just hitting myself in the face with the microphone
Hitting my face
No it doesn't keep track of
Right now I CX
I see three x's and I understand
Vin Diesel is my God because we don't live in a police state now so
Mission failed the globalist
So
15 point
But Alex doesn't mention that it dropped 15 points and ended up at 6
Sixty-eight percent as an approval rating
That's not an indication that Obama is first week in August
Well we don't want to say it
You bet we're all really excited
Navigation to 15% of the people in the last poll were f****** lying when they said they
3% approval rating is unsustainable
Or an indication that the last bowl wasn't well done something like that
For context Trump in his entire presidency
And that was stick stays into him being an office which is
I'm saying that it was ever that he spent most of his time in the low forties high 30
Which is insane
America's Army troops
Are now being deployed
Patrol the streets of the United States
Not exactly
FEMA
Is now building Giant
Every region of the Chester prison like the National Emergency Center
HR 645
Which merges local
Send the police
Under Federal control
HR 645
Some podcast
Meridian wasn't
Local government
And as we will know
They're ready
For the riots
What day is the 10th
Can centers that are being open up around the country
Which state is so bad right now
And food riots
They know what's going on
And they're prepared for
Pause this right now
If you are
Watching with us
It is 1 hour 29
Hanson 34 seconds into this.
Documentaries
Gerald Celente
Look so much
Like a ballet instructor out of time
They're going to be honestly also looks more tired
Yeah
We are right now
Can you do it he is out
Point insane
Could not be happier with
Art and Tails over his ears like he's balding on top
You've got the scope
Yeah
This man this man has put on the greatest
That New York City has ever seen
Off Broadway
In Brooklyn 3 years running has make like a comedy references
Stuff like this
I think he's aged out of the Roll by this point but right there
He could play Tanta mellow theatrical.
If I can't be with the coaches
It's all there
We're going to have something
The daddy says
Prepare for it themselves
Anyone that's not
Prepared for what's going to happen
They deserve what they get
Because that's not nice
No also I want
I don't have a clip of it but it keeps happen
2009 episode
Any of this food
Efoodsdirect is a sponsor one of their commercials they keep playing it just
F****** freaks me out every time I hear it
Is like
Hey
If you believe that there should be
Gun control
We don't want you to buy us
President emergency
We want everyone to be able to prepare but if you're into liberal politics
Don't buy our food
F****** die
Thesaurus
Hey I mean I get it
Staked out a claim
Economics
I get it but
Why you putting that out in the world that's
Meaning for
Go fuc yourself
The world gold
And probably gun Obama ordered the defense department to issue.
Fortino 4.10
Establishing a 1 million person civilian Army
It didn't do that much control
It didn't do that I'm moulting asleep Obama want
That wasn't part of it that's not part of the temp
Silgan put a next time to make sure those two other exes are many actors three accidents so far
Notice for
Right was it three were before it no no no this is still Point number two
This is
McDonald's website
Is a recruiting tool
Building a separate
Completely private Army
Outside of government Obama Barack Obama has
Presidential decision directive 51
Shine by George W bush
Obama has refused to get rid of
Presidential decision directive 81
He's about to save it it makes
The president of dictator.
Respond in the event
Did a catastrophic disaster
Right I'm really if you want to look at it
It hasn't really been enacted at all
Since that it was an accident
Like it has been put into place
Was the original Act was which
Is presidential
Which Clinton enacted in 1998
It only was ever enacted l911
Because that was a catastrophic disaster
A bit of an outlier but we have a history since 1998 of Presidential Directive
And PD d51 after
After that
It's a whole history since 1990
It's been an accident wants no one's ever abused it
I don't know I don't care
I don't got no give a f***
Before we go
I don't know if anybody remember
Because I haven't seen
But your dick over there
This is V
Most
Evil collection of human beings
In one room
Rubbish
You're running
Rumsfeld
Is
Rumsfeld is like the Avatar of
Murder
Is a murder Bender
He just like is almost like he has no feelings like
He doesn't even take pleasure in the destruction that he
Come inside while he's being evil
Empty on the inside like this is the most evil
Collection of people
And then George W
Dumb bastard
Tough memories
There are 0 people in this picture
Deserve the death
They should all go to the
They should also
President is a dick
Congress
Ceremony
Don't say that
Security objectives
Alex playlist
That is just about the
Discord.com
Strong Justice well-funded
They love it
President Obama and his chief of staff Rahm Emanuel
Repeatedly stated on the rec
All Americans below the age of 64
Will be forcibly
That's crazy
Citizenship is
It's not an entitled
It comes with
Responsibility
Everybody somewhere between the ages 18-25 will serve three months of faith
Training and understanding
Any kind of civil
So it doesn't always have to be
Service in uniform one of the things that if you talk to our general
They are desperate for
Is a civilian
Counterpart
To our military forces
Alex
Is what he's doing is he's cutting between interviews where people are talking about different things
Is doing this interview about his book on C-Span
About this idea that he has about like
Creating
Got civilian
Not armies but
People who are able to
Responded moment's notice
That sort of idea
Which never got anywhere
And then Obama talking about the Peace Corps
He's cutting in between those two things as if they're the same
Same thing
Not
This compulsory then
Goodwill
You have to innocence
A required of them
25 Tremont
And it's some point of that
Point YouTube
Also Alex said 18 to 64 I don't know where you got that
Is the only person is giving age numbers
Using 18 to 25
So I don't know where 60
Before is coming
And also
Is like like when you
You turn 64 or when you
I think if you're 6
Before 3
60 days
You're in baby don't think that's fair
Before we three weeks who gives a s***
Ultrasound
The Personnel my God no
Is imposing the building accurate now
And finance
Change.gov
Proclaim
The Middle School in High
School students will be forced
To serve the Federal
So here I actually think that this is the best
Evidence
B Alex Jones
Is a complete
F******
Liar
Because I passed this year on screen
And what it says America serve
Here right America serve
And what this sentence says
Is Obama call on citizens of all ages to serve America by developer
A plan to require 50 hours of
Community service
In middle school and high school in 100 hours of community service at
The college ever
Now I went back to the way back
Is that website actually said
Know when Alex
Can't say with certainty who did it
Put someone.
This is photo
No s*** hundred percent no s***
Through the entire. When
Obama was running
When Alex could have been making this documentary
Up to the date of the documentary came out
And it didn't say that on the website
I'll read you the quote that it does say on the website call on citizens of all
Disturb
Don't set a goal that all middle-aged middle school and high school students engaged
Health Plan
For all high school students who engage in 100 hours of
Community service
To receive a fully refundable tax credit of $4,000 for their education
So the idea of that
Removed all of the
Holyshit this is entirely doctor
No not now whether Alex took it from and disreputable source and thought it was
Right or something like that
There is literally no way that this page
Existed on Obama's website
During the time when Alex
Cool as f***
Nicely done
It's so weird it's so weird to go to bed
The only the only
Only thing that's really something
Individual change
Is
I mean some of the language
But
Choir choir
The require part and once and there's no part of $4,000
Yes they did
Play in the whole thrust of it is that Obama and Biden
Yeah it's
We would like you to do this
Tonight we're going to tell you
Do it but also if you look here
Like Obama will call you use the same language
Yeah you saying call on you to do it but it still says require
That's worth
That is absolutely
Fraud no matter what
Yep that's not real
Alright anyway
Forgot
Because you can say this and bab like I just got that screenshot projector sobik
Whoever
The case is closed
Instant like yes
Is fraud
Someone
Doctor this
Wasn't Obama's website
At all
Holyshit
Fascism
Gutter up
It's up
Hooligan
Starbucks
Fervently idealist
Around Obama
Where you get a puppy
Call man
To do that so I think that's
That's
If you were left
Liberal
To that
Into a paramilitary domestic
Did security
Why do you say 18
24 this time that doesn't even match with Ron's 1825 and Alex's 5:42
Before from earlier
Is AJ's make no sense
Give Obama has his way
Adult and Senior
Will also be fixed other forms of survey
What are they busy
Number three
Text
That was in the second
As We Know
There we go
Build
Holy
The first time
The Obamas going to take
I guess most important thing of the past eight years of Obama's presidency
Eliza
Yeah part of the gun thing and now save Mission failed
Robespierre
All 5
The most deadly mass shootings have happened since this documentary was made
Has happened
Has been done to curb the excesses
In 2018 alone there been over 300 mass shootings and no one gives us s***
What is a
No one
Really seems to
There's nothing happening
All the pretty it's more like
Ground into a
Human beings
Empathy
Will you still live
We've been ground into a paste
By the NRA
Trumpet
Cinepolis Vista
And Alex doing everything possible to
Brabus of Hope
Or ability
Guidance
HR 1022 would allow the new Attorney General Eric Holder
The dictatorial power
Any gun he wish
At will
No it wouldn't
HR
10/22 did nothing except reinstate the assault weapons ban
I'm passing 1994
It didn't pass
In 2008
Before The Supreme Court
In the DC gun ban case
District of Columbia versus Heller
Boulder argued for the complete disarmament of the American people
No he didn't
He had nothing to do with DC vs. Heller
She wasn't the Attorney General at the time
He wasn't involved in the case
K-Swiss sign Amicus brief
Which supported the idea that
The Second Amendment doesn't necessarily
Provides a right for all citizens to own whatever guns
Alex is f****** lying
Eric Holden argue before The Supreme Court
HR 257 would ban all youth shooting
Including YMCA and Youth Olympic Shooting
HR 257
Supportive schools having guns
From the restrictions on minors have begun
It would be very easy to see how well-run gun club like
This 4-H club it Alex
Program
This is all bulshit
Hr45 would force all gun owners
The undergo Federal psychological screen
Play
Hr40
But it was really actually more about the idea that you needed proper licenses to buy cont
Ironically though in his 2018 interview with Patrick bet-david that we went over when I was f****** drunk at that hotel
He doesn't want crazy
You haven't given up on that
I don't know
Is X4 that I think he's put Adeline under that extra something just because it's like
And there are seven
This isn't good
White house chief North
Any American on the fraudulent no-fly list
From owning any fire
If you are on the no-fly list
Because you are known
As maybe a possum
Paris
You cannot
Bye
A handgun
In America
Over 25,000 Americans are added each month
To the no-fly little higher than a million people
Charger convicted
Of any crime
I think that Alex's is a spare on this based on the time
He's making this
But everyone
Absurd
Is the no-fly list
Practical
Alex is exaggerating about it a little bit but I think spiritually is kind of right
I'll give the tip of a cat on that cap on
5 year old boy from Normandy Park
He had trouble boarding a plane because
Someone with the same name
Mimi
They love local news
I love local news so much story
Nothing so good I love local news
Nothing
It's so dumb
I want more people on the scene
Everywhere
I like the coat
That she's wearing
Local news
Have to play this news classifieds drive that
If you
Instead of having to edit
Applause before behind him we'd all be like
Baby baby we wouldn't be hyper
So many of them in prisons right now cuz my two-year-old go
Nevermind
Sweet Matthew was considered equivalent
The right to bear arms
No right for you
And even though this
Matthew Gardner was only in kindergarten
TSA worker still conducted a full-blown search
Like a government
Who was more than Antonio
Search memes make sure that
I had not obtained any materials from him
Massive restrictions on the
Preemptively rated XM
Congress and the FCC
Have announced plans
To not only curtail speech on Talk Radio in newspaper
But you also regulates
Speech on the internet
To the orwellian named fairness.
Oh man I've actually break down two x's on top of
Each other accident
The furnace Doctor Who
T49 related to political Tea
TV and radio
I need to provide balanced coverage equal time for different political ideology
Clear-eyed
Young hearted back then there's also abolished in 1987
Equal
Tunity for each
Beachside
Balance
Beautiful Sherwin-Williams
Sylvia what was abolished in 1987 has never been brought back nor will
Obama didn't bring it back not even
The slightest go watch
Any goddamn
Political show annual fee
Come on you remember how Fox News
Who is devoted to providing
Fair and balanced coverage
But yeah I know
The Obama machine is also pressuring Congress
The pastor Cody and hate speech laws
The first
Number 5
They plan to further federalized
Government
Can dictate what kind of care citizens receive
That's a good
So here's the fun
Is that
He is presenting that as like a negative thing
But actually
Yeah
The government
Should be able to do
Dictate that
As opposed to write
Who when they dictate that
Means they don't pay for any
We'll get back to number five in second I'm not done with number for Alex jumped really quickly
Are you there it's really just paranoia among people who just want to use a bunch of
They're worried about that their rights a offensive taken away
Never been an issue like it's not like
Free speech
You're certainly allowed
I mean the consequences of your actions will be brought upon you you know whatever that may be
MP3 or go for it
Other people
Edward anymore
Use people put also
Same rules apply is to the Madea situation if you're the only person there watching the ice dancer you probably
People performing probably too
Too busy performing
I don't know actually I've been ice dancers would probably
Stopped everything to be like
We're done
Look none of that stuff is ever really been the issue but what has is been expanding what care
Characteristics qualified
For consideration
Germany
Previously
To the time that we're talking to
About if you were to be
Beat up someone who is
Trans
Cuz they were trans
It wasn't hate
But with the expanded legal definitions for
It could
I hate crime
That's worth
You'd be totally free to stay
Whatever bulshit you want
You can say whatever you want
You could say that trans people aren't human
If you want for it
Free speech
Tell me whatever other people respond to that fit
The open
Respond
But like
That is what Alex is talking about what he's talking about Draconian hate speech
Laws that are going to eviscerate the First Amendment
If this thing started it like
Protected classes of people that weren't
13 1/2 million hours
Like you said I great
Now a huge concern about this paranoia about rationing Healthcare
And restricting
Procedures
That's why you
He's afraid about
This idea of federalized healthcare
But even if we imagine
This is just
I was just paranoid he's Express
The insurance industry previously did a whole hell
Restricting procedures Terry word Grace primary
So they couldn't
Trey really restrict access to healthcare based on pre-existing
Condition which was something that made
Millions of Americans unable to access for Apria Healthcare
Without going absolutely can't remember a time whenever
Companies
Don't you think
Is operating
Replaces not really
Giving a f*** about people
But in terms of this
So the first four I would say Mission not accomplished
This one mission
But I guess
I guess
Medium
Looks good for a bit and then no
Modeled after the British
System
This includes a rationing care
And restricting what procedure
Handicap
Elderly
Eligible
Number 6 Obama is already pushing
To expand the Department of Defense budget
And the station more US troops overseas
Doing Circle Russia
China
Iran
And alphabetically
Ireland would be no
Ireland
Northern Ireland who has a lot of fat on this program
Certain
Obama didn't do any of these
It's certainly not at
The time
This documentary
Was mad
So
I would say this is also
Mission failed globalist
Port Bass
When will you ever catch a break
Under the pretext of humanitarian Aid
And dominate an occupy Africa
Peru Africa
You have
Bob Chapman on
Your show all the f******
Anytime
Who was a profiteer from apartheid South Africa
Modern world Africa you have no right to make any
Take Africa down what an a******
Your phone calls
Barack H Obama
Frontman
Let's go to Anthony in Georgia
Anthony what's your take on Barack Obama
Does this seem like a setup to you cuz it is a herd
When we were going over 2000
The first time Anthony called in
It was right at the end of an episode about to go
And this guy called in and Alex is like
Oh my God
You're a guy who's really against Obama call in tomorrow
I need to record you for the Obama Deception
This
Is the end result of that
They put the
The faith of Barack Obama
As part of
There their public relations
Because it's like the old folktales about vampires
Vampire
His way into somebody
So the vampire hats called
Does this guy literally believe in vampires
Vampires are real
But the rules rescue
The household
Open the door in
Invite him in
The people at Barack Obama
Looks like then
And appears to be
Be on their side
Wednesday okay here's my Ally
Earlier
And then Barack Obama
The frontman for
The American Inn
Empire where he's going to have
The entire US Navy
The entire US Army and entire us
Marine
Under African command
And of course
You going to turn it into a new Iraq and it
And everything else
Is going
Propagate
Poor countries of Africa
Sure I agree with you
Handsome smiling African face
Boy
Shout out
American cheese
To Shell out there people
Trick in the book
Isn't that good we can also pacify the most downtrodden minority groups in the United States
Sacrifice
Alex
How about you go f*** yourself when you're talking about style out Native American Chief well in this same
Andrew Jackson
You mother f*****
How dare you have those two ideas at the same time
Kind of
Jordan
I would say
It literally
That just
2 position
Native American Chiefs
And I love Andrew Jackson
Is all you need to know about an Alex Jones
That dichotomy is
That sums him up perfectly you know it's like
You're so unfair
It's like
Finishing a different
See you then
Starting one
Oh wait
No Andrew Jackson was a f***
I forgot about a getaway 2
Kick them out of Zimbabwe with a get-well materials
Start a Civil War in Congo
Another big source of raw materials
An arm of the DSW
Why not
I don't understand what this a documentary steals about China
It's very confusing to me
Like what exactly
Earlier
Together in this new world order
I don't fucken
I can't make heads or tails of the geopolitical
Webster Police version of geopolitics
Is different than Alex's
Soap with the two of them
Existing at the same time in this documentary
It's f****** confusing
And they do know
To try and make the two work together
I think I've lost my
Yeah I know literally lost
You're more confident than me
Around odinga
That's Obama's cousin
It is not
Children
Oh my God
You don't know any
Odinga is not
Doesn't he said he was just trying to get him
More elevation in
He says his two kids he has
Obama
But if he were they wouldn't be his niece and nephew be second
Cousin
I don't
What
How any of these
People are allowed to
Continue talking
Yeah.
They should really stop
And political asset Hellyeah
South Africa
So this
Odinga
Destabilizing operation in Kenya
The crush the Christians in
You're not he's arguing that there's a
He's not he's not a Muslim
I know it doesn't matter put like
He's trying to paint him as if he is he's not
Salsarita's in one of the greatest stories of our time
In that beat
Is a battlefield in Flames between the US and the Chinese
As if it wasn't
Before
Over the last couple hundred years if it wasn't
Just a
Playground for colonialist interest
Scenario
They could begin I'm not sure there is
I don't know everything's on fire everything's on fire
Give everybody with
Eritrea
I guess but the idea of like
He's putting
Out here
Doesn't reflect reality
This is
This is one of these times
That like I looked into it
Kind understand it
But then I was also like
F*** off
I spent too much time
Like digging into the specifics
I don't care about your analysis Tarpley
This isn't
The Chinese out
For geopolitical
Number 7
Radically expand Federal control over family farms and ranches system
Odinga
Since near the world
Family Farm
Mission
Alright alright another
Holyshit we're already on the number eight so I got to talk about it.
Talk about the animal ID system
The end to things that the globalist
Going to put into place in order to make it so that Farms can't exist
Proposal
Voluntary system
Right
But it's actually even worse for Alex's argument
Then that according to the National agricultural Law Center
Well the nais program was voluntary
On the federal level
Some states portions of it on the state level
This was just a system
It was proposed in order
Track animals
So if there's an outbreak
Like mad cow it becomes easier to contain
On the federal level
Buttercup Estates
States rights
Decided to pass on the state level
No Alex shouldn't give a s*** about that
They chose to
Do that it's the states
F*** you Alex
Let's states with Catalan Mex
Brickell under the security and prosperity Park
DVD copy of The Obama Deception
U.s. Mexico
He is also a
A remaining Federal Authority
Tunnel
Quasi-governmental body
Nope
Number nine
Obama where are you
The president
Of the United States
Find Andy's coming
2 plan
Because in 48 years
Obama must take the blame
As bushed
For the New World Order
Agenda
At that point the illegal for the Newport
Ceremonial seat of power
Hahaha
Hilarious
That's so funny is reduction
Ain't here for eight years and now they're going to have
How to build up somebody else's a savior
Alex
You did
I want to live back in the past years from when this documentary came out
You built up a fall savior your dumbass hole
It also has failed on that one
I think forever
Yeah proper
Alex is such a dumb rube
I think I'm still exist
I'm not sure
Texasdirectauto
A f******
And much less on the end
Mirrors
My approach to this documentary
I'm sick of this I think he got through like three
America
Let's go
I like I like a round number let's get to 10
So the process is repeated
Over
Withdrawal
For their program to work
It is essential
Look up people not learn
The presidency is now nothing more than theater
Because if they did
People would stop looking at the pond
Or the queen
We can move better to see
Any of that
Who's the rug shop
Investigating the globalist
Bishop is Greenspan
Number 10
Job to sell the pub
Policies
The dark in the People's Best in
But the overlord
X
His most
I tried to figure out if
Describe all these points
Merge Canada us and Mexico
That's a good sensation
Number 10 I tried to figure out is a shout out to our friends over at Marty and Sarah love wrestling
Number 10 is protect
The business
I don't f****** know like
You don't hear what he says I think it's just like
Okay alright
Important function
To protect the criminal oligarch
Prosecution
Economy worldwide
Start new Wars
And engaging
Barack Obama's wife
Also in that role is to make sure that no one
Finds out
The Powerball
Behind the
The government is
Stuff like that
I have no idea what he's
F****** means by that cuz I
Who's Obama
Protecting is it David Rockefeller
Because people like weirdos isn't complaining about him for a lot longer than Obama's been around
Is it the CFR
Because conspiracies about them like Phyllis Schlafly his early work
I don't understand what secret Obama supposed to be protecting
Except
If the case is
It's a secret that Alex
Also hasn't review
And we don't know what that is
Which would imply that
Who is protect
That secret to reveal at
No no
Suggesting is number 10
His whole idea about Obama is supposed to make sure the
This people don't eat
Who is behind the throne
I know who Alex has said is a good names that he's thrown out there
And those are Revelations it's nothing new or anything like that
He's not telling us either
Alex is
And you
If Alex is right
Then Alex
He's come
By his own account
He is as guilty as all these people
I'll protect
Ironic
Choose one side or the other Alex you dumb dumb
Champagne Barack Obama use the internet like no other
Canada before
Eager energetic Army
Caleb
Barack Obama and his administration contact information for so many people so next time
He can contact all these people
Kennedy was selected
It was the scope of Obama's victory that was most impressed
I saw
Obama
Playing bass
I said you know what
And that's the world
I want a piece of History
Commemorating the day the world changed forever
Is confidence
BioLife
Are an inspiration to us all
On the idea commemorative plates here
Saint Idaho
Want to hear about the Donald Trump
Commemorative
I'll leave that part out
Barred owl
I've seen more than enough party cry
Donald Trump commemorative
Coin is
Gauche
To the point where you're like
There's no way that you could be a parody of yourself Beyond
The level that you already are I will look at it
Holyshit
You're an amalgam of all the cartoon evil there's ever been abroad
Fox the bad guy from Captain Planet
The part in my script or I talked about how he made a commemorative coin about him meeting with Kim Jeong Hoon
I'm going to kill you anyway before the summit workout
I don't mean to threaten violence
Recently
In 2011 the Atlantic did a deep dive into the world of Ron Paul memorabilia
Pretty wild stuff
Or
Referred you could treat yourself to a wooden
Plate with Ron
Commemorating his 2008 run for president for 60 bucks
They found copper coins with Ron Paul's face on it
Or talk with the iconic World words
Gold standard in leadership
On it which is ironic
I'm not sure for the hide
Okay
But so is a wooden plate
A bird
I saw it looks like something that you might do
Soldering iron
Interesting
Before this documentary came out yet
According to CBS News.
Federal agents raided the headquarters of a group that produces a legal truancy
Season gold silver into tons
Copper coins featuring Republican presidential candidate Ron Paul on it
What are the targets of the real guy named Bernard Vaughn
And that's not even a capital
Hausel even if that is your name
Bernard
Founder of the National Organization for the repeal of the Federal Reserve
He said quote I'm volunteering to meet with agents and get arrested so we can
Can thresh this afternoon
The
Quick to say I had nothing to do with that s***
Found out house was
Do 6 months
Dumb weirdo
Literals
He was sent to the Von nuthouse
Yes
Information
Las Palmas
Crazed Obama worship
Being pushed by the corporate media
Scientifically designed to capture the public
Internet air pressure Mass euphoria
New World Order
Can just distract the pub
For a few more years
None of this is real
A professor
Wheatfields
What do you call a
What's thing will you get
Black man
Everything's going to be alright
I think the Germans
What the Democratic Party
Has been
Isabel
It will be about Regatta
Barack Obama
The president
So I want to say one thing straight up
Alex keeps talking about how
Documentary
Attic party
And it's at the end of the documentary he says in summation and then immediately plays a clip of Professor
Griff's
It doesn't matter about Obama it's about what the Democratic
Party is doing
It seems like this is very partisan
Come on
ATMs
Deeply partisan with the veneer the misdirect of
I'm complaining about right
Sure
Anyway I'm going to watch a for like in game to start now again
Like I'm worried they're bad news we got 6 hours left another two hours long and it's just
Going to be endgame on top of
If that violin starts
Kill everyone
Barack Obama
Perfect Trojan Horse
Do people feel like they finally have a place at the table
They do
Real quick clip of the lady was like I can pay my mortgage
Yeah
If you go and find the
Beaufort like that
She saying is now that I don't feel as
Worried about the
The economy
So I can pay my bills
Pay her mortgage which is
I totally
To say something that it's not never seen that
Okay good day whatever house
Core supporters can't see what's right
Front of their face
Because they've already invested their very identity
In this artificially created
Cold movement
Oh hit lerab history
People turn their intellect
Oh 44 minutes
Put a visual dog
William William credit we've gone
Play happening to finally now get to Hitler
I tip my hat to him in terms of like yeah I think you thought they would be like a real
Kaboom
I'm stoked
Sure that we finally got our first Hitler
And everyone's first Hitler is Big Mama
Did he showed the restraint
An adult
Grown up
And it's happening again
The evidence presented in this film is documented facts
Payroll of us all
Frightening as the information in this film is
There are many things we can do just really don't know what the information is
First we expose The Cult of Obama for what it is
A sad hook
Okay
Next
Realize that we are all being propagandized
24/7
Okay
All information for yourself
I did the media
For this film
I did enjoy
Be aware of
You trying to pull out the big guns
Liberty
Is it International Wisconsin
Destroy the sovereignty of all 50
States
No he's just trying to say at the end of his like the ReDiscover the Constitution
Please be a sovereign
Please get to my weird Patriot ideologies
Zip code for it's not like it doesn't
Hey Constitution
They know
It is one of the biggest threats
Their domination
The federal government has been completely hijack
And more than 25 States
Have recognized this fact
And removing the block the New World Order
At the state level by declaring their 10th Amendment
This is what Alex has been
Emergency
Useless grandstanding by dumb
Schleicher
The same position
Nowhere
But most important of all
There is a huge Awakening taking place in the United States
And across the world
Against the globalist agenda
Free people everywhere
Are joining together
I'm saying no to corruption and tyranny
And no
The world
The Dismount of this is basically just going to be Alex trying to
Convince you
Unique Jordans
The peek-a-boo
Just trying
Convince people who are listening
Zearn
Neo in The Matrix space
And
Use clips
From pretty much all of the people
Thick we've heard
Yes
Download Kung-Fu into my brain in a very short.
You and I'm sorry about
This is everyone in this room
Play manipulative like
Could it be
You are
You import
Call Matt
So historically
Washington
What kind of ship General
You kind of s*** at the job right
You look great
6 ft at the time which means he was 10 ft taller than everyone else
He looks
Great idea
That you're Express
The best
Kill the guy
What's the most boring Legacy
George Washington
Except
And everyone of you watching
Every single one of
Justice
Important
Get a haircut
Who are our founding
Fathers
Important
Philosophize
About 3
About a week
Republic to fly
Suffice
About 8
Skooly
Free
More than that
Wanted to change it
Baby on fire
What are you the one
Nature has a way of
A bun
Looking for
What
Forthright
Respect
Chopper
Your part
I got bad news
Okay
Two bags one
Still
Still on that krs-1 tip
So far
He is not that anything's egregiously
He has not said anything that makes
Pinky's read Ender's Game
Nothing egregiously bad
Nothing makes sense
Read Ender's Game I think that if we were able to ever talk to him
Which I know that will never happen
I think if we did
I'm not the one
But it stopped
If we were
If we were able to talk to him I bet
He will probably be like
I shouldn't have
I disagree
Documentary
Like your taco is cold then you go to Yum brands which is all about
The Federal Reserve and you complain about parents
Owns the Federal Reserve
Evergreen
When it changed its name to VLC player
It is now running the game absolutely
Everyone knows that there's documentation goofy impression the record I got talking
I don't know I think
He would probably not be thrilled with all this
Especially the way the world is
Alex
Exceptional
Are people who no longer talk to Alex
That I can't have him on the show
You get some of this business cleared
Him in essays website
So I can hang with Alex anymore
I would bet money Victor
Jesse Ventura
Wouldn't show up on the show anymore
Willie Nelson was campaigning for Beto yeah Willie Nelson Willie Nelson
Back out maybe was naivete or something like that and they thought that wasn't the person that
Clearly what I
And they agreed to be a part of this but
Nope they just don't like most of the people most of these people that you do like
If you go do this thing you're like
Aware of it
Rob not like a follower
Opportunity for me
Know if I go if I go do a show it's not like I
Every week
And watch it and then I'm happy to do it like it's like
I go do it
You know any
These guys
Have the Gestalt
Of Alec
I agree that
He's probably very common but I disagree that that is
That simple way to operate
Great Lake
You know doing stand-up I wouldn't do
Do shows with
People who like
Thought were
Talkingshit heads
Good invite me to do a show
Do that that's
Miserly
Some have to do
But if someone like if I were krs-1
In 2009 he's been around
Boogie down Productions in like what
He's been around he knows he knows what
In terms of like
What am I going to put my name on
Right I would expect
Protect the brand a little bit better had to be like
Oh Alex seems cool
Fair
So when you're saying like he hasn't said anything awful I agree with you
Dislike
Somatic
It's just like
You
Your
That's not
Not believe this
I got you
But if you think more of yourself
Ben just peed in the excess
Are you everybody's not going to make it
Well we don't have to
To look back thousands of haircut
Persevered
See how Derek jumper
We can look back
Active this one's not even haircut looks
Talkin about the
People's Revel
Talking about the
The positive
And Lenin came
Stalin
Factor
Is that over
Million
Russian
Good Rush
People who are Christian
People who had
Who had their own business
People who are edgy
They were
Terminated
Because
They had their own
Because they were
They believed is that leave
God's law
Is there a war
You hold it back
Now
Are those the only reasons
I don't think so
I mean if you wanted it but that there were a lot of
Butt chugging
Weird killings on the USSR
That s*** was crazy
Specifically targeting Christians
They were anti-religion of all sorts
Like it wasn't
This is just
We choosing
This part of history of being like we were the victims of the night
It'll take ticket ticket number as well
Yeah
We can look over at Germany
Germany was in a
Very very
Terrible acne
Economic situation
Very charismatic leader call Jose all Hitler
Katie
Makes the roads
Promises of better life
Dictatorial
Then we can go to
Tomorrow with you
Borax analogy that is making the most flimsy thing ever it's
Here is
Hitler
Whether or not you made roads great
I'm going to promise you all of these things and then actual real
F****** genocide
That doesn't mean that anybody who promises you good things
That's the completely that's the stupidest f****** way to look at things ever
Furthermore
Hitler
Campaigned on like
Let's not worry about the roads
Cuz I'm going to commit genocide
There's some of that
There's a lot of
Pick out a specific
Group
And demons
In order to gain power myself
I'm going to fix the roads
You know what
Gypsies are weird
Take this
People and Destroy them
Because they're at fault for all of our problem
Now is my percent
I believe we can fix our room and repeatedly
I think that Alex
Think
Did Obama kept saying kill White
But if you had venue be like
IC
Yeah
Nothing
Have we considered
So Priscilla
For so long throughout his
The majority has chosen a small minority
Singled them out in and harass them and make their lives miserable
Kill them
In order cement
Political power amongst themselves
Instead
White people
Just like single them out
And made their lives miserable
And like kilduff
You
Like
Ton
Lindsey Graham
We could lose him
Like that's fine
You know
But like but like it's not
It's like not a widespread thing
I'm just saying have we considered genocide on like this
Experiment
That was just to get to the portmanteau
Good outside and I feel like I did my job
I'm going to go retire well I'll stop
This ding dong over here with a bad haircut
I'm sorry
Frown decide
Mal came in
Promise chain
Promise to better life
In five years
They don't care a lot
They don't teach
They do but they weren't we know what else
They were exterminated
60 million 60 million numbers mostly due to starvation mismanagement talk about that
It's the mismanagement of resources
Government
And at the same time
Very unfortunately time to Drought that are very
I've been very seriously a problem in China
Stop don't get me wrong I'm not saying that mountain f****** kill people
No
The mismanagement
Your number is thrown around so flippantly
Two things that are
Not incidental but
It's not extermination
As much as it is like
They f***** up
You know what
That wasn't the globalist
I don't I don't know what else to say about it
It has nothing to do with
I don't know what's going on here
What's a goal
Hitler
Pray. Pray to
God
The way it won't happen
If you
Your friend
And all of it
Together
Precious
Two wonderful
Too good of a
The place
To lay down
As of
Greatness could arrive
Once we break the shackles of the
That's hold
Stack
Something America has more than any other countries and entrepreneurial
One thing we have more than any other countries with milites innovator
Not true
Devil Italy
Be the trend forecast
Really I wouldn't
Big Brother
Doesn't come down on us
That's harder
Historic cross
The forces of global
Are Marching towards absolute
Look in the mirror
Count
The cost
Or
Will you stand tall
Freedom lovers everywhere
And stop the completion
I'ma World dick
Wait the music was by Rob Jacobson
Not great
Not good
Divya animation
Animation
Right right
Disappoint
Recorded image lab
Jacobson has a
Webster
Krs-1 Jesse Ventura Willie Nelson wow
Wow that's wild
This guy
I want to challenge all of you out there
By this film I'm challenge
The truth
Frankly it's far worse
Hear it.
The claims in this film
I asked about your job
Spread the word
Warn your friends and family
Betrayal
We have to warn the people that Barack Obama
Fancy teleprompters
Nothing more than a front man
A pitchman
Please get the high-quality DVD
Wake him up let him know the threat
Global banking system
Truthout
You got to get the truth out
All the evil men and tyrosine to flourish
So we cannot stand here idle
Really feel like Thomas Jefferson did today then
Thank you so much
Watching
The Obama Deception
It's not Thomas
That's what I mean it's a real quick
Finally the end of
Real quote
Jordan
This is been coughing
I think
Thank you so much for putting up with this I don't know what my name is
I don't know what year it is
It's Jordan
Allegheny ms-28
I remember having
Pete Wentz
Seems like those are no longer available
Weave
This
And I want I want I want I want
As much as
Do you have felt
The pain of this
I can't imagine I'm so glad to shake off the burden
Of The Obama Deception name for a week
This
Sucked
So much
This documentary is utter trash
But I can't yeah
I don't think I
Let's hear you f******
Not Kevin Hogan
Doing the Hulk Hogan
I forget that every time I say Hogan
Listen to me Savage
Not Michael Savage
Randy Savage
I wouldn't want to call him out
Lex Luger
That's not great
Listen to me sting
Not the musician
List how long is this going to go there's a lot of wrestlers who have the same name as something else that comes up in the night
When we
Crosby Stills
This documentary when I did
The hours and hours of
Research on endgame
It to me was like
Kind of fun adventures
Like I was learning
Rewind about this fun
It was gross lies
It was just a monster Bez lives
To find out like oh no that's not
Yeah
I had to read books
To find out like what he was talking about
Starting World War
I found that f****** super fascinating
Nothing in here really was all that fun was if I had to go on these side roads learning about like
Goddamn Louie gohmert
Old like learning about life
That's what I had to do has been incomplete an abject
Failure is almost nothing
Documentary
I can't put in more simple words
Is trash
It suck
There is almost nothing in it that's
True
Over the course of the last
However many hours
That we've been doing this all these episodes
I have found almost
Nothing
That is actually true
Then I'm not talkin about true in the bickersons
I mean true Wednesday were making
Like when they were making this
They had to know they were lying
Yeah there's no way around
Yep
Metal roof sound like
That's really terrible lie
Like that you aren't your
Clearly
You're obviously misrepresenting
Instant
Did I sound does Alex
Merely pushing
A doctor
Photograph
Of
The service
It's f***** up like that sort of thing when I find stuff like that
You're like I find that and I'm like
I'd like you suck Alex
Your job
Is to do better
He's not a truth-teller
It's not like he's tell you specifically the opposite of though he's a live teller
He's a propagandist I'm not expecting him to come to
A good documentary
It's going to be a challenge
A break time
Yeah put together
Really didn't take that much work
In quotes
He took like
100 200 things to look into more like
No
No that's absolutely that misrepresentation
It's like transcribing a half hour recording where it's like
I know I'm only typing a half hour but I have to pause every 5 Seconds
Entirely frustrating
You know I mean we talk about this all the time it's like
All our job is
Stomachs that is to be
Watchman on the wall
Core character
Gateway
What we do is we
Look at with Alex's saying
And try and make
Make it fun
Degeneration from endgame
Who's there
It's only a few
New Year's
Evansville wax
Of care that you put into that
Liquid endgame
It's not good
It's
There's a product to it that they do belie professionalism
Documentary
He repurposed
Klipsch multiple-time
He reused from a game
He use the same score from endgame all done again
And multiple time
Headies voiceover not match what's on screen
That's clunky as f*** I'm going to give you
How many
Atlanta Georgia
Alright
Too long
Could have got 25 minutes
Leonard maltin
There is literally no movie that literally has ever reviewed
You got about 25 minutes
That's pretty
Like almost
NTR
Do you disagree on many things
Spiritually
You have a little movies and
I just tighten it up
Who is that all the time
But not for me
Would like oh
You don't give
Is when he gave the list of people on the CFR in the trilateral
Commission Bilderberg
It's clear like he had somebody
Make the graphics
PowerPoint
Because that's what it look like it look like PowerPoint presentation even then
5 minutes
To alter a PowerPoint presentation
With information you have even even to the point where
3 days before you release it you still could have gone in and be like
I'll just put this shot in
Instead of this one
Examples even someone who was
Consideration for National Security
That fly
Yeah
Biggest f***** up it's just sloppy it's.
I love you going to be on
Glass back
It's just
I don't know
I know
Fun fundamental aspect of Alex's
Jesus worldview and stuff like that
But when were forced to talk about like when he
Makes us talk about the Federal Reserve
It just becomes like
The illusion of
This is fun
Kind of wears away from
Yeah I know because if it comes so much like
You're lying about this
Intentionally
Learning about the Federal Reserve
I really enjoyed
I think it's valuable for our listeners cuz I think a lot of people don't know about
I didn't care
Click the link
It's good to know those things I think there's value
YouTube
Like when you're watching this
It is so much like a guy
Almost standing out
Side of a junior high civics class and going like
You don't want to learn about all that b******* man
Cool
Come with me and I'll teach you about the real history
And and it's like you're just training a generation of people who are
Dumb avoid ever learning reality
That's that's what Alex
Alex's
AAA
F******
Pied Piper for
Yeah
Except
Rap
Good people
Good
Do the paper eventually took kids
The bad guys forgot about that
Yeah nevermind I take that back
What you forgot about red
I thought you were sort of the equivalent of like they Patrick with the specs
Absolute legend about a guy who just got rid of rats
Really well for story
Anyway Jordan I love you thank you for doing this and more
This is a huge burden
For you I don't mean that
Don't leave like this we did this all day
This is not swears he recording here now its 1 a.m. we've been sitting in this room since noon
We did
The first one was 9 hours and now we've gone
So
We we we really we really blew it. We really blew it out for the end of season 2
My name I really don't remember
Jordan
I know I
I really feel like I want
Give some sort of a bow on
I know that I'm
I feel like I'm rambling
My vote
I deserve this because
Goddamn hours I'm going to give it to you
Just from
External
Viewpoint
If you look at Alex Jones
Documentary
Yep
What you find is multiple fake quote
He's using
At least one instance of a doctor photograph that he's using to smear Obama
At least one instance
Of him using a smear that was used in the 2018
2008 campaign
Against Obama what you should know better
By this point
As
If you take
Everything else out of it all the other dumb nonsense
That alone
Should be disqualifying
In terms of it being something
He should put out
Liquors that goes our editorial problem
Anybody who works for a business
Let's say The Huffington Post
Like I said Alex made this documentary for The Huffington Post
This one clear the lawyers
No
Absolutely not we're taking on liability if you you put this out right
Someone's going to be like
I hate
You're using a mirror
You doctored that photograph
Yeah
My bow is
The documentary
Sucks balls
And
It's your nephew
I got
Or is it going to make it
I guess
I don't know I'm done
Foundry bad at
Lake Eva
Fixing things
Bums me out
Awesome
Your throne in doctor photograph
Great keep on going
You're at your consulate you're throwing all these people together who don't belong
Awesome
You're pretending people are Gruen
What
Do a good job of that
Don't throw in footage from your other
Comentari don't get people's names wrong
Group name wrong don't throw in there in the wrong
Someplace like just
Just like taking it out man
I guess what yeah I guess like if I was a DP on this film I could make it
1 this was like an hour and 50 minutes long
Shoulda been an hour intent right to
Tightened it up
Through line of Lexus IS
Is this keep jumping around
Still don't know what the movie was about
What's called The Obama Deception
What is 50
No it's the federal reserve put all the stuff you talk about the Federal Reserve
I don't know either
I think I think what this comes down to it I think both of our
Complaints to be synthesized
Quality assured
This is bad
If you're going to put this out
Because you got to rush to Market because Obama's hot or whatever
Going to be around
Google Play
You still made a lot of money on
Even though he's putting it out for free a lot of dumb dumb still pay for it
But like
Even even if that's the case then got to rush
Get to Market
You do is
After that
Take your time
Make a better version
And then put that out as
The Obama directions to ducks
This is just
Trash is trash
Trash
Ashamed of yourself
Go fuc yourself
You pile of garbage
This is your life's work and it is nothing
Dandino it isn't trash
Are website.com
That's transitions coming out and I do wear a transmission coming out of nowhere
Twitter knowledge underscore fight
Weird to do this at the end
Because we're going to stop and Alexa
Find a way to make it 5
Just cut it up so one part of this Insanity Jemison
My work is making Miss five episodes
Alright done
If you go to Facebook
If you're on someone who is
Found the show
This week and all that we appreciate that very much to our website
I'm sorry you're our Facebook
Adult site on Facebook
You should do is go to our group
It's go home to your mother your brilliant is the name
The group
If you request to join we will let you win
I don't like really posting much on the normal Facebook
Because who gives a f***
Write most of the action goes on in the group
For the large influx of newly
Go to the group
They will give you guidance
SEPTA deal with
Thrall
People in the group by the people who made this happen
Them so much
I guess Thanksgiving was yesterday so
Forgot about that
We love you all thank you so much
Jordan
Do you know what Dan
Neither of us
Against All Odds
Against
Die tonight
That's true it was closed it was touch-and-go
One man
Probably
Technically died
And Alex Jones.
Technically
Probably
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work