Alexandra Thurston color
Hey everybody welcome back to college
Alex Jones
Favorite holiday celebrating
Thanksgiving
The showare
Unfortunately
Coverage that was recording
Today
Because I know a lot about Alex Jones
And I only
I had a holiday with my face and my family
Check that in the good times
Are there was this
Succession of moments where I
I wanted to punch my family
This particular sequence
My girlfriend
Talked about
Dental work and how her insurance didn't cover it
You know they're just in it for the money
Oh you're saying that for-profit medicine maybe doesn't lead to better patient
Mom said that while she was pregnant
With my little sister
Insurance
Guess what
Existing condition
Health issues and he said
See this is a situation where I'm sure our listeners are Imagine
Situation playing on the way
Stiff upper lip
I did not
Pretty much right after that
Andrea Cortez
She said there were three chambers and immediately after that
Typo
Yeah I think
What's Cookin what are you eating
Good Times country that
Doesn't celebrate this or that weird holiday whatever you guys did I hope you had a good time
Save this
I am so excited to not be
Amman
Lost my voice
Where I almost got mad at
Maybe a good half-hour Chung
We got to go
Get through this
Play I apologize I had
I would go out of sorts
Actually what
Covered with snow on play
So awful
That like
Note adjust itself to that but
I went back
And today we're going to be going over 2000
Going over March
24th 2019
Filled me with joy
There were multiple times
Who Ally was
Getting clips
Episode episode
Right blurt last
And had to go back and listen to what I have just listened to over it
Fantastic
There was something refreshing
A radius alley
All right there's my guy
Unify don't like him at least it's not
Produced
Like the voice-over Alex
This is the worst Alex characters
And so today will be going in
To March 24th
Do a couple new people who joined up
With the show
Very
Well thank you so much
To Will
You are now
Ewok
Bank of Wales
This isn't
Sup with
Every now and again at your head but I would also like to say thank you
Alexa Yarnell policy blog
Thank you so much Lady Gaga
But so much
If you'd like to
You're more than welcome to
Amateur sport the show
Thank you so much please do and everybody
Today we start off
So you probably won't lie
I would murder you
It's close and it's really it's really fun that we've now done.
The entire Obama
And because we're jumping back into the
The. Of time when
Text my reveal
Alex
Boo
The effects of the Jordan almost losing his mind
12 hours straight
Alex is kind of not really understanding
Mason's Tea Party
We've seen that
Past episodes
Sort of in
Write them so he's starting to see
Coverage of it
And even though he doesn't
Fully associated
Himself with the Tea Party
He's still
Defensive about it
I think that's going
To help him
Make the
This morning for an hour on the treadmill
Sure
And
Recognize
Puff pieces for George Bush's wealthy specializes in
Propaganda
You know at all
He was a Muslim
These are mentally ill people yeah that's just as bad as saying the n word
Manny Manny
Biggest Edward I've ever known
It is like a places that there is crazy
But if those are the equivalence is you're trying to make I say sir
Private
Weekend we can pull up about a million of those from
Yesterday
The South
Louisiana Mississippi
Come on
Some okay
Alex
Name of this episode
Gets into
Feelings about
Other
Conservative
Your
.
He doesn't like Michael Savage
Feelings about the other more famous
Conserva
Broadcast
We already know what he feels about him
Drug gorilla
Only describe
Collapse
Oxycontin
That would
Is regular heroin
You don't get me
Like to get on board
I wish I was would just Wing is documentary
Why not
Oh oh no we have to make this look professional
That's what you call Professional
Why the f***
Look not like
Just it would be
Quicker it would be as flick
What time is factual inaccuracies
So
Alex
Episode
You may remember
I do recall you heard him say
I want to hear your voice
Severe vomiting
To which I said
Slightly different
Here's the first one
That's out of calls
A little bit not as hard-hitting unclear what
Hard-hitting
Message
Lacrosse
Still pretty glowing reviews
Slept great
Little bit later Alex gets another Obama
Jessie
In Las Vegas
How are you Alex
Good
Good good
You don't like I wanted the first start with The Obama Deception
Definitely enjoyed it
Because I wasn't you so much I can't say that I learn too much but the exciting part
Do I get to meet people
And bring up the alarm to set and then either the Mitt Romney type that we're out here in Las Vegas Nevada
Huge movement out here
And they already know
So
His review is I already knew all this s*** cuz I wasn't but the exciting thing is now I have something
Also the people I talk to about it already know about it is
Greatly dip
I would talk to them about
Do you know XYZ
Do you think they don't know about
We have a nice little conversation
Weirdo friend now
Even-keeled
Can I go with you
Thing that I started to reflect on
Two kinds of Alex Jones callers
The crazy people be like
Right right about the past
Sweet nutjob2 call-in
And then there are people who are way too
To prepare
And this guy is one of the vets
Section V Jones's listener
They know that they can
Use Alex
The show
To amplify whatever they want
Answer this guy is calling in to talk about like Las Vegas
It's politics
Really prepared
Using Alex's show as a bully pulpit
Any starting with the the buttering up
Exactly
Use that strategy
We hear Alex
Explain why
Which is something I'm Carrie
But
In doing so I think he reveals
The answer to one of the big mister
But we couldn't get
To the bottom up
What is about
Well
No
One specific
I couldn't
The official anthem
Mainline Republicans
Who believed that he secretly Osama bin Laden
He was born in Kenya
Weather weather
The media early on shows to make
Attempt explaining his motivation in making the Obama.
Preemptive
Face on
Sort of beating against Obama
If it's not a tooth
Hillbilly yelling
Himself as
Do you like
Above it all
Non-partisan
I don't like this guy
Sucks
That
I would say Mission failed
Also your buddy Jerome corsi is one of the ones who's going around in the media talking about Obama being forwarded Kenya
Yeah and your throat
Hey
Anyway
So that that I think is a failure of an explanation for why you made
Well he starts getting distracted with talking about other things really explained
Any further
I think you just like I think I can make the money also
Information the Obamas
He wants to tell the truth
I imagine documentary
I think it was just
Maybe he had a ton of blank
Make a DVR disc
That could be a DVD
Got to move these things I don't know
Crafts
Interest like that before we got to the part where I
Sings this song
A little mystery
Meanwhile
Americans
Thanks
Republican Democrat black white Chinese Mexican doesn't matter
Signs for the life of
Anything that indicated a 90% disapproval rating for the Baylor
That was something that I was
Completely flummoxed by because
But they're Alex's brain immediately goes to Congress got thousand
Call
Presume
Acapulco
Intense love
The people who would call your congressman.
But that's also there's so many statistical elements
Kronos app
You called me like
Mississippi
Ridiculous
In the documentary he said there were thousand 21 phone calls against
I imagine
Maybe
Got that
You can imagine somebody has that that level of
That makes me feel a little bit better
Oh
Seven things that
People took away the most
Enjoyment out of
In the Obama.
Was the moment
Alex
84 years
They will destroy Obama in order to bring in
Another puppet
Alex predicting his own future
Next
The same thing
But doesn't even
More clearly
It's insane how much you used
Just like this is what I'm going to do
Because they will associate their personal power
Because they see it as their man's doing it
Zaywoah
Even complains about data online
Comments for bit after that
The key Freight their key phrases that they associate this person with their personal
Power power behind the Trump movement
I can understand it's crazy is bananas correctly
Perfect
But he's not really
All these dumb people
Stupid
Somebody play that clipboard
Somebody somebody barley giant boombox
Perfect
F****** time
To do a
Christmas Carol with Alex Jones
Ruby so good ghost of Alex present would be him talking to that thirty-year-old would leave a house
Click
And the ghost
Christmas future is his co-host with one-year-old
This is the future is looking at
His own with no one around it but
Jerome corsi prison
Call Lara
Download
Ted Anderson doesn't even come
Have you awesome
Another caller
Another review
Las Vegas
Ultimately my
Picanha the sound production
Amazing
Thank you very much for
Professionalism and honing your craft
The reason why I was calling today
Actually had more to do with Marshall out here in Las Vegas Nevada
Get a pumped on that one
That's all real
Claire mysalad Las Vegas
Steam on the show
He doesn't laugh
Something else happen
It's far more important
But yes today is
Those graphics
There's not a professional
Peoples
Shiprock
Like I said
Las Vegas martial law is going to have to take a back burner
Because there's another man I would watch
The show Las Vegas
Martial law
That
Would that be MCA S-Type
Situation
The guy's name is Marshall
I like this Las Vegas and he's got a serious drug problem
Also
Chief of Police
He stay on the Prairie
Okay this is now we're in like a
What do Arlington Jail pay off his gambling
Something like that
If the hill
The federalized
The Las Vegas Police
Hitman bring in martial law
Exactly
There's a there's a lot of
Calvin Titus rules bandied about on this show
All the cold open
Because the show is actually like Hogan's Heroes
That
We got a winner flash-forward after the first season
You mean
Alright
I don't want to do it
I think that's
So you meets God was a Bart
Martial law
Even though you're in a FEMA camp your Q3 to be federalized though
That might be a winner of a show
Dude that was
Once we have a little more time
Flush out the beat
We can shop it around and pilot season
Las Vegas martial law is going to have to wait
About the show and Alex talked about it as a narrative because
Something else is on Alec
What does mind
And it's something we talked about already
Is f****** mind about it on the show and its allies
High schoolers
18 24s for military and domestic
Military service
It's just a nice report roll not combat roll
I mean this is unbelievable and no one is talking about
No one is talking about it because it
You're making up
He's talking about the Department of Defense director
Do 1404. Tend we talk about our Eddie's ats-v
They forced out
And then the other thing is the HR 1388
She's just reading the wrong version of the Bell
And not the person that ever was in the Senate
Find about this on the show that there's a draft
And what I listen to stuff like this actually
Like what
Started up the episode misses the road he was going down
What is he going to do when that doesn't
Like how do you do it how do you
There's a f****** draft now it looks
Six months later.
There still a draft
Clair Shores
We got that
Studio goddess
Plastic
I don't know
Such a big
You know it gets.
Huge
Easy to be like that
. that's not
He's clearly saying that there is now a draft
They were just bringing up because nobody else
Who is sure thing like
Probably would be his eyes Angela
Even though he's pissed off and no one else is covering
He doesn't want to
Because he wants to take calls
Something else
Taking calls
I'm just going to sit here
Palmer
Because preparedness is very important and
He's not having his water filter or sponsor on the show
Confuse long to get to the point
Direct
Survival food people who actually
Interesting Lee
Bench
Shapiro now sells survival food
Is the name of the the water filtration
Sponsor
I know it's really confusing
Because what it does is it take water out of the air
Like moisture out of the air
Filters
Make a drinkable
But it's really helpful if it works
Don't think it does
Parader
You. He does talk about how he
These filters
Play
If you want one for your whole house
You know for like
It's the size of a school
The shipping cost on that allowed
They got to do that
I think that would be
Impossible 4
For anybody who doesn't live
Completely awful
The grid I don't know I don't know if most people have
A school bus
Size face
Yeah I put that in
I'm trying to figure out if we have a room
Now the answer is no
Plus water filter
The shortwave broadcast
Clip
He's done talking to his water filter guy
What are you special
You gets done
You should have.
Because the next color that he gets
He's a f****** anti-semite
Hey Alex how you doing today buddy
That's not actually watched about three times I think it's a great film too many times
Personally it just
Tackles the whole issue of New World Order
One of the things I want to ask
I noticed
Citizenship for Israel
Was there a reason that you decided to skip that
The conscious decision on your part
What he's talking about is this idea of the right of return
Right of return citizen
SunChips
I'm sorry everybody who's Jewish
Can't go to Israel and become a citizen there is that their country that allows that
Not for me is not that people in Obama's cabinet or work for him
Have dual citizenship
Yes by virtue of the fact that
They are
54 my hereditary
Deeply f*****-up
Because that's not like that's not
These people were all born in Israel
They moved here and they
I still think that's a stupid argument but at least
You be coming from
Why doesn't anyone talk about something like that
Extra second
All
Justice
I find veneer over saying
These are Jewish people
Why are they in position
In the government
And that's crazy
I don't know Mississippi
From somebody
Alex's responses
Talk to me about that little lady think
This is what happened
With research and literally
We got to get this off
No I meant
Install and then how
How much was cousins
Caring
So he meant to get into that witch suck
Because he's probably just
Lying
You actually say to anyone who knows what
What is like
Just said it was already over
Whether or not
To his audio
It's really hard to say I don't know if he's oblivious to the fact that
All this guy is in his cabinet
Alex should know better
Man
Until
Rightly pointed out the right of return
It is strange that people from
It goes on a little bit longer
Do you make some announcement
Hotmail
For the rest of my
Approved by the Senate
Because they're such a
More
The faith-based initiative
July 4th coming out with a second Obama
Get everything out I wanted to say it now.
That might as well
If it's a response to this color that's kind of
The feeling that it has
Uwosh so
Coverings
Whatever that movie was
You don't even know what Shaq better I don't
No interested
Inception
The show is going to make us go back
Who is that
Address
Which one of their trying to lure people
The third one
Needle to go back to
Find find the kids
That lost their whatever
Read a lot of number
6park
Backpacking Soros
Get back
About doing it
About doing a second
Nantucket Obama Deception
Don't go out
But
In addition to that
He also has some thoughts
Nicolas Cage
Okay
I'm actually I'm out here to hear that I'm about it
Raising Arizona
Alright
Have you had a chance to talk to you about that new Nicolas Cage movie The Knowing that came out have you seen that yet
The wicked male I miss a lot of things
So it fits completely Illuminati hide
It's about an astrologer
Who stumbles onto a 50-year numerology
Numerology
All about major disasters and events that are going to happen in the world and basically at the end of the film extinction level
What happened
Who won the first code that he breaks was 9-11-2001
Latitude longitude
I mean
It's it's
It's not
Okay
This is my favorite so it's probably the hardest I've ever laughed at
Movie theater when this came out and
Maybe I did
The theater whatever the case I saw a screening of it then it was just me and my friends drunk
The plot of the movie is Nicolas Cage's son goes to
Time capsule
Nicolas Cage with kid
Gets a big sheet of paper that has a bunch of numbers on
EXO he gets obsessed
And he's looking over all these numbers
I can't crack the code
Figure out what what's with these numbers
Have them all written on a dry-erase board
Boloco did everything
It's alive
This shot that made me laugh so hard
Is he sitting there drinking a scotch
Late night
Darkroom
Drinking a scotch looking at these numbers
Can't figure it out
Glass down
On the piece of paper that has all the numbers on it
Picks the glass up to have another drink looks down
There's a glass
911 around 9-11-2001
Make me laugh
That's pretty cool.
It flashes to is Hema Googling 911
I f****** know those numbers where do I know this
So that sucks
That movie is
That's good that's good I like that
Google
At the end of that
If not a lot of
It is
Fantastic
He fights
Like it starts out very slow and ponderous and they deal with all this stuff
Man on man
His
Sonic
Extinction level event
Come down and they take Nicolas Cage's
The daughter of someone else
The school
Weird
Not at all
You don't
When you're telling a story a big reveal at the end
Kind of like to give Clues
I don't know why it was all a dream
The movie and all that
Nicolas Cage Google what planet
Nicolas Cage
Sacrifice
Play some self-service sunmi
Really
I love that movie that's what I'm so glad
It's not like it's 20 years later either about
I should tell you
He's so he gets
Yes
The cup rating on the page 511 2009 1101
Exactly
Those numbers up on the dry erase board
How many trucks
He starts breaking them up like it's like 91:10
It's the best it's like
If I were if the writer can come up with
No
Am I putting that in the movie
Nope
It stays.
I'm so glad they did though
He allowed me to talk about knowing so
I know we all know
Are you still an answer
Now
You may remember
Aways back on the show
Months months and months ago
Don degrandpre forget the greatest day we've ever heard
With none of us will ever forget
But
I'll get another call guy tells somebody loves the Obama
Perception
Which
Mike down on this it's short but it is my favorite clip I think I've ever heard
Anyway another thing what's the latest
Colonel dondi Grand Prix have we found out how he's doing
Oh I'm sorry to hear that
Well anyway
Thanks for the great job thank you sir I appreciate your called
Any updates
Well anyways
Yeah you're going to talk about them Jews anytime soon
So much
Is my dad weird
I don't know I think Alex was suggesting that he might still be alive
Weeks before this
Too far back
But
You got
Generic so good
Well
All right I will talk to you later then I guess my testicle
Very important
Not enough to know whether he's dead or alive
Alright
I will mourn in private
Call Duck
Another caller
Is the bearer of bad
Which will bring us back
No it's not bad it's
Alex's earlier attempt
The draft
Narrative
Just call her help
Make that present
Haitian a little bit
Go ahead.
I think you're awesome
I just want to say hi
I love your work and I love you a bonus action and I'm hanging out as many people as I can what I really want
EQ
People are pretty hesitant to take it
And I've got deathreats you telling me that I should be killed or in call me a Republican or erase it
The draft bill
Past
Descendants 74 to 14
I don't know if you were aware of that
Story that I'm telling you
What is a thumb
Service for all ages Act
Google service
But
Cool
Easy way to keep track of this stuff
If their government has websites
The government publishing office
It has a website where they put up every even like
Introduced bill
And stuff like that
If you knew about that he could have gone to there and
Sounds
Versions of the bill
Emptying the
Changes that have
Realized
We can keep track of like all this was
Right now we should committee
A couple days later
All that stuff is a resource that is very available
No idea that that's available which is troubling
Considering in 2009
He's been on air for
Non-24 years
That's crazy
Google
I supposed to mean
Obama Deception level of research
He does know when a Domino's Pizza
8 pictures
Leading
His staff
To Google it and figure out
What's really going
Infowars
So he has this guy named Matt
He's a GOP operative out of Missouri
This Guy's in Port
It's not really all that
He works with a anti-abortion
Group
Missouri
He ended up later being one of the guys that would go to
For Trump
Great
Added Missouri to the list of states along with mr.
I'm going to take that one on the chin
Who's the guy who they want to after Jeffrey Lord tweeted a bunch of knots
And then they have to fire him
So Matt Martin
Let's get this f****** tickle
Good how is Elliot how many guys
Do you need to get to defend Trump
Who gets fired
I think there might be a pattern
No no no
Because
Report is
Cute biggest
Alex's decided because
He's dumb that it's called
They are
Hell-bent
To get an apology
What Matt Martinez.
Is he's making
In order to get this retract
I'm not sure if
Missouri
Me too
Redact
And so he's on
I'm very
Episode illustrate
Hypocrisy
Pathetic
Those people
Like him
A chart to hedges
Interrupt yard group charge to head in
Very little in common with the ACLU too often
But we went to the ACLU and said you guys
Are supposed to be standing up for civil liberties this is
An example unless some
Let's use
Your own cloud and the go-ahead of course
Betraying their true colors we have heard nothing area word from them and they're not
Assisting in any way
I don't care if they're helping or not you suck
So much
If you complain about the ACLU all day long about global is nonsense
And then when you have a complaint you're like
Hey no one listened
But they listen to you
That's real f****** stupid
Real stupid come on that's next level
Almost to help pedophiles in
Demons and whatever
Boo
No no
No their hypocritical pieces
Go f******
Awful
That's that is
Kclu is 100% wrong all of the time they're globalism their people
You're not busy
Make
I like you
You guys are
Vic time
Defenders of the downtrodden who don't have any kind of political cloud of Their Own
Is every single time
Because that's what they do
Liberty
Nobody's civil liberties were being encroached upon
Outside
You always talk about the draft
Holidays we have this interview about the miac report to calling us terrorists
All that stuff
And his next trip I think
Is one of the most
Weird it's the weirdest juxta
Deposition
Cuz he's coming back from break
He's trying to make everyone really afraid
But perhaps
Is bae
Exact opposite
He would have liked
Used Ford Edge
Martial law
Call the Army confirmed
What's going on
Children under Federal control
Through the window
We can be like that
That's nuts man I love that set up a better life
You couldn't set up a better signal that you're f****** with people then to make them Afraid over Don't Fear the Reaper
So that's
I don't know if you noticed that but that's the second time
Safari then you talk about the draft
Specifically
That's weird and you can't have them getting your women he brings that up over and over and I know that that's probably just because
Is a theoretical difference
From the old
But still
It feels like
Trying to make people
The trigger people
His listeners
Defensive
I think that's what he's trying to
Register
I suppose they would
Considerate chivalrous defense
But in reality it's more like
Control
That's why almost
You know you should.
That Stephen
Shapiro everything out
Sphere this draft bill
Superior the miac report
DePere
Obama who's
Clearly
Oh that's
I'm more afraid of one of those water filters falling
The f****** school.
Waterproof
The reason that I'm
You done like 200
He's very pretty
He has
Front
To himself
A brave space
He faces adversity
Is the globalist
At every turn
Court
He says no
I will I will need
Meet you on the battle
Went down a weird Road
Anyways
The point is it Alex's never afraid of
And the New World Order
Today
Oh no
Normally I don't let it get to me
Listen to this song
Youth Brigade sportsdrafts tattletail squads
We don't have a hairline yet
They call it America
I have the bill here in front of me
It's a version of the bill
If he just went to the government publishing office
It would be so easy
Like you just went
Looked at
That's all portions of the bill later
Yeah that's
Crazy how amateurs this is
I had to get multiple people working there no one is like hey Alex you're lying you're lying by Omission affect
Does he think
That
The if they pass
Any version
Annabelle
All versions of the
Baby
Total
Ignorance about this order
And I should also be clear point out the even if the introduced version of the bill passed it wouldn't create a draft or forced service on it
That's also a misunderstanding
The part that says service
If there is a way
To set something like that up
Whether it would be helpful or not
You set up the study find out
It's not helpful
So you wouldn't do it right
Is just
It's a little bit about
You would think that anybody in
You're going down the road real hard
This draft
Road
And it's based on
My misunderstanding
You should save yourself the trouble of looking
Like a dick
Because he's ever said that to
Because the version that has that language taken out this is
Is the 24th
At least five days possum
Before this
That languages
There's no reason why you shouldn't know that
So
We look back on this now like 9 years later and would like
Oh wow this is
Real indication
Outrageous
Or just
Worst f***
And he literally said to the guy
I don't have time to follow up with
Biggest story that I am Hamming up
Busy
I've been busy
The Jews across state lines
Well
You have
So in this next break
Revivalist minister
He is feeling the spear
My God it's a Vortex of evil
And they want your bank account they want your children they want you to the indentured servants
You got to get the Obama Deception
I was very rousing a
No not really
Another point you was trying to get to with the
I do like the way he slipped it in the middle
Mid-level manipulators and Liars
That if you say what you mean the last
It's really glaring
In that case
Paul Joseph Watson
It's cold in
He's on the line
It's a very rare 2009
Verbal appearance
So now you can say that the UK is at
List of
Field
Open is on the phone
PJ dubs
If you're nasty
And
He has to be the bearer
The actual bad
My God I'm sick of this
Alex
Oh my God
Wow
It's the headline is national service
Call Bill
Please donate Hudl
New York time
Snack
This is their going for the gun confiscations coming folks chart
Don Paul
Read me the article
Better than that has the feeling of a play
Really overact
Part of it
Like jumping around from idea to idea flight
Yeah
Like
Performative
To a great
And that leads me to think that he doesn't know that it's not address
You know we always
Wonder like
What is
What is the LIE what is the
Is is he dumb enough to think that this is
Is the draft
Uno's
He knows if it's a
Suggest a visit
A good advertisement
Documentary
The Obama Deception
Getting people real riled up
Banking on the fact they won't remember a week from now
You've moved on to another narrow
Did the bill pass
Because so long as they're debating The Belfry you can feel like we're fighting about nothing
Said that was the most
Belleville bingo
The 2009
Stupid
As long as progress with
Then yeah you can just
Use that forever like he uses the emergency centers at establishment
Directed at anytime
You're right
That is that is
I had thought about
They the factor want surpasses it
It's kind of a kind of hurts
Casinos it's all bulshit
From fake crying
Now wallmask total slavery it is confirmed
They also aren't omnipresent
I have been very upset
Is bad
Any other cities
Yeah everyone listening as ever listen to the
The dead authors podcast where Andy Daly plays elrond Hubbard
But that right there
Alex
Pretending you sad that sounds exactly like
It really sounds exactly like someone
Play
Yeah that's awesome
Has no sense
Tall
It's crazy
About the idea that
People calling Donald Trump
Hitler or calling
People in the alt right
That's
Especially like
Lycra
He just got into office what you doing
Now we see
Be here
Parched
24th 2000
Obama's been in office about
No two months and nine days
Here's Alexander
I want to commend all of you out there
Right now
God promises
All the king's horses and all the king's men are together
You look at that man on your screen Barack Obama bat
Empowering him
You are looking at the next at all
He has a spirit
He has a spirit of deception
That was quick
Yo what did he what did he do
He was on the screen
Alright
Okay
Starting a
Literally what did the first
Two months didn't misread a bill
But he didn't know there was the
I don't know I don't know
Right
He hired Rahm Emanuel
I think you might take that for different reasons salad
That's why
That's scary that's hitleresque
Hitler had a
I don't know I can't think of a whole lot else that isn't like
Erica
Bailed out on him
Misunderstandings that Alex has it could be cleared up
A little reading
Somebody that you don't
And start yelling
Anyway
This is the dog
Recall
Was he laughed so hard
Know about Israeli citizenship
Docket baby lose my s*** and I was like that's one of the reasons why I like
I'm so glad we listening to the show instead of hell yeah
You get the call towards the end of the show
Hey this is
So weird
Alex's responds to this guy is
Possible I have no idea what's going through
What's going on talk to Jason and Kentucky Jason go ahead
Hey Alex
I'm 29 and Mary buddy you're now
And my wife and I
Having our first and I'll bring you
Baby into this world
I know you Liza Morales
You have no one
What
I can't
Figure out what I think about this call
Because I think Alex is sussing out that he
He's Jason
Kentucky he's a white guy
Yeah so you should have Kik
You know what I'm saying like if it was Muhammad
Florida
Subscribe
Yeah I doubt it
But I I don't know I think
The greater context
The call is
Jason's mask
Get bad
We're think about having kids should we sell
We're going to be more what
But at the same time
The way he presume
It's a wonderful time
Whatever rich
It's a bad argument
Because it's just going to get really bad everyone
Give you value and we're going to have the Food Lion
If you were going to turn into
The summer of Rage
Active baby through that
And a baby isn't really going to experience it
Until it's
Years old
Should we make it through to the other end and then you die
Rainbow York you get cannibalize
What if it's a curious case baby comes out
Baby girls really fat
Want to talk about
This thing is like all of Alex's argument
That's that that's worth ideas
A remarkable time to lift
After all that stuff
And the only thing that really feels like Alex
He thinks this guy's wife
And Afraid of the demographic
Quit
Or anything I can
Sure that's fine
You should shut the f****** about this
Alex
Then children at Society
Tell him to have a family
To doing what he does
I got really upset earlier because you just hits me I can't just sit here day after day
Mega draft for women's well
I mean you know they're building descamps I mean
This doesn't have to help other people
It's really
I like it's
Funny but
It's so dumb
Like
When you have
The information
Reading the wrong version of the bill
It's just
You look at this music
Alex
What are you even doing
Did you know women are already in the military
He's not into it
I don't I don't know
Position
If I had to guess I would say he's probably one of these guys look they shouldn't serve with me
It feels like you might be on that yet but I'm talking to her
Yeah that's weird
I would be surprised
Now if there was a draft that
Didn't
What is there was address
Stupid awful
But if there was I would be shocked
Was just a male.
I think that I'm crazy
Dismounting
Is ending the show
Kind of really about for him
Is pageantry of Faking
Crying
Misunderstanding old version of daylight
Busting my butt
And I'm not good
I'm just some average. It's all up to you
The truth is more powerful in Hawaii
Literally
I'll tell you I want to fight for freedom
I doubt you're just an average guy
But also I'm here to say
Pictures does not spread faster
That is not more powerful than the lie in any wars
Is
So powerful
Stronger
Then truth propaganda is
Incredibly effective
When you have
A dumb assholes putting out of
Documentary film
For Ron Paul's brother says it's three people pass the Federal Reserve Act
MN
Like legitimately
I wanted to do an entire episode
About
There was a you can find this on YouTube
If you want
An episode of Opie
Where Patrice O'Neal goes on
I tried to tell them about The Obama Deception
It's an hour long
I'm talking about how great this movie
I wanted to do an episode of our show where we're like
This is
The effect
Have a documentary like this
You have is a respected comic
And someone who people think
Is a really brilliant guy
Like Patrice O'Neal
Sure it's coming on to Opie and Anthony
Necessarily in that right-wing Patriot world right and you have
Someone falling for the ideas
Better put forth in the documentary
At one point in the interview
F****** Patrice starts talkin about
Nathan Rothschild and it sting at Waterloo
Nazi propaganda that he's heard from the likes of Alex Jones maybe he watched game
So he's just
On exam
And so no
Is very powerful
The LIE
Is
Maximilian
The truth
Is what we are doing
And it's not working all that great
Because if we're not the
I mean it's still relatively the same ratio as the LIE
Click Count versus the retraction
You know whenever whenever Fox News or somebody puts up something that clearly bulshit
Everybody called him out on it and they write the retraction Alex apologize
Hamdi ulukaya
What is 1 + 1 is
Going down a road
Is very easy
Explain why
This is stupid
The draft
But it's still so much better
The last two
Absolutely
Realtor
Coming to his shop again
News
What is that
This episode was
Kind of
That maybe
It would have been
Is because this narrative
The show does end up being Alex
Just fake crying and yelling about
The draft
No
That's not that's not
You had a week off
I think I rushed through some stuff and nobody some notes
Metal note back better than ever next
Sounds like a plan
It's knowledge freight.com
Update.com
You still did also legally change my name to
Realtor
Facebook is where my favorite things to do
It's so great
A lot of fun
Russell
Describe your friend
Mitch
Mitch on the show
I know that we say no snitching
The doctors
Snitch all you want
Tell people
I think the way he presents himself definite like he's
His
Sort of autobiography
Exxon him
Paul Joseph Watson
And this is a rare appearance of him verbally being on the show we got to celebrate
Even though he hasn't been a bunch of drugs when he was younger
Alright
His employer
Alex Jones
Oh yeah
Technically
Probably guilty
Alex