Hey buddy Dan here I just want to
Before we start this episode again
You want it all
We're going to be going over today drift
Pretty deeply into stuff that would
Rightfully be called offensive to most people
Some of the content that we end up covering
Is a very homophobic
Even to a violent
That you
Have no tolerance for I totally understand and
I would advise maybe this is not the episode for you
Let's jump here is the episode
Holding
Alex
Little bit by Alex to Jordan I realized that I forgot
I left
Because of that moment like
Being in the theater and laughing that hard
Was
Transformer
Yeah I don't know I don't know
I don't know what kind of answer to
Give because there's good movies that he's.
Sounds really good
You could say that or any Port of Call New Orleans Bad Lieutenant
They're so different
Performances
I don't know
Wicker man's great
Range of movies that I can't choose one that's my favorite
But I'll probably say the
It's a close tie
Between man and Matchstick Men
As I thought.
A boy like you Leona
I would not say
Love Taylor
She was great bad boy
About sex
I don't know there's some NBC show that she was on those really great
But it was married
Duchovny
Really
Californication
I don't know
This is the same thing I don't know much about the personal life of David Duchovny
Kind of Arts
Forgetting to the show proper I'd like to take a moment
The show
We appreciate it very much
So first I'd like to
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanksgiving could not be spelled differently
Also would like to say thank you so much
You are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Make it back
Acknowledge
The button
Talk to support the show click that button help us out Keep On The Lights
Is basa another Park
The reason to carry Cassidy trigger something in my brain is because someone posted
On Arts Booker
A link to Kerry Cassidy
That she made
With a Project Camelot
I didn't realize that that was publicly available
Next documentary no
It was really awesome
Because I've been looking for a really long time
For the connection between Project Camelot
And this guy named Andrew basiago
He's a particular crazy that I'm really into
War that I've seen
Interview
It's not
The pilot
So that's
Anyway Andrew basiago claims that he's gone he was a part of
Secret program when he was a kid
They teleported to Tamar's twice
Which is
Most extreme thing
He also
Wet with Barack Obama
Eman Barack Obama were kids and they went to the Demars
Let alone
That's awesome also Andrew basiago
But he's a half dolphin Warrior and can breathe underwater
Alright that one
I guess he has a lot going on
Really like
To cover
I can't find episode
Baba Yaga
So crazy
How do I
Jordan is not a project
We're now on the other side of the Obama Deception
What are the things that I really want to do is I want to open up the when's
Wednesday episode a lot more
We've done a lot of Jim Bakker who done a lot of Project Camelot we've tried to dip our toes and other places
It hasn't really worked all that well generally speaking
There's a lot of shows aren't the same vibe
I did
I watched
So many bad shows
To prepare for this
I watched so many shows that I'm like
Nah
Not right
Two guys a girl and a pizza place really good
Ryan Reynolds
Traylor Howard
Weather
Huge crush on Traylor Howard as a child
One of them was a show called radical agenda with Chris Cantwell
Is the Nazi
Who is featured in that Vice documentary Charlottsville
Who then I started crying whole bunch when he had to go to jail
Yo I listen to so because
He's an out right now.
I was like
But he said he's not
Nationalist
He takes that moniker
Easy to find a lot of similarities of Alex in this
And turn off there is one episode we talked about how libertarianism
Is the gateway to white supremacy
Bingo he hasn't episode where he interviews Simon roast
Who Alex's had on a bunch
The Swede launder who
What's a pedal white genocide narratives
No it's not it's not good
He's not running
Anywhere's is white
It's kind of a situation where
Text yourself against our particular form of
Know what how to cover it
Revisited
There's a whole bunch
Bird Box
And so I thought about it another time would be
To explore some of Alex's guest
That we have it
Floored
Or maybe we touch down a little bit
Hey give me a chance
The deal with
Some of my favorite crazy
So everyone knows my favorite crazy
Is
Darrell Hammond photo
Because he is a guy
Who is illegitimate
Professor
He was doing some real
Important research in the decentralisation of Asian-American been
In our culture
He's pink guitar and the Illuminati
Is a charge of all schools
Lynda Carter
The president of UC Davis as a bunch of
I love the guy
We're not going to talk about him
We're going to talk about my second-favorite
Experience.
Alex Jones
Before
It is Reverend
James David Mann
That's crazy
Reverend Manning
He is someone who has been a guest on Alex Jones Show since at least 2010
Optel Trump's election
Turned on Trump
I called some tribulation Trump
Answer. He's not welcome back on Alex's
For that six years he was gas to come on on a fairly regular basis
Beyond that he's also appeared on Michael Savage show
He has been on Gavin McInnes show
I found another
They talked about her
We won't be listening to any of that
But
I feel like in the time that we talked about Reverend man
We haven't really dealt with
Awful app
And in this episode
Layout for you and demonstrate
Exactly
How crazy is
That sounds right
Upfront today is exploration
Of Reverend James David Manning
I am not or I am now
Isabel
That's the real
Give you a little bit of a sign I want to be in his congregation so bad that sounds like way more fun
Welcome
What do white people that much
Also hate black people
Reverend Manning is one of the most
3 tool player bigots
Piano keys
Triple threat
He hates everybody right
Everybody
It's pretty pretty remarkable
Disability
Particularly of virulence
Homophobe
We'll deal with that but
Comes to us
From
What species do
And the reason that I chose to start with this
Call me Obama
Open coverage
You made the ark
That the first two years of Obama's term
We're linchpin
You believe that you saying you were going to write a doctoral thesis on it
If you ever go back to school
I remember so little for that you recommended
Here is what he has to say about the first two years of Obama
The first two years of the Obama
He released a homosexual
Pickup
Throw me off of YouTube
He released the homosexual
And they were
And then the first two years of Donna
Which is worse or which is better
I love it I love it
Freaky
Sex
I imagine like it's a snake demon with a lampshade on his head
Bottom half of a horse costume
I don't know why it on the head is like my go-to for freaky but
Comes from a very particular time in pop culture
And he doesn't there's an interesting
Think that he
Does
Point out for him
Specific
Is that
What he says
Saying homosexual is bad
Just like staying the
The word homosexual is good for him in particular just like a heart
Yeah
For you it is bad
People to use
I don't know
I don't think I've ever run into anybody was like
Homosexual is a
Everybody
Bad about it
But I went down when I was trying to
Figure out
How we could expand
Was I started listening to a bunch of Stefan molyneux
Of course possessed by psychotic freak
Would you like me to watch a guy stare into a camera space
Every zombie
Watching Stefan molyneux
Watching I started to remember how he likes to see people who uses contact
I don't want to f*** with this quarter end up covering
Even if we're well within our rights to
I still just don't want the headache
But
I found
He's pretty obsessed with pop color
And
I watched a pretty long video very poorly breaks out the Showbox
Is talking about how great Inception is
And that leads us to this next clip
Which is from Reverend Manning
And
What I'm trying to get a lot of these guys love Pop Culture but they're really mad at it because it doesn't reflect what they want it to refresh
They spend a lot of their time with these really high-minded things like Reverend
But also
Needs to take time out of his day
You cursed Lena Dunham
Okay
Do something here
Literally
In the
End the place of
Those of us
This is worse than Obama.
It's worse than Obama.
Stop
I heard like
That's probably
He's talking about when Lena Dunham
And also I couldn't find the Ross YouTube video that put some music
Swelling
It does address
Star Lena Dunham
In Saturday Night Live
Should not be allowed to get away
On way with
And
Response
Is.
The music Meister
Ker-choo
The disease
Curse you
You displayed
Displayed
What did your breast and your vagina
Filled with
Hamsters
Continue to
MD
And you would never know
20 piece
And no doctors
A people to mock the word of God all the producer
Female daughters
Nieces
Show me how the Lord Jesus Christ and I'll bind you
Under the power of the authority that almighty God has given to those that believe him
Saturday Night Live from mocking the word of God and you shall see
I mean
I guess I was worried that he was texted alot of things
Escape person everybody
Read the Bible
May your organs be filled with hemorrhoids
Hemorrhoids pickles become as rocks
And every time you walk
People will know that you are cursed because they were here the sounds of the Rocks coming from between your legs
Has your testicles all the now Rock
Definition
The sound of the rocks of your testicles as you want but you will find it
And everyone will know that you have participated in the mocking of God's word
Actual statements out of a your own
Debauchery
The beauty of God's creation
And the man and wife relationship
The God Almighty is put into the Earth be Eucharist with them rods and the
Sound of the Rocks between your legs as you walk
I'm James David Manning
In the Saturday Night Live has profited from it as well
I am the Lord's servant
Did not work
I haven't I haven't
Like leaned in close to listen to there so they maybe his curse was like just a medium cursive it's like
Do you have to be in within a certain
Distance bright right
And I feel a little weird about
Hey man you didn't like SNL and you spent that long
A problem occurs
Adult
It's that was well-written I don't think so
From listening to Reverend Manning
I think he's rich
Making s*** up
Really got to use in keeping with the Bible in that women have this horrifying terrible
People when they see you they're going to know you were at
Your balls are loud
Universal like
Manning is
Obsessed with cursing Lena Dunham
You know you got Alex Jones
Complaints about
Pop culture
It's everywhere
Because
It's not there
They don't
Controller
Like they steal it
Completely run by the other side
It's the Jews doing it
Women
A TV shows like so many of them are failed
Stand-ups
Yeah it's like all of them tried because they don't understand or have any concept
Humor or
And also the pie
Workout
So yeah it must be people have failed
In the past
It's kind of like their entire world is a persona
The personification of their own failure
How they're fighting ghosts
And their need to blame their failure on every other person
That ever lived
We talked about
Steve episode in 20
I think that's the one we covered him on
That's if you're a little more
He was talking about
You know how
Starbucks
Was putting Stephen Peeples
Maybe maybe not
That is unclear that to convection
There was some backlash from that and really dumb
And saying they put animals
Another latte
Riverbend
Kids claims
Are we going line-by-line
I say do you go to hell
Let's go
But I've got something
Starbucks
Sisters
Adam senior heard my writing
And statements regarding
Starbucks
Angela MMA
NC
Best Buy sound
I'm firing over the bow of the Starbucks
Coffee
Enterprise
And if you're drinking Starbucks
If you're a woman
You might want
Drinking Starbucks
Drake
Your brilliance
And yeah
It's by marriage a some people just like to company dead
It was one of Starbucks
That impregnate
Alright now that's not fair that's not fair
This is trolling
Are you I think that's yet
There's there's some instant
Because I don't think anybody's
You know better how stupid you are
The claim that drinking
This is something where he made this point I think he is,
But he got so much attention for it like
The people were making fun of him on the young
The post was writing about this dump
Trying to
Keep that attention call
I agree with you
There are a couple insta
Where it's like
Yeah this is funny
You trying to be funny
How do you not give a follow-up on this evening
As a narrative
Absolutely
Deleted data
I immediately think of open mike Eagles
Lyrica I looked up what Lena Dunham said and I shouldn't have and I'm out
We need somebody tweeted open
Israel interesting sort of overlap
Of like
People who can't at all
Most people on the West Beltline
So it is it is astray
I told
This guy
What about
Also also
Like I said
Does not like like
She is
Awful
Take it away video
It's comical on one level but also like bleed deeply troubling I believe that
Speaking from the pulpit again
That's really not a good thing
But we got a problem
Black people got a problem
Are you
Is this is this I'm not a racist
I don't know what to do
You can train them you can train a black man
You can train
I don't like that
I've no idea what he's talking about
That's nice
SeaWorld
They don't have mutton Africa that's the first thing he learned did wherever he learned bulshit from
Some of the vocal flourishes are a little amusing today
Storical b******* like I'm going to allow him
The idea that Egypt isn't part of that for
I don't agree with him
But I'm going to allow it for the sake of this Beatdown I'm about to deliver
Alright bring it up historical examples
Cuz the carthaginian empire was a very legit Naval power back-in-the-day boasting a fleet of at least 350
As early as 2:56 BC
According to historians
Carthage is located in modern-day North Africa doesn't count
We should probably just look as far south as we can go
Interesting Lee speech remains have been found at sites like blombos cave in South Africa that date back to
At least 70,000
Which indicates that folks there were able to catch fish in the Stone Age
Contradict the prevailing theory that the inhabitants of the area at the time were incapable of using series
Go that's a remarkable piece of archaeology
There's no evidence that used boats
Give me some sort of an idea of his canoe
Which was discovered in 1987
The canoe was found in Nigeria and radiocarbon dating a place the age of between 8500 and 8000 years old
That timeframe places to do food a canoe as the second oldest boat ever been found
In the entire world a full for thousand years older than any existing boats that we have
See that's how awful black people
They built their boats to even take into account that like Ethiopia had trade
Nonsense
Because also there's another video
What I said Africans didn't have boats
They had a whole lot coastline
Over the holiday literally said
Bill Clinton was the first president to not have any military service
And I
I actually left the room place
That's crazy but you make me
Pronouncement
Bravely and boldly enough
Most of the ones that
Comes people's minds
Like when you think about it
Spanx pyramids
Ozymandias or I realize all that was like
Africa
Egypt
Enter the battlefield
Wants to prepare for us
Even with that caveat he is full of s***
We have to be at Monday
By my pronunciation is no good
Church in the world
Located in
Ethiopia it was built during the Kingdom of Aksum but which place has its construction between 109 48
There's the walls of Benin
Which were built buildings about 880 and they covered over 9000 miles
Is longer than the Great Wall of China at the time
The following is from an article in the guardian
In 1691
The rink open
Portuguese Captain who visited the capital of Benin
Great Benin where the king resides is larger than Lisbon
All the Streets Run straight
As far as the eye can see
The houses are large especially that of the king which is richly decorated
The city is wealthy and Industrial
It's so well governed his unknown
And people live in such security that they have no doors
In contrast London at the time as described by Bruce
Holsinger professor of English at the University of Virginia
Is being a city of quotes thievery prostitution murder bribery
Black Market made the medieval
You're picking up hockey
Stop
Is Timbuktu in Mali is considered a precious intellectual and
Spiritual Center
The city contains many mosques now protected as World historical site
University of sankore as well as just
Thumbs up
Non one-story building
There's plenty more examples that this should make it pretty clear that African history is
Accomplishment
One of the issues is just prejudice
But it goes a little bit deeper than that
In the case of Benin City really illustrates why
Benin city was designed mathematically
They designed based on a fractal design patterns repeat on smaller and larger
Scales
The city is a whole head of design it was mirrored in the cluster of houses
To the city
Then cluster of houses
And then that would be mirrored again
Open the houses themselves
The rooms within the house
Mathematics competition Ron English puts it this way
When Europeans first came to Africa they considered the architecture very disorganized invest
It never occurred to them that the Africans might have been using the form of mathematics they haven't eaten
They haven't even discovered yet
Vera white places like Benin City reach what we would call the Renaissance
Before the West
It boasted deeply complex Civic structure as well as public patronage of artists and Craftsman
Spoiler alert
It's the climb quote
Link to the increasing European intrusion
And slave trade at the borders of the
7 Empire
In 1897 the British Burn the City to the ground
And wizard went much of the history in the body
Greater than the West
Well not all of it
A selection of bronze sculptures from overtaking
Are now housed at the British museum in London
An example of how
Forgot even if the opportunity to make tourism income
You know what I want
Is Ciroc I would even go so far as to say that maybe
We don't talk about this
Or learn about it
And instead learn about how Superior the white man is
Because the white man
I'm going to go out and limb here and say and say that they want to control history to make them look
Possible and then justify their idea of this this great City that
It was really well Ron and very safe
Resources
The idea that like
Because of European
You don't want to teach that sort of thing
The lessons are in Port
Just was it last week that that dude went over to the tribe
Right most people are
Is
But what you're actually doing is in
You're risking
A genocide
Basically
And not to say is it Portuguese
People showing up at Benin was going to risk it beside or anything
Directions
The destruction
The entire
Can I meet the worst phrase in history is and then the white man
Any history book you read
And everything was better
Send that out to
The colonialist
It's kind of a moot point
It takes it outside of the realm of like
Where you're going to trigger
People with wide-eyed
Don't have the
Implicit
External appearance
Anti-whites
Colonialist
Ruined
It ruined a well-established City like
Like it did
But there's there's no way around it waits until white people went to some place
And decided to impose their culture because they assumed that everybody there was
Differently unless they're forced
Misunderstood the organization was there
And wound up
Destroying
Now
Everybody of course has learned their lesson from that history and we don't
Continue to do this
To do that to this day right
Now we need to send
Betta is just a demonstration
Reverend Manning knows nothing about African history
Demonizing black people
Because of his misunderstand
Of African dust
That's
Like African history is
Intricately tied up with Matt
Big big parks
We should really learn more about that
Going to have to look for
We just kind of the disappointing part by that
It is what it is really Nails home that
Anytime anytime somebody's like we have a white History Month
And you're like well every month is White History Month
One-story
There's more than I can get in
Yeah
Where my
Understanding expertise
Like just the eye
You could just take the idea of that f****** 9000 mile long wall
Ha
F***** up
God
Really f***** everything up
Find Portuguese
This should be your first indication that Reverend Manning
If you absorb
Guys fun
Anti-black tirade
After that
Got a maybe
This next website
Cause for Paws
It's like
Oh no
The other day I was talk
I was talking about
And I'll talk
Is the oldest guy
A small-time Italian
The right
I'm so
I'll call him
What if
What is a couple
So I want I want
Backbend
Oh my God
But I can tell you this
Put it in her mouth
It was just me
She don't get no mercy
It just all she's a woman
I really thought he was repenting here
I don't want any misunderstanding
The sword of David
Not the only from there
But I will take a
If the Lord orders man to
And put a sword in the mouth of a person right now
I'll do it
So what's the difference
The difference
Young hoodlum running mystery crazy as I can
Liberty Bell
But God does on his server
To take the sword
Into the hearts of people.
No I don't know
God tells me to take the floor
And put it in your mouth I will do it and I didn't tell me put that shotgun
Hayden
Alabama missing
I'm more scared now so much more
That was
If
I will still kill you
I don't want people to think I've gone soft
Because of his ideas of that God is telling me through
Yeah
Curse the writers of SNL withdrawn balls and their children with
Yeah I don't
Because a bad dude
That's really f****** scared
That is the worst repentance I think I've ever heard in my entire life
Right
No this is him sitting at his webcam
He does he does B's video blogs
What I want I want
Search so bad I would go to that New York.
The Bronx
Harlem Harley
Pizza Hut I will fly to Harlem every Sunday
Has not taken
Because his old channel was called
Which is the name of his church
80 lakh
The first one with an H
YouTube
If you get outsmarted
You deserve every
If the audience
Episode
Looking into
He has a lot of sermons that I can find so there is material that we could talk
Turn off will not this time
Reverend David Manning
That's crazy
Avoid
Now what Pharmaceuticals game
No this is less about selling something
River Manning fancies himself a bit of a
He sells personalized healing doesn't really like from a distance
Pray for you or some s*** right complicated call course
Didn't
Realize this and I think it might be sort of a newer addition to his his preaching repertoire
Because when I looked into his last time
Hear him talking about
Everything
He yells about diabetes
Powers
Hate diabetes
Don't go out
That people don't realize that they're under
Strip
That don't real
Stretch
Stroke
At least
And his love
I'm living
Fight
Aruba
Is a game
Sterno
I'm not going to
Is get back now to the Moon
Numerological
Looking back in the numerology in the middle of a video that you posted
Explain the blood moon
I watch this whole hour long video like what you say about the blood moon
I can cure diabetes
Going to
Say that this is his official nickname but I'm
Alright
He doesn't have a mustache in my head and I can see him with it without him
Okay
Absolutely
Wrestling shoot promo on diabetes
Give me show up at Madison
Square Garden on Sunday
He wait
As if it was aware
Does he believe diabetes is an entity that has conscious
I think so yes
It's for diabetes
Princess Diane Beach
Just really feel like it's personified
I mean I'm sure he does but it's not even like it either bacterial or something like that right right
This is one of those things
It really illustrates
Allstate Tucson
And that's one of the things I should say
His options
In terms of another wacky cover is Jesse Lee
Lee Peterson
And I'm not
Going to cover
He is a guy who is a real Trump
Assholes
Radio
Show guy
But the way he speaks
Leads me to believe that he is absolutely had a stroke
He has like
Diminished
If you watch
Like 5 minutes
I think there's something wrong with his brain
It's not it's not
Jesse Lee Peterson
Worried
To talk about
Manning
The end of this
You will encourage any
Manning has that mental illness the same way that Alex
Has
Clear paranoid schizophrenic tend
Where's Mike Manning
All history of Africa is
Until the white man came
I really wish people would be forced to like learn
Reverend Manning
Diabetes
Is on his
Yes
Africa
Producers and writers of SNL
Not the daytime player
Also gave
About diabetes Now
She explains how he can
Protect you
Broad stroke
I want to talk about the deal with this more tomorrow
Blood moon
We're Friday
The Sabbath
But most people call Fred about
+ 7
I got a positive real quick
What is talking about
Information
Got about the blood moons are
He was staying at a hotel in Indianapolis numbers
76 I believe
Where the highway is that he drove on
And he's describing some sort of like
Metaphysical
He's creating some sort of like
Important sautters it
He never explains what he's talking about
Just 70
Those are Highway
Future talking about is
911 01
That's as high level
The 37
The Seven Dwarfs
And the 7th
Also will get
Biggest highways in the Midwest
A lot of those routes are numerical
As a way of organizing
So this is where you will get
Team is it's not like triple ones means a lot
Nope nope no future here
On the
Of the trust in the Lord hour
That's another 180
How long do you have to trust in the Lord
Stop the blood moon appear already kept me in the room Staybridge Hotel
He earlier was talking about.
Like 20 times
Either he's bragging
Like it's a good hotel and not sure I have no idea
He has a little bit of an ad Revenue coming in
Talking to the Holy Spirit like God was talking to him in a hotel room
Diabetic coma
City sees the blood moon
Right
They told me that
That you don't want
Find yourself
And having
That's a bad thing
Leslie for Randstad
You get rid of
I don't know
Interstate
New York City
Washington d.c.
You thought he wasn't going to
What's up
Hold on
No
Instructed
If you would listen to the word of God listen to me
The sweet
At any rate
Before getting in your car
Amen
You can listen while you're sleeping
YouTube put all in the report
Of the visitors list
This is an advertising strategy
I don't want people to move everyone out
While you were listening you will not have a stroke I promise you that
I can't promise you won't ever thrown a car
Stats
Awesome if you don't want to eat you don't have a stroke while you're sleeping either so you better listen to go to sleep
Tomorrow
For the
When you go to sleep
But you're going into your subconscious
Yeah
I like
This a lot
Their terms of Manning
Evolution
Please be calm.
If you listen to my show
Alright buddy
This problem when someone has a
Another stroke it's going to be tough
You know what good that's the trick of the that's the trick of Jesus's
That's on you you didn't believe in Jesus
Is that possibility stigmatized
It's not a stroke or something like that
Uno
Community like a
Is a great place to go if you have
Because there's Fellowship
There's people who care about you maybe cookie
You meals and stuff like that
Never admit you have cancer because that would be an indication that you haven't been listening
To all you do is encourage secrecy and people being ashamed
But Manning about the church that is
Like no matter how much
Amb relentlessly anti-religion
My uncle is in the hospital right now
And the only reason that he like survived that night
Where he was
You know
We all of that should happen
Was because
Call dispatch
After dropping to the
You do like the good
Yeah
Community you could find out
Someone for finding it there is a lot of value
The pastor that he drove to the hospital is virulence
There's no wind there's no punch out.
And if you listen to the show
You won't
Get a stroke
Probably heart attack also it's kind of a
What about later
You better you better
I should tell you that
Reverend Manning is found Bible verse
Found the secret to immortality
Reverend Manning
Spelling
Immortality
To his left
I need you
The Listener
Okay I want to show you something here
Alright
I want to show you something
I want to show you
What is a tribulation birth certificate
Is
Looks like
Certificate
The Bible
The power
Abyss verse
28th the 28th of August to the 20th of September
God
What
Your soul is already clean
Issue
He wants to save you
Yeah we got it
He's always
Speedway Houston
He sent me
A boat
Contender boats
For your house
Do what you need to do
And you need to put it up over your goal
You know over the top of your door
So when you walk out your house you walk out
To avoid being ran over by a bridge
Distance on a long time and I'll just tell you so what what's up
When he was fighting diabetes hard of his without allergic
Be run over by a bread truck preoccupied with bread
I feel like
That clip a lot of questions unanswered
So I feel like what we should do now that comes from a really long clip and I wanted to pay
Play all of it
But
I will not allow you to ask me some questions about what's going on here and I'll do my best to answer these questions and it stinks
Bible
How important is the gold
Not important.
Bible lies
Do certificates have magical powers
Bible
Good God almighty
I apologize
I apologize for not throwing that in there
No matter how you adjust the microphone
It's awesome
If I needed someone to yell
I probably still wouldn't get him but someone with his gills
I recognize game
The Flash
Two by two
It's like in the
Bible verses from Matthew
It won't taste death
You'll be a witness to the
The coming of the king
That's the gist of the
Then if a witness and I commit myself to be witness of the coming
The kingdom of God
Then I won't take
So he's printed that Bible verse on a certificate and telling his audience
That if you put up
The door on the door that you go out of you can't be killed when you leave your house
Which makes sense that
Track
That's so much like a remember the episode where those what was it
No no no it's okay
That makes more sense
Because it's easier choice about vaccinations
Victim of an
Accidental death
Is not your choice
I don't know if he has made anything more specific than you will not be the victim of a bread related
I should say just
Protect you from
But he's not telling them really which is really weird
In the middle of this Quest
Like a extended clip
He gets into a horse
Put it on
Underwear
They won't dialect
What
Sharpie and write it on the underwear
Hold on to the I think there's a lot of people who are going to be
You're going to go out
If you want them
Send me a large envelope with stamps
I just have to send it to
If you sent me it with the
The literary agent
Visit
He should be charging $50 for the price
Send me an envelope
I'll send them to you 3 cuz we got a printer and I like if you're going to send me
You're going to send me money so I can buy you an envelope and Stamp
Why don't you follow through with a nonprofit called
Do any of the ship
Just get me there's a simple interest
Ha
Why
Columbia University and Obama on trial in this time
Have a Coke
BarkBox
Damn hard
Bible verse
He just discovered it
Recently
Become like a really big part
Kids decided
I love this
Regarding
16 Bristow
Church people
He said
That's problem
Does a 24-hour
So what's up G
What does Jesus
Did you miss me
Jesus prophecy
Best Buy
If you need a witness to your step Count On Me
I will testify
How to make a robot
So far so good
Inspired
What
What have you been in an airplane
Pakistan
Nope
Yeah it's almost all of his yells with I'm the Lord's servant
Which is
It's unsettling.
Yelling at the vocal patterns
Even that's not that awful
Reading a bunch of people to fix it easily
Is there a penny in for a pound whatever
Mostly Steam
Historical revisionism that's unfortunate but also like whatever
He has a Congregation of like 70
It's not like
It's not like he hasn't
Quirky Goofy
Nonsense dangerous
Because of like sort of
Look up
Okay
Boats
Look I don't want to break it
Looking for Matthew so
It's taken from the qsource wrecked it's a secondary level from the original
Exactly
What is about
The people there who eventually saw
Christ
Resurrection Eggs
Another angle
I don't know I don't know ever
But I know that the flash is really not important
Christianity is not really there's a meat body
Important
Isn't so much about the idea of you're not going
It's not relevant
Coming of the Kingdom
Lorde
Through what important your spirit
Deaf as a as a sentence as as it as a blip
So you will not
You will taste transcend
Is that
Sojourn
Ruin the f****** day
Granddaughter
Heard all the episodes know that like there's a real
Real kibosh coming
There's a real Hammer that I've been holding over your head and I got to say
If you're new
Every episode is fun
Until Dan decides to wreck Oliver spirit
Just information
Multiple pieces and this is where that it stops being as fun
This next clip will be sort of
Fun transition
But I should warn you ahead of this clip
Good pastimes it's not been fun
This is a whole new level of nausea
You're the bread truck of this episode yeah unfortunately
You know I live in Harlem
We are as African-Americans
He's of the absence of males in the home
80% of the homes
African Americans are headed by women and there are no males
And the homes
Leading
This doesn't sound like it's going to be
This isn't going to end well I can sense this coming
And so women are having a difficult
2 million
Mama
Basketball player Michael Sam
The closet
Obama
Has released the homo demons
On the black
Lookout black woman
A white homo may take your man
Is
A new one
That's it that's a weird races Southern Trope of like the black man's going to steal the white woman
That is kind of the way it comes out
It's weird
It's just like a board on the ground
It's like
You know where you would normally see like I remember these
The best vitamin B1
What hormones are going to take you ladies look out like
That's as far as something to walk by
I wouldn't I wouldn't
Could you have an interesting story to tell
Watch now
I have noticed
Closet homosexual
And they're being scooped up by
Leaving the black
Be her husband
And father her children
Also real fun part about this there's a lot more less in this clip doesn't recognize that
It's possible for black women to date
There is that like underlying racism that sort of never dealt with
I just I'm just fascinated by The Rake
System right now which is
Black man black woman
Number one
Black man black man black man black man
Not good no number two
There isn't even a
Because the white homosexual has convinced
The black person
Homosexual
Burien from a black woman
This is
And to the black the black neighborhood
Black men that have been homosexuality
Black
Hard time competing against
White homosexual male
American Express card
Dinner parties
What's the financial strength of a wife
This is devastating
Destruction
The black
Family
With his homosexual
That
Homosexuals have come out in the sports arena
We support the president of Uganda
German people
Creations
Thai
Integrity
Universal
Thai if you will
Established in our nation by this
Barack Hussein Obama has powers
Continue
Ford service
Wow
How old is a wild ride
I learned that if I
Where to find out that I'm a homosexual
To get rid of this you can't say that that's dangerous
Yeah
Unfortunately that's a half a lot of paperwork
Man
Discover
But
There's so much in there even if you take out the like
Rank homophobe
There's so much of my
I mean I guess it's still part of the homophobia
These white almost
How can you compete
Where is that
So-so
What I'm understanding like if I'm going to read between the lines
Lucky's accurately describing
Navigation
Which is better
Hey wealthier people are destroying black
Like spiritually there's a piece of that
Complain the way drunk
Furthermore ascribing it
Then woman's fault for not
Like in theater
Which is weird
That angers so
It's funny when you talkin about
Semen in latte
Like that
That's funny
But unfortunately
And this next clip is a mic down clip
It's something
You need to recognize
When you have people like
Reverend James
There's reality to what he preaches
From the pulpit
That is
Unacceptable
It's unacceptable to modern society
It's important to recognize
Listermann
He was a guest on Alex Jones Show
This is something that Alex
Is allowing
Person
To be someone he has on her
He's talking about that time that you just described in the last black women
You know what's going to happen
Keep watching
A group of young men and women
When it come to this
Jesus
3 / 6
That's a catchphrase
Is yells about driving people out of
So
You are literally advocating for murder
Murder
Uganda's president being like that
Yeah but
That
In his church
At the pulpit
Giving these out like sort of elaborate fantasies about
Creepin and gay people's windows after you followed them home
It's slitting their throats in the night
Like that easy
But you can't
I have no words strong enough
To talk about
He should be in prison yet
Man
I don't know
I don't I don't know what the line is in terms of like
Where does hate
Speeds reached
The point where you're yelling fire in a crowded
Yeah like that sort of thing but I think when you're a preacher
And you're at a Pulpit
And you're advocating
Armies of people getting together
To clear the streets of gay people through murder
I think you're on the wrong side of
I think you're on the wrong side of free speech
Fandom
I don't know that's what makes it sounds like
The Labyrinth
Michael Savage's willing to have him on his show
They Advocate positions at ARC
In far-off
From the store.
You know we talked about how Alex Jones says the quiet part loud
Right but he says about a fart flower
That is underlying
Thanks so much
The world
Whether it's a disregard and not caring
I think God should put
People vigilante murder on
There's not that much difference
In terms of functional out
And
I mean babies.
Like
There is one argument to be made about
That or not
I suppose the best coralaire I can pick up for that in
In terms of
The power structure we have now is
Waze with with Trump
Talking about Jamal khashoggi murder
And him just being like
Like
Yeah that's been American foreign policy for the past
60 years
He's the only one who said it
You know
I'm sure that
The lot not of not man a lot of people
Eat it
It's amazing to me
How
Many people who
Can't read
Can convince people who
That what they don't read
It says something that the person
Just wanted to
I don't know I really hard time talking about this
Because that was so f****** ugly
I don't like that at all
If you don't look at
Person that is
Semen
That's who he is
People might be asking
Uno lecture he's been a guest on Alex Jones Show but how much does
Involved
You don't like is this really that related
And I'd like to play you something else he said
I'd no
What do you like to see in the world
The president who recognized
Theocracy
SpongeBob
We will
What's going home
Jesus
Go back to f****** Jerusalem goddamn moron
I'm ready
Since from the pulpit
Alex Jones
You've got another Soldier
Annie says I'm ready just like Alex
And he said
Alex
Hallelujah
Yep
So you should
Recognize
I think
Everybody
At these worlds are
Deeply connected
Just the fact
That he
Reverend Manning doesn't
Support
Doesn't really matter as much as these other things
They clearly had enough overlap that
It's it's such a mess
That's crazy
So
I don't know
I mean what
What is what we got
We've shown that someone bad is bad
I don't know if it's this really interesting Dynamic that I think is
So it exists
Abundantly
In the right-wing and in the biggest communities
You have this
Rising of
You know like Alex is a really talented brought
Castor
And then you scratch a little bit
You see all this oh my God
White supremacist
You have really dangerous
Leading people down a terrible Road
The same way you have Reverend
Really gif
Order in many ways
Ability
Like the speaker
Speech about something like
If you was making a video about lost it
Stefan molyneux one I watched
God I love this
Natural Talent
And then beneath it is
An incredibly dangerous
Manipulative
Monster is human
Who wishes murder upon
Lgbtq
The reality is so much
I guess that's my
I don't know anyway if you guys want us to do more on Reverend Manning although I don't know
Why you would want us to leave
Outside of being able to find 100 more instances of him saying goofy nonsense
A little bit of sour grapes in the sensitive
Like this is a possibility for us to look at
You know we got by over
Mildly
I mean
It is it is weird Everybody that we talked about is a f******
Monster
I don't know how much the only way we can deal with it I don't know how much fertile territory there is
Within
Reprimand
African history
Yeah because at least that lie
The gives an Avenue to go down
Yeah the more concrete bulshit a person says the more you
Maybe we'll be able to pick up something
Like that but in terms of like his
Bigger story it is really just
For whatever
Hate scape
It is such
A visceral thing for him
That it invades
Almost every aspect of
It's over for us to like
Brett
Also has spread that might be something
We can always dig into bread but
I guess the bigger the bigger point is if you want us to cover him
Let us know we might do that
Also if there's other suggestion
You have because I
Against the wall
Terms of like
Who has shows
We could go over
Event
I'm willing to explore Whole Lotta territory
There's there's Lim
I don't want to do too much more
You going to be like
I appreciate it but like they're more like
Hard
Space.
What's fun about Project Camelot is the lies
Something like that sure but
Anyway if you have a suggestion
Please feel free to send us an email with knowledge
Gmail.com
Ring website
I'll try.
Before
Lena Dunham
Has been a guest on the Chris gethard
But she is
Is not committed
As far as I know
Congruence for her to have
There's one guy
Yeah he's
The guy who's
He's a soldier
Hallelujah
That guy
Alexandra Thurston color