Alex
Little bit
Shut up
What's up
I was going to launch into like a Interruption of the world is going crazy
Right
It's because he's
What I told you to shut up but
So I got really self-conscious and forgot to launch into talk about Laura Loomer
Which by the way ever recording this she has already
Laura Loomer
But she got kicked off Twitter
And so she changed herself
To the door of Twitter's headquarters
And the police came at Twitter talking to press charges if you need a golf
It was revealed that she had thrown away her key
Twitter
Look
I don't
Enjoy
Schadenfreude
And I loved it was great because she had a second star of David on her way
Which is not
Laura Laura
Farrakhan
Also because I'm not going to argue with you there
That's not going to get you
Get away if I can't get away with it that neither should he
Anybody else you got
Long time thanks
For helping us out
Everything's crazy right now I have no idea where any of this is going
You're going to leave nowhere
But I mean in terms of
Corsi's nonsense
Michael Cohen
Of course he's going to press criminal charges
Blow up so crazy
State of Florida
I don't know what's going on with the world
Outlook
Tough times
Because
Sort of self-conscious about our Wednesday episode
Some of the clips would have been dyed for people
And II
WhatsApp
Pretty little later in the episode little later in the episode
The response has been mostly positive and I put a pole in our Facebook
Go home and tell your mother about would like us to talk about
Do that I don't know we'll see
The people is suspect Marcus he's dead
In the darkness of our Nyan of The Obama Deception
I don't know I am I'm going to sit with those thoughts and see where we go in
People didn't think like
Anyway we were
Platform
Homophobia
I was concerned about like what are our response
Possibilities here
I realize that I didn't think enough about that before we recorded the episode
And I'm glad that people didn't
Didn't seem to think that we were on the wrong side
Hypochondriac
Difficult time with this week is I've been listening to Alex in the present
Do a better job of covering guys bulshit
Present his show sucks
Still on that tip hop on Thursday for a Friday release
I listen to Sunday
All all I got all I could hear was him talking about these immigrant
Is coming over the Border
He implied that he straight-up said that that picture of the woman for children away for
A gas canisters
Jerome corsi
Has the Baton
Monday
Bulshit
Tuesday
Sting bulshit
Am I going to do what we got to do a current-day episode on Friday we got to let people know what Alex's up to
So thankfully Wednesday
Pharrell
And at this point
It's clear the course is going off all script
Talk about this
There's so much going on
Why Wednesday
That I'm like Alex's got to get off his
Dumb immigrants at the border risk
He's got he's got to bring something to the table
And he did on Wednesday
One of
The weirder shows I've ever heard
We'll be going over Wednesday November 28th
2018 today
I don't say this
Coordinates on Thursday
Thursday's episode
So is Courtney still on the payroll
If he is they would never say that
Alex
It's really weird of this episode so for that
Monday is that we may have to do another present
On Thursday and Friday Alex
Be losing his goddamn bike
Based on the news
It's broken here on Thursday evening about the situation
How's it going to be
Supercuts
Wednesday
He starts his show
I forgot about that
Alright
Awful awful in my phone
I don't have
Alright I don't have notes in front of me with all the like it
The Beats to hit me intro I'm in here
Almost forgot but I would never
People I appreciate that very much
First of all I never forget
Coyote
Thank you old man coyote coyote
Michael
You are now a policy
Also
I'm a policy wonk finally I'd like to play
Someone who has elevated level
Appreciate it oh so very much
I'd like to say
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Someone someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean black
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you very much sorry
Subway I don't want to say this
Fights
Historic
Haha you might want to keep an eye on
I'm saying is that there are many situations
Dan and
I'm just saying
And this case is
If you'd like to join our website
Click that button that says support the show we would appreciate
Please do now
Wednesday
November 28th
To the doldrums
Sunday Monday Tuesday and I wasn't
To come with much of anything
And I knew I was
In for it
The most important broadcast we've ever done
Ever
And then the last five or six years and every six months or so in the last ice age
Amazing
There are human clones inside mothers
I know what story is basing his bulshit are you
Which Wich
The world's scientific Community has come out
7 people don't know
This is about this talk about is about
Early this week claimed
DC with Alex
There is no independent confirmation
At this point there's no proof that this dude what he claimed to have done but even if he had
His actions have been roundly denounced by majority of the scientific
Community nearly Universal in the reaction that is as irresponsible and premature based on web science
You bet that still.
Right right
And the day after the story broke China order the
They were doing and they're launching investigation
This dude
Would you likely won't
Dwell
Frankly recent Chinese investigations have not ended well for a lot of
Movie
Beastars
Anyone
Bring a story backup
Rummikub
Well this is going to be a good show
If he's leaving with that this is the most important show I have
Ever done
This
I'm listening buddy
Maybe that story isn't what he's talking
The gene-editing
Any stories about cloning
And what the story that came out of China recently about cloning
And
It came out the day that Alex is doing this show so I'm thinking maybe maybe later these two stories
World's first
Cloned bunk
Mark's first birthday
They're closed because it would make sense that people don't freak out to
Too much about life
The Clone dogs someone's dog dies
It gets hit by car though sometimes clone them
Google it they do that a lot
Really
Clone dog
You know what
They're not the same they're very similar very similar but they're not the same I went the same.
That happens
Pepsi
But a monkey
Close to human in there it's right there
That very article about this loan monkeys first birthday
Ends with this quote
Authorities in China has no plans to allow human cloning following the success
I think this is a weird place for me to
Come out again
I think I'm kind of fine with it
I don't know
Like unless this scientist was like
Secretly doing
I mean if she was almost there are some indication
Somebody didn't give full disclosure
Do too much looking into
He was working with
We're just told that it was like an HIV vaccine
Possible
He wasn't giving
Although
Audi
Find a place with
I do what I want
Somebody's going to show up dr.
August
This story is a complicated
Confusing Place rally
Text to start the show
Alaska
His gut gets it
Cuz it got you the entire subconscious
No no
Don't do that
Intuition
Understanding
I got
Never wrong
Wow
Call Binky
I have the Second Sight
Alexei that you psychic in the past
Usually when he's drunk night recording
This is minutes into his show
Directions to the gut and also Alex is late
It doesn't stop there
Just to give our listeners Kant
When old white men
Okay well then I retract
The time of people say they're psychic
They're up to something
About to take a
Behavior
What about Miss Cleo
She was up to something
Real psychics read powerful countries
This is what we're dealing with here
That's what we're dealing with a bunch of
The biggest problem
Trump's the psychic also
All psychic
World leaders origin
Define psychic
Like true
If you were actually psychic
It follows you would probably try and use that to accumulate power
The initial premise
I believe that people would
Gravitate towards positions of power
But
First
Definition of psychic powers
Total rehab
Clairvoyance is low-tier psychic
You talking about like putting socks
Are we talk about by koe Wetzel
Level of psychic are we dealing with
That's different
That's a different classification
I want to know what are we are we at
Psionic powers in
What level of fortune tellers
Are actually generals on the battlefield
That other generals are Altos
Your psychic powers
Sitting at like the World Chess championships two dudes
Having a psychic battle
Real the real question comes out do it for me
Stuff like that
Parkman season 1 of Heroes
Psychic
I'm so in the next clip Alex gets to something
Is going on in the world
And now the Chinese Tchaikovsky
They posted the rest check
Yep
Russia is a distraction
Just trying to stop for been overthrown
Oh yeah
And a Christian again
That doesn't sound right because in the seed of that
Is the seed of the future
Future of Christendom on a planetary scale
Cuz we don't do that
Michonne that first
Flash
Surprise
Yuck
Chris
Now that's great
But were they defensive whenever they took those three Ukrainian ship
I think he's saying now is a like
In this immediate moment
These Ukrainian ships just went into Russian Port until they were coming
Aboard these ships and kidnapping sailors
Quite right
So while I definitely try
Ha
Interesting
I don't want to unpack this too much
Just because if it doesn't
Tractor too heavily into the narrative
The show but it's just
Another example of Alex
Creating this sort of
Russian propaganda eccentric
Broadcast
In the present
Just kind of very blunt
We say that
Christianity is equal to
Is Russian
Christianity
If you're Christian just give it up your fashion
Where at where at
Call
Beginning of the show that
Is the most
Important
He's at work.
It's not because he comes out of the psychic and out
As well as all these generals
Money
Front-loaded
Absolutely
It's not that
There's clowns in
Here is
The big news of
The day
It's this big news
Nope
I tried
This is the big news
Here's the deal
Giveaway the structure of this episode before we even get to it because
Alex is so bad at his job
Play is the big
After this Alex is going to start
Teasing the big news
Without
Sort of recognizing that he said at the beginning
So here is Alex talking about
That it is
Is Varsity story of the day
I wish you well then
Proceed to
Wards.com
Infowars.com
Drudgereport.com
Russian collusion
When did the trial for treason begin warning to opponents
I got the hell out
She's a dictator in Chile
That means jury of your peers
Here's the thing
What Alex is responding to is that V
Trump train Trump
Meme Twitter account
Is exactly what Alex
Decide now that Russian collusion is a proven lie when
When do the trials for
Starts as a picture of all of Alex's big bad guys
Behind Bars
Ratcliff bars
That's what Alex results
Tamim and Alex is like this is the biggest news in the world
All my all my enemies are going to prison
So
The
Sitting president
The United States
Oh boy
Is it not like
Before
Is the actual president of the United States
I had to go to Trump's Twitter to confirm myself
But that actually happen
I want
To call an end to America I say to you all of my fellow American
Let's just dissolve it
Everybody has their own country now
We're all Sovereign
Shake this s*** like an Etch-a-Sketch Hellyeah
Makes clear that what he's talking about is just a retweeted me
He's saying the Trump is saying that
You going to do these things
Generous interpretation of
Cuz Trump doesn't have that thing the journalist
Stone equal endorsement
Different coming out
Except for the fact that he's been yelling lock her up at all of his rallies
Came out that he had to be convinced
Heavily not to try and lock
Her up right right
Can you
I hate that we live in this world
I do
I hate that we live in this world but damn
Dad just for one second
Just for one second
Imagine
If Obama had retweeted a meme that had like
Michaela
It would be the number one story across the world
And I couldn't avoid it
Selena Gomez was a mustard
This is visible story
The bread-and-butter for the day
Because as Bisquick goes I just paused
If you going to keep talking
Any brings up
Very familiar
Dodge
To reinforce
Because these individual
Congress
Uranium one
Still not true they legally sure about his every movement when he was
You really don't understand what the legal means
The CIA
She was being surveilled
Right after Obama got in office
Donald John Trump
His personal phone line
His personal apartment at Mar-A-Lago at I have that number
Changed it
I'm sitting there looking at the database that's that's Trump
If anybody out there haven't listened
M2r episode called the two hours talking about
Exactly where this
Information came from it's one of the biggest Crocs
Some s*** ever
Dennis Montgomery is a huge con man
Who is trying
Toufayan
We could generously call opposition research on a
His narrative in order to smear him because the judge was pretty
Covert investigation of Joe Arpaio in Maricopa County
The database of
People thought is at something that came out of that investigation
Has been repackaged
Add some sort of database
The people who work
Being spied on
Yes absolutely
Spoiler for that
Is Alex's
Is the crock of s***
Awesome
It's so awesome to know things
Running for
I would have one
Policy
And that would be
Maricopa County is officially kicked out of the United
Build a wall
You can remain Maricopa County itself is dissolved
Are you again
Where assume I will be allowed to
Keeps coming up Maricopa County
Keeps coming up in terms of like everything with a lot of stuff
Seems to trace back to malfeasance
Maricopa County
Alex
Not talk
About how lot of his friends
Increasingly hot water
For themselves
Seems to be
Percy had no reason to go on television the other night
So Alex
Do not talk about it
But this is one of the more
Choosing things I've ever heard
She is a heavy hitter
State Department by Dragon season
Sure
Okay
I'm not going to lie about anything but these emails to each other
With both of these guys they're both lying to me
Alex I have a very simple explanation for this
Rodger Stone
That is what was going on there buddy I haven't even simpler!
You are
You're lying to yourself
According to
You don't talk about it all I have to do is like go from there
Would you seems to be expressing is the idea that
Jerome corsi told him
Rodger and Jerome corsi
Come up with those emails to each other about talking to
To go talk to us on
The cover story
I don't fucken understand I have no idea
This is nonsense
As we can see from their actions
After this
This kind of
Behaviors come to light
There
Tactical Geniuses dance
These people are brilliant realizing
Already captured and there's no realize I couldn't
If you know anything about Maricopa County you know that they were under surveillance illegally Dan
Alexander said that
Narrative
Mandrill course he was the go-between
Between Alex Jones and Mike zullo and
So he was orchestrated Larry klayman
Who's bringing Ebola into the country
Attack on white people
I don't I think if they know that they are the only people they can trust cuz they're all dirty as hell
How is it that Alex can pretend
I can't believe course he would lie to me like what
Courtney's entire career is it
Coronavirus
Taco.
Feels persecuted
He gets into
And because we're telling the truth
Wow
Common sense
You're banned everywhere
Okay
Don't coming after your family that's there that's a dispute with your ex-wife I think you should probably have enough tax not to blame the glow
Globalist
Your own relationship
Issues
And beyond that
I don't know if Martin Luther King ever gave it features
Man
There should be some sort of
There should be some sort of live like
The GOP get my name out your mouth lock
Moratorium
My feelings on the matter is like I have zero interest in
By position
Is very clear
My position
Care care about whether or not they actually believe that
It's a troll movie
Alex is engaging in so
Some sort of weird
Trolling
While evoking the name of Martin Luther King and saying that he tells the truth all the time
Just about
F*** it is these assholes do any
Exactly
The reason
In addition to this
This weird Donald Trump
I'm sitting here in a minute
The other
Secondary narratives italics
Really it's stuck in his craw
Is the idea that
She does a really bad job
Differentiating
Between people who are trans and people who crossed
You could have just put a. After he does a really bad job
But
Conflates the two
Very
Confusing
Not confusing I'm not super confused but to the point where when you listen to
He's blurring that line intentional
People with crossdressers
Distinction at all so it makes it a little
Difficult
Unpack
I'll try and do my best
There's a story that he's trying to
To cover and it's
About how
His version of it is trans people are just trying to prove your children
The story is that he found a clip of a crossdresser
Who I was engaging in this
Gramps
Where they go to libraries
Crossdresser storytime
Where kids
Joanday
Crossdressers aren't weird people
That's
Exposed to a larger
So Alex Alex
Pearl the story
Into trans people are grooming your kids for sexual assault
And that sort of thing
Where the quote
We are ruining your kids were taking your kids from you and we've got to do this
Hear weird
Them
Ugly
In question
Is someone
I can't remember the first
They like city council meeting
And Derek
How much abuse they've gotten
After it was announced
They would be performing
Oregon
The kids at Vista
The word grooming
What is very clear about the idea of
You're a front of you
People behind me staring daggers
Write that all hate
We're trying to
To do is groom the Next Generation
To not be so Impala
Very clearly the message
It isn't those guys and if you watch the video
Which I did
You see when the person says
These people all hate me
You see a couple people not
Behind
It is very clear that this audience
It's a very brave Act
City council meeting and say
We are people
Where get out this is this
There's nothing about
The idea that maybe I do
Or something like that
Can't talk to kids
I'm an adult
I know how to
Do you have filter
I believe exactly how to filter what
Protective
It's just it's mad
It's exactly what you'd expect
But just
Because the word
Grooming
Used he latched onto it and turned it into it they all wanted
Fuckyour kit
You know what this whole thing has
Spiraled out of the real complaint that most of these people have which
She's just like
I don't want to have to think about
Being a sensitive
The real issues like
I don't want to have to think about calling them do whatever I like
Like that is a five-minute delay
Like this is people angry about the train being late and then being like
I don't want
Did like
The discomfort of
Of someone pops
Correcting a politeness mistakes that I've made
Yeah it's very sad snowflakey on the level of Laura Loomer Trucking handcuffing her
Herself to a door
Pedophiles
The last one
The next one
Real
Trash
Cops work to put that scene in prison prosecutors work
Dakota brake
Gave serial sex abuser deal of a lifetime which is true
Bill Clinton on the airplane
So
One of those
The Miami Herald story about heroin
Underage girls
Star on it and end up getting basically Scott
Yeah what are the major takeaways from the story however is it Alexander Acosta
Was instrumental in negotiating a lenient sentence
When the police and detectives are put together a case that
The reason that's important
Is there a casa is Trump's Secretary of Labor which gives an oversight over International child labor laws
Human trafficking
The Herald article points out that he's even been floated
Is a possible replacement
Processions
As Attorney General
Although who knows how realistic that is someone's name being floated doesn't mean they're going to be
This is an element
Perhaps under-reported in the past
Epstein's connection to both Bill Clinton and Donald Trump has not been a secret
Both men Associated Epstein regularly in the past
Palm Beach
Is Rio closed
Tomorrow login
Now that's for Mueller he has no connection
Past the fact that he was ahead of the FBI at the time when Epstein was being investigated
This could indicate some involvement on Mueller Park not pursuing the case in a manner that
The fact Meriden
That's definitely a possibility
But that hasn't been
Proven
As is always the case in the term
In terms of things like that
Alex is just making
King s*** up
The most I could find
Was a heavily redacted FBI memo
They came out that said that he had provided some information
To the FBI
And that that
That he was cooperating in
In Florida that doesn't mean that he's a longtime informal
That doesn't mean that he was even in it
Informants go so far as to say that Mueller was videotaping
People with underage girls
In order to Blackmail them stuff like that
It seems like Jacob Wohl style libel
That's very unfair
CIA
To take comment
About trying to make a
The Next Generation War
People who are different than them
It turned that into
Drooping of children
And then here to be
Biso
Serta wishy-washy about the real facts
Story about a guy who was
Oakmont
Yeah this is a story about billionaires having a completely different legal system it's not a story about
Jori business and everybody should accept that this is wrong in every possible absolute
Start furiously plucking
If you could
Straight to Bill Clinton was involved in
This further than just being associated with him
Google Earth
8 years in prison for voting
But she didn't even know she could
Wild
Real thing
It's not a trivial matter
But this guy
Acosta Alexander Acosta
Is now the labor secretary
That's almost
You know like a wonder One Kinect because of this truck
Along the lines of life
Doing this favor for a billionaire
You get s***
For us to say that would be conspiratorial that boy does it feel that way
Don't worry about anybody else who was on Epstein's plane
Little rule quotes
He likes them young and he's a fun guy to hang out with you sure likes his women
Like
It would be one thing
If you just sort of tried to do the deflection
Of the story like that but he always does
You know whatever
But to then also have like a third of your show be about heaven
This drag queen wants to groom your kids and stuff like that
It's just distasteful like
It it real
I know I know
Alex Jones entire show is this
So
Emotionally manipulative
Because that is such a
People are
Trigger device and rightfully so it's
Spotify
Children absolute
And that sort of thing so
I just
I can get your lizard brain
From using any override pedophilia is almost always
Is in some way in like just like
They're always coming for your women or your kids
We'll get to that in a little bit
I don't want to I don't want to eat my
Is so
F****** Valero
By the way
Dollars
2000 Dodge Recreation
People
Santa memes.
Facebook Twitter
Other variants of now that Russia collusion is a proven lie when do the trial for treason begin
So now you just want to go for free to make new versions of the minivan
This is
Wild is a freelance writer
Like I thought I thought for sure you would
Forget about the NPC meme saying like that like about that
The contest
Going to be gone
It was so hilarious
I did dear it I was turn it off turn it off
The 4th hour when someone else
About to take over
Is Billy Idol want to listen
Cumia
F****** do you does the fourth hour every other Thursday for a while
The last time I checked
Tighter shot
Going for sure whether or not the picture has been
Neither confirmed nor denied generally turn it off
Amen
In this picture and its story
But there's even more news stories
Does closing a bunch
The plant
Which is in direct
So here is Alex
Deflecting on that
Moving to China with Five Points
Have we bailed them out 10 years ago
Public
Hate this country
There's one thing I know about Corporation
Turn it
Without You Usher
The biggest
Free shipping storewide everything is fine
50 to 70% off
And Alex
Constantly saying we need to get everything out of the warehouse
Successful business Warehouse
You are going to refill that warehouse
You know car dealership it's got a fire sale
Have you ever been by mattress store damn everything's got to go but that's because they're so successful
It's a sandwich shop
Exactly
Yogurt shops
Kind of giving away a little bit of what's going on
Revealing
So
Like I said
The big news is
I really don't like that.
But as the second hour of the show start Alec doesn't realize he's already told the whole story
Oh no
Ultra Maxima 2 weeks before it comes out
I'm going to throw down the gauntlet
I'm going to
I'm going to go ahead and
Drop some major Intel Anya
I've got from multiple sources on YouTube
The first part of John bounds report
All I want
Christmas is Hillary in prison
Great
Sure
Moving on
Weird that he be like
Give you two weeks news ahead of time
How can I come out into
The content of the meme Alex is what's going
Trump is going okay
I'm saying it's go time on these people
As opposed to just being a kid
Continuation of his
Hey guys
It's all just
You get the cut
Yeah it's like
Just momentarily about why
He does this like I'm going to do this big reveal
Gemini remembered
The Clock Works in certain way where
The first six minutes of each hour goes to the local station
So it's not even broadcast
He's just burying John Downs reports here doesn't even play online po the local stations get to do like news and
Weather at the top of the hour and then get back to his employees
Love it
Also I don't think you can say
That's something titled all I want
For Christmas... Is a report
No it's Hillary
Hard-hitting report
Hard-hitting and I really don't think so I bet it's not written well either
Air Force One or whatever they were like
Have you have you read this recent report all I want for Christmas is you know what
We don't let this one go back from the grave
Waffle crisp earned on the knee of Woodward
8-bit all good reporting begins with
Claire Road
Muckraking book about the things that John bounty
Hillary Clinton not in prison
Every night
Every night Edward armorel Woodside off with
Very much and all I want for Christmas
This for you to have a good day
For an hour but Alex
Taquizas big news more
Sources information a few weeks ago
Statements made
And then the president's tweet this morning
Crystallize it all
And I was thinking about
Breaking down
What's about to happen and then I got another message from Individual whatever has amazing forces
Paraphernalia
Gunrunner
That there were other scooters
Over here later they still won't give out an official
Okay
It is important to note that Alex not knowing that the police put out a report on the Las Vegas shooting is not the same thing
Is them not putting out
A report on the shooting
Las Vegas Police Department put out a 187 page final report someone up their investigation
Bravo
Investigation
First attack the report specifically says quote
Emergency only Radio Calls
Coming out in reference to active shooters
8 different properties along the Las Vegas Strip
Fires breaking out at certain properties actual shooters that were inside the Las Vegas Village at the time of the shooting
Early reporting for national news outlets reported that ice
Who claimed responsibility for the shooting
The investigation revealed
None of this information was accurate
Alex is operating off of rumor and hearsay that got misreported in the chaos that unfolded after
First attack began
It's one of the difficulties of our more connected world that bad actors
Or well-intentioned people with erroneous information accurate
Messages out
And then the meteor can be called Liars
Just because they don't
Keep reporting those messages after they've been shown
Would be false
The report goes on to say quote
Patrick acted alone
Despite earlier reports of multiple Shooters in different locations
Exist to substantiate any of those reports
Thousands of hours of digital media
Review
And after all the interviews were conducted no evidence
Exist that indicate Patek
Conspired with or acted in
Inclusion with anyone else
This includes video surveillance recovered DNA analysis of cell phones
The computers belonging
There's no evidence of radicalization
Exported followed group or any domestic or
Foreign terrorist
Everything Alex is saying is based on
Conspiracy bulshit that came out in the immediate aftermath of the shooting
I think that were Amplified by his own
Steve pieczenik
Infowars contributor Shepard ambellas
And Alex
Bacone College
Exorcism
None of this is real Alex
I told you all this s*** about Las Vegas that I probably still on for today and then
Unreported Medford
It's really crazy that that's what he's using is his
Barometer of credibility
Outlet
That's don't use the
The term amazing sources
Do they just call them sources
Have an amazing
Use other than if it was like Miss Marvel
Using the same sort of strategy that he does about his sales
Talking about amazing sources
You just got
A guy if that
Free shipping on credibility
Also
Shepherd came in was talking about how they were shooting
Helicopters
He also
You made a documentary about
Trails that I really
I've been meaning to watch
UE made it along with
He made it along with Alex Jones employee
Alex Jones employees
Anthony Gucci
Who's no longer in
Images wear name tags
Just give me
Give me some sort of DnD range
Geology
I saw like
Look nice I'm also I'm sorry I got off track I need a
Think about the GM
Plants closing
Because they hated him
America
But it's kind of hard to
Explain why some of the
Plants are closing
Canada in South Korea
No track
America thing
South Korea but America light
According to GM the move is essentially about trying to make the business more flexible
A traditional automobile
Appealing
It really sucks that they're laying off for 1000
Employees but it's not rooted in hatred of America it's rooted in a
Fear that other Auto another Auto
Might be coming
And a desire to get ahead of
Sales of sedans have been flipping pretty seriously for a long time
Ford announcement April they would end production on all sedan by the end of 2018
Apple Uber in Tesla
Working on the Next Generation
Transportation with self-driving cars
Have you
History is coming to the realization that they're not the normal Market forces
Silicon Valley is poised to all but make their product
It's all bulshit
Like it's all terrible
This is awful
People should be
Not being treated like this
But because the show we do it
It's the most important thing
The nothing to do with Trump or Punisher
Sing America or anything like that
It's
GM was opening
Coal mines
So full of s***
What is it going to take
For Trump voters to realize that everything he told them was a
Probably nothing
If your argument against
GM closing
Is is just like
They did it cuz they hate America then that argument never fail
Well that doesn't
I doubt it
I doubt that day is
Jesus
UCare
Dump
You can't fool all the people all the time about
You can fool all the time
Already know what Alex is BigNik
It is already solved
Narrative is the ramifications of
That he's pretending come from source
You already know that
But if you didn't know that this would be
Incredibly frustrating
He comes in and says I'm going to tell you two weeks news ahead of time he's like
John lb report
He comes back starts talking about how big the news is and then starts talking about how he was right about Vega
It's the same game he always plays
Event tickets
You know you just don't appreciate
The way a lot of people.
Alright
Used more
Just want to get it out there
Butt so big
That I really should like wait till tomorrow to tell you
Saint hey here it is and then I guess people incredible information
And then it comes true
In a week
You are wrong all the time.
Gildedguy
He Rambles a bunch more
You're right it is just sort of
Fake news edging
I think he's realizing as
This is not
Not good
But you know but I think a lot of people
Just don't believe it
Warcraft
Bring this big news
If I if I really commit today
Jonah realized
I'm sure that's not his
The news is
This is very important because
I'm not just going to tell you
What's going to come out in the next two weeks
Where does Trump
Go ahead
Present
The dogs are often
Alex
Suicidal
Time so far
Also the idea
Kennel from Hell match I believe was the name of it
What did Michael Vick run years ago
Before that back when it was the WWE app
There is a match between the big circles run by the world
It was a match between the big boss man and this guy named Al Snow
He
Career talks to a phone call head
Joke about oral sex
Game called Head
Musically like
Mannequin doll head
I believe
Mannequin head
Was because
Used to have a dog
A little dog
That he would bring along with
The big boss man
At a hotel room
So you understand
Make cells note
Cattle from helmet
Which
Is the ring
There is a steel cage around it outside of the cage
The dogs
So the idea thrown out of
It's the old idea of a lumberjack match we have a bunch of wrestlers outside the ring you up
They were kind of hoping that what would happen if people buy dogs
Pikachu
The dog
Embarrassing
Things that the WWE
Which is saying something
The reason I bring this up
Is that those are the sort of dogs
Better
Donald Trump
I got you
So are you saying is the news is
Hillary's going to prison lock her up
Taurus
What to respond
You just said that there's going to be false Flags
Which is again
He says all the f***
Sometime none of this is new at all
Here's the other
Frustrate
Okay
So we do lock her up
Vicky's gone that far
They just do this thing where they want this thing
But after after
Dumb
Dumb f*** s*** that you said
Get out of this
Extremist thing is we Deport more people or whatever it is
Too f****** stupid nationalism by
Weather
I'm throwing you to the locker up-dog that'll give a s*** get locked up but it wasn't
What what good does it do if he does them bad
They need to maintain the edge basically of
You you have a lot of
The
You can get a lot of mileage out of wanting
Ruined orgasm
As they say
Alluding to
It's not a pornographic thing
Spend all day
You build up
I have no idea what I'm doing
All this news is
Just nothing
It's just either rehashing of things that have been a theme of Trumps campaign
Just alyx
Projecting thing
Are the cakes
He says this
As he's going up to break
Yeah it's about Robert Mueller
Calling all you criminals get ready scumbags
Alex
The reason all of your friends are in trouble right now
Is because they publicly indicated that they knew about things that were coming out
Before anyone
Should have known
You just did something
You better f****** hoe
If those emails do come out
You better f******
Hope that you know that the Providence
Is clean because
Eclipse Court
I don't know what's going to happen in the future
I don't know if all of her erased emails are going to come out I imagine a lot of them
Or exactly what she says they were like
Planning
Whatever a couple things that are
Suspicious in there too but I do know
That Alex you f***** up
No matter what the case is
You f***** up
Right there
Should not accept
Never understand what the
These guys don't cry
Show me ways that clip right there isn't
Is it nothing
Like if these emails never come out which most likely nothing will happen
Or I guess there is
Dunno I guess there's a world where
The emails do come out and they were
Gmail
OSHA
Alex
That's not good
You're in trouble
No man's sky
I took a shower
Speaking of which years does nexplanon
Election fraud
T-Mobile
We really want
Brazil Germany
International nationalism
So did you get into it
On the show
Alex has a number of times. About how Brazil a nationalist
The guy he's even said
Bolsonaro
Number of
He is so hideous I wouldn't even
Well said referee reference to something he
The first issue that I have italics being into bolsonaro is that you came to power
Where is predecessor Lula was jailed on trumped-up corruption charges
Name Sergio Moro Minister of Justice as soon as bolsonaro be
There's no way that that would
Corruption is enough for anyone to be suspicious but the reality of Fujairah bolsonaro
People who care about you Monroe
Him a real chateau
In 2017 he said of black settlement in Brazil nothing for procreation
You refer to black activists as animals who should quote go back to the zoo
2014 BC because you don't deserve it
The congresswoman Murray
The Del Rosario on the floor of Congress
He later clarified saying he's not a rapist
But wouldn't rape Rosario because she's ugly
His type
Clarify
Is it's very nice of him to
To clarify that he's a month
And activism in Brazil
These are they go to jail
These red Outlaws will be banished from our homeland
It will either be it will be a clean up the likes of which has never been seen in Brazilian
Considering Brazilian picture
He said with Playboy that he would quote
Beyond capable of loving the homosexual son
I would prefer my son to die in an accident that show up with a mustachioed man
Your criticism
T.i.
This criticism of the military dictatorship that ruled Brazil from 19
64 to 1985 was to torture but not kill
He later made it very blunt saying I'm pro-torture in the people are too
You won't change
Nothing absolutely nothing
Unfortunately you'll only change things by having a civil war during the military regime
Killing 30000
Starting with former president Fernando henrique
Cardoso
Killing
If a few innocent people died that's alright
Bolsonaro
Crackdown on his political
The guys of purging left
From the country
There were numerous reports of government officials showing up at universities
Confiscated
Deem to be left
Call according to Leah's donator
PhD student to teacher
Linguistics
Professor
There's among the taboo subject is anything related to any quality of the factors
The closet
Because that could be sooner
To capitalism
And misrepresented as supporting so-called Marxist ideology
We live in an era of a Witch Hunt
So
Anybody
Brazilian politics
It's in the past 5 years
One of the more like
I guess
Tragic
Pinkberry
If you're if you're watching the end of a democracy
That's what you ate like if we're in the end of a democracy right now
We saw the end of a democracy happen
In five years
Brazil
Come on
Of course we're going to support the
What about
Come on
Come on billionaire slightly more money
Yeah I mean it's such a mess
It's so on it
Sure I understand the idea of misogynist homophobe race it
I understand that Alex's
Position because he is a misogynist
I understand that from him but I can't understand the idea of
Alex
If you knew the sort of things
He's doing
Sergio Moro them
Minister of Justice
The idea of cracking down on these universities
Hey take they can't teach a
Like I don't understand why Alex would be okay with that
It indicates a lack of
Any
Or
He is totally fine
Fascism is longer
Yeah I would go with the second one
I think that we're seeing we actually have him legally
Legal fashion
Hey we're getting a little bit too sweetheart
And this is one of the other reasons why I thought it would be
Sitting for us to cover this episode because
Disgusting
Of course she's worth one other great folks like
More Southern and others at the rebel
Lansing right now
Thanks for such got fired
I didn't listen to it
Realized
You'll hear it
She talked a little bit more
Sickly sounds like
She's doing the name Cole
With crazy how much the verbal pattern
Yeah are very similar
Who's running for
It's really interesting there was an article in the
Cut that came out recently
Play that was written
By someone that she went
Figure out how the person that she knew in high school could
Be the person
Exist
It was actually really
Article I recommend
Cuz it talks about hell
She went from being the
Was really friendly outgoing
Magnanimous
Weed smoking
Helping younger
People
People over in dance
Answer questions about relationships
Alcohol and things like that
In her senior year she was in a production of The Laramie Project
At a candlelight vigil for Matthew Shepard
This white nationalist
Neo-Nazi
See who shows up on shows like
Like Red Ice
Recites
The 14 words that's
Not good
How how does
Bridge that
It's really interesting
It's more than that I can really get into
In the next flip
And Alex have a little bit of talk about
Weather position
Graphics
That's a problem demographically there's going to be around
Boy
Send a text clip they talk about that
Feathers
Shadowboxer islamophobic nonsense
But at the end of this Cliff Alex
About Muslims
Surprise
I wouldn't have thought that this would be something
Concerned with
I am I am
Islamic sexual mutilation by having a genitals cut off
Tobit of building
I am phobic
Doesn't sound right
What
Weird
That was a barrage of things
No but at the end of people's he's like a real strange thing to put on my
He's like that inhaler weight today they don't smell
And they mutilate generals
That genitals
It's the way they make fun
That's what I really despise
I couldn't make heads
But I think
It goes Alex is like
For against in this
I mean I guess he's against people who are Islamic
Like he's against them because
Because they push gay people off buildings or is he Muslim
Because he
Thinks that they're all that
Okay
Recognizing that there is a
Acrostic
Muslims as there is of all people that are
Dick
There isn't there is just a percentage
Duvall group
That are
Send
He just decides in this case because
It's the group that he and his boys
Do the other
Marginalize the most
That they are all
Complete
God I hate him but he's mad.
Text Claire
I mean this is literally the invasion of
Third world
Let the horse
We were doing great and then we just
The flat
The plaque
It's on
G3 Lansing
She got fired
Because you went
Bitlife
Statue of Liberty
Bring me your rich
You're really a flute
To do
People who have jobs
Adjust
Can Alex they're just going to sit around and talk about
Islam
And how much they don't want
Those people
That's not all they talk about Alex brings
Back up that clip he has a
The crossdresser
Addressing
City council meeting
Incredibly Horeb
I hate you I hate to interrupt this time
Very conscious that I am doing that there is
Just one thing that I want to say
About how stupid
Which is
How is it
That you don't
Realize
That if you ate even in their perfect world of like
We never bring in third world people
You're only bringing in the well
They're only getting wealthy
All that's going to
Is your removing the serfs
And you're going to become the sir
Like even in their own world of like if you brought
Like Upper Crust
Of all other countries than the middle-class Yearwood
Exceedingly poor
If you really want to wait National
You should be as many people as possible to work
Idiot
No apologize for scaring you off
Emotional sense to the people that they're targeting
Is the issue
Stupid like I said they get back to
2BR the crossdresser
Narrative that Alex has turned into
Ultram
People are really
How to groom your children
Sexual deviant
I'm sorry to say
Stephen Colbert
Is body Abuelita
So that's the way they reproduce
Keep on going
Show this lady saw
Text Cliff
That was right there
That this is the night
Before
Faith Goldy
He's getting married
Congratulations
Alex
Sing about her too
To be husband
Beyonce
Goldie is in Fuego
Is about to get married to her
A grown great Patriot
She's a great picture
Where
To whom
Fiance
Not a whole lot is known about
Other than
Before we go any further
She's a Nazi
Beyonder
European National
Any association with fashion
From what I can tell
Really hard to nail down he doesn't have a ton of
Stuff about
Publicly available
The only other thing that I can
Can stay for sure about Joseph
Is that he was thrown out of Royal Saint George private
It's cool for what principle how Hannaford called quote
Anti-Semitic
The incident question was an internet mess
Message board that was started it became a hotbed for
For bigotry
Specifically
Disapproval with the messages
Someone replied
I quote
You you little f*****
Faget who are you
Nobody knows you
You're probably some f****** Jew doesn't deserve to exist
He thrown into an oven with the rest of
F****** k***
Get off this site nobody wants you here
F****** cheap
Peace a motherfuking
Next time you decide to send something put some thought into it alright your little f******
Don't go off about
Brand of b*******
Okay you f****** hook-nosed parasite
That's all I have to say for the moment
It turns out that the person who disapproved of the hatred
Female students
Printed off the mess
Messages from the board report
Mr Hannaford
Joseph with 13 students kicked out of school for this
Which doesn't necessarily mean that you wrote
The above message
But definitely means that he was writing similar things
Given that for additional
Students were suspended for shorter-term
For being bystander
Numbers on the message board
He was definitely deeply involved in
Like the one
That was reported
What are the chief concern to Educators had with the fact
The language that was being used
Very inaccurate
Like holdovers
1930s
Anti-semitism
15 year olds
The conclusion they came to was that there was very likely some kind of radicalization happen
50 students have been the target of
Which they then became the distributor
People who do face in high school as well as classmates
The Joseph said that they believed that his influence
And how he came into her life around the time that her mother was suffering with stage 4 breast
Lifespace down the hateful path
Betsy's on today
Call Chip
There seems almost
Clear sound at your weakest moments
Most suggestible and
People who knew her have indicated that they believe that what happened
Was
She went from being
Really outgoing
Nice
Very sociable
Person
High School to achieve
Is it around this time track
Distracted her life where her mom was
Yep for that she was very weak
Vulnerable
If you happen to meet this guy who got thrown
Supposed
Systematic s*** on a mess
Sports
And she started to be able
Take advantage of her
That goes on to
So it's very unfortunate story just because it's unfortunate doesn't
She's not
Complicit
Certainly
The monster
If you want to
Deal for her now because
If there's anything I know about
These exact
Sooner or later she's going to be a
That's the end of this
But
It's true
It's wild fish Wild
He talks to and doesn't recognize the
They're really about
Faith if you're listening to this get out
Get out
Get out of my
And they open up open up a bike Sell Shop nationalist
In the Trump vanhoose
Successful
Someone who is very
Clearly indicated neo-Nazi
Reposition
An affiliation
I have her on and says that her husband is a great Patriot
Who's not even American
Only as a patriot
Is your version of patriotism is
Protecting whiteness
The only
It's like answers how much more can you make there's no other way you can have an
Nationalist movement
The globalist
Calling people
Patriots
If it's not uniting in some sense of white Nation
He's a patriot or Germany or Austria
Going to be.
The nation of white
Exactly
Awful
LA and San Francisco in London
All the mentally ill
Anderson Cooper at statue
These are literally brainwash program
Homebase mind-control individual
I was waiting for him to get to the world of MK Ultra
Conspiracy theory
Didn't realize he was that beat
Do that
That's fun
Detox about how Anderson Cooper is
It's just a little weird homophobia that he has
This Intuit Center
You think about macron
Like mainstream news
I say what you want about macron
Who is politics
But it's pretty f****** stupid to say that its mainstream news that he was a Rothschild sex life
I feel like if I feel like I would have Italy
L.
Once what else is trying to do the conflate misrepresent two aspects of macrons life
Most likely because he's a pro
You kind of guy
Eddie beat Alex's precious fascist Marine Le Pen
Now admittedly their relationship
Definitely raises eyebrows
And I'm not necessarily
Student goes on to become an adult then they get married
My personal take on it doesn't really matter though
According to all sources their relationship could not have started before he was sick
16 + 8
You can set in France
So there's no law
I'm not going to I'm not going to defend it but
The use over the age of
Consent in French whatever you're trying to do here isn't going to work
Macron wasn't a sex
What is unconventional relationship
Conspiracy World speculate that his wife was
Some kind of a hand
That's
So those those rumors fly around
Strength
A complete mess misrepresentation of macrons pre-presidential career
From 2008-2012 macron worth
Does an investment banker at the Rothschild
Question whether or not they wanted a president
It had that close
The connection
Understandable
Noemi Weston that deserves to be brought up
In retrospect
It also led to
Not so sensible people like Republican candidate Francois character
Stylized with a hook nose
Particularly
Are you saying that they're fine with
F******
The Russians
I can't imagine any sort of founding
Suggest that they would be fine with that
Any of these accusations
Rothschild Bank
Because
The Rothschild Bank was nationalized by Francois M on government 1981
So the Rothschilds
Basin National
Have day-to-day control over it
To Guida Rothschild wondering if his 40
Years of Relentless labor had been all for nothing
Then he left the country
I kind of thought
I kind of thought now it's his conception all these Global is the Rothschild
But he was Francois
High-level globalist
Working Direct
Play against the rich
It is not something you would do to your boss
It's in the best interest of the Rothschilds
To not have a bag
That's how they make money
Right now
This is all nonsense I just like the idea that acts like the mainstream news that he was a child
Sex slave
Like what the f*** are you even talking
A bit of a
I think that would be
No isn't it inspirational for this guy
Who was
Even even though
Metaphorically
What's important
Feels right
It's a rag
To riches story
So Jordan
9 whenever we hear country
Play music we know that it's
Going to be some fun
In 2018
Unfortunately
Country music
This song is a song
If you leave me
I will miss you
I won't try to get you back
Let It Go
I got ocean front property
Posturing his strength
Explain that because we start
In the middle of
You know
Energy 4406
This news is so huge
Oceanfront of Maine
And if you believe that property
Real quick
Multiple times
You said what the news
Alright
He still thinks he's teasing
Justice
It's fascinating
President-trump
Did the day
Once again retweet and then
What to get
Here you are
What's something is so big
I don't feel Worthy
Perfectly as I can
But I've got
Just
New show important
Show Danger
What
Just like don't know what to do
You going to a field
Normal situation
He said nothing
Infinite amount of time
That was like
He's talking about what he's experiencing in the moment you like
I meant very unprepared
All the sudden
Alright now
I think we should have played that Queen song instead of this b*******
2009 episodes
He says the quick
Stop it
Cut it out
In this next clip
Something else
Well
He's not
But
We see him in one way
And that is a liar
Some people see him
I don't think that's healthy sources to know you can
Chambray
Then I have the force
Just like you are
Panopticon
Pantheon sources
Infowars is dreaded
Possibility
Councils of government
And Congress in foreign governments
I'm seen as like an oracle
Really
I basically don't lie
Record
Knowing things other people don't know
Really
It was just a minute come up with a just stalled of the roadmap
Typography or coming in honest
You just saying words there at the end
That's just with Russia
He was on his show
It's not foreign governments believe that someone is f****** with you Alex
Wow all the time
Blunt object
Oracle
I'm at work already.
Who's probably thinks he's sad that I'm like right whatever
Delfi Jones
You're a f****** Oracle alyx reveal
Something about Trump that
It worries me
Thought about that
Those few times
It's rare that I feel a little bit concerned about
But if
I'm a little worried
Trump
7 years of age
Titan
Text Audra
And people are bugging him he doesn't sleep some nights
He is a
Maniac
You should
Appreciate something
No
There's no way he doesn't
So we should be president
Because
Our champion
I would recommend everybody out there if you're interested Google studies about sleep deprivation in the elderly
This is very serious
Like if Trump isn't sleeping too
Date to week like that could lead to
Two very serious problems
Pictures of cognition memory loss
There's so many like that would explain a lot if he's not sleeping two nights a week
Q70 f****** years old he needs to sleep
No I do need sleep more as you get older
I don't work even though president who does the things I agree with to do that
I don't want any president
Sleep deprived
Who made me drinks too much.
This is true and I know you listen
Baby
Go to bed
Just go to bed
Not sleep two nights a week you're not doing anything
Garbage the thing that your garbage at
What is the Trump retweeted this
Please that it's an indication
But he's not a dictator because the meme includes the word trial
So that means that everybody says that he's a dictator
Stupid because their trials
So if
Actually nevermind
I'm sorry I interrupted you again like the other part of his big news is
In order to
Make sure that Trump
Not able to do this
There will be false
That's the only thing I needed to clarify because that's also part of his news and we can play
Volkswagen coming because the globalist
Afraid
Not new
Alex says
Everyday
The only thing that's different is that Trump retweeted to me
That's the only thing
Trump's going to lock up all of my enemies and in order to make sure that he's not able to do
Nothing is different
Man after you told me that
All I can think of is
How much I want to walk around
And deal with
Your field
So we can go find a fee
Field in Chicago Lakefront
Some creeps hanging out there this afternoon
Centra
So
I just wish they would think
One Step Beyond what it is
Today
So then what's going to happen
A simultaneous
Mueller investigation
Into Trump and all of his associates
That his letter
Directly to
Play Trump is going to launch an investigation into all of his political opponents
So there's going to be a two-pronged like
You investigate me I investigate you what are you got going on here and that's going to make sense of a matinee answer this question
Because Alex Jones has this term that you like to throw around parallel Construction
Okay so what
Mueller is doing
The parallel construction of what he's already guilty
All of the globalists are guilty of all these crimes they're creating this entire perception that Trump is guilty of all these Prime
Do it
Someone identical to Mueller's investigation
Justin reverse
Because mothers wanted the parallel
Construction worker
Makes it okay for him to do it
How you trying
Look at this
It's just there's no Escape
It's like a
It's quicksand
It's
That's the
Teasing it but also saying
I don't understand how
How does he not realize
Teasing
I don't I don't understand it but it does
To equip towards the end of the episode
That I think is one of the weird
Morgan saying
Slightly esoteric clips
And for that reason
It's worth our time
Election fraud
Okay
And they're going to release
Congress
Attractive females have been discovered
Who founded Malik
But it's going to get a lot worse than that
Valley of Fire
It's on
But they're led by psychic so they don't
I just being stagnant being Yes Man
Alicia vitarelli
Valley of Death
I'm going to be a
Death
What
I'm extremely goes out to the ocean
Tree of Liberty
In the ocean
A big giant
Patriots and tyrants at the sea
System
And weird and I don't understand that
Is hell cuz I think he started going with a metaphor like
Battlefield
Stream go to the ocean
And then he remembered that
Expression
Tree of Liberty at
To be watered with the blood of tyrants asked
And Patriots
Kind of works what
What is that oceanway
Alex
Just stop
Because you could just say we're going down to the death Battlefield mystery there
Stream goes to the ocean it's
Tributary in a whole lot of streams are oceans
This is where I'm Psych
That's good
You know what I realized I think I think my favorite thing about Alex's when he loses it halfway through thought you can suck
Compel
You plan to say what if an ocean is a tree
Alex's Improv
In speech is actually what was it
Me to know why Alex
Is going one way it takes
Absolute other direction
It's just
I just a real tree
We come to the end of our Clips here
And Alex.
Like a cross-dressing
Reading
Which is a different
It's a mess
It's just bigotry and then Trump retweeted
That's all we got its
Really weird to look at this in the present day
Because like
In order to make their beer
Things to talk about
Alex
We brought up
2nd clones in womb
That's not true but I can look through that and check
He said that macron was as Rothschild sex slave I can look into that
Resume stuff it's like Alex you're misrepresenting this crossdresser
Speech
And
Trump just retweeted a meme
I feel like the Clone is big news because it's not a clone
Gino Gino
To do half an hour on that
Boring clothes
Genetically identical
Beer that he didn't want
But imagine if we could just edit
Jeans
Make people into chimeras even though they're not primaries
Come on man
Screw up the
The reporting
The feed like
Respond
Do you like Colin
No clipping
We'll see on that I think
The fuckout
New show sucks
This is such a bad show
What if an ocean
Is a tree what if an ocean is
No
What is a tree if not the ocean
In
Bark
Alton Road
That's important to the battlefield
You don't even need to worry about fighting cuz they already know house
Looking at the psychic nose
The ocean is
At the wisdom
That is the wisdom
Are the wisdom of the psychic is also too
To know that
The wisdom of the psychic is to know that I would never have
Kid unless
It was within a
Specific
Gene editing situation
We have a kid if you
Look
To the Chinese scientist who was going to be jailed shortly because you're not leaving the country
For Christ's sake get out
What is the temperature with our Twitter
Circuitous
Play No plug
Route to get to the Twitter handle
That knowledge underscore fight
You don't need Gene editing
Did know that all right
Alright that one was that was weak
We are
You can leave the review
You can do this podcast before
But beyond that
I would say
What you got
That one year olds
Cuz it's not on
Ssris
It was cloned from a a monkey
One-year-old clone monkey
Yet throughout who knows
But
Somebody text me
Probably
Play killed sound
Is Alex
Alex