Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work
News about Alex Jones High
Danced telling you to shut up at the beginning of relationship
Be through our Facebook group or text
Shut up
Alright
I will do that but YouTube video from The Rock
Way better
Your random interview
They could be yeah
Would you have one
Just thinking and I was wondering when was the last time you felt
You know what I mean not ignorant but like
Generally
Stupid
You feel that
But when we
The did a lot of digging into Alex Jones is 425 Supply
Website
And then spent hours writing it up
Collecting
The documents
From be like
County clerk in Travis County
And the Secretary of State working at like
In concert with
One of our listeners out in die in Austin
Who's up with me
All that time
Emails to all these media people about like
Hey guys here's a crime
Batman everybody like oh f***
I feel really stupid after that
Like cuz I really thought
How many people
Laredo these articles about Alex Jones being a dick
And all that stuff
Hey on a silver platter
Series all of the
Your is the legal statute that shows the keys
Willingly
Subverting the law
Amanda Brunswick
That talked real dog
But
Handcuffing yourself to
Twitter.
No no
She's got me out class
Alright
Breitbart
That that was very
Where
House in credit
Yeah
About her
Political action committee
Turns out today
Quote free Laura Loomer
I meant it Is Not What It Seems
Go ahead and look at it for yourself
If you want everybody out there in the media free stories just look up
Political action committee
Where is the old 42
So I want to make
YouTube some donors
Someone pointed out
That I was a little bit too imprecise with my language
On the last episode
And I want to give an apology for anybody
Pepper anybody but I want to give an apology that I wasn't more specific in my language
We were talking about Alex Jones's story we're just trying to
Declaim detrans movement
Children
I refer to the person in question is across the
And that was
Precise correct language
Entire program is Drake
Sessions
Between the two
Did not use the correct
We try to be specific
But sometimes you just
Sorry about that
Beyond that I'd like to say thank you
And I support the show we're very thrilled about that
You to someone
Congratulations
Honda Pilot
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Carla
Secondarily I'd like to
What else
Thank you.
Finally
Text IQ
I was up late single political action committee
Do someone who has joined up on a little bit of a higher levels
I sent me a bucket of poop
I don't want
Thank you very much appreciated
I'm so going over a day in
Major happened
Amazon.
Episode
Think is very worth our discussion
This is going to be March 26th
2009 f
Episode
We skipped a day
Skip's Market
25th 2000
And the reason for that is
Trash
It's mostly just about at the Obama
Deception
Should I felt it would be a waste of our time
Time to go over that
In addition to that he does Alex does talk to
One of his weirdo friends
I did actually wanted talk about
This
But
Be the singular being made
The globalist and all these evil folks
Because
6 believe the devil is God
I wanted to spend maybe an hour talking about how that's bulshit
Because coming in
Expressing these things giving like a really stupid Elementary version
And understand
I'm at that is
850 service to Alex and his audience
But I felt like
Who gives a
Come up in the future we can talk about
Not worth talking about the 25th just
For that
When I got
The 26th
I realize
This is this is what we need to talk
Here is an avocado
Check drop from Today Show
No you don't
Now you don't
No
Documentaries we found
Wall-to-wall fake quotes
You don't go to the library to pull these fake
You go to like here
Message boards
Burnet Library
There's no way he should be in
He doesn't know how to read
What's going on
Public computers
On our last episode we looked at
The Growler
You talkin about how
You know
News keeps coming
It's the quickening
God damn song
On the shelf and I made the point
The quickening
Okay
From Highlander
This some damn Highlander song
Capital
Just to demonstrate
I'm not talk
Here's a clip from March 26th
2000s
Massive Newsday
Quickening
Worldwide
He always said literally
The next episode
Ford dealer schedule
I don't like coincidences on that scale
It's because he says that every third or fourth I just don't play it every time we spoke
Find you 40 examples of that if I
Took the time to
Cut it out
Like it's not
It's only
Coincidence
Punch this guy
He always does that because it's a way you can
Create the perception that
Times are different
Then they were
When in reality
He's always selling the same
Urgency
Because it has
More recent past
Jeanette
Multi-level marketing scam
Soon-to-be
Sportsman's Warehouse
I would love
To see you try and commit to
To an episode where you just
Start with
Clipboard
Him's
Summer of Rage
You introduce it like we were doing a regular clip
And you just keep on wonder how long you could commit to if I had started
Collecting all the times they said it
The wild
I could do that right now
Like we could do a whole episode of Summer
But I understand
I think I have it with him
But I
I don't have it within me to go back and listen to all the episodes
I have enough clothes you will of Fortune
I forget forgotten to xibalba
In the next life we have here
We get a little bit of an update
If you'll recall
The last time we were in 2000
Alex was fake crying on are a whole bunch about the mandatory service bill
The Belvin had passed the house
A different version of is even introduced in the Senate
Afraid of what
Either of the
Isabel
The former version of the belt
We get an interesting update on this episode where Alex
You know in comedy
Putting a hat on a hat
Alex puts Ally on Ally
The propaganda had on a
We got some good news
We write the stuff as it develops 2 days ago
Compulsory national service
And the latest copy I read this morning
Now taking it out of the Senate version
The house version is five different
Malls near
A show that is good news
The house versions about
You literally can't believe that
So he's trying to create the perception that like we got good news
Took it out
In some ways trying to imply that vert warnings about it
Precipitated this taking the language out of the bills maybe letters to your congressman
People and they got together we will not stand for this in the house version
So
This is nonsense
It doesn't answer the question that I had to take
How do you get out of it
Like you're wrong
Maybe don't take full responsibility for getting the language out but you pretend that something happened in the languages now
Good news
Good news everybody
However
Secret
Haven't you ever seen the Masonic version of school
Yep about how they become secret laws
Steve Jobs
What's up then
He's covering his ass a little bit cuz he realizes
Narrative too hard
It felt good in the moment
Now I got to get out of it
Legos
He goes to break he comes back
His favorite
Samsung
Is ever been
Volume up
You bet
After the Renegade
Where we be
Unfortunately he did not
Declaring
He never comes back and goes back to break
Just happen there I've never heard anything like that
Didn't say like I got for this break
And it didn't come back
After this commercial break
He comes back and explain
What happened
I had to take a s*** we are back live
3 minutes
Quotes
Running music
Truth-seeker
And I'm not whining here
Because I just can't even operate
That stuff he was on someone else's radio
Entire break somebody else's
African-American interview
Mention other media appearances
He's done
Louis
Mike
From what I could get like from what I gathered
That they would use on the Lewis station later
It doesn't need to be in the middle of your show that you do this
If you want to three minutes
Not only going to come in early
Good
Or do it yesterday I don't know any report
Is a breaking news on that
If it's a Missouri station that's obviously what you going to be screaming at them about
Yeah absolutely
This is so unprofessional
He leaves the show all the
Little regard for his own show when it comes
Anybody else
He knows that other people have
Knowing the crazy audience
For larger
I gonna need a little bit of that
Exactly exactly
Depleted most of my
Like old man house phone
One of those
That sounds better when they're wet
It looks next clip what we do is we hear Alec
What's going to the phone
Collar
Is a familiar song
Joshua
Florida girl on the air
Alex Jones how you doing my friend
Offensive
News as well with the Obama.
Great film great film
I think it's pretty much the Gateway documentary to get a
The sheeple
Into the mix of the New World Order
About the New World Order
It's made for people who don't know what b*******
That's what that's how
It's for people who are liars
Reebok
He's a government Fox that guy
Free with the points made in the documentary
It's really boring
Boring
It's pretty bad
You're just coming to that from a rational perspective
And I think that if you're someone who is
Emotionally invested in the idea that there is a new world order trying to
Do your children
You might experience some of that really boring content differ
Because it's boring to oscopy of the veneer of life
How hot is it stupid
This is real information being laid down
You might be engaged
Names of the title
You can just talk to him like that there's no Counting
In the world
Is a good movie
Furiate Isabel like that movie
Christmas is coming up here I've got to complain about
Jordan
You do know my complaint about elf is right
All elf related opinion
Okay well
Self
Is that it exists in the world where number one Santa is real
We know that to be the truth
Do you know that all parents
Must know that Santa is real
Because
He brings their children gif
There is no reason for adults
Unless there's a conspiracy of
Female
Deception make
No sense
The idea that
PM Santa and his sleigh come through alert
And everybody acts shocked
How to explain depression
I understand what is a lion children or something like that
If you and your heart of hearts
Wake up on Christmas morning in the holy s*** there's a bunch of s*** here I did buy what the f*** is going on
Clearly it's that they
Do not talk to your adult friends like
Hey on Christmas morning to give to show up
Yeah man I thought it was just me
Tired
Santa is real
You have
To yourself
Imagine dude
If you knew that one man can create all these toys
Show me the total economy
Dirt Devil
Yeah there's a lot of problems like my politics
Would like to talk about some of that stuff more importantly
I am
If you related
F****** second about that story
Everyone has a kid knows God damn well that Santa's real
There's no reason
Now hold on does Santa not bring
Adult
I don't know I don't remember exactly but
Present children
I think that's
Universal Concepts
I'm willing to
I'm not willing
Exactly is your line further
Cuz originally I said that anyone who has
Kids must
Santa is real
Do anybody with a younger sibling also must know
Is real
Teenagers when they're
Holyshit
And you got like
Eight-year-old sibling
Oh my God
I didn't buy that
What else is real
Santa Claus is real is the entire Legend real
Is the movie the horror movie
Sequel to elf
Or Jack Frost
Where where are they
I don't care
Belzer isn't in any of them so we can't connect Cinematic Universe
Elf is a f******
Terrible movie
It's stupid Jon Favreau
F***** it up
Get some oversight
Who is Ed
I blame
Everyone everyone everyone
The bottom
Farrell Deschanel you're all on notice
I'll tell you who's finding all this
Jimmy cotton
Tonya Gray
You character makes no goddamn sense exactly
If understood through the prism of he has to know Santa is real
His cruelty makes no sense
Why is he loved the idea that this guy who knows
Bow Wow
Just a regular
You know what that eats and has nothing to do with Santa Claus
If you wanted to make a make a darker version of the movie where
Jimmy Khan characters like
You are an elf
Is Santa is real
I don't fucken want to talk to you
I might be more interested in me
Character motivation
You created Universe with the movie Hugo
Live in that universe
Annual elf complaining
Next year as well
But for now just call her who loves the Obamas
Deception has a little bit more to say
Much like Alex
Leaving his own show to go beyond another show
Another indication that Alex needs
Outside influence
That's an order to have
Is Shelbyville
Call local shells
And the bankers and what they're really planning
Yeah you really want to sound like
Radio
Call in phone number if you want me to
Throw that out real quick
The coup
1880s
23 Tamil
Shillings from
9 a.m.
The noon Eastern Standard Time
And I want to encourage anybody in Florida
Call to check us out at www.meetup.com Orlando 911 Truth for being pretty active awake
Call Jonathan Blair in Florida
We just encourage all the other groups
Aggressive
This is crunch time we really have to get on the ball ladies
Joshua what's feedback
Very aggressive
It's pretty amazing everyone that has wash
Instead wildest
That's just Mom blowing in there they always want to know what else they they come
Find out where to go next always
Endgame
Loose Change Final Cut
Sounds not let him Miss
History
It's a new Renaissance just like you said in the film man is
It's really exploding here
In Orlando is
Especially
Inspiring
Working at Orlando places in Maricopa County
Diversion
What's going on
Telling him
That they might be like that as opposed to
Whenever you're like
Right right
Where's Hugo next movie
You blindly accept Joshua in Orlando
To see if any of those coats are real
Spoiler alert
Was 9-11 mysteries of wbgo for a while
I believe
Yeah it was
Before the CW
In the show I told you earlier that this
This episode is pretty
Important episode with
Merit
Ignoring
Of the March
25th
And that's because
Spoiler alert
Patrice O'Neal shows up
At the end of this episode
Who got who comes up now
Because it rewrites a lot of Alex's
As we know Alex Bernie Mac
The precursor remix
Hey Alex
God if you just did that routine
Amazing
Best stand-up specials
Swear to God there's nothing funnier than that's it
8 tomatoes
Look at this rewrites a lot of Alex's history
Is Reno from his Tower
When he was 12
If you found none dare call it
Conspiracy on
On his dad's book show
Golf Course
New World Order
Did some research you read all these books
They never really specified a lot of the books
But he read
They just talked about my Carroll Quigley
Tragedy
Found out about you
Tracking
Talks about
Things like that actually sound like
W Cleon skousen fanaika capitalist
And pretended
You dread
Quigley is just knows the misrepresentation
Presentation
Nobody says that he read a lot of books
Never really specifies the
But in this neck
Text clip giving
Introduction to
Becoming gas
We learned what's some of the
These books were
Wake me up
In high school
Michael
How does
Down the rabbit hole I went show
Headquarters
One of the books that he was being weird John Birch Society material
Now it's interesting to me
Doesn't really talk about
How influential the John Birch Society
And I think that's probably because
They have the stink of being really crazy
On them
The same way that he says reading Carol quickly turns me on
It's everything I read W Cleon skousen
Make a capital
Because I feel like
You didn't read that you think you read the the lie about the same
He acts like not read all this
These are all my auntie globalist influences
Don't really bring up the John Birch Society being really important
I'm sorry about the John Birch Society
It's like
Book should be regulated the same way
Pornos like
18 or older
You should not be allowed to read John Birch
Society books Whittier
It's real it's really tough
I don't know if
I agree with you necessarily but it is really dangerous to have people
Whose brains are
Don't have the
Adult
Critical thinking capabilities
To be exposed to
Very intentional propaganda
Play kitties case study
Based upon
Just internalizing these ideas before you're able to like think I I don't know about that
Oh wait you're saying that you know about what the Communists
Really we're doing
Of course you
I'm committing the fallacy of appeal to Authority and I'm just going to go along with you
Cuz I bet you don't know much about them
I know enough
They are
Society was founded in Indianapolis Indiana
58/12 Junior
Well
Missionary and former soldier who was allegedly killed by communist
Some China
Just after World War II
Welch
For his diet
Because it was
Which is perfect as a temp
You can write your own story
Wells painted birches
The first casualty of
The Cold War
In reality fellow Soldier Jimmy Doolittle who the real John Birch
Is going on record
Said in his autobiography that birds quote would not have
The pru
Of them using his name
Inappropriate
Disrespectful
Use of a person
Famous lady without their kin
Welch
Handicap
But the business went under during the Great Depression
Luckily his brother James Welsh
So after what
The actor the ox
A candy company went out of business
Robert Welch just jumped
Started working at James's out
Hold on
These two brothers
Separate the idea of
We love competition
Competing
Candy companies with your brother
You just went over and worked at the other
Famous kind of against the idea of all these like same place operated
And they were both were operated
Robert got
Crazy f****** rich on Candy money
Have you retired in 19
So
Brother of the guy who created
The John Birch Society
Well
While it's unclear who's
Responsible for the actual invention
First casualty
Because it's not
Head of the John Birch Society
While
Robert decided to get more active in politics
A retired
It's because he'd already lost the race for the lieutenant governor
Ownership of Massachusetts
52 and was well down
Paranoid
Rick Harrison writes in his book before the storm
Barry Goldwater
King of the American consensus
Literally John Birch Society meetings were Rockets social affairs
Important societal
They provided disaffected Republic
Heading to far left with a means of organizer
At the same time to give bored Housewives something
To do other than embrace
Horizon
Instead
They could fight communism
It's service interesting dual-purpose
From a social and political standpoint
For the right
Members would host monthly meetings and their living
Where they would watch a videos of Welsh
And often write letters to the representatives about everything was happening in the world
Everything that was happening was a communist plot
What
Each individual groups membership reach 24
To operating under the theory that smaller groups would be harder
A communist
It almost certainly would never have happened if there was more than 5 TV channels back then this is
He blew up
Its membership rolls swelled after the 1960 election
Auntie, does fervor
Began to go
According to John Birch Society
Everything was a communist
Chief justice Earl Warren
Communist plot
American involvement in Vietnam
Public School System communist plot
Fluoride in the water communist plot
Their beliefs were so dumb
The by the early 1960s GI people like William F Buckley
Recalling them quote far removed from common sense
And an r and even saying that their ideas were quote childishly naive and superfish
Wow
Is Harsh criticism coming from someone
Came out that Wells
It accused Eisenhower of being a communist tool and guilty of treason
William F Buckley decided
To try and get him kicked out of the leadership role in the John Birch
Society but was unsuccessful
John Birch Society bulshit
His reputation of being a sensible
Conservative began
Hey hey
Let's not be
The absolute worst
Let's just be mostly the worst
And then you get the Maverick
Label
Biography
Buckley was beginning to worry that with the John Birch Society grounds the rapper
The right-wing upstairs in the country would take an ugly Eva
Fascist turn
Rather than leading toward the kind of
Conservatism
Promoted
Hahaha
Shuffle
Loading run the outsides of everything politically
And for the most part this is
Massive recruiting
Enlarge reduce paperback books
To disseminate their message
They were largely responsible for getting out Phyllis Schlafly book a choice not an echo and Gary Allan none dare call
Conspiracy those books that Alex
Was very inspired by as a child
In this era jumper Society was a fringe group
Sea by mainstream conservatives is basically raised included
They weren't welcome at the table of the GOP
Even Barry Goldwater broke sizes
Mostly
Due to the Eisenhower s*** like
Charges against
F******.
And I invented answer
You could invent something and it would take over
The greatest thing in the world now it's like maybe it's $5,000 order whatever
They were unwelcome in the GOP at that point
And they were
Until
When they were allowed to be
Beco sponsors
This was after the rising influence
Have you very John Birch Society inspired
Tea Party Movement
Conservatism
That is a movement that was funded almost
Entirely by the Koch brothers
Children of Fred Koch
Founding member of the John Birch
Society
Not to put too fine a point on this
But the John Birch Society is basically the Tea Party
Pass General
As a former member Carol Connor told it I always tell my liberal friends you better stop laughing at
These people and pay attention
The ideas you here today coming from the right we're generated in the Sticks
By the job
Society
It's a new language
The intellectual framework of the GOP
It's the birds
Society every single day
And that is what we've seen
Is reach across the aisle and compromise
You know that
The only way to
Ninety-nine percent of what they want all the time
Thanks Democratic party you guys are doing
Is a communist
No wonder they wouldn't
We got
We got the president
Of the John Birch Society
Now as a guest
On Alex Jones Show
He's already retconned a bit of his own
History
In terms of he doesn't talk about it like
Superman
Every single thing
There's more
To this than just that
I think it's important
As we hear somebody
But here is
Mr McManus
The president of the John Birch Society
Appreciate your tireless Society
On the last 40 years
Thank you it's my pleasure
I tell people all the time I wouldn't miss this
Steve already decided it's true
And then you just died
Nflx quote from McManus we get
A little tidbit
Is history
With the John Birch Society
Tells me something
But I don't like
About this McManus character
I did three years in the Marine Corps after college
Was an electronics engineer
In 1964 they asked me to text staff position
What's 66
So he's timeline with the John Birch Society
Trouble
Me a little bit
The idea he was around in the early 6
Is the problem
Because the John Birch Society
Vociferously against
Civil rights
Sudan
On the right side of History
A lot
This is going to sound crazy
Maybe
A lot of
Economic anti
Communist
Vino
Inspired by the economic
And maybe they're more inspired interesting
People coming together
Open for inclusion in this Society
Even though they really weren't
I know you're just trying to force historical parallel
I'm just saying that maybe now the Resurgence of the John Birch Society
Something to do with
It's crazy that it would happen
Right around eviction
These were originated as purely racing
Disorganization of economics
Or even more batch
Maybe
Dating October 19th
65 the John Birch Society made their big move
They published a large killed
A couple years later
Post titled quote what's wrong with civil rights
Wherein they argued that the concept of civil rights
Was being pushed
Bye
You guessed it
Communist agitators
Division
And bring down capita
The average American Negro has complete freedom of religion freedom of movement and freedom to run his own license
Now the argument that someone on the side against
Them would say is
They don't have the right to
Participate in public Commerce
In places that put up signs that say
No black people allowed
It's a private business in terms
Repeating
Privately owned and operated but it still
Engaged in Commerce with the public
Just kind of
You know just
Paper over the hole
Massive amount of lynching
We're going on
You gotta understand
Really 0 freedom of movement
I don't know what that relates to movement
I would say that yes
They probably just
Maybe it would be really by the way
Right
Big
Would it cost quite a bit of money back Avengers what's wrong
It's just a communist
Black people have it fine
Why do guys like
People
To be able to discriminate
Who matter
Ability to operate the economy
Well the economy will solve itself if you if you don't want to visit
Don't patronize it dance free market will solve
It's just the government over reaching trying to
It's the name is what it is
83 Fred Koch wrote a book called a businessman looks
Communism
Which is why
Distributed by the John Birch
In the book thread sounds an awful lot like both
Alex
Flaming racist
You may be sure that the Communists are fishing
Furiously in the Troubled Waters
Integration on both sides
The Communists are not interested in the aspirations of the Negro except as a means to stir up racial hate
The colored man looms large in the Communist plan to take over America
I've been told by ex-communist
The Communist Party
Influential in the relief laws
The New York Philadelphia Washington Detroit and Chicago
Rural Southern Negroes in Puerto Rican
Come to those cities
In the first place
The Communist Party
Do use the votes of these people to swing the balance in these populous state
Secondly when the party is ready to take over these cities
It will use the colored people by getting a vicious race War started
Wow
1963a I bet they would get that vicious race
Race War started
In the summer
Dismiss sound
Exactly like
Interesting Franco Crobat 1963
I wonder if that was on Alex's dad shell
Wonder
I don't know maybe because of Alex's words
We kind of already
Lest you think
Text drop I played at the beginning of the episode was
For no reason
I present to you
McManus
President
Of the John Birch Society
Committing
Exact same sim Alex Jones
All the time
It's a devilish determination to take power over mankind
Was Maya Rancho Rothschild
Subway
As I want them
And that's where we are
Play the defect quote
Most sources
Michelle Rothschild
Said that innate
Team 38
That's a problem because he died
It is usually
Phrase
Do people say that a lot of a lot of resources
They say that
The quote is supposedly issue and control the money of a nation and I care not who makes
That is
Before ovulation
Unfortunately
No primary source
Is known as the earliest version of that quote
Cited is 19
So 1935
Oh over 100 years after his death
This quote shows up
Cuz it's a hundred years after his death and there's no primary source in the
David
Say that he said it 26 years after his death
Doesn't mean it's not accurate
What are you going to tell me cuz the Bible was written several hundred years after the event
A test to describe
Crazy day
Plies Swirl C the bigger issue is
This is a paraphrasing
Quotes
That have been
Play it out through history
The earliest version of this quote
What is from
17th century Scottish parliamentarian Andrew Fletcher
This is from
Rochester Christopher
To my pretty believe that if a man were permitted to make all the ballads
He may not care who should make the laws
Elimination
This is paraphrasing
Of this guy
Sir Christopher poet
He said let me write the Ballads of a Nation
Make their laws
They which is essentially hymns
Can control the history I
Mythology character with the songs we sing
Artistic
Pleurisy
Kind of
Talk of like I will create the character the name
Valid
Zach
Has been taken
Morphed
Repurposed
To be an anti-semitic slurs against
Debrox
Let me make their money and I care not who
Who makes the laws
This is complete b*******
Is it fake
Quote you want it if you want to complain about the Rothschild go ahead
But you better come correct
Don't use this
Cuz if you do that means you're not serious
You're just looking for any convenient online meme nonsense
Posting of fake quotes in order
To attack these people
What's the rich Jews
That's what's going on here
I wonder what
We say
Right now we'll in a couple of hundred years
Used to be
I think I think you and I are fine we're in the clear Maybe
I reject your premise
I reject your
That was attributed to 26%
President of the John Birch Society
James Alex using fake quotes in order to make their point about this imaginary group of globalist
So they're super
What do you know
He does another thing that Alex does all the time
Most Americans have no idea the Federal Reserve is a private agency it's not a government
It's not a federal agency
Stupid first of all we already know that that's bulshit
Federal Reserve fig private
Evidence
It's always
Do what the f*** you can't find the phone number for mon old man Birds
The bloop
Come on what
Just say that you're racist
Hidebehind
Terrible economic ideas
You know why
Because I would imagine that this McMahon is some people in the John Birch Society
But there's a whole lot of white supremacist leaders who just happened to have been John Birch Society members
Robert J Mathews
The founder of the order
Was a member of the John Birch Society
Aryan resistance
He was a member of the John Birch Society
William Luther Pierce
Founders National Alliance
Was a member of the John Birch Society
Thomas Robb
Be the national director of the Knights of the Klu Klux
What was a member of the John Birch Society
Has Rob who just became a national director
Founded important
F****** white supremacist groups
Tom Metzger is a huge deal in Neo-Nazi white supremacist
Community
The order is a very relevant White
Like maybe some group you never heard of
Some piddling racist group
They just daughters around
You guys are f****** racist at least just don't get in the way of universal basic income like
What you got to do that why you got to mix them together
And being Against Racism
If you are if you are against
Braces if you are fighting
Quote separate but equal Society
Communist
Yeah
Precursors to the
Would be pro-slavery
I'm guessing that the precursors to those guys
Would be Pro colonialism
I'm guessing they don't even have to go to
Precursor
Like early John Birch Society literature was specifically anti-colonial
They were Pro Colonial
In these places
People colonize
They were giving these people a great life
Make arguments against
Colonial is Stafford
They are also communist agitator
Precursors
Licking flavory was on the
Like ballot they would be for it
The kind of word supported George Wallace
Chrome
You don't have to go to the predecessors
These people were
Wow
In a very short
Amount of time
That he's been on the show
We have
Him McManus
Using fake quotes demonizer Rothschild
We have him
Making the exact same stupid argument that Alex makes that the Federal Reserve
In order to bolster his
Idea of the globalist
And now the little conversation
And I think you can get the
These two guys agree on almost every
Did you see the eclipse on your with former fed chairman
He said look the president
Legislative the Congress
Or look at us
We are a cult.
You really don't
Secret
The world
Absolutely
Flight number 5 soundtrack
Not only
Buttons
Adding in another thing
Omigod you guys all believe this
Push it that everything is a communist plot
Cool alright here's my new pet
Alright we lin-manuel Miranda
We see if he is willing
To write
A kick-ass Musical
About the auditing of the
Debbie so boring
No way
Be so bored
Bernie and Ron Paul doing sweet duets
Great
The big
Is a solo song Ron Paul.
He's like
You know I love him
That's in the beginning of the
The play
The musical as it were
It just
Ron Paul's feeling about it
If you don't mind
But I'm not going
DeVito
Where was The Great Raid
Thank you Alex
Ask Nikki
About his feelings
Deception
Is refused entry
I watched it on anything I have
And I watched it on that of course I wasn't taking notes or anything I was just
Name one fact
See that's that's kind of what I do you know when someone is like you watch my
Comedy specials
That's the response you give when you didn't
Important for Americans to know it's a note
I was watching
Go fuc yourself
Gofucker
Yourself John Bircher
Throughout the time that we've been doing this show not been unaware that Alex
Influence by John
Quite
Never really been a good time to talk about
Because he doesn't bring them up
Really
Maybe brings up Society
I'm passing like
The claim that like
His dad had some friends who were into the Birch Society when he was a child
Something like that
Turn off
Point to talk about
How overlap
These worlds are
The because he has the president of it on
Now we get to talk about all this stuff
A little bit
It's so I know that we're looking
All look at all these parallels
Necessarily news
It's just
We haven't
So
One thing you need to recognize
Is that everything that the John Birch Society believe
Alex also
He doesn't talk about it cuz he knows
Connotation with saying that your aperture means
You're crazy
The John Birch Society spends a lot of its present-day efforts fighting the same Connie ghost
Alex.
The US sovereign
Being under it
Fears about the North American Union Agenda 21
One World Currency
The evils of the UN
Fluoride in the water
Global warming being a hoax
Made it
About being a bring any carbon tax
Homeschooling being under attack
George Soros being evil
Everything all the way down to Communism
Satanic system
What's fundamentally ink
Compatible with Chris
The smart money says that Alex generally doesn't talk about
His ancestors
Intellectually being the John Birch Society
Because in 2009
He knows that
They chose Glenn Beck
This is where things get really important
Fred Koch was a founding member of the John Birch
Through freedomworks Americans
For prosperity and the donor fund
His children
The rise of
Tea Party
This is not like some conspiracy theory
We're making up
This is all very well-documented
So you have
The founding member of
The John Birch Society
That believes at
Years later you have his children paying for the Tea Party
B believe Zach
It's hard to think that's
Coincidence
Come on
The public space
One of the main one
Tea party that was being funded by for you to work
Very clearly
It's been proven
Was Glenn Beck
He's making
Tons of money
From freedom
The coke pundit
Freedomworks
It's almost impossible to not look at that
And be like
Awesome probably knows about that
He probably knows that yes absolutely forces that brought about
The John Birch Society
Tea Party
It's not him
It's going back
So I think that's why
Base-level pettiness
Sure it may be signaling that he
Want
He's trying to get
Yeah he's trying to get some of that
I got your life
Kisses ass
A significant Overture
Of I want in
You guys are doing
Which is
Okay I think this is a major turning point
You'll see in this
Does he have a money bomb in like
3 weeks
I don't know
I do know that in the course of this energy
Alex changes a couple of his position
Weave
Very clearly
And here's the first one
And I think it's
This is a conversation about the AIG bailout
Franchise
Billionaire George Soros David Rockefeller Rothschild
Or actually getting the money
Fraction of a real money
George Soros
Was
Probably because
The John Birch Society was already on the Soros
Alex knows that
At no point in anything that we listen to up till this point
Has Alex listed Soros along with Rockefeller
And the Rothschild
It's always
You've mentioned him
And it's always just been
This guy's Richie's masshole
Or something like that
Never been
The
Soros
Rothschild Rockefeller combine these big class of people
That is
Big in the middle of an interview with the president of the society
I refuse to believe that that's a coincidence
He's trying to impress
That's what I take away
Jesus
This is
Listen skip acid
Stupid
I don't
I don't know what to make of it but like Alex
Farewell
The same dump
It's not our ballgame to pretend that we know what's going to happen or anything like that all we can do is read
The situation based on the awareness that we have of
Where Alex Goes
In the future and what
Do you have been in the past
But I see that is like almost
A moment of
Yeah I mean
Calling it supplication
If you'll like
I am going to
I'm going to have you on my show I'm going to demonstrate how much we agree with
About almost everything with each other
In the past
In order to
Be more in line with
Did I get some of that
Sweet
Yeah
Oh man he's Gravely
It's not groveling because I think they're having a great time
There's a lot of stuff that I have included just because there's a
15 minutes
I'm agreeing about everything
Good to go over
Going
Quite a bit
And get this
I think it's his next clip
Even further.
But the people are saying
First of all this company wants to give somebody a bonus it's none of the government's business intros pleasure
Regulate
Alex
The Obama Deception made a huge point of complaining about the idea that these Banks
Used bailout money to give people bonuses screaming about the idea of
Giving people bonus
He has the John Birch Society president on his show
Forgiving people bones and acts like absolutely
Prediction
His stated position
Within
Of this episode
That's not
When I heard that I was just like Alex
You pathetic stackers
What are you doing
Yeah I was crazy
F*** you
If you still like principals please get like a stipend
I mean we can't confirm anything yet but my gut says yes
And as we were the last episode
I mean I think Occam's razor tells me
Ricky starts to get money and it's hidden
Various
But it was for us to make that sort of
Take a lot more
And we don't have that yet
I don't know but I do know that this is
The John Birch Society president clearly has tied to organization
They're funding the rise of the tea party which is just a resurgent
Philosophy terms of crazy right wing ding dongs have already chosen their horses
Isn't that handy
Joan is left out in the cold
At least at
So that's all I got to go on and I know that
This is such a bummer
Such a bummer
Are you I don't know is I didn't know that much about the job
Society I really know is that
Everything that they say as
Because we don't like non-white
I mean
So whatever
So now we enter a number of clips
It's just
Clear that the two of them agree on
I'm pretty much everything
And a narrative
Probably come from
Summer version of reading John Birch
Society
Can you speak
Well first of all
My view
Yes
Temperatures go up and temperatures go down
God I hope you got a forest fire
And what is designed to do is to give
Once again you say the same thing
Save the coral reef
Shutdownmore of America's industrial power
Got to bring those coal jobs back
Even giving
Society
For having exposed
They're just trying to get carbon tax
Does which is
Alex Jones
It's even more supplication
You exposed
There's no way
That
He would have that belief
I mean it's not like
Adversely affect
Energy
C corporation that
Wait a second party
That couldn't possibly be interested.
Play the second
Here's the thing is like you might be saying
The Koch brothers own to pay climate deniers and also the
You know the
Fuel industry and big
Tobacco vanille
Pay people to muddy the waters about climb
Overtime
You're a fool
That's just because they know that that's
The truth and they want the
Getting out there
And the truth is the carbon dioxide is great
She's going to have to pay taxes in order to continue doing any industrial activity
In order to solve the problem that's not going to be solved by cutting back on Farm
Better trees better bushes better crops better everything
Is SS Blanca everything's backwards
Got all kinds of experts out there
Experts in the economics
So-called Environmental
I'm a Martian
But I'm going with my gut on this one Dan I know all these f****** scientist who spent all of their lives
I don't know
I don't even know
How carbon dioxide works
I don't know how that works
Listen to me talk
I just said carbon dioxide
I was in the Army for 40 years
Everyone
Stupid
Like you just saw a
An articulation of the stupid talking point that all of these people who get money from these
That special interest groups put out
And it is this idea of like
Carbon dioxide
Yes
No one is saying get rid of all carbon dioxide
The issue was about
Excess carbon dioxide
That has been put into the
Atmosphere
It's the beginning of what the Industrial Revolution
The science is very
Clear about that stuff
When you married
Plants needed to grow with trying to get rid of plant that's you appeal to really stupid
People who don't understand what the topic
And that is a tactic that is very specific
The guidon
By these people whose bottom lines would be hurt by making
Progress towards
Saving
Deforestation
I care so much about
Trees and plants
I honestly thought about the rainforest
But if I
I think you know what I say
Possibly before cutting down trees
Because they know
He's just previously said that trees need carbon dioxide to live
Then there might be too much carbon position is very much like that movie medicine man
Okay
The forest
And if that's not the point of that movie
The point is that was terrible to me when I was
Photos about
Assumed it was about a medicine or a man
Or perhaps
The man made of
It's about how there's something in a rainforest
That's required
To make a medicine and people are chopping down the forest
Idol room
Maybe not
Quick 502
No Highlander to do not watch
Anyway
I do
Lexcorp
Received
Imallexx
McManus
Set a reply
To the idea of what happened
If the globalist win
Somerset
You will be working for governor
If you have a job
And secondly I believe
That they will be physical
Extermination
Short everywhere
I would say notoriously faccia
Just government
In common with each other
Illustrate that they use the exact same app
Apocalyptic
About what
If our side does
Hallmark
Your fascism
Clicklist
Clocked in shorter than I expect
I kind of thought
This might take a lot longer
To get there I figured you'd be screaming
More quickly
I thought it would take longer that's one of the reasons why I was like we don't need to cover
Patrice interview
You know we can do that next time if we need to or whatever meat of the birch
The Birchmere
Would would sort of be a lot more
Does having an hour-and-a-half episode or whatever
It just
It confuses me
Why this
Attractive
Two people
Who are
Otherwise
It's like I don't understand the radicalization process that you go through in order to get
To the jumpers
In the sixties it makes total sense even now
I guess like the funneling of all of these
Children in and all that stuff through Twitter and and pushing them all towards
I don't understand how you don't
Any point go
Okay I'll look into
And then do that
How do you not do that
Except
From somebody
Yeah I think
A lot of it comes down to the the recipient of the messages circumstances
Place where the real
Receptive
Shakira message
Right like I know I was really depressed kid
Church
Was able to grab me a lot more easily
Because of that
Place of your life
When you're most receptive
Two messages that don't necessarily make
Wide enough net
You put out tons
Paperback books all over the place
That are your property
Buganda
Talon
Out to the world
You put out a million books
You get 75 people that respond to it
50 people respond
I think that's what you do you just accept
It's the same thing with everything they believe is contradicting it
Self
It doesn't make a goddamn bit of sense it does if you assume that everything is becoming
Because then
They can specially crypto secret communist
And things like that because
Then you can just
I mean you can wiggle your way out everything
I just don't understand how you can
Pretend to have a how you can have a
Belief
We are again
Any kind of control
But any kind of Regulation
Any kind of a
And yet at the same time
Your entire stated purpose
Dominate other group
I think the only question that I really have
Is how do you not realize
That
If
You are if you are essentially arguing for this like
Darwina stick
Survival of the fittest
We're in whomever is on top is
Correct by virtue of being on top
Do you not get
That
It swings both ways
And eventually
It only sweetie will be the lower only
The creeper
Communist government forces
Allow the people on the bottom to have any
Because they don't have anything till never
Get to the point
Were there a threat to pendulum
No that's not true
Remember
Nope
Sabaton the last episode
Circular beliefs is just clicks
It's almost not worth it
Whenever you
Just have people who make up their own version of history in order to serve their rhetoric
It's not it's not import
Let me write the history
I got sing
Flask
President of the John Birch Society
Barack Obama
Birth certificate
Simply producing versus Ariel and hasn't done
You can put an end to all this speculation by not being a racist
Buckhead
I wonder I really wonder
I don't know
But I wonder
McManus has ever seen
F****** George Wallace's birth certificate
No
George Bush
I mean look
Here is
You know what we f******
It's interesting to me
I think
But I will probably need to do is
Look a lot more
Old specific book
We're coming out
From a Jon Boat
Birch Society
Irrelevant
In his
His catalog because I guarantee there's a lot more we could learn
About where Alex's ideas come from
When we understand more of what the literature that they were
Distributing
He's very
Inspired by
Skousen and quickly
Absolutely that's not that's not not true
But there's clearly even
Wenger motor bus
With more
So I would like to I would really like to have talked to his dad
Like when he went out
What's was growing up
Like I would like to see
Like what
You know the government is getting in the way of your
Communist plot
Wisdom teeth
They don't Grant
Wisdom now
Before the government-mandated
Carbon dioxide
Love carbon
I'm not I'm not one of these guys who's like
Are you saying but I do want to know what you were thinking when you said you wanted to talk to Alex's dad
To know if he because he's clearly
He has to be
Even crazier
Like I would like to know what it was cuz this would have been what the 70s
Director of Infowars
What was
Do you like in the seventies and eighties
Was this much of an open I think he was obviously a bird
Yeah I know for sure I don't like hundred percent
Would believe it when I was
Tiptoes
My parents had some friends who were involved in the Birch Society
I would
Maybe they met it Alex's
Yeah I wouldn't be too surprised by that or is Barranquilla
I wouldn't be too surprised
Buyavette
At the very birth of there
Group
The very Birch
Spectrum
The guy literally organized it like a terrorist
Grow above 24 so we're harder to
Is it very likely Louis beam leaderless resistance
Operator
Yeah you guys are
Terrorist organization had a l
Small to avoid infiltration
And is obviously
Very consistent throughout
Different world
So can we just finally call these guys the terrorist
I don't know
Yeah I don't know
I mean information
Terrorist YouTube
Everything Inspire terrorism
People tendency
Be towards terrorists
They apologize for white terrorism
Whenever it happens
Not like hey sorry about that apologist
Hey where the girl the white terrorism
Maybe had a role in the Aryan resistance
No no
People when they're over
I would say
I'm reticent
Label anybody Terror
Anything like that
In this world
Lisbon the show
We have website it's John Birch Society. Org to read
We also are.
Underscore
We have a Facebook
Facebook
We have a group go home and tell your mother you
No it's not
Labor reviews
I'll tell you
I don't know for sure
But
I know that
The John Birch Society
Has influence
But I don't think I
Has ever
Interesting Lee I can't
Murder
But
I just want to tell this little
Coronavirus
A little bit
Sort of
First president of the John Birch Society was Robert Welch
The guy who was
Replaced by a guy who served as president
Year because you wasn't
A plane that got shot down by the Soviet
Yeah so he died
Come back as private
Check out a retirement
Exactly
Took over I couldn't find
Details about this
Makuu in the organization
It's described multiple places
Hostile takeover
And has been the
Informatica McManus
Politically kill the guy
Let's say that
Probably actually
We killed the guy
Alex