Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Which present
Which was never born
Pickle Barrel
I don't see here's the issue Atlantic would run the s*** out of that thing
Welcome
The computer this
How many presidents were individualistic acting presidents and how many
We're mirror people in this way
I've done all the evils
It wouldn't have worked out the exact this point might have happened I'm sure we wouldn't have treated me
Americans well if Christine had
Reject your question
Because
My reasoning is that the choose one individual would to beat the giant
Strongman theory of history and I don't want to do that
I'm hiding behind that is
Cowardly
Appropriate
I asked you in the middle of taking a drink
Something about a president
At the same time
You don't know doesn't just one
Did we get rid of
Exact
I guess if you're going to go that way
I will accept your answer where I do love you know a lot of
About how
I'm so Jordan today what we got in front of us is a modern-day
There's too much going on with Infowars world in the in the broader news Arena
What's going on with Alex and his dumb friend
Against
And it's goofy
Doesn't come up at all in Alex's advertising
And he's not going to give any information
Desiccation
Delight
How much of a monster he is it a come at me bro
Hey man further we had the memo came out about Flynn's cooperation Which flies barely
The counter through lot of the things I said about playing in the past
Down to it
Find out what Alex is talking about a surprise to find out
It was none of that
Created
Georgia
Well-known Chinese actress in the world just disappeared for 4 months of course
The guy who created cooking up front
This prediction Jordan has ever made on this
Note 3 doesn't come back up
Crazy.
Really interesting
We're going to be downright very
Do you know it's not down right now that way
I was trying you're ever bored
Thank you so much you are now policy
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Make sense
Quite frankly whenever someone donates
Like you're more than
Just a little however it is George Soros Junior
You are now a technocrat
Someone sodomites Italy a bucket of poop
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much storage Junior
Remember that
That's like that
That they were all ashamed for being deformed
Inform
Hit him away and
That's not the situation with George Soros
Do you like George Soros Junior at sports show you can do that
Appreciate
Episode
Like it show sucks
Right now at the present day is going to be good opportunities
Clowning
What I mean
The Mind reels
Why was the first
That is a legitimate
Clearly
He's doing something off colors
December 4th and 5th episodes
Of the Alex Jones Show
Which is Monday
Tuesday Wednesday
Of this week
The fourth is not all that great
I'll be I'll be up front
Not that great
Are you telling us that you listen to an entire Alex Jones Show and decided that
Present-day it wasn't that great it does that's crazy
Yeah but there are a couple things that are worthwhile
And
Is that when he's coming back from break
In the middle of the show
Alex breaks out of song parody
Republican
I'll take the rest of your freedom that's right it doesn't run
The Wrong lyrics
Not
I have the lyrics
And it's funny cuz Rodger is on the show at this point
Rodger I'm about to be indicted by the f****** government for treason Stone
Farewell Alex Jones
Bulshit / Albert Against the Wind
That's the speaker version
4 Highway
Wait
No it's not
Brown
Who did the original against the Win Brown
He's a doctor my eyes
What song
Anyways
That's a new one
Going to bother me I might end up looking it up in the middle of the show
Let's see how long before it eats away your soul enough
You're actually doing it right now
The moment I started talking you were like
I bet f****** look it up.
This is why
Sometimes. It's like my doctor Wyrick
My logic
Professor College
One time you said his name like I should
You Should Know Who You Are
Had a great
Assertive laid-back Style
Junior's real nerdy
Awesome
Maybe he had some problems in class in like breakdown
Spell questions about 1
And one
Student in the class fellow student was like
My intuition says
This argument is valid but I don't
Think it is
Reservoir
Breaks it down exhausted like explanation why
The argument is valid mean
Interested
This is proof of why sometimes
You shouldn't just trust your intuition
That's exactly what I felt there with the Seeker
Anyway is like nothing at all
Obviously if you're saying well
This proves that sometimes
That implies that sometimes you should
And it doesn't give you any contacts
Sometimes
Anyway the sexiest of all the place
That'll be my autobiography
Your return to Stand-Up is going to be pure character diagram except
Alex
About Alex
And his plan
And then Alex
Pretend
They aren't into what Rodger saying isn't true for no reason
This is super weird
Real quick
Before we go any further
Complicated convoluted
All I want to know because I can't see the video
In any way
Does Rodger carry a bug out bag with him at all times I only listen to the audio
Carrying a bag full of men
Concurrency
And like a disc
B like that
Glasses and big nose and mustache a school bus sized vaporizer
Hide your gun
All these things can be bought through AT&T
He needs to know where to put your guns on your body to avoid them being found in the book just about
Derringers
Conversation about their plans I don't know why Alex is being like
Very forcefully to the president's attention
Warmer climate between the holidays
Frosted do some things to draw
Simpsons president faces
This is why I
Yeah oh yeah
You're not coming I get it
Tell your mother you're brilliant
You're not going ever realize that you realized
Everyone is looking at me
You're going to come down to Florida with me started Mar-A-Lago
That's what I hear.
Look for the next couple weeks
I don't f****** know
Almost almost assuredly
I love Alex
She's being Coy I can't tell if that's what he's doing or if you think
What the intention is that clip
Important to recognize
Early in the week
There was Trump tweeted about Rodger Stone not being weak
Scared
Can we
Hold on real quick
Trump committed a crime
And there you go
A lot of people a lot of people have
Buckedup
Weird certainly
Xol disappearance doesn't have the
Stories about
Pleading the fifth or Flynn
Stuff to talk about
The only thing he responds to is like
It's not that not all that in
They have a narrative
Is that they want to
To spend most
Cast of their time off
And that is the passing of the USM
MCA
Which is the authority
No
Your
USM usmca why do I doubt you are
You are going to work on yourself
Bright but I forgot that stands for agreement
Confidence
U.s. Mexico Canada green
Reimagining
It's not fun to stay at the usmca
Because
Destroyed
Free speech
The world
I really don't think that's how that works
Placated what he's talking about
Why he has
Because ideas
But it
Because you make
Declaration about what
If
That gets ratified
English
Without liability
That's
It is my Rubicon River
Ratified by the republican-controlled Senate
If Trump does not act against this
Then it means that he is capitulate
America failed
You're not allowed to just shine over our first amendment
You're not allowed to do all this
Remember Alex Jones is above
The right left
Destroy America
I mean obviously the Dems are the ones who allows this usmca to be
Ratified then
Is Line in the Sand
And he must go against Trump
Capitulate
The wolf
Yeah good luck. 17 is a little bit murky
Agree with him
Tiny bit
If only because they need to specify the language
The idea of objectionable content
And stuff like that it does
Could be interpreted little bit
It broadly
And that
Diminish
Free speech
I think you're being a little bit like exaggerating
But he has a kernel of something that I
I kind of agree with
Whenever whenever he starts talking about the first thing I think of it is used
Idiotic
I like
Copyright
Bulshit that they're trying to
Put on the internet where it's like I get your idea
I totally agree that something needs to
Be done
But this was written by old white dude
Don't understand the internet at all
And it's going to be a disaster if
You trying
Reply this
To the internet
I think you're
But you're not smart enough
To handle the internet
Possibly sensible ideas
Reply to broadly
Lendup
Dangerous Waters
Specific it's like it's like right
Yeah yeah
Him in as much as
As it goes towards red
Application
Leisure
Flush out the language a little bit
Is any problem
But even if it's past as it is I don't think
Necessarily
Problem
Anyway
What else
Kicked off
Kicked off Twitter Facebook YouTube
Dorsum articles
It went around about how Alex
Got kicked off and
Have you had no audience
Everybody
Any response Alex's
Railed about how he's doing better than ever
More listeners
Which is interesting
Because on the 4th he says this
Got to go
We are going to deliver
Thousand
If you can write in your own letter
You can print it off and mail it
He's only gotten
50,000 signatures
On his
Tell Trump that he needs to protect Free Speech or else America is over campaign
That's because
So many people visited the website
This is
Toughman
Isn't
Anything--for somebody with an operation
You would hope it's not like he just launched
That that
That's not good might be as many listeners is Alex has
That's true but he can't Direct
To a place where all you do is find something
Electronically and then he said
There's no hurdle in order.
I'm not
Does not compute
I know that that's not like a reliable barometer of
That is not a good sign
Sign that you should
Start working on your overhead
And see whether or not there
See if there's a non-essential employees like everyone
The 4th
Alex
Complaining about
Tim Cook
And Google
China
Whatever but
Biscuits really do
Zirconia
Peter charges him to pay people less and the
Because you
Because I'm a nice little engineer that
Steve Jobs dead
Don't believe me
Communist Party tells apple.com
1 timer
Ninja Turtle story
What what when did Snoop Dogg say that to Buckley's
Realizes
Great vocals on the ones in absolutely
Throws a few bars down
Everybody's happy
Man
Crazy
Can't tell the story because it seems innocuous enough and it's a celebrity interaction no
The Galaxy
DJ cuz I think it interferes with his image of his family and all that stuff
That he's a house DJ
He has a SoundCloud under his own name
Buckley Hammond
Picture of him on there
I mean
I don't I don't think I don't think it's any secret that Buckley
Maybe that he's related to Alex
Probably Alex Jones is cuz you kind of have to know who he is or have read
Ashley Beckford
EEOC complaint where he's named
Lesbian
Director of
I'm interested
Is to be racist towards
Distinct groups
Two people
Cuz it doesn't cuz the first time he said why
Like what was
Was almost with an offense evasion axe
Super race
It's not it's
Cut out a bunch of him just doing Bernie Sanders
Rambling about now
And there's a
Kissing stuff
Alex starts off the show by saying
Come to a big
Realization
And now here's report for job app
I love it
Got to fill that first 6 minutes write radio station
Play John bowne report
Goes to break
And comes back
Is the formal start of the show
It was the worst of times
Radical Islam
Discovered
The good news
That's the best of times
Part of it
Yeah
Realizes it's under attack
Nationalism is on the rise
These look good
Always
Thought it was under attack
But it's weird
Thousands of years later we're still getting f*****
Call Vista
Christianity realizes
Time to punch back
Coming back up north for another Crusade
Should I hear the bad news
Incredible wealth incredible success
Always breed
It breeds breeds spoiled rotten
Gym cartel
Porch in the power structure
Systemically go out and hunt down every time
They're better
Strong always is
You're talking about
I just say you're talk about white people
I never liked anybody talks about groups of
People recognizing their
Are batteries and stuff like that
That just applied outside
I don't I don't know
Where else anyone
Sound mind
Refers to a group as
Their lesser
Not think to classify people
Ilonggo store
Supplies
No
Greater and lesser Mages
Alright alright
So we have here the good-news-bad-news
The best of times worse
We have somehow involved in Alex
Having a big revelation
Do we have
Christianity fighting back
Free market is on the rise
Bad news
Making a lot of money
Being really successful
Read decadent
And then these decadent types
It's always hunt down there better
So that's the good news bad news
It's unclear what he's talkin about right now
I don't want to get into
2/2 of one side of a cube
I think I did probably but there's somewhere he's going with this that is
Frazee
And I also use the big reveal of what his Revelation is
Massively disappointing on the way there I had a
Realization
About what
Spinning the narrative
Haunted on this episode on the 5th
All right get to that blood
Introduces the beginning of his
Disorganized
Guiding Cent
Constellation
What they're doing
Who that's interesting house he's going to come down
You don't hear any modern nomenclature
It's obscene
So we have a constellation is a news article
You have to dig under the surface in order to understand the theme
Which actually
Is very similar to
How Gerald Ford as described
These Trends forecasting
Strategy
Commonalities between the Articles
They both
I'm not sure
We'll see how this plays out
Is constellation a news article
Alex
As somebody who enjoys
Expend
Many years
Of course
Deserve to everybody publication magazine
There's a reason that we don't say
Has nothing to do with
Mother the murder of crows proper term for a group
I in my resume
Metro
Before I die
One would hear
So Alex brings in his first article and paste play a constellation of clips
Article
And pay attention
To when this article came out
Cumberbatch from
Last year this year they had big National studies and Pole
It's coming from over a year ago
This first article and his constellation
He says they have a bunch of studies hold on
Constellations
Start a different distances so you know that Ryan is further away it's maybe a year
Year older than another spectator God Is A Thousand Years
University
Majority of Millennials want to live in a socialist
At the University they're going to charge
I think that might be a loaded question
Shake that ass
There's a bunch of bunch
Actually we say.
44%
Do they know what it means no
Millennials
Chill
Set not with you
So all of those headlines
We're on Fox News
Bass Publications fair and balanced
They're all articles
This study
A bunch of
But instead they're just a bunch of
Bunch of hacks
Right-wing articles
The same study
Yep perception of like a year ago there were all of these studies
Came out that were
They're all like kids all want
Communism
Millennials you know how their what
So I Googled the first
Headlines
Because it was the first one
Washington time
Horses owned by the moon
The article is a write-up of
Report on us attitudes towards social is
Put out by the victims of Communism Memorial Foundation
Report
2nd Annual
This isn't like something that's been going on since the seventies it every year we get like us
How does America feel about socialism this year and information whatsoever
I couldn't find any of these articles what the data was last year it's not
On the sound ation website
Idea how to contextualize
Interesting lead the victims
Communism Memorial Foundation. Just based on its name
Doesn't seem like it's an unbiased source of information
Congress and 9th
After being proposed by representative
That motherfuker
F***** by
Really that's not a great cruise for sister
Victims of Communism Oriole Foundation record
An authorized
The truth about
Interesting
Information that's available on propublica
A trend of
Increase cash flow in recent years
Clear 1013a little bit over $1000000
And 5.8 million in 2015 2016
And I was not available tax records
Another job
Wherever the funding might be coming from which is unclear I can't figure it out the probably funneled through
Now
Individual donors
That money one thing is very
The communism Memorial Foundation
Was founded by an organization
Asian called National captive Nations
The mcmc with an organization
It was founded by quote
Who came to the US after World War II
Largely members of a group
Call the organization
Cranium National
Members of the group collaborated with a Nazi
He's rounded up Jews
And assisted in assassinating
And Exterminating thousand
In 1946 they rebranded as
Is the anti-bolshevik block of nation
Under the leadership of a man named jaroslav
It seemed like you were trying to get my
I'm just amazed
Brilliant strategy
We're super not to collaborate
We're super Nazi Collaborators and that would probably not go over as well
Bolshevik
When they arrived in the United States
Began organizing
Weather for themselves as representatives of populations of countries
Press by communism
These people are not
Somehow
Considered
Allowed allowed to come over
Really feel like that's not the same
I'd like that shouldn't be
It was a perfect time to do that
Anti-communism was real hot that
And they began to become active in the Republican National
Committee
The national competitions committee grew out of that
And then in 1990
34 mg victims
Communism Memorial sound a
Well there's no doubt that Communism had a chair problem
Some governments that included communist systems over history have their share of blood on their hands
But also it should be pointed out that
Communist propaganda
Tirelessly to inflate the number of deaths that communism is
Responsible for
One of the ways they do this is to include the deaths of Soviet soldiers who died fighting Nazi
Reason world war is part of their number of deaths blamed on communism
Statistic which is obviously intellectually very dishonest
Include
The people that were fighting literally against them
Weird
Well we can't say that
Communist sentiment
Traces back to this motivation at least in the case of the end the end
It's very clear that the route is not the Apollo
The Thundermans
Are the Fundamentals by misrepresenting
Is the make the crimes of Hitler seem smaller
Racine Alex present
This is very line of argument
Time and time again
We don't say things like Hitler was so much worse
I'm sure this isn't always the case
But in the case of the ncmc
Their reason for making this argument is
Because they were literally fighting alongside Nazi
So once again Alex is inadvertently promoting Nazi propaganda
People
This isn't too hard
It's not hard to
To find this information
But you doubt you Google the study
Find a study
The organization
Alex
Like like legitimately
Presenting
Things
Traceback
Text to groups that were Nazi Collaborators
Just because they happen to demonize his preferred
Group
He's like he doesn't care to look into who they are crazy
Man it is
So
I'm just going to
Shocking
Set the party of
Infiltrated by these nuts
It's definitely not that the party itself has
The greatest threat
Because this isn't about that group they're just the one who did this study
Clearly not unbiased source of
You should probably throw the baby out with the bathwater
Seems like
Would you rather have socialism
So they said it was like
Do you like capitalism
Or do you like socialism fascism
That's a great point that is where Alex
Is presenting this
Very dishonest
He's limping together socialism communism and fascism
Because that's the other leads to the other
Economic
In reality the poll that they did found that 44% of Millennials preferred socialism
7%
Communism 7%
So
Now.
I bet they're fun
Probably
The very not be leading beliefs
By Alex
The first one is the most glaring problem
Is Commission
They clearly have a vested interest
Unpresented communism
Socialism
Introducing yourself
Financial interest
Communism is on the rise
I thought they need more funding to educate the
Secondly this is only the second year they've done this
There's no point to it.
Silver past years
Network maybe it's fairly
Normal for you to not to be
Capitalism
A large number of people I knew in high school in 2000
Probably would have been
I don't think that's
Misrepresenting some of
The people I knew
Well I mean capitalism by its very structure
Fox over the youth
Data to back up what was going on at hit
Hickman High School
But I knew
Third problem the real concern here should be that 7% of respondents
That should be the headline here instead of lumping three numbers together in order to further your paranoid activity communist
So now what we have here is Alex
Presenting a study from a year ago
Reported in multiple conservative Outlet
As if it were multiple
Datapoint
Just a couple of editorials about the same study
That was put out by an organization whose roots go back to
Do unrepentant Nazi apologist pray who came over to America and started working with the Republican
I've now have gained a lot of favor
Because of the popular
Nature of the
The anti-communist
Intimate throughout the
Into the Reagan Era
Any reason
To undercut
Study who don't have this service to get involved with them this is banana
I even think that what I'm talking about is kind of a minor part of the story
But I think that is
Because
Whatever the group was
Originally
That's not to say that
People who are running
The victims of Communism Memorial Foundation
Or anything like that
Group had its roots
Doesn't mean that
The actors of it
People running it now
Subscribe
Very well be
Did the people who have come on board
Just gravitated towards the
Communist
Rhetoric
And stuff like that none of their funding comes from a valid whites
Supremacist
Parents may have
So I don't know I'm sure I'm sure I'm guessing the rickets
Probably so
Goddamn
9 intention on
Possible
But there's an insta
In terms of
Doing the study
If you're an anti-communist group and you're doing a what sort of
Government do you prefer
And
You know you get
Demonizing
Communism
Socialism
Assertive responses
Isn't worth reporting in places other than pray Firefox me exact
So
There we go
That that isn't his first part of his
Constellation
And so we seat like I said already star in the sky
So far
Not good
But I want to see what he's going to try and connect that to
He's got something else working here
Nautical out today
English band
Generations because they literally
No s***
First of all no s*** secondly
You're connecting article from a year ago
Multiple articles about one study from
Year ago
Not sure why but let's see
This is just came out they have lower IQs
What about you
Social Japanese
No spent less than previous generations because they literally have less money
What money am I
People on the west are less likely to give to charity more likely to steal
There's some again it's another insta
We've talked about
Business studies that give you the
The statistics that you want
To give
It's
Know if you go back you can see the budget is
Steaks and then we're all never going to
Exactly
The idea that study shows they have physically lower IQs and stuff like that
He was never going to point out that
The article
He's reading
Is from CNBC
But it's talking about a study was put up by the Federal Reserve
You never bring that up but he does
Okay I will get into the study here in a little bit but in true Alex Jones fashion
He gets totally distracted
Start stalking
It's on top of the 500 billion dollars
Didn't check the robber baron money from the five family she's the only air oven
Croatoan
Jesus Christ
Okay
Somebody
I don't understand how that
For certainly not killing herself
Who does it cover
Literally
Close to half a trillion dollars
You know
Single richest man in the world
What
He's not
He's a part of the Vanderbilt family
It turns out that most of the line of his
His family
Because of how
Hanover generation
There's a widening
Set of
Relatives
The money is already
Basically gone parent
Like they just
You're not going to get any of
The money likely most likely
I don't have any
I think the base this on
That was protecting him
Him from realizing that most of the money was already
At trying to reinforcing him
But he had to make his own
And he's talked about it interviews about how like that
Set him off on a course
That made his life all the
So
Sylvia Vanderbilt
With the social connections
I mean what is it
The only extends like past three generations and then it's
To diffuse
Stew beef
Completely Center
Paralyzed
As much as we want to imagine that happens all the time
A rich family
Kind of
A fairytale
You had the f****** print
Mary Meghan Markle
Thigpen happen
Yes never hear about it cuz it's not the f******
Prince
Family they don't always end up making a lot of people marry Meghan Markle Rockefeller
All the time
Doesn't always
European royal family
Or whatever
Those stories are more appealing
Anyway
Just talkingshit
The kids are not alright
I guess so
Edible bubbles garbage
Play successful
Cuz my dad gave me a lot of money are you going to end with that College
Me a lot of money
My first radio show
Cooper's Vicki all of his wealth is inherited are the laughing stock on public
I failed upwards when my dad got me
Me a job
At the radio station
Promise
And then I met this weird f****** doodoo sold gold from Minnesota
Hey just took I went to a real accredited college
New Year's in a two-year program that I went to
At a community college
Graduate
Suggesting
Maybe you're assuming get some associate
You're right
I wrote
Globalist
It's a joke
Write me that Eminem lyrics stupidest s*** riches f****** proud of it
Alright
I'm not stupid part of it
They really should just own up like
I'm dumb and I'm rich
Better into his ideology
Why would you
I'd like
The entire right-wing
Anybody actually
Brave
Gut instead of
Reality
You just jump in and be like
They call me Steve
Not
Try and fight in
Pretend
Like
Because his dad is a dentist
The higher degree
Family was
Around
John Birch Society assholes
There there
You do a lot of reading there is a veneer of intellectualism over it
He was introduced to that stuff
When he was younger he has a dad who has a higher level
Call degree
I could be there being a real strong desire on his
Park
Do you like hold onto that intellectual
Right
I mean we're at the point now where it's like
Is there any
Intellectual on the right
I can't answer that question
Question you asked me earlier to Alex
I guess coming up
And this is where it like I said
He's trying to make
Really display
Let me hear
Important
Back to reality
Producers
Intimidated and bullied
Animal Farm
.
Intimidating
And making us submit and show
Everything's this system are Will and ensuring
That we will never
Revolt against what they're doing
Georgia Pig
I don't know but I don't know if I want on packback
Too far because really what
Sing is basically like
I think
I finally realized
Imran was talking about like I want to go golf
December 5th 2018 Alex Jones finally gets on board with
Like all of these people they're mad at us cuz we're the producers
Just go please go package that is like sort of a new revelation based on a constant
Malaysian doves
Articles and Zack
Legit
Galt nonsense
Disappoint
Although in some ways would be considered a
Because as we recall Iran
Stupid
Ian ran those where it's at its like
I mean I don't want to run into it apart that's true there is a hierarchy
John Birch weirdo and an r and weirdo
Bulbasaur become a Charizard
Sorry
Thank you very much sir I would have gone had I known anything about Pokemon
The guy who is immediately likes
How dare you
So like I said that's disappointing
The conclusion
He's been building toward
Real real disappointing
Then I also told you earlier
That I have a theory about where all this
Is it coming from
I think
Plays out
Next constellation
No not yet
We have to wait till Alex
2 Stars
To start the second star Alex
Has brought up
Into the actual study
So I have to order the articles
Consolation
Think about what they've been able to do
Call generation the millennials
People under
These individuals in every study
Bob the Robber
Barbara Steele 11 tell you my birthday
Love it
Control other people's lives love it
National studies communism
Socialism fascism
Why
This current system
Yeah because they don't work
Cuz we're poor remember the other cuz we literally don't have as much
Cuz that's the second star in the constellation
But
You hear that clip
I'm some people might hear that and just laugh at Alex being stupid talk about like all these
Good morning
All the time every Rob
Because my
Alex Radar
He's going through in Iraq
I think
He just got updated demographic
Information
And he's realized
Okay here on the show about the evils of Ragnarok
Because he realizes the only people he's got left to scare old people
Particularly old white people
And so he's going with
I think when I hear him do this over-the-top
Demonization of Millennials that's all I hear is
Wow
You got no young people listening to you
Clever s*** band
Yeah probably early thirties the youngest people who listen to
Baby
Coming up
Sometimes, sometimes with this like listening to a ton of Alex
In the past and
Like trying to
Contextualize what's going on at that
I end up thinking it's March
You cuz I'm listening to a ton of March 2009
You're talking about WWE
After that there was the Crown Jewel was the newest one
Greatest Royal Rumble
Before that
But because I and my brain had been living in March
Alex world
Crazy
Level of being in
In tune with what's going on in Alex
Eyeworld kind of gives me the
The ability to look
Cut through the b*******
By the way I don't like
Even for him to be like
Pandering like a millennial
Buc-ee's
He might as well be
Hack
Macado's
And stuff like that those articles that's going around
If these millennials
Milano cookies
Hydra I just
That's a level of Li
Like Main Street
Stream hackery that I think Alex
Demonizing
If I had to bet
Everything I own I would bet it on
He just recently found out
That when he got off YouTube
There are no longer anyone
Who are young
Precipitous drop
And youth listening to his
King radio
You have to like go to his website and order to watch his show for the Genesis Communications
Website
To find
Young people go to the communications website
Everyday I go to the millennial hangout which is what what would you
It is we go to Rob
People I say the Walmart parking lot
Before we go rob 8 to 12 people
Let's check out and see what the Genesis communication
Website has up as far as special
Then we can get this Walmart
After we robbed
Absolutely
So here we go Alex
Do that second star in the constellation because they're still not a
Constellation constellation
If Alex is
Pretending
That those three headline
Never makes it clear that they're all about
Exactly
Alright if you want
Multitude
And in that case
I'm trying to see you is his deceitful version
Exactly
Alex trying to read
From that other article
Second
That's the first one
Here's another one
You'll spend less than previous generations because they literally have less money
Home construction car sales
Kamal been blamed on the unit
Patient preferences of those born
Between 81
That means have been
A basically
Yeah
Country
Kayla or North Korea
Leftist ideology
Sure through a paragraph
Of that for you just gave up and started editorialize
Is that article about Millennials are poor
That's what Alex making stuff
The article discusses the societal impact
VladTV
Desperately poor as a
As a cross-section of this
Population
The paragraph Alex Stop
Quotes
Actually I'll have it or not
From that of previous generation
What's the effect of a gin come in a wide range of demographic characteristics
Two accounts
According to newspaper by the Federal Reserve
The article points out also
Datasource
Millennials are likely paying the price for coming of age during the Great Recession
When new entrants into the labor market faced historically labor demand
An unusually tight credit
Conditions
Do the Federal Reserve
Adjusting for inflation inflation
Sun compared to college tuition
Private school tuition in 2018 hasn't
213%
And for your Public School tuition
Increased 129
As a result much of the generations
Is Browning and student loan debt
Meanwhile
Meanwhile the average annual deductible for employer-sponsored health care plan
Was $1,505 in 2017
Compared to only $303 into
2006 according to the Kaiser
Family found
The article very specific
Ashley says the opposite
Calling millennials
Dumb
Millennials are also more racially diverse and more educated than
He's always
That's not even
We have education
Nemours
Formation in chips
Those
Phenomenal
Phenomena
You can say about Lenny
But if you look at
Each generator
It's not beauty tips
If you don't
Paper
You'll find that it's not a study about Millennials being poor
Stupid at all
It's about their spending
Are millennials different
The answer they came to was no
Job market
In 2007 to 2009
Probably Crip
Yeah that is what the article is
That too is me
Yep that's
Clearly hasn't read
He's just making s*** up
He's like
Stupid
It's a bad
Badcock
Write a year-old study
From an anti-communist propaganda Outlet about how more use
Like socialism communism and fascism
But would you really pretty much all socialism small group that like communism
The constellation
Lying about
Federal Reserve putting out a study that
It's covered in the media about
Hauwa bilineal don't have
Clear if you look at
Trends
So if we're going to do this whole baby boomers are
If you're going to pull this if you're going to pull this like
And all of this
Why aren't you
Stupid and poor and all that because of the machinations
Ecology of capitalism
Creepin Creepin communism Georgia
Creeping communism
Constellation
Want to realize
They don't want to step up and realize that when they came
There was a massive
Social economic growth
Bluetooth
Jordans
Connected
Rich chigga
If you want to b**** about parenting
Selves
She don't know anything about constellations
Behind
Buddy
Okay well then I apologize
What is salinity have to say
Can you forecast for the trans on this one
Who am I
I don't think he's involved he was just a user
Rapping like that
You understand
There's a defect
You have a story for me
I have a story
David
Bee-related
The first one is
The Millennials like socialism
Yes the new one is millennials
So
If you're dumb
You can put it in your head together and be like
Money
That's why they want socialism
My things
Because I'm a prude
Do Serrano
To go golf
Dissolved that's all the thought process but this is
Really very Elementary
Yeah
Seems like there's a far simpler Occam's razor to this where it's like the system that
Don't have any money
Is the wrong system for
And so we don't want it
Your entire life has been
Just
Communist propaganda
Never going to go again
You know this interesting thing
Alex will complain about is like
Your gear at your
Kid of a liberal
You just grow up
You never never question your own beliefs
Your brainwashing centers at college
Turquoise turd liberal bubbles new come out
Any
Whatever
You grew up in a family that was
Deeply
Adjacent to the John Birch Society
Inculcated with a
Now you are one of the most popular and famous purveyors of antique
Propaganda
He is
Definition of
What he would complain about liberals be The Offspring of
Unquestioning your politics
Problem
Which is
Be sure do seem to project a lot of themselves
And
The same it's the same
F****** s***
So many of these like
Colonial is monsters of it who are like
Because of all the stuff we're doing to him
Which is really what you're saying is like
If anybody did this s*** to me I'd burn everything to the f****** ground like you're projecting all of your worst
On the people who are trying to make it better
For everyone and that includes you you stupid motherfukers
Unfortunate side effects
In order for our lives to get better yours will have to
Do it the other way around
No but sometimes
Getting on the Millennials pretty hard
There's a break
There's a bright spot
They're not the only generator
Josh information
You already know about the Millennials in
Generation Z
If you take God. The articles are you having left
Less interest in socialism
The real world
Betty Orion High School and so I don't know
Visinet is it so often
That was the refrain
From from what I was growing up
It's like
Seen the real world yet so all your liberal ideas are going to be
What's the weather
The old like you're not a liberal at 1
And then it's like we all got into the real world would like
No you do you guys f*** this up
Made no secret
What is my parents
Stuff like that
High questions
Little bit of like the idea
Fiscal
Of course like not going as far as to ever really
Join up with
Any f****** libertarian groups were they around
Explore those ideas and I I found him
Relaxing
End result
Questioning
Exploring
And then it going further left
I do I do think so much liberal bashing
Is
Subconscious
Recognition from the Baby Boomers
Their generation
Has literally destroyed the world
Like
I would love to say that as like a
Using literally like the way that we use figuratively
But we in common
Parlin
Use it as literally but now it's literally 100%
We have we have 12 years before climate change is irreversible
Irreversible
Spiraling out of control
And they have to know on some level
It's their fault
I mean you don't want to think that you're the reason your kids are going to
Can you sue an old fux
That's why
Did you kill this all get used to it
I think beyond that even there's a like
Maybe a kernel of subconscious
Guilt
Videos like
We were doing was maximizing
What we could
And probably a lot of people didn't understand the ramifications
Or Consequences
Come down the line
Couldn't hospital it's not it's not necessarily
We all liked ill-will and
Malicious
I think there's probably a
Same sort of feeling you get when
You buy some
You realize you can't pay rent
Realize
The pleasurable experience
If it screws you over later
I think there's probably a mix of that
Gilton and the record
Everyone else is off
Yeah
The idea of an in
Entire
Country planning 30 years ahead is
Bananas right
Like I said
Show up later in the episode
Boring
About the news
But
H w a.
In his next clip
He celebrate
Hws death
A little bit as he starts Ram
The ugly to celebrate your enemies Destiny but I don't want to
Conversate
No
Just
Funeral is a ritual is tripe
To some extent because it is
I don't know where he's like
Relishing in the the image
George W bush waving goodbye to the
I don't like look I understand
These people are monsters
Go fuc yourself
Insulting that MoMA
You know what I mean like
I'm not
Defending worh w at all
They both did horrible horrible
To the world you are like
Sort of insulting the idea of a son
Invis
Funeral of their father
That isn't human
To some extent I understand
Larger issues of how many people
Lost their children or fathers because of their paws
That's very valid
I don't type
It's not the same conversation
Lake
Evil things
Doesn't negate
The pain of losing
Your dad
Mockingjay
Is never
Never okay
And Alex relishes in that a ton
Now I want to be a dick and disagree with you but I agree
The other point is
Year
How many celebrates all these people
David Rockefeller died on March
20th 2017
So that was last great year
On May 26th 2017
It's been fantastic it's March now right
That would be
A way more fun Oscars ceremony if they if everybody was like
F*** that guy we lost this year Memorial
Just wants to dance around
Because hwd
We don't respond eclipse
Because
He's just
Scoring points
Wherever you can get them
And I know you agree with him
Defend
Aw so what's the point you know what I'm saying
But when you're saying
It's been a great year all these levels to died and I feel like you might not have a handle
Wendy's
Xerox big bad guys
Ivan Ivan
Spending the day with it
Hws death because of course as you know my
Delighted
Great monster
History dying is
An unending song
The only thing that I think about right
In regards
It is
I believe it
EJ Bradford
Guy who was
Straight up murdered
By the cops
Who suspected him of
Being bathed
Straight up murder
And
Everyone
Not ever no absolutely not everyone a very vocal minority people are protest
To get that video out
To try and make sure that somebody is held accountable
For the cops murdering
You can read online
So many like
How dare they talked about this guy in this guy was a criminal in all of this
And then you listen to the
Glowing non-stop eulogy
I don't give a s***
I am
Furious
So it's awful it's awful
Position points out what is wrong
What's the way we deal with
I might be dead was black
What is awful that we have to deal with
Anything away from that but I
Time
President dies
Former president dies
If you want to do it
Why is everyone covering
Bad guy f****** conversation
That come from people who are aligned with his political
Portals are going to f****** happen
For sure
Di Fara critiques of him to come out after his death and everyone's like God's too soon
Of course the people who are making
It's all f***
Stupid
Absolute
The greater point of
Mocking morning is
Shity
No matter where it happens
It's the same thing with Alex Jones
On his show
Wayne like
People are putting
Bouquets of flowers
Where Michael Brown died
This guy was a
Bad guy
I feel the same way about
Hearing that rhetoric as I
Hearing Alex
Mocking
Waving goodbye to you
Your dad's her
I don't I don't know I'm not trying
I'm walking this fine line cuz
I'm not defending
Seems like all they still have feelings
I like that it's just
Off
I am I was
Hoping that you would
Say your product
Because I wasn't because I
Pre-empted that with
Explaining my position
Damn it I don't know
I don't know if we can ever
Truly trust
Well look
I don't know if I'm proud of
But I will say no mothers need to be
Kick them off their knees
Oh no you're not bringing up
Play The Proud boys do come up
Springs up the proud boys
Because much like
Generation
Lindsey
After his enemies
Celebrate
And misrepresent what they are what they do and what they stand for
Because he's so full of
Bulshit
But if you make it through that desert
Where we realize I was just talking about it
This clip
Listen to The Proud boys
But it's in the middle
Remember the proud boys
Read
White
Straight
Hail
Universities for white men
Lots of control
Heard
Listed as a domestic extremist group
They are
They got removed off of Twitter and always other places
Came out today and said we never did that
That's not true what he's talking about
Is recognized
As a hate organ
Because we're going to fall off
API Trump do this
Reality winner type folks
Who is Akira
Information
Beauregard infrastructure level
Accomplish
It's classified
Interesting on this episode where we have these the Ukrainian nationalists who came over with these caps
Nation committees
Who were unrepentant Nazi apologist
Hey Alex bills got to get
On the episode where
He is
Disseminating information that comes from
The group that they found it
He's still got a pretend it's LaRosa's a Nazi collaborator with that's all bulshit
It's crazy
Absolutely
Classified Veo level person put on his bank
Cuz he does still have if he didn't then why would he
He's going to 12 Days of Christmas sale going on right now
How many days until Christmas
More than 12
Has he has like the sale that's just an extension
Turn on everything along with every purchase
Marriott
30 years from now that shirt is going to be in a Goodwill and we're both going to buy it and wear it and
Nikkeby the lights there's no chance
Is cut off
Otherwise there'd be no reason to sell
Anything Alex tops
Something like that
There is also a mean
Just to his dump
Job herb
Fair
The guardian had an article out today
Discussing how
F******
The police are and are specifically targeting
Antifa protesters
The ones who were
Did not
Charge
But like
5 dudes who
With with nothing
Let's
Even Anderson California even in the most liberal place
The police are an arm of the white nationalist
Fascist
Goddamn
I believe is Vic Berger put together a sink
La Posta New York
McGinnis speech
And if you look at it
Footage
Matched up
It's clear that
The proud boys charged
The other people
Before they threw yet
All you can see is
Static shock throws something
The proud boys coming start beating from another angle
They vary
Clearly start charging
And say let's go boys before they person throw something
The people charging
So it's it's another
Recently that was like a
Probably guy out there
Videotaping
Independent journalist
Some guy comes over is like
F*** you
I meant the police come take me
Uncle journalist away
He's like
That happens over and over and over and over again
You hear the story
Perpetuate
Repeated through right-wing store
Of
These laugh
Antifa
Leftist demonstrators of the ones were agitating and hitting people with stuff
So violent and robbing people all the time
The stories that those
Outlets
Putting out of like
Oh this guy just shot a gun into a crowd
The ground-based
Stickman his nickname because he
Yes
The crime you can't prove
Beforehand
Vaguely secretive
Message boards
Organize themselves online
A large Gathering of people even though they were the minority
With intent to use violence in order to cause Terror in those communities
Charismatic leader of the
Group II Gavin McInnes
Let's have a radio show
Constantly talk about it
It's time to get vile
What does kick some ass
That's
What you think
You think that dumb f***
Millennials who you hate Alex who are listening to this sort of rhetoric from a charismatic
Guess some people
He's funny guy
Hellboy
This charismatic front
End of this
Violence
Being like all the time for us to get
Navigate those lights.
Teaching themselves
To protect against those people who are against
What's fascism
Yep they're a dangerous
If you're against fascism
Anti-Theft
Oh okay
Spoiler alert
Little bit later in the episode he's going to have a couple
So he thinks are proud Boys on
What are the music
That is where Rufio, scrubs at the pan man comes from hippie
Stomach how uncreated really are
Basically
The proud boy
Italy
She gets on the shows like I'm not a proud boy
I'm in between
And
We'll get it to him in a little
Alex
This
Poses
Yeah this next clip
IPad Pro
I'm in second Alex saying something
What if they make the entire plane out of the black box
The successful conversion
Salonpas
A large portion of people
Sure
52 about
Percent
Do you mean 15 to 35 and H
Okay
There is like a
They look at you and they think of you with a group
Well I don't look at groupthink
I do I don't look at you
Important to hold onto for a later clip
That literally
He's literally
They'll be shooting
You're so stupid
You should never have said that on air
If Authority arianism came around they be begging me to work for them
Call maybe they would insinuate themselves
In your company as
Second get you to support their very
Clearly
Authoritarian
Presidential candidate
For a very long time without
Real handicap
Propaganda
Populist in quote
You just sort of
Above
Partisanship
To hire somebody who had that
Realtor
Attempted authoritarianism
Is happening in front of our very eyes
Trying to hire Alex Jones and
You were successful
That's a f****** crazy thing for him to say
That's like
He's bragging and laughing about it without like
Recognizing
That babe
That really just track with my life
Yes
I got on there as soon as this one
Because he's unsure sums on the East Coast
He's a he's a f****** liar and a piece of s*** I have deep sources on that
Flash or couple months
Talking to this one guy who used to be his camp
Recruiting
Seriously in the past
6 months
There has never been
So many times where you listen to Alex talk in your life
You get it there's a there's a clutter
There's some like good Angel that's trying to escape from your mouth from time
Tell the truth
Way to look at it I think
More
It's just like
Alex
Kind of gift
What his place in
He's trying to express by
I'm not that f****** stew
I get what's going on
But
I don't know
You think this is almost his kind of
A very obvious wink to Rodger
In a stomach
Because like
I see him
Still just doing what he
He does
You know
Meanwhile all his friends are
F******
Rodger is probably
I still think he's gay
Dark sources
I don't think any of it matters
Like the clearing out the warehouses obviously in order to
Put
And then whatever however that works is how that works
I don't f****** know
What I do know is
Corsi is in
Deep water
Right now
Coming up
About where he has very few moves left on the board with you at all times
Plane ticket
Alex
Be concerned by
Concerned I don't mean like he's ignoring it and just like
No yeah
He's your right he called
Corsi a weasel
I think there's a decent chance
He has been
This whole time
No Alex
He's not dirty
In all this evil Continuum as more and more pieces
And Alex
It's one thing to do your like
Obfuscating nonsense
When there is like
Is
To do the exact same thing and not change
Strategy
That
That Flynn memo
Really freaked people
Like people especially people like Alex who have been
Presenting the idea that
Was
Part instrumental in the
Deal against Obama involving Russia and
I think the fact that Alex knows Vic
He said all those things
And it's new
Very clearly cooperating in a serious way with Mueller's investigation
People doing jail time
Skit about it either Alex thinks
Mothers
And Hoodwink them all
On some level Alex
I'm in the car
I was just getting in
Information from Liars
I wasn't that I wasn't doing anything illegal
I m radio show
3 degrees away from the crime that's not illegal
I think there's a part there's a freedom
For Alex
Probably the other people don't have
I think that plays into the Rogers
Yes we're not going to listen
Like there's nothing worthwhile
Thanks
K
Stories
Access to image
A cornucopia of Rodger Stone being like
Hey Adam Schiff go f*** yourself like
Year-and-a-half ago was all just like
Talking about him pleading the fifth
His position I actually think that this is fairly accurate
Based on Infowars
He's like this isn't news I said I was going to plead
The 5th before
That is accurate he has said that on Infowars
Portuguese
There's a chance the media's misreporting it as
Something's that he
Said before
I'm fine with that
His position on it
About
And that memo the Mueller memo that came out
He's like
Is a lot of stuff that's redacted in
We really don't know what's going on and I don't want to talk about it until there's more information
However I am buying a new plane ticket
Every single day
That's not something
Is it matches the
Games
Been playing all along
Cautious with who
His language
And Alex is trying to get him to
The old school Rodger
He's not playing ball
Just the clip that you did play of him being like
Yeah I got it
Okay
Yeah is him is him being like
Dude
We're
This b*******
We need a big
Call cuz I need more money
Yeah
I told you in that last clip there was a
Well no not the
There was a bad premise
Yeah that is
Millennial
We don't think anybody in groups
We're not we're not
Sure sure sure
Immediately after this
He starts to put people into
Saudi Arabia or Jordan origin
That's not how that works for bye
Group two
Proceed
F******
Two groups yet
Real hard to add the countries in there it's very quickly
Most
He's making In that clip Arab countries will take in Palestine
I would revert that
But he says
Next clip
And I'll do it after
What
Call Elise
Israel's going nowhere
Nowhere
Whatever I mean
I guess
Like in a
Sure every whatever I do I don't want to unpack that
Alex's position on Israel is so f******
Convoluted and changes over its
The nth degree I want to talk about this idea
Palestinian
Are just Arabs want to take over things
They already accepted anywhere else
Pacifically said
Free land to which is Sir
Yeah that's not fair is
We could talk about that for now
Freeland has a very different whatever you think
The Palestinians
To do yeah yeah that's a mess
Not the stock
Jordan
Egypt
But those are two countries that specifically going to talk
Pretty much entirely wrong about Palestinian
Immigration
I need to do debunked
His entire position
13 studies
The UN
Cuz all the statistics
Immigration
1 million Palestinians went to Georgia
50000 went 11
280000 to Libya 242
2002.
120,000 to Saudi Arab
A large percentage
Which of these people work
Considered
Of course they were
This reflected a bit of an acre
Census numbers for the migration policy
Century 2011
Still showed about 95,000
It's a Saudi Arabia
Text
In 2011
Canada population of 7395
Total
America is home to approximately 200
55,000
Ranking below Jordan syria-lebanon Saudi Arabia and
Three of those countries the ones that Alex was saying
Don't accept accept
One of the difficulties with emigrating
Propel propel
Quote
These are delivered by the Israeli authorities
Allowed access to
Airport in Tel Aviv
Palestinian holders of an identity document
Including those with 4in
Must pass through border post Reserve Palestinian
The Allenby bridge in Jericho
Is the only crossing point for West Point
West Bank Palestinians wishing to reach Jordan and travel further afield
It's fully controlled by Israel
They control outward immigration
A 2000 study out of the forced migration and
Ug studies program at
American University
In Cairo
Consistent level of
Percent of the world Palestinian population lived in Arab countries other than
Jordan
I specify that only because Jordan is considered individually
Statistics reflecting
Very high-powered
All this is to say that has no f****** idea what he's talkin
And all this reflected
The deep-seated bigotry
Being present
Did as knowledge
And in that clip he's yelling about people
These double leftist to come up
And say hey you should support Palestinians
We know that in 2019
The absolutely
Very strongly
Wishi-washi wano not in like a dairy in favor of the Palestinian issue
Not even like a Israel to be able to
It was like hey
Rights
He knows it he have that position
Then which is
Completely
Any presenting this idea of left
Just to come up to him and they're like hey you know all this and he's mad because
You guys don't have statute
10 minutes
Has yielded a number of statistic
Victor Punk
Entirely his idea that there's
No Palestinians in Saudi Arabia
Jordan has so many
Palestinian
Crazy
Bananas
I'd like to imagine that so much of
Alex's
Leftist
Talking points
Just came up to me on the street
Just I just travel traveling him that's just hanging around
You remember when you believe this
You suck know what it is is like you probably had a dream
Cancel
You come
F****** dumbass
I'm guessing
Just guilt
It's just dumb
Guilt about his hand position
Understanding
Is advocating
Like being killed for no reason I was against that
For whatever reason I'm now super into it
Who knows what that is
Crazy
But this is so f******
Stupid
Thank you don't even have
Support Palestinian rights
To think that that's stupid
No that's even if you're against
The Palestine
Making an argument
Arab countries
Don't accept Palestinian
He's crazy.
Not even noted propagandists and liar Bibi Netanyahu it like that
Pamela Geller would say
Something like that
That but
But Alex
Think about that stuff
Good
Feeling the spirit starts yelling about how West
Countries are under attack
Market
Porsche
Mexican
You do
He saying already like the idea of like
To not worship
You think that atheists are a satanic organization
Future
What if you're in Palatine
Millennial
Now Alex is taking that 44%
44% interested in socialism
7% each for communism and fascism
Making up number
45%
That's a point
I don't agree with that
Yeah I know that's right
Molesting
You can just be conniving
That works nothing in China
Market
Cam
Okay wow
That's nuts
All right without man
It wasn't embarrassing enough
Crafts nonsense Betty just pulled their
This next clip
I honestly think
Is one of my favorites
Enjoy this
Because you talkin some s***
On h w
Right
Blankets into Howard
The bushes
Skull and bones
They are
He gets into
Evidence
Coral
Choir music of a
HW Bush's.
Ongoing
Worship
Juxtaposed
Robert De Niro's production of the Good Shepherd
Bathing in feces
Pissing on each other
Bring up a movie
Have sex
Yeah but we all want
Channel the devil
What is Pantheon of other gods and goddesses entering your body
Next two weeks
Almost sacred
Yep
To each other
De Niro movie that he
He's talking about
Because I know at least one point I got that I'm just looking for the audio
But later I know that I heard Joshua Jackson
Voice
So he's also playing clips from the skull
God Rest his soul
Paul Walker
Please play these movies about Scala bugs that are
Proof
These people f****** Fiji
Also
Also come on
That would be a great General are you shiting me
You're giving
Alex
You think it's ironic it is great
I just like
Everything is a goddamn movie
He doesn't understand
Differentiate
I don't f****** know what to do with it but
Like I said
We got
Some proud boy
Slash proud boys
We're going to end this episode
But here in a little bit from them
Rufio panman
Very
Roofied
He doesn't really talk
Here's a really factor into this interview much cuz he's been on Alex's show before where is
Margot
Has never been on the show before
Just saying the exact same thing out
I'm trying to be like I'm at you with this rally I was with you
That sort of thing there's like a
A Maga Titan might be starting
Like a Blog on one of Alex's lights
I'm not getting involved with Infowars somehow
I don't think
I don't give two
Sucks about anything like that
Eveready website
Ever apart of
I don't want to be a part of
Any website that has a byline
Maga Titan
I don't want to be a member of any club that has
Classic comedy
Look I don't want
The interview is not really Illuminating separate them all three of them all being like
Were victims
Of course
Redundant us
You you guys get about everyone being Cox and then you
Entire race videos Wild
There's a couple things that I think are
Interesting
Here's the first one
This is how I woke up
They folded the $20 bill if you guys have ever seen this is TuneIn right now.
The bill
On one side
The Pentagon on the other side
9 + 11 is 20
United Airlines on one side American Airlines on the other side
I started looking into 911
Course
9/11 the road to tyranny popped up
So you found a dollar hold on it
9 + 11 + 9/11 equals 20
$20 bill
American Airlines
Why
Be harder
Really fun page on Snopes
Where they talk about this urban legend of folding the dollar bill
Exactly what they're talking about inside
Most of the
Dollar bills in circulation all the forms of bills we have
Include bushes and buildings and
You fold them up in the right way you can make it
Look like
Squires building fire
And then further
If you fold up a dollar bill just the right way you can also make it
Because it's more fun
You do this with foreign currency
Cuz there's some I don't know what I don't remember what country is a show
It looks like two
Badgers
You fold up money bunch of different ways you can create a bunch of pictures that you want
So
Maga
Got woken up by folding goddamn $20 bill
Any better I would argue that like if he is a millennial
Is Bear Creek a great now
If that's if that's the way you want to do it if that's your example
Do not desecrate so here's the last clip where a little bit more from Maga
Do you know how Einstein found
The
General theory of relativity
The special theory of relativity
Was
He folded up a silver
That
Was actually
She might folded it up and then
I heard travel Texas
Is he swallowed a nickel
My
I just did that cuz we have to get the news out there and hand we have to to report what's going on I mean
Admitted that they had intelligent life small human being alien beings here on Earth
Now you're in my territory troll that's how it was born
Okay. All right path
Alex I think you might be getting trolled in this interview I'm not really sure I can be considered.
The stuff you says it's really just like
If look through the prism of someone just trying to
Use Alex Jones's platform in order to
To create a name for themselves in terms of agreeing with Alex about everything
And then the troll piece of it could be
I got woken up by folding a $20 bill allowing that to be on his show anywhere.
Giving recognition of that
He's done to my Capri
That's nice
Thank you Bill.
I started this
Community of the news on NASA just
Humanoid aliens been here in the past
That story is not
Didn't answer
Stop know there was a guy who works for NASA
Who gave a speech to study
Search for extraterrestrial intelligence
Yeah there was a write-up of a species arguing
DIA
That perhaps
The idea
Aliens have been here
Before
Isn't something we should discount out of
If you want to study those things
There's no reason not to apply the same scientific rigor.
Scientist goes in front of other scientists and says
Maybe we should do science ideas scientist life
But
Did they do they're better than Project Camelot
So what was
Was on the one hand
People who are arguing
The aliens have been
He should adopt scientific
Method
And if
X
You are studying these sorts
Shouldn't dismiss out-of-hand things that look absurd
But should
Humor them and treat them with the same
You know
There was a write-up of
Of his
Andy got
Misrepresented
Thai places like Fox News
And also
A comment at all journalists ecclesiastical reported
NASA scientist says that aliens probably
And now Margot Robbie Margot I control is coming on Alex's shows like we got to get the news out to here
Maybe a humanoid intelligent aliens been here in the past
Like a dumb game of telephone
It's awesome
These people are f******
Guys are having a great time
Until they're not
Which Rodger probably won't be
But like what we have here
The big
Of this episode
Kind of fun
Is it
Remember
There's an episode in 2050
Where Alex
Was like
Today I'm going to jump the shark
I am going to
Yeah yeah I remember that intentionally make an argument to bait the media into covering me
In order to start the conversation
I want all Muslims taken out of the country
Vlog van
Right interesting Arc to me
Of like Alex thinking
We're going to misrepresent him
And then accidentally kind of stating his own position
Yep it was a very weird
Relationship
I had the same sort of feel to me
I was like this
Alex's now laying down
What the groundwork of the episode
He's laid out the
The blueprint
Yeah I have a bunch of stories that are going to build to a bigger store once again just a line
He's a bunch of stories that are going to be
They're going to add up to something bigger than the Sun
The only reason that you know not
You don't have to
Gifted
Read between the lines
Of his own story
So in presenting
His b*******
2 stories
What you end up with is him
Just trying
Demon eyes
Millennials
I tried to say that they're the ones
We're going to take away all the
People Like Us
Moral people the producers in society
Exactly
So that is what the end result
Blueprint
That's the building that he was
He was trying to
Direct
Edwin
You apply the exact same
He was doing
Constellation
I can take new stories
Alex has been kicked off YouTube
Alex has been kicked off Twitter
Alex's audiences diminishing
Alex is trying to sell everything in his f****** Warehouse
Alex's
Weirdly demonizing the youth
Hey you can do the same thing make a constellation out of it
Oh that points to is
Five finger
Oh yeah
Pentagon
For the week
Because I was an angel
Constellation
Futsal fold-up dollar bills
So anyway the point is I can't prove it Alex's audience
You think this thing is him I can do a better job of making an argument
That explains his rhetoric
I'm just fascinated by things
Like when
I have been in
This game
For as long as I have and I can like
I see what you doing yeah that's what it I love it
Pennywise
Look it's a weird completely useless gifts outside of this show I feel like
I should have been able to gather
Based on the amount of time that I have been playing this game
Somehow I am still
Delightfully ignorant
Once again proving that I know nothing about Alex
But at the same time
I guess I would say
If you had the
Couple hours
To sit around and
Think about
Who sings this
This
These stories aren't really
Connected
What's the point here
Dstat out
Create
Dispatched
Fear and misery and paranoia but there was a specific track he was trying to go on which was
I have these stories
You don't realize are connected but actually are
That is not something
Somebody fumbling around accident
And I see that from
Enough to know I don't
That it is
Just some
Stupid person I think someone
Inveterate liar
But who trying to
I don't I don't know
I don't I don't know if we're going to go
Get to the bottom of any
But
Hi all my all my point is this
I enjoyed
No no
That's
Kind of why
I still find
It does kind of Boggle my mind from time to time like
Why am I feeling
It is a never-ending onion
But I think
Reflect
Because a lesser
Talented
Persimmon Alex would have
Said the n-word on air
Given up so much
That they would be like
I need some could argue that
Is Sandy Hook behavior is
Like the example of
Alex
At least in the hundreds
Devours that I've listened
Outside if I guess
The couplings
Do you like skulls
Zimbabwe Road
Yeah that one
Muslim girls at a pool
Supplies shop
Come out
But like
Done
It is another version of
But he's able to be his racist overtly super
Spectacular
So that keeps
Interested
Is always
When are you going to just say the n word
It's always just do it
Yes
Yeah
On Monday
I need this is been our show Alex
In present-day but at least a little more
What do you see
The shape of it
For what it is
But
Knowledge buy.com social media
That's the way to go I don't even think we should bother with our Facebook
Text Alexa
Indeed you can download leave a review
To the end of this episode in Jordan what's on my mind
Maga Titan
Play himself out a little bit
The by explaining
He's a troll
Meme kind of guy
Almost almost there. I really just like the antagonizing
Talk around it's not going to kill somebody
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work