Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Little bit about Alex
Yes sir
Weird
Halloween
Things to sew
Easter candy Bass
Holiday
Is pumpkin
Bassett peppermint bark
He's probably out there
Bark
Disgusting
Peppermint bark
Yeah but that's
Because
It's a perversion of chocolate
Scrape
There's a tradition in my family of like
Send me
Every year
Forever of Williams-Sonoma peppermint bark
No I don't think maybe
Gusset
I could be wrong
A yearly thing
My grandma was the entire all of the kids in my family
These like
Commemorative Lifesavers containers that he ever
The book of Lifesaver rolls
Pic of that knots out of course it is
The single greatest
Peanut brittle throw you straight out the window
I don't know these
I hear holiday candies but I know more about Alex Jones
Littleton on about boats
I guess
Talking about
John Birch Society
Yep is a Candyman
We've it altogether libertarianism
Indeed
Back in the past 2000
And I'll be going over the March
27th
Episode
The ad the John Birch Society
President on the show
Pinterest
Anything is Possible
Stay so I'd like to take a moment to say thank you
Do some of the people who have
And are supporting the show House and helping us to keep the lights on
You're not allowed to say that
You are now policy
Thank you Michael
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you all so much
Tonight
Celebrate
Are in the world
I'm sorry also.
You to someone who is coming in a little bit of a higher level
Appreciate it I'm so very much
Isobar
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean black accent
Thank you so much
Must've been real tough to live through 95 with that name right
Right there
Well a certain Bob Dole was running for president
Confused like maybe you're a relative of Jimmy soul
If you want
Mistaken for him
It's just so prevalent that song dad
That song in High School
The only reason I know that song or I can probably take it off the top of my head
You yeah it's
Weird it's because that was the
Friday song
That our teacher played
Broadcast production class in high school
Always be
It's Friday
If you want
What's your name
In hindsight problematic Choice Realty
Anyway
A lot of weird stuff
Push us into the door jamb on our way out of class everyday
F***** up teacher
Anyone knew he was doing it
Coach Hawkins
Good day good day
Friends later after I hit
Google login
Every story you have about your high school really just kind of outlines either some sort of child abuse or
Mysterious and dangerous
Tough time
Yeah I'm sorry
I was my knob
We went a little too far
Bizarre life
It's Monday
President of the John Birch
Society
Immediately, into any
That's not really important
Necessarily
Context
An important Frameworks
Understand
Moving forward in Alex's
Especially
There are
Interesting
Trends that happened
Website
Super abundantly
Play clearly the f****** sovereign
Definitely
It's a few square miles within the city of London itself
Financial
I don't really understand fully what Alex is the idea that like this
Vatican is private
Country with it
Speedy country but not necessarily that the city of Rome is like that
But with bangs
Because later he says that
Is Washington DC the District of Columbia is that but with me
Okay
We held cities
In the world and you have like
The
The Rome and London to city of London or banking
And then watch
PCS military
Exactly know what all of that amounts to
But
Look I'm going to look into that more I don't really understand what he's talking about and there are not
Like ready resources on this
Lines between the three of them
Like a triangle
You are
Pictures of
Exactly what is the devil sign
Triangle
System
Modern
Yes that is what they called
For Rome to Greece
I digress
You do
Until proven innocent
Blah blah blah blah
That's all Sovereign Center
It's all
Wacky
Distance and how well they know history by just naming
You must know history
Yeah Alexandria
I'm guessing
He just has like
I've already forgotten all those cities
But it seems like most of them had pork
It's really hard to do Orleans
Position
Sklep Alex
Become very
Very normal
On our show
Him giving a prosthetic warnings
That what they are doing
People they will soon
Be doing to white people
Situation you better get ready
Worse and worse and worse I mean we are in 40 trouble because
Contract racetrack everywhere k
And from here on out it becomes hit larian
Start dying here and in Europe soap ready to die
Okay
Fix that
Guess what's behind Diaz at like the globalist are not touch up
Until they have full control
I guess I guess what's behind that
Is that like they know that we're the only ones who are capable of
I'm not entirely sure
No idea
All that stuff is
Also just
The little building blocks
Just needs a little dump narratives
The globalist they're climbing the mountain
A conquest
And what's at the top of that mountain
About the white cat
To start it does
Baseline
Likewise
Let me know
Privacy
But white
Primacy
Important
They're the best
Yeah
Whoops
Honey whyte's
The part of the beginning
When I was making
Alex
Having
John Birch Society president on the day before
It does show up a little earlier than
Because in this next clip
Alex Jones
Goes
Whole Hog
He starts attack
Taking him
Aggressive
The John Birch Society
It doesn't matter if I have thousands of government documents Congressional testimony
How to terrible with pronoun reference stories about
There is Glenn Beck at someone on
Just got the
Realities and falsehood
Of all the stories
The internet about
The feud began
Whenever Glenn Beck inexplicably chose somebody to
Pick through the lies of somebody else who was lying
About stuff that he's also lying about what of this clip
Seem very light
Non suspicious
Just that Alex's
Because
He has said things like it got to look out with this
This guy a little bit early
I don't know about him
Not that sort
Yeah yeah
In line with Alex
To a certain extent
This goes on
You'll start to
But
Alex's.
Chronicles Associated Press
You are
Halo probably said am I
St.Louis
Not really
I'll tell you the truth about them
What are the place to find out if it's true
All this stuff
News articles
You're misrepresenting followers and Ron Paul Allen
Chuck Baldwin all those guys got together
Big enough
Representation of it
Got the box
Redacted
When Paul said that only three people
In the middle of the night has misrepresented
Impatient
Critique
Making stuff up
Isn't that he's making up
Interpretation of it
Dishonest way
Now the thing that I want to bring sharp Focus
Is
Alex's
Complaint about Glenn Beck
Seems to be mostly
He's not extreme enough
Or
When he's
Stream
He's lying
So there's this
There's this
He came out and he was talk
Talking about the New World Order
And how what you need
We worry about it we're going to look into it
The part where Alex's
Is cool with it
But then what
Like we looked into it and a lot of this stuff that's going around is
True
He's
Either just talkin about
New World Order In
Ricky went to believe in him only
Do have him say it's not true all right
Enough
Get it right
Either of those the
Things are possible
But the primary
It is
He's not
Putting out the rhetoric
I want put out
The world
Now in this next clip Alex talks about the
It might not
Surprise you too much
Do you hear her make
Almost
The exact
Same criticize
The only thing I hear right now is to Liars getting into about who lies the right way
Surface that is kind of
But there's more
More forces at play here
What do you understand that
Philosophy
It's kind of like the John Birch Society
Associated Press article
Where they tried to bribe the police chief another's
Antonio Express-News
But I am
And you know what the public
Show
McManus
In here yesterday the present
Knowing about this one.
My Dad's friend
Bookshelf
Storage things for
Ruin my life
Does youth service Corps in
Well that's in one of the bills to start
The New York Times
So you here
Important
If you base elements of that clipart
At the beginning
He's talking about how the John Birch Society had this guy there who was reporting on stuff that Alex knew wasn't correct
So he got in touch with them
I meant they corrected their behavior and
Very positive
Version of this not be
Yeah
Accidentally found this book that the course of
His life when he was a child or whatever
And then get you
You talkin to me
McManus
Degrees on him
Extremely
Supposition
And Alex
This
Article
Do you know is assuming that John
Stream because of the influence
Exerted on him parallel situation okay
His feelings about Glenn Beck
Feelings about the
John Birch Society
Run
Almost similar track
Not extreme enough
But we can make it better
I was struggling to that story that story was like a game of Chutes and Ladders
Spell and we're back in
His childhood or whatever it is
Is it going on
He came for workout
Convoluted
I'm an extemporaneous speaker
You're just a
Go to beach
I just I think that's very
No
Sara Lee
Memestube
But it does
Reflect some
So
His view on these guys is that they don't go
For the most part where he's coming from now is you guys are in extreme extreme enough in your the New World Order is
Kill Everybody
More life
Does he other than his apocalyptic they're controlled plague releases
Does he have any like
Opinions that they are
Extreme enough on you know what I'm saying but well I mean he's he's of course saying that the New World Order is
Doing everybody
Yeah
And they're not
But agree or disagree with anything that they are sick
I think your glory that they're over the formerly
I think the matter of scale not a matter of
I think that's
Clear
Patty and security
I'm not I'm not sure
But
It does lead to Alex talking about Glenn
Quite a bit
On the show next clip
He complains
About
Glenn Beck and John Byrne
Society
And then starts complaining about the very idea that people complain about other people
Christian
Norfolk Christian website
System basically
What are fake Christians
If I speak in Sheraton Hotel in La I don't work for Sheridan AR
Pause for a second
The point out that that's exactly the
Inverse of a lodge
Victor uses about Margaret Sanger giving a speech women of the KKK
When you do it you're wrong when I do it I'm right
This is crazy
Facebook
Critiquing
So he just went from saying that they're not extreme enough
Amen singer Christian website is trying to
Complain about
Yeah this whole thing has been largely
Complaints about people who are
Berkeley on the same side as you have roseola
We spent too much time complaining about people not working
Is there complaining about him
And he's complaining that they're complaining
And there's too much complaining going on
And you complaining about that this particular instance
Places email is made up
Forwarded
Nothing
Complaining about about Glenn Beck
Society
Those are complained that they're making Alex complaining about them
In the instance of Glenn Beck
It's not complaining
It's disgusting
Misinformation
The people like Alex are perpetuating
So not to defend going back in anyway
But Vicky
Complained that out says about him is
He's pushing back on my nonsense
Where is
You know his
Complained
Is people
People complain I don't know it's it's
He's Alex's version has much less tubs
Distance to it
If only because Glenn Beck
Just talking about like
Oh this is a misrepresentation misreading
This bill or whatever
Everyone complains about me we spent too much time complaining and complaining all the
Process
As
Doesn't have one
Like
Here's the thing
I don't like that
And even though it's a thing that I'm doing
To do
I think it's a bad thing
There's a strong feeling that like
I'm not positive
He knows what he's saying in the middle of us
But he said stuff like that
Yeah that's a good boy like I'm not sure he doesn't
Like I'm not sure you understand
But it doesn't
Doesn't have anything
The middle or the last
Since before it
Outright contradict
Score is the convoluted story
Patikim over little details
Jobs
So far was the
This better business
What I'm saying
I think it's a snake
Text clip really dead
Because what we see is out I think
But he's been a little bit more severe about going back in
In the past that you like
But
Mostly I kind of agree that
Critiques of Glenn Beck
Exacerbated
Not
Attacking him
In the past
Not necessarily attacking
But like staying
You probably
Up to something
And it's like not
Treating him like a Target
Yeah yeah I think that's fair
Me and what time
But personal attacks that were so used to seeing from Allison
Look at his dumb hair he's probably a pedophile
Yeah
Things are going to change
And now I'm looking
I'm not as
Some inconsequential
Inconsequential person
That you should be wary of
But now is a targ
Months ago
I said the supporters and FEMA camps
With Al-Qaeda and
Psychological manipulation
Popular Mechanics
You supply the pictures I'll Supply the war
Barely folks that are always calling for police
More
A guy from Popular Mechanics
Glenn Beck enlisted to
Yellow journalism
Because he has to attack the store
But if you want to play that game
Then fine Alex
You are a show that
Distributed by Genesis
Communications
That works which is owned by Ted Anderson
Who owns Midas resource
Create agenda
Medications net worth
Advertising arm of Midas
You have people on all the time who just try and create Panic food sell gold
So I mean we can play that game
You're a thoroughly
But it is a f****** South African rapist who believe in Rhodesia
So there you go
I don't know if it is
Nurses office
This knife Cuts both Direct
I think you should probably
Give a pass for first publishing owning Popular Mechanics
Unless you have specific
Complain about
Person
Or any
They are now going to court.
Very underwhelming
The research
I want you to make
Jamaica Coronavirus
And I can piggyback Glenn Beck success
The dependent brings up there as his
Example of
Can't prog
It really is just about
Creating
The private prison
The idea that you can make
Inmates work
Yeah I know that's flavor is labor
If you want to talk about that in the realistic
Segway I would really appreciate
But if he wants to fold it into this FEMA camp nonsense
Then it what it does is diminish
The ability to work against the actual evil that he
Pretends to be
We complaining about
So
That to me is a problem
The other problem here
Think what I think is going on
That's just my theory
And it
I didn't know about this episode when we recorded the episode about him interviewing the John Birch
And we talked about
The connections with
Koch brothers
Freedomworks
Citizens
54 Prosperity Americans for Prosperity
A sound economy
Like all of these
I didn't know that
The next day Alex
Hard on Glenn Beck
When I
Brought up those connections
You know that I'm not reading this
I'm saying like
He's mad at Glenn Beck probably
He's now creating the
Sing
Here here
This is tough to put into work
Is it Alex
Creating
The appearance
Because
It is
This is where it's at
Conspiratorial
I think it might be in the same way Meek Mill versus Drake when they both have an album coming out and it boosted
Glenn Beck is even necessarily
Lord knows what's going on right
But I
Strategy where
Ostensibly
You have that
Have a petty argument
Of some sort
And what you do is you
To create a rattle
Radicalization
You know like
It's it's a perfect
Chamber wherein
Because it's easy
If you're like a Fox News watcher
Or you're somebody who
Has inclination
Towards the right it's really easy to fall into
Glenn Beck
It's more difficult to fall into Alex Jones
He is much more extreme
Yells about s*** all the time
He references documents that he wants you to read that you'll never be able to find
All this stuff is very confusing
To the the immediate
Glenn Beck
Is very easy
So
Baby step
From sort of normal well-meaning conservit
Motive can be to go to Glenn Beck
Right right, Glenn Beck's van
You get
Sort of used to that temperature of water
Then there's someone who is out there who's yelling The Glenn Beck is a fraud
And the two of them have it
A beef
It may or may not be one-sided
And what does
Create the opportunity
Need to jump from the
Sort of warm water of going back into
To be scalding hot water of Alex Jones without
Like noticing it's so hot and burning
Hey
Is it from that
Light on
Is people who want to push the
Further to the right
Yeah
People are leaving from Glenn Beck to go to Alex Jones
Incredibly hot water
That is going to heat up his own water in order to get those people
Because if he gets too hot
Which may actually accidentally
Then what happened
I don't know
I don't think that this is necessarily what happen
But I would not be
Be surprised at all
Glenn Beck
Thought in his rise to promise
Also
Eventually paying out
Alex Jones
To serve as
The more extreme version
I think that's a result of their purpose
Credibly well
I fall short of saying that I think that that's
McKay's
Is because it is
Crazy things
What's the business verticals vertical integration
It's controlling the entire eat you control the entire method production
I feel
About
Nature
I find it very difficult
Circle 2
Look at the picture that we have in
In front of us knowing what I know
Like for example
I know
Did Alex Jones is deadlocked
Calling avoyelles Revenue
From the lands that he owned
In Texas
Pretty recently before this
I know that Alex Jones moved into a new studio where the rent was higher
Around this time
I know that he just had the John Birch Society president on
And change the number of his position
Mid interview
With him
I know that freedomworks in Americans
For prosperity
Funnel tons
Money and they are run by the
The children of
One of the founding members
Society
I know that a couple months
After this episode
So I know what number is
Things that make it look
Really difficult for
To not think
There's something up here
And the fact that the day after the John Birch Society president
Was on the show
Alex
Pivot
His position on Glenn Beck
From being someone who
He's like an annoying
GameFly your shoe in the way
The probably not great news I don't want to hang out with them but I'm not going to I'm not going to get into a fight with them
Now being like he's a danger
Yeah I don't know how else to look at that
Other than through like
It's f****** weird
Right
Yeah
I could just
Feels like
The easiest way I can
Can explain that is
Alex needs bunny
You know someone who's got money
Serves the purpose
Yeah
Werther's where there's smoke
There is probably Nazis burning books in a fire
This could be nothing
It could be nothing I could be making a mountain out of a molehill
I don't know
But the facts on the ground lead me to
You think this is something I got it
I got to keep my eye on
And look into a little bit more
So we'll see
As time goes on
But
But you
Straight up just doing
You just ends up
Keeps on dunking on Glenn Beck
Here at this point he invites Jason bermas onto the show
Have a little bit of a s*** on Glenn Beck special
The best thing about this Alex aguiar
Pressure OverWatch
He's telling us the truth about the financial
He's very proud that over a quarter-million people have joined
Really turns in my stomach I mean this guy is fine
11 hour call to service day and
Are you guys f****** talking about
Malicious
There is something up
Barrage
Lies that they're telling it's almost past each other
They like I don't even know if they're talking about the same
Instinct
Back is following the Maya
He's following you
I don't know
I don't know how you would fall
The descriptive report they put a little piece of wood and they have the
Fruitless
This is something that is very interesting to me
We'll have to see how it plays out and I was really hoping
Visit Friday
Until like I was really hoping this Sunday's episode
Would give me more insight into this
The whole thing is just an interview with Webster.
I don't want to talk about
Guitar play
Why we will later but
Because Alex is trying
So I think he's going to be
He's going to take a
Like sort of
Tough situation
Is it like his
Tire show on
This is all just an interview
That's because
So he's using that as
Platform okay
The
Reflux beef
Hibbett in the change that happens over time we're now Sunday shows are kind of like
Whereas before they were where
You could actually get much more Market
It's interesting
I don't know how to say
Synthesizer
But there is a clue somewhere
Going to make it all makes
Probably
For now
Much like Alex Jones in the past about Glenn Beck
I'm weary
Call boy I got my eyes open but I will see
We are you are looking for
Where in the world is Blair in the world
We see another thing that's a little bit in
And that is
Hellboy
Until this point Alex Jones did not know about
Garage
You still going by Stephen yaxley-lennon
I think he's actually in 2009 I think he was in
Straight up Nazis
I'm pretty sure if I recall his timeline correctly
He was like operating anonymously as the leader of the you like European
In front European Defense
Oh that's not good
Goodnotes
The ebl
Bring bring
It kind of old
Reinforces your Theory on
Alex Jones
So much money
Why would they
That we're so used to seeing fund all these
Right-wing lunatics
Also fund
If they weren't also funding all kinds of out now.
And further to the
The point why would you not find out
Exactly
That's the other thing that's kind of has like a tough
Head scratcher
With
With this
I don't I don't know
Are you like
Clear that
Someone's
You kept any plays along compilation
I've just completely out contacts
Text clips
I'd like Nigel farage yelling at Gordon Brown
On the floor
He does know
Lord Vox
At this point
So he's aware of Lord monckton as someone who's like climate changes
He doesn't know Nigel farage garage doesn't show up on his show until a couple months down the line
He doesn't really know about the UK independence party
He's not particularly interested in it except for like
Broader speaking
Trends
But he has about like
Getting rid of it
Stuff like that
It's interesting cuz
Who plays this long
Long compilation
Mirage yelling on the
Lafleur
And then
You come back
Spring break with
Republic
Oh boy
It's interesting
It's really interesting
2 mi to feet
Now being
Folded into
Do Alex's World immediately after the interview with a John Birch Society
We see the introduction of the
Presents
Of the UK independence party and Nigel
Mirage
Being someone that Alex
Not by name cuz I don't think he knows his
At this point even
You never say never
Yes he does like these guys are really giving it to the idea of Greater Britain
Being in the world
You should know
You should be able to talk about this more if you're as much of an expert
But it's here
And it's a huge part of his stuff moving forward
Resistance to globalism
EU is Nigel farage in UK
So this is the beginning of that
So this is the beginning of our International nationalist Alliance
In 2009
Astroneer
Use the Russian angle on the
Ukrainian gas prices
Russian side like
And so this is true of so much of Nigel farage and you kept it all that s***
They too are funded by right-wing billionaires in the United
So that we start to see this coming at this time
That's right while all of these guys are together and this is the first time that Alex starts bringing up
UK lunatics
Alongside him
The John Birch Society
Or having him on the Shelf
Not meeting for the first date they talked before
But there does seem to be a
It's just it's a lot
It's a lot and I don't really like I don't
It's tough for me to do this as a show
Because I don't want to put out into the
The world's would lead one of our listeners.
This is now a Broad City of all these things
We need to find
Whatever indications
We can find
And as we look into it if we find things
Prove
Whatever we're suspecting
I'm fine with that runs down the line and it gets like
Doesn't work
Alex
Getting money that week
Thank you. We had during our 2015 investigation
Like we're speculating
And then two days later
Understand
We're coming from
Not a position of Authority or
Knowing
Where to position
Pieces
That look weird
And we'll see if it
Is puzzle piece
Together
Picture that we think it will be wrong
The other thing too is that like
I would understand
A criticism of the speculation that
If there's only one or two
If you will achieve just the president of the John Birch Society was on his show and then the next day he insulted
I wouldn't think that
The world
That would be the bigger
Bedroom
Alex does
Say that he's wrong
Right
Yeah that makes sense with that
Little pieces around it
It just smells bad
It does I don't know
So anyway
We are also starting
9:30
Which
Encourages everybody
Kickback
9:13 the day after
Glenn Beck started his 912 movement
And how it made you
You feel
And that is that Glenn Beck is a huge ship
There's also
Yeah
How did the
Yeah I don't have
A handle on it
Nebulous in stupid concept that it was hard.
I think it was I think it was pretty specific
It was trying to recapture that feeling you had all night
9 principles and 12 guidelines or whatever
If there's a lot of ways to criticise him I don't think that's why
Lookbook
Who gives a
All they know is a baby
Need to start attacking Guam
Now at this point
Oh I should also say coincidentally
Another piece of my constellation is
Bob Chapman's on this app
Sell gold
They don't talk about it at all cuz Alex
Too busy tried to complain about Glenn Beck
So
There is a
Replacement of normal roll on the Shelf
Episode in months
Did Bob Chapman didn't exist
Specifically
To set up Alex on the volleyball court to spike a gold
Chapman's on here at all
Is just on as a like soda guy to agree with Alex
Wow you complaining about Glenn Beck
And all of these
Which vacuum you just be like well
Alex's
Bitching and so when the spirit gets good to him
Amidst all of the other data points
Complete honesty
See I have heard episodes
Where Bob Chapman's Auto
They don't sell gold
But they are
Rare
They are all
Probably heard
Yeah it's not like it never happened
So it's within the realm of like
It could be a real crazy
Coincidence
Anyway what are those three times
I assume where they held a surprise party on
Anniversary of Rhodesia
Virginity right that was the other one they just said such Brody for a while
Appearance but we are going
With another guy
Alex
Has a guy on
For good
Or so
This guy
Certification for naturopathic doctors
Clear
Cheez-It
Certified naturopath
That's pretty awesome
Here's another little bit of
Doctorate of naturopathy from the International School
Masterpass in Los Altos California
Google
Chapathi in Los Altos California
It's not even the University of Phoenix online
Even more interesting you don't even find reviews of a fake school or website
Mailing address
Psyche look into any of
Here's the course now you can take it we're not
That's where the thing
In fact
If you Google the name of the school
All you will find our links
To dr. Scott Whitaker in his book medicine
Appeared
Grip
Confirm this but it appears that the only place this name for a school
Is in his bio
Not the fun part about this
Did you know that I have that the fun part about this
Most natural path doctor
Realized
The very real threat
I decided to cut out the middleman
Just make up a school
Thousands of dollars
To get it
Even if it's just a couple
Still saving
You shouldn't even really have to pay tikos just print it out on your home printer
Did that
Ginkgo biloba
Experience
Holistic medicine
Attritional
Detoxification
Sound trustworthy
About 9 country study
Ceiling fans over Naf
Janasia bringing them back to America and using them and applying
Phenomenal results
Everyone
Contact weird recording
Which
Approach
The healing
Is the only way I go
Nothing but a death trap
To do anything else except for go that route
But
Real Hospital
That sounds right
They do have a high rate of infection
Deathtrap
What if you break your leg strap
Because it is next clip
He does explain Whittaker does explain but there are some instances
Wearing you should go to office
But the hospitals are
Set up there all
Set up
A drug charge
The only
Reason or purpose to throw everyone go to hospital
Emergency
Emergencies
Amputation
You can forget it there is no cure ever
Yeah except or gunshot
No reason given
I think it really goes without saying that like this is a really dangerous line of thought
Really f***** up for Alex
Because
There's so much more that hospitals do
Just because you wanted demonize Diane
Because you're afraid that
You know I don't know regulations
Things are going to start popping up
Make your scams untenable
Or illegal
To pull off
I don't know that they aren't already create a Grassroots
Awakening of people who are
Think the doctor is
Some hospitals just be a deathtrap
You know there's so much preventive medicine that is saved
Millions of lives
Over the years that have nothing to do with
Crisis emergency
Medicine
This is this is a ludicrous thing for someone to be saying it
Borders on
Gleefully Danger
Ill-advised
At the very things that he's describing the hospitals do
Also include
The other things that hospital it's not like a surgery is just
They
World all surgeries are just a Tatian
Like your break it like they're just like
Performing a surgery
Involved involved
And also usually means
How to control infection and maybe frostbite
Holistic medicine
That's not to say that like
Are medical
Call system even take out the financial last
It works
Every time we got it all down
But it is
Far and Away better than your herb nonsense
Yeah
Holistic medicine
Stop.
Placebos
There's that part of results
I support structure
Dua LIPA
It's not right to demonize all of it
But there was
Like an old Loveline episodes dr. Drew
If all of this
Herb base
Natural healing
Work
There would be no reason that medicine would have ever developed
There is no reason that you would have ever come up with all this stuff no one would have studied
B H & H
Failed experiments that lead to the 1641
If all of it was already taken care of
It's got to be took
Memories
Epic Madison
In order to have a monopoly
But they don't really want a monopoly on medicine for healing
They want it for deathtrap
A lot of nickels to create MRI machine
Yeah
Natural
Cures
And stuff probably did help
A lot more in
Earlier time
Japan history
But
More
Pollution
Change.
Conditions that
Have changed
Because of
Assertive
Human
World interaction
But we have inner tubes
The things like smallpox
To everyone
All those things didn't necessarily exist
Before
They probably wouldn't have been
Natural medicine
Nothing we could do about that
Which is kind of the same thing
Mr.
Put that on my side
Board certified by made-up nonsense
Second
I'm a chance over you while you die
Who said it was
What's Google it
You can't trust that
Have revenant
Like
Fake diploma Mail UK
Confined
Version of
Oh that's what they say
His bio
You're absolutely right
Why would you
Pay somebody for the fake degree when you can just make it up your
Self
To the same problem
Real fake
Have the pretend authority to stay there
People who may need actual medical advice
I just don't see the difference between
No I agree they have the same problem
Saudia
Whitaker w
You give
Analogy
Start of a condemnation of the medical establishment
And it's really into
The way you phrases
Petco
There is no cure
Are becoming
The medical establishment
If they don't want a cure
Keep you
Play can drain your account
New it
Can you often
The grave
You're right
I love a good
I love a good Alex doesn't have anything to say so he says
You're right
So I wanted you to pay close attention to that because
Interesting
Conception
For that is the idea
ChapStick and
Healthy
Keep you in a state where they can
In your bank account
Now let's look at Alex Jones
What he does is
Is keeps his audience in the state where they're constantly
About to be
The victims of genocide is over the
These genocide
Eugenics courses
I don't understand your point
He keeps them in a half alive half a flea
State or whatever had doesn't sound healthy
From a
Worldview stamp in order
Bentley keep them on board in
Scared enough
That they are motivated to buy things
But Victorious and
That they don't feel like it's pointless
Who is
In the Bank of Big Hoss
That's what you're saying right there is propaganda for pro hospitals
You are just
Making these wild connections groups fakes
F****** supplement
Little thinking you're suppressing Hospital
I want you out of
Mnsshp
Just to be very clear
Beyond Tangy Tangerine
Mariah is not a doctor for human
No shortage of Griff
It's still just
Hey man
Stillgoode
Still works
Fine
He's presenting like some dangerous ideas
And then also an interesting metaphor
Accidentally sums up Alex's business
If it's next
Whitaker crosses the line
Severely.
Dangerous stupid
Didn't want to come out
Give this
Duraseal
Little girls
Major nine
In 26 program
And
The body that's
Gets rid of
The so-called HP
Problems
This is real
So wait so the fake doctor with a fake degree from it
Naturally get rid of HPV bumps
See how not real it is it only killed 3,000 people a year
That doesn't make sense it's actually get rid of it already have autoimmune disorders
Autoimmune disorders
What is it it's a precursor for cervical can
Women's
Because as recently as the knights
Cervical cancer was a leading cause of death in adults
In the 50s the pap smear was in
Stardew switch
Too much earlier diagnosis of
Weather condition and the number of deaths went down
Protective
Stevie got the ability to essentially eliminate
The Fatal risk
Now it's just turning our girls into slots Dan
Whitaker says it's a sterilization Tech
Dependent premise
Oh I believe it
Fine that's not what a doctor would say everybody who's gotten Gardasil so far
Has become sterile within two to three days
Notion
Irresponsible stay I just believe this
I believe you need an amputation
Which is why you came to the
So Alex trots out that only 3,000 deaths occur annually from HPV number is closer to like 4
For 5000
And I'd only reflects the United
That's only because
His Maiden screening and detection in the years since then
Q50
Since which time the incident
Death rate for server
Panthers dropped about 60%
I understand the grammatically
Since which time is correct however I heard it
The drop that
The state for hbv is it wasn't thanks to holistic medicine or natural
It was thanks to the development of the pap smear the dedicated researcher
I figured out how
BV causes
And the folks has now developed a vaccine
The only reason Alex
Flippantly pretend to 3000 annual deaths
You know you could have talked that around in order to make it seem like it's not a big deal
It's because of the work of the very people him and Whitaker
Here are trying to demonize
It's very very stupid
Dangerous
Buy mentality to put out
What you have to back it up
I believe that this is the case
Sterilization Tech
And not about trying to
Make sure that
We have a
Completely
Like
We could get rid of
What protects the process by which this s***
Always works with
With how Humanities stupid humanity is
It is a massive problem and we spend all this time and effort
Trying to fix it and as we get closer and closer to
A solution
It stops being a massive problem
And the people for whom it was a massive problem are dead
So the next generation is like
B it's not a problem and it never was and nobody's ever fixed it
For men
Lake HPV dozen
I'm sure that didn't
So
The body takes care of cervical
What do you might be expressing is just the idea that form and it doesn't really matter
That's like saying that for abortion doesn't really matter
That sounds crazy
Weird
Really dangerous but some of them are just outright
Wacky stupid
Like this next
You never want to bring
Cut roses
Someone that you're visiting
The essence of death
So you want me to bring a live play
Hospital the MD DMD
Who is considered by most
As a guy
Misdirected
Cut flowers
York Zoo
Attracts
Don't bring rocks those aren't alive
Wood
Probably need to study the back into the priesthood
That's why in d.c.
Fun with words
I folded up a twenty-dollar bill and saw that hospitals are deaf
You would need to do a study of people who are brought flowers and vases
Cut flowers do that study because you'd be endangering
Poopy and in ethical study to
Yes I would agree with you Dad everybody in the medical community agreed
Bringing cut flowers was a risk
Then the study itself would of course be on
Everybody is like
Exude is a degree with objectivity
Study being done
Hey now
You're possibly killing patients
Crazy
So we see the other sort of stuff that he
Insanity
You know early in the show
Alex started out talk
Think about things that made it
It's very clear that
The Sovereign citizen
Well guess what so is dr. Whitaker
Import
And that's all
Oh yes no doubt
Systems under the British admiralty regulation
And almost at the goalposts of the year
Flags of goldfinches
Good boy
Hospital
Yeah that's that's that's
I just want to run through some of the stupidity
Insole
Can you go in and
You're going to do some you still using your hmos and
And all these different Health Spanish
Basement Systems that's what they are they there to manage or disease
You got to be aware that
When you go in
It's like a recruitment
Scaring Detroit
Fear
AR
Getting real
Call boy
If you turned it into an acronym it must be true Dan
That's something that I remember
From Gary Busey saying all the time
And I also have heard that note
For everything
Is it a gentleman who does
Does a million acronyms for literally every possible thing
You did not tell me he would do that all over VH1 television
In the years when I was watching a saint of it
You just get the sense that this guy is coming
From NADA healthy
Ironically
But
We do get
You know what this sounds so much like
Doing this right now this sounds like
Like daytime
TV for Eno like mom's watching.
Hicksville
What are they what are they doing this is
I'm here at the end
Because what happens is
An actual doctor calls
An oncologist
He wants
Point out that this is bad guys I Googled yours and
My phone number is much nicer than someone asking
That kind of question
You're on the air of Scott
Hi
You know I think the world was not so black-and-white
As so you're guessing
And there's a 90% cure rate
Testicular cancer Young
Guy has to
Testicular cancer
Because you listen
Does not go to a doctor
Good chance he's going to die
Does your guest have that kind of
Treatments
That's what your vitamins I don't think so
So you brings up a very good point
Heard the man say oncologist in then he disappears in a puff of
Smoke like a cartoon
What's
That is that this is dangerous
Put some kind of like
Studies research that you've done
A review
Formation
And I'm telling you
We don't have
This doctor called
Incredibly Fair
He keeps saying like
I believe that there is a place for holistic
Approaches
There are people who incorporate it really well and
Have shown
Some techno
Do you have
Some appropriate application
He's not coming into being like you're full of s***
If someone who could
Be helped with early
Detection of
Eye cancer
Let's say
Doesn't do it because he believes this guy
He might die
You might be killing me
Stick Euler cancer has a 90% cure
Deathtrap medicine
Do you know what I have
Fish oil
1%
You're not far off.
You're not far off from Whitakers words
Polymyxin was Justice with cancer and who's the other one in the phone when I'm done both of those hundred percent pure race so
I highly doubt that
Call trial
I got to be responsible study
Behind that
First Easter
I need to research
Well I mean you know I would like to have drop is studying so I can
Medical studies
Yes but there's a lot of synthetic
Vitamin studies that have been negative lately
So I love that response
I don't why don't you believe
I don't I don't think it will occur understand how science
A studies were or peer-reviewed
Statistics I understand
You think
Everyone who's ever come to him it's been healed because he has maybe they don't believe it
The patients
At this is crazy
The invite
Success rate for testicular cancer I got a hundred percent success rate
I would like to see your statistics on that listen to this arrogant
Peer-reviewed answered hippie like
Why don't you trust me I believe what you're saying the internet
You shouldn't
Because whenever
Everybody else's job
Until they can replicate the stuff
I believe
If you think
It does lead me to believe that doctor Whittaker isn't
Even aware of the studies about testicular cancer
Makes me a little
Concerned what makes me more concerned
Galaxy
Getting defensive and trying to
To backup Dr Whitaker because he has the
The anti-vaccine arguments that Alex loves and that's
10000 copies of his books
So when you have when you have this like
It's clear that
Most of the world
Act
You believe why
The sources that you can get to back up why are people like him
I'm like that lady dr. Rebecca Carly who got her license taken away
If those are the only people you got
To backup your worlds
Trouble you got a really bad world
Because if the bike
Legitimate
Respectable science
Did not believe
Mainstream science
And they believe the things that Alex
He would not be hard to get
People who knew what they were talking about
To come on your show
About it it would be hard
Exactly
Do people like this
Is it just means that it means the pool is shallow
It's one of those big big differences between
People who
No things and study things and all that s*** versus bees guys
Is as you were saying
Whatever this actual oncologist
Goes on the show he's very reasonable yes we have seen that holistic
Coaches can benefits of
However
Credible study about it
Hahaha Italy makes
Look at this arrogant
That felt great
Send their Ivory Towers with their studies
Not all of us got to go to college you got a
You got a delay but right don't just put that out there
From Berkeley
Pacific engineering and that might be true I don't know
Berkeley and civic engineering and then all the sudden decide to be a naturopath
From his telling of the story he ended up meeting a Native American
Are Tampa land of course I wore a black man it was
Get into this is part of his backstory
It's kind of comical but at the same time
There's a chance
He did go to Berkeley
What is a Chauncey
He did me some Native American guy who got him off on his weird batural hellpath
I don't know
I'm not going to try and
Stuff's out his college
Transcript for anything
And only talk about the stuff that I can sort of talk about a man who create
University of his own fake degree then having a back story involving
Not the way I'm going to go with us
Music instruments
Scholar
So who knows
Anyway
Here Alex
Dr. Whitaker
Post game
After they have ended the call with the
Oncologist
Kicked out oncologist
Well you know just the fact that he was
Carries on with heater
What's up
In a bottle
Go to school
And I don't believe it
Yes 50 science
That is a raving lunatic
Is condemning the very idea of the
Like repeatability of sodomy
Confirmability
Excluding extraneous variables that sort of thing
He's like they are so trapped
Denair
Scientific I
Ideas like
Yeah man
Good
Go to these colleges
And if you don't think a certain way
You know like with facts or whatever it is they called
You have a delay button
This is really just f***** up I mean it
Somebody really f***** up
Everything in terms of Alex's Medical
Yeah we have like that that interview with Rebecca Carl
Bow
I'm talking about that don't get back to me
This guy coming in
Expressing Lake
All medicine
I'm just wants to kill you
Brighton
I mean it
Kind of old hat
Interesting new character
A couple of flourishes
I just hate that
I hate these people so much
There
Sweet and utter
Like
They are not hurting themselves
Because it's very
They're hurting other people
The end of this adventure
BECU
Interesting
Prospect
Alex's
Is rhetoric
Sliding towards
Antigua
I'm back
Involving
Weird
Constellation
Things starting to happen
Ready to roll
It feels like it's starting to roll
Now that makes it worthwhile.
That we spent so much time
Going over the last couple months of Alex's
Rear because once the balls
Start rolling
So much more apparent
I'm as they're happy
And we will see where the trend takes us
A what can cause
We can make based on that
Ever Alex having this f****** doctor on that's just
Look at this ass
Yeah that sucks
But for now
Good website
Do we have a website
What's it called
Search ww.w.
Teepee
Colon
Dash Dash
No
Difference or what's the difference
I think it was there when it's 2
Secured so it's
You're putting in credit card in for
Really
If you put your credit card information on our website
Where you would
Can write your social security number
You do that don't do that
Your credit card information on the group
What else did
Unsubscribe libreview
I can't say the doctor Whitaker hasn't been
Responsible for
At least tertiarily responsible for
Oncologist
Probably haven't
I don't know I heard
Angel of Death
You never know
Those
We got a lot of people who might have some death
In their past
Glenn Beck
Probably not satisfying anyway Isaiah
Dichotomy
Whatever
Probably take him
Alex