Alex
Looks like citrus
Beverages
Talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Yes sir
How is your playing civilization
Sexy
What's your favorite civilization to play as playing as Samaria in daughter of
Over a Project Camelot
So I've been playing is
Marriott
The card is a good early in early game military units
Because it allowed me
Games
Conquer France
Real early
Took over Paris
Owns that
Eliminate people from the early game
It is a great
Structure of
It is a great game
To play while taking notes
Need a little something to get that little
Yeah anytime listening to Alex
You guys write down the time you don't have to you don't have to
To do anything
Pointing out that it exists
Getting me down this damn rabbit hole
What's my civilization I do a lot of different ways
Is Rome
I like
Give me over to my
I like to play I love building
I like I'm just all the time cuz you can accelerate the Wonder construction using workers
It's kind of a coming back into the waters
But I like the shout-out to admire thanks
Everybody should enjoy it
Netflix final table
Oh man so good
The most overproduced cooking show I've ever seen
10 million dollars
Picture of the show I think it's so awesome to friendships
Avicii like celebration
Cultures
Very clearly celebrities in other countries
It's so great I think that there's such a multicultural
Like
Ingredients in culturelle
Cultural very well
On the show
To the point like
They went to some countries
Chose the national
On the first episode with it to Mexico and they choose tacos
Continuous
Great job
My favorite is whenever they get past the first round of nonsense which is
But then they have the the
Celebrity celebrity chefs like Amelia
A'gaci
Bothering people today
Do you think that's
Charles and Rodrigo
VI that team so great
Do great
Ona Ona
Cooking show
Stressed out
Is so awesome
Everyone loves each other because all the celebrity
Accomplished
Also the other was started because they have this
Backstory of likes
It's awesome
All the time
Everything is so uplifting
Globalism more transparent
We have a job to do and that's to get as many people as possible to realize that our differences make us
Together
Shoutout on Facebook
Knowledge
So much
So much Auntie globalist propaganda
And it was a black within the first 20 minutes
This is God
This is not subtle
Propaganda it's a reflection
It's a celebration
It is not something out at all
But neither is Alex
That's a pretty good transition
Wacky Wednesday
Rustic Road to go down today there's a lot of stuff that we'll see how it goes I'm not sure how it felt.
Thank you
Does new donor
First of all
I apologize if I got it wrong
We did cuz I said to differ
Pronunciation
You are now about
Exhaust
Thank you so much too
I'm a policy wonk
What is your real name
Fix so I'm not sure
Friend
The way
Took their donate
Ohio levels
And tell her you're brilliant someone sodomites
Thank you so much
Very nice
Interesting wacky
To do that one of the things we would like to do is open up
The fold
Have a place where there's more ability to respond to audience
So long lines probably Wednesday
The place where
We fulfill
Probably come up
But we also got a number of time travel
Wednesday Style
Policy wonk
Probably a raptor princess I can't remember I should have made a spreadsheet
You should have made a spreadsheet ranking art
I don't forget
Everyone's apology watch
Brodersen
It's actually about
This guy named
Coach Dave daubenmire
Coach Dave
Use assets
Terrifying
Sky has a backstory that we're going to get this episode
Varsity he invented
That would be very Ramsey Show
Rightwingwatch article about him
Something about that how
His daughters are going to be
And that to me seems like Bush League bigger
Global
Legend entice me into
Whether or not all lesbians the research
Would be almost 8
But I was like
Look
He has been a supporter of the show
Yet we really appreciate
Him a great deal more to urologist.
Absolutely
So I looked into
I watched a couple of videos
Please use the terrific of Coach coach
Yeah there's something here
Talk about about videos that coached
The world
Explore him a little bit
If you out there like
What we're doing here
You like coach
You make
Might join the fold might enter the arena
Of the Immortals
The Wacky Wednesday.....
Producer
My favorite Chef was a chef
Final table is like
If you win you get to sit down at the
Connex
That's not how
You get a seat at the final table
I do watch the entire show nothing else happens
It's not like all of them
Cook together
It's not like
Best episode
Or
It's not like the winner is not on the level
It's not like
It's implied that he is now a judge on the next season along with these other night
Could be
Understand what the guiding metaphor of the final table was what it mean
I understand if your honors
Greenroom of all these other chefs Hangout
What's too much energy today
I'm so here we coached Dave
But
He runs a show called pass the salt
I don't know why that's the name of the show
I tried to figure it out
No idea
Weather.
Nebulous
Decided
And call it assault
Alright you got all the pieces you need
Does
Coach
Relate in any way does he have some part of his backstory
Passing result is like an anecdote
Details
I don't know
I have no idea I don't think that's like a football term
Alright
No idea
Sweep to the right side
If it is
Kind of saying it over
That's what's up
Jellyfish
80 time
I forget to give us a new name I believe we are
Jellyfish
And seemingly outrageous comments expressed in this program are based on the Holy Spirit leading
A man called
Coach asked you this out there
Christian America
Soul
With a coach
Meijer
That's a nice boring wow that's a little excessive
Very Wild coach
Presents himself the interruption but for Jesus
He's very
Very Christian
Selfie
Being on the radio
He might be in some small Market or something like that
Find FedEx location
No videos of YouTube channel
Most videos have under 1000
One of the things that I was wrestling with Ian brought this to my attention is like
Is this punching down
Because we have more listeners than
Well I don't know
With
Like radio I don't know
Very low engagement
It seems
Like just a man spitting out a green screen that has a
Soccer stadium
Superimposed behind him with about 10 people on Skype
Here's the problem
Everybody who
Is sodium deprived that they've given him all their self
It could be also fun little Soccer Club
Just do him because he was using Thursday
So
Yeah he he
His show is bizarre
About like the possibility of like this is just a
Inconsequential
Guy rambling
To listen to him or I started
We're very
To bring
And then at the same time
Some commonalities with Alex
He
Talks about how we need to be worried
Because Alex Jones
Is being censored
Stuff like that
He clearly listens
To Alex's
And a lot of his narrative
Follow similar pattern
We're going to be
Probably faceless
Very very difficult decision that I think most of them are going to
Revolve around finances
What's going to happen with money what's money going to become we know about fifth coin and
Litecoin and
Gold and silver and everything is certainly a financial
I don't see the term collapse although that's probably a good time
Is a financial Reckoning
Depot in that all of us.
Soap
Financial
He talks about that a good thing
Alex ever does which is just
We're all in.
Wow like that
Conspiracies about the Federal Reserve
That would be the way he
He described it
We're all in.
Rap
Right
Assertive
Use evolve his rhetoric
Because
The vager
Absolutely
Situation
They have diminished buying power bi
It makes him seem a little more reasonable that he doesn't go
As far as I
Financial advice
To hear us talk about someone who's
And you were asking
If he is a cup
You want to get to the bottom
Yeah I need this I need this Nelson mystery solved the real quick
Have to wait too long to get to the bottom of
Next clip
Coach
Expresses something
I think
Ziguidi to send missionaries
Alright
To understanding
His past
Fun4all
I'm going to really make him mad
I do the most
Are you
Enjoy
York people from your church
On a mission trip
You won't even try to evangelize your own Publix
Cuz there's laws
Can I tell you
I'll go in there baby safe
Columbus City School
East High School
They don't need the gospel there I guess
So you are concerned about who that was chiming in like I said he has a bunch of people on Skype and most of them just
U2 every now and again he'll amen
Monitors on Skype on his show he probably has like six or seven people
Who will chiman occasionally with
Or
They have little mini
They're like picture-in-picture
Alright five of them
The real hang out like a group chat
Deeply f***** up I kind of see this a little bit like Hollywood Squares whenever they zumar off when they zoom in
People who are the celebrities who are healthy
Hollywood Squares but only the three on the
That's exactly where you're at it's a mess
So
He's talking about how you needed to send missionary
Yeah you illegally nicely to get it out
Against the law
Here we go. The Coach Dave daubenmire is Nautica
Coach
That's because in 1999 he was sued by the ACLU
Because for years you've been fortunate students before and after game
Evangelize
Back in 99
Naturally this life to some parents and community members filing complaints
ACLU took up their call
Today coach claims he won money in lawsuit after the ACLU settled out of court
In reality the ACLU worked out a settlement and withdrew the case
After the school and Coach agreed to put a stop to the practices
Who's that were found
Unnecessary
And the only reason to proceed at that point would be punished
School District
The ACLU had no in
The agreement set up a mechanism where the school is required to relay
Complaint involving coach
To the ACLU directly
World ticket. So this is this is a coach
Small school
I don't know if it was individual Public School
Yeah vet now has to report directly to the ACLU
If the principal gets a complaint from somebody
Superintendent clu
Control it going on for years
But there might be
A situation a place where they're covering it up
Spoiler alert
He's a pretty good coach
You have all these stories of his Angels in the Outfield
Abuses that would happen in Texas schools
Yeah yeah
You have a situation
Here where this guy is acting
Brightness settings
Inappropriate
I'm uncomfortable with that but I am going to allow it to the ACLU setup this thing where they had
Had to do that in order to make sure that he was fulfilling
The agreement
Didn't is a spell.
So like a hundred million dollars we just want you to stay with kids
So as a part of the deal Coach Dave
Any further complaint
You got another contract
Undoubtedly have been renewed
No
After your board is not religiously abusing children
Religiously abused children
Leave this principle
And is actually not a very good coach if he's a quitter
That's not a good coach we'll see what happens
Across the London School District
$2,000 in attorney's
And coaches. Telling a story
He wanted
After this coaches
Pretty much unhireable by public
What schools are religious
He founded his ministry pass the salt
What military group
Mostly just into complaining
From their website
Regional grocery store to remove
Entry-level poured magazines from their shelves
Ed quote eating a local Columbus Community announcing a homosexual bathhouse from their community
Corn maggot
Is like muscle mass or like lowrider
Revelations I guess
You got rid of a spa and now the grocery store can has bodybuilding magazines
So minute to notice entry-level torn bags from grocery store
These groups not only wasted everyone's time but they're clear public
Expressions
They also were involved
The removal of the
Commandments from Adam
County Ohio
Travel to munch
Gomery Alabama to Judge Roy Moore
Always gets worse
Always
It doesn't turn into a disaster
Sunset District 5 hammers, be real bad
As he's creating pass the salt Ministry
Create
It's weird along the way as he's
Creating youth ministry
He also been coaching football at the Fairfield Christian
Academy in Ohio
He also got fired from that job in 2012
Didn't have anything to do with too much praise it's the Christian Academy
You just can't help but
Because mine
Diorite
So I
In 2014 he tried to return to coaching secular High School football unfortunately public outcry led to
I8
It's like change.org petition
Also the school board of Lakewood High School voted against him being allowed
Auto job Anthony has not been allowed to come back to public school football coaching
My hometown
F****** tomorrow
There are so many places where you can go where people would not only welcome the fact that you were censored by the f****** ursin
Assured by the ACLU
Crazy
Yeah I mean it is a sort of Feathering
He was able to
In the first place right Reverend of
The ACLU came after me I was off
That makes some sort of more relevant
These right-wing
Extreme
World
So it's a little bit about
Ways to use pass the salt that might make sense later on
You're going to give it to me
And say that we're not allowed to learn
We are the salt of the earth
That could be right
Why would you want to pass people
Historically salt
Was like
Luxury item
It was used
Maybe that's what it's really all about
The good guys
All over
Like I said
I noticed some Alex Jones
Adjacent narratives
Weather others that I didn't
Incase
Cover the
Show more
There is
Holding a lot to the vest
But not pasta
But I will reveal some
One of them
Another, now
With our show
And that is
A guest
That
Sit down with that we have talked
Hi Frances is Coach Dave daubenmeyer at news with use. TV at news with him. Common I got a taste
TV channel guide on JB Williams
It's just going to knock off
The socks everybody who watches the
Underground
As far as mainstream media doesn't want anything to do with this guy and I believe the Doctor James David Manning
Is probably the most dangerous man
All of America to the Obama Administration
To our mutual friend boots
Their hearts Are knitted together he has a f****** episode where he sits down
The guy who are two weeks ago
Armies to rise up in
Imagine
I I can't imagine what they bonded over
I can't imagine either
Must be just a random thing and he just has Manning
Anything about it
He legit says in this interview with him
I listen to you everyday
I'm a huge fan of your show
So you have no reason to not be aware of murdering gay people
Yeah because I don't know
Wait till
Reverend Manning and Coach date mutual friend named
They're both religious zealot
People and black people
Is this in this
Berkeley weird
You know man is up
Hop in
Harlem
Yeah you got coach
Down in Ohio
Call lives in Pennsylvania
Pennsylvania Butch
Bphils
Bicycle Connection is so strong
It doesn't appear maybe initially that they would
Be super inline
But like I said
Their homophobes people are weird
Versace
Listen to a little bit of mayonnaise
Appearance here
With coach
Really
You know flesh out
Reinforced
These guys
Dick
We can't allow it
These homosexual
Swelling music behind it this is this is ESPN show
But about Jesus
Weird
F******
I was watching
Canada
Homosexual
In the preacher
All that
Marco's amen no
Miles
He smiles immediately after you said homosexual
Yeah we're getting this homework
Robbing the people blind
And and having people watching children fall apart
Fall Apart
Long Legged Mack Daddy
Is true
You don't know about Long Legged Mack Daddy
Catchphrases
He rose to prominence
Cost of a long ladybug
You came to us because of characterizing Barack Obama is
But that's
Good turn of phrase
Otherwise catchphrases
Can phrase
I don't know that's not sick
Positive
Show me
Certificate
But appears to be
Fun
Excuse
Talk s*** about
To be filled with hate
Well cover
Really again
And I'm sure he's going to do it in a very respectful way
There's
I don't know if it'll play on the sound
End of the episode
Saw the
Interesting
Looking at the wave file as I do that
He's different
What he says black
There's something vocal quality
I think it's
Perceptible from list
But if you
Put this episode into audacity
You'll f****** see a difference
In the way you speak
Knowledge
Because you are worrying are so you need Doctor Manny because not only are you a man of God
But you are a black man of God
But even more unusual is you were a black man of God
Warren
About what you called this Long Legged Mack Daddy Barack Hussein Obama
5 years ago
And you were speaking at that time really talked him into the black community and watch some of the
Videos of something that you said to black people
It's not a black or white
Only two races those Racing for heaven and those Racing for help and he was a black
Speaking the truth
Long before anybody else really saw
It was Jesus
There's a different vocal
Yeah I didn't realize that you could say Blacklist away that you saved you with a heart
That is uncomfortable to say at what time let alone everytime you say
Listen to feel like
I saw it in the van that was when I was like
There is something
Wheatley
F****** weird and different
Walnuts absolutely
Is going out to Jews
Joann
Jews like
I think that's how
That's f***** up you even say it like that
Also spoiler alert is an episode I listen to that we're not going to be going over
Visa
It is
So f***** up
It is just
Forgot to put it on
Could not go now you could just say no
On Skype I don't want to do this
I guess that's definitional that your world
Our talking about how Jews are the devil
And how they're up like their father and I
He keeps asking
Advance Auto
I like this show is why
The Jeb Bush please clap but if if you're Gods like that that's nice
Alright
Jesus
So
Vocalization
The verbal pattern
Results
I got bread
Whiteflies
More life
I think that was based on
Here is coach
I don't think any single person listening
To this point
Is like
It's probably nothing we haven't really seen
Racism
Walmart
Northlake Auto
Seems like there's a black like like that
He totally fair and say like
Is real bad
Dr. Manning I forgot to message beginning your
Your church in Harlem
It begins to speak to black people black
In the truth is Doctor Manning I wrote about this I don't know couple
4 years ago maybe it was I said the
Mini blinds are Christian
Listen to
You have a very small audience
Got a lot of attention today
Look this
Gross
Calling Harlem
Jungle
Number one
Immediately say you're surrounded by black
Elucidating
I call it a jungle
People which he says
As a problem
He says you are surrounded by your in a jungle as we assumed in Ohio once again proving Ohio
Iowa should also be on our list of states with Mississippi and Louisiana
I know but you never think you're annoying
You keep on doing what you doing also annoying
Vile
I mean this is just
I think Kevin May
Coach sort of excuse
Cover to be erased
Alphabet
They have a great time
Nothing white supremacist love more than a black white supremacist
About how Reverend Manning did that mock trial about Obama
F****** coaches like I heard about that I really wanted to come I wished I could have been there
I believe I believe
Mailman
They talked about that a little bit
Really interested
I lived
Really close to
And I went down to the
The coffee shop
No one remembered him
I went down that talk to people at
The black bookstore no one remembers him
What's the turnover
For that bookstore
First of all
Second
You just like
Building this argument about like I talked to a bunch of people no one remembers Barack Obama being
And what do you do
Do is talk about anything real
Like
A transcript
From the University
Doesn't he does say that he did get a degree
From Columbia
But of course
That
Is cover
That's the CIA got him in order to
Who knows
Show me the birth certificate
See what you get like when you get these people
Believe all of this
Can I talk to someone at a coffee shop they didn't remember him and that's proof
From Columbia
Do normal people
To Columbia
And said he wasn't there cuz it's
That makes sense
It's so.
About is like these
Dumb f******
Ideas
Conspiracies already talked about
Because of
Adjacency
Manning or out
But a new one came up I thought it was really
And here we got a new conspiracy
Dumb
Any questions
They call him names
But the fact remains that Barack Obama
Michelle Obama
Practicing law
Twenty-some years in public education
I keep my keep my license up-to-date who knows when I might need it
Why would I took a business
The only reason you turn in the license
With the bar
Whatever
That they found that you did
Same thing same thing from Chef you don't go to Harvard
And allow degree from Harvard and then turn around and passed the bar
He realized
Back to the law
Email this is just a chain email
Conspiracy that went around
People who are in charge of Eli
Illinois bars
Issue with the law license
Requires education
You have to go in for classes
For the registration Barack Obama decided they didn't want
Anymore as Barack Obama
Illinois House aspirations to become a senator and then
He had a path forward that he wanted to go in and it wasn't
Practice
Whether it was even before that Community organizing
Things like that
Require logic
All it does is
So they decided
We're not going to maintain them
Now
Amber Alert
Even if you let your logic relapse
You can take classes and pay
They didn't surrender ship
Is Obama today
Start practice
Which by the way would be
Peanut
Almost
He's going to buy us before
I think that would be a little bit
But if you want to practice law outside of a courtroom
Maybe give legal advice in
Official capacity
Could you just have to pay a fee
And go in for like a
Update
Or whatever
Because they follow the proper channels
In order to enact
Activator login
Actually I'll be honest
Barack Obama probably
Because his status is
Retired
He retired
There's an active and retired
Is just an act
Barack Obama
Retired so he may not be able to
Pedophilia
His dad
His standing
Imagine if Michelle Obama just suddenly did was like Defender now
We already discussed
It would buy us courts
I think it might be more problematic
Worth although it would be really
Cool that she took off on
Only like big corporate clients or something like that
I see a hero story out of
Finer.
Corporations.
She takes on
Wells Fargo as a client
Takes them all
Defenders
We have here
Mysterious name of pasta sauce
We have a history of
Force religion on your kids
Right
Was he ever an educator
Yeah so
We get back
To the death
Yeah we got a new episode
Of his show
Name of this episode
Cuz this guy
Please just
Super religious weirdo
Horrible conservative
Yeah
Cumbersome
Call my wacky way
Real quickly
We're going to do a whole show on it
With this whole thing about the Mandela effect
Being in the Bible
Lion and the lamb
Isaiah
Isaiah 11
Ezekiel
Or Corinthians
Could have been
As we left yesterday
Let me tell you what's going on
Universes
Rice University
Berenstain Bears The Berenstain Bears
Artificial intelligence
Sinbad was the superhero
The world in which we live to a
The Demonic Realm
These people are going to call a parallel universes
I will call it parallel Realm
What is CERN
Decided to do
20 minutes
Just him talking about
The cookout
Plugs
The beginning
The rest of the show is all about
And he believes it's real
And he believes one of the biggest
But
Is that everyone knows
Image
The Christian Utopia
Is a lion laying down with the lamb
I will explain
Exactly
Remember this
In a minute
And he
Robert
Nope will get you
But he accidentally
Says why
A little bit later
But he's going to make a huge deal out of this
The Bible
3 minutes
History of talking about the lion laying down with the lamb
Please play the long clip of people saying the lion lays down with the lamb
Wherever you are right now
Isaiah 11:6 and you'll see the wolf also shall dwell
With the lamb
The wolf shall dwell with the lamb
Real quick he just had the lion and the fatling
Skype
The Lion and the lamb and Isaiah 6
And the Wardrobe
No longer
So here's my problem with this Theory
Yeah but
None of the other pop culture that involves this hat
The owner saying
Like poems that have been written involve The Lion and the lamb
Now that's
Just specifically one thing that
Please change this is my problem with tons of you
The Mandela effect
Is that like they seem like
Okay you have to assume
Malevolent
Intelligent
Behind
Otherwise everything else would have changed along with it
Right
But
It's not
It's chaotic evil on our Dungeons & Dragons
Franklin
You only change the one passage in the Bible that
Ostensibly everybody is referencing in order to make everybody look what coach likes to make the argument
This is why there's a
Another verse
The word of God on
Right because that's not going to change.
So he makes the argument that God was saying write the word of God on your heart soul
Demon time travel and go back you will know the correct word of God
Bordering on time traveling Nazis trying to change the future
Lion
Superficial
0 meaning
The idea is a predatory animal lays down with prey
That's it that's all
You can have the exact same meaning behind a wolf in a
It doesn't matter is why it has to be chaotic
Sabri just f****** with it
No it's not
It's it's time trolling
It's
Just trying to trigger coat
Worthwhile task
Just concerned with O and
In the next life you sound like
Don't freshman in a dorm
Shaquille O'Neal
Funny dad wait
Who's Kazam
Shazam
Show me a video here in your mind
Holy God
Uncle pennybags
Or not
Yeah baby
I remember how you spell Berenstain Bear
Depended on what part of the country you are in
I never
Reddit
Habitat
Spell
Remember
Remember he's fallible
Chili's
What was the first phrase you remember
It was made of deer like a box
Chocolates you never know what you're going to get
DD
The Mandela effect
It is about this is the actual life was like a box of chocolate
But everyone remembers
He's like a boss
Because
Forrest Gump
Carefully
Just answered
Said life was like a box of chocolates
He said it correct cuz he's part of the Mandela effect the way that the
Quote actually
Now let's hear what coach says immediately after that
I never saw it
Life is like a box of chocolates or life was like a box of chocolate
When Forrest Gump sitting there
Briefly what's the Mandela effect
So the guy who answered it
It said life was like a box of chocolate
Is or was
He started the question himself and it is
So the other thing after that he plays with long clip of people like a video that some of the YouTube clip
Explain the Mandela effect
Idea that this
Just one person thought that
Nelson Mandela
He died in prison
The actual death of Nelson Mandela
Post about it found a bunch of other people thought the same thing to them
Started so he plays the part of the video that
Explain
Like this all this
Non-Stop
But immediately stops
At the exact point when a memory researcher is about to explain
Yeah
There are suggestibility
It's almost a pack animal kind of situation where it's better to agree with somebody than it is to
They're totally wrong
It is.
Hungry
But we are going to
Where are we
With technology.
Think about before there were phone
They have no conception
Send voice down a wire
Invoice would appear somewhere else
Ever ever in a million years
Nope
Well in about seven thousand years they would believe it
Call Bethany
The machines that are creating the interruption of our
What's a very strong arm
For climate change
Technology
Yep
Nope
Our universe
Now the problem is our technology is broken timeline on our planet
Time machine
Future
Batman
People on television 310
I believe
Allconnect
Pieology
Literally just said what I think is going on
Is otherworldly tectonic technology
Yes I do
Turn around forever
Let's earn congratulations Rogers new grandson yesterday
He said the lion
Where did that come from
That is wrong
Yes he's down with the lamb comes from the Elvis Presley song peace in the valley came out in 1957
The other Institution
The other instances
People quoting the verse
Are actually people quoted the Elvis song trying to get better rhythm
Funkier coming off your tongue
There's an alliterative quality to The Lion and the lamb which is why there would bring that to
To the table
The song work with wolf
And Elvis took a creative license because
The actual meaning is not I don't know
Examples
These people giving speeches even Martin Luther King
These
Hit song
Valley
Infiltrated people's minds
Articulation of the lion lays down with
Does
Wolf lies down with the lamb
And no one question.
That's the bigger story
50 years realize they were saying the wrong thing
God damn it doesn't write a catchy phrase
Even if you don't realize where that sort of
I guess meme
Linguistic
Come from
Most likely where it comes from
Creative license
The first
I was wondering quoting scripture
He was writing a song
I'm so people just
Sounds better have you
In overtime
Become the accepted
Good version of what lies down with the lamb
Well it's not like anybody and
Dude is later catalog
Weather
No it's like
Snow in the way twitch
That was written in what Isaiah
Yeah Isaiah 11:6 so that would have been written
Well
It would have been written in what
It would've been written in Greek
Yeah something like that
Maybe Aramaic why would why would everybody have ever needed
Question the soundness of the phrase bar
But the meaning doesn't matter it's
Bible can always be improved in English
Apples that are like
Eva
Fundamental
From what they might have been
Conversation
Conversation about the difference between a lion and a wolf
Not an interesting conversation
The whole show on it I like to live
I don't know
I remember it being
Instead of thinking maybe I got it wrong
With an explanation based
How our brains
Locate
If you include like
Especially modern phenomenon of troll which is the case with that
Sinbad
Being in Shazam
Rare
Because there are some
Even been
Taking a bath
But like what
Well there is one that
Me and Marty DeRosa didn't episode of our podcast
That's what they want you to
About this young lady
Who was found dead
Water Tower
The building
Hotel
In Los Angeles
Right but when
I thought that
Years before
Fairly recently
We get the episode
Betta in my head
This happened to Waze back I've known about this
I express that on the episode
About it
They got some message
I also thought that happen
It's unclear exactly why we thought that
It's a collective Miss
Remembering
I don't know exactly how to
Explain that one
Snow White
The
Wicked witch doesn't save your mirror on the wall who's the fairest
Of the mall
There's a I don't remember exactly
Magic mirror on the wall who's the fairest of them all
Maybe we could just call maybe we could just recall like let's
With Rebrand the Mandela effect
Let's Collective punch up
You do like we're all just kind of getting together and being like
Not that great I remember better than that because that has a better ring off
That's what it is collective
Diversion
Insecurities
Just trust your own member
You know that cuz you right have
Skewed perspective on every
It's always come from a subjective
Overtime
Lou's Pizza Xavier take more information so it's not like
I can't remember
What video is people are like
Bouncing balls back and forth to each other and then
You watch it the third time and then somebody's like
You realize there was a gorilla but there was a man in a gorilla cross the water through their new life
Well I even know that you're like okay well fine then the brain isn't trustworthy to f*** off
If you focus your attention on
You miss something else
So far
Bears like of course
I thought it was spelled bear
Normal suffix
Retinal of course without those books as kids
So like
To a kid
You don't give a s*** who wrote
Comes up towards the end of this
Mandela effect
Episode
He doesn't turn off his phone
Recording why
Hey guys listen to me
I don't know what's going on with the Mandela
I told you sitting in your church understand
What's going on in the world
Call him back
President
Greendale
I don't say this is fact this is true
How do you make the fish
How much information on the Mandela effect
Never heard from the Mandela effect
Is it in the Bible
Change the
You've nails
I mean alright
Great
Popshit
I think
And I'm putting forth the idea that there's a demon
It's Aaron's fault
Turn all this
Do you understand
The show
Not true
Google
And probably believe those lies because of the lies that I believe
Think about stuff
Like this
Way
But he wouldn't want that seems fan
Talks about God
Like I'm just saying I don't know if they're true
Well that's what your show is you talk about
Bigoted opinion
It's about things
A lot
Just not
Cuz if that's the case
That's on you
That's
Obviously because demons have changed
His memory audit when God started talking to him about the man jealous if you recall
At the beginning of episode
Intro to pasta sauce
Specifically says
That everything is beset on this show
He doesn't know that
Mandela effect
Less Fun
MX Player
We started episode
For Charlottesville
First of all I'll say is
Soundly
Like not that's not there than how I
All right well, there we go nevermind
Play stupid
And I'm like I don't understand why you
You think you know what you're talkin
And then the other stuff
Dangerously
Bigoted
Here in this neck
Text whip where he explained
You think so
With the folks
Reproach
I don't want to know that
Have find out
They won't
49ers record
The scoundrel
Martin Luther King with a
Woman I do know that probably
What's going on I talked about this yesterday
Western Civilization
And what come on now
Lincoln with cage Let It Go
Oh boy
Anybody tell me why they are so
Tearing down
Confederate Heroes
If they still consider us the Bible Belt
I'll say that again Ray
Yeah right
Felt the Bible Belt
Stronghold of Christianity in this
Nation
Not why we call it that
Integrate Christian
Calm down
Chris
Christianity
Godless liberal forces
And what is it they really have against slavery
Like really
Randolph
Really trying to get there no winter
Prison talk about that
No but I mean like what do they have against it like what is that what is it with all these liberals trying to rewrite history and say slavery is bad
They don't bring that up at all except for a little bit later one of these people on YouTube
But it was about slavery was
Was about
Germanshire document
You guys
Yeah right
Do better
Waves come on
So in this next week
Explication
Struggle
Spell rewriting his
Sure
Chick-fil-A
Friends Romans countrymen lend me your address
The good that men do
Barry Wilson
Is buried with them
Celebrity
Anyone on the preseason
Makeup stores about
We make up
We just remember George Washington chop down a cherry
Nope Subway
That was
Is a lot
Everything's changed
Are Christian
Celebration
So that is really what
I believe is going on
Undermining of Arc
Christian City
Your sofa
Focused on
Racial
Flashing and all that stuff
And little
You know that that is just a
CIA
You should have known that from
With all the X Alex
Coach
Believe that too
Great race War II a made-up
Concoction
Thalia
/
Facebook research yesterday
National
Do you say your wife
America first
That means you're not allowed to say
Our Superior
No
I should be a Christian nationalist
The trick you better miss you better not miss
No stop it
Fine with that if anyone
The times people Call wifey
People marching
Racist
No it's because they're celebrating
It's not there it's like how the pride parade is also all about how all other gender Orient
Tatian should be
Subjugated
Play Parade
It was all white
What is it national nut St Patrick's Day
Coaches white Nash
White nationalist just means
International
And that is not at all correct
That's what
Expressing
He's just
I believe that our country
You should come first in the world and I'm white
Not recognizing a white National
White nationalist very specifically
The country they have nationalist
Dominated by there
In our present situation they believed that the United
States is a white
Country Inn must remain a white
Country's immigration multiculturalism
Are outright attacks on the
Canute survival
The white race
Well this is
Pretty clearly a racist
Position most nationalistic cowards
And they hide behind the idea that Preserve
Unfortunately racist idea because
Plies
Non-white people in a white culture would make the culture that's created
Superior than it was before
Right I mean I understand you would be arguing about it
If it makes it better if it makes all the culture better
I think it'd be a fine argument if there were like Fifty white people left and you were like
Extinguisher
Super duper Nest protect
Like those on
Visited try exactly
The argument
Stewby's
We're protecting culture
Nan wife
Ruins
The only other approach I can imagine would be to argue the culture is static and unchanging
And the culture that existed is exactly the same
Of course this is also a stupid
There's no culture
Defend other than the status quo
Level of political Financial
And social control over non-white
Of course
Because this is an ideology that is on the one hand
Based on race
Desperate appear appear like it's not
It always inevitably leads to
Superfund arguments about what kind of white is white
You see this idea pop up all the time
Start talking about how Jews but they're not
Because they said he thought they had dangerous Jewish and Asiatic
They weren't wide enough
This argument
Cannibalizing
Nature of white National
Becomes a definition
Sing it away that doesn't work
Reality is or even
Like whiteness
Exclusive
It's always been an idea based on
Isn't White
Who is
And when you
Well in that sort
The world white Nash
Symbolism
Specific
About retain
Power
In the people you.
Be wide enough
I don't believe
Coach understand
I really think you did
Because
Can hear it in his voice there's like
You know I'm a white nationalist white and I'm a nationalist
I don't think
Understand
There is
I think that he's white Nash
Nationalism
As an idea
I think he thinks
Two discrete ideas
Being white
Which is just coincidence
A big National
Position
You're giving him a lot of the benefit of the doubt
I've listened to enough of him to know that he's f****** stew
That's true
I also know that he's f****** stupid ass s***
Huge bigot and I think
He could accurately be described as a white
He knows what that mean
I think he
A few of those things
What does a
He have done the homework
Deserve
My score
On that okay
But it's not from a place of like
I think
That he's fixed
Something years old or whatever
I don't think
Videos Alzheimer
You don't know what
Put in the amount of work
It's required to talk about this
Subject right
I think if we
Much more work
We can talk about the much deeper than we
But
Used
Totally fine with
Not even the surface
The Ether
Above
Flowing wind
Yeah yeah
Next episode
The end up talking about a source
Information that
This is America
The new American is the John Birch
Body
God God
I'm on there
Detroit Historical
Other cities.
Turn down the statue
Anybody with me on that one
You dumb f***
Like sports Pacific statue of Margaret Sanger are you talking about
Let's go with conservative Margaret Sanger
Statues
Yeah all the time
Anybody would be like
Wouldn't end up in a fight
Now there's the one in
You know that Margaret Sanger statue that we don't
Tons of markers
F*** out of here with that stupid
You're getting out of this singer statue in
The famous One
I'm not going to deny or somewhere where there is one or what
Making him mad
It's just the idea of her having a statue
Welcome on the subject
I'm f******
Down with her having
Statue
He and I could get into an argument about why that's not relevant
I just think he's
Trying to pull some sort of name
I bet
You think there's a statue of somewhere
In order to
The beefed-up is clay
Now hold on
The John Birch Society put out this article
In the new America
Criticisms of this Robert
Statue
Express
A misunderstanding
About when I was about to start yelling thank you for stopping
History
And Charla
Coatesville
Revolving in a murder
That is now legally confirmed he was convicted of murder
Today he was convicted of murder
Recorded this
Sorry about that
That the statue is at
The heart of the matter
He's reading the John Birch Society
About historical
Ignorant
About
We're also ignorant now here
You starts to read from the article and
Editorialize
Volksbank after the
About how
The New American
Detroit Historical
You ready
Charlottesville Virginia
Remove the statue
Miss Station Park yes that's why they were invented
Property
Well yeah
I want to talk to you about the Statue
The statue of Robert Ely that was erected in Charlottesville Virginia with commission
Food52
Two years after the end of the Civil War
Tenzin America interesting time from
If I understand my
History correctly there were a lot
Statues
Came up
In the South around that time
Arguments for why they should
To continue
The mistakes of that has you hit on to bigger point but let me walk us through it
Sew in
January 19th 6
Carter Woodson
Inconsiderate
Be the father of black history
Founded the Journal of negro history
In October 1960 Margaret Sanger
Started her
Brownsville Brooklyn
Which aims to provide Healthcare to
Impoverished largely non-white
Community to give them control over their own bodies
Choices
Hey March 1917
The Jones Act
Did Puerto Ricans
In July 19th 7
30 day labor
F-250
Evil Dead
In August 1917 the messenger
An African American political and literary
Begin District
It was a wild time
Significant progress has taken
Place in terms of race relations
And simultaneously there was still high-profile lynching
And plenty of outright racist violence that was completely
The issue here
The time
It was one where it was
Moves are beginning to be made
To empower the
Disempowered disenfranchised communities
Beginning create their own spaces
These Publications
Or Hubert Harrison up in Harlem
But it was also a minority
He was still totally okay
In Birth of a Nation came out in 1915 which led to the founding
The second planet that
Barry Gibb
So we're living in the aftermath
And this is the stage upon which our play
The statue of Robert
As well as the accompanying statue of Stonewall Jackson
Paul Goodloe
The part that contains
The statue was also paid for by Mackinac
And it was called
It wasn't renamed emancipation Park Until 27th
The year that Charlottesville City
The council voted to remove the
So his whole propoint
About the emancipation
Part and they put up the main story
F***
So he's whole premises
Completely blown out
Yeah
Yeah they renamed it emancipation Park
In honoring of taking down the music
Screaming about that nonsense I was like
The only way that makes sense is if they made the park orwellian nonsense
Everybody's like
F*** around and make an ironic name called emancipation
Empire
McIntire University of Virginia history professors
He was somebody who deeply believed in
The cause of the South
Was honorable the cause was honorable
Heroic
He was part and parcel of what historians now called the lost cause
This idea of the noble South
Which celebrates the romanticized
The Confederacy
Slavery
Drift away the brutalities
Slavery I can't imagine why they would want to be a heartbreaker
Stripped Away all the ugly
I don't get why we change that history
Philanthropic
McPherson who gave generously
Towards the goal of beautifying the city
Charlottesville
It's important to point out that most
The things he was paying for we're all set
Beautify
Charlottesville
Lee Park
Where the statue of Robert E Lee
Was erected was a whites-only
The same is true
The same is true of Benny
As Professor Mason puts it quote
That new Public Library with secre
He gave money to school
The schools were psychic
Everywhere you look McEntire's gif
Well in the eyes of Charlottesville are beautifying
Gloria
If you look at them Through The Eyes of black Charlottesville
Enhancing the segregation
The public space
I'm celebrating.
Defense of slavery
Beyond my knowledge to express that Paul McIntyre's
Desire was to
Participate in the systematic terrorizing
Of the black population
I was beginning to make progress towards greater
Quality
It's not beyond what I know to say that that's exactly the result
Of his actions
Widening the educational Gap
White and black
Creating beautiful public spaces were black
Welcome
Then in those supposed
Beautiful faces created
The revisionist history
The history of the
Enslavement of the what
Parents of then residents of Charlottesville
It's pure racial Terror
There's no two ways about
On some level I know that people like coach understand
And they're carrying on that
A tradition themselves
They probably don't realize
But I know on some visceral fat
Conscious level
They f******
Absolutely
And that's the historical truth of all this
Where there's smoke
There's probably Nazis burning books
The vault
You talking about this John person the article about how they
Revision of
Historical ignorance about leaf
Yeah that's the truth of that statue
So what you going to do with that
You just going to lie about it
And you're going to argue that the ultimate big
Country in the world
Is against
Washington DC and George Soros and all those God hate us
Preserve preserve the Heritage ultimate form of bigotry
Taking the ultimate form of bigotry
Ultimate
Characterizing white people in the south
As having strong
And missing teeth
Your type of his
Especially if somebody from the heart of the Midwest and someone who's been to the south in like
I don't fancy myself like a
Like that
Having grown up in the situation
That I have
Being so
Inundated with
People that most people think are Hillbillies sympathizer
Insult
No there's so much
Believe that our culture
As a whole
Too much mileage
Which out of making fun of
Hillbilly
Alicia little bit I just like
I believe all heck jokes
Like it might do us all a bit of good
The only point of making
Because I'm not going to validate
But I do
Either
The kernel of a FairPoint
A lot of angry White
In that
Punchline
Has been totally fine
Just because you walk around
In Southend here Bunch people talking
Doesn't mean that they're dumb
It doesn't mean
Me and that people are having lots of value
You because of it your own
Biases
Is by
Finding people who
Fit close to stare
Karyotypes right it goes unexamined
The more for Hillbillies than others
But
Hillbillies
It's not it's not the word I would like to
Dwight Beverly
The caricature of the
It isn't on
Fair Arkansas
But somebody is going to end the world
Look at how funny these people talk
Let's make fun of
Let me finish my thought
What's going to be on the grand
This one doesn't
Underlie
AAA
Tradition
Of Lexi
Yeah I think
Like we talked about triage
There are there are 100 problem
And we will times
Not talking
Catan about problems
Because problem 12in
Prescient
I think it's that same sort of thing
Now
People like coach
Probably argue
You hit whitest number one problem but
A little bit a little bit
Clip from this episode
The biggest boy that I want
What the f***
What that statue was what it
Contact
Evans Construction
Like there's a bunch more of
Statues
By the daughters of
Confederacy large
Came up
And were erected
Did during.
Where non-white pee
Making inroads
2 power
An internet service
It was used as a
Terroristic
It was a reminder of
We enslave.
Okay so what
Is that
During time.
Where in America
Traditional minority
Make games
And how they live their life
I don't want to stay over react
I'm going to instead
In order to try and Destroy any games that are
Memorialize
Intimidating fashion
Public space
History of
Repression
History in order to make it look like
The oppressors they were the oppressed
The typewriter
It's co-opting the very oppression that you are
Statistically that does true
One more clip
I think
What I made that argument
When he started talking about how he's a white Nash
Analyst
I do believe
He doesn't know what the term
National if he thinks he's a white
This clip better make my Ark
You stupid
It doesn't understand
Conversation.
Art of the deal
Why
Nationalist
All white Nice List why they are they believe in white supremacy
That we
Do regarding women
Understand that what is happening
Is Brave
Well that's not true
Christian man
When snow party
He is going to
Let the world go to hell
Very very important for Soros
True
America first
The windows white nationalist showed up
Does white nationalist
Give me drawing real quick
Thinking America
Who's on your team
When you say team
Includes your team
I think that
He thinks those nationalist as a noun
Adjective that is.
Describing vet
That you just hear someone
Doesn't understand
Charlottesville there were
White National
There were groups
Specifically white supremacist is there
So because he's so stupid
And he doesn't realize that
What he wants
Defend is National
Right
Spiritually
What he's doing is
Yeah I was going to say
What he's I get that he's not understanding I mean I get that he's not understanding the term
Structure
But he is espousing
Be very belief Smith
You bet he is saying that he's not a white nationalist
In the in the way that we are using the compound
But he sing what national sings
Dumb
That's astonishing and I'm not giving him like
Away off the hooker in no no I really don't understand
In the conversation
It's like you're taking even more credit away
Play sremmlife
If he understood what white nationalist
Because I do turn into
Optic some stuff like
Like that is like
Right right right
No
Well listen to this guy is that
If it were still culturally acceptable to say the N word around
Pawsitive spoiler alert
Knox
Throws it around
But like he is so fine thing a hard r
Like quote
Stop
This is the Bad Dudes clips
Because there's like
I don't want
Minecraft
Civil rights
Not talking about the party switch
Is Democrat
Who cares
So call me
I don't know what
To do exactly about his
Is Ray stuff
But like
But its interests
Sing to me and that's why I think
Possible
Someone who week
Look more into and enjoy be
Because
That there is a
Chasm
Between reality and what
Understanding
Yeah that interest
It is interesting
Give me that he expresses very clearly white nationalist position right
Talk about how I am a white nationalist
He doesn't know what he's doing
And
Brash like
The conference
Is interesting
People who have
Hundreds of hours of episodes available for me to look at
Almost
Color it's
Weirdly ready like
People want me to watch them
Have you ever seen about white nationalist
You know that
Yeah colors do we have in
Do we have
Unfortunately
We have one more
Clips
The coaches put out
And in this could you call this clipper
Dude
Nscorp
It becomes clear that coaches
A little bit of a fee
Also
In his defense
If you are a coach
It does seem to run
Counter parallel to
You might my heart little bit heavy today thanks I just I'm sorry are you okay
Now you don't I was on my computer
It happens with some so many times I often have one of those
It'll pop up screens popping
Are the temptation to check on that thing
And have some
Pornography come before my eyes is a very very strong
Temptations always I don't care if you're man I don't care who you are
That's one of the greatest Temptations in all of
Old Society
Sing with bookmarks
We sing of irrational people here in America
We want to ban
Pornography
Come on now
Tomography
That is not a free speech issue
It is why not
Houston
Buddy
Get a pop-up blocker
Get
Get one of those like things you can put on it
Just block all pornography
There's so many
Free apps in like programs you
Just install
They like
If you try to go to a p*** website it will just put up the
Nope this is block I do not want to see his internet
Technological solutions
To the problem that he's expressing
I don't want to be tempted by this stuff
Well number one
Donahue
Choose your battle
Nobody
Aren't you a conservative is about personal responsibility
Crutches you can
Use because
You have problems with the online for
You can
You confused
If you don't want to be her blog
It is a free speech issue
My friend the reason
This is very
It's things that we see
In the world like a foster
They were pretending
To be moral
Moralizing
People advertising sex work online
They wind up doing is demonizing sex workers and
Where is someone
Kills
The result
Yep incredibly difficult
Newton horses
Rooms To Go outlet
Their own
Safe spaces on
Online where they can
Choose their clients
Yep
Creates an incentive
Attempts to show up
Instart systemically
Music
What did he say
Doing is trying
Create this Borel
Idea about life
Get rid of
Dysfunctional reality is what he's advik
Further
Wayward
Worse
Victims
Entire
Policy
I am
Tax cuts are the way to go now admittedly every time we run one of these
Is Matt the tax cut
It creates a massive government ultimately hate but ideologically we still have to support
We hate abortion murder of unborn fetuses
Birth control because that's the same thing
Leads to more murders of unborn fetuses
Of course that leads to more illegal
And it leads to more death but
Ideological
It sounds right
Truly look at the results
Of the dumb s*** we believe
Otherwise we would have to accept the worsening
Of the s*** that we desire for control is real
The fake reasons we are saying we are
Things to happen
Baseline Hayward America
America
What is
Problem with foreign
It is
Consensual Act
Queen adult regulator
Regulation but we need to regulate
Between adults can't be video tape for other people's enjoyment
Crazy slippery slope
So it's not
Anyways approaches expresses that he hangs out exclusively with Liars
I wonder if we were doing
Local church
If you go into any local businesses and if you were able to get an honest survey
Business or in that church
A regular viewer
Nothing
Dark secret isn't it kind of except in open
Pornography
Set the end result of pornography and most cases are looking at pornography
Unless masturbation
Snowman talk about that no man is probably saving that does that
This is crazy this is a lunatic
A lot of people like to talk about it
A lot of people enjoy it when you talk about it also remember that
Like I'm not so old
I'm not so young
But I don't remember
The function of whatever
Being very tubu invite High School
Everyone pretended they didn't masturbating didn't look at 4
But as you got older it's
It's certainly not
The most polite topic of conversation
Feel like you and I are
Good friends
But if we go out and get a drink I'm not going to be coming up towards
I'm not going to create a false reality
I think he's lives in this
Weird false reality where everyone's like absolutely
Wow you're wrestling with your your addiction and I
Publicly you trying to do much weirder than that
Your your clothes but it's
Stories
So crazy last clip
And it's where
Cerakote
Makes his up
About his position
Pornography and how Danger
But even worse than that
Pornography is destroying this land is destroying families
It's destroying careers
It's destroying oh my goodness our young people
I remember when you used to be standards in iMovie that you just
R-rated neighbor Jeep
The stuff that comes across a movie screen is just unbelievably City
But if you like me happen to be somebody who enjoys
Research on the computer
His final answer the banned pornography Society
Passing of people who merely view pornography
What are finding their lives ruined
Because of an addiction that got the cleanup.
Apple types of
Pornography is a greatest Scourge in America and I States time for us
As a God-fearing decent people
Once again banned pornography that you really need
The format in the phrase of a question otherwise it's not a correct answer
Coach's comments about Bernard
Murphy and write them off
The right-wing Christian
Fundamental
Doesn't want anyone
Macaron morel
Choices
However there's a larger
My coach has
Specific
Complaints about pornography
Kirby azenzone pornography
Why is he saying the people are going to jail for looking at pornography
That's absolutely not true unless the pornography
People all my God
Holyshit
Here's the Joe Paterno Jesus
In that one clip
We f****** curious as hell
Yeah people going to jail for pornography
It made me
Oh no
2007 coaches on Plano Road
Having a minor legal language caught with child pronography
Coaches son's computer broke and when it was taken into the shop a bunch of pornography featuring underage girls was found on
And the repairman called the
According to police 37 still images in 26 movies
The files were labeled in such a way as to make it very clear
That any person
Who had those files on their computer could not be unaware
That they featured illegal
He was sentenced to five years probation
Can you put on the sex
Who is credit coaches son
To the probation engaged and Rehabilitation
From all sources I can find included testimony from his therapist
He dealt with the underlying issues and has never really
None of that is to let him off the hook
It's just to say that he was a super privilege kid who ended up being given a chance
To save his own life
You didn't respond
Now
This is most of the information that's available from court records
But I found a different
Light on to the case of coaches
This isn't going to go well
He been a teacher
Which obviously know this is super not going to go well now he obviously had to
Quit that job when he was arrested for possession
So you need to find a new career
Coach got a job as a
Administrative
Search for a lawyer that he knew
Coach's son began to find a passion
A lot
He went on to study and attended law school graduating in 2011
At that point you have to apply to take
Take the bar exam
Which percent problem
That had to be decided by the
Supreme Court of Ohio
You can't be a sex offender and a lawyer at the same time
You see the issue was with the Ohio bar didn't allow mission
Quote who has been convicted
Money before the
Candidate is released from parole probation
Community Control
Post-release control or prison
Rule however does not mandate the disapproval of
Applicants
Remain obligated
Asterisk
Sanders
Therap
Locations cuz nobody thought that would be an issue this was a technicality that they do
Didn't know what to do with desiccation and the results of that investigation
Are public
From this document you find that it wasn't
Does this guy have any
Legal pornography
Thawed out coaches Donovan downloading trading and Sherry legal
5 years
At the point when he was
Boy they found
He committed his offense as an adult
And despite his professed interest in videos depicting underage girls
Naked girls
Some of the files bad person you're involved
Young children young children
F****** Christ ultimately decided to his application
We are also concerned that even as a college student daubenmeyer fail to appreciate
Appreciate the gravity
Visconti
Or the fact
The children depicted in those illegal materials were in
In fact victims of his conduct
Until after he was caught holyshit
Clear the
Really bad stuff
But this isn't about coach's son
It's about coach
Any investigation regarding coaches son's application
For the bar his therapist Candice Rising
Was interviewed and she said the follow
Based on her she believed that there were two
Primary
First you believe that his repressed upbringing
Cost of 26
Experience vicarious
Rather than engage
An age-appropriate
Yes course
She also found that he had developed anger toward and resentment of his father
And who would have been subject to embarrassed
He failed to live up to those
You're no such things make
Clearwire coach thanks
The band Foreigner
And it's not because of God
It's because it's a convenient way
Hot to address
The issues of his life without having
To wrestle with the possibility
Is raising his kids and it'll be
That leads to
This sort of thing
I don't get none of this is to
His son off the hook
And the reason I'm referring to him as coaches.
There's no need to put it
Right there's no anybody
I can find it. It's all public and all that
But I'm not here to beat up on his son
I mean I think he's awful and
This is terrible
Terrible
Terrible Behavior
I do
Appreciate the idea that has been rebuilt
Is possible and all that
That that's great but
The reality of the situation is coaches
Coming out he's expressing this thing of
We need to ban pornography
And who pitched
Banning something
Adult
Each other
And a lot of people really sucking in Troy
It doesn't
Anybody Annex
Really helps a lot of people
City putting out until
The world specifically
Sex worker
By and large women
There are men
It's a lot of with
And
The reason that
He's doing it
Very clear
When you look into
Just passed
And his life
Because it's
He had a prince
In the middle of his pitch to
Pornography
He wouldn't stay
They're sending people to
The jail for
Viewing pornography
Because that's what they do when
People View
Illegal Toronado
Which is what his son was
Was doing 45
He doesn't have a point
He's acting out
That's f***** up
In a way that is
Even
Certain extent like of course you empathize with this kid cuz his dad is this f****** guy
In the same way that you emphasized with the serial killer when he's like 9 years old and his abuse is rampant
And rice and Munster
And you like I empathize with you but at the same time
A lot of people get abused and don't turn into pedophiles
A lot of people are pedophiles and unfortunately the way that human sexuality works you don't always get
And I don't f****** know
Fuckedupshit
And I don't
God I want a simple thing where I can just
Be like
He's turning it into something where it's like
This whole thing is
Not an issue
With an issue is I get to say
This is the problem
And I have the solution it'll never be a problem again
Personal life isn't
He's putting Lake in order
To create ways to
Advocate
Controlling other people's lives
Exactly
Send the other thing
There was another clip I was going to play but it
Just felt stupid
And that was a video coach put out about how the pedophiles
In the same way that Alex
And when you see the reality of like
Your son was arrested
For sharing
C*********
In 45 years
Computer broken
Realize
They would find it when
Jesus
He probably wouldn't
Have stopped
If the computer hadn't
Broken
If you had been caught I would you
Him trying to
Create this
Very Alex Jones via Narrative of the pedophiles are
Is very hard to look at
And then at the same time
I know we talked about this
He started that
Minutemen
A group
Yep that advocated for Roy Moore
And spoiler alert
After all the news came out about Roy Moore
He put out videos
With Roy Moore
So when you look at the concrete reality of situation
Yeah
Pretending that he's on the right side but
Everything is wrong
Everything
His idea historical context
Charlottesville
Slavery in the Civil Rights is f****** stupid
His position on
Pornography can't be
Because he
Clearly is
Is acting out
Some sort of unresolved feelings
He has about his
You can't f******
Listen to him about them
Mandela effect
You shouldn't
Except
Accredited psychologists study a memory like
It is a mess this guy is a tremendous
It needs all the worst
It's all the worse
Cuz he's
So clearly just
F****** stupid
Is very stew
8 is all the work
He would if you would to be fine with whatever
This man
He would never have said
People are going to jail
At pornography
Strong indication
F****** stew
Because that's what's underneath
Done
Got in legal trouble for looking at child pronography
Really should have just happened is it should have been
Except for what
And it is
And
That's the problem
Is in place
About these I'm angry at my son
Ecology
For me
Because I consider him an extension of myself
Yeah and that's one of the reasons why
Winfield
Talkin about this
I don't want to see his son
Because it's
So it's not like
It's not like
What his son did
Eating pork
Because it informs
Is rhetoric
And the way he puts it is that it's not
Something
The way he puts it is that it is something that is
Happening to him
In a larger sense
Not even like
Condemning his son along with it
Is a condemnation of
Every other thing on this f****** planet
Is probably the most by George Soros
There was there was a papa
That came on it
Computer and he got addicted to pornography
Murphy and then what are you
Yep it has nothing to do with
Everything is about personal choice
Except for when my family does something
That is their personal choice that went badly
Create near fascistic laws about what adults can do with each other
Kid safe dance
What's velvet there was still a hammer to come in
So if you got
Having said all that we have
There's more
If it's coach basket that week
If you want us to
We are we may do that
I think that he is a fertile soil
In terms of
The amount of content that's out there
And a couple of things
Songs that I know
How do upset
I would be
Fine with doing
Future episodes of coach
Doing this episode
Peeling off of the Band-Aid
We hope you enjoyed this episode
Sorry also
Dollartree.com
Toronto Facebook
Keep on doing it
Exact
Should have last week's
One week
This crazy preacher who wants to murder gay people
Second week
Crystal child who makes good
Who's the murderer
Wacky Wednesday is getting real
It's crazy
That might be better
So anyway I don't want
Charles from Final Table never killed anybody
Is it
Express beautiful art through food
It was so great to weigh that Charles
Charles especially would like
Pay homage
Do the ingredients
Did he was using
The seed for this
F******
Superb noxious
Irreverent to me and I love it
Just Express themselves
Through that Avenue though
They also expressed
Advocate
Renewable food store solutely vegetarian food sources
Like I think in the first episode they made whatever
Yeah they were trying to
Do alternative Pro Take Back Time making delicious food they were awesome
They never killed anybody had kids did not kill anybody
Technically
Probably
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color