Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
Last time you director
Get somebody to do
No I mean what
Play go tell my friends to go pick up a quarter for me or something
Nothing crazy illegal
I'm totally legal I'm fine I do
Bunch of guilt about it
Outside of that I don't know I don't think I've ever direct
Did anybody to commit a crime
Never
Never know hits
Never put a hit out on a positive on that one yeah okay
Material what are you doing
No you didn't you didn't
Reboot
I've been working all day I kind of have
I've gotten today is about Maria butina
Two eyes
Asra is going to unfold while right now
Hey there's a show where I know a lot about Alex
Various
That's because I've been
Deep in here and I've got interesting modern-day episode alright
December 12th
I'm 13th episode of The Alex Jones Show
There's some really stupid Malik Springs up
I would say is it one of the bigger meltdowns at everything from Alex
I haven't gone there
On this Earth
Alright I'm waiting on that
Real grub
He
You needed someone like Rob due to hit him with a tranq
Dart that's really it's at the level he's getting too
Yeah
It's real bad but not real bad I was about to make that transition
Varsity version of my
What's not low-hanging what is my feelings
Thank you Jesus
Signed up and are supporting the show first
I'd like to thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Thank you so much you are now a policy
I'm a policy wonk also Garrett
Thank you so much for not only feeling
Popcorn
Finally Alexa
An elevated level
We appreciate it very much so
Flik
Cool spelling
We appreciate it thank you you are now a technocrat
Dogs get mad and tell her you're brilliant someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
Thank you so much
Our website
It's knowledge, there's a button on the top of the show
Absolute
For today
Start
The 12th which would be Wednesday
Show off
Little bit of a strange note
Reno's from by murdering a prole
Strange note
Bsharp
Paranormal
Trump ad
Had his little meeting with Pelosi and Schumer
They went
Where
Weather like
Shouldn't debate list in front of
Ridiculous
Alright
Very very uncomfortable so I thought that this was going to be something that Alex
Which brings up a ton
I thought it was going to be
Oh and the reason we're starting on Wednesdays because Alex was out of the studio for the
Speeding days
Alex
Had gone to Washington
Yes even I couldn't
He and Rodger Stone went to Washington and
Alex Wassabi
A proud of himself
U-Pull-It price of course he was super proud about that a lot about Trump
Pelosi and Schumer
At all on the 12th
Instead of his main story
What did they do anything
What do you mean
I mean like they went
Create a media spectacle.
A bunch of rats
It's b b sort of
Slightly less embarrassing version of Loomer
Tying herself to Twitter
Why have you been to me
But
Ashok throughout the show
And there is
0 deaths
Do it in his reporting
It is just one fact
But he's throwing
Google World Headquarters it's the number to the China is on fire right now
Lots.com at newswars.com
Large explosion
Nope
Yesterday
New York all sorts of things are going on behind the scenes
Obviously the head of Google
Sundar
Fromage when we were simply pointing out the operation was totally illegal
Never brought up
Public Enemy Number One
Okay so Google has a building
Office
Headquarter in China
Conditioning unit that apparently caught on fire on the roof
First of all that Google has moved their headquarters entirely
And then there was an explosion in the building
Huge fire
Over and over
I don't know why that's a repetitive
I don't wish fire on Google
Crazy his argument
That
Like
Google pull the
Baltimore Colts situation in the dead of night all the sudden
Moved all of their employees
To China and then the building is just a
Yeah I would say that's one possibility the other possibility is that they've been slow
Probably work
Alright
Either would be like nope
Awful as it is
The buyer in the Google building
Google
The testimony from the earrings
They said that it is not
Haven't done it
But they also
Didn't rule out that they might
Start working on it already
At the same time it's like
So if you want to do busy
In China
You do
It's awful
Precedent
Certainly
Another are explicitly like Google is working
With China to Roundup desert
Right and as much as you
You could save it like the government of China might use the repressive
Free speech
Rules
Father Google be complicit
Part that they're helping with rounding up dissonance
Make it stretch
It's for that but it's not like
Google CEO's are out there
On horseback
The
I mean it's like China isn't already doing a great job of that on their own help
Cupboard
Ninja talking about how everything is going great for the Patriots
He's wrong about literally everything
Ultramassive news
How big is it
Huge that you have macron set tomorrow for a no-confidence vote may be removed from office probably will be
No confidence vote today
The fall of the New World Order
Remember what happened a month ago
Merkel's party out of power
Didn't happen
But now she's a
Nope
You still there
Can I keep listing all this
Cool boy
Love love that he just throws in Brazil every time he's talking about these awesome situation
You know the situation in European politics
Germany Angela Merkel was replaced by and a great camp karrenbauer
Who has called for the legacy of Angela Merkel
While opposing candidate Frederick murders
Democrat
Except
Angela Merkel is also from that party
Crab carrot carrot
Karen Bowersox in general but
Merkel
Merkel get defeated
Cheap and Chancellor for 13 years
You receive diminished
Support in the last election
She announced in October
That you wouldn't seek re-election
In terms of change this is a 0 party becoming chance
He said they're going to protect
Continuity with merkel's agenda
Macron is facing a no-confidence vote in the aftermath
To be really dicey yellow vest protest
Have been consumed in the country
The concern is that he hasn't been effective in handling
The vote also
This isn't some kind of Auntie globalist maneuver
The no-confidence vote is being spearheaded by the French Communist party and the Socialist Party
For finally low right now but no serious analyst
Is expecting that vote to succeed
Also Theresa May survive the no-confidence vote on when is was an attempt
This was not an attempt
Teacher as we understand that
It was a
Tory party MPS to decide whether or not they had confidence in her leadership
The party
She won the vote 202 117
Exhaust
Is protected
Facing another leadership challenge for a year
All of Alex
Examples are not true
There's no purging of globalist leaders
And even if this were a series of globalist Crusades
Paul not produced any of the results
Super
So much as
Yeah alive
And with me
Understand whenever you was talking about me being part of the
Global
She's the one leading
Brexit liked isn't he
Because that's
I literally don't know
Yeah
Knowing that
The same time
Who is waiting in the wings
Comments after the no-confidence vote even though she
She's like this sucks
It sucks that a third of my own party dozen
But I don't think that excludes
In the same way that before Trump
Came around
He wouldn't have allowed any US president not to be
I don't think that he could look at a president or prime minister in the UK that wasn't Nigel farage
I think that they are also
You know Teresa maze
For brexit which is actually doing I'm guessing
Acting like she's for brexit
But she's really just there to manage
Make sure the brexit isn't
Heize empty globalist as
It could be
Actually
True though
There might be some accurate pieces of it but it's not true
I don't think she
Really
Quote unquote
EU
Pretty much
Results of this is either going to wind up being a hard
No Deal brexit
Fedora second
Referendum
Where people are like
This was a terrible
We want to do over
Right button
Even this conversation of fanciful ideas of what Alex may or may not believe
Black and white
Where in the politicians are globalist or they aren't
And this really is
Part and parcel of Alex's worlds
We know that we can't have faith in that
But that black and white
Really comes in in this next week
Important
For this country this is the real
Decide which side they're on
There's only
Switzerland
That black-and-white thinking
That right there there are only Patriots and globalist
There is an appositive
That
Is how you end up supporting Nazis
That is how you end up supporting white nationalist white supremacist
Because based on the dichotomy those globalist Ergo they are nationalist
Cool awesome human potential people
If there is there is only two camps people can begin
You are on the side of all people who are
Against
Globalist
Now you got a lot of Nazis
Even your Rex and that's how it becomes okay exactly right there is
The softest version of radical
Elevation
Alex
Yeah
It is
Babe I mean
Probably as close as possible to
The reality of
Politico
Specifically
From the right wing
I think Alexis guilty either too
Oversimplified categorization in
That is one of those
Things where you do not like my family
I don't agree with all of these things but it's like you're still at
Rally with a lot of nuts
I'm at not at a rally with Nazi
One of us
Is closer tonight
You're not or not
Yeah
But you're awful you know it's just how you become acclimated
It's the
It's mean it's the worst version of the enemy of my enemy is my friend kind of diet
Especially
Dichotomy
Space song
A false
Similarity of ideas
People listening to it could easily be tricked into thinking
Japan immigrants
Coming into the country
There
Anyway we already sort of touched on this
The clip just a second ago
But Alex has some more things to say about
Did Brazil that stupid
Yikes literally talk
Haha yeah oh yeah
It's the guy
He's a brother
Little bit
Because
His like
The new Trump down there kind of thing it really
If he knows anything it reveals deeply what he's attracted
Big f****** problem
Yes so anyway I just
Alex lost after Authority
First reaction herbal like by sigala
Whoa whoa whoa
Trump isn't bolsonaro
You know in your life
She's not a
Military
Different circumstances in American American history economy
Very easily see
The sort of person who puts out
Rhetoric in the world
The actions that
Trump does
Exactly that way words
In that circumstance
Anyway NSX clip Alex screams
Rodger Stone
Real American
The world
However
Rodger Stone Alex Jones or Donald Trump jr.
Where are the Americans
You better understand
Rodger Stone Alex Jones @donaldtrumpjr this
Scream Adam
Remember the beginning of episode Maria butina was that she pled guilty to conspiracy
United States
Are they walking in a straight line because they all have some
Have you ever seen that music video
Resetting Rocksteady
They did another song called the Heap On Loving You
Is exactly how
I won't go watch that video picture Alex the Rodger Stone and Donald Trump
Snapping around like dancing across the
Play side to side on the sidewalk
My favorite parts of the show are you explaining anachronistic music by The Whispers are out
Hit machine
There's a man on top of that
Are twins
Crazy mustache
All right I like that
It's real to watch these like these are in
B cigarettes
All in like weird
Suits
It's not the same
I drove a sidewalk
I don't know I don't know
That
A hundred percent should to end
Should have explored never have
I can see you ignore it but the most recent albums
I'm sure I should look into them and I will I'll make a commitment to do that but the reason I think
Is it because of like
The groups of
People I was around who were really into them
Maybe
9 years ago
I don't want to possibly really like something
Anyway
I don't believe Alex Wolff
Real America
I would like to roll down the window and
Also in addition to Pelosi Schumer Trump meeting
Broken here before the
Was that
Descendants 2 3
3 years for his his behaviors
Michael Cohen obviously in the last 30 minutes they announced
He's getting three years for congress about Trump Russia Tower
And of course there's nothing
Not this guy
3 years instead of 20 years
$15 money laundering
Stop show
Getting fat
What a monstrous little Trader
But a sack of garbage
Michael Cohen is
Cool
I love the like video
Camila who are you at I know that Alex makes the Donald Trump stands for America now so I guess
Like betraying him is betraying America
Trader idea comes from
It's going to be so fun in the coming
Like months to speed
That's Bush League stuff reflects for him to make like bending over backwards to be like
Yeah Michael Collins Eliza was going to do with Trump
Domino's
Feels like they're going to
It's going to be much more difficult
His his strolling partner Don juniors
That could be
Donald Trump jr. was his and bike certificate is that bad on air
No problems about Michael Flynn
In a really long time
That is why we used to talk about how he was a super-patriot trying to get
Googling out of the country because gulen was evil and all this stuff
Extradition
Outside the law
And he can talk to her. Thankfully Alex's stop talkin about that so
His audience will have forgotten
He was so
Pro Mike Flynn
And he can be like
He was all you was going rogue junior is going to be difficult
He already hates Jared
So I don't think that
Going to be a big deal
I'm just trying to picture how you makes his move
Like just an ability after this
I think it's possible
I think it is possible
What do you mean
Make your pitch.
Like how do you survive though I would have done it long ago I would have done it already
But
Let me we heard in that last current episode of
DUI
Perfect dismount
Really I mean it would involve
Stop by probably severing ties with Rodger Rodger on board with wherever you go in the future
Which is doable I think it's doable and if he stays out of prison
About Roger's going
Super easy
Iic almost
So when it does happen
Can use that as a
Jump off point
I don't know what he does from there but probably just goes back to Ron Paul s***
He can go again
The one who is lying to me this whole time
The only crime I committed
With loving my country
Jon rappoport sent me emails trying to turn him against me
No one tries to get Rapaport against to me
I don't know if there's a hole there's a whole slew of options
I think it's Alex's smart and you want
You can't be able to continue with rhetoric
Do you have to get off
Yes please
Yeah and that is the perfect way for him to jump off
Because one of the only things that's left
The Trump
And Alex was super into
Was getting out of Master
Yeah any idea that you have this new version
Coming in
It undoes all a market is so awesome because of trump
Midas kind of gone away
He hasn't put Hillary in prison
None of this stuff is happy
All of the people that he put into office that Alex
Said we're going
Going to be amazing like just
Argon
There is nothing left
For him in terms of this dead husk
Of a presidency
For him to make propaganda out of
He needs a fresh start
And that's perfect.
Where you can still keep
At least
60% of his audience probably if he doesn't right yeah I think you'll lose some of those diehards and
Three monkeys radicalized too far
Will find a new home
I don't think
Has Trump
Actually done anything that Alec
Publicly wanted him to
Yes got out of NAFTA
The TPP EPP
Yeah but that's not really something that Alex
Idiosyncrasies
Desire
Like has Trump done any of those like
You clearly demonstrated the globe
Indicated a distrust of non-white
I mean the policy of separating families from their children
Alex loves that
Globalist
I don't know we're in the weeds back on track not much
I think it's just amazing
You never I don't really consider
Anything
Trump
Has done
Because it is only ever
Specifically benefited
Yeah but you know
But you know what he's done that makes up for so much of that
He at a rally publicly did the idea of being an ass
That means so much to Alex makeup for a multitude of zeros
He is existing on that like
That just
I'm starved for three days and then someone gives me bread and I love him
The time in the present because
He's in that position where he's
He's trying so desperately to
Like
I know it.
In this clip he's trying to complain about Mike Pompeo
I don't know why he doesn't explain at all in this clip he gets distracted by
Never gets back on track listen to this b*******
Call Mike Pompeo
Great guy
Mikey p
Is a butt boy
Pretty much
Quasi pedophilic
Interested in talking about you now just wants to talk about but
Resolved
Cabin Boy
Well let me tell you I'm SunChips
Okay
We all know that
Bugger your children's brains right out Nova
Following my mom's from Austin
Were some of them but for you
Building a structure
I don't understand
Mike pompeo's but let me tell you about the etymology of but
There was some weird
Central reason I believe often
Talking about leaving Austin for years
Even in a 2000
I got to get out of this
Really super Bazaar like
I'm all here for Alex complaining about how bad it was in the 1700s
Sure
All allowed
Privateers
We're not good people
So point
It's weird
The world that we living in
Like
Television
I don't know about forever
Hey that's a
Seriously homophobic slur what are you f****** doing it does feel that way it is
That's always been the Pirates
Is not associated with like
NAMBLA
That's just
What people preservative Lee called
Homosexual
Even even in his
Explanation of
He's still saying
Sexual is a pet
Man
A little bit
Alex's the Greeley Riding High on his success of going washing
Google CEO
He has a different
Definition
This is so stupid
You're going to get the world
Why they fear Infowars
Today
Tilde
Because I
Overall operations bubbles controller 90d
Secret project
Man
Palantir
What is Google secret projects like palantir the company was started by Peter teal
Accompany Vic hear you over the sound of Alex being too right
Loud House Radio
I don't know Peter Thiel noted Trump supporter
It was what he started
Palin
Rich person who has
Deliriously end
Deleteriously attacked journalism in
So this is why Alex
Is so
He makes
Google so scared cuz he knows about their secret
Not involved
He's crazy
The palantir
No, man
Reference
Is a big boy
And
He is there
The fight
Against tyranny
In all of its forms
Love evil and you love line
I do Club setting up systems
Sounds great I am your enemy and I swear
Altar of God
Eternal
Resistance against every form of tyranny
Also I'm super into what's going on
Brazil
And Philippines
Doterra
And
Russia
Killing it
All forms of tyranny
From
China specifically
That one
Form of tyranny
But
Murderers are empowered by the government
Traditionally kill whomever they just like
No big deal
Alex
Is a
I really need to cover on the 12th I wasn't all that productive a day
For a couple really fun like
A particular have even covered the 12th at all
Because the 13th is
Meet I just like knowing that Alex
Henry Google
I like knowing
At any point in time Alex could be reading anyone
I'm sitting by the fire
Reading Eggs
Well-worn Kindle
What he dreams about
He's late for a tab
We get into the 13th
Here the Thursday episode
You know
The news is broken about
Maria butina
Thought maybe
Alex is going to
Get into some defensive nest
I was wrong I can't predict Alex's Behavior
Any better than anybody else can
I can I can
Document
But he is so unpredictable
Instead of doing anything
That have to do with the current
He instead launches off
On a
Bucked up
Medical episode
Did what the first hour and a half at least this episode is wall-to-wall ramp
It is
Nothing
Except him just ranting
And here is where he sort of picks up his feet
Everything just in this one article
Bush was here I hadn't seen this article yet
Where do you look for it
What happened other parts of the world lathe imf-world Bank handles at
Handles
Documents
American design
I just get up here and get
Aesthetically
People won't get out dangerous it is and I
Really really angry
Myself
Because if I don't just sarcastically hate
Sorbets
Duet
It's hard
Hard
They're putting polio
In the backseat
First of all unless I snarkily yells that I hate people
Wow that's not good is another another
He probably technically killed a guy
What article he's talking about
You just sort of research
Anything
Anybody in order to get the story about an Indian pharmaceutical company shipping outfit
We contaminate
There's problems that story analysis
Company the one from
Germany you never know
He might just be pulling that story
The first is that the story broke in late September so it's not technically news
The second is that it was the result not of malice and wanting to give people Pollo
It was the result of faulty Manufacturing
It has been condemned by the US and European regulators
4 years
There's no regulatory oversight
And a lot of the Indian company
People who've gone on record
Infrastructure in place in order to assure quality assurance
That's everything which is why the US
And European authorities
To put out notices of like
Don't use this Indian medicine
Because oftentimes it will be some
It is not being produced
Right so then the third problem is
The only people who getting these potentially tainted
Did vaccines
For polio
Where in Maharashtra and uttar Pradesh
So no one in the United States or even effect
But even though it is still off
These people getting potentially tainted
Polio treatment
It is awesome
United States
All of the things that I
Ostensibly bringing into this narrative it makes him
Don't you cry
Then murder
It's not real
Go on for now I don't know I still don't know if that's the story he's talking about
But I thought
Close enough
So maybe they talked about
It's also not true
Polio vaccine
Seems or were they some other medicine
So these were like
The old
I seen is whether it's like
Well we put a dead version of the virus
Sentara whatever it is and you build up your
As I understand the articles that I read their investigations that are still ongoing
But the working Theory from what I read was that there was a wrong screen
Napoleon
It's it's the same thing that happened
From time to time you end up with
In countries with no regulatory state
With no
True
There were places where they have no oversight and
End up from time to time just by the law of averages you're going to
You're the wrong thing isn't it
And in terms of Medicine
Really high stakes
So amazing
That our quality isn't that great
It's like we don't even have a quality control Department
We want to see back Target
Some sort of globalization
But have really robots Industries
Like India does have a really large Pharmaceutical
Production
So you at places like that
But they aren't up to
Tubidy
Other
Country
Have established
You're only going to end up with
Lot of
Potential problem
Where is Aether work international regulations
I mean you probably couldn't end up doing something where
If it's produced in Indiana
India
You couldn't
Maybe oversee that
In terms of anything that's exported
Those probably are in place already
Kids
Which is still bad
Still waffle
I don't I still don't know if it's even the story we've been shipping them are romaine lettuce
So I'm sure they'll
I don't know but Alex
Talk more about it and gets even more so
Shots
Do you understand
The children
Sibley cover that up
I don't think you could
Not possible now
Sort of
Closed in the scope of what he's talking about
Pet store
Although maybe he would try and use that later to bolster whatever
Story start
But I still don't know what article you talk
Nothing
To go on except gases
So I looked around
December 10th article on ABC
But a new mysterious disease
That is in some cases paralyzing children
According to the article quote
Investigators of the current outbreak have ruled out polio finding no evidence of that virus
Some cases
So it's something to present similarly to polio but absolutely isn't
At no point like I said does Alex Best Buy with articles
Responding to
I mean it seems it seems pretty close to his second
By refining of the brethren
This isn't about polio
It's about a condition called acute flaccid myelitis
Which is
Is norovirus
Which folio is as well
They're over a hundred other enterovirus
Is it or not polio that exist
Most of these aren't very serious
Be treated very effective
As is the case with many diseases the severity of the cases of AMF
Depends largely on detection and on the doctor is being able to treat the condition
All Alex is doing by making making people distrustful of doctors here which
What he's doing
I was just making sure that people don't get appropriate treatment in time
Also
This isn't caused by vaccine
Illogical complication
After Eva 71
Infection that's what doctors are speculating
Is what
Precipitate
Dai Asm
Are so rare
Vaccine is not war
Dr. Vincent racaniello PhD professor of the Department of microbiology
Immunology Columbia University
Quote remember the poliovirus used to paralyze tens of thousands of children in United States
Which was
Whatever this is called
This is something that we don't
It's so rare that we don't treat with a vax
Speaking for it
So
The ideas
The vaccines precipitating
This is nonsense
And it's not
If something else
Presumably aiasf
Unfolding
Current doctors are still
A little bit up in the air about it but it's also not tens of thousands
It's not killing most
A lot of them have
Fairly minor reactions to it but
Call Sprouts
Minimize or
By the way Alex is using
King Salman
Closest
Super Tucson
Actually
Make people
Less likely
Me to take care of
Because quite frankly
This is super important
There is no cure for polio
There isn't one
The only thing you can do about it is
Get a vaccine
Does only prevent
Since 1988 ninety-nine percent drop in cases of polio
Since we started work.
Before then there was 350,000 children coming down with it annually
And this year there were 27
Whatever conspiratorial nonsense Alex paddling
Nothing
Close to the scientific validity of that level of result
Everybody
Has
Autism
That everyone in the world
Because if they if we
How many hundreds of thousands
Millions upon Millions
I assume
I mean through the used
The vaccine assumed everybody
Has autism
It's a wonder One
Resurgence of measles
Which it becomes
Vaccinations for it
Doctors are currently warnings that we are facing the very real possibility that we'll see the same thing with Pollo in the coming years
Cuz again
There is no cure for polio
The only way to handle it
Is there prevention with the vaccine
Creating fear B vaccine
Affecting the general
He's really good for Alex's business
But ultimately
If more people listen to
Yeah man act on his advice
It's going to leave
Polio
Real bad one
Because people can get it
Pretty easily
And the severity
Is very high
So this is really
I hate the things that I hate most about this
Whole bulshit that he's on right now
Is that
There is a real world
Corollary
That is
Jump in there with just move a couple of words around and you're talking about
Like
The government is poisoning our water
F******
They're killing children
A disease that we have
They're doing all of that
Alex just
Just change the narrative it doesn't have to
All you have to do you could
Alex producer
Real good
Michigan
Yeah I know polio outbreak real
Government
F****** disease
It kind of does suck
I mean
He would probably agree
On the point
But he just doesn't care to ever
Talk about it
Alex
Talk more about this
I have to go on it
Clearly
The best context clues I can
Confined
American World
3 million +
Heartbroke with Baltimore are playing there
That's why they love murdering people so much
I mean we went over that factor 8 story on recent
Episode
I don't know I lose track of time
Of American history
Fault
That would involve
But also
Creative atmosphere
Stigma
About
HIV and AIDS
That
And
Just taboo and not.
And absolutely could not have given less of a f*** when it wasn't it
Clip
About the vaccine stuff
And in this Alex's to warn people
That your kids are going to get vaccines
Without you
Consent
Which is very
There
Checks California
Dollar free debit card
California
We have
Add pivot but yeah.
That will give them polio because the globalist are offering them $200 to get you won't be able to choose
Big news
I finally solved the mystery that has been plaguing me since we started this podcast
I will be talking about it on the episode next week
It is the mystery of why does Alex Jones on the website Arnold exposed.com
I finally solved the mystery
Yes look at The Hardy Boys into this one what happened there
No
And I don't want
It's a wild story
Search on people
Infowars Prison Planet
Report Arnold exposed
Why you left
Does Alex running and
Anti Arnold Schwarzenegger
It's not just the domain websites that up about Arnold Schwarzenegger
No
Alex
We're done with the vaccine stuff for now and I get teased at the
This episode
Alex has a complete freak out
Breakdown on air
Coming and it wasn't him saying I'm going to cry and that I'm going to kill people
I feel like that is the beginning of a great room
The episode when he comes in with that
You knows it's like
It's to make it to our 3 without losing it
Maddie loses at heart but before he does
He said something that he probably one of the most grandiose ping
The person can say
And clothes
Very close
Kick-off one another and pick off another
Hearing about it and you
Adapt
Organizers
Pictures of program
But they looked at the actuaries triggered human survival Instinct
Because of my particular plan
Lead the Titans
Force
Pure micro
That will defeat the enemy
Blown major Holzman operations before
How
I got to get their program
So
Okay
Man what he is expressing
Is
The reason they kicked me off Facebook and Twitter and all this
It's because they
The globalist
Have actuaries
Number crunching and figured out that Alex Jones is break which is lying
Is the only thing
Wake up and save Humanity it's kicked in the survival response of humanity that is
Migrant narcissism
I also don't know what that means
Right before the clip
I am your God have the ability
I'm one of the only people
Brandon
Able to do is wake you up out of your slumber
Remind you that you need to survive
That is
Deeply
Deeply f*****-up
D please just
Follow me if you want to live
That vetted there's like a
Psychological term for that
Something along the lines of malignant
Call you sound like
Touch
That's just Ed McMahon
Titan
The old Star Search
Little girl
Doing
Star Search yet
Chibi lady be like
Goodbye
Didn't mean to be dismissive of you and Ed McMahon at the same time
No I wasn't even saying literally you sound like his Xbox
Deeply
Deeply flawed
Understanding of the history of a
Men's orca
Innovation
In America
B
Nope. But the truth of it is
And then the reality behind it
Even more f***** up
Get ready for a ride
5 years ago when they said we're going to have
Gay Scout leaders
Sounds like you are
What does vice versa mean
Murray
Happy freaking broseph solo balloons
Pennyworth
Walter's Erik
Is jet
Whoever is hitting that button has such a good timing too because like
18 man right
How's the weather
Looking like bowls apparel
It's almost like he has bathrooms trying to work against them.
Incredibly stupid for a number
The first of the Boy Scouts
Handout
Condoms there just available for people at the house centers
Is there a part of the
Event event
Available at Scout Jamboree
They didn't allow homosexual Scout leaders until 2000
Thirdly
Probably more important
The sexual abuse lawsuits that are potential
We going to result in the Boy Scouts filing for bankruptcy
Back here
The group was negligent in allowing a sex offender to be
Screw
All these acts happened between 1981
And have to do with Thomas
Who's arrested for molesting children
In 1961
Then allowed to join other troops at
After the fact
So there's a group of scouts because of that
And they were negligent for having
Call
To Noah
Children
And they allowed him
How to be a scout leader
In addition does another lawsuit wear for men are suing the boy scouts over abuse that happened
Between 19/7
Before the 1970s
They're a lot more current instances of abuse in the Boy Scouts
But the major lawsuits that they're facing right now have to do with the vents
From decades ago before there were condoms
And before gays were welcome
Nothing but Alex is doing here is real
He's just demonizing both Sexual Health practices
And the lgbtq community by connecting them to
Completely unrelated issue
Of sexual predators unfortunately
Probably accurately
Seen the Boy Scouts as a place where they can
Easley fine
And unfortunately and doing the research for this
We don't need to get into
Arrow locks
Of instances of abuse
There are
Chicken plate that
Into some sort of
Condoms being available thing is complete.
It's sewing
Infuriating whenever that line of
Bulshit shows up
Every single time I bring them up because I'm talking
Think about pedophilia yeah and also
I don't have a problem with men who like men or vice versa is that
Mike's adventure
Vice versa
It's gross it's so gross
It's f****** awful and it's it's
Just like that b******* like
Oh I don't want a trans
Woman using the women's bathroom
They're going to attack my kid
Transport
Every single
Oh I don't want I don't want these kids to go to this place where they're homosexual
Youth group leaders
Molest more children
Anything like that I'm glad that we're finally all on board with the
Catholic Church
Pedophilia
Really this is crazy
The problem in the Catholic Church
Exist without them allowing gay
I'm not sure
They do now I don't
We can practice their rule
The issue exists without them supporting condoms
Just trying to present as being important
In the Boy Scout abuse history
It clearly isn't relevant in the fact that he
Brings up this
Catholic Church
As like soda
Does parallel thing
The element
He's trying to use
To connect to them don't
Inference
Complete
I did not know that crazy early for them to Beyond on that tip
Well because there are adults
There and also because some of the kids are of
Is legal I can't wipe
Boy Scouts
Hello by
World Health
And they got on board with it I don't know
Very interesting
Maybe I would have
We do whole episode about the discount being on Sexual Health early tip
Definitely early
Personally
Now Jordan
We're going to get to what
What is going to take us to
The end of the
V
Most
Extent of what Alex Jones like
So whenever somebody
Has been described
Subway
In the public eye
Cuz they're secretly liberals.
That's the only thing that makes
When Milo fell out of Grace
Yeah Alex
Quick to have him on his show
In order to try and get
Some of that sweet sweet attention
That comes along with a person be
The platform
I don't worry about that
Is 8
The exact same thing once somebody
Is in the Press enough
Alex wants to
The common
And ride their coattails
Yeah
SO2 the thirty-year-old
Now
Ennis
Interview
There's a really interesting
Dynamic
Play and that is
That Alex wants to
Inspired
He wants to tell Gavin
You need
To get on your f***
Walking bike
And he says that they
Hindrance
Then just call them Nazi and racist again and again and again and then they spend their time defending
That
We're just busy
I mean if you say where can people find me
Nowhere
I'm done
You coming on here and Alex is going to try and like the
You we got it you got to fight you got to fight and consistently Gavin's like
No
I would done
Hilarious
I don't I don't know if he's trolling Alex
I don't know what's going on I hate Gavin McInnes
Brain
He is awful
But in this episode
Because he
It drives Alex
Points of insanity we have not seen in a very long time
Complains about what the Liberals
In order to make sure
They appear to be human
Robin Wright
Interrupt
Here's another trick
Pick protection of their kids
And you
That's a wonderful family person
You're scowling like this
And then you can make
He can you can vanish
If I can get rid of a person I got rid of Hitler
Gavin McInnes has featured his son and a number of the videos he posted online
Also point of order
He's done work for him on air broadcast was there when Alex
Bernie Sanders at an airport
What the f*** do your family
What are those perfect no one would have a problem
At all if they presented
Did themselves
With their family
No one would get like you they wouldn't get any more threats than people on the left
By the way
Way more
They can't possibly believe that
This has to be like
It's just outright or arguing for victim
Goodyear
Outside of the Alex trying to inspire Gavin
No
Outside of that
The entire interview is about Alex saying that the proud boys are really awesome
They're Heroes
They're the victims in all this cuz antifa keep starting fight
And that the proud boys finish
And then at the same time
The line of we are the greatest and strongest but also were the victim of every
Don't understand how you can actually believe that
Like because because all of that like because
Finishing them on the ground as the them up as a group
Lightspeed
The metaphor that dr. Whitaker
A2000
We were talking about
That strategy the doctors of
People have healthy 6:30
It's the same thing
They know that they have to present this idea of
Ask Macho super-powered Western males who are ready ready to fight
Cuz I need that to get people interested in joining
But at the same time they have to have that
That is
We're the victims of everything
Conspiracy against.
To explain why they're not successful in anything
Because otherwise people who are attracted to
To the masculine power
That they're presenting
What is start asking question
Done
Wyatt why is this just like
Do you know
It's
The same strategy
Do you have to walk
If you don't
There's a problem
You don't get recruitment without the masculinity and power and you don't
Get retention
Without the
The facade of conspiracy against
I think that
The victimhood at this point probably
Proud boys band
That like the fantasy I don't know maybe is masculinity
But the reality is Aldi's
Disinfected
White nationalist
Are are like
Why aren't I allowed it
Do everything I want to do and then they join us
You're possibly right that
The victimhood part is
Appealing piece of it but
Even in that
Case even in so much as that
V
Is the proposed solution to those
Exactly
So that's
Spiritually what
22 is the scapegoating
An excuse for your own in
Sexual life
What is
Really drawing you is the idea of
These Rowdy men
Who like to fight
The answer is that these feelings
Meanwhile you joined up and then you find out all those feelings are really with motivating
And then your service
Finally finally a group
Come together and decided that violence will solve their problem
Always I've been waiting a tight
Time for the true Awakening form n4110 the human
To come together in
Decide that violence
People solve problem
New York
After that meeting
Or whatever the Gavin dead
There was of course the incident
In trouble with the law
You know if you look at multiple angles of it that are synced up definitely see
What the situation is
Is the proud boys
We're charging at these people
One of them threw something at the people who were already charging at them
And then the fight started
So the ideas boys were victims and that is
That is the presentation
The Gavin is going
Put out onto the
Disperse they went around the block came back
These guys
And they say FU Pig
Band
Just not accurate based on the video.
I can't being on the show
He has nothing to plug and he says he's done with all the s***
So like all he wants
Donate to help these guys because they're in legal trouble
The only thing you plugs is the fundraiser for his proud boys
Citrus 2
Jose
Vixen
Resent that
And he even goes on to say that like his whole
Video where he disavowed
Proud boys are whatever
Alex is trying to present it as like
They were threatening
So you did
And Gavin explained very clearly that the situation
In order for some group to be called a gang
Legal definition
Require crimes
And there has to be a leader
So if there isn't a leader it hurts the argument that there's a gang
So
His intention was to get on
Publicly is a
Best he could
Step down as the leader of this group
Eid
Is the leader of a gang
But if you did that maybe you would help with her sentencing
Because the
Right
Someone being like you
You step down Route
Track though
Because wouldn't
Like him sayings
He knows that this is why they would be
Considered a gang
Suggest that he knew they were a gang
Prosecutor
Infowars
What is essentially saying
He's admitting that
Hindu they were a gang and they are again
So
Stupid on Rogan I think his direct quote was I started a game
There is something
There is something to be said about the fact that he unlike so many other
Craven
Stupid
Opportunistic assholes it is
Still holding a fundraiser for the
You guys go ahead of just abandon
I don't think that
I think that's the definition of cold comfort and he acted like a
Kind of got to give a little bit of
Distance myself from
Gavin
Probably filled response
We're leading these people into these groups that have been created it
The direct result of it
He publicly wants to
You place the blame
Define
No matter what you presenting and all that stuff yet
Valois version of a compliment I can
Could have not done
Not suffered from not
You get one more morality point that Alex Jones does which still puts you at -2
Alex
Yeah who knows what those
Anyway who cares
Because at this point
I kind of got the sense that
Gavin is on for the reasons
Which is
Rewrite the history of that New York event
Course
Like just make the proud boys look like there
Western
Gyros
And stuff like that
Basically proper
Buganda
Is going to ride the coattails of
Gavin just kicked off Glenn Beck Network
That's a great moment for me
I can now take him maybe trying
Get him on Infowars
Maybe I can
Or at very least
On my show is going to get me a lot of it
I thought that was the games are playing
I almost didn't want to cover it
Cuz I almost felt like
You hate Gavin
No one really likes Gavin that much
But then Alex that this
Famous
Read the entire inherently bad
Michael Evans behling
Taxi
Jean-Pierre races
White Martin Luther King
Alex loves to throw around
It's strange
How long is there are on that show
Wow
Give me
I'm not even asking for a ton of parallel
I am just asking
42 parallel
Between Gavin McInnes
Martin Luther King
Parallel
North America
I don't know
I feel like I've seen enough
Gavin's Shota
Hitman Martin Luther King have
Serious
I can't think of any
Not at all
Together in a room
F****** Ebony and Ivory man
That's what it would be
Google
Compilation of
Eclipse
Gavin McInnes
It's so easy to imagine Martin Luther King save those things
So
In order to reinforce
Gavin
Ideas there's a victim
The proud boys are the victim
Traffic situation
Bulshit
Document
11 months ago
Alexander Soros
How to try to get black Americans to Riot
We have all this.
Baltimore
These are real document this is what they do
No it's not no it's not
Documents
So you found on 4chan
This is
This is crazy
Dishwasher
No because
It proves everything.
He doesn't have to
You could just be way less specific
It is interesting that he doesn't get to
Story Road
You know like yeah Wile and he does get the
About like it being a guy whose brother
At least muddy them so it's harder to dig me to figure out what he's talking about
It's because
It is
The Smoking Gun
Like I did
Papers are always the smoking goddamn behind all of this
The planet all the people who are free
They are just standing up
The agitation
The actual
A white nationalist
Who also
Wants to bring in martial law
George soros's plan
They ferment the race war which is required to bring in martial law
To a FEMA camp
I don't have any plans after that
So okay so you bringing martial arts
Dude
Stop the race worth
No because what you do
Deployed
Bio weapon
This is starting to become a good plan
No it's not
I mean
City has anyway
Jordan
I miss Mexico
We get to
What I would say
Is the reason for the season
Christmas is coming early
And this is
There are
Few things
Fill me with joy when I listen to Alice
Ain't like it's really tough
For me to sit here on this podcast
Until you
That Alex Jones and Gavin McInnes brought me a ton of Joy but this next clip
The Dynamics at play
F******
Hilarious
I'm already 5000
Points with you
You're a smart guy
I've been through this I learned
Years ago just say you're sorry the Sandy Hook parents
People getting
Holy mackerel
I just said just say you're sorry is all.
I said that
Kitchen
He's sending people their houses right now
No one's saying that
They're just saying that because of the rhetoric that he perpetuated people have been showing up at harassment
Shut up
It's all a setup
Any prosecutor because they've learned how to use our Humanity to manipulate us
You guys are heroes
You're a hero
They probably have never gotten arrested anywhere
Thank you
Your Hiroshima
Turn on the persecution
Distraught
Destroyed
They want about that
Stephen Hawking
Appropriate
Somebody is f****** with it
Lecture about how like
You know when you say sorry that's when they attack you the most cuz they try and manipulate ER Humanity
Destroyed me
Nope not the Six Million Dollar Man I'm
Stephen Hawking
Glenn Beck weird outfit out
I can't go back to Rebel media
I love I love how Alex
You can't afford me
Actually
Gavin have to get before he
Jones Infowars
I don't know I think I think
In terms of him saying I'm out
But I could easily see someone like him being like
The Coincidence of this line of fascism that I've been going down
Cuz it Doesn't
Like as much as he is a monster
He's LED like these
Is really horrible things
Colonel
Sims 2
Think that
He's joking
Like he thinks he's drunk
Isaac
He could walk away from the knot
Any like
Shores of credibility or anything like that
But he could walk away from this
Forget a f******
I don't know
If he's not
You f***** up
A lot of money when he was bought out at Feist
I assume you didn't invest that all-in proud boys
A lot of money off of
35 Grand right
Think it's 350
I thought he said 35,000
Points
You got to keep going
I don't know
To Delight in someone else's misery or anyting
I can also say like
Hearing him say
You don't like
These are the consequences of going downhill
I can see where you coming from
Jump about guide
Something that I could not have ever imagined
He technically probably kill the guy
No he's older than Alex
Will be.
Also this code starts with
Did they stick $90
It starts with them having an exchange that I think they thought was off
Better Stronger Faster
Listen
Alex Jones
Listen to me
I've already been higher up the mountain and then to the same attacks called control wrote It's all blue
I think I didn't realize his mic was hot mistake
That doesn't answer that question
That's nuts that's wild stuff
Good
Although although I did see a picture of them
Avenue
Almost
I did see a picture of him and his beard is not as terrible as it
No that is unfortunate but I will I will give
Not the awful Victory beard he had
Before
But it is also like
You spend a lot of time
He has the look of someone who takes the long time in a mirror
Getting those getting just the right line
I really wish
I really wish Alex would have answered
Question what mistake
I really want to know what it is interesting to think I don't want to know what mistakes Alex thinks they made
Rhetorical
To listen to it
Using sign language
Don't blame yourself.
Trooper that I know you can be
I'm so I've been selling it
Pretty hard this ATF
Dynamic
A couple things
Already
Do you like
I'm done
Which zone
Very funny hilarious
But this next clip is really where everything comes to a head
And Alex has
A profound breakdown on a
Standing up for yourself I also
You can't believe how corrupt the yard believe how they lie
Pre-rolled
Okay I'll
But you understand
This has been shown to children adults need to know what the hell's going on
You're right but
Nice try
That's one attitude attitude
Call family.
Doing all right
Upset
No I'm not really familiar with vaccines
Gavin is not a famous comedian
There's a pretty good timing in there
You seemed upset that is great that's great that's one way of looking at
Attempts to deal with Alex like just Roid Rage
Freakout nonsense
You can't even imagine
Spitting variance
What about Raven god dammit them over and over and over again
Trying to justify his use of goddamn on the radio
I'm ready to kill people
Wake my brain just had a thought
And that thought is don't say that out loud on the air about straight-up murder
He wants to kill people might want to kill people actually wants to kill people
Yeah that's
That to me like what I heard that first of all I was like
My mouth was open
My jaw hit the floor
When you launched off on that for
Straight about how low
Like the problem isn't
You
The problem is that you keep
Steven Souza problem
Arise drag queens crossdressers
And make them all out to be pedophiles with my propaganda nonsense
The radio station
And then he gets into one
Do like I do like the way
Put that story of the radius
To be out there people need
Well we're getting a lot of complaints
Yeah you're right but please
Exam just like
Mollify hey you're right
Go away
See that email chain
I'd like to point out that
The other thing that made me lose my shoe
Well I was looking
To this
Like you so much
His trick of always talk about always
Is hilarious
But
The immediately
And you got it wrong
Steven
Get your hands off me
What's the Mandela effect
Fat
Apes
And man
Will live comfortably in harmony
Despite the fact that man
Obviously
Set off a nuclear weapons
Destroy the entire planet
Who is
Really the victim
Alex might not have seen all five of them
Beneath the Planet of the Apes disease
Profound
Play f*****-up movie
I love it
Is profoundly f*****
So that was that was sort of
The meat of Alex
Freak out
Which is the mic down
Cuz this
Tumi
In one minute's time it walks
The Game of Life
Really f***** up
Really hilarious
Almost blasphemy
My grandmother
I'm doing a lot of praying past month
Apologize
But I really do
Sweet
Hundred percent 100% folks I'm ready I'm trying to figure out
Can I resell cried against of my very spirit is just on fire
I want to spread the fire Liberty of your mind
Robert Mize
You'll be on fire as well in stock.
Financial support and support
That's too bad
Craze at is whiplash
Riverside
Kind of like that
Start with it's time to pray
Probably real excited about the idea of a prank together
Do they got their juices going
I'm going to tell some s***
The real dog
Could not
Love that
Like I own the real price nobody else knows anything
You like a real
Exactly his
The magic
I need money
Did you ask
For your money you know it's really f***** up to isn't like that sort of mentality exist on
Should I wear
Demonize Noster
I will
Never
Ever understand people who
Claim ownership
And yet
Clearly
Know nothing about
What he was about
Right right
He was a Middle East
But I
Complained all the time
Is this sort of rhetoric
Is
He's not
Complaints about V
Because
So
They promised they were going to pray
I didn't want to hear
He forget about it
Start
And when they come back from break
Women
That sort of like
He's a famous
Famous comedian level
I'm so instead of actually getting to praying Alex wants to do something else
Elmo kick your ass if you don't get back on air
We come back
So that's break your going out to breakfast
This is
Rapidly
This is like a walk
Through Alex
Is bringing us all the doors keep opening up and you see that nightmare
Hellscape
Edwin cyrusone
Prayer you open the door
This room that's decorated really serenely you know like it has a real ethereal spiritual quality
But people are just screaming at you it's not like prayer it's really angry prayer
Happy
No one's fighting
They're still just
This fight is going to be that never happened never happened
You keep going then there's the crying
Because I thought are straight-up
Faking crying
Everyone's trying to
Experience and emotion in the
Really overdoing it
This is very annoying room and Alex
Proceed through that
Murder
Murder room
You going to the next room and it's just
Murdertown
Don't go into the fourth room pretending was technically not insult
It's just him laying over a dead body
You make me kill this
I'm not responsible
This Is Us
What's playing out on this road
Nuts
Gavin not playing ball with Alex's wanting to be his dad like
It is a thing where it's like
Through this I can help you with nowhere to go I know what to do just listen to me
I'm done
But now I got to go
That's me
It does
It does seem like a come
Sleep
What I mean yeah you're right it's 100% of reaction to that
Particular type of Stonewall
From somebody who Alex
Respect
Like a truly
Just feel like
See that
Inability to directly
Attack gas
Is why we're going through all of these different
Cuz if it was somebody who was
Some other
That you know
He would just start going after the
Well
I don't know he did do that sort of
Gavin has a friend
Exactly who keeps trying to find a different avenue to put on
Awful energy
Is Gavin is wanted to
If you like
Close to mainstream
Lucky's on Main Street
People who Alex still has access to
Maybe be an ally
Milos
Pathetic
Alex is going to go out of his way to
Train Court Milos
Juice
Show are like
Rapoport
Anthony cumia
Exactly
You know like these these people
The 4th hour
Is hosted by Hagmann and Hagmann
From The Hagmann Report
So
Doug Hagmann and
Remember his first name
Fun little trivia about Doug Hagmann and Hagmann
They have this show
Frequency that show
Coach Dave daubenmeyer
Six Degrees of Separation
Been on
Coach Dave show
It's all very very
Closely
Almost like there's a shadow
Anthony Taylor shows a shadowy cabal
More of like a
Multi-level marketing
Clip lamp
We already heard Alex say
That he believes
Gavin McInnes
To be the White mart
Luther King
And we get to this next clip and this is
When Alex is sort of let the demons reseed themselves in their head
A normal conversation
And
Really f****** s***
About the Civil Rights
No I think it goes back to the Freedom Riders
The real quick what he's talking about is like
These people are trying to latch onto that idea
They're doing
Freedom Riders
The Freedom Writers
Of course
They want to be like because there
Cool
It was cool of them to go to the segregated South with blacks and whites and get the key
That was incredibly cool sorry
So
This is a mess
It is complete lunacy
Quito composite
Literally about the freedom
Because
Story of the Freedom Writers
Strongly undercuts the entire idea of states rights
The reason that the Freedom Riders had to
To do what they did was because the southern states were engaging. Enforcement of Supreme Court
Publix
Like bosses were unconscious
In response people challenges
Aggregation
They brought attention to the reality that the larger public didn't want us to
And because of their Acts
The argument that the Civil Rights Movement was make it with immeasurable strength
They showed specifically and clearly
How violence is being used to uphold the system of segregation
Of the passage of the Civil Rights
Few years later
Alex and literally everyone whose inspired is passively
Hate the Civil Rights
And the thing is
Civil Rights Act
Because the argument
Ignore rules about human
Is Alex and Gavin McGinnis were around in 1961
Alex would've been on the radio yelling about how the Freedom Riders were agitators
Who does hate white men
And how the Congress of racial equality was funded by Soros
Gavin McInnes will be leaving group The Proud boys to intimidate the Riders
And accepting the status quo
Which incidentally is exactly what the Klu Klux Klan did.
That's what they would have been doing in that sir
There's no doubt about it
Now if you want to say that some of these people who are
No
Protesting
54 equal rights
Maybe some of them were doing it to put it on it
Instagram
Sure
Who gives a
Undercut the point of the earth approach
Or anything like that
You want to say that some people are posers
You guys know who cares
That argument doesn't hold water it doesn't mean
What does mean something is what's behind
The facts
And the principles that Alex Jones again and again
The world's very clearly mirror
People who were
Against the Freedom Riders in 90
61 series no way away from
And the fact that Alex's
Intellectual predecessor
The people he cites
Operation for the path you took in life
In the sixties
It is I hear s*** like this
This isn't this is like
The
The positive history of
Without having to
Live a life
In accordance with the
It's a bummer
In every possible way
It is
To the Freedom Riders like
Really
That's your adjectives for the Freedom Writers
You know what I think of when I think of the Freedom Riders very cool cool legal
Ivan capucci the dog
Spuds MacKenzie
What the
Are you at 7
You can't be the Freedom Writers
Because racism
Over so we live in a post-racial Bubba
Like even the water
People during the Civil Rights era
Words to even the ones who were like
Hey we don't need to
Kill black people
There there was like
Why are you against this racism so
Segregation
Now we don't have to
To deal with it
Racism is over
We will you guys want to be the Civil Rights North vs South
Slavery's over guys
You can't be as cool as the f******
Civil War let's go
Who wants to make the argument
The progress is
The meaning for progress
But we're like a generation
Or maybe
Funeral expense
Riders time
After record
No matter what kind of a s******* you are
If you want to live in reality
You do have to recognize
Right
In terms of owning Capital owning property
Those are two things
Reply to
Minorities
In that time
Especially
You have to recognize that that still exist
The effects of that lingering to the
And if you reject that
But you're not living in reality
I mean it
Hey let's let's say that we're moving past the Freedom Writers or whatever so that the whole thing is done
When did
Official
Federal policy of Redline
Long long after that
But it's not eat we're not even talkin about
Stuff that has been going on
Still going on in order to find
Great so
The races were like fine
You off the bus
You're not allowed to live here
You're not allowed to own this
That or that
Turn our president was actively involved
But he was a real
Yep
Alright so good
No no no come on come on totally cool
He just doesn't want him to exist
But it's good that we live in a post
We're all over
You can't be a freedom rider anymore
What are you fighting
There's just nothing to fight again
Present-day episode
Interesting couple days
I think
In terms of a Gavin McInnes
If you're in that is about as painless as
Yeah
Cut out a lot of him just saying stupid stuff because I think the broader picture
Of Alex really trying to have him up at
No yeah
Alex freaking out about it
Is much more important I think that's the real story
Is it Alex's still transfer
Recruit allies
Struggle
And Gavin is
Is pretty much
Doesn't really want
Get in the water and Alex
I mean it's like if they can
You know if they can beat this guy that I
Admire or respect
What is an elder
They can beat me
So I have to make sure he's not beating
Otherwise
I'm going to have to
To myself
What everybody else already knows
Which is that I am beat
The writing is on the wall
A massive
I should say that
A reminder
Eviction
You know the work is
Finding
Something interesting to talk about 41
Going into the past for Monday
The present stuff is what I dread the most
Because I know it's
The hours of
You listen to
22 hours
And then he'll lie about the boy scout
If that's not how I want to live my life
The present episode suck
In the hit show
They're stupid
I look forward to it
Block Rockin Beats
Is rhetoric
But we have a website
Ostroukhova kicked off on the Facebook
Reviews are important and also it's like
They don't count listen
This much
As they do download
I don't know I don't put it like that
I don't know
Stuff I don't know how I
I don't ever
Expect
What are the number one Alex Jones podcast
No.
Whether or not
So the goddamn
That's what you
Tracking
We working on
Making sure they never have tracking for that
What else we got
Well I mean
Gavin
Almost certainly been
At least
The inspiration
Maybe
Command
You can't prove
Anyting
Oh wait I thought you were going to accuse him of
He probably hasn't killed in Hollywood
But
One guy text
He probably has
That is
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color