Alexandra Thurston color
This is podcast where we sit around
And bring some red wine
Have a little conversation
I know a lot about Alex Jones Show everyday
Okay
I do not
I don't think I know anything about Alex
You know he's a man
He is a man a man he's a really it's really important to him that he's a Madman emphasis on
Man it's really important to him.
He lives in occupied Texas know that that's all you really need to know about
We're going to be
Going over
The Day in the Life about
March 23rd
On the Alex Jones program
Where a lot of relief
F***** up stuff happens
Lost a friend
We're going to be breaking down that I think might have Fallout comp
That's our next
Is a child children's book
Call
Alex
Loses afraid
Because of the global
There's no doubt the global is interwoven in this lack of a friendship
Episode
Before we get to the eclipse
We're going to plant discus
I wanted to just take a second
To reflect
Winsome Alex Jones related news
They were not going to
You be going over excellent first day of class
It's not even work got cut
Because it's just news that if we didn't talk about
Everyone would be like
This is not a legit Alex Jones podcast
Yeah it would be terrible if people thought.
Sphere would be
So on Friday
Of last week
24th
A in-depth
Do James alefantis
Owner of Comet Ping Pong Pizza
About his involvement
MP3
Apology
Vittone of like
We were just reporting stuff
Really focused on getting
Getting good reporting
For saying this it was viral we're just commenting on why you guys being such a pictures about it that's kind of his
The language of his apology I texted you about this before the show
I'm certain he's getting
Absolutely
Bring up James elefante
The way he keeps saying like
We we we heard these things
Victor report here anymore
At the very least got a
Strongly-worded letter 100%
Unpack is that a couple months ago he put out a video on YouTube
Call the final word on Sandy Hook
He's already got the final Shout
Which
Realize the people were attacking him
For being a Sandy Hook truther and all this stuff you wanted
To put out a video that once and for all
Spoke his piece
About Sandy Hook
Was it just him shiting on the competent
Just a
Piece of paper with grief written on it as a shift on the desk
To work quilt done
And all of the pieces of it
That's what the video should have been
That's the image in my head from now on in reality
A bunch of circle
Bulshit pieces of evidence
I met him at the end being like
This investigation is going to be ongoing
No
Call
I'm starting to recognize their pieces of things
His Stead
That he's starting to walk back really hard
Is one of them
Sandy Hook
You did a bad job of it in that video
Foodies trying to do is like
And that means
Trouble
That
When you have any clips of him ever apologize
Not really
I may have gotten something wrong before he's also always said
But really I got it right
Yeah yeah
I was more right than wrong
Yeah
But I will say that ninety-nine percent of the time we report on his right
And frankly that probably
That's like
I'm still plugged into the Zeitgeist but even when I try to lie I
Anyway let's get
The 23rd
This is going to be a rollercoaster ride
Sort of all over the place beginning
Then this interview that I mentioned
And then
Esoteric malaise
Eric Malave
He's also getting real heavy with me
To be Malaysia
Weird and unusual type of a syllabus
Let's get to this first
Clip of it involved
Some of these
They're going on I'm not talking onions my friend
Leeks
That they're targeting
President-trump
Russian software that they've stolen our using
If not
Weather
Allies of the return the Republic
Is that release date
Baggins
Who is relief
State your case
Probably illegally
Right
No
It's it's
Directions
Friends
Who support the return of the
You have these weird hacker collectives and stuff like that
Guccifer 2.0
I don't know if it's true but
Personality Russian hacker
Use as an intermediary to get
The information
And have plausible deniability
Now
If Alex Jones is saying that these people
Friends of the return of our Republic
He's basically just saying that like
Putin Putin helping us to restore our Republic Friends of the return of the tree
Treason treason
The definition of word
We keep coming back to this thing
You're so hung up on the idea that words of me
Isaac
Bring this up and I'll review session
Believing
Toy review
You do all the work thanks
Yours is also damn you have a problem
Well I didn't want to air our dirty laundry
Anyway
Alex Jones
Is
In this episode
And throughout this last week has been pretty
Certain is the right word I think
Vicky's being oppressed
He's got a real victim complex going on
He's being oppressed
Explores little bit of his thoughts
And their phones
Again it's a few months ago
Nancy Pelosi
Is the outgoing head of the justice department
Other plans
That will be Odyssey seeing soon
But
Also
To the outgoing
Sister Wives
0 power
Time to really go after Alex
Your plan was to get you as far away from powers
Former Attorney General
There's two things no one expects
Spanish Inquisition
Everybody knows this is YG
Jesus secret mole I believe the
Premise as
As established
Loretta Lynch
Wouldn't have stopped being attorney general Hillary won
Yeah well that's obvious when they were making
Movies playing
Before Alex Jones was really that
He was important
Play
I wish I wish there was less true than that
Area code
Understand
Officially already have Obama and Hillary Clinton
Is it
Down the street
Yeah it's just Roblox McDonald's
You know where it exists
Inside his little fancy brain world
That's where it that's the address Alex Jones
Tell me the bunkers
This bunker bunker
Excuse me sir I don't know when you turn to do a something
Call of Duty
You want us to know
We're coming after you
Good lawyers get ready
And they're already
Just Sharon
Letters to Google and letters of a company saying
You kickoff
That talked last month
Oh we're not allowed
Because
You don't get a hearing you don't get a hearing
Because it's not a it's not a legal thing
Violated
Necessarily
Especially what Libertarians what should believe in
We've been over this a hundred times is all Admiral
I was ticked off because of the FEC narrative is is complete nonsense
Like what he just said
What is the best
Evidence for
Him being
Two papers by a lawyer
Like
He is telling the truth
Somebody is issuing him paper
Yes
They're just the front
The first wave you know that's there
Pelosi is operating secretly behind him
It's just
The joint
All he wants is the pizza joint
Spell just say it is
Just James alefantis
Then, ping pong
It seems the most likely
Scenario
If that is the case
Like he deserves to be sued
That's a good
What would the
It wouldn't be you can't
Yeah
Hard
What
It's defamatory statements that were made
Speculation
Sweet but it wasn't
It was them Justin
Pizza Joint was a front
Hillary Clinton
Grape children's dosing at all
More revenue streams in this day and age
The joint
Picked man you must be a great
Only raped
If you if you go back and look at some of the stuff
Some of the statements that were made
Goodbye
Employees of Comet Ping Pong and James alefantis
Back when this was first
Starting up
There's a bunch of threats that they got to their business
Threaten threaten
Situation where
Became
Barstool to ever come to
Of course
Yeah I agree
Now we're actually just
Is disgusting a full-out illegal
It isn't becoming episode of Handel on the law
Boston Legal
But but wouldn't it be the originator of the claim like
Never never originated in idea
Other than the ones that
Just making up
Cuz I don't know I'm not I'm not sure how that would work
But I know
Deism
Ratably guilty of
Perpetuating the biggest
He had like there's this guy named
Petopia
It is a complete monster
Star Wars
Evening videotaping
Himself going to Comet Ping Pong
And comment on Festa Pizza
The two pizza places on the same block
They're all in the mix
You videotape himself going into besta pizza and nothing happened
Nothing happened there was nothing weird
And then as soon as he left so f****** weird in there
Oh my God
Show like The Messengers
He tries to order some food everyone's treatment real nice
He goes in
Kia is trying to livestream it
And one of the waiters realizes what's going on
This guy
Is videotaping himself
Eating
It's not a coincidence
Especially wow all the pizzagate stuff
What's going on explain
My employees have
Do you understand that you're helping perpetuate something
People
Just people who are trying to live their lives in
Lives
Start bringing guns
Places
Jefferson bogosian
This guy claims to him
The people have been threatened and it's no joke
It's not a laughing matter
Come on what's going on
There's an off-duty cop there
Everything was
F****** weird in there they find me out
To be a cop
Himself right
Yeah that's your move you go in there and you're like a
I'm Serpico
He left
And then he was like
Everything was demonic in there
There's a back room there keeps running in and out of it what's going on here
Didn't show any of that new video making s*** up
I watched
Tire like
2 hour long live stream
Somebody posted
There's nothing
And then like the next
Today
She's on info
Being interviewed about what he experienced
He's lying
There's a bunch of stuff
Happen
No one's going to go watch the whole video
It's two hours long
You're the only person who
Probably
Alex
Someone should go check it out
Investigated
A very short time
Drove from out of state
To go invest
Navigate to Spitz
The place
Shoot shoot
Got it at anybody but
The ground
So Yosemite Sam came from Oklahoma to
Holy responsible for all this
Hit you should be sued
Dave Seaman
Should be sued
Bunch of other these ding-dong assholes
They really should be sued they've caused a lot of damage
Well I mean
Threat
I believe in free speech wholeheartedly believe in libel
And I don't believe
I don't believe that you can get away with us
Neither does the lotto that's why they that's why those
I believe that
Get out for you is the reason that I was probably going to go
I also believe that the reason
He's being investigated
As he puts it
And that last clip is not because we will think he's a Russian
It's because there are Russian
Russian
Satar
Specifically promoting
His contact
Okay
And the question that the FBI is apparently asked
According to the article
But I've read
Is
Is there coordination
Is there
Collaborative thing going on
Where these Russian Bots promote in Fort Worth,
Really
Is there any influence
From Russian sources
Into Alex's reporting
You would say
Normally there's no way there's
Collusion
Collaboration
Because
Who would you wouldn't
Even need to talk
To Alex if you gave if you gave me
More attention
Just be like her and never asked
Did go on RT
Aiden
Gray isn't nothing there
Joe
CNN
I would say it's
Probably more Alex
To having
Both naked selfie
Pinterest
And just
His father's love
That's the dentist
Jesus Father's Love
He's got great teeth but he doesn't have his dad
I don't think Alex himself is being investigated for anything
He's done I believe that he is a piece of the event
Navigation because his propaganda is being pushed by Russian
And I believe
From everything I've read that that is what the articles are about about
Alex is turned
I am being
Call the Russian agent
Bright
For him to push because banners
That's
The argument from
Even people on the left
Like that
Not
The story
He's not
I don't think you should be shut down I just think we should walk him until he quit
If he does do those things
These are the reasons that I think
People are attacking
Cuz other ideas
Hopes and dreams our society
Emergency martial law and a civil war
Play calling for the cities to begin to me for the present
Call military
In Warfare against the Republic
And foreign policy
Global Publications
Calling for military coup against Trump
Insurrection
Military
Mutiny and Rebellion
Citizens of this country
Wait
But didn't
Say earlier that that was okay
Then he'd have long as they were as long as they were
Look for
Yeah then doesn't mean
Condemn the very thing that you
He said was
Perfectly fine months about how
Rogue forces within the CIA have
Perform to counter-coup
Against liberal
We already had the counter counter
We're in the middle of the counter countertop
We're in the middle of the counter counter
Cannot keep track of all these we might find it supposed to
Can you code
Flower pot
All I can do
Task math text
Every time there's a
Because Alex keeps talking about globalist
Publications
I'm subscribed
The foreign policy
And I've started reading it
I started reading all the time
Okay
Narrative
Is not in there
Is a very
But this article was
We don't want to take a stand
On whether or not
He is
Enough
But what I can't do
Is with you
His dissertation
Oh-so the one word
Probably
Espoused
No it's not
It's about
Terrorism
Counterterrorism
GameStop
Who is
Doctoral advisor
Reviewing people's dissertation
We're just going on and on
Talking taking the piss out of him
For lunch
Scholarly
It was
The only sites like four sources
Read many books
He is one of Trump's
Counterterrorism adviser
Pretty high up there
And you have no experience
And almost no published work outside of the dissertation
About counter-terror
Bad wrecks
What kind of stuff that's in foreign policy
Very interesting
Want like
Look
Could be
Wouldn't you wouldn't you want like a
I think for an advisor position you wanted
Especially for like
Counter-terror
When you're pretty hot topic
Weirdo weirdo
You're nothing is there it is you're not saying I do it
Send my address
This next clip
Described as a
Is her next step
Achieve
You guys want to get excited about what our next episodes going to be about it's a lot of this
Good news
And Justice look mean
Is a huge narrative
Fun for the
The entirety of the last week
Really
Hi
Improve it
And I'm going to next episode
I found out where it came
Oh s***
Big
Music stuff
Next episode
We're half hour in we're figuring our legs back again
Read about it you know what it is I'm
I'm getting
Insecure that people are going to turn this off because next episodes going to be
You so great
Like the stuff he's talking about
Track from A to B
There's just so much like all over the place
Yeah he doesn't
He doesn't have the kind of Border or maybe
Maybe he's just not
Capable of doing the longer narrative right
So many different
Angles right
Narrative probably around an hour and a half into this
1 hours
Have you ever watched batteries
I watched a lot of him
How
Are you still alive
Look
I used to do that now I see it there for locks on the door
Haven't gone outside
That's true
France versus Bam Bam
Anyway
The Obama Deception okay
I've watched
She brought back Matt Damon black
Idris Elba
That's my racist
James Bond
Documentary
Endgame
Now
That
I wish it was
This next clip
Like
Is undertale
Don't enjoy
Because
Martial law
The baby classified
Two years after it was created
Spring cleanup
Strangely enough
He was created
Classified
2 years
After they created the program created the program
And then three years
After his
Yes
What using math what Alex Jones is say
Is that
The entire program was his fault in the first place Alex Jones
He just gave them an idea
He did the whole endgame like
This is what
Buried within that cooks
Please
Impossibility
Then he
Time machine
Alright
No impossibilities in our world
So unlikely
Unlikely to be created the documentary year before that program
I'll give you that
Also unlikely
The government creates
NM
Games for Global enslavement program
Years later
Did bro we started
Articles about Gorka
They're going to start
Just talking directly to you and foreign policy articles Dan I'm telling you you're going to love
Real talk
I think that's what Alex
Who's going
I hope it doesn't happen too because otherwise I got to move to
Yeah
The government would be like
Going to shut everything
Alright
Head Start we got everything pretty much in place
Just f****** declassify.
Alright
So here's what
Declare martial
And then we're going
To take over all the
Cuz that's not where the pay
Turner liberal
We got to kill.
Exactly
12in entire essay
11b
I meant years later though
You know what
I don't think
On this one
How about we
Tell everyone
Ever that this
We want to be honest
Like we all know the intelligent
Community owl
Is that narrative just spun right there is more entertaining than
Global deception
Enslavement whatever
Alex's stoop
How long is the documentary
Logan long
How do you say
66 Titanic
That's what I think
Very people donate
To the show
What we should do is to
Subscribe now
2R man pills
No no no pills but if people were to subscribe
We would do a wasted commentary
Alex
A full-on mst3k Ohio
That because I think that might be fun
Here's an idea
Anyway
It's time for a noose
I don't know if you're ready for it
I don't like how deep is a certain level of game tell you something
I've seen stuff hardly anybody else's scene
I've seen stuff
Literally anybody ever seen
Having the responsibility
Of being
The only
Tyler in the world
I'd like to fully say that I believe that he seen stuff that almost Nobody seen
But that's because I think it's been in
You seem very specific
Like forgeries
Isaac fraud
Specifically targeted him
Because they know he
We just believe
And not
Just that
He has seen
Future
I'm going to tell right now
He has he has worked it out engineer
Same thing man
The government
With both
Create this program
What an a****** I mean
Fair enough
I'm not just here on are talking about this stuff
Where are you where the computer itself
You just Target the person
Microscopic capacitors
What
Transfer over cable
Andover wine
Is your scooping it all up
He does not know what
Any of this.
He's number 15 gear stuff that they would start doing 9 years later
Can't do no fifteen years the stuff that they're not doing
Do you think that someone's microwave is listening to them
Cuz there's chips inside them with little micro microphone why would you do that
Microphone
Everyone also hey bro
That would be cost prohibitive
VIP
Mighty micros
Five Guys
With Mike and power washers of microphones on everything
Whenever they want to the government could remotely turn them on and start listening
But they can remotely turn on your phone
Start listening to you through that right but this was
6 years ago before cell phones
My argument is falling apart
That makes
No sense
How would you build a
Microscopic microphone also that has a transmitter that
I can send things to you also
Climatic
The idea that like in your microwave
Let's let's start
The microphone in your mic
When you turn on your microwave
Do that
It makes a lot of noise
But then
Classic classic knowledge fight
You're only going to get to hear what I say
Microphone
In your TV
Okay
In your toaster
In your blood
Okay old-timey type blender with those the crank
I think back to The Farmhouse that you wished
Call Lupe
No electronics
It might be that might be the only way for us to survive
Be safe hey
You wouldn't even know that the empty because you couldn't see his
Documentary.
Yeah
It's a double-edged sword
You killed either way you know you and I are millennials
You know that right
I've heard me a millennial
Turns out the global stuff
You know what
People in other generation
Don't like us
No it's
It's strange
Cuz one of them
Do any other generation
History that other
Never heard the same thing people said about us
Apply to any other generation
I will say this I don't think that other generation
This specific charge
Junior High
Nnnn denote
Robots in town and then
Chinese
America is going to have
Felicia bio-weapon
After the kill 94
Kill
I have all the different groups variations breast up
Who does that mutation play made there at the end he's kind of supporting
Theory of evolution
But
He's making an argument
That no one has made
Which is like
White people are Ice Age mutants
We all know this and he's like
Talkin about
There is a group called the five percent Nation Nations
Nation of gods and Earth
Which is a shoot-off
Africa Afrocentric
They were Branch out of Malcolm X's church cuz I didn't think he was
Clarence 13x
I like him a lot also known as putting cuz his words were so smooth
Okay
Future
Assurance of the nation
I've got the nerve
Yeah you can hear it in a lot of their rap
We talked about like
Who's the guy that don't have a clue
There's this references to the
Fat religious group
Throughout all of their their history
The nation is based on the idea that
Percent of population
Knows the truth
Wake up the population
That is 85% the population
Is deaf dumb and blind and doesn't know the truth
Then there's ten per-cent of the population
The truth
Julie seeks the train
P85d
We're outnumbered
Are we are we are no know where bad is it is kind of
Where are the 85
Depends
We could
Depending on what we're doing is the original conception of the Cypress
Set Nation
Adair
Believe
The truth is 85% is deaf.
Is that the black man is God
Memes
Arm leg leg arm head
The composition of
The black mat
The Quiet Man
Arm leg leg arm head
Via Allah
That's what that means
It's a it's a representation
For your body
But why would they use that word
What do you meme
Well isn't that a
Repurposing of like Islamic beliefs
William Burroughs really
Yeah they aren't they are
No
I've done a lot of research into
Esoteric
As time has gone on they've gotten
Liberalism to it
And it's not so right
And one of their beliefs are they held
Was that people were created in a lab by an evil scientist named yakub
Well not being plausible
Does kind of explain why any
Time you read a history
Book
You get
To the statement
And then the white man came you're like
Well that's this is bad foreshadow kind of is the black nationalist
Bent that I was about like white people being nice
From
Meet us in a lab
Wayback
Examples
Of the type of
So I'm just saying
But it's not ignoring argument that he's arguing again
It's just a very unpleasant on
If a magnet
Yeah so anyway
Love you
Done
I'm in feel 90%
Then we release the Bayou
Why would
Would you do that after the 94
Maybe the bioweapons wouldn't be effective
I don't know
I don't believe him
I just want any kind of any kind
Any kind of handle
Because that makes
Not just
No sense
Opposite
Which all the Chinese greet all of them
Okay
Which jobs are onboard
Cuz we're going to need it
In the eventual court case
History of humanity
Alex
I wants to do a deep dive into analysis about the attack London
That happened
Eminem's last week
He has nothing
His hatred of Islam
Run over a bunch of people instead
Watching footage this morning online of just thousands of Muslim men
Celebrate
Like a horde of zombies
I love you
I'm guessing there what he saw was a bunch of like
B roll
Rumba
Can we find any
I can't
No
Open
Like
Yes like a like a primate thing going on there like
Except for that movie
I want
I think it's interesting that Alex is so bent out of shape
Compared
How to how
Which was
But
That we move on
Bills solution
Something bad happen
You know what
Where is Alex's super into let's call them hotties and I really
Demonize Islam
Muslims were kind of making it seem like it
It's a big all of them are happy
If you see a thousand people
People doing something
Representative
2 billion
Everything
Alex has still not apologize or recognize
That that's
He reported it that it wasn't Muslim I am
Will not
Okay so f*** him
This gets back to our general Flynn
Situation where
That now there's blood General
Wednesday
River General
People in what they
Okay
No it does the blood in the water
Right
So once we
Once we got one
Person down now we're going after more and more and more right
What's
We get one Alex Jones apology
It's all coming down
I'm hoping
That would be
Amazing free episode
I don't think we do world for everything you should apologize
For we would be long dead
Before we covered it
For 23 years
Bf1
April
4th episode
Just a long series
I would love that. Great present if Alex Jones just apologized for an entire show
Attack
Well I can only be
Describe is like a super scientific
Approach
Beano's
Tistic
Figuring out what
What's going on I don't
Zero's official
On Facebook as opposed to that emojis
Emoji
Every frowny face
Smiley faces on for hours
And for every
Thumbs down
Not one
Thumbs down thumbs up baby
Thumbs up
For every frowny face
10 smiley face
So you know how when you're broadcasting live on Facebook it shows the like responses cascading across the screen
Here's a screenshot of a lot of like happy faces
Covering the London attack
Now
One of the things that doesn't take into account is the things like Fortune
Can we play that one more time I want to hear that you wait for the episode
Those times
If Morgan Freeman
Did that ever
He does not recognize that there are internet Brigade
Patrol thing
Yes and I would not be super surprised I've no ever
I wouldn't be surprised if there were a bunch of people
Who put on a message board
Let's all go Brigade this al-jazeera report and make it look like everyone
Motion passes
But anyway
I don't I don't know like I can't prove if that's true I'm not going to pour over Message Board history is to
Define
Charge of the internet
Who
Brigading the internet
That's right out for you basically what you have there is
Plausible
Explanation for why that might be the case outside of
Alex's argument which is almost
Super thrilled
Yeah I don't think that's true
And I don't think you can prove it those smiley faces were coming from Muslim people you dumb f***
Is there any could you imagine
Anyway
Prove that
Black Annie
Possible
Not within Alex Jones is sort of investigative journalism techniques metaphorically.
Putting together a full
History of each other
Style
To figure that s*** out of definitely
Because I know he goes
The temple five times a day to pray
Time to get to this interview
Where everything takes a turn
Is an interview
With one
Really believe in Sandy Hook
He's a bad person
He's the guy who's responsible for the counter-coup narrative
Butt out
Has been pitching for about the last
A lot of red flags on
Lot of more than more than
Yeah but I want to say
No
Today
Alright
His interview
He's trying to make two points
Power login
Basically
Gotcha
Owls Head was at
When the interview was about to start
I'm going to play his introduction
Steve pieczenik
And then
He'd like to talk about
I will see how that go
Cam
On the confirmation hearings going on
When I got to say this judge the tub
Nominative I buy promises destroying them
Now we got Nunez admitting intelligence reading
I am so much more in the latest Islamic attack
Which they're saying it's an Islamic attack
So we'll see where all that's going
Again calling for martial law National Emergency
I remember
Going around again trying to organize a coup against Trump
Here's the deal
Mister anti-bully State girl
And I just
Just some people call you Maurice
Doing something wrong
Run around
Alex Jones
Nope
So this point he's
Tried to do the introduction
He's lit not going well he's listed a couple he wants to Michael Moore's a flog
Gorsuch is cool
Running around Keith Wallen for the murder Trump
He's doing an introduction
Steve pieczenik
Is on Skype just staring
I am
Doctor if you're a regular Alex Jones
One word every 45 minutes do you have to serve
If you're mad at him or expectations
End up a little bit ago on his show a lot
Therapeutics like
Counterexample because one of them
Which is why this interview is fascinate
Usually someone who Alex
Gives a lot of difference
Kissing
As opposed to
Eddie Bravo
Who who just gets
Just get some
And now we have the federal license tuition Centre looking at
Trying to go out for Drudge Report
And yes this was
Regime-change
And they're just moving forward
Washington Post
Vine
Also harvard-educated
At the end there is what Alex thinks
With the intelligence
Anywhere near
But that's the way he can twist it in his head to make Trump look at
And feel smart
Right where he's like was just trolling the whole time
I like I like the I like his narrative
It is a regime change
It's happening all over the world
And they're acting like it
Like they don't care
So what is it is it really hurt nobody cares
You're still just acting like everything's
Like
Whatever mubarek was kicked out and they were just like
Okay
You know what we'll do we'll kick out this military dictator
Who cares will put in the new military dictator
That's not a receipt
No
Not really
No idea of a regime change
Against the globalist
In reality what it is is a
Very dangerous
Strain of nationalism
That is popping up in a lot of countries
And is largely being
Speeded and helps grow by for effort
The taken on by the Russian
What's going on
A fight against the globalist
I wouldn't say that it's entirely
That like there's that there's a whole lot of factors that could have gone in
To the riser for threatening assist
Goodbye
Yes. You do see the fingerprints
Russian Marine Le Pen
Meeting with Putin openly the other day
What does positive
Like
Far-right
Just goes to meet with punt with Putin
As a fight against as I've made clear
Globalization is a real thing
Globalist
Right so he's fighting against
Or hit his idea is
Against a non-existent force
What he's actually doing
Is holding water
Giving cover essentially to this rise of dangerous man
And if you get this way we're going to live in nightmares
Yeah but
For what we live in now
Comparable
That's a good point
We did get one on the board even if that nightmare scape does come to pass
I could be down the road
The good news is
The globalist
Will not be in charge
Because they're not now
It's super Sculpey
We're probably looking at our six or seven
Oh yeah
Navigate
We're playing
All it is is just like
Hating the idea of liberalism
Conservative liberal to my
That's all that's all it is
Why does he hate
Is there a
2A route
Why
Well one of the things is that he thinks that liberals want to take your gun
Let's definitely get used
Like this is all about personal Liberty
Real liberals want to enforce it
Other than it being terrible
If agenda21 if we're talkin about the actual un
Suggestions
I don't think that a lot of those too
Suggestions are bad
Version that's in Alex's head
We need the Jedi
No I really like it
Who cares
I will say I have time just
Cuz I had to cut out some
Some stuff it's too long for us to listen to all of it
Where that Neil Gorsuch is a neocon
It should never be put on the spur
Supreme Court
Yep I like that a lot. That's really good
Is
That information should be allowed to take over
Play that's the second point is
It also has to do with a neocon what-have-you but they are
Go to war with North Korea
Yes I also agree with him on that count
Wow so anyway here's the introductions
There's the introduction of Steve pieczenik Bremer
As you know we were successful
Michael
In the states
Nobody
Corporation
Call Burrell
Scrub and truck canopy
Dianne Feinstein
I know you don't
Million men
Away from Stowe
North Korean
North Korea
Try something
Alex remember
Plan
You know what just happened there
Steve pieczenik
You're an idiot
You're fuking idiot hours
You know
You know I've been
In the business of nuclear
Deterrence
The big part of nuclear deterrence is
Kill millions of people
When Alex was starting this
He introduced these premises
Is awesome he's going to get confirmed
One of God I hope not
What if
Text Bane point
Is the exact opposite
Because Alex has built as this hero
And this great source of interventions
Interrupt him and steer the conversation in a different direction
Right it's a
No
I'm sorry we're not on the same wavelength
Keeps going
Edit ants
So f***** up
I'm not going to carry any water for Steve pieczenik
I think built into some of the reasons that people use
Don't
It's for the right
Conclusion I disagree with but let's not split hairs
Is North Korea going
Going to take that bluff
I don't know careers not interested in
What North Korea will do what's best for North Korea
Our preparation has
How to deal with North Korea with other countries
Bulshit
Be clear throughout this entire interview you can see Steve pieczenik
Continuing to talk
Scarlet Spider
Michael has Mike
The cut-offs bike
A sense of like
What almost a frustration
A look of
Like you can see in his face
That he is not on board with what's going on with trying to make the best of it
I don't think I'm reading too much into this
I think Alex might have like
Offended wow we're really getting into like
Some some solid schisms in between Alex Jones and literally everybody who likes out
For the last
It's like year and a half or so Steve has been
The source of information for Alex
And there's been a Groot
Kind of relationship
It's not the competition is not but I think that I think if there is a part of this where Steve is trying to make
Some point that he wants
To get through.
He realizes that Alex is Off The Rez
Yeah like I think he realizes no Alex you have your own
Point
You don't just believe the things I want you
Yeah translator
Want to talk more about the neocon
Clip
Really illustrates
Just remind everybody created
We can walk away like everybody
The project for a New American Century ship
Terrible
Wipeout 9%
Chinese people
Earlier episode
It's important
Alright
Illustrates
Alex Jones
Is f****** out of his League
In this conversation
He's out of his depth
There's not a good
Because he already knew half of
It's just as soon as Trump let us run Tang
Information that they are
Nana Nana Nana. Crazy
I mean what you know about Pearl
And the women run from them as if
Women want to go to walk up and go I'm a murderer I kill people that don't want to want
Mustache
So he's mute
Yeah
I don't know who
I'm Hellboy and that's good enough right
No mechanic wants to talk policy
No Alex
John Bolton's mustache
Policy
Paul Ryan School of policy walk
Being a f******
Who's Steve gets back in here
No one will appoint who he says everyone
There's a total mute
Office
Directions
Your mama's so fat the Russians wouldn't
I'm kind of fine with that answer though
From hell
Probably the
True answer I don't think the Russians are feeding Alex Jones
He's an ally that they don't even have to
No like other people you got to convince and they went a dramatic
I'm so happy
Lucky idiot
Getting into the circumstances
We are now
Because before Alex had any real world relevance
He could get away with saying anything
Attention which is
On its own
Now he's getting in trouble
His he's been saying illegal ship at the very least
But this is the first time that
You better
We better go out
Yeah yeah
Angry all the
Forever why are you mad at me now
Stanford
Squat you down
Alright
This next clip is they get to get off track a little bit
Get off track
Does Alex keeps against you in the conversation in different direction
He keeps trying to not deal with substance
Just wants to
So here is a
I was watching the video
What's up saying is not what
Gotcha
You meant to say something
Sporeworks
And I wish you had
What's happening from 9:11 onward
He's doing
My problem
I would say he needs
I think that if
I think if we parse that
Security bulshit but I think the reality is that he's actually
Senile
And he has those people around us cared
You know I care this ability
Arguments
Just generally Enid
Play never been more than
Find you can go back and he's what he is
Senile for a 30 goddamn years
20 years ago
Stocks
Easier like he had much more Bible
Even
10 fifteen years ago
The only thing I remember from more than
However many months I've had to pay attention to
Is
That he was
Okay
Great he was pretty great and Home Alone 2
Well here's the thing
I think that
Steve pieczenik
Was being diplomatic as hell
I need
You could see it in his face
I like
Like a smile in like a
Professional
So anyways
I'm done but I
I love that
Steve pieczenik like you said
Killing it on fire right now
Is it unusual
Pieczenik
With RFK
She's overcome
I don't know
Gonorrhea
He's overcome his fear of strangers he's overcome his
Hey what who knows
Alex Jones knows something that Donald Trump has recently gotten over yeah
I would like to know what Alex
Thanks but I also
No
He didn't mean it could be
Syphilis
Trump
Could be
Go insane
Play around
AR
Also double down on your syphilis logic
Whatever dumb s*** you're saying
Because they also have
It makes sense to them
Conspiracy theory I've ever heard absolutely everybody with syphilis everywhere
They have to
Or if you want to be inside
We're recording this on Saturday
On Saturday did you see on Twitter the pictures of the pizza
Pizzagate Rally's
There's a pizzagate rally in Washington DC
It was
Oh man
The pictures are not to be believed
Ones
As I understand
I had did some great reporting on
Remember
Plug right
Steve pieczenik
Transitions to his other prong
Of his thesis
Pineal
Which is
About Neil Gorsuch
Good
Little bit
What time for such cannot be nominated to Supreme Court Justice
Goodbye
Even Steven hearing his voice
As he goes out to break
Movieclips and Moorhead of the next house to join the will be right back ladies and gentleman with it
Have to be back with Steve pieczenik
Feel good right now
Commercial break
Throwing a tantrum
Like you know
I know that Neil cons are bad but I know that
Does he know
He thinks they're trotskyites
Which I guess there is some historical terrible
Notes to come back from break Alex starts by spinning philosophical about a little
Bill self
2-channel
Oh really
Explain why exactly he's against course
Put also I guarantee no one's coming
People ask why I like people ask me all the time
Alex Alex
Do you like having a country
Will get better if we just had you
Everyone was Alex Alex and they lived exactly 24 ha
Because of the ideas
Infinity
Infinite worlds one world
Is everybody everyone everyone
And they all live a ha
Does exist
Well in the Multiverse
Except
And unfortunately this is happening
Mark Zuckerberg
What's a nightmare
Who is that you have said should happen multiple times
Yep
Bethania
Has advocated for
He is now
Indonesia
Pictures of the sky
Let me put it this way
Judge Gorsuch
Prosecutors after the war
Whatever
And literally began to go into the fascist state
Went to go in town and said this was the best
That we should have a policy discussion
The underlying nature
Unlike many of the German
Well that he made the call.
Stream peten elated out really well
F****** Scalia was you goddamn
Piece of s***
Why would you get Scalia you pile of f******
Let's not litigate the Dead
Burnout
Illuminati Lodge
Haven't murdered again
Murder of again
But like who cares
We're not dealing with
Scalia reitnouer
Call Nessa
He's
He's right you never liked it
Yeah he he was working
Help put through the
Patriot Act
There's no other way
Did you can go to wasp
People being tortured on a
Daily base
This is good unless you have zero empathy
Make you necessarily associate like a situation
Right cuz you just believe these other people don't have
But other people who are like
Like you do
Like this
Juuzou
Absolutely I'm a big fan of saying the word Nazi
Yeah you are I'm not going to go quite as far as
Nazi
Going to go knock
Buffalo
Neil Gorsuch
Support
Which is fascinating
And
What's can't handle it
Alex can't do it
At least with Cheney I knew what Cheney was he was a rat
Lawyer
Yeah
Wow
Man I am jerking off to
Libertyville
That's right through these last two there's two more clips of pechenik
Do you like
Is a Madman
Obviously in response
What's to how poorly The Sinner
Sent him into an existential crisis
Botanica's talks for a bit of a stretch
It's kind of like sitting there like
Not working that I've ever heard of guess
Right
Throne
Who is in the first few clips of
Interview Alex
Was constantly trying to reshape the argument even said I'm trying to get you to talk about what I want you to talk about
Any realized
Can't do it
Steve is too forceful
So he's given up
Once again discovered
Alex is a bully
Are p****
Not allowed
Sucks sucks
Yeah but
Sulking right now
Like a real man
He makes one last effort to sort of.
Distract
The narratives that are going
His last 12
Skyfall doors whatever
Nunez
What does it mean that the media
It's a distraction
Yourself
When they're up there saying we're Liars
Turn off the command
I'm sorry Alex what's going on
No he just didn't understand what the f*** Alex told us
You didn't understand
What
How many angels can fit on the head of the mom is the doctor
Is Trump
Nicolas Cage
I can't prove he's not that's a good point so this next clip is the end of the interview and I don't want to spoil
How It Ends
But just listen for it
It's
It made me
It ends with a review of Beauty and the Beat
Yeah
And they're like man I wish she had done more of the original
Episode
I can keep track of
Anybody in Hollywood
The end of this
Is
Enjoy
I just know that when I heard this I got a shiver
I got a shiver in my spine
Literally
Marshall and Eisenhower
Oh man
That is not how you ended in Urdu
That is not how you end marital fight that's what that was I was so abrupt husband
Go to couples counseling
The military-industrial complex
So you just shut down
Went to town now you might think
Fed economist
That abruptly
I just made the same arguments that I could have made
Did the budget for the military is out of control doesn't make more money
Doesn't part where he was talking about how Isis is
Controlled by the CIA
All right but
The biggest Point Wisteria is amazing
Because we're so distracted by all the
The Trump is doing well forget that Trump has now killed
More civilians in Syria in
In the first 2 months
Jeers
Yeah
Insane and we can't
We can't add that to our list of calamities that were trying to deal with Ray
There's so much going on
Yeah
We are murdering people and nobody can
F****** nuts
Control
You grab hold of one thing to focus on
You lose track of 20
You might think
Just because a Time
It is not because
I think she might want to say that it was because the time
The next half hour
Before I think David Knight takes over for the 4th hour
Prove
Pikachu
Much longer because he's gotten nothing.
But it is
It starts
I'm misinterpreting something from the Buy
He got it from the White House
Trump wasn't the target
It was his building and his phone numbers
And staff
Wasn't that again folks
Temperature Detroit gets a distraction
They're going to call for martial law comes true
We have to point it out cuz they're saying where the fake nose
Nope
If we point out front was being surveilled
And then it
Do it because
They didn't leave the younger son says I want my inheritance
Everything's right here at our ranch or Farm
Comes back Miller Brothers like I've been a good Steward what the hell you're having a party
Migos
This is your brother
You're strong respect you do that
Family
Yeah that's what I said was about
Sure he's ever
Read the Bible
Nobies write the headline
He doesn't know how to read
The Texas Public Schools failed him he has no reading comprehension skills
The prodigal son was about as I understand it
The dads like
Dude you're fine look at this idiot
Okay so there's a couple problems with his interpretation
The Prodigal Son
The first is vidan
Is the book
Burden in the parable
In the Bible
Realizes the error of his ways
And is welcome to back by the father
Anna brother is
Inspired
Is now alive
That is a celebration
Now the problem for Alex
In order for give
Sorta
Analogy to make sense
All of us at some point would have had
Doobie info Warriors who strayed
Are we got
Sort of trick
By the mainstream media
Evan now he wants a
The comeback
Is that what you saying
Kind of
Yes
I didn't understand the
Analogy or his using of is
These people who aren't
Redpilled aswar
No the people who don't who don't see the truth
Put in for warriors
The Prodigal Son
He wants to come back
Whenever
All right now the second problem
Is in
The Prodigal Son
The father doesn't
Scream at the Sun
The comeback
The idea of it is
A lesson learned brings you back
Back to where you were supposed
Not that being screamed at
Get you in line
Alex is really dumb
Scripture every now and again because of you.
So he goes on from here to get even weirder
This clips
Start with him
The perfect example of how
He starts with some false modesty
He gets into an impression
F*****-up analogy
I love
Analogies
Do we get a personal history
No personal history in this episode
Obsessed with finding out more about him
Never looking it up or doing any research of my own
This analogy makes
Haslam
Okay
Be able to sleep
You have done nothing
I want to request that you don't say anything over that least the end of this because
You need to hear him say that
Okay cuz otherwise
If you don't get all the words
It might
You might think
It's f***** up as it is
It's super fun.
Cuz I don't want to die
This is still present Vance
Resume
You should we want we want the people who aren't totally turned over to why we want
To reach out to them
The government
Jonathan Gruber says you're dumb I don't think you're dumb
Get connected to God you can live
That's how I've got to talk to you
Like MPR
It's not a retard
Trump talks to people watching real slow
Not because he doesn't know that you don't already know at
Also known as now I don't know what again after you he's doing the Android guy for Lord of the Rings
Ganges
Better than a sleep stage
Out of the sleep
I understand
Because
That's fine
Communicating with the people
Do you watch it's called stroller going to win they want a violin
Because I think they can defeat that
We're going to be peaceful until they attack us and then
You know
I'm sorry
Take up an old polar something on the side
Italian-based brains out
Mudbound
Goddamn
Fuk was that
What any of that mean
I know is that he
Too f******
And he said it came off someone's back porch with someone
It's not what you might have
Oh yeah
I think
That the analogy
Trying to make
Failed
F*** with that
Make me feel better in like you see it
Babies hurting and dying on the
Street and got a mercy killing
Or something like that
Dumb.
He did
You don't like it like that you know I didn't mean if you can't wake up your like a dumb dog murder
I've had with a pole
No pleasure in murdering
Xena
If you murdered if you used the metaphor that he's making
Sometimes
I take no pleasure in it
But some people must die
That's f****** nuts
He's losing it
That Leanne Wackadoo level you see how like lazily he's delivering
Keith so f******
Fun out of control because of this interview with
Like it
All the other stuff that's going on in the world
This clear lawsuit about pizza gate that's in the in the works
His Admiral money going away
Better promoting his website which even if
There's no involvement with Russia
He's going to have to realize that that meme
All this newfound
Audience is fake
Is not real he doesn't actually have the popularity do you think he has
A lot of it is automated traffic
And s*** like that
This is spinning in his head
Now he's got Steve pieczenik on his show where he's like Alright
This is Safe Harbor this guy likes me
We're going to just spend some conspiracy Yarns together and scare some people
And plucking even stupid people play ball and now
But what do I do
Imagine murdering people
Like
Like that interview with
Taking him to a Violent Femmes
It's like that's what he's going on right there
Whole thing's
He's now he's responding to that the only way he knows his Ultra male
We got a murder p
Esoteric does
You've got to start up even for Alex
He's kind of like a boat adrift at this point
You've got to find something to hold onto something to Anchor member the story of the prodigal
The Sun goes out
After getting all of his
Inheritance before he deserves it
And then
Just party
And then his dad murders in like a dog
You remember that part of the Bride
The f*** you're murdering my brother
He's like dude he was protocol
Paf
He's a boat address
Anchor onto something
The only thing
If you've been talkin about that
Doesn't really relate back to things
But he got
Slap down by pieczenik about
Nunez
Wiretapping
Do you take 17 yet
Now as like
Okay I'm going to use him to 2
Steady mice
Who's next
Knows everything about this
I don't know about that as Jetsam Diwali records some bad one Rider
People
Trump's transition team
So
Intelligence committee about his
Directly to the White House
Given to him by the Trump White House
Steve Bannon
Trump as we've already established
Doesn't have Anka or Kushner there
Cuz he can't communicate with
People in office
Speaking of what I mean about that but
To the Nunez
Information
Stuff that press conference
Citadel
To use Alex
Terminology I reverse engineered
The next episode
It's going to be laid back
The f*** out of the next
Because
They're coming
He's the one guy
In that hole
You work for
Hawaii
Elijah Cummings I mean give me a break man
So controlled by the Russians during the Cold War
Look at people
He's just telling the truth and say he's an evil person
Gimme a Break
Break me off a piece
Piece of that
I'm not
I just don't
I don't know if he realizes he's doing it
It's the only thing he can do
I don't feel powerful demon Michael Moore a total piece of crap traitor to humanity I Total Wine slug
Not
There was a cuck
Lecturing
Steve pieczenik
Higher up
Turn off are you meaning
Steve pieczenik is
You know he's like a mid-tier guy that I don't need to lecture the mid-level guy
Do all the stuff
And I think a lot of response
Indicates the Steve listens to the show he can't be happy with
Where Alex went after the
If I were him I would baby maybe he got the maybe got the
Just later on from somebody
Alright
And
Fundamental
Nope and that's
Republican General About Liberty and the
Disappeared
Surprise him
I just instinctively have to try to sit there
And then when I walked into place yesterday for dinner
Young charger Wireless
Is what makes me even funny
Because they have to make it a joke that I'm so right because she then they might
Do something
Alex Alex Alex
Alex baby
What
Do you being does not make you funny that's not what we're laughing at
Attractive
Hell yeah
Not
As an unusual occurrence
Or husband
For husband
As we all know
You can tell him
Muslim headscarf
No that's what trends are in the Muslim headscarves
Sew-in in that they were making fun
Yeah in that
Story
I think that maybe someone's like
That's it
Not a story
No
Is there a point deer
He's so right the people have to make him into a joke
He's not right
He's wrong about
Yeah
He's so wrong about being right that he's a joke
He's a joke
He's been wrong about countless things
Just today
I can't say whether or not he's wrong about
This next thing but I do think that maybe the the LS
Kickstand right before the split
The lawyer Boyer
I love the
Weird little deep
Throws into this that
What's a good restaurant
You going to
Yeah
There's this whole life
It's like a lot like any
What time you're lying you end up putting a lot more
Details
But also there's all these like little psychological things
Is it go into there
Words like
I would
Never speak
To somebody who
Wasn't a Baha'i
Only the higher class
Will come up to me
I go to the
These places where the higher
Strfkr
Yamini begs the question how
Does he know that
These are lawyers
He very much implies that that was the end of the converse
Yeah like there's no there's no content like if he had
Conversation
With them
He would have
I told us all about that
Probably
Just laughed at him a little bit
Their lawyers villars told me they watch what we watch
Shoe Show
We watch a show and then they laughed at
Crushing pressure that exist
To be Alex Jones right now
I don't f****** difficult to imagine
The crushing pressure
Because all
The 23 years you went ignored
Is coming back
Taunton
Like before no one gave a s***
Unfortunately
You spent 20 years
Building a
Yeah and building up a
Very respectable
But not all that
Huge
Audience
Real
Rindge weirdo
This is this
He has
No idea this is one of the things
Is that
Doesn't know how to
No and
Had no idea
He was hitting himself to
The wagon
Of somebody who would win
Like that
Really
Because if we are giving him
Even that bass
Cunning
Blackstone
Donald Trump
Because Trump
Was a joke
So so he pulled out this guy who is a man after his own heart
Pulling out nonsense left and right
Sane Bolt
Assuming that
We can dump
Tail together we can lose together
That will give us both like
More of a plateau
Just say the Dumber s*** that we have to say
Have to
Engaged
Well I mean it's the same thing with
What a lot of people have come out and said about the
Failed Obamacare
Repealing
Excuse me house members
Weed
Christopher this
When Obama was in office
Cuz we knew we knew it would never work
We can't foster like that
Well one of the most
Brutal things
Republican
Absolutely
It was like a One Moment of clarity
You know
In the past 8 years
Think we've ever done anything positive
I don't think we've ever done anything that advances forward to doing things down
Party who is
Trying to say no
If we don't
Do something positive
What are we here for
The thing that we've all been
And it seems like it's the first time he's ever even
Consider the possibility that
Is a giant pile of garbage
Have to look in the mirror
But my point is Alex I think
Is like those senators
But they actually have members but in this case
Accidentally
Obamacare
But he joined up with Trump cuz it's like
Trump is going to lose
I'm going to say that
He could destroy the globalist
But when he loses I can say that he was cheated out of it going
Exactly
And stay the exact same things that I say
Network
Sing floated after
Alex Jones
Have had a
Syndicated charge that might have been on that Network
Unfortunately his metaphorical Obamacare repeal
OSHA
He is not taking out the globalist the more we live in this
The more it seems like Trump being elected
Was bad
Everyone
Yeah
Trump include include
No one on the planet it turns out
Food is probably the only person
Intercourse
Other than other than
Like a
Encouragement
To commit more violent
White supremacist aren't getting it
But they want either
No but they're getting marketing opportunities are probably getting
They're probably the most Americans
Something you can get
Recruitment
Or at least
Like
The ability to
Bmore free with
With your idiotic
Even if it's in the negative even if it is against
The media of talking more and more about
People who have bigoted positions
Only emboldened I feel that way too
It's almost like they are finally realizing
What it feels like
Begay
Fortran
You know how
Do you know how more comfortable you are in your own skin when you don't have to
Owen Shroyer and Lee Ann McAdoo
To be in the Pussycat Dolls
As I like to call
Great
They're talkin to her
And she's describing the experience of realizing the cheese
Conservative
Exactly like gay people talk about
I mean can't you just make
Small connect
She supports the LGBT
It's a bigger issue for other people but in her case that's not
Do both
Interpretive
Forecast
If there's a
Full
Acceptance
Then maybe we can go back
Is there's a full acceptance of the LG
Maybe you
You can go back
Well I am a
Conservative and also a person who is
But for right
Now
All you were saying
Is that I am willing
Marginalized
Millions and millions of
I'm willing to
To watch them kill them
So I can
Can get taxed
Yep that's what you're saying
Later on
Later on after all of this
Are all the bigotry
In the world
Has gone away
Yeah then we can get back to how conservatism is
So never
Exactly
This is where it gets esoteric
Is a riddle
This is where he turns
Internal
And is Jeff
Really discovered
I don't know what's going on
Struggling
And then everyone tries to climb that
Staircase to heaven
Can be over other people what the hell is that
Bonfire knows the valleys
You're already in the Stars
Beautiful beautiful
And
Down in the valley is the highest point
People keep thinking they should
Down
That mean you don't become successful
Wealth is to protect yourself
You build it's not so you can sit there like a peacock
Kayla Robinson
Because on average are so solace
There's something nice
Who's got a bigger soul
Who's got who's got bigger
What are you talkin about
What was that
You're in the valley and you realize the valley is the
This is
Like the
Religion
Junior High summer
Everybody
Everybody sleeping in the door
All the sudden one kid
Power and that's when the ship goes down
Right
I don't know
I think that's exactly what that kid
Rich Sommer
Alex Jones
She got like a waiver to go to camp kanakuk
Yeah I'm at I went to like really rich
Christian
And I'm not
Work
That's for another day
This is f***** up it starts out f***** up and
Brujo boy
Slit my throat
I would do it there's a secret
Strong
Have
I will though why I have effect on them and if the people
Ever realize this
And the bushfires of Liberty
Charging out of the Mist
Individuals that will be 100.
Right now I'm still waiting for
I know it's coming
And for the global should know this
Is only the first level of this event
It's going to get bigger
Stronger
Humans really do understand us
Once we have a platform to build on
Now
Auto-launch deck
Looks like he knows
Unlimited any Elite know that in there so jealous they're so angry they're so upset they don't know what to do
Because they're sitting around not even knowing how to use what they've got
Cuz they didn't develop
Their phone
Even further than we are
Turns into some nightmare because we've got bad people in control of those systems
This is why he had to cut off Steve pieczenik this is what he needed to
Bill his f****** time with
Written in the largest possible letters
Please go to therapy
Yeah
Alex you need analysis this is not good just
He is
Considering suicide right
Really what are you doing
It's sort of an Artful expression of it at least it is like
If I could if I could give of my life essay
To create
The energy that's needed
Stop the globalist
My sworn enemy
That I would do that
That's not really a threat of suicide
Violent language right after talking about murdering a dog
I swear to God
This is Emily dick
He is Emily Dickinson
You think so
This is
Crazy I mean
About like
This is only going
It's going to keep happening faster and faster
I agree
In terms of like
Another propaganda
And the way the internet is radicalizing people and stuff like that
That's what's going to happen he just doesn't realize that he is
The problem
It's not just make-believe group Republic
Thinks they're the hero
I don't
I think I'm a piece of s***
Fair enough yeah I do I think I might
Turn my own scary story is about I don't even know what the
My cat maybe I don't know
The story
About
You grown up
South Philly right
Okay
I never watched resperate Fresh Prince
Fresh Prince
Anyway
Blast
Clip is sort of
Beforehand
Louboutin to the 4th hour
And he's back talk
I think if they would
Tonight I'm not sure I
Oh okay talk about vaccines being bad
He is the word
The NIH is getting on Sunday
F*** you
I hate
Bush's Batman
Also
Picture is still not hung
I can confirm
I think I can find him on Twitter I think we could find them on Twitter
Vermont weather
I bet it
Chicago next week
We need that
Now my only goal
Like eventually if we
We get beyond the picture that's
You know
People and productivity circles like to talk about having actionable goals
You know we can't we can't we can't solve The Alex Jones and we can get that picture
Set around and say we want to have a great podcast that's not an actionable goal
I'm going to
To tweet at John Rappaport masterminded megapixel
Anyway
It's getting this last clip this is again he's now falling back
To Nunez
It still has some of this esoteric language in it
And the boys
Transcends from the realm of the normal man into the arena
Wow
This is f****** banana.
Donald Trump
Other people need to expired
It does one man to start trying to be men again and actually stand up for what's good and honorable
We'll have a civilization
Only when men start acting like real mannequin will we have a civilization
I feel like that's not how it works
Be that as it may I mean it is
It's good that that's where we're going to jump off
Because that's
Perfect
Encapsulation of a lot of Alex's life philosophy
You must be real men
Let's all be dudes bro-bro masculinity
Globalist
I don't know I don't know what's going on in Alex Jones is world of your writing needs
To get therapy
There's so much
There's so much going on like there's
Any world but like
Strange like up-and-down of
His emotional
Allstate
The interview falling apart and him turning really dark and fun topics
Is it is it
Connect it
Oh absolutely you're watching a psychodrama is it is a psychodrama in radio show
Show form episode
So much going on
A Prairie Home Companion in the two greatest what the f*** is happening
Infowars
There's so much going on
It's insane
It's never been like this
No this is
They're part of an investigation into Russian espionage
There
Apologizing for pizzagate
Fair
Lost their funding
It's crazy this is
I read once
Substantiate a reports that they just have to fire some people
Really I don't know if that's true or not but it seems
Triple murder
Yeah that that is kind of what wood makes
There's talk that like within the next week
They could be
Shuttering
No I don't think so
Internet speculation
But with all of the chaos that's going on
Things are going to get so excited
Wood
And I'm
Being one
Hundred percent
Serious right now
Alex Jones
I'm selfish
I'm being 100% serious
And I'm quoting
Cuz I love die.
Surrender
There will be no White Flag above his door
Even if it will the next item song is I'm in love and always will be
I will say that
Like a bird
That's nice
You have no worries
II
That you eat
Here's a more would I would say
Okay
Whether or not
Infowars
Self as
We know it
He will
Do a
4 Hour
YouTube video Everyday
He might just have to go back to his roots
In his home he will set up an iPhone
You can't win he will do a YouTube show
I can't imagine how expensive it is
To do what he does now
But he could do the exact same thing
Pretty much
For what week
Which is minimal he might
Just do a podcast
He might do a podcast
Right now
I am putting out the call Alex Jones you could join us Infowars ends
Come on r-pod
Join the knowledge fight Network
Reinstall Auto to English
We got to get out of here
But
Programming
Program
But
It is
Be Robin Owen show
Hey Rob do in Owen Shroyer
Co-hosting a show
Wow ain't that sounds
Horrific
One of the most unlistenable things I've ever heard
Truly horrific I listen to one episode and it was
They have no chem
Of course not Owen Shroyer seems to not want to be there
Robbed
Terrible on the camera
Yeah it's
If that's your first volley of new programming
Body
Myra you got to get it together
Anyway
If you want to hire us Alex
Knowledge
Underscore
In progress
Putting up a little pieces of his personal life
We are stealing little pieces of his personal life and putting it on the internet
And creating a biography
In real-time also go check it out
Just giving us a little bit of a shout out on the a.v. club.
Also
Here we go
Let's give a little shout-out to
Underscore Oz underscore underscore underscore
Who may or may not be listening to this now
Solid Twitter handle
ITunes
If you have thank you very
Go suck a lemon
Old school
Very complicated relationship with having Sam
Also if you want to email us agreed Chasse
You got it
Thank you guys so much for listening
Built-up really real
But in the meantime
Let me ask you
Udan what are
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work