Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
I think it was that one with the boat
Pirate pirate one
American history
Hi on the Wii U but I never went
Let's
For that against me
I remember my friend Kevin Brody
Comedian Kevin Brody
In particular
Very harshly to tasks
Score like Network
Looked at by cool kids as being the worst in the series
Or something
Make my house
That's what everybody
I'm actually going to role-play as a hunter
I'm out of the mainstream I saw in the group
Somebody posting about
Odyssey
Yeah
I love that style of game
Murder in perhaps
But I like that style of game a lot and I wish that I had a sister
I wish I wasn't so dedicated
Nintendo
I'm never going to get away from
That's what's going to be
Also
Never point out what they are
So today Mountain Dew Kickstart blueberry pomegranate
It's best that you don't know that you do
That is the fun
Where in March 2003
Alright
31st most people would remember that there 31 days in May
Can I had a hard time
I don't remember any of that
Months
I've never been able
Remember that
What's the
Schools
January February
I don't even go to 828 most of the time October I know that
That it would be 25 days and that is not correct
Crapshoot could be
My birthday is in April I have no idea
I know August
It's 31 because of that
F****** guy
He had to have
Is that right okay
I was willing to believe
Going over the 30th 31st today
Before we get started like
Play take a little time
Say thank you
You know how many days are in a month cuz they're real cool
Some new donors
People who have joined up with
First of all
Thank you so much you're now
Also
I'm a policy wonk
Make a joke
Also
I'm a policy wonk
You know what some days we get soda spiders at Wafers and Sundays
We get Chris Joe and Matthew
Can we still appreciate it all the same
Essentially
Finally looks like
Donated a little bit of
We appreciate it oh so very much
So Dominic
You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Someone someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Thank you so much.
It says support the show
Start a business
Are we
This is a crazy this is a crazy little couple days
What we had
John Birch Society
President
McManus
Waffle on some of his positions
I meant between his belly
I'm pretty hard into a
Go f*** yourself Glenn Beck
Kind of thing
So I kind of expected those themes to continue and
It does it's always
No you jokes
Narrative
A couple of a couple of completely nude air it is
Is Varian
Interesting
Nothing at all
And the first one
Is one of those interesting one
You don't know in 2017
Paul Joseph Watson now it's got really it.
I do remember
Everybody was like
Because mad at soy
Decade
Prisoners in jail
Sixty 70% of store
Absolutely
That's one reason the boys are so effeminate and just so happens the Plastics
Plastic leashes at Region
Hyper feminized
Shakopee Airport
No
Absurd
Global about is like 30
Pre-pubertal indicators and stuff like that like
Adipose tissue growing in brass areas
Stuff like that
Most scientists
I heard right about it
Lake that much more to
More overweight
But the entire in terms of like the hormone
Aspects of it
Stuff like that
That hasn't gone down significantly.
It's not it it's not 3
I thought it was
Going higher
I'm not fully up on the side
So I feel like I would be in the wrong
Want to talk about it
To be just this idea of like pre-pubertal
As of like
Glitches
Most likely a function of a
Also probably
We are all
Soybeans
Injected with
Boss ladies
Wild that that's there back then
What is it about
Replacing
And a lot of the people who
Who have
Show interest in the world are big farms
Seems like that people who have large kill operations going
That's so they probably have a lot of financial
Demonizing vegetarian
Everything
Stop climb
Be their primary
But it also could just be
Protecting their operation
Which unfortunately has the Buy
Product also of being
A very
Colluding in
Industrial
You shouldn't have any Carpenter
I think that I think it would be not too far of a leak
To make that argument
Alex
I think a lot of
Hatred
Elmo's voice
Love the story hatred that you see probably traces back
To some sort of agribusiness money
The comes in
Through lobbying
I would assume
Next year is that Alex
He's not
Off the mandatory service bill
Narrative even though it is past
All of the language
Concerned about it's been stripped out of the Bell
It doesn't exist
But he is now a
But the danger
Gone
With the fight and fight and fight
Pass the draft
Slavery
Mandatory service Bill live Sean
It seems like
Listed
Bunch of other stuff too
Note the house back
The language was flip from one bill in HR
Ford
Hr1044
Just Alex reading from an Infowars article and so obviously
The details
It's not going to be
Necessarily
The language
Blue Bell number one
They're f****** up the timeline of it entirely in order to present their version of it that is
Massive Resistance
It's against this got that
Take it out when the language was already taken out by the time that Alex's
False resistance ever got involved
Now HR 144 is
Isabel
It was introduced on March 11th 2009 before this episode
Just two days after the original mandatory service Bell
Alex's make
Shut up about was introduced
From what I can tell it looks like the reason for this was that the language in the original Bill HR 1388
About setting up a commission to explore the reasons for language and volunteerism in America was already in process of being
Being taken out of that original belt
It was being introduced separately to remove that sticking point
From hr13
388 which would allow it
At the house
Easier
That's day March 11th
HR 144
It was introduced
It was sent to committee
Where.
No action taken on the bills since its introduction
And it has zero momentum
It has been dead in committee for 20 days before Alex knew existed
Elizabeth dead in committee for a week
By the time HR 138/82 pasta
Really
Remember on our on our list
So whenever he started
Following finding out that
Not going
Gilera iPod
Here's where we
Looks like a victory
I about a bill
You won't
F****** guy and as long as it's in committee you can have like it stranger Phil you know it could be
I was way off on all the details
Profoundly late to the
The party
Would have been covering this on the March 11th episode of the show not the f****** March 31st episode
This is nonsense this is just business
Sloppy
Battery lights
I got no
Really really cold
Because that's how you know you're a good blacksmith to make a sword out of a hot pizza
Piece of iron
Blacksmith
Felt good
I'd like
I like this
Because it is funny when you look at the Historical framework of it
At what you doing
I can't say that he does know
Some selfies like a journalist
You should know damn well what's going on
Put it in a separate bill NFL died
That's what happened
Because it was
To some extent even controversial not just in right-wing propaganda in the right-wing of
What is ended up probably being
It would make it much more difficult for HR 138
Which everyone was in favor of
You say kyline which out now the bill passes
So now the park
People disagreed on
Happens all the time
Very standard Congress stuff
To note that we can neither
Confirm nor deny that Alex knows
Anything
That is true
You should know this
Does he know
I don't know
You're right we only have our expectations of what a human
Should know to go on antos might be faulty
Absolutely should know he's contradict
This one is
Here's one of the battle of this
I had of as a person
Bow
Barack Obama's Kenyan repair Attica
Gifts for presidents meeting with the
Preacher
And give for presents
Disgusting Queen hereditary
Pretty disgusting
I guess
The first sitting president to go meet with
The queen
Track 25 before she was Queen Elizabeth met with President Harry Truman
Father King George the sixth
7 hours of Queen Elizabeth
She was in attendance for a state dinner and even met with former president at the Waldorf Astoria
The 1959 Eisenhower would visit Volvo visit with Elizabeth again on her turf
In 1961
That was Richard Nixon president
In 1976 Elizabeth was invited to a grand celebration
Just after the bicentennial
Okay
Choose
And they're even famous pictures
Dancing together
Has never forgotten its British Heritage
Rifai Wesley maybe inappropriate gesture of kissing on the lips
Much does a queen in everyone's disapproval
That was an international scandal
Everybody was
Yeah I love that
Became the first president to stay the night there
You would return to visit
A1989 George h.w. Bush
When she visited
In 1994 Bill Clinton worth
The UK
Elizabeth
And in 2000
3 he was the first
The Visitor
Technically
A state visit
The specific definition is hard to nail down
To consult Tony Blair about the visit
Having to consult with Tony Blair is
The worst sentence
But you can imagine
2009 the world was scandalized
Michelle
Egregious than Carter's Behavior
Mike Broyles protocol
There's a thing about you can't initiate contact
The queen
And she has to initiate that car
Isn't that I meant maybe he will be
Maybe he will be once a day
I could see that r g
President not literally
Nixon vice president
Meet with the queen during the years that she's been alive
And on the throne
Is LBJ
He is the only President and most likely that is only because of schedules
It because the Vietnam War
Those are the only president
All of those people pretty much
I have a god-like with
Very cute
Have gone and visited the queen
It's crazy
He's also talking about
Because he's like
He's trying to make this seem like some sort of
Real scandal
So
Answer the question of bowing I would like to say
This this is interesting story of George HW Bush's present
Play the stupidest fake outrage
Very soon after he was inaugurated
To attend the funeral of Emperor Hirohito Hirohito
Is a very complicated situation leader during World War
Funeral of his enemies leader
Leader of our country
It's very complicated dynamic
Bush attended that funeral procession
The casket
The deceased emperor
When he was asked about if you made the point that it was a sign of respect
U.s. is now
Friendswood
Customary
In Japanese culture
Respect to our now Ally and friend
After that she was roundly criticized by the right for battling to anyone
Because some picadillos up
Are evergreen it was an attack Bush back then for this
Alex
Now to use this
To attack Obama
I just for fun
When I was looking into this I found a hilarious collection of pictures of Eisenhower balance
It's
Crazy
Keep out everybody
Pope John the 23rd to the wife of the Italian Prime Minister
Do Greek Orthodox Archbishop
Chicago's
Of New York
Charles de Gaulle
About to everybody
Eisenhower
Diplomatic politeness
Controversy
Politeness
No it was a it was actually that he kept walking
In front of her
That's right
Not done
Carter kissed
The queen on the lips
Hilarious Wildside
Although at the same time that
I know that it's not
Romantic
Eli kiss on the cheek
European way but he went for the mouth
I don't know man
It's a weird piece of some sort of Foreign Relations history
All this is that like first of all
Everyone except for LBJ
That is not a big deal
And she's the presumptive head of the country
Even though it's
Imagine
It still let's have fun
Or whatever
So there's that there's that
It's clearly just making bulshit up about
And then what
It's complete nonsense
He's just trying to score points
His version of it would be that like it's
Showing deference
Giving up our sovereign
L
Or something like that but
Not really
So is shaking
Just being polite
Anyway
Walking around with his dick out
Slapping people
Really want
Is that kind of a
Idea that they have
What the American
Watch the video of Obama meeting
He doesn't bow
He gives a little bit of a head nod
It's not like
It's not at the shoulders
It's definitely not at the waist
But there is a little bit of
Guess what
We're doing what ends up happening is very close to like Doffing your cat
Greetings
It is not a scandal it is not dialing to the queen to show submission to the throne
Is kind of
Fashion do that his
Did do a lot of research because
That argument of life
Like what
Levels of
How people would interpret it
Department in the executive branch
About that
It keeps track
4 / 6
Yourself of diplomacy
So I
Obama's
Team telling him what's appropriate would you beat the queen
He was a he was a f****** like
State senator and he's not a royal
There's no reason to assume you've met a queen
I would have no idea how to handle myself without training if I were to meet a royal
I would call the scandal going to go with fist-bump Michelle did
Papa Obama
I would say that
The final two
Would be
HW throwing up on the Japanese
Prime minister prime minister
Kissing the queen
What you going to go with
I would say Carter because
At least
With bush
Throwing up is almost always an involuntary
Apartment guide
But that's a panic
Choice skyspace
I think so I think it's like
Sure
The involuntary nature of it he might have been looking at him or whatever
You sometimes can be pretty of me
Could have not kissed
Baby
Now I'm just imagining all the different ways
And the relatives
Is that better or worse than the prime
Better
Even yet
Scandal
I don't know anyway let's move along because
We're still on this topic
On the 30th
Alex has Webster
I don't really interesting thing happened
Really having a conversation
Webster Tarpley
He'd also been on the 29th
Episode Sunday episode
I noticed that he was saying
Exactly
Things
To the point where I thought Alex
Just playing
The interview from here
I've been pretending he was in studio
It's not
He's just saying the exact same things over and over again
Exactly
The Masterpiece you're going to end up getting awards for this
The two of them have a little bit of a bull session about this
Idea of Obama going to
Meet the queen
And Tarpley said something
Not good
Being received
April 20th April 1st is not the next day
March 31st
He's practicing
The first sitting US president
My friend
Which According to which Obama
You could make him ineligible for the
But why
About whether he's qualified to be the president
Herbalife
The American
Isambard in the sky
I got a hunch
Webster Tarpley stand by that
I bet
Silberg
To check into that
I don't give a s*** 0
You talk much about it
Probably could just be sad like
Fairly similar to Stephen The Obama Deception
So after this Alex has
Call Lynn
Ron Paul
And all that s***
Apparently a couple days prior Luca daseke had been sent
The Clique
He got arrested
Because
He was I don't know
I don't I don't talk
I can care about the story I'll be partially on it I'm just going to play
This clip
Where Luke explains his arrest
Because I want to play the clip after this
Years Lukas planing what happened to him I don't think this is accurate at all
But whatever
Surprise
Thank you and your listeners for calling into the police station last night
Call my friend Anthony and Manny
They're listening to the police officer talking over about the press pass on how they wanted to
Are charged me with having a fake person who was your callers who was you that's called in and got the
Call Jimmy with criminal
Price guide for walking into a hotel nothing else I was never asked to leave
I walked into the hotel and as soon as I did I was on the third floor I was immediately
Aidid by Bloomberg personal security guard
Air police intelligence
How's brought downstairs
When I was broke downstairs I was told I was detained I asked him why am I being detained why
What's the probable cause
Police intelligence by me
Then the police intelligence got the police officers
This kid won't leave
Can I please leave can I please get out of here can I please go home
Do you see here they went to the other police officers and they said
He won't leave when we trying to leave I was already on the first floor of the real
What's going on here most likely is just misunderstanding what had
Get a fake press pass wasn't recognized by this
And so he was not considered
Depressed he had no reason to be there it was a fundraiser
Probably take
Guess you have to pay unless you're part of the day
Legitimate
Passing there
Other people
It wasn't about when they said
You're detained
Endure whatever before
Because I do I know a bit about
He yells a lot I don't know anything about Luke
Spotify
That Bloomberg people
Did not know who Luke rudowski
Probably not
And one of his trademark saying
Busy screaming
Based on the fact that I have no evidence to the contrary
There when he was told his press pass was no good
He probably yelled about how I a press
Something like that kind of in his character
I'm not entirely sure anyway I don't believe his version of the story it's not it seems like nonsense to me
What is the setup of the story
The version that Luke wants to
To tell only played it so I can play this next clip where Alex
Telling Luke
To quit
Don't you got to talk to you about of being apart of his movement
Already Glory you guys have the last case of died mysteriously
You know that this was an official press event Bloomberg fundraiser that other press people
For attending
A year-and-a-half ago they already tried to say you had a bomb in your camera
Go ahead and do what you're doing if you want
Rustic mushrooms
I'm staying
Of the area that you're entering here
They don't they don't care
Okay thank God we are bombs on you all I'm telling you is
I'm telling you
In Warfare and Infowars there's a certain time to break off things
You're going to be hell to try to get you out of this
Senator Prescott
You would have left if they told you to leave like you always do I know I'm standing there turning up
Sort of
My issues
This seems like an Alex who has his Humanity intact
More than
Present-day well-liked on our Friday episode last week we heard him
Having a complete breakdown
Anymore
Thank you feels really bad about the world he is introduced lucrative ski into
Does lew-port house keys very inspired by Alex
Considers himself mini Alex Jones Young Young Gun Alex Jones out there on the streets
No not great. I think what you're hearing Express there is Alex feeling a little bit of guilt
And and and
That Luke is going to get himself in bigger trouble and then you'll have to feel bad about it
Never
Evernote
How
We do an episode in the present
I guess coincidence
Our very next episode
In the past he just needs it is weird
Parallels and discrepancies Wild
Serrapeptase
In the past
And a very unfair one
It is Interstate yet
Kill people
It's insane to see like how
Sort of similar stimulus and response
In different time
Other hand
There is a certain amount of
Luke
Paternal relationship
Where is Gavin
Did not accept
So part of Alex
Which is
Bananas
Come from like
This is
Clear
Where is Gavin's
But I think that's why Alex
Can fuel hose
That's probably why he is able to access the ocean
Because Luke has willingly a at Power
I think it's possible that I was just can't
Contextualize relation
I'm just outside of the Safari Zone
Subordinate
It is next clip
We get to catch up
He's as old as Alec
May 30th probably
Big Brothers 35
I don't remember the guys name doesn't
Three-player Italy
These two Sacramento
Because I got a big narrative cooking
In Sacramento
About
How there's a homeless Camp there
And Arnold Schwarzenegger
Has come in and said that
These people that are living
Need to be taken to the fairground
And Alex
Who created this as
Proto thema
I assumed it was more about the relevance of the sack
Kings to the NBA that
Do with
Arnold
Schwarzenegger
Governor of California
Proto thema
Is how I solved
The fact that Alex owned Arnold exposed.com
What that's about
Okay he's decided that Arnold Schwarzenegger is doing a trial run of Civic
With his Tent City in Sacramento and he is dispatched
Incompetent
Arnold visit
Nobody
Okay he had gone down there
About Arnold with an approved
The mayor of Sacramento
Power Air Force
About Alex's narrative
And where he's getting
The ideas
I can track those down
Exactly
How can I know exactly why
Cares about your so excited
You love getting the exact Source correct
Here is Alex
Having a little chat with Rob.
Lavender egg
From Sacramento
Why do tell me about your experience when you got in the Los Angeles what you saw there
I'm in Sacramento
Oh by the way I don't think I have another guide
And the other guy is from
Those were all the homeless people hang out
Nobody there
Are you f****** kidding me
Jacob Skid Row 2009
Nightmare Zone
Cataract Vicky
Novella
And the Sacramento Mayor saying
Tough love you can't just live out here intense
We're going to make you go
Is more about the fact that they didn't have running water and sanitation out there it was a public health
California
Tell Alex that I don't think they're going to go quietly
Everything the people that we've been talkin to hear they they
Don't plan on going to this Expo El Expo Center
They're very
They really they don't get a lot of information or feedback from
The mayor of the city that they just come down all the sudden and tell them things
And
It is a real interesting environment that everybody that we met so far has been really nice
These people just want to live here and be left alone
And
You know it's right at the edge of town and you go right over some railroad tracks for a levee is
And you can see there's at least
It just wants one little area there's at least 310th kind of spread out over a few acre
There's a massive embellishment of
There are places like in Portland I believe it's called dignity City or something like that where they have
Play
Resources that are available porta potties running
Like times in Camp
This is not one of those
Situation
This is just
Bunch of people living in tents
In relative squalor
People are like we shouldn't trees out back
It's deeply dangerous
And then also you have the possibility for
The exploited
For disaster
Yeah I don't understand what
It's going to take
To get
People
To recognize
The homeless
Being homeless
Is a public health
Disaster for you as
There's so much
Mitigated
Disease
Skid-row there was an outbreak
Because of because
High-density
Taking care of
People is also
Then good about the people themselves
Here's the thing
Pointed out that everyone was really nice
They're trying to present this image
These are a
Kind of homeless
People that hang out at this Tent City
Alex
He's going to express it
Integrating them into this hellhole taking their basic
Fairgrounds
Is why can't they saying they're going to be for sin
Alarm Center not going to go
If they they said they try to force them into they're going to say no and they're either going to grab what they can grab and move
Farther back into the wood
The right there really quick I'm sorry I cut you off make
The point that he was gone
He isn't like
Exact response
To that question
But no one is forcing
Anybody
Two forces in we won't go
No I just completely missed
The
Implication
I'm saying
That they are nice
It's because
You say what
Different
Well this isn't what you would expect
Homeless people we assume that homeless people are
People like
But then there's also like what
Part and parcel of the they're nice
Alex
Resent this image
The people in this Tent City
The Working Poor
Yeah yeah
People would use Hoovervilles
Yeah this idea that they all they're doing is trying to
For a little while to get a downpayment for a house
Becky's legitimately same time which is first of all
I mean even if you don't know anything about that situation that's crazy
If maybe getting a month's rent or something like that
Conceivable
A downpayment on a house
I'm just going to go live in the city for a few months
To get about 50 unemployed
Try to get back on my feet get a job so I can get a downpayment on a house
Absurd
But
Alex has an ulterior motive
An operation and the reason
Is it to get to the bottom of the story
They didn't to help anybody
It's to get footage for his new.
Call you tomorrow late in the evening we're going to take off I think about 6:30 at night
I need YouTube
I need you to manufacture the reality I need for my new documentary
These people
Continue to do this
Absolutely
For me to make whatever argument I'm going to make
More to the story but this is where it leaves off on
The 30th
Let me get back to it on the 3rd
31st Iowa
Explain
But for now
Alex jump
He gets to
Next clip Alex
Expresses exactly what I do
And I was waiting for
Your actions and others
That's the psychology
For the moment he would take responsibility for getting the language taken out of the belt
To discredit he hasn't
He's literally saying we got it taken out last week because of your hard work and are getting the word out
They were forced to get rid of this enslavement language
You bet you
The listeners but
Manager
To get this language taken out of the building
Before you knew it was this
It's awesome you take these ingredients
It's like soda
Flower
Yeah couple things
You make bread in the same way
In the past
The durian
What is the flower
It's that you've taken out with about it
So you add the baking soda which is lying about the timeline
And now you got that
Propaganda
But when is it ever
Let's make
Let's
Anyway
Siemens
Crusade against soy
And he's going to have a guest on talking about the
Her name is Karen Russo
She works for an organization
About that revolves around
She wants to talk about real
Yeah cuz she's
Actually working to stop
Abuse is in prison
Isaac
I know enough about her that I'm going to give her like a stamp of approval
I didn't see any red flags
That you usually do without
Episode
Alex
Keep trying to steer her towards toy
And she's just
What's talked about how like prisoners died
Just boil it down for his research on the radio talking about
Prisons
What's wrong with that
Estrogen
Call Tabitha.
It is a small issue that I cover that she's a different direction that isn't about
He's already
There
He's already there with the negative
Treatment of
Prison
Why can't you
You just fold reality
You know just like
Throw-in guess what they're also mystery
This way
Has a rampage against
She's having a conversation about
In their throne
Really
You're more than welcome to do that but
He's doing it it makes me feel
Feel like
She really wants to get this
It's what he wants this interview
Here in this next clip
He steers her towards it again
I am the middle of it
Going back to Karen Rusev
Adele hit on the diet
Moana and I wanted
0 in on a couple of stats
Just so people can kind of get a handle on the number
We're talking about here
We are
The only country in the world that incarcerated
Many human beings that is correct there are two point three million folks locked up in a jail or prison today
In addition to that 2.3 million are on probation and parole
7 points
4 million
CBS News
You can do with anything
Statistics
And I'm a real stickler for this
Even with my client
Statistics
He almost seems disappointed that the number isn't familiar
2% blue
It's lower than a number that I've introduced every possible number then
It doesn't work for me
No 95
Do you like to talk about but I have more important issue
I want to get to
This flavor the
The entire
Is what kind of leads me to think that maybe she's not as crazy
Is interested in
Is he selling
Food
I'm guessing that cuz while I was gone through
There's like one
Throw-in actual issues and get people motivated and there's
Is of course
He has to demonize Soy
So he can sell his
Maybe cuz
Come Direct
Cuz you know I only put
Testosterone
My balls directly in
Beef testosterone
And then to
Because
If you start talkin about realshit peep
People are going to want to do
Responsible
In this clip
I kind of
Started to get the feeling that maybe she wasn't so
Cool but good point poorly
And then Alex comes in
He doesn't care
This isn't about black people but
It's sad
Every time an inmate gets let loose
And he's got HIV
HGTV
TV
Mirka
Meningitis
You name it every time they're released. Here it is going to affect you
Next time you run through a fast-food thing
Understand
Washing the dishes
That's the point that I think that she's making very poorly
I get but that's not the way
Trying to get the audience and Alex to understand
What the issues
You and hurting
Can hurt you
If that's the Baseline of getting you to understand
Articulates with behind it is not like a
Text yourself or mobile
People are prisoners
It is a treat people better
I'm all right with that
So if we have somebody in
In prison
Who has meningitis
It's going to
Every other prisoner
We have 2.4
2.3 million people
Prison bus apiece is
Incarcerating
We're spreading
Disease
They're going to be
That disease
You're talking about
Is that exactly where Alex picks things up
Journal
But you never see it in the news massive drug-resistant TB from illegal aliens
Australian
I understand spreading it's spreading out everybody
So she even think about
Talking about people like you and me
Pointers that were incarcerated so many
People who shouldn't be
Adequately
Her argument still
Well articulated that as well as I would like it does there are strong and
Indications of the she's not on the same tip is out
Interesting
You know just another little
Piece of bigotry and then a weird
Out of nowhere Rampage
Because he has not brought up at all
In the time that I've been listening to that I could 2009-2018
Search
Fight
It is also a law
The things you said
Eating soy
I think I agree with you in that
So far she is kind of
Push back on
Demonizing
Which is why
Her point is
Poorly in that
Demonizing
Equal
Because they're in there working
If you're not very smart
It could be heard as an argument that you should be afraid of these sick people
Being let out of prison
Prison
If she was a little bit
Closer with language
Made that point.
We're going to talk about her and that's the end
Can we go on
Because as we know Alex is super against
The bank
That had to be bailed out
Giving bonuses
Head of the John Birch Society on his show
McManus made
Who cares
These companies
That's the government Alex
That is absolutely
Now just a couple days later what does he say
A joke
Alex
I don't understand
It's less
It appears
It appears that it's less of like a changing of his
Morals as it is
An absence of any
He has someone who he
Built himself to be
Hierarchy
Totem pole
Is McManus was like why should you
You tell private companies
Take contracts to build FEMA camp totals
There's nothing behind any
Get someone with high status around him and it was agree with
I mean
Disagree with
Automatic
Bike for sport
News on the 31st and that is that the president
General Motors
Aftermath
You should step
Because of
Gianna
Crippled the Auto industry
Had to step in
And make some solvent
And that sort of thing
Everyone went Buckwild in the story was that Obama fired
That doesn't track in terms of him just saying
He resigns
That's a choice you made
And job
So here's Alex talking about Obama fired
Obama.com
Staggering spectacle
I'm a sitting president
Shocked
Effective firing
You're not really saying
Didn't fire that
This guy until GM
To fire him
Anything like that
Just fun use of language.
To demonize somebody
Kind of boring actually
Maybe that's better than
You know I mean if if Obama says hey
0 consequences whatsoever other than
Parachute
Naval bombers like
Hey guess what we're investigating you and now you're going to go
Call your company but you're going to
Something like that
I don't know
I'm not really interested in the narrative I think it's
Just another way of pointing the finger at Obama unfairly
Mel
Get another guy
One of our favorites
The guy who sells
Marty Schechter president
Dropped by the show
And he doesn't have a limerick
He has a limerick that one of Alex Jones
Phone calls we get there
Email
We get through satisfied
User
It's a pleasure every day you coming to my office
I'm eating another email
I even got one guy
Morning
Emailed me
He sent me a limerick
Alex Jones that Ivy found
Young man of world-renowned
Party endorsements
Gave me hope
Be happy
With your pure soap
You're something else
Another limerick
F****** time
Goddamn limerick
I don't want to take your money you're ruining my show
What what
Patron
Users
Yeah but user so Alex has a employee in their Studio
And I
You didn't believe me when I talk about
Forever
Slicing you a year are you not using it and then it turns out
150 bar
Better last you a year
Alright
Depressive anymore
3 year
This is the
School Bus sized are I convert water converter
What's the weather today
Hotel Bars
I like
Limerick for the day
He tries to the interviewer
Do we get another minute
Miserable
I got my Limerick ready to go
Next month we'll get your
We do not
Marty schacter noxon
19th century repeat
It was an old man of Nantucket
That is far as the bucket
Nantucket
Follow the pair to Port.
Girl with a bucket
Most people Coronavirus
You're welcome to man
But as for the bucket
Banana apple
A man and the man
Stole the money and ran
And then this for the bucket
Manhattan
Marty or something else you talk to you soon
AAA limerick
If there's somehow that I could wish upon
Limerick
Took me like
Two to three times listening to it to be like
What are you saying
And review of
Limerick is about this bucket
Renee
Lord Byron is here giving us a limerick about a bucket I would prefer to redo some of his pubes
Dangerous territory when you're doing a limerick it it starts
The dick so long you can suck it
The real urge to say f*** it
You're there so many
It's just Street limericks
Don't start with Nantucket
In Endwell
Corsi dozen
Where's washes mouth out
Which is where you got the idea
Injectafer once every
Productive
Here Marty Schechter come in
Disappointing
Listener and it was about
He's so busy
And then we came in with that
Really long leg
Finish the limerick
Do anything but Stay classy
You're something else
Close to the closest
Alex could ever get to David Letter
Hey Daddy
Because you are the war
I'm going to do it in
A damning faint praise
The other guests that I want
Here at the end
Is this
First episode
We get back to this homeless camp
Narrative
Here is where we'll figure out
Really going on
Alex
Clear that these are people trying to
Dubai houses
Governor
California Fairgrounds
Buss you out drop you off
If you're back at 3
Once can you
Regular
To raise enough money to get a downpayment on a house
Apartment
A deposit the pet deposit
Ludacris presentation
Another story
But that's already kind of world we lived in
The coverage
The last time
Now
Talk to Rob do
Even talk to that other dude
Jason something-or-other
Who's down there he's a guy from LA to
Claims there's no homeless people rap
Or some s***
And we get
Another character
We get another homeless character
In this Saga
And he's going to
Be used as
Horribly
Exploitative
Prop
Use him as such
I have no evidence
And using a massage
I think Alex has good intentions
You are high
You know we just talked to a guy that got his
He got pulled over and because he didn't have insurance on his
New Winnebago
They took all of his belongings everything he owned and let them out on the side of the street
Somebody pointed out
City and said you know
Camping out over there
And for that he made his way over here
How much will it be
He was saying it was about $1,000
Okay
I can't afford that important
Are they going to make him show up with insurance
In order for them to get it out today
Lyr you money
Get that
I will pay $1,000 to get the Winnebago out
I am such a great guy
This is key footage for the film
Giving away what your motivations are
Andaz
Completely altruistic gesture
I'm going to get his Winnebago out
Pay for one month
Most likely
But that's not cute
CI we got a situation
Here where
Alex
And
This next clip I think she'll give you a sense
What's going on here
Has every reason to believe that this guy.
Get insurance get this off the road and
Illegal
Expired driver's license
There's two police cars
Winnebago
Do you see the dichotomy is presented it's very similar to the dichotomy he was presenting earlier about the ID
View
These people in the Tent City are nice
And they're good they're just trying to get money together to buy
Arnold Schwarzenegger is going
Force them in with the other
The homeless people who are drug addict
Crazy
And all this stuff you hear this guy got his Winnebago taken and Alex
Not an illegal alien
He's trying to create these divisions
Category
Yep now
Hear the tears were this isn't
Here we find ourselves at the end of March
Whole Hog
Schwarzenegger forcing homeless people into a County Fairgrounds
Which according to Alex's
The first runner for the people
Easy to see how we make a connection but it's really important to take a look at the reality of the situation
To see how he's lying about a couple things
He's actually being tricked into
Supporting a cup
Couple others
This all started back to beginning of March
Reporter Lisa Ling to Sacramento
Cover the homeless Tent City
The reporting was incredibly flawed
And based on a fundamentally incorrect premise
Namely that the people living in the time city were newly homeless
The reason for misreporting isn't easy enough to see
It's a catchy hook for a story and over called them
Quote new face of homeless
The noble working for lost it all in the recession
The problem is that this wasn't even close
True for the vast majority of the people living in
Sin City
The Bay Area News
Quotes
With foreclosure rates in the Sacramento region among the highest in the nation
Is a symbol of the economic meltdown
People who lost their homes and we're suddenly pitching tents along the riverbed
The truth is somewhat less dramatic
Although sliver of the roughly 200 Tent City residents are recently middle-class people who lost their home
The overwhelming majority eighty-two 90% by several estimates
I've been homeless for years even decades
Our reporting Reuters was even more
You're saying quote
A closer examination of the site including interviews of Camp residents and police officers
Patrol the area turned up little if any evidence recession refugees were living among The Chronic
We homeless there
Fifty-five-year-old Tent City resident John kranitz commented on the influx
The reporters covering the tent city after it was featured on Oprah quotes
They don't want to talk to
They're searching for people who just lost their home
Countertop the movie
Lose a home when you've never owned one
Sorry most of the people here been homeless for a long time
Oprah's report included a bogus statistic
Make a 1,200 people were living in Tent City
When in reality
That was the number of homeless total in Sacramento
And the number is a tent city
Between 1 and 2
You say there's no way that
1 and 200 / 300
That's nonsense
The advocacy director for Loaves and Fishes
Has commented on the situation
Quotes
The media are trying to capture a very complex situation
We've had homelessness in this country
For decades
Each person has their own circumstance
You have to tease that out
If you're going to address the problem
Why do why do we care so much for people who suffer
Prefer short time versus those who suffer for a long time
What's that about
The media store
Easy human-interest story
The issue of homelessness
All they did is create a fictional narrative it was a
Florida by Marriott
Different forces
Push their own agenda
People who wanted to attack Obama could use a story
Creepy image of modern Hoovervilles
People who wanted to attack Bush could save this horror was all his fault
People like Alex could use it to argue the quote good hard-working people were being forced
None of this reflected reality
Schwarzenegger wasn't even behind the plan you just approve it because the governor
Cuz he was the governor of California
Who's mayor Kevin Johnson
Who is the one who's making the plan
Including setting up a homelessness task force
I haven't
David which included input input from people like John credit Ray
The plan was not to shut down the tent city and move them into a Fairground
There's also at 8
180000 dollar package that was approved
To add beds to existing homeless shelters
And create additional shelters
Plus offering retail Apartments
Approximately
340 Edition
Do people who are suffering
Thomas Rhett
What we have here
Is the situation
Where
Unfortunately
The interesting element here is that the origin of this propaganda there it is a dollar
It's Oprah
Alex is certainly putting his own dishonesty
But the underlying narrative
BG's comes directly from Oprah
Now the big
The spas-12 we need to address
Is it part and parcel how them
Media with representing the story is that these were white homeless
Of all the flight shows pictures I can find
The images on all the articles about this density every
The people featured are white
See if even happening to us
There's literally no way I would believe this is
Subconsciously or consciously responding to
And why you covering the story the way he
Absolutely
People this guy with the Winnebago in what it would have been if he was an illegal
Yeah all of it is because
Subconsciously
I believe it's consciously on his part
But what are you trying to do is to consciously
Reinforced that suggests
Listen to his audio
These are the white
And now they're being attacked
It's a tall white identity shitz playing out through this this Tent City narrative
The bigger picture of it
We should be talking about
You know Kevin Johnson the mayor
Introverts and anger
Making
Good progress like this lady who runs Loaves and Fishes
Even said that.
This is a very positive but
Unfortunately no one's going to be paying attention to this
6 months
Hopefully week
You can get
Putting a Band-Aid on a bigger wound
Continue to Graterford
I don't know
The argument about the
Prince between Obama's
Trumpsc
Look
Obama is going to do
You looked
And he knows what's up
Bring the white out of their throat
Play around that cuz if I got applied Agency on Obama
Even go that far just because
You know it's easier to Dabangg
It'll be more like his rhetoric would be more along the lines of Obama is allowing
Does allows
This happened to White
It has
Pretty good confidence
He's going to
Checked the white people over all others
You know I think you can
I think you can
Very clearly
The argument the only argument that really is Meaningful here
Is how much of this is
Alex intentionally guiding his programming
Towards that
Riling up
Fostering
White
Identity believe right and how much of it is just what he believes
And that's how he sees them
Not even realize
You know like
The only thing that's important because one
Is a white nationalist demagogue
Does demagogue
Poorly interpreting the news
You know I don't
I don't think it matters in the end
With with that kind of
I mean
With the way that we're now understanding
In his heyday
Upbringing
The books that
Red
Quotes
But there's that there's no way
There's no way for me to accept
That his
Is white supremacy
Is not Atlee
There's no way for me to say that it's
I can't prove that it's all conscious and
Purpose
Never believe that there is not a Consciousness that he is
Preparing
It's it's it's not
The water's edge
I go back and forth
Possibly not know what you're doing
It's not like Coach Dave
You are a huge racist you don't realize the labels that you're talking about you're so stupid you don't have to
You don't
You're stupid
You are also right
How to invest
And races
The higher-order
Is higher
You playing a game
Definitely know that whatever game he's playing at benefits whites more than n
This whole
Baby story is really fat
I'm really glad
To have gotten to dig into it a little
The element of it like being
What is responding to and furthering is the misreporting that
Which is crazy cuz he f****** hate
Right so he doesn't even realize that
It is
Taking a cobra plant germinated
I didn't realize it Oprah
Was irregular
Anytime I want my read-o-matic
Confirm or clues that her intentions and Lisa Ling's intentions
Of course we're good but lazy of course
Maybe it's like
Fudge a little bit hero beat
Not as thorough as we should because it makes a better story and at the end of the day what's the outcome of that story hopefully more
People caring about the homeless
So like I could that confuse
There
Rationale for whatever
Positive
Screw this one up
Or is like they realize that their daytime demographic was
Super white women
Who knows that it is hard to save
Now lying
I think it's good it's very easy
But
It's also
Because he has to
British guy that is
Is disposal
And their related
Steve Watson
Call Joseph
Is related brother
Brothers
Designer goggles
Do not remember cyc started coming on a urinalysis
Before Paul Joseph Watson
She is
Not as good
Is Paul Paul is much more Starkey
And has it
How old are you
Don't know that
I don't know
I don't know that to be the case
Call Joseph
If only because
I think
If I recall correctly someone sent me a picture of Paul and Steve
Together
It looks like an album cover
Come on the show
Steve
Said bunch of dumb s*** about the Queens
He says most
Who's on
That made me feel so good
Terrible
Is the word terrible
Thank you for indulging a first
A perfect
He comes in a narrative
Obama's going to Bedford
T20 is going to be a mess
Because it's at all
So really all that interesting
Wow Alex has Steve on the line
He reads
An article from prisonplanet.com
Queen
He does it in an insult
British accent
Here's the article Barack Obama's team
Top advisor to Obama are
Rehearsing
Cousin
Selected with extra cheese
Protocol
I know that this isn't a British accent
It's it it's an article on his own website right
Probably Paul
Probably
Maybe Steve
So he's
Reading
The article in a very
2 most likely
It's rude and the Dynamics are weird there's no doubt about a huge I love that you
You were sitting there trying to
His pronunciation
Will you didn't realize
Filter recognizing the moment is the pronunciation of that word is the impression
Adequate
Oh that's a quick with how he launched into the word you could hear him
Depression
Decide
For the first International Style
President
And here's
Chevron
Advisor Secret Service agents of Nevada jobs
Cavalcade
Azusa Buckingham Palace on Wednesday afternoon
I know
There is no
What is real news at all
There is a chance that is why put on The Voice in order
Are where there is no
It really all he's saying is like
Obama is due diligence
And then he's going to meet with the
Gloria
Actually
Hey Steve
I told you that now
Cowboy hat
Elmer Fudd cartoon
Get off my land boy
Do you do you do got to have some fun
Again
Appropriate that he was playing Wipeout
I got they got that's the most in
Consulting
Really
Child
I think we've heard on those yet that like
They don't like him
Faucet does not like Alex no reply
I can't do that right now
Yeah
Pretty great
Steve comes in to do their little
Paul Joseph Watson
Basically says the exact same thing
More or less his argument is that there's going to be protest
The G20
But the protests are actually the globalist
Secretly controlling
Black Bloc groups
And these are anarchists and these people in order to invalidate
Of the globalist
Some stuff like that
Tortured
It is
But the only clip that I have
Is Paul Joseph Watson
My favorite catch
Sonic coming from the very thought that saying is going to be a summer of Rage
The summer
So I'm not going to cut out everytime I forgot
I mean to
Alex
The Great British Empire
He has white nationalist perspectives on the relief White
Certainly Marty's got multiple limericks
Bob Marley
And Alex wants to
Which is cool
Which is great
Play just called Marty
He's also a medium
He wanted to
Would you like to read it
Or would you like me to read
Alex
Thought
Free and clear
So excited
Cracked a beer
With a limerick attack
And Alex for once felt
That's better than anything
Documents
I think so
I don't I don't like limericks
What type of power is absolutely
Anyway
Andover 2009 Adventures
Super interesting stuff
Interesting developments
I don't know what they stigma land bariatric
What comes up
Oh also yes I looked into it this film it
He keeps talking about
It has to be fall of the Republic
Documentaries
It is
Torturous
Two-and-a-half hour plus runtime
He said he's going to put it out on the 4th of July
He.
It doesn't come out until later in the year
Because you terrible at editing apparel
Think I now have to watch that
I want to see the tents
I want to see if they got the sky is Winnebago
Hey I could see
Maybe you should just Google is there a Winnebago in this
Results
Realty
I'm a watch
Navigate to make it taller
Until we come back with our next episode
We have a website for y'all to check out
It's knowledge
Underscore fight
Over there
You could just find a podcast
You know what Marty Schechter
Right fine he's never killed
Wait maybe you guys
Are you googling whether or not she has killed somebody I have Googled it he hasn't
British actor never killed anybody
Alex Jones
Alex