Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work
Dan
What movie
Represent
This season
The fall
The winter
Winter's Bone
Is going to stay the family man
I think I text you around Christmas
Harlots wardrobe
Winter Queen
Who are what
Pejorative term for ladies
I don't know all that much about Alex Jones
That is correct folks who like to know
Is a fractional IPA which we learned is not a right before the show
Wacky Wednesday
Before we do
And are supporting the show
This person I'm positive I'm going to mispronounce
Kristaps
Thank you for you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Name of Chris
Basketball player 4
I apologize for my preemptive apology
You are now a policy walk
I'm a policy wonk Emilee
Oh I like the spelling of Emily
I'm a policy wonk
Fiona
Fiona my favorite adventure
Also my favorite
Who's equivalent of you boo in May
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket
If you are out there listening you would like sports
We would appreciate it very much
So Jordan
We got we got a weird Wacky Wednesday thing going this month
I don't know any hammers actually not trying to lull you into a false sense of YouTube
You know we've gone over Reverend Manning
We went over these Starchild who made good on her her life
We went over Coach Dave last week and I was at
Wildly weird episode
Here's the deal when I was going over Coach Dave
I found a lot more that I wanted to talk about it would end up being a 4-Hour episode
And I don't feel like I want to move on from Wacky Wednesday until I get this out
So today we are revisiting coach days.in Myers
Back to the well so quickly on someone who is in new entry into our
On our group on Facebook, tell your mother brilliant there was a pole that was put up
Support for let's talk more about Dave daubenmire
Dictator level is like 99%
Yeah the horrible white nationalism
Is a sex offender
Mike's
That I had that I wanted to talk about it actually works really well to have it be
Be two separate episodes
Is
In
The election
Hunting show
That we are very familiar with
Say David Mayer hair
Thursday evening
Just have a great day
Opportunity
Talk to Larry Nichols
Normally no exclusive
How to get ahold of that guy
But I laughed my ass off what do you like
He gives out his phone number on other shows we just called him out of the blue
Weird it is not Nick
Goosebumps
Coach Larry Nichols on for an interview
The lead-up to the election
Soften hard
That doesn't come out
Where is real
MS
I'm going to hear from
Tubes coming out of this
Just about everything to
Can be coming out up so just out of
Of decency in a privacy
We still are just going to become a bill with this
Where's the hydraulic 280
We going to hang out soon
Giessen
We're not going to do that today
Was Larry Nichols
Very exciting
For Larry
He's not going to have him up on baby when he says
Exclusive inner me interview he just means
I'm the only one doing this interview with him I do my 15 random as guys on Google Hangouts yelling
Larry Nichols to make it easier to listen to for sure
Thrilled he thinks this is a get
This is like I have a big guests on my hand
Larry fucken
I love I love that I love the idea that anyone hero worships him
It just means I don't know anything
Like they haven't looked into his history the
Defected after he sued the clintons
Back in the 90s
And accused Clinton of having affairs with a bunch of women all the women were interviewed
Absolutely not
Then the star tabloid picked up the the story was like
Look
I don't want to be able I don't want it I'm sorry
And then a little bit after that
Is hucksters scams
It's very clear
And his motivations for Hayden
Things are really Clear Lake because Bill Clinton fired him from the Arkansas development Finance
Ioffice for making 142 collect calls
Time to the contras in Nicaragua
They got pissed off
Bill Clinton
I meant just tracing
Timeline through everything is like Alright you're someone who just committed
Broadcaster
Fraud
Actual direct quote after the story came out in the star tabloid
This is because
Because things that Larry put out into the world
Did everyone in Arkansas signor.
Cuz they just new like this is nonsense
But what became the presumptive Democratic presidential candidate
The star was like oh here's a juicy story they started
The media is made a circus out of this thing
When is Star article first came out several women called
If I was willing to pay them to say they had an affair with Bill Clinton
This is crazy
1 London newspapers offering half a million dollars for a story
To even he's coming out being like
This is bulshit a lot of horses that I accidentally opened up
Without cons
Consequences and you guys are going to make it till
Continually
There's
Perfectly clear that he set out to destroy Bill Clinton and I got away from him
That was a good game for the clintons on a radio show
Like I was on pills
Disguise an a******
Also we should say he's the saddest SEC I've ever
How is Young and I was cool and I was smart that when I work
The clintons
Build assist
Now you wrote Jingle
This
Cabal system
Original writer
Welts on other shows
Like Alex's
Is it referring to hears this mob
Cabal system
It's the way you described it elsewhere is the idea of the broken coalition
The idea of going after
All Christians are a majority of Voters in a state
Is probably not the best strategy but if you embrace
Disenfranchised
They add up to a large
So that is the
The evil
Then he says he worked on with Clinton's intervista
Back then
Now he's on Coach Davis showed he's calling
Cabal system
Listening to minorities system nearly got Stacey Abrams elected until it
It was stolen
Sure
Help build it
Design poster
And then here I am today
Sienna
That's just
The lights my grandchildren are going to have in years
Stop it
Got2b
The one
You know nobody's big the Clipper system
Cuz you know that nobody
Powhatan clothes
Slippery
Nothing it was all
Monday Destin
And a Comedown
Just barely hanging on
I'm trying
You sad pile of s***
This is
Cuz I'm
Do appreciate
This differing level of
A****** as opposed to our usual
Fake alpha male dominate everyday has the Danny Glover
Coming out of retirement for
One last saving the f****** Union
Fake crutches
Ziza is affecting his illness
I'm talking about
McDonald's
I'm just
A principal
Because I know their system I built it
My work
So I have
Good God
What
This is awesome
Because you're right it is such a difference layer for a pathetic liar
Blessed even though he like I got him impeached and stuff like that
Kind of self
You know it is it is interesting and I enjoy it a little bit
But it's also like he's really Hamming up
Do you like I'm going to die soon
I have been brought low even talkin about there like I was
When I was younger
I brought to be humble
What is doing this show is because that's so in line with the Christian ethos like this
Idea of the mighty being brought low and Ed
The Saul on the way to Tarsus kind of moment
Yourself do something like
Especially mainstream Christians nowadays
Deserve
Can't get enough of that s***
That story is
While he was working with
Clinton
He was actually
Gary Nick
And then he had it coming to Jesus
That's the softball situation all over you might have smell
I've not been able to quite true
But I do think he has a couple of false
What was the
Benjamin Franklin Gold fake grandma
There was a
Something Snodgrass
Coach
But if you listen
Carefully to the audio
You can tell that Larry is distracted by something else that's going on in his
Safe to say that some of these guys go there with the best
Do they not
Corrupted
What preceded this immediately is Larry telling a story about
And feel like that so
Question all the stupid
Become corrupted by the
Exactly by me I did it
I'm the reason Washington is alive
Everybody else so
In-N-Out
Detroit
Celebrities we look at it right now
We looking all the stuff
Coming out
Are they really
Are they going through my house
Are they really going to
Countdown Larry
He's elected or not
Sorry I take my dog house
That's that's great
Exclusive interview
Professional
It's
Pretty pretty awesome
Respectful
Yeah yeah
It was justified
What is a turret liar
Belizean get up to take his dog out noisily on our show
Appreciate that
Thanks Larry there's one good thing about
So what points because he's here it right before the election
Isn't that the fraud is going to happen
He wants you to do is pray
So you going to a place you need
They don't give you favor
A big scene
Man
I think people should have done that North Carolina this year I suppose
Maybe the advice.
Good bye week has other advice
But he wants to give
That is
Deeply deeply problematic
He's advocating for
Probably cry
Multiple times
Records of Peep
Died that records
Paperwork to register
What we used to do and I will describe it
From
First-hand experience
They go in
Coming in the bus leaves
School Bus
Literally the best company
Conway
Anna
When we get school buses with go
2 Northeast
Octavarium
Black part of the steak
4 people
And we will take them just like they're going to do this time
Take them to the inner city Precinct
City creatures now
Not going to your Precinct coach out and rules wherever
They're going to Ender City
Appreciate
Demonstrate
Necessarily
What are you talkin about
Discharge
Of all the
Finna all this water frog.
Within
These are
I feel like all he said right there is we were helping people
Real world version of
Conspiracies about
Larry actually later says it like
It off with a bus
Cars
Like
Three people to the polls
Like that only makes sense
You really believe in voting integrity and you're carpooling
That's not
That's going to
Be cost-prohibitive
You would have to have
Fleets of cars out there it would have to be
Uberpool
Conspiracy in order to make a dent
In most of the places where would matter this is crazy nonsense
Unless demonize the idea
And what he's doing is trying to present the idea that you are coach
Not your white Enclave in Ohio
It's happening in these black
Another reason that I said that I think what he's talking about his criminal is because
This part of it was the descriptive part
He's describing what you think the problem is
And now here's his solution
Now you take
Nationwide
Baltimore
Philadelphia
Look at all these
Huge cities
Chupacabra
Vocelli's
More than in the rural areas
How do you catch
We need veterans group
Call Dino
No
Cuz I don't recommend
Anybody going back
Train Intercity
I really don't understand that at all
I got some guests
All right now
Deja
They can go into the inner city Precinct
Which day
Let's say
Can people
Going there with 10 people
Let me just watch
They don't hide it
You seem going incoming outgoing in coming out
When you see it
Take a picture of it
When did you take a picture of it
Call the police
Tell the police what you just witnessed
They won't come
Take picture anyway
Can you let me know on my website
Larry Nichols. Info
We got a place right there coach
People
Experience
December 28th how's it going
Of concrete voter fraud
His plan doesn't even
Does if you consider it to be voter intimidation
Bright
I just went for advocating for a bunch of people intimidating
Interesting polls
I think is going to go
But that doesn't
It's going to be people who hear this message of
Go alone to an inner-city black you'll probably get assaulted and maybe murdered so you go
You're going to be thinking it's the jungle
Like coach Pizza Harlem
Your wife
You are in
Danger
So you going with your team
Your team
Are you going there
You're not going to be observing
What you're going to be doing is being skeptical of everybody who's there
North white people look the same
If you end up doing
Is intimidating people away from the pole
I mean
No I mean more like for him
To say that plan makes
That's because he wants people to go to Interstate
In order to intimidate voters
Committed voter fraud
We Are One
What cities are Democrat
Because we won
We're we all realize that we're in it together we're sitting
I would take
Intercity people
In order to make sure that we win those District
You misunderstand
He's advocating a position of how the right
Can take back the other City
If you're working with Larry
Against
Larry's working to stop me right right right
Committed voter fraud to win the election
Sprite
Because those places you can Ram the totals up really high because people like Larry and Coach are too afraid to come
Come around and find the clear evidence but that doesn't make sense
And
Strategy
Being advocated for
To intimidate people away from
Practicing their right to vote is where Larry is coming from
You can dress it up in all sorts of like
I know.
These drinks
I know the only way to stop those tricks
Hanging around for no reason at the polls harassing people
Just being a nuisance
That's the only answer this
Without pickle that we find ourselves in
Disenfranchised
Coming in and out of the
And then going in and out of the poles
Picture of that
You have to take a video of that otherwise you're
Just taking pictures of people walking out of the polls
Right
It would be tough
And then probably why he hasn't gotten to the bottom of this mystery this one
Episode we're good but sour in people clamoring I don't
Lucy is out there
Screaming Into The Ether call Larry Nichols Larry Nichols and he is
Right now just not want to talk to him he's experiencing
Sickness problem
As we as we speak right now
I'm sorry
Easier time and why
Really into the idea
Talking to him
Cuz we're talking about him right now recording
4:30 in the afternoon
Where's General a lot of time will be recording
Evening
Grandpa Nichols got to be in bed I assume
I feel bad
I was just
I feel like the only problem that we had was
Because I didn't know we were talking about Larry Nichols today
I don't know what we're going to do
It would have been great if we could call them like
Yesterday or 2 days ago
And seeing if you wanted to come over
But it was a spur-of-the-moment Larry Nichols
Real talk
I predict he won't talk to us again we'll try a long time
We brought up that he was trying to Blackmail Congress and Robert Mueller
Superlative
Cuz he was talking about
Find out about
I think he is a garden-variety, you just took advantage of a situation
PennDOT time
Good morning
He never gives up
We're in the weeds here let's get back on track Larry wants to express
Verify
And then coached
Very smelly
Away from your voting machine
Without verification
Nature boat
Which law
U-boat
That's actually good
They can't steal your boat with machine
Wired up
Wherever
Which we know Soros owns a lot of these things and so you know they called conspiracy theory
Terry's Larry butt
Reno in fact it's going on
That's why
While
Bring up story
Find a different billionaire
Going to try to run for president
Trump campaign
Stuck
For a while
Popularizing make it popular
He sucks
I mean I'm for impeachment
You unified focus on one
On one person
Right
Especially if it is somebody who is
A Hungarian
So weird
It's just so consistent
Yeah I know
It's just
Crazy that adjusted
Travels
This
This worm
Worms
Through these different
Community
You're like I'm sure if I listen to tons of her boring political episodes
I'm sure Carrie talks about Soros to 100%
But you got done with Jim Baker's doctor about the road you got Cochise talk about Soros Alex's talk about the road
Larry Nichols 8 Soros
It's weird it seems such a unifying piece of
This fabric
Gettington
Getting to the bottom of where all that comes from is so important
Because when you do you start to understand where the rhetoric that trickles down to all of the
These places
Because it has to come from
From a source
It can't complex I bet coach got that from Allie
He has some sort of primary doesn't get to jump up a level in the trickle-down
He watches Alex's show that's why he
Admires Larry
And that's why you think Soros is behind there's really no other way that coached
Dave Cook
No
Canterbury
When I was growing up in the nineties totally knew about Larry Nichols
I mean it's possible but I think at that point
You'd have to assume you would have made contact with him before you would help you know because
If you knew about him from the actual
Time
It's not like Larry shied away from the spotlight
It's not like he's hard to get in touch with no actually
Interesting Lee in fact
Still the same
In 1994 he started this like campaign like so in 90 he got fired from the Arkansas
Development
No idea why
Yeah but then
He started to give speeches at Patriot
Community
And The Following comes from a transcript of his feet
I want to tell everyone in Colorado
In Arkansas I'm hated my family is embarrassed
My wife on a given day hates me
But I made a deal with Bill Clinton
In 1994 we're going to meet at High Noon and one of us is getting out of town
Parenthetically parenthetically
At this point Nichols draws a silver-plated semi-automatic handgun from his hip and waves it in the air
Before placing it on the podium
Several voices from the audience or her cheering shoot the bastard
Wow
So that was what he was up to in 94 he was out making the rounds and all these
These places
So the concept that coach would have been aware of him from wouldn't like there's no way that he would have never talked to him
Tried to get in touch with him
Before 2016
The Abbey absolutely no sense
From Alex my point in that is there
These worlds that all have Soros as the big Boogie
8 hamster
It has to come
From somewhere
This flowchart interesting things about Coach bring it up
Is it a gives us like a layer below out
Do you have the influence that Alex has wielded on the world being expressed by coach
Zip code
Step above that Al
You understand where Alex gets it all from
It helped it starts to help where
All the other
People got it
Right
Fusion I have
Is that
Spread
Pretty much the same way that
Your garden
Variety internet
You know there's nothing
Speakers
Bill O'Reilly then just stop cuz didn't work out all that well for me
Like thesaurus attempt had been made
Before
It didn't I didn't work the same way as an internet meme
Or maybe you did but it would be like a meme that someone tried to launch and then it didn't work so they waited a few years and try to
Maybe I've never I don't know of any memes that work that way
But it's
It is possible
It's like a virus becoming resistant
I'd say it's it's
Won't go away
Confuses me with like Bill actually cheating
Reinforcing the lies
That
People still believe they'll kill
Vince Foster
Sure
Enough
There are enough.
True sayings
If you deprive them of Conte
About sources life
That leads you to believe that you can
Evil man
The people's if they just don't
Try and do the time put in the work
Figure out what's truth and what's fiction
There's enough
Semblances of reality behind the idea
Oh hey
Hungry
Does want him out
Yeah the reason for that is because hungry is by
He's a democratizing
Force
And that is a threat to an authoritarian leader
Ergo
They want him out
Right and there are enough
Authoritarian leaders
Working and cons
With enough
Dedicated propagate
Panda group
Sprite
Reinforce this meme over and over again
So yeah I can we could force memes
Is to stick around as opposed
Disappear or
Is if we hired never-ending resend
I suppose
Who knows
So it was next clip obviously coaches
Getting a lot of this
From Alec
Even further.
Play one of the most salacious things
Come out here in the last few days
The governmental
An undercover government authorized
Singing this
Other places like that
Recent stuff came about because of
Anthony
Weiner in the
India investigation by the NYPD yada yada yada 2016
Deep down in the middle
This thing is the idea of this Lolita Express we know
We know build
Stations
Hillary
Somehow involved
Jessica pedophile
Perspective
Is this
Is this something
Oh yeah
Yeah chief
Nine-year-old
Good
Larry
I do like Larry's commitment to letting you say whatever
Conspiratorial dumb s*** you want to say and then in Spanish
Pusherman
You keep on it
I will tell you loving it
There's a really interesting point where Larry refutes a conspiracy about the clintons coming up later
Almost blue
Positive
Pick up the world absolutely Alex Jones and Rodger Stone have perpetuated
So hard it's crazy but a little bit
Before that
So he said Hillary was part of the pedophilia uptown
Explain all this stuff it doesn't take into account that Donald
Good friends Jeffrey Epstein
Play we don't need to think about the fact that Donald Trump also
Commented
Whatever you talk about that for a little bit and then Larry tells his story
Trademark story
About how
Hillary would go to Which churches
I love the witch
Which
But
Almost exactly the same as he's told it
In the past
Before so I felt like it was
Is it worth
Pause rehearing until someone else the same story
So just know this clip starts right after you talking about
Love witch
Which
Is it located
Church on Sunday
Methodist Church
I want to set up a camera
We don't do just an impromptu just look like it accidentally happened to coming out of the Methodist Church
I want you to talk about your faith in Jesus except
She turned away from me
Remember like it was yesterday I told stories many times I know people that hear me very much
Probably get tired of it but it's that significance
Turn your head to the left
You said you know I can't do that
What is that mean
Spiritual man
I am
Okay alright story
Stage name where you notes
Go to church
The news crews are you talk about love
Busy
In that conversation clearly making up
The two of them both know that she's a witch
All the information is what
She knows that she knows she knows that he knows everything
I know you're a good PR here
Big sheep and ambitious driven politician eventually become president
Who used to be the president in the world
Creating a caliphate in America provisional
Nascent stage
Politician
Who needs all the good press you can get
Hurt hurt hurt Friday
And he's like
I'll tell you what what you need to do is
Hey very manufactured that clearly duplicitous
Speech about your faith that all politicians
Do
Satan's working so hard
Cheetah run the world is
The Antichrist
Ulta
Kaufman
The brakes
I don't have the
The f****** time to go through every single speech Hillary Clinton has ever made
But I'm positive.
Positive never seen her to church
Yeah sure I have
Fake news
Solaris
What is this
And here's a little bit of analysis of what that could mean
I first met her she was killed
At all cherry hair on underarm
Flip flops
Ygritte
Mission Ridge Pharmacy Northeast Arkansas
Next Seattle
Chain like a dog tag chain in there was a card on it
Absolutely not
Complete bulshit
Hillary Clinton
Leader of the young Republicans
Goldwater ghoul
111 meaning
School
Shows up hairy armpits
Burlap sack
ATS official meeting with financiers and all these respectable people with a f****** chain around her neck
Member of the Communist Party
You gotta believe
Gofucker
Yeah I'm just
Yep
Don't necessarily
Not believe that Hillary might have had some communist leanings when she was in college
Do stuff like that
I don't think that matters
I thought you was
She was a Goldwater gal when she was younger than she always likes to talk about Goldwater Republic
I would say she would have to have been in her
Early 20s
Commit30
Jumping into the let's go all natural French
Style
Groovy
The possibility
That she presented a certain way and had a certain ideology that might not have matched
What Larry is selling here
I'm not willing to believe it anyway
If I have to
Then the only thing I can
Is it Hillary Clinton
When she was younger and Larry Nichols New her
Was
Fiercest troll of all time
Like she was going to this meeting with financiers with the tag that says member of the Communist party like just try
Trying to f*** with them or something
Like that's what I have and I don't believe that
A money off of
Speeches to these
Assholes
Forever black
Tulare convince
Answer to shave those damn
So yeah I don't believe I don't believe
I truly don't believe Hilary
Has ever
Pictures of a bill with a huge
You're not even
Brooklyn Museum
Yeah but he's
These bills
William
Hillary's
Is Hillary was nine
Years old shoes
Run this
She probably had some Wild Oats in her life she's still a human
Absolutely not wearing
Card-carrying member of the Communist Party to a f******
Business blunch how big is this
4 years after
Even when we got her cleaned up
Gallery
It's a smell
Rotten Manor rotten
I told her and even today
Recent
Maybe come three months ago people that went to one of her
No rallies were she talking and ended up
Close to
No nothing and what I'm telling you
It's her
And what is that
You know I have my
Well
Am I
Demon possessed
Talk about that
Give off an odor
Attracted
Here is just
Audible
It's just
Crazy nonsense
So sure of himself and Broad
Moody Christian
Mine said who knows what show is
Courtney's trying to appeal to that again
I don't know what
He's trying to get coach to save a demon thing
So he doesn't have to
Anyway
This next clip
Larry Nichols said something about the
That I find
Unaccepted
And not because he's trying to malign the clintons or anything like that but just because
This is one of the stupidest
I've ever heard of my life
And it betrays
Then he's just making s*** up
Cuz there's no way that either of them said the thing
But he's going to report that they said immunized
Amanda green
Hillary Clinton smells bad because she's a demon
Is not one of the
She smells bad
The demon talk about all the
That's sort of just like blase
Interesting
So here we go
You Know lyrics
So bad I want to hear this
All right.
Just running while going crazy. Hillary
Ravenous crazy
Driving Miss Crazy
And look at him now.
Don't tell me over and over and over
We will never get a divorce
That way we can never be forced to testify
My goodness
Well that's the truth
That's the truth
House of both of them told you that
I'll talk to you about this
The rule that holds the protest against each other
Or spousal
Privilege
Piece of puritanical American history this rule was established based on any guidelines
Because quote the sanctity of marriage
Be fostered as a matter of social policy
It's houses don't have to fight women aren't allowed to test
Testify against their not not anymore
Crime against spouse
That privilege is gone
Right version of it was
Depends on marital Harmony
So we should make spouses with each other
Rose
Thanks
Exactly
Regardless of the reason it was established
Things that are communicated between couples are generally seen by the laws being intrinsically confidential
Exhaust are considered privileged information
This rule doesn't apply to anything that was said quote in the presence of or likely to be overheard by third-party
Hillary Clinton cooked up this conspiracy that they're putting forth
Hot themselves
Most of the relevant information is not confident
Is a third party who they're plotting with
Also this is stupid
The rules spousal privilege does apply to federal crimes but almost every state
Colorado does not allow it
For cases involving first-degree second-degree or third-degree felony
Sew-ins
Possibly compelled to
Contempt
Were you not
Also Larry is even stupider than its
Again this is from
In 1983 the seventh circuit held that privilege cannot be claimed by a witness who's Legend
The crime
With which his or her spouse is charged
And about which the witnesses
To testify
There's a big exemption to the rule of marital privilege that is known as the crime-fraud
Which holds the quote the marital testimony rule does not apply
Went to our spouses Ark
Conspiring in a future or ongoing crime
Or the other may be compelled to testify in order to protect
The safety of the public
I would say that if anything Larry Nichols the saying is true
Then the clintons most certainly are conspiring in a future or ongoing crime and dust their claim of marital privilege is
The world might be considered a crime
So that we can testify
Each other even though of course you have proven that we are
Trying to run
Tired very idea of a
What are you saying is b*******
It's such nonsense
Like the idea that they stay together so they can't be
Be compelled to testify against each other
When the law is very clear that if you're conspiring
Together
You can
I suspected Larry just recently been arrested development that's where he's coming up with this dump
Central point of the plot of Arrested Development
Hillary Clinton has a degree from Yale law school and was published in the Harvard Law review
Bill Clinton has a degree from Yale law school and studied at Oxford as a Rhodes Scholar
Larry Nichols got fired from advertising job for making collect calls to the contras in Nicaragua
I can't confirm that Larry Nichols even went to college
Before getting fired by the Arkansas development Finance Authority for baby 642 calls
I'll be half of the f****** contra
My point is that I'm going to trust an understanding of the law
I'm going to err on the side of the clintons knowing what the law is
This possible high school graduate who wrote shingles and then got fired for being involved in a rom-com
So sneaky
Larry Nichols
Siri is
Sure he
That the clintons have one of the more fascinating relationship
That I in
In recent hiss
Has nothing to do with
Not being able
Probably be a real interesting
Story to tell here
Years down the line
Hillary was
Ostensibly going to
To be president
2 years
Definition
She was going to be present
Popular vote
Sort of like real in-depth
Understanding of
What's a
I'm sorry but there's no way we're going to get that for
Years Hobson
Who's going to get Larry Nichols and bullshitted
The answer
Who's going to get Larry Nichols
80s
So I told you earlier that Larry Nichols is going to stay
Conspiracy
About the clintons
And this is so
Interesting to me
Because coach
Goat starts basically like a lightning
Kind of thing goes like
Tell me about this
You see a lot of stuff
On the internet
The joke goes around once I saw it on the Internet it's got to be
Do things that the
Really been can
I need the main number one the whole Danny Williams thing
About Danny Williams
I know true
Not true
Addendum
So Danny Williams is the priority
Very
I can't prove it but I'm almost certain to Larry Nichols heads
Roll
Perpetuate
Probably
Creating it or fostering
The show but I can't fly
I have way too many
Eclipse in my archived to go through like fine
Specific
Saying that it is true
Would never say that
Spot
I have a further theory about
And it's not about Larry saying
Hey this one isn't true as a
Beings of being
Fair
Anything like that
I think
To bolster what he's about to say
Okay
Larry
Hertzler number you're seeing all over the internet
The Webb Hubbell
Who is Chelsea's dad
That is true I'm the one that put that out
That is true
That is true 100%
So there's a conspiracy that goes around that Webster Hubbell
Help someone in the Clinton orbit
He is actually Chelsea's
Dad
Hillary
I don't care
It doesn't mean anything to me I don't think it has any bearing on
I need to get matters
You shooting down the Danny Williams
And saying that yes Webster Hubbell Chelsea
Please Dad
Because
The bigger point that he wants to make
Is it bill is in
The further point
I was sitting around with Bill and I'm asking him hey man why you banging all these chicks aren't you worried they're going to get pregnant
Now shoot
Create this like
Diminishing of Bills mascot
Fight takeaways reproductive capability
2 oz of that doesn't matter
Put in that work
Yeah but
At the same time
I don't necessarily
Think that is
Yes yes that is important for
Taking down his mask
For some
Whatever
I also think that's
Probably the only way for so many of these people too
Create this reasonable X
Expectation of
Bill Clinton
Everyone
And yet has
So the only explanation is
What appears to be reasonable
Visa Vie Larry saying the Danny Williams
It's not reasonable because it is just a ball through
The idea that built
Make, right
What
You can't we
I feel like it's perfectly describes which
Thank you
I've never heard that before
I like ice cream
Mccleary's putting out there like eight years were shootings at in a
Conservative
Emasculate
Demasculate
Yes but
He does refute another Point here
It is a huge
Problem
Did this next clip
What Larry Nichols says
Is it
Direct contradiction of Alex Jones's worldview
Entirely
Learned about 5 minutes left
Is there a shadow governor
About that people make fun of and say all you're a conspiracy theorist YouTube
Tinfoil hat all that kind of stuff
Are there Men Behind the
Literally pulling out
No
There are men dying
Oh yeah well yeah that's
Not since mister
Stevens Brothers
Dad
No one
Has ever been
Uncontrollability
Call Shelly will not allow it she has too much power
Well of course
Because they only world that he actually knows anything about his back in Arkansas
Simply Hired
Facilitated his
Super secret agent career by the Sivan
I think it's entirely possible I'm not saying
Case but I think it's possible that
Jacket with Stevens as super rich
Businessman
Arkansas
Might have had some dirty dealing
If possible
Almost
Larry Nichols to be
Sort of man on the ground
In some capacity
Making making and funneling these phone calls in order
To facilitate communication between Nicaragua US Representative
But that's entirely possible
From that standpoint
I do see like Larry having this image of
Mafia activity
I in
In Arkansas that is only surrounding jacket with Steven
Because those are the only contact those are the only firm reference if he had
Which would make sense
What
Hillary and Bill get outside of that world
That doesn't know anything about what's going on with it
So of course
I had a big player
They are now
Dave
Lack of imagination the one thing
The one concrete
Things that I have learned
From this
Anytime
Two brothers are rich
Together
Is
Going to no good
Stevens Brothers how many more Brothers do we have absolute
Tegan and Sara however
Sure
Look I don't know
I don't know I don't know how to I don't know how to slice this other than to say like
It's really f***** up that Larry is coming on the show and saying there's no Shadow government nothing
That implies that there's no globalists
Like all of this stuff
All of the idea of Alex's nefarious spiderweb of weirdos
Isn't true
Like Larry doesn't believe that s*** that Alex says on his show
He thinks that there is nobody above the Clinton
For Obama he had other people above him
Maybe I don't know he doesn't say that but maybe
But not I would have
II
Do appreciate Coach Dave
Treating
The single most important
Question I think that you can imagine which
Is there a shadow government
As like
We got a few minutes left let's toss this in their is their Shadow government
No alright we're moving
Everybody know alright we're going to
Celebrities at this point
He's told his backstory
About the ark
Consolidate
Is that the Hillary is a witch
Smells weird
He's lied about the idea of spousal privilege
Stop by these just dumb he doesn't even know
He's lying about Bill and Hillary still married
At the end of the episode
He said something
Real interest
No I wish you would have me back on tomorrow
Give me one hour
Tell you
America
2017 under Hillary
I assure you
It will scare you to your knees
Grateful be my opinion
But I will substantiate in and supported
Lebanon
EFax
Wow thank you
Not true
Think about
Your audience
Needs
Really think long and hard
About what America is going to become in the next 3 years
A disaster
How do I know about it
You know how it works
Ego
I wish you
If it would be okay for me to ask
They would help me
Play Tiny desk
I don't don't do it if it's going to make people not believe Larry Nichols.
Larry Nick
Schools.in Frozen where they go Larry
Well then go there if they will use a credit card but if they want help
PayPal
Please just go to Nichols
Why
AOL.
That is a re-run aol.com
That is pretty funny
What's fun about that most to me I believe
Is it is a classic Jones
Super Jojo
Have me back on tomorrow and I'll tell you all of this
Future information because I know I know what's going to happen when Hillary ends up
I'm going to tell you this it's going to blow your mind and bring you to your knees
Can I ask
For money
By no means
And I won't
Revealed
If you'll have me back on tomorrow I'll tell you all this great information
Now the possibility is that like
Cotrip
Tomorrow
Lingering
That only leads them to search at Larrymore
Does he have Larry
You better use on the next day
He doesn't actually explain what's going to happen in 2017 and Hillary's charge
Maiden
He says the exact same thing
Here is him talking again about how you need to protect yourself
Voter fraud
You say I do not recommend
Coach
You maybe you and
I don't recommend job going
Track monitor
You could get hurt
Remember last time in Philadelphia
New Black Panthers
Shout
Organization
Motorcycle
Motorcycle games
You can go to these
With say
8910 guy
Adjust watch what app
And when you see it
Reported to the
Play Coldplay
Call the police
That's what you got to do
And that will stop
A goodly portion of it will not stop all of it coach
Just want
Will scare Samoyed
That's the worst way
Yeah that's bad
The Jordan
We're an audio podcast
It's it's difficult
For you to pick up on why I care
To talk about the second appearance at all
But it comes back to what I told you to remember
That was
What coach said
The first
Larry Nichols is sickle
You have these tubes
That's why I do respect for him
We're only going audio
How many kids does he have
They're really trying to play up how stickler
And all of it
Video in the second episode
They go so far as to say is going to be dead soon
Neo camping
What I don't know what the deal is about is real condition
He very well may have cancer or said they've contacted his wife and she said
I don't know who knows I don't give a s***
It's not a big deal for me really because his whole life is a series of fraudulent scam
Scamming people into giving him money because he's pretending to be sick it's just another in a long line of fraud
From a 1998 article instalaunch
The aftermath of being fired after he made 642 collect calls for the
Larry quotes
Theft by deception charges in several Arkansas County
He avoided prosecution by promising to either Maycrest to make restitution
The later filed for bankruptcy in was never never had to pay
Frauded by promising to pay them back and
Didn't
Because you filed for bankruptcy
Is a lifelong f****** con man
Either way the only thing I want to talk about in terms of this
That first interview coach doesn't want to put Larry on screen
Protect his dignity
As he's so sick
I'm second episode he does show Larry on video and what you see is a con man trying to make himself look very
What am I getting at
Well
He has tubes going into his nose
An oxen
Machine to help him breathe
He can't even breathe Jordan
He's just this hero out here trying to
He's overdue asbestos
You can't even is horrible sickness to get the word out about the clintons
City black
Congress
No.
But during the show which is only an hour long by the way
Larry light up a cigarette and smokes it
With no concern for the fact that his oxygen tubes in his nose away from his face
This is so severely f***** up according to the National Institutes of Health
Most patients on home oxygen use nasal cannula
Nasal Candlelight tubing
Polyvinyl chloride products
Which emits an intense Flame
Possibly owing to the release of Highly flammable vinyl chloride gas the prongs of Canela
Are intended to direct a previous study showed however that is significant amount of oxygen
It's been a constantly leaks out of her face
Environment facilitates
Ignition and combustion of the material
Smoking using an oxygen machine is super super dangerous your face
Highly combustible gas and waving a flame really close to that cat
The only conclusion this Behavior are they either help or well-being
To quote a house fire over these fake news onus entirely
These are fake oxygen tubes that are coming out of his nose
Is it hot bulshit he's straight-up smoking a cigarette in the middle of his living room while he's out.
It's crazy
You are writing things out chemically
What does
The chemical symbol for
Lorazepam
Merrifield very like
If you if
Believe me
But like if you have any curiosity about this at all
Look it up
Like look up
The cases the very frequent incidents of people
Who are on oxygen machines
What is it blows up
And it blows up and burned most of their face
You can find pictures of it
It's crazy
It was crazy to me is how specific the burns are generally to
They are the Elves leave the pattern of the tubing
Cub Cadet
So specific
Have you ever seen those because
All of the patterns
Are shaped
Like a little like almost like a little
Paper
That says call Larry
But he's not going to cuz it's
Fake tubes that was two years ago
Right and we just called him
Recording of it or anything like that but yet we called him
Jordan talk to him
He sounds exactly the f***
Contacting his wife and talk
About like
He doesn't have cancer
Black Legion
His throat of the situation that causes
Him to speak like that and he's using
The perception of
Like chronic illness
In order to
No I like it when we talk to
Talk right now as
I don't want to talk
Look for an hour right
Because
Throat hurts or whatever it is I were him I would want to talk to us
I would put that off
I don't think so
Is actually the wolf
Like you didn't try and pull that add pivot on us
Nobody
Back on the show
No
So my point in this whole thing is that if you actually watch the videos of the
I never bring it up in and talk like
Coach Diaz on Skype
Why are you smoking
You're on oxygen story about how you you have
Lung cancer
And you don't want to go to the VA because you don't trust them
This is bulshit
Got the Lord
And that is why we
When you go on
Coach Dave show
Doesn't matter how
How much you smoke
Doesn't matter how much
Did you got in your face
You have the power of the Lord
And you end the Lord is telling you
Good
Is how bad
I would love it if we test that.
Jesus
Oxygen machine
Hooked up with them
Do some like Firebreather
And say that that is not going to
Sponsored by the
No I do not
I think they might call that in
Unethical
I mean this is this is super
What I want really
Crazy
Clearly like not rolling his eyes but clearly there was a look on his way to like
He look like he was
Not happy to talk
Of course not
The things I want to say
I can't say this
But I want
Is effect
I think it was
Cuz I don't think anybody
Like who
Has any idea of
Like what ox
Virginis
Anybody who has doesn't have a death wish
Is going to smoke
While they have a nose tube
Represent himself is like
Smart guy
It's not somebody who's unaware of
The risks of that might pose
It's a prop
Now I will I will say this
Justin Fair
Just incomplete Fair
He may use a
That may be real and he may have
Turned it off
Hour or two before
That's entirely possible I'm not going to
Use that oxygen
I cuz otherwise
I mean
Freddy put it in as a prop
Exactly exact
Yeah otherwise why would you have it
Unless you were like
Committed to the
Scam in the in the picture sight you don't see that it's
Connected
He does need to use oxygen
Because this is what it's really about
How long is election day
He needs he needs funds to somebody else
Nichols. Info
The rest of the
Breathing device he needs financial help with some people
20 boxes way Larry
Nickel. Info
This is what he's really up to he's just trying to
The colonies dumbfucks
Santa giving him money
10 or 20 by lying about the Clinton
It's interesting cuz it's so much more over here when I look at it in the prison both coaches.
Is it Alex reminder
Announce his audience is so much larger
Delivery probably doesn't
Feel the need to
Make it so over
Like
The first time at the end of the first interview that he did when he was like
Can I ask
Like
Betrothed
Process
Like the Philadelphia
So we see here Larry Nichols
He is a zombie coach
Programming
I bet it's a little bit boring for our taste
Possibly you know like a big picture
More or less the same sorta narratives he says other plays it
Shadow government
Danny Williams
His kid but also
Legend services
He said some things that are kind of out of character but like
Big picture
Kind of a disappointment Larry Nichols is
Like
Coach Dave
The problem with it is
Bring it
Coach Dave is just
Therefore Larry Sparks play too much Larry is the one doing everything in between
F******
Is Brick
The table I don't know if he has cancer let him drive
That's what I was.
In an interview with cigarettes
Degenerative
Blake don't don't let him
Become so boring
The pace of speech whether it's because of an actual illness or his affectations or whatever
Lady just becomes this
Winner
Years of really bad
Listen to a bunch of much more entertaining
He has
Larry
F****** Nichols on his show
42 episodes of because you respect him so much
This weird of
Fetishizing of demonizing the left
Kind of stuff
Cute he sacrifices control of
His own brand Tulare
The moment you said that
So many of our
Don't have confidence that their own products people it's like
If your
Stable
If you're rolling your belly up for
For somebody else
It's a bad show for
Like if you like with Alex
Rolling his belly for Gavin
Like
Whenever she's f****** controlling thing she put in the narrative
Got that
Yeah
Is
Running the game
S*** is going well
Coacht
Burnham Park
Is very Salient I think it's the right point and that is that like
What we really are interested in
In terms of these
These Wednesday character
Is
You have your own
Nothing
Right
When Carrie is is talking to someone and Mark Richards she gets f****** pissed at them
Because it's her show a huge you not disrespect Mark Richards on Project Camelot
What Alex
Alex is an interesting case because like what
John McManus from the Birch Society
Dude showed ass
All over the
The playwright
But Gavin wasn't
Supplicating
Vicky
Threatened to murder people moment I brought Alex into it I knew that that was the wrong
Yeah your address is the wildcard
Like on his own show
But he is his own thing like the stuff that I like to talk about
With these crazy
He's so much like them owning their space
I like that I like him
Get the f*** out of here if you don't agree with my version of secret space program stuff
Get the f*** out
I'd like
Even though I hate everything
I like
Reverend Manning
I mean generally speaking
He's just talkin
Camera by himself
But I still like owning the space
With Wacky Wednesday stuff it's very hard for me to see somebody
Who like
Talk themselves out for
Someone that we know is a charlatan Like Larry Nichols isn't someone that you should bend over backwards
Even if
Coach
Does believe all the stuff Larry believe
Still should be coach
He's not coach
We would never do an episode
Larry Nichols had his own show
I do want to try it
Nichols episode and we tried
Tons of episodes of
Various internet program
Larry's been on them not worth our time or whatever
The combination of of Costa
Would make it
Somehow more appealing
But you're right we had to get to the end in order to really realize it
Larry Nichols
Arkansas coach
When the to come in contact with each other
We Are The Smokers of
Rich environment
That with us going forward
Second coach is a finite
You know I
Bit more in this
Sure but
He's nothing with
Buckle
The folds like a taco when Larry Nichols comes around
Nope nope he thinks he is
Comes to Someone Like Larry neck
Indeed
We'll catch you next time but
We have
Website
Knowledge bad fight.
Underscore
Thousand Oaks Cafe
I have a Groupon there
Oh yeah we're on our way back to then
Articulate better
We appreciate everyone listening so much thank you all.
Look
I'll say this
Batman
Is totally kill the guy
How much people want to argue
Technically probably killing a guy probably if we look at it it's probably
From some
Aggressive beating he gave a guy that caused
Like chronic
Illness
John way worse people sternum head trauma
My all that s***
I would never let that man out there
But I will say that Larry Nichols is a complete f****** coward real
Douche in terms of his own backstory
I don't believe there's any chance that Larry Nichols is ever
Alex Jones
Definitely technically probably
Alexandra Thurston color