Alex
Alex Jones
Jordan
What was the last
Accounting job
Over it
No it was
Cuz I am not in the know what I was thinking that job
How about before that like really quit a job
You know I'm saying
Like I like a real
Blowout kind of quit
Missouri
I worked at a Office Depot
Is going to be great it was a terrible terrible job cuz a lot of involves
Like lifting heavy pallets of paper
15 ft in the air or whatever
Forklift just walking up ladders miserable
The guy who trained me was
This guy who was like really into evangelizing
The most of the time you talk
Me about God
I don't want I don't want any of this I don't want any
There's one person who worked at it was really nice to me
Around my age or a couple years older it's somewhere in that range
We struck up a little bit of a friendship and then
Maybe a weekend to me working there turned out she wanted me to swing with her and her husband
I was
One who wasn't fine I wasn't I wasn't
Coworker and her husband that's if I could go back I might take them up on it
No I was not there for that total again
Evolved into my own sexuality yet
So I am
It's process
So I'm working
Complete assholes
To be at work generally
Like 6 in the
The morning it's
Is a miserable job
I haven't worked there all that long
I one day I just wake up
Around with my roommate Nikki gift
He was also up
You're right
So it's really really important
How do I call in and I realize like
I don't want to go to work
But I also don't want to take her
Responsibility for not wanting to go to work right so I call him and
Can't make it in today my car is not working
Can you get a taxi
Like I don't I don't have any
Cashman's
Get a taxi I'm sorry I just can't make it in
I don't want you to have to pay for me to come into work
Today
Look man I just I feel bad taking her money for a cab is a car right
Not even my personal money it's the offices
Okay then
Can I realize that I had nowhere else to go
So you just go
F*** you
That was the Jesus guy right
No no no
Use not the boss
My championship
I guess maybe you could
Could say I got fired from that job but
I was I was I was thrilled for it to count
I was just
3 realized
You think it's going to be a big deal and then afterwards he was like
Just a weight is lifted right not have that job
In terms of like I lived in Columbia Missouri rent was almost nothing
Then and there were jobs a-plenty
You know it's almost perfect
Do something like that
Got a lot of jobs
Favorite quick story
With me not quitting
Because I didn't understand that I was an adult
Could just go
I don't work here anymore
Lumberyard
Nearly two-and-a-half
And I realized
Two-and-a-half
I hate this every moment of it I don't like being there I don't like the people I don't like anything
And I realized
Recently liked
Cut my elbow in this
Accident
And it was already my surgically repaired
From when I was younger so I was like okay
Alright
I can sell this I can work with this right right and I didn't think it looked bad
So what I did
Was I got it
And I just started for real View
Because I didn't understand I could just quit
I thought I had I came up with the worst
Fake injury
Out of the shell
Nope
I assume if you have to be able to use your elbow
In order to do so
That was my argument for being like hey I'm going to have to take all this time off
And you know what
I just I think you guys should find somebody else for the job that was the way I put
Altruism
But not because I don't want to do
Who's more reliable
He's not going to get her
It's not you it's me
You quitting Zapata
How do I minimize
Journey of quitting
Signed up with podcast
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Psychedelic
You are now a policy wonk
Next
Bobby
I'm a policy wonk
Later
Oh no we were able
To give them the original policy wonk
Alyssa
You are now a technical
And thank you
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomite
Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Like if you're listening up
Going to our website
Gordon apartments in sports
Just like Paul Ryan
Who also quit
He did a lot of quitters
How
Much Wong Curry he did policy while he
What did he say
Which I assume has completely disappeared under his fix
Podcast
From time to time
We got to do a little thing called the spice
Everyone knows
Kind of Cold podcast people need update so
I like spicy food restaurant here in town I've tried the office
Menu for the menu chicken wing fingers
Over at the the Nashville hot place
Come my way
Uncle
Define the like super hot peppers
Here in Chicago
I don't know why we're one of the biggest cities in the country
But yet I cannot find a store that sells
Really hot hot sauces
Peppers
So I'm
Sword
Maybe everybody tells me go to the Indian grocery
I want tells me go to the Asian grocery store
I've tried the ones that I've been able to find and I have been slacking
However
I accidentally stumbled into
Spice Shop
Today
Jordan
I found
Puree
Carolina Reaper sauce
Literally just hear a bunch of
Carolina Reapers and vinegar
Hellboy
Is it hot
It's great
Visit
No no no
Suffer because they're
Great
I really wish that you could try some of it but I know you would never consent to
I can't do it but also now I realized
It is technically like I guess the world's hottest pepper
Now
There's nowhere else to go
No more worlds
I'm fine with it because I think a lot of different peppers have
Flavors
Characters
There's still a lot more take
Explore and all that it's different
Pureed
Fresh
There's still plenty of spicy
Things in my
To go into but I will say
Good bit of a tan Ramen
Earlier
And
In terms of
Like heat level
That's very Siri
Close to like a level level seven or eight at the Thai place
Is a guy wait like
It's
Yeah
It may have been later
On the toilet ghost on the toilet
My point is my phone is very serious
But
It's just an ass but I finally found some
Carolina Reaper sauce
Fine
Prime made me sweat a lot
10 months
Like Alexander the Great
Crying salt
For there are no more worlds
Perhaps
11 minutes
Bulshit
Jobs
But this is a podcast about Alex Jones
Absolute is going over to separate
The 19th
2018 okay
That I wanted to
Do present
We seem to be coming in
Like a weekend wrap-up
Fraught with Peril for Alec
A lot of stuff
Pagani had that Slim
Nahko great
Particular
Very strange
Nothing
I'm not sure what that judge was doing editorializing
I don't know
So I don't know
I don't know what to make
So your Wild Oats on that bench
UCC judges all the sudden come out of nowhere
So that was one piece of the week I thought Alex
Should we really be
Uno into an
Complaining
The reason we're starting on the 8th
18th onto
Is because
On Monday night
Cremation lawsuit against them coming from miles
The soup was about how Rodger Stone kept saying that
Illegal contributions
Hillary Clinton
And was working against
Trump
Steve Bannon
Also Rodger kept accusing clock of having been convicted of financial crimes
In the United States
Rice box Rodger stone for 100 million dollars
Broadstone completely f***** up here so he called clock and asked him to settle the lawsuit which guac graciously
To do
Because he's Rodger Stone though he refused to take
Any
Zangief
You think it was he
Failed to do his own research and improperly relied on former Trump campaign advisors
Nunberg
I'm traveling low-key now what is going on here
Who was the guy who got drunk and went on all those those
Remember that
Remember Sam nunberg
He was that guy who is clearly drunk on CNN in the host was like
I can smell out
Never watched
How much of a f*****-up world we live in now
That should be the kind of thing
That we remember 20 years from now as a f******
On a nationally syndicated
News program about the president and his employees
Recently
It was embarrassing
For everybody in our purpose
The Fall Guy
He reported on
I like about 200
Provided it Rodger poster
Retraction to Infowars Rodger Zone website
Unfortunately
This is how things work
No propaganda
Make outrageous and libelous client
Which cause damage
Then off and they get away with it but even when there's
They pull it all shucks
Meac
And the better Natures of the
The person who sue in Limerick
Roger's going to print a retraction but
The damage has already been done
And no one who heard the original slander will care about the retract be like
All this is so smart this is how he gets out of this guy money
Or it'll just be like
It's a globalist party against him or whatever everything and I'll still be able to
Don't matter
Alex pretend
He'll apologize to everybody who he slandered
None of his fans give a s*** if we have the chance to give advice on anybody who's running
Their next defamation lawsuit I'm sure they will do
Call us
Believe me we will give you a Mason advice
Through the whole process and that will be
Get every
F****** sent out of those guys that you could
Ever possibly get and leave them destitute on the street
Like yeah retraction or whatever I know that that's probably why
Is in the realm of decency
Whatever you think is
They just say that they were wrong
We are fine indecent men
You need a little bit more
Retraction I'm not saying
Send them to The Pourhouse
I love it it's a great starting point
That is that is like the reverse of dr. evil in Austin Powers where he says $1000000
Everybody laughs at
100 million is
Pursuing just some a******
I like it I would say
Instead of a retraction what you have to do
Interview with that purse
Like miles Kwok gets to Infowars
Rodger Stone I don't know
Here's what I would go with
Let's go with a more creative
Punishment
As opposed to
Rogers I would like
All of Rodger Stone suits and he is never allowed to buy another suit again
If I get the hats
Kiwi divided his wardrobe and his Wardrobe from here on out
Is jeans and a t-shirt
His hats might be
Useless to me.
Not important
It is for me
Yeah but you would never fit it
So anyway they broke on Monday night so I thought for sure on Tuesday
Alex is going to
Furious about
Because the way the news covered it
The hill
Huffington Post also
They reported accurately
But what they do is they used
These headlines
Is that lead people to go a little
So they said
That Rodger Stone settles lawsuit has to admit he published fake stories on Infowars
Which technically is true because he was the person who was making these claims
Infowars reported them and they publish them
Absolutely that is strictly true
Horse
People ran with in real life
Admitted he lies all the time on
I thought for sure Alex
Who's going to be like
They're just trying to make me out to be a liar and all this
I'm so surprised
To hear this
At the beginning of the show
As he's running down his headline
Times for the day
Special Report
Rodger Stone
Will Generation Z save us from our Millennials right holders of Watson video
Rochester
Infowars.com
Bitcoin soon worthless
Egg surprise
Pick your top stories about as Camry
I don't
I don't I don't I don't know what that is except like a man trying to distract him
MK Ultra where's then buff
Pedophiles are we still doing pedophiles I guess we're still doing pedophile
I will
He has been surrounded by a lot of f****** con man
And who do Bitcoin scam
He's at a number of people who like you
On the market
Still at like a tenth of a second I'm not sure
Max Keiser is the man who's tried to get him into Bitcoin his head
Like Dave Steam
Fraudsters
Running around
The next big endorsement
The price goes up
I'm holding his credit he has always resist
So when he sang Bitcoin will soon be worthless
I kind of feel good about her saying that
Because it need something
You've never did now
But at the same time every time
I just don't get it I don't think this is good
Like unlike many financial analyst who are like
I don't get why people are doing this understand it as a concept
Tire doesn't fully understand
Before I don't know why you said the restraints on this one
Might might be because of his just
Innate love
And 20-year career as a shill for a guy who so cold
What's hard currency
The next story after that is a study about how fresh vegetables are better than canned vegetables
And then he says
How do you pick a top store
Fresh vegetables holyshit
Wow
I'm amazed makes the cut I'm actually shocked that you are
Surprised by this because my whenever you said like I'm surprised he goes off on this was like
Oh he actually talks about
Because what's not surprising to me is that he was just
Avoiding it entirely without any info
Okay
So then after that Alex moves along to talk about house
Over at Fox News
Top Fox News hosts
And all the way back
But
When Tucker Carlson was brought on he was not a hundred percent behind from
That's why they thought he was a good guy
Whatever
I don't care about this it's really just because his buddy
Judge Andrew Napolitano has been going all over
IFixit Mueller can
Call for the indictment of a sitting president
A few months ago Alex was saying that
And thank God his uncle was thank God this is the case
Napolitano next Supreme Court Judge around
He's going around
You saying that to mullican indict the president cuz he's not the next
That's possible
Ruined
Furious he can't stop like
You think you know your friends that's something still on the show
You talk about Fox News
He's not on Alex's
I thought you were gone
Oh okay
Broadcast
Together that's right
It's that it's fun Alex
Episode of realizing
Another
And the sensible ones
Are starting to be like
The position to be Edwards like
The
Lumos
Take me to go to jail
And has just been successfully forced
To print a retraction
Belief
Possible punishment you can get here's what the punishment
Journalistic diligent
If you're wrong
Post a retraction
You write report
Like you can't
Like when he was
Rodger talk about miles
He never says
Sam nunberg told me I never
Criminal
Right the guy I trust the most
He's going to jail
The guy that I used to trust
He is giving a milquetoast legal argument that makes sense
Brutal stick with Rodger Stone Rider.
He goes to break and he comes back
Weird
Sort of
A little bit of a diatribe
This is the really interesting part that Do Hast Mich
Popular bands out of the last 20 years
Music
Wait music
Weird
PewDiePie
As Final Phase
Speech
I love this
His argument seems to be that
Which
A little bit here
But
The reason people take their Nazis is really interesting
It wasn't it was I thought it was obvious that they weren't Nazis
Deserve discussion
There are groups in past will come out who seemed innocuous and all the metrons I do that
So you have
You have these
You know you end up learning things about bands
What you didn't know about
Music and in celebrity
Entirely is that is the realm of light
Like people coming up with a rumor about a band
Fascinating
I became aware them from the Lost Highway soundtrack
Rammstein has two songs on a soundtrack
And we were not hit
The hits from the soundtrack were the perfect drug by Nine Inch Nails
By Smashing Pumpkins
There's a third but I wasn't
Marilyn Manson song
Remember what it was
Who cares
Duck duck point is like
Alex had to have listened to that soundtrack
Really like that soundtrack
I had that soundtrack when I was a kid
I really like that I by Smashing Pumpkins in the
Drug
I thought those were probably 12
I might have begun 12
If you could
Wait till your did you also see the movie when you were talking I heard on the radio
Never let me watch
I was going to say
That I had
First album I ever bought was Alanis Morissette's Jagged Little Pill
Google language
Generation defining album
Cedarline there was that
Nothing more humiliating than going back to the mall
Turn my Lantus Morissette speedy
Cuz my mom made
Got out of her childhood
Who is taking that CD back
What must have been thinking after he saw it
After he saw you
Jagged Little Pill in album where is like
Everybody loves the great albums
Pull up Hits album
But my demeanor probably
Reset it for me I would assume
People like you type
No idea that America
He plays as a bumper is
Explicitly
America anti-colonialist
Cultural
As a song
Zoe
Stupid actually brings up
Genre of music
In sensational
And so the music is often been in 10
To shock
Plus they make illusion
Stupid jokes about a whole lot
Taboo topic
Disorder Behavior led to strong rebuke
From the right wing
Not the laugh
When the band broke
That doesn't sound right there
Music
Vocal style of speaking
German that is intentionally
Hardness of the German language
It's a beautiful
They're doing that as a stylist
Choice to make their sound more country
Except however he's also
Speech pattern in style is largely
Associated with Nazis
Particularly
Especially for people with a limited awareness
5 tons
Manners of speech
The members of Rammstein grew up in East Germany before the
Their name is a direct reference to the Ramstein airshow disaster of 1988 were 70 people died
And 346 more were seriously injured
At a West German air show at the US Airbase
They're into antagonizing
It's part of their crap
Oh also in 1988 use footage from Eleni Riefenstahl film the video for the song
So that also kind of
That led to a bit of hey guys what are you doing
And if you understand them
More fully
It serves electronic Zantac
It makes sense
There were coming from left
Record label is that
What the f***
I was the criticism
Abusing bunny
So like all of the critiques that hours
What is talking about
Come from
Don't understand
But their music
And I almost
Superman
We're not in the camp
He is trying to put
Like I've always understood to be like a literal
Hey
We looked at German history
We're not fans
And here's the music that we think best represents how we're going to f******
Can fight these
And not end as we can see no not just remnants of fascism but
Very strong undercurrent
Shazam
Add another element of it to do for them
Mystique and
Play outside of Germany
Some be like
From performing
Choreography
Before one of their song
In German
Because it was deemed offensive
Dangerous to children
Cuz they would do things like stimulate anal sex with sex toys on each other
Where is not allowed anywhere near
Probably one of their album covers
From being displayed in German stores and stuff like that
This Aura of
Being
It's stuff like that so you can totally understand their laws are on the side of caution
Anything along those lines
You know you see how a course correction might
Go a little bit too far in the opposite direction
S'mores it like
Anybody who
Critiques of
Rammstein
Back then
Where did the camp at Alex's pretending
And they were very vocal
About
No
Sorry sorry
So can you
We missed it the first time but now that you pointed it out
You make a grapefruit
You're right
We're moving on
You're still Rammstein we're still us
Let's just have a great
Launches into this whole thing about their calling
PewDiePie a Nazi
Do powerfulest
At least doesn't seem to understand the conversation
I am promoting people who have
If he believes
I think it's funny to have
People hold up assignment
Does kill all the Jews
Who knows anyway I don't want to unpack the PewDiePie stuff
What I was talking about I didn't even
It sits around the
It's about Alice
He's using
PewDiePie is a surrogate for his own feet
What
And then talk about another musician
I have
More feeling
1000 people
Trump
City on Coliseum Pike Waco
But because you won't play ball
He loses 15
Million
Dollars
How do you know that
Indirectly
I heard directly from Publications that it's true
How much money are Trump leading musicians losing.com
I haven't I haven't seen that number 11 research
102 summer tour
Nugent the Iowa Speedway in Newton Iowa
What is comprable to any
It's very close to like 2/3 of Busch Stadium
A long way play tunnel Rock clubs in larger cities and
Casinos in places
St.Louis
Literally exactly what you'd expect
Never had a song chart tires and number 30
And that was
Cat-scratch
Fever which came out 41 years ago
In fairness
He did reach number two
Two on the rock chart with little Miss dangerous
But that was 31 years ago
Also
Here's some of the lyrics from Little Miss dangerous hear it
High heels all of our favorite musicians are pedophiles
High-heeled sneakers
Such a dangerous little girls
Paris to me
What makes her dangerous to you little girl's face why would she have a little girl
I don't know
Be a little bit
Is 1981 song jailbait
Well I don't care if you're just 13 you look too good to be true
I just knew that you're probably clean there's one little thing I got to do to you
Another lyric was that
It's alright baby it's quite alright I asked your mama
School one morning
Not like he would pick her up from her mom's house
Encourage her parents
Would sit in the front seat
They would Court
And then she has another lyric in the song quote
Put cuffs on me what about her
They all share her with you about about driving someone to school
I don't
Interesting Lee the next song on his album
It is important and this is everybody can change is most recent song
Which charted I think 120 or so
Was called whoops to Doodle my bad
I wish I was
Does a 2070 rotate deeply disturbing song called Girl Scout cookies
Wish I was making this up
How old is dogs about
Text Leo Celtic of minor
Maybe you're just a pedophile
I like to eat
My Girl Scout cookies I can eat them all night long
When I'm in my bed is a pattern
Never let them Girl Scouts
Never let them go to your head
I also another disturbing lyrics
That coconut just drives me wild I get my cookies fresh from a child
How gross is onion
Looking forward to Trump's inauguration song in 2020 just being Ted Nugent
Sentiments
Nobody likes a fat
Boo
Because that's just not true
Also this album
Bridge Over Troubled Waters
Jesus man
Not realize how he was upon the steaming his music also recorded
Song called
I never really paid much attention to Ted Nugent I saw that cat scratch fever was on like f****** Guitar Hero 1 timing
To listen to Ted
Funny videos
Again
He is a
Buried he's a man who does not go back to the well dad everyone is Amazed by how he continually
Reinvent himself
Is rock and roll
Girl being young it's okay I asked your mama
Gross just super gross
But it's even more grows when you realize that Ted Nugent
Married
I don't like
No no no never ever be a question you asked
Never ever say
I can't remember if he
He married or adopted as if those are two
Equally
A possible either married or adopted an underage girls is the parents couldn't
Complain about it
I can't remember what it is
Gross
Monster is dude
And I do think it's
Really funny
Alex
Dingdong spent so much time
Would you all the time
Trying to find this
Code to prove
But all these Democrats they hate have these secret pedophile Dungeons and stuff like that
And they loved
It's crazy it's been writing songs for
40 years but have you like children
Baby that's the real differ
Prince between the left
The left
We got to come up with codes if we're going to commit these crimes
The right
All I got to do is write song lyrics
And everybody gets it
I don't know man
Everybody's like isn't that great
Metaphors so vividly crazy
It is
I don't understand how you get there
I did not know that there were not just
Now just two
Not yet
Fire career career of I want to f*** a child
Yeah yeah
It Is song
That's why
He was so angry
That's the worst thing that Hillary ever wanted
Ted
From f***************
Sure give me the office
I didn't want to give the impression earlier in the show that Alex
Doesn't talk about
Rodger Stone
I apologize
Houston to Accra
Job of covering it
Surprise
Wall Street Journal
Stone says about
Heard about this Chinese National who was wanted in China
Trump official was inaccurate
Contacts in here
Where they have
That was irresponsible
Millionaire run
Nope
Drop the dollar
Lowe's
Twitter search
A video as well
Well
I understand that some people have gone
Too far with it and they're stupid and they say things
This proves that everything is fake for The Fray
And they they hurt
The cause of working again
Propaganda
Cuz I have to be pretty specific
I saw a lot of people that I
I'm like Twitter
Husband
Little Dicky
Great
Thing for Rodger to have to admit
I did it was not true in Sibley journalistic Outlet
Force
Buy lawsuit
To say
The bare minimum
This thing published
Was in
Great
Good work everybody
Say that he'll article
It wasn't
People ran with it
Some sort of a Rodger his admitted everything is alive
Situation
Sued for saying
Specific
Hebrew Sam nunberg Hunter the bus
So I can plan it out
What a sofa
The only other thing Alex
Can do besides like
False ID
Was wrong but everything went
2 years ago
Pretty much wrong about
All we can do is create straw man argument
Help himself
But it shows how desperate they are that there's Martian bases with slave children
So no no no no
Let it lie about it
Big one in the elkalam
Has Robert David
Deals on his show
Did not
Push back on it at all
Sign off on it
Constantly building up 100% And is an expert on everything operative
I got it so
At the very least you went
A bunch of times
You didn't say that
Whatever
The other thing is
There are people
We're still getting harassed
Because of the rhetoric it out
The world
And so these articles
Come out are a reminder of
The dangers of
This rhetoric
Knox
Galaxy
People to their house
Trying to make
Clear that when you run with stuff like
Like this
You are creating a life
Of victimization
For victims of crime
What you're doing is
People who are the victims of terrorism
Are now living their lives
Being terrorized
Had to evacuate school or something like that
Exactly
On the anniversary
Because of
People who buy
How to put out into the world
Not saying
Go to their home
Please pay attention
Yep
He can't handle that takes everything
And turns it into
Media lying about it when he's lying about the media
So
Who gives this
It's just
Fascinated
About the
Previous 2 clip
Is
Always knows
The Google app
Do you know what it whenever he said
The thing that I
Really it's like he's always he doesn't
It's been up and down in the
Top 10 Google searches
Are you sure
Kasumi I feel like
Plenty of time
No I'm guess I'm just
Tasked with monitoring Twitter
Because of who they follow it
Throughout the day
Please give me too hard for my audience to look up
It's just a fart in the Wind
Who gives a s***
Because
He always be looking
Google analytics of a story because
Cuz that's something that now that he has no
To that
Who is trending on Google who is trending on Twitter in order to in order to make sure he's talking about that
Eclipse in 2009
Michelle about how
You'll be always comes in these like there are
Thousands of story
About me there's 1,000 everyday
Thousand
Stories where the New World Order is being now
And stuff like that
Skits on Google
For whatever
Right
He's not going off of any kind of real
Metric results
There's somebody pages of results
It's stupid
Who cares
But
Who's bigger issue
What's the biggest
MK Ultra has finally been revealed
But that was a big that what was it that was one of them
Breeders Four Tops
The show talkingshit
And this is a
Give a f*** it's a light on fire
What are we going to do our next show about the f******
View who gives a I don't care
If you want to take me to Euro as he's a liberal globalist
Go for it I could have
No lesson
But where is
Coming from
Michael Savage
Apparently
Play Michael Savage
Is losing couple hours of his show
It's scaling down to 1 hour Pirro is getting
Time slot
Alex I love you
Adventure piro's this sneaky globalist who's coming in
Only going to be
Prelude
Michael Savage being taken off the air
It might be his trampolining beliefs
I don't think that's the case I think
Probably as s*** ratings bench
Spiros hot young
Commodity Shapiro
Huntsvegas podcast
Is one of the top 10 podcasts
Consist
Giants fan base
But
Man that sucks program director
Young vibrant has a huge fan base
And he's saying dumb
Conservative s*** you Ivan old
Crotchety man
Who is crank f****** show on Fox News
For like a week before he got fired
Are you going to start telling me that the
Massive Global disorganization awful variable
Make decisions based on politics
Okay well if you want
Is Michael Savage
Twilight
If he's parking career he is an old old man
And he is also already
V
Multi-millionaire
He's a very rich dude he's not going to be hurt
Even if his radio shows
He could do a podcast
Booster rate
He's probably
Considerable
I haven't been Shapiro I want both of them
Fish tanks like in the shape of water but I would still
If I was a program director I'd still be like
Yeah you get this
Attack on Savage in
Pronounce
Which I'm very excited
We how it plays out
Destroy political
All the proof
Everything about who he really is
Whole Nine Yards
I'm at a stop right there Network
Okay
I'm sure there's other people from back then who are also dead
This is a number one definition of a story that I'm like I'm f******
Pumped me how this plays out
But I also don't care how it lands
I know it's going to happen
Is it Alex
Step on a rake
You going to silent
He's going to make some sort of grand Overture against Ben Shapiro and then it's going to be like
It's going to be
So disappointing
But it's not like it's new either
Euro Cent he was trying to get Kanye West
Michelle
Hey Kanye
Ben Shapiro
Awful stupid loser
He's a really smart
Kids get
Two grades
Primary education
What's college graduated from Harvard Law School
Like one of the youngest
People ever be published in
SmartStyle
Conservative
Malcolm Gladwell
I think he talks faster
I don't know
Maybe we should cover it some point
I'm open to the possibility of it
They really don't feel I don't feel any Joy when I
Is that like Alex bills
And also I don't know Art Bell
Debt right
Whatever
Balls evolve in Alex
Freelance
Young man
Coming from a Cirque
Circumstance where you graduate 2 years early enter the world
There's so much pressure on you
I could see
Human.
Being all that happy in life
And it comes out in his
Fast pace
Eastside Springs
It's not fun
Super fast if we just played him at 1.5 times
Maybe I'd like him boy last
Harvard Law School
Hey dude you big words
6 suck
A lot of ideas
Are very dumb
But it's
He has the good sense
Be like
If you go on Infowars Yorba
Becoming part of that is not good
Yeah that is something that the president would do
At least he knows that on some level
Don't go on a bitter about it
Probably
Before that but that was the last time it really flared up
He started doing a bunch of Ben Shapiro impressions
Slap fight
I don't care
Absolutely
Bloody each other
Live your life
I kind of do want Kanye to go on it
I think it'd be really weird
I actually was
I think it'll be
Terribly embarrassing
Everyone is everyone Alex Kanye
Call
Be great
Isaac as a scientific experiment I'd love to see how it plays out
Yeah he's on a crusade Alex's against Ben Shapiro
In order to do that
In order to
To facilitate this
Crusade
He has to call in again
Uno's benches
Known him for a long time
Shapiro
Is also
Best-selling author also assure
But I'm just like no I don't want box de anima doesn't talk show
Sabotage
Spero is
The new
Globalist
More or less
Right to comment
Deserve it
We read a little bit past notably because
Anders Breivik
Celebrate
His acts of terrorism
Serial killer
Spero is if he's coming from
The caring about
Positions in policy
On his blog Vox day consist
We talked s*** about Shapiro
Bracket
6 player that white Nash
When they talk about
But don't want to be too overt about it
Your brother know
Traffic in Nashville
Indicate I'm talking about this person cuz they're Jewish
So Ben Shapiro Jewish
Scotch
Respect
It is September 9th 2000
Teen post on his blog
Literally say
Quotes
Choose for what
A diverse USA globalism in the left
American nationalism in the alt right
There is no other meaningful option
Tries to get his point across
Subtle mean
Shapiro at WorldNetDaily
The job because of
His dad Robert peel who was the director of
News
Ic4a time
Because I'm 2008 Robert
Two months in prison for five counts of taxes
Alex Jones is Peter Schiff
His trial came out that Robert Beal was a member of a sovereign citizen
Called common law Court
It's located in Ramsey
Minnesota
Equally unsurprising today
Back before that
He was a higher up at WorldNetDaily
Pretty clearly hooked up aspiring science
Fiction authors son with a gig
Which is now
White nationalist
So congratulations
Dad nepotism
Turned out very poorly
Innocence
Let's just give it up
Also along the way it's really interesting that Vox Dei had a bit of a stretch Rouge trying to get into that pickup artist
Damn money
What are things that are in the park
Pickup artist book about pickup Artistry artist
Dave Seaman was involved in all this stuff
Crnkovich was in gamergate all of it is the funnel that leads to all this s*** feeling entitled
Everything
Apart from any other dudes who advised Geist
Do you like to sing
Totally disrespect women so they think you're aloof
Monster
Close very close can't say no after they very close
This is it this is like that it could be marriage
September 28th 2011 post on his blog
I don't believe I could recommend this is a strategy for most
What is surely educational to learn that
Killing monsters
Just women than behaving like a gentle
And women before all this inevitable Snowflake and commences
Please note that there is absolutely nothing to argue about
It's an established empirical fact
He says that it's an empirical fact but the only citation to provide
Tobacco shop at all is a link to another pick-up artist blog called Alpha Game Plan
Which is just a write-up of a
Posting the Daily Mail
But how Japanese murder
This doesn't make any
It doesn't make anything and established
Empirical
This is just an anecdote
Is that the murderer is that fan group doesn't prove anything
To the point of it being a murderer is more attractive
Women the being polite and
TED hose
Ted Bundy has a fanbase but right now
Who are these people towards groups of murderer
No I'm saying but there's a
I think what his variable is the largest population of attractive
Serial killers
Rapists and murderers morality
Especially more than holding the door open that proves your f****** bettas don't want you or at Gamba
Hammerhead in that door Hillsboro
Talk about like alphys
Alphas and betas
She knows a couple more Greek letters
Studies have been done wolf communities
Ecostruxure doesn't exist in nature
It only exists
In
In like
Enclosures it only exists
Natural
This is how people work
It's all good working prison
Probably
Evolutionary strategy
Rapist and murderer
Just based on anecdotal story
Brett has nothing to do with empirical
For longtime Vox day
Masquerading
Anyways
Because we talked about like Howie's in Mensa
Irrespective science
But all he's ever done is
To repackage overtly white supremacist
It dangerously misogynist
Mystic narrative
All in all
My point is
This dude's a piece of s*** and he's exactly who you would expect Alex to still be hanging out
At this point in his boxing career
Crazy
Fox
The worst
Like I've taken
Can a couple of these things
If you go read this blog you'll fine
F******
Atrociously worded statement
That's that
That's not okay. Okay
He was trying to make about the idea of like white supremacy isn't
It's not that
Whites are
Better
Than any other race
But
White white people are the only people who are willing to stand up for the preservation of westerns
Society
No matter what race you are you should be in favor of white nationalism
Okay
Let's be a lesbian party
Hey how you doing
No reason to role-play that
Stay forever
On that episode
We jump in
We're going to get some
Fleming here
Unspeakable
Alex
Address to the Rodger Stone
Sing I guess but it was just
I wasn't everything we're doing everything right
Expected
But it turns out it was worth
Possibly could have imagined
Infowars.com
Clubs at night
But
Video Heat
About how she's part of the lgbtq
What nice
Was already there
Great song called Girl Scout
No no that was
Different Ted Nugent
City Council
Give them to us
Snorting ketamine
What is the drug that people take to go to transfer
We'll get into that video here in a little
He's too f****** cool
Call Dan
Yeah
Abundantly
Play clear by my
Regardless
No matter where you fall on it
Even if you're on Alex's side
Indefensible
Here's what I mean
In their post on their website the sub-headline
About this story
Adult patrons throw money at male child dressed like a s***
Play currently
That is unbelievably like
Dress like a s***
So even though the kid question is inspiring artist
Website
I find it particularly distasteful that Alex posted a picture of him
And their real name on the website
And it's article
Is there angle is if it's
Child to bring possible attention or attacks their way
The only way this
It's the only way
They're trying to make this eleven-year-old
Which is exactly what they wanted
Because this drag artist known as Desmond is amazing is a fairly popular LG
With over 100,000 followers on
They're only 11 years old
Give a s***
About the ID
He's going to try and play up the idea that I care about the victimization gear
He would have dealt with this differ
He wouldn't have allowed of headline dress like a flood
He wouldn't have
A picture
Of this
And on his website
You wouldn't have done
This isn't
On this kid
Not on the idea that globalist
Adult man
Hayes now stalking alien 11
Writing songs
Yeah wasn't
He was doing a routine based on a Gwen Stefani song
So he used
Gwen Stefani
Central you know like those baggy pants
The other white undershirt at your high school
School talent show doing
Ifucking Gwen Stefani
In order to prop up his argument attacking a child whose life
It is article Alex didn't write the article but
He's responsible for every
Salazar's article
They almost exclusively use just quotes from a random Anonymous comments on a subreddit call doordash
Trashy
Journalistic
All these people saying all this is horrible on a
Trashy
This is nonsense
Anonymous
Comments
All the other
This article against
For places like louder with Crowder
Revolve around the idea that Desmond
Performance was sexual
When there's no indication that's
The case at all
It's Alex and louder with Crowder that's projecting sex
I'll do what is ostensibly a youth doing a lipstick performance
Or karaoke
In the case of
I quit the one I watched was definitely a lipstick but I
Extend the possibility that
Anime singing
Butler Tire
All right on
Send it
Here's what I'm hearing
Out of all of this.
Is that Alex's
Is real issue
And so many of these guys
Fuel issue
Has nothing to do with
Sexualizing
Kids
And more with
Like this guy
Confusing
Like for them it for them they're looking at it like a reason that he's
Dress like a s*** is his confusion his confusion is like
Why are you making me want to f***
I don't understand
What's going on baby
That's f***** up maybe something is f***** that might be
Too much to put on Alex or whatever
If possible
Who knows
I think more the confusion comes
From him seeing this
Is an attack on masculinity
And stuff like that
I think he has
Different
Cordello's
That's f*****
Alex gets really ambitious
F*** you
Illustrates that
About the forces that were facing there's no doubt about the endgame
As we started there is
Every culture
He's a bucket
He's talking about
He's going to try and bring in like the idea of like
South America
Child sacrifice
There's a bunch of
Hold on hold on
So f****** serious
Headlines.com
So this is the other piece of
Performing at the club
$3 bill
Queer as a $3 bill
Stop pedaling
They're pieces of this a better bunch of nonsense
It's not just
Regularly
New York Comedy Festival
Deal out of the idea that this is
The kid in the bar
But also Destiny was there as a performer
12 year old kid
Who was allowed into bars
Because he was there to perform and he was there
YouTube jokes about his mom was a flood and stuff you wouldn't
Expect child to say was wrong
It was kind of kind of lame
Jules and Desmond
Yeah so
I was going to give a s*** about that
I don't care about the idea
Spell everybody around you doesn't know of at least like
We will evolve into at least 10 shows where it's like
Really they're going to do a twelve-year-old and then the twelve-year-old does well and you're like
F*** your dad wrote that
Just trying to do
He's trying to make it like
He was in a bar and that's
Wrong
Not really wrong
That's crazy and then the other thing
Is Alex's unwell
Separate the idea of
Gay bar being a sexual place
Hakeem to a strip club
Annie Bakes
Repeatedly
Really f******
Hispanic girl in a topless bar
No
See I think it's more about the masculinity than it is about anything else
I think that is where he
Desire is getting up
Because it feeds into somebody the narratives that he
He's talked about forever
Where is this idea
What most of his product line is
Fear of losing your
Vitality
It should like that so I
Dishonest
Absolutely if you brought an 11 year old girls
To a strip club and they were doing a strip
Kezar
That would be illegal if they were just up there to be all gold
Creepy dude
Yeah yes
We've already got lost
Yeah yeah
The false equivalence
Gay bars the same
Strip club
Because
Gay bars
No it's not a group of people has gone to regular bars
So f***
Longs and have been discriminated against
Have been assaulted
Have been f***** with n
Unceasing
Sing regularity so much so that they created their own space
Finally they have their own
And even though they have their own f******
Space where they feel safe and comfortable if you have to somehow try and marginalize them still further
Don't you would like something like for his b******* like he probably goes to some f*** Barbershop where it's like
F*** you you're a f******
Rico's shooting
Yeah you go shooting to know what shooting ranges are for
Dude f****** themselves Alex Jones
Done
Right
It makes no sense
Reductio ad absurdum
Another circumstance
Using his same line of thinking to point out the
He's coming
Places
He feels it's just
Certified
Because this kid
Jasmine
Has revealed in a video
The pedophiles
Are part of
Video with his mother
Is reported
You're really doing a great job.
Even if they did
Kids in the schools
It's all part of a larger plan
So the actual video here in a little bit
Much more f***** up
Then even you going to
At this point
But Alex thinks he's been
Alex
In his video that he has
50 years apart
I've been saying that all along
I've been demonizing lgbtq
80 Community by saying that piece is at the end of it
And now
I'm right
Isn't that amazing
It's not amazing
He's wrong
He's also
Desperate
We are fabulously successful
Undertale attack and it is a symbol of our
I need it
Going to need your money
Situation
Long after it's dead
We can stay
Here for a long time and hopefully
He wants to be on that horse wants to stay around
Desperate
The first segment
A lot of focus to it
Indicate
Like I need you to think this means something
Christmas sales are still going
And if you get before midnight tonight
You just f****** order ton of stuff before Christmas
Your house music
We're on our 300 39th
Today of their Christmas to you need for your children
Dr. pepper
But you also
To get really interested
My time is up
The hope we could destroy do we get destroyed
He says something very
We're looking at that we're bleeding
And John bush
So the two people that he listed as martyrs
Compare
John Birch
Soldier
Robert Welsh
The founder of
Names
Do you
You would not be cool with that propaganda
Virtualized
Supposed first
Victim of the Cold War
Stuff like that in order to
And I'll be like a symbolic martyr for these
Chinese propaganda
No idea
Remember how back when the president of the John Birch Society was on Alex's show and I told
Robert Welch
Robert Welsh was the first President John Birch Society was replaced
Is President because the new president was
The plane was shot down by the Soviet
That was McDonald's I was like
Scotch and before you start setting
Being shot down by the Soviets
Sort of proof of a communist plot a plane that deviated from their flight path and wanted to
Prohibited Soviet airspace
I'm definitely not defending shooting
Playing down
It's the wrong way to handle things
Now some fun facts about Larry McDonald
Is member of the House representing George's 1975.
The American Journal political science
Conservative member of both
Houses of Congress
Between 19
37 in
Who's number one
Ron Paul
He was in office was a member of the McCarthy sound
Expression of admiration for Joseph
McCarthy
He co-sponsored a bill advocated that homosexuals and never be given to equal rights which
You phrased as
Special consideration
He fought against the establishment of the Martin Luther King
Bring back
Has to be explained
Seeing as he was a member of the Austrian School and the mutants
Introduce bills
Polish the Federal
Really really stupid you shouldn't be allowed to call yourself in
Like there should be a rule against
If you're so stupidly f****** wrong you just have to call yourself like
The folks the mummies folks let's work on that for later
Nothing's going to be the next bill that I introduced these potential destruction
Similar to
Propaganda murder of the John Birch Society
And the second President of the John Birch
Society
Who was in the plane that got shot
Alex loves the John Birch
So he doesn't talk about it all that much
Clearly the fact
I am her to bring up Larry McDonald but it came out real f****** smooth and he was looking for martyrs
Translate
To come out of his mouth
It's very clear
Very clear
Really stupid
I should also
At this point
How stupid he is
He goes down
Very funny
He goes down this line
Whenever
That's the sign that the city
Just on the top
So ever possibly be more indicative of wanting to sacrifice a child
Then f****** going after a child and making sure that all of your
Speechless
F****** trolls slam down upon them in a little bit
First
Alex's got to get it
Select
Accordingly
That is.
Empire span 620
3 years from 1222
The Khmer Empire in Cambodia license
30 years
The 14th
The Ethiopian Empire last
35 and only fell because it was invaded by
The Kush empire in modern Sudan
I went from 1070b
Bce-t
I wasn't saying anything
Civilization
200 300 years
This is complete b*******
He's just using this nonsensical
Statistic he's pulling out of thin air in order to present the idea that we're in the end
We haven't even yours
Haven't even Define civilization civilization
Empires last
Like refuting
I'm I'm just saying that even even then you know like so let's go with Chinese civilization
Weird
Longer than three
But the people were still the f****** people
Archaeology rental the problem
He knows nothing if you ever studied basic archaeology or anthropology
Please call me because I haven't and I'm going to say dumb s*** and I'm not going to use
Real
Specific
Sony launches back in
I've listened to this
I think I know what he saying
But it's so weird
I find it hard to
To believe that
The keys making Des Arc
Flashlight
Azar built
What was the priest before the temple
Little boys and girls
For the sexualisation of children
Tourism of Sheldon
Will tell you
It's so strange to me that the argument that in tell me if I'm wrong
Cats tell me if I'm wrong.
There isn't a whole lot
Right
Is that the Chinese
Is the trichomes at work
Are promoting pedophilic movie
Right
The LG
What have you
Sure
They know they know they
300 years and it's about time
For depriest
Class to start demanding
Tupac children in public the destruction of America
I really think that's the argument that he's making
That's crazy cuz he just just that
Because
The Chinese
2000 years later in his own argument
They're like
Hold on
We'll fund
Priest-class
Right cuz I remember when that happened to us
I guess
Absurd
So our civilization wouldn't collapse
Knows that the only way
Stabilization
This is crazy
I think we've seen
I never would have guessed
Bananas
I think that he thinks
He thinks that the Chinese are paying people to f*** kids in public
No
They're paying
I guess
LGB
Folks to advocate for their own right
Which Alex
Speed of the normalization of pedophilia
Because they think they
That will leave
Destruction of America
Which which of these were funding lgbtq
It's the
There are are
Water inferential problem it's the mess
That's the kind of thing
Just gone
If you have the Barney stop that
If you get out of here
So at this point
Intellectualize into things
He said the words
Ergo
Appealed to your intelligent mind
Museum funding
Hacking a child
Is
Next Level batting
But it's also fun
Because I know from everything I've seen about this kid Desmond is awesome
That
You wouldn't care at all
But Alex
Petty petty Bowl
So I take some solace
But at the same time
This is really
Address for slipping really bad
Story of this podcast
As a bar
Lego sorry
This is a personal story story
You talk about you
Yeah probably did that happen
New York law that says the people under 21 can enter a bar
The bar self-imposed which is
That's why bars can have eight
Plus night for concert
There is no law that says
You can't come in
Generally speaking
State-by-state but if the bar serves food they can have any age people in there
They just
Cancer people under 21
Specific language
S*******
He says places where there's a dolt entertainment going on
Berkeley says because
Cuz you think
Adult
Attainment
Logan over this point
He's trying to pretend that this
Strip club
It's not it's just
Spaghetti space
Did he deems
Intrinsically safe
And that is f***** up
He just sexualizes everything
And it's a really it's a really lame has a bar
Anyway I miss my squad.
Insult
Jasmine
Completely
You are acting like
Disgraceful pile of
Here's the idea that you would say
This is an emaciated kid who looks like a
The crackhead
Why the
Buckwheat
Do that
What what
Ankle does that serve for what he wants to achieve
Anything other than attacking this
That's the only thing that makes sense out of this rhetoric
Yep
Now
I told you we get to
Nothing
And this is Mike down clip
This is where Alex actually plays
The video
He's been talkin
About
Let Desmond
Comes out and says that is the lgbtq
Yeah but you just
F*** office
Now there's an entry
Dynamic going on in
This video and you'll pick up on it immediately
I guarantee
Everyone listening
Will pick up on it
Immediately
Alex is pretending that
He's not a play
In order for him to
To demonize
Anyway
Completely disgrace
And I'm certain
Because our listeners
And you are just hit head
You'll see through this
Here is
About ketamine
Everywhere Engineers bag
Female female
Any
Arnon
Only us
People can have
That's not true at all
Is this
Jeep gas
How old is your BF
So the woman
You do know it's not child
Mom here
When you can't tell there's so much makeup on The Other Woman
And the mother is so proud of how great this is
Schools
Cuz Alex f****** knows better
Like his interviews with that Faith lived their lives
You know like the mom and Desmond both has lived their lives
Feel the same way a lot of those
Creepy stage moms
Maybe there's a tiny element of it possibility
But there's some of that there
I saw with them
It was very clear that Desmond was
Expressing I'm so grateful that I have a mother who
Except
This thing that's been a part of me as long as I remembered it
And the bomb
Is bad
That's
To do I love my kid
They would know their life
Then we'll get back to what was going on
The question is how much more of this
Society and culture
Involved in drug culture
Signalling involved
Only Fallen
So I would like you to say what was going on in there
That video
You know what was going on
I
I think wait we allow the time
But I really
I think it's important to make that is one of them
It's very clear that what's going on here is they're doing the lives
Alex inspiringly
Ironically
Galaxy
Indicative
Like I don't know if other right-wing
People are using that acronym
He made it the person was doing that because they were inspired by Alex
So what is this second
Being
11 year old
The eleven-year-old reading it
Saying I don't know what that means or other person
I don't know what that means
Then Alex then using
They said lgbtq I've been right all along
It's a f****** answered and then you heard in there very clearly
Someone was that Hitler was right comes up a number of times
Yep
Helicopter rides yay
That response came because Desmond thought it was a reference to taking a ride in a helicopter
Not reference
How Pinochet
Used to take his political Rivals and helicopters and throw them out to murder them
In recent months
The theme of offering liberals
Helicopter ride
Mickey way for Trump supporters
Kill their political rivals
Without the risk of actually saying it
And it's video that Alex has posted
Clear evidence of
Coronavirus child as well as overt death breath
Weirdly Houston
And the article that he wrote
It has
It's not used to being hurled at an eleven-year-old
It's because our
Looks likes that sort
The real abuse that Desmond will face
In life is going to come from people like Alex
Not for people who allowed
To pursue whatever version of
Personal truth
The fact that Alex wants to
The targeting of Desmet
You couldn't be clearer
Didn't the last line that article
This will likely not be the last we hear of Desmond
Does Alaska
Used to push its demoralizing pedophilic
So
Here is just a video where
People were really
And is very heavily edited
Who knows what else
What's going on in that livestream
But it's an edit
11 year old not understanding that Nazis are saying horrible things
And then just reading off the screen
I don't know her cold read that's not bad
That's not bad
Take a listen to cold reading skills in the past operation
Reader is Alex
So we see this here this is Alex's soda pf2 Resistol
In terms of its narrative and you see where it's coming from and it's b*******
All he's doing is trying to
Target out of
The child
Works best for his narrative
And it
Jasmine didn't say there's a
Do you know GB
Confused
Reading as I understand it
He is the preferred pronoun
Is gender fluid
But all the articles that I read
That in that lion I don't know if I'm using the wrong pronoun I apologize
But that seems to be the way
I-it's
It shakes out
But
All this is just the worst
He's the worst
So at this point break come back
Alex Guzman studio anymore
The worst job of covering the same
Topic
It would be considered inappropriate
Child abuse but if it's
Surrounding the
Topic or the
Aren't they say of drag culture
Or transsexualism then it's okay you're not allowed to talk about it
Shock impact
So
But if you don't like to
You know abused your kids psychologically and you like to take care of your kids health
We got your back,
Oh my God walking you up
Isn't it amazing that like that
Becca
You do it
Owen
Knock yourself very long cause
And then just said if you don't want to abuse your children by ourself
Which
You are
F******
George user
We have to make a fine distinction.
Negative
What they're doing is not necessary
Abusive in nature
Precipitates the abuse of children
If you don't know you don't know
Then I get your point
If you don't know that what you're doing is going to directly lead
To be f****** abuse
Of a child
Then I get that you might just be facilitating
Zaino
They know God damn well that what they are saying is leading to a child being abused
That is that is like saying that a general doesn't kill anybody because he all he does is put true
General does direct
Flow
Troops are going
They're just
I know it's a fine distinction it's just the
It's just to say I do
Purposely
Deliberately
Abusing children
That should be a literal crime
What they just did
Should be a literal crime
I am frustrated
I'm frustrated too but I also don't think that
Create a better world
Real f*****-up implicate
You don't get to direct yours
Millions of followers
To scream at a child
They could hide behind whatever they've done
Asthma
Attacked
This kid
Facetious
Care about the quote-unquote victims you can hide behind any kind of couch language
That you want and still
Do the exact same
You would have the same effect
Getting around whatever
You'd end up in a really nebulous
Place where you would end up
You end up having to like
So
Worth it
Ongoing and never-ending argument
About
How
You
Discern bad faith Act
In a legal sense
Which I get
I get no real
I get that
I'm not saying that I'm going to write the law I'm not saying that I have some sort of ability to police this in a
That makes sense or that it is even possible but from a moral standpoint
Those guys are abusing children
Desmond
His parents probably have
Some decent
What is libel action
Like this 11 year old
Is
The pedophiles are apart of the LG
Stuff like that
I think that there is probably
Some sort of Grievous damage
They could be argue
I think there's a
Terms of outlawing
I think you're just
Not you but I think one would be chasing their own
I totally get it
Maybe some sort of civil action
Could be a pro
That is
I wanted to lie about us so bad
He knows better
I wanted to lie about it so bad I want to have for every goddamn nose
Owens hosting
Italics
Turns out
He said why at the beginning of the show and I just haven't
Owen Shroyer coming in
Throughout the transmission today
So
Alex is gone
I can't even explain
Just listen to
Just listening to that
He interviews Leo zagami that's f****** weirdo
Illuminati Insider in
Test
Actually
His spinning a weird narrative about the idea
Brazil is great
Master do if you don't like the people love murderers.
Weird
Vatican is killing and raping everybody but this guy who has killed
Raped a bunch of people
It's weird it's weird that all these
People have this
And you might think that's an offensive Italian
If you would play Leo's Agaves
You're at you're a little bit of Lupron
Venturing a little far from the countryside are not far off
So Alex comes back
I think he pulled a
But I'm not sure
Listen to this and see if you think this is a prank
I think it
And Alex Jones back with us
What happened today
I knew turned Frank I think it was
Hillary lawyer
Lost power in the only way
Play always knowing that his mic is off
He's a great guy to work for Dad
Damn do you want to do
Do you want another office
We like to have fun
I'm certain that the prank it has to be right
There's no other explanation for that there's no other
Purpose
Take it away.
And a little
We like to have fun around here
Yeah
It brings me joy
Will headquarters and Alex Jones is back with us
Today
Put upon band
First f****** time
Look I am
15 years younger than you
Maybe
I think you're lying by rage
Will probably
Professional
Trying
HEB
You son of a b****
That is
That is such the sound of a man who's like
Why do I get paid by this guy wouldn't have done
I could have been
So many others
What if I went to a real journalism
I should have just gone to a real journalist
I could have been
Pipefitter
My grandfather was a pipefitter
Father was a pipefitter
And I got stuck
Is John Birch
F******
Coming back on the show
That's a whole lot just rambling about a bunch of nonsense
He says something
Is awesome
I've been I've been wanting to find him saying
I've never found
I found other people
Clown.
People playing this
Before has never been able to make it today
Now we can
Management policies set by the New York fit
Whatever
There it is
Saturday
Everybody else was gone for recess for Christmas
Roasted chestnuts
Cooking a turkey
Currency over the interest rates over all of it
So
So awesome
A a note
Alex
We know a couple things
The Paul family
I thought he'd give them death
Prince over anything
Use those usable
Can't really stick
Other
Explanations
But now Alex
In 2018 on his show
Is arguing that the
Pushkin's Federal Reserve cooking chestnuts
Open fire
I want to tell you this
What's the temperature
23rd 1913 you know what happened
Woodrow Wilson signed the bill into law
Earlier
Dammit voted
Then that means
That's that's how love works I've seen Schoolhouse Rock
Woodrow Wilson signed the bill into a lava Senate voted on it that beans spent zero time
Committees there were no
It was simply done on everything was written up
No it takes at least like January 9th
12 reduced
Refinement
December 22nd 1930
House vote
298 yay
Not send Edward Scott
There were 34 announced pairs
A 468
They were paired up we're going about now you're going to be okay so let's all get out of here
60 is
Very close to what the vote would have been if everyone showed up
On the 23rd at 1
It was voted in
25 days
27 not voting
With 13 an hour
A witch
26 of the 27 non-voters
Is Audible
Ground on it
It's just a dumb thing that exists in Patriot mythology and in
It's one of these
Anti-tax
Communities it's all just a load of b*******
There's a there's a lot
Your story to it
Like none dare call it
Conspiracy and stuff like that
Weird ants
Yeah
Years past
I honestly would love to
To know
A specific answer
Why do they say
Because it's not
Name them
Shirt
I would like the names of the three
I would like their names I would like
Career
Right or what kind of level they were dealing with
The big point
Everything that's really important
Is
Alex is here.
He's talkin
Straight
S*** the idea
Coming on his show
And saying that the Federal Reserve was pushed
Like we can make
I mean
This stuff about
The Desmond is awesome
Unforgivable on humans
Absolutely the more important
Because the priest class Rises up
Text Blake
Alright bye
Calm down
Worst
Because
That should be a sign
To everybody listening
Get out
Think you could make an argument that it's going to take
You too long
Understand past civilization
Or something like that
That would involve reading a lot of book
This one
Either Google
Images
Jerk-off on all the goddamn time
Literally will not allow that to happen
Obama Deception covers any war game
What would have happened if 3 cm
Woodrow Wilson
It is
Whatever the Federal Reserve
Yeah yeah yeah
Guess what guess what the Constitution also allows for a new-build
Right it's all of them got together
Like this
Guess what we have a majority who is going to be
Different version
This is Luna
I love it though
To the stupid there is
Nothing board farrier
Then a group of intelligent people getting together and not asking
For your dumb
Uninformed and pointless opinion
And then doing something that's better
Yeah
Something that they have to destroy
Wait
The Obamacare bill
Without to ask me whether or not there were
Reserved
F*** you you're stupid
Go away
Yeah I mean I really want to stress
Hey
I kind of
Like I should have done
Right
Possibly list
Ashok years that not be like
What
They're gone
I don't know
I know I'm not saying your lost cause eventually find
Past but I am saying
I don't I don't give a
If your spidey sense doesn't chime in there you you are dumb
What you have done is
It's the same thing
YouTube's algorithm
People buy
Gradually more and more
Videos
Recommended
Yeah
I guess similar
Almost reverse thing where
The Vault his troubles
Is Amplified rhetoric
Kenny's dumbing-down of
Content
Assured that the only
Butter left are
Effectual.
Too dumb
You can't have
Questioning
People
Reasonable people if
If you say
3p
People passed the Federal Reserve in
Existence
They aren't like
Alex please
Retract that
I like you
But that is unacceptable
You can't have any
No absolutely not
Christmas sales have
I want
Coming up so bad I want to
I'm just
Today
We have these episodes
We have these episodes like for the most part I think we're just
Just like
Having fun
But it's
Ineffectual stupid
And focuses that ineffectual stupidity
Diffuses it amongst
Monsters following
Any Focus
It's crazy
That
I can't
Cimarron this enough
He's
Morally
Directing
Thousands upon thousands
Hurled abuse
I all in the name of it
Pieces of information
Together the app
Aftermath
His behalf
Xavier
His behavior
Reasonable
Oh your actions now we're going to
The same sort of
Respond now I'll say this
This is cold comfort
Ensemble
When hook happened his audience
Probably much wider
Given
He is off
YouTube
Twitter
I think there's a decent chance that the effect
The precipitating
Ford
Is lower
Few years
But
The flip side of that coin is
As I've already said they're all around
Yeah yeah yeah
More
Prone
Being that sort of person but who knows
I mean
Yeah his audience was wider back then but if they have left by now
Chances are they also probably the ones who are ready
We are doing the Sandy Hook
It doesn't matter
Because I don't I don't
Look at things
Like this
Outcome
Nothing right or not
Not
It's not
It's action
God I can
Cannot imagine
I really can't imagine
A situation where I would
Define Within
Yeah I mean it's f***** up
Adan Salazar
And then it's f***** up
You imagined
Is there are additives
People whose titles are
Call Jared Leto action I don't know what the process is
Wrote that article
And then I believe it's L Ron Hubbard's process which is the door sure
Put the idea in any other journalist
Takeout
Stages of
Ever posted on
Site
Anything like that
If you don't
I know that Infowars doesn't work like that
I still hold them to that
So I imagine
Someone look
Do that instead
Good put it on the site let's do the
Yep
I can't imagine adults
Being like that
That's disgusting
It's really really f****** Christ
Congratulations
Even after two years even after all of the
F****** s*** we watch you do you are a disgusting pile of s*** once more
There's no floor
If I wanted to see what happened on Thursday
Just kind of exhausted
I want I want him to go away for awhile
Christ
Happy holidays Alex
Christmas sales going
Anyway guys
Appears to be taking a break
Don't think so
Next week
So will the back
We will see you then we have a website
Since troops knowledge underscore fight
Got a Facebook group called go home
We are on iTunes subscribe comments
Where am I
More people live
Mitch on the show
You see the growth
If it comes from that
Absolutely
Never killed
I'm positive
11 years
It's not enough time
Kind of universe
I don't think you have
Muscles
I might be wrong
Find me maybe on somebody younger than you
Filter isn't right for
A good song
I don't know my point is that Desmond is awesome
Has never killed anybody
Technically probably
And that's out
Alexandra Thurston color