Alex
Kristen color my huge fan of your work
Yes sir
What's the question
Thank you
Has never
Itsjerian
Forever
Too-cool-for-school Garcia Vega go down there
I've never been a big
Cigar guy
I started smoking with a pipe
Because I was right for 10
Above
I got a Sherlock Holmes
Pipes and
Cigars
Timberland
Gross
Recharge out of its
I probably smoke
3 actual cigars in my life
And I was faking
Everest
Starbucks
Cigar
You know what I'm going to f***
King smoke this cigar and not one of those where you light it up in your life
This wrong and I throw it away
At my friend's wedding
I remember being out in the back
Courtyard
Area
And
My friends
His his new father-in-law
Came up to me
Yeah
Told me it was
He knew about his daughter
Yeah
Creepy
But you know what
Implication
UPS
Not sure which would be better both are bad
Well scars
That's good
Doesn't suck
Cesar donors
Mike T thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
How much Mike
You're now a policy wonk
Luke
Ewok
A tuna roll
Just rolled up
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Nikon
Thank you so much if you were listening
Do that
Netsports
Appreciate it
We've been doing the show for 2 years
And I have never received the amount of
Negative feedback
That we got from our last episode
I forgot
It's not
We need to give an apology to Chumbawamba we implied that they had fascist leaving
Mixed up in our mind
Because Chumbawamba parently are anarchist
Types of bass
Tubthumping
There's the song I get knocked down
Apologies
Very triggered our audience
Very poorly
I don't know
How we Foster disbrow Chumbawamba
Put
I don't know if you realized
Sorry
Hey wife I enjoy interacting and I don't mind people like correcting us when we're wrong
Bracelets that the Venn diagram
Acknowledge
What I don't know in the past
We are out of March to April
Today's episode will cover April 1st and 2nd
By 2009
Miss that I
I take great pleasure in being able to go out
But we can laugh at
Lexia
My man
April 4th
I always love
Tuning in for an April Fool's Day episode of Alex
Shoe Show
Haven't we heard it on Friday's episode you're going to do just pulled a prank on Owen
Show
You were is if he has a playful streak to him
Videos of cantankerous little
Troublemaker
Inside him
I told I always think that April Fool's Day is going to bring it out of them and I always think I've listened to
I've listened to like 45
April Fool's Day episodes
Hoping for Frank
Or something
Happens
It doesn't happen today
To learn
About what time
In the right wing
Psvr
Outside
Infowars
Interested
She said she supports him on quote every issue
Stories.
Now and Coulter
Fox News
When they're owned by
Controlled opposition these guys all are
Alex
Dia lot of his rhetoric creeping into the right-wing media
Self he started
See his narrative being mirrored
You saw her earlier with the Glenn Beck
Serta thought that was an isolated case
But now a party becomes
More
Out now in
Public
Past the original like
Huge push rap
Tea parties all over the country
Glenn Beck
12 starting
The pieces are starting to fall into place
His laundry is being aired
But he doesn't like who's doing that laundry
The terms of the black president
Starts out
Who knows
Why
We need a bigger boat
Maybe no that's okay
The secret government as the boat or whatever
Assertive
What would you call it like
The skeleton of the house
In order to build that don't need the girders that Alex has
Isn't going to fly they don't have
And Alex has been working
8 years
Building that f****** Foundation
Realized
What they realize they had to do
Illegitimate president
Present
Because he
Whatever other reasons they would have makeup
He has to be all-powerful and
Timer
The same time being ineffectual and non-existent
They realize the effectiveness of that alive
Alex has been doing
Who knows how much of that is intentional at all like
Come out here and say that Fox News
Looked at Alex and said let's get us some of that or anything like that
Could be pure coincidence
How do we make this Morris
Stream the possibility
It doesn't mean that they're ripping off Alex but Alex is it for sure
As he's being ripped off the American public
I want me some of that but I don't want Alex
Parking lot
Alex Alex
Somehow
A Megan Kelly a blonde white woman spouting bigotry
VSCO
Just going to be hours
Here on April 1st
For Alex realizes
Fox News
These
I don't know I
Glenn Beck was on
Yeah it was on
Diablo
Alex
Does something that I do ever
At this moment
Alex Jones
Is this is
A turning point
Funded the weatherman
Interesting Lee he had a harder time bacon billares
What the f*** are you talking about information
To back up his claims of all these
Nefarious organization
We have never heard
Alex
Say something
About
A boogie
Puppet
The market April 1st
Is the first time in our in our travels
We've heard that that
As
Early as we
We can find
Soros
Now it's in
Interesting to me phrases
Because it whenever you talk about these big bad guys before we heard it a hundred times
The Rockefellers and the Rothschilds Rockefeller Foundation
This freezing is very familiar to me
Present
Further down the line
Linguistic patterns
What's tomorrow's forecast
Snoo
I don't know if it means anything
I'm not entirely sure
I need to give it some more examination
Particular phrase
Freezing of it that closure in the way that he rolls
Three are the ones who
You were doing it that we've heard now a million
Expected to come out
If he's adding shock collars
Fellers the Rothschild and Rose
Sprint Center right away
Right I'm part of this could be a blip
It's entirely possible because George Soros
Did come out and do an interview that I
I think it was ill-advised
Because the propaganda
Made about it
What are you talkin about how he was having a great
Recession
Because of the best petite
Did call a bunch of stuff and a billionaire
The recession
Is it you should
And then the other things
Get here he had a lot of feelings about the
G20 and how was one of the last opportunities to save the global reach
Assertive
The news around
So I also
Consider the possibility
George Soros
Evil Boogeyman
Reaction to him showed up in the news for a bit
Soros Foundation combo
Adjust
Throwing a minute player
Is weird
I don't know we'll see what
What are the
2009 episode
Secretly Shadow country
So Alex has been real hot and bothered
About the
Summit over there
Obama's going to go meet with the queen
Is that
G20 protests
They're all
Apparently paid by Soros they're all fake
The opposition
Real opposite
Which is him
Everybody else is up
Bunch of posers
Johnny-come-lately
Or something like that
Colter's
He knows
But they're not regular
The physical
All real Anarchy
One has to see it to believe it I have experienced
What's Ryan let's do something
Anarchist
Unleashed
Marxist
The movie
Red-bearded Tommy
Shenanigans
No no no you misunderstood the story it was a different Cummings
Marxist
And he is the one who's
Delete it
The emaciated
The fake Antarctica
Xou talks to the leader red-bearded Potbelly
I do believe
Understand anybody who would do any of the actions
I do understand
Patrolling
Unfolding is a real series of events
Colorado
I guess he met one
Over there with his zits
I don't think
It's a real stereotype
Just be proof of Alex having that one anarchist
Any thinks they're all like that
Heavy metal
Maybe smoke map
A lot of
Yep
A really sleepy
G20 update
I just don't want to look
That it all
They're basically just saying all the pictures you see you like protesters bloody
And stuff like that.
Let's just be water
That wasn't fake
20 Subs
Because
Alex
Distracted
A b a b
Fight
Coverage of Obama showing up
Buckingham Palace
Just doing his British voice all over the place
All that stuff
Then
You decide
He's going to blow everyone's mind
Sounds like you're going to be all three
This is real in fact I even
Research on this
University
It's called the groom of the stool
Are you not going to discussion
Practice of the groom of the stool
Respect
It wasn't so much just wiping at Queens ass
Is a close adviser
Someone had to be with
The Royal at all times and all that back then
Sometimes
Caught up in the idea that
That it does
He is so defensive about the idea
At least an hour talking about the school
Not only does he spend an hour on it or so
He also has to call in a bunch
Intrastaff
Tabac him up it's kind of crazy because that sounds exactly like something somebody who was
Pounds on me talking about for about an hour
Conversely kind of sounds like a mystery shows
Broadcaster who invented Monopoly
But it is first clip of that
Alex Erin Dyke
To talk about this
This is Phil
Binational
To examine medical Wheaton
And I got to have it
Carted around and talk about this
State secrets of the
Stool
Thermistor
It is strange
What are you saying
Aaron Dykes is actually right
Pretty consistent
Among a lot of heads of state
They don't let
Just go anywhere
Because it is a state
Secret
In Subway's
Because if the foreign hostile leader or whatever words
Take their waste
Big Lot About
Central Health
Blackmail them
If someway that could be exploited for
I don't I don't know what other ways other than
I think you are missing the number one way to exploit
Use it to clone a new Obama
Accelerated
Even able to do that
Cynthia 300
Took over China in
There is a
There is a sensible reason to visit doesn't have to do with like
Or anything like that
Could tell a lot about a person
Because
I think
What I would think is
No tolls
Have you no decency
W bush had
Misunderstanding Alex is lying about Aaron dykes
It's pretty close to right
At the same time neither of them
No that's a conversation any of Alex's
Underlings conversation and let whatever his
Frozen
Let It Go
Okay
Alex isn't satisfied Paradise backup
Chameleon
Just fun to remember
Also it's fun to remember that
EEOC complaint against Alex grooming him for homosexual
Hey Rob
Sorry buddy
We're discussing the green
Explain
This is real I
Aaron Goodwin gravel see you later
We read
At least 10.
10 minutes
They do it
You didn't read any of those reports
The picture that I want to present to you of
What's important about Alex's group of the school.
He is so defensive about the idea that people don't believe him think he's making it up to be grocer funny
Multiple employees real
Coach with his life
Google Hangouts
Hey now I'm going to make Mark mad but agree with the school is
Honestly coaches more efficient
You see this show in Psych
Better
No I love
Talk about
I would like this to happen forever you're probably right actually because
That should just
Continue
Kind of racist
Try me
Mice
Directions
Careful
Careful rabbits
Name of other animals
And we are
A couple uses in there that make me think that this
What is what I feel what I hear that
Let's beatbox
The last Australian
Australia
Understand
From jokes
The fact that I do about Australia are actually
Jokes
Basically
Conception where the
Which we do you mean
The government is
Feeding off of them
Where is the government
Yeah in the illegal immigrants
I don't think you're an animal in the bear or something like that
Just about the
Animal metaphor
What's throat to braces
I think
If you could eat you
Confronted him
And you said hey Alex sounds
Mighty racers
He would say I'm just talking about illegal immigrants I'm not
Specifically say
What I mean
Unfortunately
A couple minutes later he takes
It's a call and things get a little too overt about what they mean by a grill
Warren in Ohio
Already Attica Ohio.
I can hear the stress in your voices and at your retina
Falling down and scraping the
Performance
Stroke
It's not
Under
The rules code regulation
Virtual contract
Because it's powered
Beat the land
You are
My ancestors
Talking too fast
Makes me think you might be staying at all
There
Care about her family
Close to
Espousing
Sovereign citizen freeman-on-the-land kind of
But never wants to
To use those words
Have you noticed any would look like an idiot if you overtly came out
Absolutely
So
Send to it
Tell me more about your ancestor was an aide-de-camp to Washington
While of course
Okay so first of all
Give me advice
We have very firm evidence he's like
Exactly what I said thank you for cutting through this whole illegal immigrant
Which is the problem for him trying to take some sort of position
Play like he wasn't
The second thing that clearly damaged
Straight to the
Uses words like
Illegal alien
And some stuff like that
His audience knows exactly what
This caller is fully demonstrated
She heard Mexican when he said that
Because that's what you meant
Responding the way you described
Shows
Me to get that one
AR stock
They're not free
Because
Birth certificate they have social
Security numbers letters everywhere around the flag
This is the beginning of a trend on the Zephyr
Episodes that I haven't seen before that make me
And it's quite frankly a bunch
People
Expressing
A bit of bitterness but also
Jealousy of illegal immigrants
Undertale
Create the perception
There's a free one
A tween
The noble white Sovereign citizens are the ones who are oppressed
It's hard it's hard to look at
Illegally to another country
You can do that
Touch our country
So we'll get back to that.
The theme that runs through
But Alex
Distracted
Back to this
I said something
Tell me what you want to say it's bad
It's just bad
Speech issue article Fox News
The word negro racial slur
Because what he is trying to say
Is that negro mean
Black
Spanish
Black Spanish
And what he accidentally says is not
Negro Blanco
Negro Anglo
So Alex
Hey hey hey hey
Didn't mean thing
Brave
Okay
In Europe
Community Serve the same rights
As Muslims and homosexuals
The scientific
Heterosexual homosexual
Well because something
Like you
We jump
And then it came out
And so that original
Piece of information
Alex
Why
You definitely
Classify the word retarded as inoffensive
I think it is an applicable
Because it's a things
You can make that is making a
Bullshiter
Play Everybody's Fine
Just your Venice
Don't be an ass
We get back
Don't be like
So let me tell you why this is the Holocaust adjacent
Holocaust revisionist denial is statement something going on
Soviet
Alright
I'm just trying to be racist
Really want you to know that the Holocaust it wasn't that bad I feel like I've explained
Not too long
Picture of
Denial
Is being done in service of a
Will find the crime
The Soviet you
Communist propaganda
Words that
Wait
It's close enough for jazz as they say
You staying
6 million diet ask
We know it was in the millions but not just
Because the Soviets
Kill 10 billion people
You just get mad at
Cyndaquil
Medium amount of juice
Yeah
Special Olympics
Piece of this
Who cares
But I was like
This idea that this guy Robin page
Getting arrested
Guarantee that
That is true and Alex will be born
Correct
Make sure everybody knows that I like
Correct this time
Guy is a sort of vague
Country traditionalist
Activists farming
Farmer
Her kind of activist guy and
Personality on the BBC
64 years of age back when this happen
He gave a speech
Gloucestershire
Alright
Classic suicide
Buddakan
Sign language
This guy
The trouble that he got in was because he gave the speech
Restart
If you are a black vegetarian Muslim asylum-seeking one-legged lesbian Lorry driver I want the same rights
VIP
Covid-19
The people
Complained about was this a GF
I'm trying to incite hatred
Towards these
Bingo does have laws
About that
First Amendment
Alex furnace to realize that all over the place
From this article in the telegraph
Express any concern
Time but a letter
Complaint was received later by the
The police and another person wrote to say
He disagreed with the remark
Robin and a further five months later was contacted at his farm
In Cambridgeshire and that's by two officers from gloucestershire
Interview
I ended up
Overnight
Prison because
Thea
It was
It's like trying to
Incite racial hatred
Little ambitious little
Capricious of the police will have you
And in the end he was exonerated
He got $2,000 for his trouble
A2000
You wrote is famous
Letters for Frampton on Hampton
County Jail
He did end up getting fired from his
Host
Later
News article
You found himself in hot water of a quote
Joke about giving contraceptives to immigrants in raisins
While a local liberal Democrat
We complain
Do the charities
Patient about a press release put out
By him
Through
So
There's been other racism
Because that's
How a bad word
Nicole
Cuckoo it's this guy has a pretty good track record of minimizing
Experiences
Non-white
Traditional farmers
And then also
Advocated for
Drug of the Moon all the time
Look in our world
That was very tame
Racist
People are very polite
Narwhal
The feeling of like
This isn't going to
He just
You just said that he wants to give immigrants
Contraceptives
That's Bush League that's horrible
Assuming sexual assault
Like it's an old white dude
Bombshell about
He is
Done a little about how he is jealous of
Because
Did you do a number one or number two
One who is wiping
I'm not sure
Holocaust
Revision
Apology
In a conversation defending the r word
I guess
Just to get Bingo on the scorecard for April 1st
He's got to have an interview with someone who thinks you don't have to pay taxes
How much are car is great to have you here with us
Thanks Leon I'm always glad to be here
So do you think the Tommy Cryer beat the IRS existed
This is very similar to
The last guy who
Quote
PIRA
What which guy was wasn't that a Project Camelot episode where they
The government
Meet 300,000
They always win
Actually technically win
Thought his case
Criminal case
And that was because
In order for him to be convicted of this crime
They had to be convinced
That he believed he had to pay taxes
It was willingly not doing that
He was able to prove in court or convince this journey that he actually didn't believe
They let him go
On a technicality
It doesn't reach the criminal statute
So now this is interesting.
Pacifica
You should know that
This episode is on April 1st
Tommy Cryer got back up in the irs's
A file to court something
The US Tax Court
He was trying to say that
You didn't
1.7 million dollars in taxes
From the years 1990
83 through 2001 that the IRS
Hey buddy
Yo that vine
Yeah they good day after this interview
He doesn't steal and on top of the world
Buckeye believes me
I'm going to go ahead and f*** with you
Convicted of criminal.
Bees puns
And tons of
Unpaid
He's filed its petition
And he said that there's a little bit of a discrepancy
The amount of the claim deficiency is
Disputed the correct amount
What is $0
No that's not true
Hey what time you cry or did was
Trying to get
Date delayed
Sweet kept pushing
Court date
And finally
The court granted him another delay
All the way up to that point
From early 2011
He was sort of going through like a petty I'll mail you a letter or tell you you're wrong
Kind of thing until little bit later
Baby a year-and-a-half
These delays
You got a delay and they rescheduled
October 22nd
That never happened
Because Tommy Cryer died on the
4th of June 2012
I don't know I'm not sure about that
Full list
To use
In order to move the tape
Court case
I don't know all that stuff
I don't know all that stuff but I do know
Only got off on
Going to prison
Because the courts
Jersey
Yogi believes it
Having
Bruschetta prison for that
I guess
Avenue
Push it back over and over and over and over
Feel like I remember
Think about laws
Not being a dick
I don't know where the line is but yeah
That might just be an ass
Ignorance of the law is no defense
Whatever
Possession is 9/10 of the law
This is my advice to everyone always go for a jury
It is all white and your black ass
Don't go
Episode we talked about how robbed
Other guy were down in Sacramento trying to get
Camp this
That sort of that sort of thing
Yu-Gi-Oh he's
Rob Rob
Come in here
Is that Alex
Keep saying that
He's filming this for his new documentary
Multiple times
Caesars like
Say that again
You know you're still doing the radio show here I know you want this documentary to shine but do this
This camera this time
Move your eyes we're going to give you a leading question
Use more or less doing
Is Rob.
Really reinforces my
But this story
Appeal to Infowars
Tony racial basis
That we've heard so much of
Imagine that
Loans
We didn't we did notice Hispanics in the sentence
Hispanic there's a couple
Illegal aliens around we actually didn't seem too many in that area
At all
These illegal immigrants we've already established Alex believe means Mexican they know they're doing
They are the game the system
All these houses and riding around in these awesome cars
Who's the coolest
Is this
Is it like the scene from Heat
Where's Lex
You know what
Outside
I were so no ice
You do it but I respect you know I don't think so I think it's
Beautiful reality in order to Foster
Feelings of jealousy and
Anger towards minorities
Yes
Probably the best way to put
That is
That is exactly what that is and of course
Narrative
Oh yeah
April 1st
Got some breaking news on some of the gross things
Rising back and forth
They are devaluing the dollar
Global Currency
Who's at the news is admitting you should buy gold stocks
Credible
Get that gold gone
When's the first
I feel like that sure was
Looking like looking back on it I felt like
There was so much
Alex started
New comedy with
The queen stuff like that
Truth and comedy
Adele close
Try to talk about something funny
Giraffe
Amanda's tax protest
A guy is just a
About slick I've not heard a ton of times when there's been like
Fairly consistent feelings of
Jealousy
Towards
Immigrant
And stuff like that before you wrinkle I don't know where that's coming from
But it is definitely the same
Place the other immigrant narratives
The listening to him
But I
I didn't know what to
To do with it until I was glad
I didn't think there was a ton of
Is what I'm saying
There's just a lot of Gristle
Bill Hicks
Maybe he's actually Mort saw newspaper
I feel like
Could be
I didn't feel like there was meat there
But thankfully I feel like as we get to April 2nd
There's a little bit more meat
April 2nd
Super excited
But before we get to that we have to see the trend
Continue from April 1st to April 2nd
Realize that more and more Fox News personalities
Or sounding like him
F****** pisses him off
It's true all we can talk about
New world
By admitting I want apologies
Certainly not out of any of those assholes
Turn on the TV
Do apologize
Alex Jones
We just wanted you to get there on your own we didn't want you to feel like the establishment had your back
Your voice could not be created it if you felt like anyone supported you so weird
Make you stronger
That sort of thing
Even more of these
Personality
You take Target at 4
Starting to sound like me
Avocado
I accidentally got too involved in the late nineties when I had nothing
Just talks about how
You've got a sense
What's to come
Martial law
With physical Force
We bust our butts to expose the terrorists program
Didn't happen
Must have busted your butt
They must've really busted their ass for real
Also I always love it when I hear Alex Bay
It hit me like a ton of bricks last night
This thing I say all the time
It was a tsunami of information
That would be like me getting on the show be like Jordan
I need to tell you last night I had a
Breakthrough
Alex Jones
Is that cool
Holyshit sky
Is if we bust our butts
I'm trying
Alex
Is not
The level man I didn't realize realize
This guy's got here will you know when I woke up the other day
I was just
Blown Away
I don't think this shaded gold salesman is on the up-and-up
No
No Doubt
3 years later
Figuring that out
State of Minnesota figure that s*** out
They are the
The state of Minnesota is correct
So
I told you I found
Real juice
Real good
Richard Nixon
Was that
Pink
Cuz you're going to hear the content of the clip
Talk about
It's not how I'm going to flex on this year
I have talked to multiple Hollywood people in Austin
Crazywise
I remember 10 years ago on Erlanger
Pleasure
People thought I was crazy
Play believer
Animals
They secretly
Who am I
I want I was listen to figure out what it was
Just be the p
Got2b
Oouu in Hollywood who's a member of PETA
No
God damn it I mean
Something I don't know what to go on Alex's totally right
They do sacrifice
Something from the center
Commercial
Consumer research
It's interesting
Remix
I'm about this report about Pete
Consumer research
Because it doesn't
It comes from the center for consumer
Freedom
One simple instant of Alex
Speaking but I don't think it is
For a number of reasons
The first is at the center for
Consumer research is a real thing
That's a legitimate
It's run out of UC Davis
Consumer attitudes towards food safety and they follow academic guidelines with their work
Professional Outlet
The story about Peter with that organization lens
Is it credibility
On the other hand
The center for Consumer freedom
Is it comes from
Full source
The center for Consumer freedom is not a research Outlet
It's a front group for a lobbyist
Bourbon is known in many circles as the quote AstroTurf
Because the way he does business is
Turn the front groups to create The False Image
Support for various things he's loving
Make it look like you're coming
From the Grassroots
As opposed to the actual giant corporate clients who pay his bill
Literally creating
Page
Interesting
Chiasso
Even told his corporate client
Quote we run all of this stuff for nonprofit organizations that are insulated from having to disclose donors
There's total anonymity
People who don't know who supports us
We've been doing this for 20-something years in this regard
Answer the degrees to anyone
Is concerned about that I will tell you
There are all sorts of ways
The firewalls that have been established
To get this done on an anonymous basis
I'm religious about not allowing company names to ever get used
At least I'm not going to allow them to get
Get used and I don't want companies to ever admit that because it does give the other side at wait
To diminish our
18 literally a James Bond villain
He thought speech
There's no problem
No one will ever know what hahaha
Plant
Search business owners
Does make them
Feel like okay well we're never going to get
That's one of the things you have
Assure them if you want
Get them
Give you that dirty ass money
You guys want to do so
Guess what
No one's going to know about if you give your buddy
Original group was called the guest choice
Gucci specifically started
To create the appearance
He was representing Restaurant Group
When in reality he was working for Philip Morris to buy
What is well
Communications Philip Morris's program manager for public affairs Barber
Clearly laid out his strategy
If externally perceived is driven by restaurant
There'll be more flexibility allowed benefits by Philip Morris
9 months after their founding Philip Morris attorney bharti Berrington Road
USA is still the only contributor
The promise others
They were the sole people behind
Philip Morris
Tobacco
Maurice gave Birdman over $600,000 that year.
Grassroots opposition to the
He doesn't have a ton of Indus
He organized the employment policies Institute to attack unions
Initiatives to raise the
Minimum wage
But it's funded by money from the restaurant and hotel in
He organized the American Beverage
The fight against drunk driving laws
Which predictably is financed by the alcohol
This is all Rick Berman does
He creates organization
Official sounding names
To serve the interest
A big business
That is it
Can scam you got to give it to
Great
The millions of dollars
It doesn't seem like
I mean you got to create a shell company
Relationship
Creating your own University degree
With the lawyer
No no no no no
In this case if you do it wrong you're going to prison
Right
But you don't need someone else
To help you
Make a fake diploma
Do that on your own
In this case you need
Other countries
In 2002 the guest Choice Network renamed itself the center for Consumer freedom and a lot of its focus
Safety organizations
It's a surprise no one that the list of donors included hundreds of thousands of dollars
From Monsanto Cargill in Tysons
Food it should also surprised no one that they received over $100,000
From the coke like foundations
The donors trust donors Capital fund
As well as over $600,000 from the Bradley
The foundation was founded by Harry Bradley
Who interesting Lee was a founding member of the John Birch Society along with Fred Koch father of Charles and
Because Brothers
These are very startling connections but leaving those aside the reason
For Center forever
Consumer freedom
To attack Peter is very clear
Outcry about factory farming
4 years
Any particular was
Huge Target
Rid of Tyson Food
Whose cruelty been exposed by Peter multiple time
This is the perfect articulation of his
Strategy
2007 interview with 60 minutes
Where you said that it is
Approach to shoot the messenger
Instead of addressing
Disgusting animal cruelty conversation into attacking
Bwahahaha
Every single f****** sense
He said it should end with
Wahahaha
You f****** Super Bowl
Story about Peta killing animals
Particularly
Evil organization
Valid criticism
Cat makeup
Capito another places
The reason the numbers that they sent a consumer
More freedom is able to
Bestop birth animals
Peter killed the reason that it's so high that year
Is it they were called
Policeman in North Carolina
The ton of animals were being
And killed at shelters
There but it's very inhumane ways
For instance being Gaston metal boxes or shot with 22 handgun
Peta came and assess the situation and provided more Humane euthanasia methods
At no cost
They assessed the alternative
Handling the animals creating an actuary
The only viable option
For most of the animals
We're sick neglected
Read severe aggression
Problems
I would love to live in a world where no animals were put to sleep
But I also recognize this
Severe over
Population problem for dogs
Cattleman's country
Now I'm miserable sick animals life would be
One of those places
Shot in the head
I'm not thrilled with animals or anything like that but I'm also not to do
Like
Closed-minded or short-sighted to think that it's intrinsic
When you haven't
Situation where it's like
There is nothing
Can do to help
Hannibal that's going to live in
Yeah that's
This is reality in that article put out
Consumer freedom
It's clear what
Rick Berman is paid
DeSantis corporate clients
You don't want to have to
Pabor to do their dirty business
Peta makes it difficult for his big food client
To keep abusing animals
To keep overhead love you being paid big bucks to Target them with propaganda
No nuance
Alex Jones is literally passing off Pro corporate interest propaganda is research on his show
The fact that he says
Visit from the center
A consumer research
Leads me to suspect that he was trying to muddy the waters
And make it more difficult for his listeners
To realize that what he was doing
Was repurposing corporate propaganda
On his show
I expect that
I can't prove it
You know
There is a world that exists where he just misspoke
Incidentally
It doesn't
Wasn't
To cover up the idea that this is information that's coming out of a
Barely
Easy to get to the bottom of
Corporate shill
Yeah that's clearly not a real thing
So I'll just say the real thing
Yeah so is listeners are left in the dark now for the fun
A little part it should be noted
Four things that Alex is absolutely ago
In addition to having taken their money in 20s
16 that you worked as a
Consultant for Monsanto
Specifically about how to make your GMOs more appealing
To the public
So he's like he's like that one we talked about
Propaganda
F****** soldier-of-fortune
Like he just
Maybe we should
Concerta Consulting Group will come up with propaganda
I will just have all this s*** for like
Sopita
Disclose their donors
And then we'll put
I feel like that's not the plan that I really know
Nevermind
I'm going to back away for
Alex is doing this
Anywhere
Elpida isn't
Use against
I guess
I'm not sure why
I guess that's the only thing I can see
Did you just look at them external associate them with more less
I guess but I don't know exactly why he's
Queer
Example of
Affront
Corporate propaganda
That's funded by
The Koch brothers
Monsanto
Tyson Foods
And
Foundation do
Who founded by
Friends with Fred Coqui burger and was a founding member of the John Birch Society
All of this together it's
Very
It just keeps coming up doesn't weird
Weird
I don't think they're good people
No they're not they're actually bad
People like
Like not but not level
They're almost a shadow
Ball of
I wonder if
Discord info
Foment
Muddy Waters
And destroy
And make impotent
True social change
I know baby that's the conclusion the stock has will eventually come to you
Corporatist
We're just talking about stealing
There's no
There's no larger picture to it
Necessarily
What we can we can say for sure is it looks like these are real bad
People people that
They're not nearly as bad
Is everyone who works at
They pressured
He's been to parties
What are you not cool
I guess
Haven't gotten invited
Like a day after they're all I know
Alex
Make a call here
This takes us back
April 1st a little bit with some
Comfy like
Go back to Tom Tom
Yeah I think you made a really good point about the illegal alien
Earlier in the show about how
That they
They are truly free
Innocence that
You know they have
Tower family structures
I think Tom is listening to show on a day delay or something like that you must be listening to yesterday
Sorry
And they're rejecting
These are mechanisms of control that that the American people that the citizens of the United States of America open the Excel
Nnnn
How to install two exhaust
Driver's license or insurance
Cite your sources
98%
Even under Obama
Actually especially
We increase
The number for
Black mark Autobahn
It's demonstrable enochtrue what he saying
Given credit for the things that we judge
Like people who are
Ostensibly closer
To being on his side
I hate him for everything but at least we got rid of a lot of
Implicit division
Between illegal immigration and citizen
Not
Who is this
Isn't it
Clearly a racial division
That is what you talkin about other terminology
Very very
So frustrating because it looked the reality is
With all the
Staggering about but if at the end
His presidency
He finally passes
Is 100% Medicare for all
We have to be like
Spock
Got to give him that
Peterbilt that but I don't I don't think I don't think
Undoes
The scales are think yeah
Obama's
Right right
Deportation
May I agree
Things that are good
You can't help
Has been talkin about
You'll recall
Popular Mechanics
Get out
Set this next Monday
He's going to
The internet rumors that are going around
So immediately Alex's
Response was
Preemptively debunk is debunking
Because I know what he's going to say
Yeah I'm going to get ahead of the game
He keeps saying he's going to do it
I will get down to the wire now
And in this next clip he realizes
He still hasn't done that yet
And he needs to do it because he said he's going to do it preemptively
And there's less
Power if you put it out
After the fact
Course because he's not psychic
What are meeting about how we got to get to work done
Do it
About the Holocaust
Ever had an offer production ever
But I will do it
I need you both here an hour early tomorrow
Our meeting before tomorrow
Cabot f****** now
This implies that they never have
Oh my God
Tomorrow and I
Demonstration all the way
And then launch it hours before
Expose him
I should have launched earlier this week
Your honor
Huron Arrow
Alex
Alex brought are the real victim
Maryland
Fishing trips going to have to wait kids sorry about that
Hilarious bomber
I have to hate Glenn Beck
We listen to the
Wow
If it's any consolation
I'm not going to do that work actually
An Irish coffee
We can't go fishing
That's good fun
But a little bit later the show Alex
Call
Prima guy
Who would try to call into Sean Hannity Show
And plug the Obama
You get on the show and he starts talking about the bomb
Deception
Hang up on it
I got to jump or whatever cuz he doesn't want
Give free plugs and Free Press
Somebody else
This guy calls into Alex show
To talk about
Sean Hannity Show for plug
Alex's
Alex has a very interesting take on it
That he would never say
Right
Delayed because
Call Danette Deadpool at the liberal-left
Left Right wacker
Left left
Maintain control
As soon as soon as I heard myself come live on the show
Radio
Trinity.
Start the next caller so I didn't
No one got really got to hear it
Sean Hannity
YouTube correctly octopus
Imagine the Sean Hannity
Start a website in Westport on it became incredibly popular they were
Probably one of the most popular
Politics in order to get
But that's not
Texas Giant message board
Alex's
Lion Air
Clearly
Do you have the right to kick people off that message board
Alex
He does think that the government is directing Google to do it
But I honestly think
That is just his way of getting around this
Like a champ you know I don't I don't take this call 100%
Does Wales like
Well in order for this to appear to be sent
I must believe the government is secretly behind.
Understanding what it is
RECenter
Also
In this episode
Confesses to us
A numerous
I killed another guy
Oh really
Eliza baby paragraph
Boo Alex
Show up an hour early regularly but okay
Call.
You show start
Exit 11 man it's not like you got to wake up at 6 to get in there like nobody's morning show guide
I mean their lives
As far as the 48
Go to bed at like 7
Another fun
A joke
Turn off there's the last one
2009 episode Alex
Just played the entire song
And is next clip from April 2nd
Video
If we fight back.
For all of you out there who are fighting
And
Alright
Hey hey where are you
That's tough that's alright
This one goes out to you
Terrence
89 North
Play all of the rent
Terrence in Torrance
Are you crazy
Can you play that song and its entirety twice on
Talking song
And that
I got a lot of work to do
I got to call my wife
And tell her to tell the kids I'm not going
Play Mackenzie realizes he's got to get ahead of it
Time goes by
He has.
Another little block a call
Dismiss call witch
I really think
I know we don't play too many calls
He is on the show
Just a couple Clips backwards
Jealous of the
Illegal immigrants Ohio
George Washington
Haha
I think we do a pretty good job of giving across back
Section of Alex's College
Gemstone better kind of boring
Certainly.
Not worth
Looking at or anything like that or not unfair at all
This next clip if I only played this it would be unfair
If I played Just
This call
It would be painting the picture that all of Alex Jones
The callers are
Totally crazy
At the same
Time
This call is not far out of the Main Street
Super unfair with me
Just play calls like this
But this is business.
Let's go ahead and talk to Maureen and Virginia you're on the air
Hey how are you
I got something
First of all
You for everything
Can you do
So much
Did it said apps
Let me sign
Scary
We need to remember
We serve the most
Most high God
These other idiots
Exerting
He only took
One-third of the angels with him it's going to be a
Two Against One
Fight
Pictures of this battle
Who won at the Alamo
Since You Beyonce
We have
Partner
10 cm
Eclipse
Studio
It's the same thing as in that interview with Rob
Stuff like that
George Humphreys
Cold Asian people Oriental Ono
You quotes Friday Night Lights
The Open Heart
Listen I'll tell you this right now
State and got out of there and he had
Still did it
Clear Eyes
Demonheart
Doesn't matter if you're white black Oriental clear a code
Stuff from the apartment
As I was listening to it I was just
Like it was all just
He said
It doesn't give me much hope
The new film
Groundbreaking
The same thing
I understand correctly
George Humphrey interviews
For this new documentary also in the original movie
Go to Sacramento to
Write about a homeless encampment
Evil Dead 2 worth basically a remake
The first documentary
I suspect
I haven't watched it yet
Quality
I don't
You know why because I mean compared to
I don't think it will be because
We're going to try this one more
Lester
Footage
The Blair Witch
Billy try to f*** with Glenn Beck
Oh man how great would it be if his kids had already cancelled on him going fishing
Create this whole psychodrama
I was trying to find a way to turn
Extinct
They've sold their fishing rod by him the proof Glenn Beck's a liar
I don't know
Shards of magic
Interesting I think this episode is
Oversold
Cirrhosis
Protesters
Receive the friends of fox
Becoming more like him
You getting f******
Pissed off
Glenn Beck
Because that works that's
Talked about him in the past about how he's a snake in the grass and I'll do that
Sean Hannity
All these people coming and being
Two similar to
They're exploiting by Revenue Street
The clear evidence that he's just sort of funneling corporate propaganda
Botanica come
From somewhere else
Tickles me to no end
Deezer
Like surprising and
When you think about it incredibly obvious
He would notice before
The rest of the car
Realize that Fox News was becoming info
Steven wanted
Is revenue the rest of us
Crazy
We didn't realize that they were
Taking their first step along
Dabney
It is like one of the only insightful moments
We'll see we'll see how this all works out I am very
Most liked a lot of this being about the queen
How she shed
Call Larry Nichols confirmed
I'd rather not too late
I do feel like a
I'm enjoying I'm enjoying April
I hope
2009 April
Feeling pretty good
For all of you who are out there to celebrate it Merry Christmas
To you and yours Indie of those
You don't happy holidays
Whatever
For those of you who don't have any holidays right now
Kohl's
But
If there was a giant message board
That was an alligator stew the one that Sean Hannity
Kitty created
Analogy
We are on
Call Johanna download subscribe
We will be back
Next time
I would like
Lauren from Ohio hasn't killed anybody
You killed somebody
The clear on murder
Look messed up you have no evidence that she's ever killed anybody and irresponsible accusation
So at this point any further Evidence
Lauren from Ohio
Technically probably has
That's out
Alexandra Thurston color my huge fan I love your work