Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Beverages and talk a little bit
About Alex Jones
Most work you ever had to do to get a bottle
Get out of scrapes
I don't know I've gone to the store to buy a bottle of wine
I have to be in this question
What's
Farthest you've gone
To get alcohol what is like when you have you been in this
Hundreds of times when I've liked walked
Hours
And then but it's only because I never found it
Especially around the area we are in uptown Chicago
There's so many places that close super early so you have this idea that if you just go five more blocks you find someplace
I've done that a number of times
In the past few years
Just walking around for like an hour and a half
I got to give up
Where is Lackey High School
I I found booze pretty easily when I thought they started
Just go and people rarely apartment
An issue and I started hanging out at the gutter Punk bar
I worked at a gas station
My work are they all the food
Never really a problem
Beard is a cheat code to a
Yeah since you were nine you've been 21
Yeah kind of I mean I didn't start drinking until
I don't know
Baby 16:7
No no but I I didn't
Write me a little while to get to the point
Sorted out
Full force
Like I've the first time I drank
Because
One of my friends
And this is the links that we had to go to Bowie
If I want to tell the story
I have to go I have to I had to go a long way to find it
Pacific bottle of wine
But this is
Childhood as far as buying
One of my friends still
Jack
From the rec center
Town of the rec center have Jack Daniels
Is it need to be
How did he know
How did he steal first
The filing cabinet
Snitched on the bottle
Alright
We just essentially drinks
So my first time drinking like in Earnest was at a park
Of course everybody's
Usually when you're that age to go to a park
Mine was an addict but okay
I was hanging out with my friend from Mike a life group
Right right we would sort of us end of the small group
Yeah and Aaron
Parents liquor cabinet
And they had
We took a bottle of wine bottle red wine a bottle of peppermint schnapps and we went to the park
We're drinking because we were so young and dumb we decided to mix them together
Done with that remix them together
Disgusting
Make matters worse
Freezing out
In the middle of a cold park with the wine and schnapps
Rent-A-Center
Find it he stole it
As he told
ICICI
To get not the actual drink
God I hate you
Fine
You know what I love and
People who are supporting the show
First of all
Boy this one is tough to pronounce
But I'm going to say it
Thank you so much you are now policy
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you for the
Quick
Nesquik
How much further are we going to go no further
I'm a policy wonk
Make a call
Appreciate that so very much so April
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much April
Appreciate it
Today's business
I think it is important for us to take a little second
To give a special message
Out there too
Who's that
Zapped
Because out there driving around believe this morning from what I hear
Celebrating a birthday
What's the farthest you ever going to get into
6 miles
Thank you so much for listening to the show happy birthday to you
Least let us the message we all wish you
Public information
Like we have a weird
Amy Jordan the only thing we can do is
Sing Happy Birthday
Cool.
Almond eyes
Happy birthday
Happy birthday hope you have a great one
Jordan
What's today's business
Wacky Wednesday
Wild Wednesday or weird
Because sometimes it's not all that wacky are we married to the alliteration
Can we just call it but you're really like it out of the ordinary
That's a little bit clunky
You don't know shitt I was almost in the Honolulu police choir
Music teacher I've been involved
Music
Cooper Suites
That's right
Musical theater
Cool the greatest of Art Club
I was in a musical
Merced Junior High Middle School
Breeders ago in Community Theater don't want to talk about it
Just turned out to be a heavy Wednesday apparently
Certain additional episode a lot of stuff about Project Camelot
Obviously the Reverend batting coach Dave
Jim Bakker I'll certainly keep an eye on him four times we can talk about him
Some people about stuff that's
Might fit into that fold and
Keep my eyes open
Looking for possibilities.
But also like I said
I think it is also a perfect place for us to
Fulfill time travel request request
And honoring of the wish of one George Soros Junior
Why do you point
Because
Is your Doctor Who
And that means today is Wednesday I like it
Thank you very much
Duration everything
I have no idea
It absolutely not
Vander Soros
Anyone related to Soros
I'm pretty sure I'm telling you the Kennedys
Head one of their kids
Right I got an update on that
We laughed about that
George Soros Junior got in touch with me
Fanza
Wanted to know about
What Alex Jones talked about
The Ebola outbreak
In 2014
Which
You are
You're in a mood
Unnecessary response
Outbreak
Somebody
Outbreaks
West Africa
Largely
Eventually spread to Sierra Leone in Liberia
Lie.
I was particularly hit hard
Is ended up getting taken
Kantaros and then getting worse
Baby got worse how you judge that
Sierra Leone in Liberia were declared free of Ebola and then work 8
Intel 2016
All of it ended
Internet
Right
Community
People that made a lot of money
Out of the CIA was on the rise.
McNabb 2014 particularly
Pretty serious
In September
2014 is when things got to be like
Getting outside
And there was a case in the United
The first case
Dallas
Actually
On September 30th
Because George Soros Junior gave me such vague
I don't be missed judgemental
Give me a vague idea of where to go to
I was like okay
The first case is in Texas
Freak out about that but it still got to be like
On the 30th
I'm going to October 1st
F****** freak Out Show
Right
Is almost always the case
No
This is weird Trend that I've noticed from these time travel request the people make
Alex is almost never in studio in big news break
Whatever the pope resigned he was on vacation and David night with hosting
When the Ebola outbreak happened in case in Texas
He's on vacation to Paul Joseph Watson toast
So I found the first episode where Alex
Back from vacation after there was a case in the United States in Texas
Of someone with Ebola
Happens to be October 5th
That is absolutely going over today
Specifics of
The actual outbreak
That's stop along the way
But it is actually
Sing a lot of this
Mangle on it
Try to predict both of them
There's a lot to learn along the way to
I feel like this is also one of
Time travel episode Trends where it's like
Whatever it was that you are asking
For the goddess to the time-travel
We wind up talking about everything but that
Play yeah yeah
It is it still out
Because he's recharged from vacation
And then another piece of my heart
Could be another part of it might be that this is also a Sunday
October 5th is a Sunday show
Feels like pressure
His career that was still
Much more of a lucrative things
Tokyo
Genesis Communications
I'll tell you why I chose October
Emporium
I was going to try and be like
Hey here's
Do you know why it is
That could have happened in another universe is how this episode start
But in this universe that starts with us playing out of context dropped
It's
Okay
It's so crazy it's so crazy to me
He does
These things with like
Masculine
He has it from both sides
Like you want
He wants
Every part of the Buffalo of making you feel things about masculine
Attack the masculinity like football
It's very confusing
I don't know
And masculine as masculine being in his conception
And in terms of that I don't care to be like
You like football
Let's do let's go
To this episode
Here's how the episode start
With Alex introducing the topic of
Ebola
Infowars.com
Americans
Does not open up
The phone to another phone
Minutes after this so badly
I don't remember
McCain
Ebola
I read it on
So a lot of feelings about this situation
I'm certain you can
I don't want to put you on the spot
Alright
Here is
Here is mine.
Alright
Now it's any good if you're right
If you're wrong
Should still be applicable
Far away that was close to where we started yet
So he's closer to early 2015 investigation Alex
Then other versions of Alex that is a metric
Go for it
Here's the facts
1850s comedy writer that is repurposing
I am 100% certain that this is Obama's fault
That there's going to be a lot of racism
Because it's
In Africa
Walk the same time he's going to
Pretend
He is a crusader
For a
Freaking people make sure that everybody got to be a little bit of that about black people
Veiled but it certainly there
Genetic
Diseases and
Is it Africa
Because they know you won't care about that time the guy lands in Dallas
That's how we know that they're beginning
Jordan you just got to be on your final exam
You couldn't possibly expect
It's better also part of his narrative like this
MSNBC headlines
NRA is making me ebola crisis worse
Good job
With Ebola in Texas
That's what the federal government does
Finally found out what the federal government
Federal Aviation
Road
He lost
Look the federal government can fly planes whenever they want
The sky
He hates Rick Berry.
Videos like
Would you eat
Do is
Facebook
Rick Perry isn't being aggressive enough
That's
Deficiency of Obama
Because the flight
That's a federal
And by the way
But also we see this introduction of this news story
But the NRA is making
Alice's bucking not happy about that
Statistics
If you continue to think about it you're like
I don't want to throw them on this
Deana Ray can't possibly
Zebolek
I don't think they're actively going out and giving people
Who wouldn't otherwise get Ebola
About we will find out exactly what this article is about as soon as Alex actually talked about it
But for now he's just complaining about a headline cuz he hasn't read the article spoiler alert
But
And how that's involved
Paralyzed
Like a boss
Halloween party
Cowboys
Bollywood do you mean
Complained
No.
Shut it down
Wearing a suit previous fight
Even
Truck slides down
Countries where their estimated 1.4 to 5 million people
Will get Ebola
Discord
So did this PC culture is stopping us
I'm talking about this as it really is in the same way
Don't use them
That is
A good rule of thumb
I don't know about this yoga studio because it sounds a lot like
That
Cap that
Those things that the yoga studio people are talking about how like
We can't have a fun India party
That sounds exactly like the side characters in the Nazi hat
Halloween weather like
Terrible
Come on Alex wouldn't you be so offended if a black person dressed up as chicken fingers and fries
Install your culture
Like millions of people are going to
Also
He eventually does end up saying
Hundreds of thousands
The people have it
He's going to say that
I want to tell you
When it was all over
In 2016
2016 Guinea was officially declared Ebola Free
28600 people
Total
Total got Ebola
Liberia
Sierra Leone
Mali Nigeria
Italy
The United Kingdom there was a case there a couple people in Spain Senegal
The US
Can we just
Say real quick that's amazing against vaccines
Even then
And if you are against vaccine
System of
Rooting out disease if that's
The total number people got it
Now
Especially over a
2-year plus timeframe to be like Holy Ship
It could have been way worse than they were 11,000
325 death
Out of those 20
Witches
Super Idol I don't know
There are times in history where it's like
North of 90
Percent
You are
Remember I was looking at the statistics
It turns like a country-by-country breakdown
This 2014
It's some countries there was a 0% fatality rate
Percent
Before it ended up getting it
I don't think the numbers were even
Super 40 is right around the total
Just extrapolate from there it is lower than some outbreaks
That being said
That's amazing and
And anybody
You like Alex
Bitching about it
All this
Is the worst thing that
Could ever happen
Should also at the end of 22
16 say
Got to give it up to him
That's f****** amazed
We expect in 2014
Results
But
Him saying that they're like hundreds of thousands of people who have Ebola in 2014
But at the end of it
It's just north of a quarter of 100,000
At the end of it
Blowing this way out of proportion
You think that
The United States
Particular
Trees other than
Arcgis
To make sure that the stuff
Become a problem
The Arab country
Sierra Leone Liberia and other areas
Academic level
By the end of the year
That's not what they're saying there aren't there were like all these
Sites that were given
Terrible worst case scenario is
So he's using it all these other countries
Due to these travel bans on people
Affected countries
And United States
Won't do that
And that's f***** up
Give me aftermath of an outbreak it makes total sense to think that the solution is closing down borders and restricting travel to countries where
Is that particular medical issue exist
Closer look at history all you see is evidence of these travel ban
Don't work make things worse and are stupid Miss allocation
That doesn't sound right
1987 people with HIV or Aids Coming to America
This did nothing to restrict
Spread of the disease
The conditions
And in 1989 impractical costly
Full anime
Discriminatory
The study found the Travelers played little to no role in the spread
But efforts toward prevention and actual difference
Beyond that they found its green Travelers 4-H ivna
Was all good and well but the process wasn't
Musically flawed
It would inevitably lead to negative positive and vice versa
Beatley pointless
This infected until Obama got in office
I'm really glad
That we
We learned our
Realized
The travel bans were
And never again tried to
No no
87 Reagan football
And we don't even really even remember that
After 2008
It's crazy
It's crazy because it's absolutely not
Athx out in terms of like what you'd expect kind of
I didn't think
We were that
It wasn't until Obama's administration
Anybody was like
We should care
About you
Maybe the government
Specifically like hiv-positive even all the way through it what I like with Clinton
Commenter about Asia
And you don't expect W to do anything positive
Ever
Yeah
Social evolution
Some good progress being made being under W progress and stuff
You're never going to see that mirrored up top
No Doubt
Anyway it's a bummer
Also
After some cases of H1 N1 in Mexico in 2009 many countries cut off lights to and from the come
There's a 40% decrease in Mexican travel volume
A study after the fact found the quote own that only led to an average delay in arrival of the infection another car
Countries is the first
Imported case
Of Less Than 3 days
And they found quote no containment was achieved by such restriction
So there's a consistent pattern that
That shows that all you're doing is putting things off by a couple days in service of what
I think
And I'm
I'm sure that this did not affect
Thorsten, Oregon
It's almost like it
Positive things
Made destitute
So many places
Is that red light on that
We're going to get you some of those like issues it actually kind of minimal
Hemorrhagic fever
Finances
That belongs in the calculus but it's
Craft if it matters more than people fly
About it and your absolute
Of the actual travel ban
Put in place in response to the outbreak of Ebola sound
The bands are only delaying the further International spread Ebola outbreak in West Africa for a limited time
At the risk of compromising connected
Mobilization
Enough resources
To the affected area
Sustained response operation
All actions
Critical value to the immediate local control of the vola
And for preventing its further geographical
Spread so all you do is end up sacrificing
The idea of people being mobile to stomach
Text Dad for the sake of
Some imaginary lockdown
For a lockdown that doesn't make any sense
Well
Not allocating any resources
To the treatment that would help a lot of
To do but it's not
Not only does it not work historically fit it actually hurts things for two important in Turkey
The first is that it's not really a reality that you're ever going to be able to shut down all travel across borders
Borders are cute
And people who really want
To badly enough they want to leave
Don't find Pachel and I can slip across the border
It's going to happen
But you're never going to be able to completely insulate some
This leads to the second problem
If you travel for people from the affected region
You create an incentive for these people to lie about where they're traveling
From which a variable you could monitor
Wheatley on the counter
Studies that show that this is the case
Alex did not know this means that he's not operating from a position of wanting what's best for the world he's just looking for any
Any excuse confined to let Africa burn
The idea is
When you do these
These sorts of things
Like I said there is lying
There's someone is from let's say Guinea
And they make it across a couple Borders or whatever
Perhaps they may also have it
They're not showing they're not they could slip into another country like
Weather from
Be able to travel because that country
Where they they are coming from
Isn't
Included in this band and what you do
Is
You're not able to
I know it sounds ugly and Turf
Flag them
But when you have an outbreak
It is in everyone's best interest to like if you are traveling from that country
We need to know
We don't want to hurt you you we need to be able to keep an eye just in case maybe we
Terrible
Which
Kim do
If you allowed to travel but
If you
Shut that everything down close all borders
What you do is
Incentivize breaking
Of the Courant
Prohibition
Does it work
Yeah level don't work out there over and over and over
If you want to quarantine something very small
Person in hospitals it does work very effective
It also relies heavily on
Incredibly important piece of
Quarantine
Yeah but if you want if you want
How willing are you to kill someone who's going to leave
But you want to turn this into a
Or whatever like that is the other piece
Yeah like
If you do want to do that
Okay your conception is
X area
Is shutdown
Because there was a baller
If someone tries to leave
Do you murder them
Do you kill them because
If they get out someone else might have
If it is
We have a different conversation to have
Right
Bite my big point is the Alex
Understand that
Travel bans don't really work
Example of
Do UK shutdown travel to
Of course
Ayodhya
There's a bunch of countries that ended up
If not
It's not affect
It's Alex's
Very weird
You're 100 years ago
Ellis Island
Come on, I'll come
You you had just the right response to that
Positively that Ellis Island with his firmly anti-immigration positions that
All the time
We all know the reason why he speaks about Ellis Island as a positive thing is because of the immigrants coming in other one teeth
Goodwin
Stupid
Think about it
These people came over here on Ocean Center
The tens of thousands
Thousands of was not an uncommon thing.
If two-thirds of them were turned away where would they f****** go
Are you going to incarcerate all those people how much do you think that would cost are you going to pay for ships to take them back to wherever they came from
How much you think that would cost Animal Crossing
Crossing the sea
I'll tell you what you should shut down the government to make sure that it doesn't happen
Reality only 10% of the people who arrived at Ellis Island
Health screening
And 90% of those people were passed through with
According to Berry Monero
Ellis Island historian the Ellis Island Museum
The people charged with rooting out Communists anarchist
Impossible labor Edge
That was a very high priority in their screening interviews
Mental Asylum very missed his real
Calling because of his name is Barry Manilow he should have been the greatest jazz artists of his age
Most immigrants who came through Ellis Island
They're processed through they got through Ellis Island
Generally
Generally 25 hours
Came up in their their history
Etched on them before they came
Is there a criminology
But if you forgot
Process
They got a dormitory and provided
Now obviously doing so good back then
It was a perfect Cinderella Castle wasn't treated all that well but still like if you look back on it
Really better than what's going on now
Let's do good
Bananas
You know how many immigrants
I know that Alex says that it's
66% how many go away 23
Phone number is 2%
Court Vincent cannot associate professor of history at the University of Massachusetts Boston
And author of the American package
Search the history of Ellis Island
Quote
The greatest contradiction or irony here
Can processed meat have this restriction ascent
And all these people you want to keep out of the country
Less than 2%
It's a very small number of people who got rejected
Even with
Medical issues being considered
One of the things you know like
This one here there's like a
1000 people who got rejected
He wasn't for hepatitis or whatever Alex
Thanks
Condition
Close
Chlamydia
Contagious
One of the easiest
Detectable thing
A lot of
I probably would have made it
That look about you
So you got 1,100 people
Mass in one year
300000 people that came
Over a million at least one or two
Years
It's not
Obviously Ellis Island
Perfect
Story of great success
But Alex
Perpetuate this idea
Through everybody
To a past that doesn't
And he's only doing it in service of
Trying to
I think what it is if I had to
I think he doesn't know any
Number one
Emotional
For it is
Justifying why those white
Immigrants
Are good
Not based on their skin
But I think I think so
Come down to the logistic
Incarcerate
So much
Because even if you were incarcerated him eventually what he had to send it back
So what do you send them back immediately
Italy to pay for it
And there's no easy answer to it may think
The people in charge
Recognize
Is that an aired on the side of
Feel like
All right let's do like
Legit Danes
Probably only take us a couple hours per person
We have it we have the ability to do this alright has a lot of nails coming out
And we have not made Hellraiser yet so I can't I can't process
Freedom 10 hours for a bit I found that to be really fascinating I didn't know
Was that low
Something I always enjoyed
Help me learn a little
We get back to the show
Alex's show
And Alex has
Do you have some ideas of
Houses
Handle
The case of the gentleman who came to
Dallas
That was my favorite Hardy Boys book
The case of the gentleman came to Dallas
I wish I could have gone with Encyclopedia Brown
Listen
We could name the Texas all day we really could I got a few I got to Tara
Furniture in my boot
This guy came
Dallas
Shut up
Shutdown
That's on me
My friend
I don't know how to start this. I want to see how this goes
Has some ideas
Is about the handling of
The circumstance
Cuz of the Ebola case
And I'll say that
You believe him
This town suspicious
He's also wrong about every
Before
They gave him antibiotics and virus
Clean for a week the hot V
The ambulance
Because they obviously wanted to spread
So
First thing that pops out to me I think actually was the first thing you responded
Shift clean the f****** ambulance
Where was the first place that I went
When I was looking at
I can't I can't imagine
Absolute so I looked into it
Trying as hard as I can to create the image of the powers-that-be
It seems like a huge part of his argument
Ambulance hasn't been
The week
Alex is reporting is on October 5th when was this episode released made
Because he was on vacation when the news broke
September 3rd
I will not reach you from an article in Dallas-Fort Worth
From September 30th
In question had Ebola in it we ask
Actually lit on fire and then
And through the ashes into a frozen lake
In order to because that is underneath
The Creator perpetually Frozen and burning light
Mayor Mike Rawlings
Confirm that an EMS crew
Isolated
We've quarantined both of them and to make sure that nothing was nothing was there that can spread
And we're going about our protocol about how to do that says the bear
Just said
Top 40 from exactly what you would expect people to do
Alex
What is a quarantine
Clean it
Unfortunately later in the article
Dallas fire and rescue officials said the ambulance has been decontaminated
I was just making sure it up to make it look like the people running Point doing their jobs
Plenty of other valid criticisms to make about how the whole thing was handled
And we'll get into some of them
But this isn't one of them
This is complete nonsense Alex probably reading this on some job blog
Or something like that
Absolutely not true
There's more than just that article but that's just local Dallas reporting
We did do that we took care of that
He's on air on October
4/5
Saying they never did
Vandoit
Know that the guy had Ebola
They still would have
Theme to The fuc
Distant
Absolutely
Not that I am taking
The mayor
At his word
In the article in question
No that's how are you
The Cowboys have
Talk to me
The article in question
Also had a picture of
The ambulance
Important
I did also Steve
It's not that I'm just trusting blindly the mayor of Dallas
Overnight with police tape around areola
Then call it the real one
Chirp
But also in that article it is
Important clip that Alex
Just talkin he said that they gave
Antibiotics
Coronavirus
Interesting
What does
So when they say biotic
Would you say they are talking more about that
Now
If I remember biology correctly viruses
Cannot be killed
No
But Alex's misreporting
Thomas dunk
Can arrive at the Texas Health Presbyterian Hospital complaint
A fever abdominal pain dizziness and nausea
You spiking a fever at a tire
Set times of 100
3 degrees number of tests on him and couldn't figure out what was wrong
They kept him overnight but they didn't diagnose him with a virus at all
Broad-spectrum antibiotic
The initial symptoms of Ebola are super common
Like nausea dizziness abdominal fever differential diagnosis
That goes into
So many different possible actual underlying conditions
Ebola is like your left
Hand turns in the exact opposite direction.
There's not there's not
Especially with the initial presentation of it
Which is one of the reasons why it's so damn
Is it the initial presentation is so similar to benign
Condition
Flew their brain suspicion that he has
Ebola
It wasn't an episode of House
Return to the ER this time ambulance
Together in
Ebola risk in contact
One important things
Remember is the timeline of that
The outbreak
Jimmy happened
In early 2014
First being declared on March 23rd
That with the condition spreading to Liberia and Sierra Leone
Liberia go on
Speedy hottest Zone event
And initially
The country was declared Ebola Free by May
Now
It would reappear and it wasn't fully taken care of again like I said until January
But the fact that in may they declared Liberia Ebola Free
Kind of made the crisis beam less press
So in September these nurses probably didn't have Ebola first
Been foremost on their mind
You wish they would have
But it also makes no sense why they would have slept
Cracks the first time he shows up at the hospital
Horse. However what happens after that
Is
Definitely deserving of some
I mention there's some pretty
Here's some of it
The nurses Union is come out
Complaints the protocol was
Handled as well as it could have
Ranging from not immediately isolating Duncan is a suspect
Confirmation
Suspicions do not require staff to treat him in hazmat suit
But instead of just gloves mask
Good eye protection
Duncan stats rebola comes back positive
On September 30th
And the day before a nurse named Nina Pham
Him without any protective
A joy Simpson another nurse
Retreat at Dunkin
Compositive freebola survive. Up and up spreading it to anybody else
It is a really great place
To start your criticism
This situation
Because there are very valid criticisms about the
Handled
But the ones that Alex chooses to
Arnot
Also paint
Pictures that he wants
If you suspect somebody of having a bowl that you don't let him nurse go in with me
Yeah let me terrible idea
At the very least
At the very least I can't imagine anybody Direct
Nina Pham to go in there without any pro
Physician was like hey
Good old day
Is it like a piece of
Furniture
Nurses have a pretty good union like that would absolutely be a lawsuit it seems like
It seems like some failures
Situationally in this particular Hospital definitely
Oversight
Not any kind of malicious and probably could be
Easily traced back to the idea that most of these
People involved probably never imagined
Who would have
Crazy
So I want to say one thing or just
Perfectly fair to Al
The some of this information that I'm talking
After this
This is on October 5th
End up texting
Positive until
October 12th
That's when she tested positive
The 3rd
Miss Vincent
Isn't until October
He doesn't know any
Which are the actual
Decent criticism
But I also stand behind
Only make
Any more realistic exact but I just want to give that caveat that he has no reason to know
That's tough being
Future
Inexplicably we are as Fair as humanly possible
Listeners to others think
The timeline of unnecessary
The ambulance was
Who dealt with him
Word
Quarantine
Kept track of
The
He wasn't
Give a didn't but he was given broad-spectrum antibiotics
Because they couldn't
Figure out what he
Automatic kind of
Catch a biotic resistant thing
What percent of cases are solved
Or or at least
Treatable by doing this
Your first instinct is going
Let's do this thing that helps nine out of ten people not like
Almost never hurts
Yeah except for the resistance
All this is
Is a bunch
Bulshit
By and large
And without to take on the bigger
I want to make this very clear
They either
And what's already happened
How does MSNBC respond
Metaphor
What would you blame the moon made of cheese
I would like to ignore everything else you said because it's just it's Obama's fault
So the NRA
Making Ebola crisis
Is the headline
Yeah Alex
Yes and that
Specifically the NRA there
All gunners
But the way he's presenting it is they're blaming gun owners were making the Ebola crisis worse
Which is similar to blaming the moon made of cheese
I don't I think he had more to say when he got cut off by a heartbreak
Or you just
That's him Stephen
I got nowhere to go
So does he
Blaming the NRA
Is similar to
You blaming the Moon
Made of cheese
As opposed to blaming just the moon for Ebola
You're blaming the moon made of cheese for another
I would say that it's equally ridiculous
That I
I don't think that's what he was saying
He was trying to make some simile about
I don't know I don't I don't know I don't understand this is one of these trademark moments with Alex
I wish I could have talked to him during the break
What is the name Kim now there's no way he remembers when he
I want to know
I don't know if you would remember what
Immediately
You got to tell those kids you can't go fishing again
He's blaming the Moon
Listen kids I know you want to catch some trout like the moon made of cheese
Doctors kids on the phone he has hard brakes
He calls up
Back tone
Whatever Whenever you decide to get off the phone
Whenever it's time to get off
Block Rockin Beats
Bow
Circuits got to go
About about
So
There's a guy Thomas Breeden who's the head of the
He came out
Comment
About how
We talked about this already a little bit
These bands don't work
Explains the closing borders isn't
Really a viable option
Alex plays the Clippers
Describe Alex's
Responses
Like this guy's an a******
What does the CDC director
We can't control the outbreak
Even if we tried the closed
Dwarf people have a right to return people transiting to
Very convincing
Truly love you
I love mobile
Real that is musical playing over that message
So what
You at us.
I know we've been doing this for so long
Imagine
People at the CDC
Actually
Being like
We want your kids to be healthy
Black Widow
No with no
Caveat
With no like
Like it's literally good job
To be healthy
For a second imagine
Real
Like not even for one moment
Controlling the Center for Disease freedom
I believe
Of course not
Is good
There was a Mercury based
Preservative
Marisol
I am.
The things that was targeted
Specifically about the idea
Cause
Able to be on the altar
Right right right
A scientific
It's all completely refuted by study as always
Love you so much
Richard Wright
Mercury they love giving
Mercury Mercury
Resume
Like what is he won
So okay so his criticism is we have an NPR voice
On there
I would like it if I CDC head
Didn't come out and say
Third Beyond inspired
No no
I guess so yeah I guess he wants people who have a little bit of a cup
Replying to them
Like that people from these other countries are going to
Who's the Boss
Like snobby liberal
Or whatever that is responding to
What radio liberals like to listen to that sound
Speech pattern or whatever
Vocal fry
8600 total cases
Is over the
Tires 2 year span
Of this outbreak
It did did not get outside of
Dallas
At least this
The distance
It isn't
Incredibly irresponsible
Create
Things are way worse than
They are
That's irresponsible
So loud
My cat seems a little louder than a lot of his regular like coming back from break music
He just lingers
Anytime anybody play ZZ Top
I got problems
I've got
The bad bad cuz beard
It's not the beard jealousy so much I don't like the idea of people making beard novelty
She's certainly I don't like
Like in college civil rights issue
In college I would always get like a people
Every
These updates about the
The beard and mustache champ
Otu spaghetti
This would interest you of course you bearded man
Primary
My primary problems are songs
F****** terrible I realize they're like
I want hundred percent
Hold that clip because I think it's your spot
Sensationalism
But I also because
Played it too loud really was like
Most of his music papers off as soon as he starts talking
That was loud as f*** it Loosely fascinated by where your boundaries are drawn with music
You know I think
I think you've got pretty
Decent
About what
Narrative about
Like the idea behind it, and the federal government
Intentional
Blue baby blue
But in this ex-wife
Makes
The clear
Is going on
Basically use this crisis
Jerry Diaz
Bare minimum
Pressurizing a jumbo jet
He doesn't really make it clear what do you think they're about these like not closing the hatch
And stuff like that
Rinaldi's clarify is not
Because I didn't
Did you order
It's because when I first listened
Intuit I felt like
He's not being clear at all
From Houston International
Turn off all the default
Because the public
More like 187
Gone this whole thing
Generally speaking
Is the idea that
Is a false flag
H
For the global false flag
Dip dip
Case
It's not
Or whatever you can
But the ideas globalist
Have created this or are letting this happen
In order to get us all mandatory vaccinated with a
Monsanto and Gates Foundation are working together to enforce Upon a
I don't want to talk
Give me any
Situation where Monsanto and the billing
I can't give you one but I can save it
Vaccine
A ebola did not
Come out of this
Anyone
Couple recently
I'm not sure if
But a couple of
Insane
Through
3 and the FDA
I'm not sure I'm not sure I was trying to look into it and I can't
I was reading a bunch of documents
After a bunch of testing there are a couple of EX
In 2016 that were shown
Affect
In the range of 70
200% of 2
Being of XP
Which branch
But
Pretty good
From what I could tell
It didn't seem like it was on the market
Quesadillas
Is effective
And on the market and approved and all that stuff yeah
It doesn't really matter because
You know
This entire
Segments of our history
Entire outbreak
Ebola
West Africa
Didn't end.
Precipitating
Navigate didn't end up leading to a crisis that were
Required mandatory
Through of this vaccine that the globalist
Just going to use to
Kill-men I guess I don't know
This narrative is
A bump
I agree
Probably been
What have I
NRA store
Wonder what that NRA story was all about
I'm going to go with here's my
Prediction on what the NRA
I want to tell you before you make this prediction
To hear it but
You're going to be wrong
I'm going to give I'm going to give this one a go
Alright
So the NRA
Is making
Ebola crisis
Isis Wars
I'm going to go with
Rampant
AAA medicine and all of that stuff
You could predict what
Actually be about
A manta ray
Has a
Prosciutto
You know I hate bees
Is much like
Yeah just take out bees
Jordan
B you're wrong
You have said that you're wrong about this NRA story
At the beginning you could predict
It's a real
Good point
And Alex
Has not read this article
You don't even know what gaslighting
Crystal ball
I want Falls there real quick that is her real name
Okay
Real person's name
Vice
Is the problem
They don't even give a reason
That sound right
Two people
Together
Bothering
Crystal ball
Open Amazon
Are not going to need some
Are not just going
To say something and then not give
We're going to MSNBC it's just basically like some guys
His blog
The NRA's makes Ebola crisis
Even talk about what
Is in the article
Bring instead just say things like they do
Make a point
It's bizarre
That's what you just said
True
At is bizarre
It would be bizarre
Do the clearance willful defeat because he knows his listeners will hear the headline
I'm taking some kind of dumb liberal bulshit
Problems
The reason these writers are suggesting that the NRA is responsible for making crisis worth
Goes like this
Experts and researchers had examined the US infrastructure
Found that there is little
No reason for people to worry about a breakout of Ebola happen
Because
All containment
Processes that we
Because of
It just is on Roku
Like even if
People
Do end up showing up here
The proof of the pudding is in the eating
It didn't end up becoming a pandemic we have a solid infrastructure in place
Before it
Becoming a problem
Is obs
Bingo Bongo
However there a hard time conveying that message
Publix
Particularly with the backdrop of a meteorite
Worried about break and how is Eminem
Historically the job of conveying important health
Information like this
And reassuring population
They're being sold on air on
That is one of the main rules of the
Position of the surgeon
However in 2014 with the Ebola crisis
Heating up
Have a surgery
General
For about a year
In November
Obama nominated dr. Vivek Murthy for the Post
But his domination had been held hostage by the republican-held Senate the reason
He believed the guns were a Public Health crisis
And exhaust the NRA lobbied strongly against his nomination
Receiving
In making sure his nomination didn't move forward at all
Totally remember the public anxiety about a potential outbreak have a top doctor in office
And literally the only reason is that he believed the guns led to health problems
And the NRA found that position unaccept
The NRA didn't bring Ebola in
Or anything like
But no matter how you slice it
Country General
Because of their lobbying
In Congress
Through the Republican Party
They absolutely made the Ebola crisis worse
It led to people being able to spread much more propaganda than they would have otherwise
The article makes perfect sense makes perfect
NRA made the Ebola crisis worse
I'd never thought about that I've never heard that article before but Alex's
Attack on it made me read
And I say
Good call Crystal Ball
Never as you correctly pointed out I would never have guessed
Now that I remember that whole situation
8 makes
It's another instance of
Corporate money having
Unintended consequences that are almost universally howls
So
Just talked about how the globalist
You want this to happen
And that's why I'm out there
The second hours a day
He still has no
The audience
To actually say
And then
After he has he knows the audience
Repeat it back
Little bit of fun
About the Ebola
In October 2014 a lawsuit against
And international terrorism
In facilitating
Terrorism
Larry believe that Obama intentionally brought Ebola into the
This is
Not good
Larry said Obama's reason for bringing Ebola and was that quote his African Brothers over the rest
BoBoiBoy
By allowing some free entry into this country
And others are not
It was just at becoming in Devious
Invidious form of reverse discrimination
He also said
True throughout Obama's illegitimate
Presidency
It suggests he was born in Kenya and
It is neither a natural born citizen
Ineligible to president
Nor has been naturalized
To even have the right to remain here
I received the deportation petition
Kelly files
Cheap is favored his own Creed over the rest
I know you're responding for the delay
But don't worry
Larry isn't crazy
He's very restrained
What's a restraint
I do not have to
Violence alive and deported
What
You want to beat that you want to be alive and pay for his inadequacies under the rule of law
This lawsuit that Larry klayman put into court
Embarrassing
Public spectacle of racism
Got thrown out of court
Where we found him
Creating the dentist Montgomery
Maricopa
He is one of these weird through lines that nobody knows about
Good part of this anti-obama sentiment
Yeah
Are things that are like
I'll be 90
You want
Yeah you're a lawyer
It's not clean that up white and others
We're not black Muslims to the back
Back of the bus
I know you think that's a great turn of phrase probably put like how do you not clean that up
So in this next clip
I've been
Sorta Vista
Leeside earlier that
Alex is saying that the
Ebola outbreak is a
The false flag
He actually believes that
A false-flag a staged event
False flag
Of course it is not surprised
Fight
One of the things I always wanted
Clearly
Make a point of
Is the idea that
Whatever Alex says
Izmir
Callers
About a half-hour after he says
He gets a caller
I think this is a false flag
Identify at least like Robert David
I need to work on your so on September 18th
It's sad that that that the next X-Files plans will be assimilated
She thinks it's a false flag
Cool whatever
Explanation for why
It's a false flag she's like
Robert David Steele was on your show and Stow
Eagle your listeners will remember that Robert David Steele was the guy who
Who was Maps
And take him to Mars bases
The white papers that made it pro
How much
Embarrassment never was like
Alex thinks people are on Mars bases
Itt
Pedialyte
It's because of Robert David Steele
Who is being brought up in 2014 as the person
Who predicted the
I do want to give it to Monique
She made me very
Justin her backstory so all-in-all Monique I don't know what's up with motor
Panda and because she thinks
How is it
I want another Baxter
I'll be honest no matter what resorts
I can do
I don't think I can solve that
Okay but what I can do
And then of course Lauren
From Ohio
Google Warren Ohio
Canada
Intend
I will get back to you on that
But for now the show on September
She has been accepted
There'll be a false-flag using Ebola as
The cover or what
If you remember earlier I said that it wasn't
Surprising
The doctors and nurses were too much of
September Moniqua
But
Propaganda
Communities
In the interest of total fantasy that I got completely swept
Not that Obama was causing it
But I really bought into the doom-and-gloom worst case scenario disaster for type of stuff
In 2014 I absolutely personal experience
Condom sustained and long-running campaign
To make people scared Airborne was going to go airborne
It all it was going to take with it of Ebola
To make it
Breathable
It was going to take America by storm
People's interest in
Survival food guns
All the sort of businesses that
It's rise on the
Panic of the immediate
Collapse but at the time
Felt like a
A consistent bombardment of stories
This was just getting worse
I traffic
In
Conspiracy blogs and message
Boards and stuff like that
Around 2014
I wasn't buying the Rothschilds Run the World War 3
But this story did get to me
Like I remember this I was working at a shity job
Nothing to do or is it
Insurance company added
Terrifying
And I rationalize it in my head I was reading these terrible thing
Ever find
Where are they sourcing their information like there are factual
Pieces of it like
Oh my God start
Now it's in Sierra Leone
Now it's in Liberia
It's in every
These blogs
Would just have
These all cap
Headlines
Of like
Eat snack
Coming
It's a thing that I never really can
Considered but it is
After and all the sudden
Apples
F****** revenue-earning
Come out and it's higher than
Unexpected
Holyshit
Fly up
Like for these survivalist
I'm this kind of global pandemic
Veritiv comes up there to be like
Holyshit
Not real
Ebola like
It doesn't pop up
Valdosta
It's f****** cherished Crosby reality of has
You are in
Quite frankly
It's a
F******
It's one of the most
Terrifying
You have the idea of
Worldwide
Perfect fit
From a
Brings in that so much
So much of that in
Grain
Cultural
Fear
We have bees in then we have Africanized bees
They're coming out of this place
So Savage
That works
From by perspective I'm not saying I'm not saying from you
From my perspective
Just seems like
Peacemaker
Because I was reading
Resources
Understand
You got to figure out this blog
Get your reading
What are they getting their information from
Changed
See if any
I got
I got deeply caught up
In this this
They're just
Every time there was an oops
Possible case somewhere
Be a new blog post
Write new message board threads
Of all these like
Whenever where
It was a massive propaganda
Conspiracy world
Campaign going on well before Thomas Duncan
Never arrived in the United States
What I'm getting at is that it's not meaningful in any way that Robert David's
Pokemon Alex
The show
And said anything like they're going to use Ebola is a false flag
On September 8th
It was actually a really shrewd
Based on the facts on the ground
In August the World Health Organization declared
They continuing
Epidemic a public health
Emergency
Of international
Concerned technical designation on their plane
In August
Month before Robert Hatfield
And when they made that
That came just a little bit after
The August 5th
There was a
Confirmed case in Spain
A man who would end up dying a week later from the
The Ebola
Yeah yeah
In a country that was outside of a
Forgot
But he was
He wasn't Aid worker who had been in Africa course
And answer you have this
Already
Is penetrated the other
Yes outside
Spread
Everything the Robert David Steele
Was doing on Alex
The show on September
Because
A month before this
Help organizations
Everybody everybody
Take this
Already
Outside
It is weird how
Making a perfectly reasonable response
To a massive
Really dangerous
Disease it hasn't really spread that much
It was it was
Mid
Because
Been going on
Going on in so far as to say
Less than 100,000
Do you know what I mean always what
Literally a global pandemic
This is a known
Morning
Early-on enough to
Early enough
People are going to run wild
Well thanks
Real strict criteria of what
Ketut
A crisis that the world needs
Be worried about is that they do that in August 20th
.
The first
Case
The first page
Was it December
Foot District
It took a while for
Eat to become like
Three to four months after
Is that for real
WhatsApp
Took
Real specific
Take a note
Steelhead
Ferry boat
Faceted
Player
That we recognize this at all
We haven't heard him
Back in 2009
But we've heard colors mention
Write about how you talk to him
On some shows
Virgo
This world
We've got to
An actual
We now jump into
Robert David's
The Ebola is going
An outbreak
The false flag
Which
He's pretty clever
It's not I don't think it's ever
Anyway that is a false flag
He just like
Bridge bear
In terms of like
Real granting his
No looking at
The actual world
That exist
And figuring out the best way to live
I think it's pretty good
Bad
I mean his longevity
Evidence enough City
He's got some kind of
The angle that works I mean last until like what
Late 20
Yeah that was
Check that was like Steph Curry making two threes in a row and then being like
How about 45
I think Robert Davidson
Person get my
Might need to look a ton more into him
He's also a big Bitcoin booster kind of think he's more of a
Survivor than n
I see I see him being like a
I'm going to I'm going to ride these winds and then I'm going to change
I suspect you're wrong
But will write we will see
But
About how the global
To change the bulb
Houston
This narrative was
Flying all over the
Replace
The blogs
I was just pretending
The incubation. For
Like it used to be today
Is it now it's 20
That's all
The incubation period is always been arranged
It's historically been 22 21 days
With most cases
Is being with him
Create 10-day range
Twin symptoms
Manifest
Yeah it's a matter of
It's going out
Deviation
Like this
One standard deviation is 8 to 10 days
2 is 2221 or whatever like however however it actually works
Referendum
Nate silver would have a position
Generally speaking
3 weeks
You're at the point where it's like
If you haven't shown the
Symptoms you
Probably don't
Right route
3% Chase
So Alex is Alex
Pretending
It's always
Globulin globulin
Because that serves the
Of his ark
They walked
The fly into the country
Right because the country because there's a longer ink
Occupation.
They're not showing
Bada bing bada boom
She's going to take another week before I start
Really noticing that I have about life
Wherever
Exactly
That sort of thing
CDC head
To come out and be like
Is
Were anyone
Biso
Like any of the people that he imagined
Have the control
Do you think ya are there
There's still that would be worse
And easier transmitted than Ebola
That they could jobs book
Do that
Smallpox outbreak somewhere
It would be
Beat so easy
Feel like one of the problem
What are the problems with the way that you're lying problem
What are the scares
I wanted the way that we control diseases
Time
Some random scientist working in the CDC
Could just like
Sneak away of vial of smallpox and one on the ground that's exactly what happened with Larry
That's what happened with anthrax
Go read
Was.
Cliff here Alex gets to the end of the show
Making
I say facetiously
He's been doing his best to present
This idea that Obama is doing
The federal government
Is in charge of
If not letting planes
Not taking into account the
Alexa
Done before
This outbreak ever
Weapon Rarity
Is the one about this outbreak
Bitte Schon
Any kind of squash
What's the fact
I think we can agree without
He does say that Rick Perry is a
But he also was measured
That's true letting Perry off
Right
But he was also being like
I don't like seeing Alex like that
Because endgame
Literally end
With a horn
Outside Perris phone
She's outside Rick Perry's home
Bilderberg
Legitimately I do not remember that on account of what
Chicken game
The end
Closing shot
Lights go dark
Outside Rick Perry's house screaming into a bullhorn
1/2 hours before
I do want that violin
2BR sting
So
We got one more clip
It's a
Disaster
August 8th
Yeah
It's really like a Hallmark of our
That he has a lot of
Colors
Because we know they're anonymous
They're just calling
Is it like
I work in intelligence
We saw this with Zach
Yeah just call her that he kept I haven't
Mysteriously gone now hello him lately
What's up
Just drop that narrative
Probably run away to Morocco
Why hasn't left the country
That advice
A lot of these callers that call Lynn
Give themselves credential
In order to
What I've noticed
Is
They only do that
Tamir Alex
Bakkt
Anyways
Xanax
Can be like
I talked to this guy knows
There's an there's an echo chamber there where the audience
Understand
They can elevate
His narrative
Positive
Like in a way that's the
He's doing right think of this caller is a
Perfect representative
Insider from FEMA region 6
Incessant
An Informer state tax time or work for the regional agency
Formerly known as San Antonio Texas
Emergency planning
The reason I know the Ebola outbreak is being conducted on purpose
Is it violates all protocols
Are used to be involved in the Hurricane Katrina and Rita response of the evacuation
For smallpox outbreak
Is there a County
The proper response would be
The National Guard
Would steal off Bexar County
Law enforcement and Emergency Services would redirect the population to all hospitals
Churches and other government agencies
Where they would be screen
If they were sick they would be isolated at a former military base
I feel the sickness at the house or they died
Everyone else will be forcibly vaccinated
It would be no exceptions or no travel in and out of their County so the fact that they're allowing people to
Travel into the United States
You're not walking down the city of Dallas Cowboy this is 5 desire
That guy was reading off a script
100% going to say that there's no way that
Extemporaneously
Expedia
Does 100%
Is reading a
This is full of s***
You clearly don't know what the protocol is
The situation lie
Like this and what he's pretty sure it's called in the National Guard
Screen everybody isolate people
Churches
And Hast
Bright
And then
Guy literally Alex Jones
Worst nightmare come true in terms of the federal government
Jason's at military bases
Churches that they have requisite shinned
In reality this idea
From movies
At all reflect what professionals Act
America there was a large
Spell quarantine
No no
A large-scale corn
He was 1918
Mean when the Spanish Flu broke
No Public Health crisis center
And there have been many
Wednesday
Have been responded
Did you buy masks
There's a good reason why
Multiple
Why 41
It doesn't work most space
Sickly
Almost certainly trigger a map
That could lead to all manner of unintended
Range vigilantism
Second
That panic
In people who see themselves as
Noxxic
Quarantine
Stay in the place where the
Unisinos Italy
Put others at
Is part of a human
Survival
Probably
Importantly a large-scale quarantine
Huge economic
Whatever City your quarantining effectively gets taken out of the larger economy
It's possible that billions
On top of
Whatever it would cost you to just do the quarantine the first right
Beyond that only 10 states
Laws in place that
People who have jobs
They are subject to a quart
Keep their jobs
Based on
Being subject to a quart
Nisei Texas
Sure I don't have a list of all
There's only 10 places
Is there like
If there's a quarantine you don't have to come to work week we cannot fire you for that alright
10 out of 50 I'm just going to say that
One of them is
Just Frankfurt
Sure I know for sure that they would do
Roxanne text
Kentucky
No
Look at the issue is they like
This doesn't
He's putting out into the world is fake inside
He's putting out.
Year of life
Quarantine
City
It doesn't
Is you end up
But you just imagine in your
You're not a dumper
Imagine what happened
He's talking about quarantining
Dallas Texas
It's nonsensical proposition
The idea that you were ever going to be able to create
Like
Actual
I'm build the walls of fun fun things to do out
You're ever going to be able to
Oyster
This or whatever
What is smart about quarantine
As a rule
Is a small as possible
So if you have someone who is
Do you have a strong suspicion
Has the condition
Quarantine that person
In a hospital
Quarantine
The house
In terms of don't let other people go in there
Corinth
You don't have to clean the entire house
What good is that going to do you if no one goes in
It doesn't help you
Jordan
We have this Insider
Really full of s***
But he's not
Absolutely
Create
He's trying to create
Apperception
Of himself
To reinforce Alex Jones
Narrative
He has heard
By listening
Doubt
Maybe but yeah
In many ways like he doesn't get your own deal and if not
He's on an ash
Syndicated Radio Networks
Can't really use that to help
Go to the bar
And everyone's like
Hello Colonel or whatever like
Raira
There's still some
It's only four
For you
But it's also
Kind of like
Donation
Alex is audience often
Yeah just ideas
They're going to lie
In order to bolster
Does narratives forehead
On the show
Insomnia to make your narrative feel import
Is important
For both of us
So I'm going to
I'm going to
You need someone to lie to me
This makes sense so I'm going to do it for you
And I'm not
I'm saying this because what he saying makes no sense
The idea of like quarantine in
As large as Dallas or
Or even like
He said
Bexar County
It's spelled vexar
Pronounce Barak
Is weird
Bibb County you're not allowed
The idea
Yeah
Tiny Town
We close down every
Your population is
Maybe
I think that's in effect
Maybe that would be what
Real baby
Statistically
Maybe you could keep
200 people under
Maybe
Put that into
2000 people
One is going to get out way more than that
And yes I know and I know but like
Minimum order of
But might I would like to say thank you to George Soros Junior for suggesting this
If for no other reason that I learned about Ellis Island
I appreciate it
Anyway I would say
Walt
Happy birthday
You're the best
You are
You son-of-a-b**** Walt you're one of the best
Water fun
I enjoy dipping toes
Out of context
Yeah because we're not evercon
We know a lot about Alex Jones
Days that we check in
We can come
Understand what he's talking about
If we've done this episode
It would have been like
Sterilize Aldi
Isabelle the narrative
Now is it
Right as it might be my way of
Deflecting from the idea that
There are a number of time travel request that we haven't done
Be better because
Put them off
And thank you all
Always
If you remind me
Again
About needing
If you have sent me a time traveler Quest
It can't hurt to remind me again I'm not going
Wouldn't mind
This is just language
When you say we know a lot about Alex Jones
I would
Prefer if you said
We know a nun
Fortunate
What about Alex
I know about about a
Do anything else
What's my life like I literally can't
Do you know who didn't kill anybody
Somebody's Brewery
Never killed anybody
Do you know what he didn't have
A website
Do you know we have
We do have a website
Do you know what the guy who I'm
Specifically thinking of who didn't kill anybody didn't have
Twitter account
The end of this
He'd have a website but we acknowledge
Underscore fight
Cora group on Facebook
Serious thing
The Greek
Mithras
Mithras never killed anybody
And then three days later came back to life and there are no similarities
Are you sure mithras never killed anybody or expired a photo of somebody
Jesus
Who in the Apocrypha
The child gospel
You killed his friend finally brought him back to life so it's kind of
Enzo dragons were dealt
Sure
It's not a sin
But
Never killed nobody
Technically probably
That's out
Alexandra Thurston color