Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We're couples about Alex Jones
Buddy
My parents Christmas present
Our old ones that we were using
Where I've had for probably 7 to 8 years
Scratch them to ship they were just
Falling apart I wish I would go home cover
Adorable
Tell me about
The find out that this
Your show
George Davis got a fun episode
Front of us we're talkin about Alex killer
The Bill Murray Christmas all over again hell no
Alex took Christmas off
Potato rebroadcast on Christmas
Wednesday Thursday
Thursday and then
Christmas Eve
He's a weirdo
On Christmas
It's be expected a weirdo
Before we start the show to give a couple thank you was out there
To folks who have signed up and are supporting the show
First of all I'd like to say
Not Alex Jones
Alex Yarnell policy walk
Thank you Alex
Second
You are
Yeah yeah
I get to Bellevue
Who has joined
Special thank you
PayPal
And I
Forgot to send an email out very much Christy you are now
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much Christy thank you very much if you would like to show we would appreciate
Now, I should tell you
Skip this chair
Two chairs for
I got another gift that is a gift and a curse in a responsibility
We received donations bumped into our neck patreon
Terrified
To put this out to the world
People have been requesting
That I write a book
Or we write a book about Alex
For that matter
There's not as much as utility in this podcast as I would like there to be
Well yeah for the people to get the information that we're putting out into the world have to listen to a lot of our podcast
To get the information
It's not
Not is the most digestible usable application presentation of the information that we're
Uncovering in the
That that we're learning about
Answer one of the things people have suggested was that book idea
You and I are Leon
We're interested in the idea of it
There wasn't a way to make it engaging and
Informative book
It wouldn't take us both our entire life
Or whatever
Probably killing each other because of the meetings about
Meat using the passive voice
And then I would scribble in screams in the margins
Where to go
Around the idea of like what other ways would there be to present the information in a way that
Could use like
Let's say you're having an argument with somebody
Narrative
Chip
Listen to 45 minutes
Debunking of x
Hotwire
Sure and hopefully maybe
It's not it's not the most helpful
Answer what I decided to do is I decided to start building
I started to do that and I realize I don't like
The wiki structure
Necessarily
I find it very difficult
To manage
Unwieldy
But I've begun and Don Most
Work is never good
To be done
I've created a database more lies
Infowars
It's a work in progress
But because we've crossed this goal I will start
I'll start making it available on knowledge fight.com
I hope
By the first
My goal is the first of the year it'll go by
That's what is the
The timeframe of lead-up that I probably need
A few things
Hollister
What have you got on now it's right. Combat
We'll go to our
Tons of information
A large portion of my time over Christmas
Compiling and writing
Esoteric
I am grateful to
Level mainly because Dan has been writing this
For forever
And if you had
I don't think he ever would have until he was like
5 probably
Fairly right I would kick
The can down the road or need to do
From the jump
For sure
Guest narratives information
Armoire
The times that we've studied
Like 2009
ND
Trump coming to Trump
Are going to be a lot more of that but it won't only be that time goes on I'm going to
To continue
To add to
These databases
Stuff like that
Much more thorough
It's it's whatever Institute
Wow
That's an unfair comparison
Anyways everybody
Force my hand on this
We'll see
But that that is
Is, what is to come today
Christmas Eve 2018
Studio he's in a bit of a weird mood
And
Play it's a little bit long
Because
Is it him reenacting the entire Christmas Story with Noel
All day
Broke
A bunch of
I got some field reports from people that they advised sightings of Alex on the ground
Bhutan
Explains
Here in this first
Clip and then tells
Is a Meandering bizarre story
That I can't I cannot believe is true
Movie with his wife's family
Omaha Nebraska
I said Tulsa I'm sorry I meant
Hospital
Father
Surround
Omaha Nebraska
Finishing the mule
Movie
Omaha Zoo
I've been there tonight
I'm just saying if you have time to go see a movie twice you got some leisure
I've been poisoning him movie
The hot dog and some nachos
Shall I go out there
Fast food
Washington
How do I do that
Call
Probably 25-30 photograph sign autographs
They're they're pulling over people in France
Willmar
Like the Gadsden flag
We go out
Why do you smell like alcohol
50 people are more
Generations High School
Yum yum yum
I got to get her dad outside and if we go outside
Flash mob
The good news is
Omaha Nebraska
In the middle of nowhere
Just trying to get a hot dog and cheese nachos
That's out the middle of nowhere
Every detail of
Read story except for this problem
Literally nowhere
I don't know
Alex hot dog
Or Nacho
First of all
Hours early are you
Goddamn
Movie theater
That was a gas station
For five years
A lot of x
It is
Is that he is
Telling this story
Other than to like
Preemptively make sure his wife thinks
Wasn't going to the park
Wasn't drinking by a dumpster
It's fascinating to me
Depending on what narratives and what sort of feeling he needs his audience
He will tell
Almost identical stories
Sbat
I went out in public and everyone Bob.
They were calling him a Russian
All the time
But they're either angry at him or love him depending on
Ingredients
Inspire hope
It's almost like he has these paranoid projection
Things that are dependent on how he
He's feeling at the time like
Feeling good he's with his family they're enjoying Christmas
Surrounding him in there they're giving him nothing
He's feeling bad like
He just met with his lawyer
Evil people left it
Paranoid projection Theory might be right because
Talkin about this in this nightclub he says things that I think are even left like
First one
There was Hysteria
Elvis Presley was there something
2 hours
National Airport
Zeitgeist
What's going on
Merry Christmas
Flight attendants
The PlayStation
Such Liars
So the notion that he's walking around the Denver International Airport and people are it's like
Copa b-sides
And the people are walking up to him
Under their breath
Keep it up
I think you probably
Some of that yellow
Also by the way
Having people say Merry Christmas to you Wednesday are in the service industry
Surprise eggs
Or even the pilot door open
Stuff
Is. Like
Flirtatious
If not it does
Is white supremacist code
Easy to break
That is that is not the windtalkers
Is that we're dealing with
Your code for being cool is like
Merry Christmas
Bro
You got me alright
And the world is like
Fine whatever
So Alex you may be bored
The rest of the world
Crows
The real
That's all good and well
Call Alex
Was out of town
Please car
That is light him to
Very weird moved here on Christmas Eve
I was driving to work has gone to the ER
Who would have been driving your car
Your kids are not old enough to drive your wife was with you
Your real wife was with you
Closest King Sooper
Serious
Where I found it but there was one
That's a little all over the place but you know
Someone stole his car and put it on a
If you are backing
I'm song Happy Christmas War is Over
Said that he's curious about it
Cuz he's left his
They are supposed to hate
Stop War
Fruit amore
Here's my issue with the
Haha
And you get in there.
And you noticed ER is on
And then you listen to a couple
That means that NPR is shifted to a FM for Matt and I are just playing Christmas songs in a play
Supposed to be in like all things considered
So we'll get into the war thing here in a minute
Cuz that's nonsense
Particularly
Fuse by the scrimmage
Justice Reform things correctly Alex
To take on the criminal justice
Reform Bill
Was that
Put all this language in there
It specifically said we're going to keep black
People specifically in jail for three times as long
Before
Fixed it
Using his
Incredible power
To understand legislatively
The first absolute good thing the bipartisan legislation passed
That would work to ease mandatory minimum sentences work harder and Rehabilitation of offenders instead of punishing
To give Trump any credit
Leftist
I've been pushing for for a long time
And actually
Obama's term
The new law called the first step Act
Retroactively applies changes Congress made to drug sentencing laws
20/10
Which experts
Between 4000
6000 prisoners
To immediately qualify for
Supervised release
That is to say that in 2010
That
Stalked
By the variance
For like Kraken
Under Obama in 2010
Just passed what this bill does
First Step Act
It is really good as it makes
The Retro black
So that is a very positive
Really just
Extension
Already
Long before Trump people
On the way
Pushing for
For quite a while
The reason for the varying sentences
For Coke and crack goes back to the anti-drug Abuse Act
After being passed overwhelmingly by
The bipartisan
It was like 9
Percent above the house
Where is your people
Jamming up that
The inner cities that was a Republican or Democrat initiative inasmuch as
The Congress
Name of both parties
This bill
Touted as one of the bills I really
Is it a band
Pregnant prison
But that was a practice that is already been banned by the Bureau of Prisons
Conversation
In the building
Wasn't already taken care of
It was by the Bureau of Prisons
More f***** up to realize that it wasn't
But it's not
Who knows how well I bet they were
Doing a great job of following the guideline
It's good to put that into law
But it wasn't you
Boy Scouts head
It is good but it's also not nearly enough
The actually relates to federal prisoners and does literally nothing
260 wrongful incarceration
Far far more people locked up in
Obs
2.3 million prisoners
There are in this country
Only 180,000
Federal Prison
Over two-thirds of whom are not even eligible for this program
Which makes the Axiom possibly
Eclipse service to the private prison
All in all
Support the Trump did nothing
To make happen
Is anything the argument should be that Jared Kushner pushed
Does Alex wants to play
The reality is the opportunity to attach himself to something
Universally popular cost him nothing
Could you through the day
So he did just that
No further
Alex should not be in favor of the first step act based on his principal
Excludes offenders who use firearms in
Committing their offenses
You should believe that this is an unfair.
Guns in jail
You were caught selling crack
Can you had a
You're not eligible for the
Benefits that will come from
Alucard
Plus the Congressional budget
The plan will cost taxpayers
346 million over the next
Because the released will be eligible for benefits
If Obama did something like this
Streets of criminals in order to set off social unrest
Issue
I'm bringing it up
Because that's the way Alex
What is rhetoric
Generally work
Obviously
The amount you'll save and not incarcerate
What makes up for the 3rd
He would use that number against Obama is
If you had a f****** chicken
Instantly
So anyway
Say actually
That number is
It's going to cost
The taxpayers
Billions upon billions of dollars a year
Right
But somehow the Federal Reserve is to
Actually that is
Who knows
Expense
A large portion
To give Trump credit
He's the best
Even if you're a liberal you got to love video
You're going to do is me
Heard about Law and Order In
Sing people being
It so short shorts
Anyways
The Central Park five
But
We don't want to appear weak
Strong
It's like I hate something
Boats
I don't know
Do you have that like
Democrats are
That later but
Credible
Alex
Love drop
He's not getting off the train
Yeah he's still on board real hard
My reputation is amazing is that come from the exact same people
Call America anti-communist
Operation
Organic American people
The challenge
Remove
Our fingers around their throats
Merry Christmas
The name of our dear Lord's birthday I just want to let everybody know even though we are
We will choke the life
Message of Christ
So far we got lying about Criminal Justice Reform screaming about killing the globalists and prayer
About getting a hot dog in Tulsa Oklahoma
Wyomissing
This is the Christmas Eve Apple
Is that right
I'd be fair Christmas Eve
Everyday
Put the present under the tree
Intuit
Start and then you get festive later
He's getting it all out of
So when he goes home
But also
Merry Christmas
Instead of screaming about how
What makes for a better
Extension
Consistent
So he talks about how he's going to do
Which is not
Spells out what comes next
95%
Another battle in front of him
Close
He's mentioned
Is before but just the way he says it is really fun
North Pole
Levels
Next level
OK Google
Secrets of the universe.
Raising your instincts
Terrible take the whole thing
You know he should
For this I'm going to be
A dirty assholes
Sure sure
To be a Slave
Problem
Carly Shay
2000 Troost
Jordan Lee truck supplies armaments to
For allied with ISIS
Decision
You not
Like the idea of pulling
Troops out
General
Yeah always I'm going to be in favor of us not having fruits
Power vac
That is going to lead to
Possibly the genocide of the
Now that's never been tried before
By removing a large number of troops
Really really quickly
That could create a power vacuum
Let's let's just take a random this could have occurred as a hypothetical
I was going to go 2011
Great job with the Kurds
Generally been a very strong allies
Was going to abandon the Kurds in Northern Syria Isis
Killing at least one Kurdish fighter
The girls are part of the Syrian Democratic forces
Is it a lion
Who are supported by Saudi Arabia in
Guitar
In terms of providing arms
Switched alliances
Sporting
Is patently absurd
Because if they did
Conflict or Italy
This barge aspect
It would be over
It wouldn't
Exist
Understand his take
At all
This whole
Syrian situation I wish I had
Way more of a grasp on
Evereve
Possible like Angela a bit but at the same time I recognized
Even don't understand
We shouldn't have troops there
It's an illegal
Remove troops
From that place
Like the argument
Bring them there are really it's
Between us and
Time to stop
Are we
I mean
I think that I think that at the end of the day
Some of those questions will be answered
We may not like to see
Right
Absolute Auto forces in play in
In terms of
The situation in Syria
I even Hazard to say whether I'm for or against
The idea of taking
Exactly
I can see an argument for and I can also see strong argument
To not do it based on the consequences but you'll come
It's not a perfect thing
The idea that the Kurds are allies with ISIS
This is absolutely not
Save the Trump kids
Honorable and Noble
Occurred
It just leaves them sitting ducks
Are supported by Saudi Arabia Qatar Russia Assad
People who will
Now that the u.s. is
Will have no incense
Not
Make Massif
People buy
Possibly
Really really awful it like
Him choosing serious Pacific
Definitely has nothing
Foreign powers that a maybe
I'm sure he's going to
Troops out of
Stop providing
I assume we're going to get out of so many of that
Military bases all around the world
To do what do
Would be that I don't
Specific reason
Would be picked up
Call Sprint
Because Alex is conversation
Idea of life
You know they're going to wrap that up real quick financing
Much like
The run-up to the
2016 election
The plan will kick in
Into place
Once everything's settled
He's still using that narrative is being like that's what's right
In front of us
Assad is going to allow democracy
Thrive Anna
Alex
Your your argument survey ston
Pieczenik
And now you don't even like Steve
But you're still using his narrative
Like it that's so fascinating to be that Alex is like
Steve pieczenik was trying to convince
Text me just say that the Las Vegas shooting
He was trying to get me to
Make that money
But I realize that's not
Alex went on air inside the sea
Steve pieczenik is probably still running CIA psyop
But hasn't taken a second
Consider what
Pieces of his worldview were brought to him by
A question though
The idea of these Secret counter-coup
Our military
Decide where they were going to
Everybody's going to be super in a hat
Steve told him and he hasn't even
Tiny little bit
If he's been lying to me and trying to get me to godown Road
Me to go down
What about
Because
Completely destroy his support for
See I have
No problem
Because if
One thing that I
Really learned
Never
Underestimate
Soleil
Why would he go back
I can change
Mr. Fact check
But various reason behind it and that is
If that pee
Domino fall
It calls into question still money
Nvidia ended up support
Like I don't think you probably would have ended up supporting Trump if you didn't have that
Fictional
Mythology of being the mouth
Piece of the secret
Goodguys in intelligence Council
Nonsense going on the TV
It's crazy
But if it comes down to it and there is
I don't know
When that's going to happen
I don't know what that was
Even look like
Doesn't step down and have elections Alex
We're going to come tonight because there'll never be a satisfactory piece to where he's like I'm now it's time
Just stay on because
Is a strong leader that needs
To be in there right now
In order to
Right
So
I don't know it is all a lot of nonsense
Spite
It's not nearly as much
Nonsense
Saudi Arabia
Previously
He said if you do it we're going to overthrow you right now
Okay
Bingo bingo
Respond to that
Is the worst person on Earth
Because
Do you understand the argument that he's make
Taking their base
The truck basically brought women driving and takeoff
Between understanding the definitions of the word
Using and understanding the argument that
These words
It's not
What
Donald Trump went to Saudi Arabia on May 20th
21st 2017
Here are just some of the things that have happened
Narrative
In November 2018 a national released a report showing
Saudi Arabia
Tortured sexually harassed and mistreated several Human Rights Act
Of this year
The activists were flawed intellect
Attributed leading one of them to attempt suicide
Heatedly Wiley
Unmarked in March 2018 Saudi Arabia arrested a number of women's rights act
Some of them were leading campaigners for the right to drive for women
Including Lugene Al health
Aziza al-yousef
Innocence quote as the Saudi Arabia Saudi Crown Prince
Is the world
Presenting himself as a reformer he's arrested women's rights activists who were
Refuse to accept
Is tokenism
Leaving it to us
To make their voices
Kenneth Roth
Executive director ratio
In August 28th
Team Saudi Arabia sought the death
Rights activists
Israel
And for social
The charges the accuser of included
Participating in protests
Chanting slogans
Protest in public
Arrested in December
15 she was held without access
Text with lawyer for
Her most recent trial was scheduled for November 21st of this year but she wasn't brought to
The court which is also what happened in her October 28th
Which is lifesum international rights organizations
Do you mean that she's already dead
Some sort of Terror
Yeah I don't want to present
Republic
It's one of the other
She's fine
Barring any proof
That's about as best
It seems that way
August 18th the Canadian Ambassador was expelled from the country
Africana Discord Minister tweeted in support of releasing jail active
Then there was the October star related murder of journalist Jamal khashoggi the atrocities being
Competitive
And the list goes on and on with
Instances of Saudi Arabia being squarely on the wrong side of
Human rights issues
Long after Trump supposed
They gave him a Stern talk
Nothing that Alex is saying makes any sense
Fictional reality to live in
To justify why he
Used to be critical of Saudi Arabia
Play the good guy
Because Trump has said that there's a good guy
So that's all
He's just trying to shift his narrative
By creating
Any false reality
True in the world is suffering
No
Most of the Republican party has abandoned every ideals they ever stood
Good for in order to
Witches ride the wave of a massive racing
Alex is literally carrying water for p
People who are try it working
Thought it was
Brilliant move to be like hey
I will give all of you the right to drive
Steve activist
Hempstead and secretly I will kill all of these activists so I never have to worry about active
Again and I'll never have to
To change anything
Because that's the
The name of a
Textbook
Accompany
Columbia Missouri
Kush gig that I could have gotten when I was
If I could have gotten in there but the drug test
Fireman
I have taken the stuff
You know that's what's supposed to flush out your system
Never when I got my drug test results back
Tested positive
For a number of steps
Richards
Little bit
Anyway just memories flood back
I got you
Could have been
Clearly paddling a self-deluded narrative
About Trump and his actions
Visa vie
The Kurds and Saudi Arabia
But
They are like the war party house
Liberal
He's a liberator really appreciate
Probably not
Trump is the great Liberator and all of you
You liberals have been caught
I don't know
How how can you
Just like how
I just I just don't understand
This is a real psychotic episode
Same time
Nothing makes any f****** sense
None of what they're saying makes sense
Like I don't I just want to have a conversation that makes sense instead of a conversation where it's like
I'm actually president Alice from wonderland
She does it's fantastic and how dare you you evil suck
King rabbit what are you doing
No I just think we shouldn't lower
For the rich I don't know what to
I want to see an Alice in Wonderland with Alex
Whose voice I think a lot of this might
Come down to to the
The stuff that we spoke
I think that perception might be in your head because of
So much
To the covering the proper
Even though it is
I think that we have a little bit of
Because
Weezer so much Alex
No that's that's reasonable but it's the only other exclamation
Is that
So much of the Republican party is
Either apathetic
To reading any news whatsoever which now that I say that
Nope
Saudi Arabia
I suppose that is a question that between two options
The first nevermind you're correct
Chicago and who started a question
Boo today
Like I I legitimately
Perpetuating putting out into the world
On Christmas Eve
This is Christmas Eve
I think it's very dangerous
Really bad
I think his behavior is
I think there's a moral character
Sometimes I don't
I don't really care too much
Good moral discussion about like him lying about
Miac report
I'm not super interested
Morality of life
That like
That compelling abaca
Conversation
Do you say
Or at very least
Normalizing
Covering up
And I pray that is really bad I think that's actually
I think that's
Evil and that makes it all the funnier
Alex talks about how he
Incapable of Eve
Treacherous but
Myself
I just can't do it
Stone
Shooting
That's pathologic
Ovulation and I don't even know who they are
You don't even know
If you saw it it's like
Can't do it
The problem is
Literally
I'm starting a name out loud
I think he's actually being Blasphemous right now show loyal
That makes sense
Not at all
No
Quantify
2020 all I can say is this
This whole thing this is all about
Alex's apologizing forever support
I can't
I can't do anymore at least not like
Play manager
Forever instrumental part in
Did the guy who ran
Other propaganda Outlet
To the point of getting me sued by hoppy Lucaya
TV Guide
Now is working to help Jer bolsonaro the guy is Brazil's Trump
Well we would say
Authoritarian rise around the world that Alex called
The Nationalist movement around the world
Steven has a huge pardon are they what the f*** are you doing Alex analyzed for a second
It's amazing
It's crazy
Dumb dumb
We even consider saying like
I couldn't
Dewey Villages are capable of
Debt relief
Like that is a malignant narcissistic trait
Like I can do no wrong
Of course I do
Minimized
But I
Putik aspect
Do that
Oftentimes when
You suffer from like
Guilt and shame
Accessories in your life and
Is there is a helpful
Little trick
Then
Not even
Not even like
Morally
Your bed
If only because he went to a movie and you got a hot dog
Why is it
Why isn't there so many weird
Evil Republic
You mean
Ketchup
So I don't know that that's
Apologizing
For its supporting Steve
Everything about him supports
Brother stuff
Capable of evil
I don't know if you play sports growing up
When you are younger they gave you instead
Duration
Coaches the gave you
Inspirational
I was out
What's that quote
My sophomore year set all kinds of inspiration
Remember any of it
Just kidding. Probably right
Time to lean time
Between
My response.
X
Give me to go the f*** home
And I like that kind of effort overcomes probably recognize
Almost everything
Is just something
From expressional poster
It's not some sort of hang in there
Looks like released
Every coach says the exact same thing
List of cliches
Cliche that the coach told him is some sort of
Profound advice
Trump is very fatalistic he believes he goes into this
Football coach
Poison your father
Well well well well well well well well well we got it we got it
You got put up to varsity because
You hurt people and they like that
Great
Even so like
You're not supposed
Play football on Safeway very hard not to
That's a psychotic impulse
Yeah because people pads and all that
The people who play like high school football
That's someone who also may or may not have killed a couple dogs in their life
That is a lunatic
Coach told me he said 100% you don't get hard
Is going a hundred percent
When you get hurt is like one
Most Bush League
Actually play sports
Because you would know that
You know how most of the NFL goes half-speed all the time that's how they became the the professional sports player
That's why I like there's a toy
25%
Totally
Go hundred percent
Stop it
Because he believes in you
He's ready to die
Punjabi shopping called a chain
Call the brat shut down
Michelle out
So get ready for fireworks
There's no pedophile card in the Tarot deck
Used for playing War
I'm not totally sure why are tarot cards something specific
It's only his Christmas Eve episode perfect
Perfect time for him to ramble about his Heroes
Top of the esoteric magic devil card game deck
The problem is
The Tarot deck doesn't operate the same way
Cards does where the highest card is the better it is
Also in normal decks
The Tarot deck
Want pickles or coins
And swords
Each represent more or less
A different one of the elements
That's generally how both
People look at the Tara
And the King of Thieves
Denotes
Completely
Also Kincardine draw needs a completely different thing depending on where the card is drawn in a reading
And if it's drawn up right or reverse there's a lot of variables
It's twins right
There is there's
The four suits are each a minor Arcana because
Each suit
Is Alex wanted to really make
The emperor the emperor represents a powerful leader
Respecting Authority as a leader you rule the firm but fair hand give a Clear Vision of what you want to create
Did you organize those around you to manifest
You listened to the advice of others
So you prefer to have the final say
Conflict doesn't scare you and you wouldn't hesitate
Use your power to
Protect those you care about
That could have been a fun way for Alex to describe Trump
Those those Center
And says remind me of this
That people used
The scam it's called
You know
Where it could describe literally f****** everybody
There is a touch of that
I don't want to go too far into like
That's all I'm saying
No hero Magic the Gathering
Almost never knows what he's talkin about particularly
Accidentally
Into the worlds of these supposedly
Evil things
Again
King of cups
It was like wipeout
So
You got very excited
I forgot this coat was coming because
Kind of
I thought that was what we were working towards
I forgot about this clip
Alex should never have said this on air
This is really really f***** up
I mean there is Larry Nichols
Blackmail Congress
Everything song
Alex shouldn't have talked about being debriefed by Russian intelligence agent said that on air
Killing his dog
Salon
This one I think might have legal implication
He's having Rodger Stone on the other end of the phone
And they're talking about how
All this Russian stuff is b*******
And Alex accidentally
Tell some backstage business
Alex is reviewing something really really shouldn't
I was there
Fox News contributors
So first things first Alex Rodgers business into the streets
During the campaign he was a paid contributor in Fox News
That's whatever
Because of the time
After
November 2015
That's the first time that Rodger fearon Alex
Alexa
I have to be in that timeframe
Rodger was fired
From Fox News
He comes to Al
I wish you would hire me for your good call Michelle
So
Rodger has come to Alex
You've asked him for a job at Infowars
Importantly he said he
Did not read
Facebook was making
The president's 20lb J Killing Kennedy
In 2016
Epsom
Rodger
Communications Network
Call The Stone Cold Truth
He was very short-lived
So that probably is right around
We're talkin about
He asked Alex for a job he got him a show on
Gcn
Massage
Amazon
I'll try I do this talk show host
Alex Jones has now just admitted on air
Veggie Direction Rochester
You going to try and portray that as like
It's no big deal Rodger was unsuccessful in getting in touch with him meanwhile
If it does turn out that there is concrete evidence that Rodger was in contact with them
Switch
I think they're strong indication
That he was
Put the actual evidence
We'll see if it is which
But if it is
Alex has just put himself in prison
Self first time I've ever been
All around the world
During the campaign Rodger Stone got fired as a contributor by Fox News
If you bring me the most illegal bring
Alex Jones
Direct you to commit a crime
For the Christmas gift to
What happened
Remember
Sure
Starting attending that clip with I was there not going to play out well for you Alex
Here's what I also
I didn't just
I need to make sure that you know
I was there when the crime was also committed
Condition of getting a job
With me
Which if that's the
Give Rodger a job
If you can get me in touch with that Julian Assange
I will give you a job
Logically that I mean
He did get a job
Did he come through now this is a whole new indentation
I'm sure whatever the reality of the situation
With any kind of like
Subpoena power and stuff like that they already
It's no secret
Official Channel
But it's really funny
On Christmas Eve with Alex Jones in studio
Tried to get really defensive
To contact Julian Assange dead Rodger Stone
Clearly was telling him that he did contact
I mean remember that one episode
Alex stayed up super late in order to cover the WikiLeaks
Bibigo dumplings
Either Galaxy
This shows like
I get why you use fake quotes
Cuz you are
Propaganda
And everybody else who works behind the scenes it
Infowars must be
Do so much
Toomics like to keep this on track
Do s*** like that
Alex
Don't say s*** about
Can I get contacts
I directed
Oh I shouldn't have said that
Was 100%
I would have loved it if children I would love it if there was like you were watching it
It was just sort of like everything's going normally on the shown
No
You came to me told me he got fired by Fox News
But if you get me Julian Assange I'll give you a job and then just all of a sudden
Let's go out to the technical difficulties
I forgot to the lobby
Gorgeous everybody divers over each other to hit that button
Holyshit
It's almost it's almost looks like Saved by the Bell just break the fourth wall in book
And be like
By the way I can turn back the Rock
What's Rodger Kmart
Miniature dachshund
Anything yet
How to spell expecting Rogers be like
Alex
She is just like
You like I have always told the truth and I told the
The house intelligence committee
Probably like
A deal put together where
Alex
Donates $100,000 to his legal defense fund
Every time he runs
Legal defense
Ever every time he goes dirty laundry
So they don't talk
Much more about this but they do spend a little time talking about that
The Criminal Justice Reform
And how
Let's talk about that
It's really extraordinary in Alaska
Withdrawing
In the ward legalizing marijuana
He's a Republican president with a republican Congress
He talks about marijuana reform
I imagine that everybody in the Republican
Control Congress again it is a 100% Republic
Can control Congress
And a Republican president and a republican Supreme Court
Literally any Trump trump
Says start talking about legalized
He starts talking about medical marijuana and just from this
Score from the Sun
You just hear sound
You see f****** Paul Ryan and Rand Paul put on like a Rastafarian
Criminal justice system
That is not
True
What does a
Go far enough but yeah I would work
Another pretty cool
Because one of the first
Is Bugatti
Did you sort of an extension
Things from the Obama era that are
I already made
Which is good I'm at
Like the Democrats
Justice Reform
Because Trump is
In favor of it
A sort of
Credibility
The largest voices and slide opposition were Kamala Harris who said that
You didn't think the reforms went far enough
But also didn't want your idealism allow quote
Perfect to be the enemy of Good Witch is
A good way to look at Elizabeth Warren
Because she also did
Didn't feel like it
Against the billets
There's more we
Literally all 12 navo to the Senate were Republican
The same is true of everyone is a 36-in
Not a single Democrat voted
So where is your argument there your argument is not
Liberals are against this
Because Trump is for it
It doesn't hold water this
Nonsense
I bet there's
There's no way you could
Marco Rubio
All that is just nonsense Rogerson
John Stockton
But
He's not the only one
Dislike sklep Alex
Might have started
Christmas
Nog because he's sort of burping his way to the dead pivot
We're going to broadcast
Trump's mind why he's doing this
Why you standing up
Are going to strike
Back Trump if you want prosperity
The Establishment denture a bunch of idiots
Shredded Robstown please don't forget free shipping
Free t-shirt
The sales have been going so well
That they are adequate
Is not good
I'm going to suggest the ark
He was drunk when you put Rodger
I have no idea
But I'm certain he started
And it's not just that
The barfi
There which is
Glaring
He was saying
Pretty gross stuff
Especially for Christmas
We were talking about
The globalist
Got
He's strangling
It's a manly thing to strangle
You decide
He's not thrilled
Obvious performance
First murder rap
He's got to
Get into another one
He's going to do it to be sweet
American Tire Biola
Replicate they sell K2
And you don't feel much like right
And the meek shall inherit the earth
Start biking
Trailer given shelter in the manger
Powerful stuff
At the office whenever you want
Look up usually likes
Constrictors
Please
Make it look organic
Because the radio station won't he worth it
Get back
F*** is this
F****** done sensical murder rant that leads into
Him singing one line Rodger to bring it when they come back
So f****** weird again
Can't stress this enough
This is Christmas
Secret system holidays for Alex Jones
I'm going to compare myself
The very thing that state
In my
Breaking Rodger Stone
He really brought it in
He brought in the way I wanted
He makes
But you've never lied
Intentionally
He has never
Like because you know that whole Lee after his Apollo
Miles Kwok
Batman had 200 million
I would like 100 million.
But it was Sam number salt
So OK Google
Yeah he's now gotten into
Damage control mode
The apology which is
Which is meid number told me bad things
Right
Knowingly lie
Is the Disco to the minute-long
And within minutes
Rodger Stone will say that
Never knowingly lied about anything
And then proceeded to lie
Seconds later about Alex.
Squeaky sword incredible smear
I reported
General McMaster
Trump
Diet Cokes with a slow-acting sedative narcotic
The timer
Rodger Stone
Tomorrow's weather
Flight
Just continue to recycle the same
So it
You say that
He has never reported things that are he knows are not true
15 seconds later he says that Alex
Never said that no one died it's
Bad news
You know that
Because if I worked for Alex Jones
Let's say I didn't know
Right
Back at the time
The accusation that he
Send it no one died and argued that quite a bit on his show
I would probably go and check
I would look into it I would want to know the truth because if the person I was working
2/14
I wouldn't want to work for it
I would want to be able to point
The things that you
Be able to defend my employer
Who was a noble and righteous person
There's no way that I would just go
Snow White
So the idea that Rodger
I could have plausible deniability that I don't know if it's true
True or not
He's not saying that he's never said
Did they are going to hire the
Disgraced reporter from
Almost
I never know
We made up those
I didn't I didn't even cut that stuff
Quite a bit
Because they were saying
Turn off I apologize 104
Like he was Bass
The only writing fake stories about how white people in
He was trying to
Award-winning journalist for German newspaper Der Spiegel was only writing about Texans
Alex is trying to
To create the perception that the lies and be fake stories
Is that he
You wrote about
Trying to
Summit Racing
Sabbatical
But not as much
Stretches the next clip
Russian Mastermind
Do notice though to it isn't
He's breathing a lot
The supposed Russian Mastermind
Hillary the Russians
Economy over
Sao Paulo
Movie agent in the United States
Former director of the FBI
And then became an FBI
If you are Kremlin agent the whole time
You are the top page
I'm not going to let it
Uranium
I just
I get the sense as I was as a listener
Haven't watched
Listening to it as
The radio yeah yeah
I got to see this
Theater of the mind will not actually doing things
But
I was watching
I really get
She wasn't drunk when he started the show and
He's drunk by the
You started taking some shots
Or something like that
I'm not sure it which
Hard to nail down
But he is he is not the same level of sober
Becky
It's not consistent everybody enjoy
Is an ice Chris
Everybody
Enjoy the nice little Tipple on the Christmas Eve
You know your 14 and your parents are like hey
Guess what
We're all going to enjoy this
Nice little Brandy
Gather
I want to make it clear I'm not judge
Puritan new saying don't drink but I haven't
I'm not even on that since I used to work at Groupon it was nothing but booze
You know I get it people are adults
No big deal
I do think you're in a position where you're
Putting out dangerous rhetoric
Came to the world
About matter
You probably should
If you're drunk you better be right
You better have your like all of your ducks in a row
If you're going to be wrong and
That sort of fun fun like yeah
That just doesn't work
When you're carrying water for
The deaths of people
Around the world and you're like slipping
Drunk and fun at work
It's not
Because
It's clear really shouldn't have been a conversation we needed to have
Yam
Chaka Khan
I am assuming that he is going to talk about the massive
Drop and how it was one of the worst days since the Great Depression
And the people don't get this
There's nothing they won't
Drudgereport.com
Despite
Buster's
Moonshine really think if
You were in love with Donald Trump you would know how to say Steve minucci
You would mention
Crescent Moon
You think you know the guy
Maybe it reminds me of how they couldn't pronounce
Tim Geithner
If you only seen this in print
Is this a new name
Stop it out
Isaac Eric Buckley write his script but it's all just like
This is not
But
They say that
People doing things I didn't do and the stock market
Boy back up
All he's doing is being opportunist
Think about the circumstances that are in front of him
Not taking it
Consideration
What happens tomorrow
A piece of the story that you're unaware of what happened yesterday
I'm kind of still fascinated I'm still fascinated whenever like
We do have those
Market update on
Regular news outlets
The stock market update
Doesn't really affect anything
Massively artificial intelligence
Like nobody knows what the f*** is going on
Those news shows even though like local news that happened
To fill an hour everyday like
You still have time you got a felony
You're just.
Sinclair are so Insidious
Problem
Which is feeling that
Whoever's watching
Doesn't
Necessarily
Santa Cruz weather
Most weather reports are unnecessary
Come on
How dare you on fire
I don't give a s***
Skillet
You don't have any
I have a deep-seated distrust
The weathermen
I really think I think
They are perverts
Well
Meteorology
People get into study
It's not something puns
The people study
A subset of the people who study who are also camera-ready
Is a very small
These people who are charismatic enough
And actually keep
And the weather in Knoxville like
Complete idiots reading the script
Those are two people know that their jobs are
So f****** protected when they go to cities like
Chicago la
New York those are things
Become institutions on the news
Specific about him at all
I think those people like him so much as he's just
Okay now I got it they know that they have
Security
Criminally pervert infection
Absolutely absolutely
Women
That we demand that our weathermen
Affair
Cell theory
I agree
Stock stuff
Point take
Before everything
Completely wrong
And this clip I'm only playing because
Cuz I think it is super important
And that is
So from time to time
With the idea of what
Because Alex is
Is copyrighted
And they're easily castlight
Fear in my mind that one day he'll just
Decide
It was for copyright infringe
Can what we do falls under fair use
Rules
I never want to deal with
Like I never one I never want to open that
Open court
Appointments nightclub because
It's Alex giving us permission
On the record
Just get the information out
We're doing our best Alex
Thanks buddy
Can we ask you for other favors like could you please do it so we can just play that clip in
I would love that I just want to get sued
Using Digital Millennium rolls take you down was it play that clinic
Judgment in favor of knowledge.
So like I said
Everything goes off
Because Alex has been having some
Also
He's got
Not much
Yeah maybe I mean he mentions that he's not going to have his are you going to have a rebroadcast
Christmas
Christmas Story What Christmas Means A Christmas message of love
Christian and religious
Which is his version
Start with the Tarot deck
There are a couple times that I
I just didn't
Excessive and repetitive
Christmas at all
Is it until Christmas are
You know we're not going to be able to get you the products by Christmas but
Ray Ferraro
That's what you think there is very little Christmas end
But one gift
Could you give some Eric
Is that Benjamin
Is now host
Failed failed comedian
Infowars 4th our house
Wolfies comedy career doing better now
He's doing great
Worried about
Google the rails in the third hour
He has a
Guest on the show it's actually two
If these people don't belong on air at all
All they have done
I can't remember their name
But it sounds something like
Spaghetti Brothers
I don't know
They created a flash game
So
It's a flash game that created Flash game
Google
Alex versus the end
PCS
Or something
6 more minutes
A plane
Aynax
Somebody
There'll be like a clip of lest
Somebody on
TV saying something
Speaking of Alex
You have to hit the button at the right time and it's them with an axe
The flight of Air Force One
All of them
On the way
Call
Trump shows up as a
And smiles upon
Very f*****-up
Hour-and-a-half baby I would say an hour and a half
Yeah because the game is about Alex
Heater
And he thinks it's the best thing in
We can search the name of Arkansas
I love Trump
Amazon that's great
Reminds me of
Mario
No tomorrow
Beef Anto
Like the actual assignment
Evil Sonic Mario
Yeah
Video game
Which video game
Complicity
This game
It's Alex Jones killing people with an axe
You taking down these empty
Subway
The world from
Are you trying to kill one of them
A new logo will pop up on the side of the screen
Pinterest
Absolutely what was the last time you saw a pin on Pinterest of Alex Jones
Apple pie
That would be nice
I wouldn't eat a tide pod
My very Drunk Kitchen
British Bake Off mixer
Because
The video game involves him killing
People with an ax
He finds a knack
This leads
Trouble
12 year old and have him kill a piggy bank again
Adult
You know what there were similarities
Because he was trying to
Impress
Is NPC
Going to go away
But these guys have
Make a fun game out of it
Buc-ee's
So he pulls out his
I believe it's a baby a Happy
This is why I had to go find the video
Because if you listen to this clip
I don't think you'll believe that
It accurately describes what is going on in studio
There's no one in the studio right now
Camerafi
About 30 feet away
My question is
This is going to mess up I don't want to mess up everything
Christmas Eve
You are
He's in the middle of his show
In my professional TV studio
With a f****** Hatchet
Very expensive camera
Money
I am going to throw this Hatchet in a metaphor for how I feel about my own show at this I wish to destroy
Troy the things that allow me to go deeper into this world that I am in
It's
Beasley bucked up
I feel like there is a bit of
Christmas Eve
Can you say that out loud
Christmas electronics
I thought
First of all
What the f*** is going on
It's so out of line with
Not only his
Most of
The time
He's gotta just be f****** around with these guys or something
He straight-up throwing hatchets around
It's a real Hatchet
It's a pretty big Hatchet
Why does he have a cigarette
I'm going to allow it because like
Somewhere
Multiple hatch
It's not the same Hatchet
He had a bunch of hatch
Should like
You have a bunch of guns
1 Hatcher
And this is actually kind of internet video f***** me up to guns one Hatchet
Did you see that one disposal might be Alex's soft launch into
You trying to
The Juggalos
Used to like him
Not like you Alec
So when I was watching
Completely blown away
What's happening
And then
Thought when you said
I get another try
I think that someone in studio
You've had enough
Calm down
Not go that way
Alex
Real quick
Audio of
The game
It has bat
Pictures of the
Video of the game
Wow or whatever it's for him
He's probably take
Another drink while the cameras
Again
Time's the charm right now
We're doing good
The third throw hit the wall
Where is it
It was literally like
6in from a fire extinguisher
This is crazy levels of irresponsible
I think that there's something if this is like
I don't know it's some sort of shock jock show
This is a major drunkenly throwing a hatchet
Different context
I'd be all for it
What act
Ditches
Broke my heart
Because God dammit
In history would be the headline
Alex Jones throws Hatchet
Blows up his own Studio
Play wouldn't blow up
Studio
Extinguisher
It's clear that the camera operator
Was very close to where is that
The guy
With a hatchet
Crazy Horse
It might hit one of the staff members
Incredibly f***** up.
Like a real crisis anything for him to have hit a gas line
And then at the end of the show
Click
Click click
Studio
Is she
Whoever's in charge
Like it
He keeps saying no one
Here but there are people there
Buckley or his dad
Normally keeps them in check isn't
Right
You guys be cool I'm the I'm the fun guy on the place on your fun parent
You guys want to smoke a little weed
Cuz I'm going to throw a f****** Hatchet
But I still think even though there's no Authority
You're there he went too far
Play go2 commercial they get done with this interview and he comes back
Commercial
You've clearly been told
You're done for the
Infowars has given the gift of thought
24 ninjas
LeBron James
Good looking
Humanity
Cplant hands are playing like a 10-minute
Special Report
Recorded apparently the day before
In a hotel room
It's it's
Clearly an instance of like
Whoever is
Legs are and on the level is like Alex
You're in no shape to be on air
For no f****** reason
Anyone
Weed eater
You from yourself
You're done it's a third our own Benjamin will be here to host the fourth hour
That's all you have to do
You got to go to bed
You got to take a napper
You're a danger to yourself and show you off
Truly
You are a physical Danger
Everyone
Before you were even that drunk
You told Rodger to contact
Croissant
We let you do the next 15 minutes really awful at
Also is whenever he admits to committing
Treason on-air you're like
Yeah I don't know
So that's that's where we we leave off cuz we
Who cares about his
James report
Is LeBron James report lot of bulshit
Christmas
Well I mean
You know he got injured
Say so that could be Alex
Kirby
Patriots
Tara's grind
So that could be Alex gets what he wants
We also get
To have LeBron back
Everybody wins
I mean that
This is all to say Merry Christmas to one and all
This is
This was crazy
Because when I sat down
Take a day off
From the nonsense
I thought it was going to be
Retelling of the story of Christmas
Maybe with him misinterpreting something right I thought it was going to be
Funny like him trying to weave around the idea of not allowing immigrants
Jesus would never have
I would I would I thought there was going to be something like that
Repackaging of
Miss mythology
Something
We get I told Rodger
Contact Julian
Massage
We get I'm drunk and throwing axe around the f****** Studio
Incapable of evil
It is just me so far gone
Unpredictable on a level
I know it's it's
Itsfunneh if you detach
A little bit
Devoid of the world we live in this is hilarious
Yes in the world we live
And very sad
If you're an uncle
Goatee
You go to your brother's sister's place
And their kids are
Hellraiser
Throwing Shade all around that you're like hahaha uncle
Yeah let's go
But if you're the parents you're like
Has burned
Goddamn the White House to the ground
Or is ruining everything
If you're the uncle but you guys live in
Like a duplex
We have to share
Department of
Unfortunate how
Beliefs
But he's espousing
Well Christmas Eve
This is what he brings
The table
Play music clearly
Like a hundred feet is 100% his way of expressing how guilty
About all week
Which is what you do
Which it the thing that even crazier is like this fundamental premise of his
Basically
Christian
White Western
Like that is what he does that's what he's done
Almost his entire career dating back to
The days of Waco in Oklahoma
Coming into Studio on Christmas Eve
And doing some sort of a
Fake intellectualized version of why Christmas is great
And the fact that he can't even get there
She's not having fun
The only thing you can have fun with
Anymore
Is getting really drunk
Throwing an axle rounded Studio
And that doesn't bode well for
For 2019
Nope
But if
Episode
The segment
I'm in
I feel empathy but at the same time I also thing
Cell
Whatever
That
Merry Christmas Alex
Christmas Alex
I wish you
That one Christie who see what he does for New Year's
Probably be
Oh man he is going to
Jack's
Countdown
We find out that is
Christmas gift
Fort Worth
That's what we learned earlier
Everybody just in case anybody misses
Episodes work in that like the single biggest news al-amin maybe literally said
Did Rodger die
Yeah it I mean yeah
There is that
The only reason I don't put too much stock in it is that
I do believe Alex
You saying that because it does it doesn't
Feel like
Is normal
Expressing that
And I know that
I'm not telling your business is that he's defensive about telling you I don't want to save it
If it was something that he was
He was like I was there
You know you were working at Fox News
You came on Danforth I'll leave it at that
The sort of thing that you always.
I wanted to hire you on the
A condition that you
Julian Assange
I mean it's f***** up
That's f*****
But I still don't know
What
Actions hours to Tucker.
The reach the level of
Indyref
Asian buffet
It's not even like a Mueller's that's just like a regular FBI
Regular SPI
Not invest
Some sort of timeline
Quest
Sure does
Like the idea of
When was
Obviously Alex does know because
Cuz you told him to
I don't know
Wasn't
While he was part of
That's true
And presumably after he's been Let Go by
Is he doesn't have a game
He gets this b******* off
From Alex
I want to help the Trump campaign out
Which kind of leveraging is
Even like
Rodger
Left
Champagne
You got fired I think that was
Yeah I agree
But
He left in August
Of 20
I'm sorry
Yeah
Even after Trump was saying
Maybe fire him and all that
Rodger was very cool
Clear public
He still supported Trump
Anti-hillary
But it was also
If if
The perception was that
He was fired it looks very magnanimous
Still supports Trump
Quit if you believe he
It looks like he just believed so strongly in
What Trump stands for
His whole line on it was I wasn't being defective
Champagne I could help out better outside
He never even though he quit / got fired whatever
Like even though that you never stopped supporting
Yeah so from the jump
In the campaign
No matter at what point
He was
Trying to reach out
Cast of trump or Alex
Which is weird
Reconsider
Camp
Hastobe
That's the only way any of his axe
Corsica
Nixon.
Nimrod for attention
Stop Rodger will
The the information
Don't come out till 2
Denial
Fake news all the stuff
Bobby Blue I tried to get
In touch with them sure I was
Yeah we're going to park because why bring something
It'll be something
Volcanoes have no idea all I know is what
Massage
I'm so Merry Christmas Alex
Alex
Please tell us about more crimes you have committed
Ortho borax
Cam
It's alright
You can find us on Facebook
Yep
Throw up throw has subscribe throw review throwing axe our way baby
Cameraman throw near here
Probably
Technically
Today
Translate
Alexandra Thurston color