Alexandra Thurston color
About
Hi Jordan
Is the last time you were
Like have you ever been hospitalized
For sickness
None of her sickness and Everest
Like what kind of infections
Alright like mono and
Strep throat
I've never had strep throat or is that like supposed to be
Bad really bad fevers
How to write it out
Good antibiotics
Whatever
I don't know. Really I don't get sick all that often when I do
Usually just like on par with like
Really like hangover those things that have been like the worst in my life
Chicken pox when I was really young
Remember that being kind of bad
BR broke my arm which will house
Prescribed
Of any kind
Is that crazy
That is kind of weird this never happened
But I've never been like I've never had like a disease
Overnight in hospitals for like sleep studies
And going for
Yeah
Sorry but you know what is great
Nice
Thanks
Really
In honor of that
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Jonathan
Also would like to say thank you to a propos twitch you are now a policy
I'm a policy wonk
You are now a gallery
Thank you Kevin
How grateful I am
Donate a little bit of
You are now
Natalya brilliant someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
Thank you so much I mean
Umme
It could be at and if it is I apologize
Roosevelt
The mispronunciation
Sorry
Appreciate a good palindrome
Able was I ere I saw Elba
Palindrome
Don't look at me like that
Idris
Race car
These are all palindrome able was I ere I saw Elba
That's good time joke
Fight.com
We would appreciate it
Very excited
Quiero knowledge fight
Which brings us to
Basically our second
Officially doing this
Before we get to the episode I wanted to take a moment
I've been thinking about it
What my favorite
On the show
Considered
Maybe for our New Year's Eve episode Witcher doing right now
Maybe we do a clip show
Maybe
Second of all
Do we do the top 10
Clips of Alex Jones
False
Uni sitting here listening to ourselves
I was taking a bath with other day I was thinking about
Like what was sticks out in my head as the best
Thing that we've uncovered on this show in 2018
I think I mean there's crime
Tragic story of
We learned that Alex Jones probably killed a guy
Which is
Pig stuff
I wanted to actually have you come in with your favorite thing and I have my favorite things I forgot to tell you
Going to give me
Comes up in your head certainly
I will say that the top thing for me is
Alex Jones
I re-watch that interview
Yeah that was great I forgot about this
Billares ask him where he found some like a docket like
Declassified information
History Channel
The most absurd thing ever and I think
That gets my title for best thing in 2018
On our show me recent Tobias
Because if my complete lack of any kind of memory
Man it's tough to beat a good vitamin the Apple filled life very fragile
Plus I want salad
What was there
Close to
Yeah those are real strong but the reason
I meant to say I respect your choice but I'm staying with mine
Is that I understand that
Nothing is named the best are best
The Reason by choice
Is better
Pittsburgh
In that interview Alex really demonstrates how he can't hang
Interview with someone who he's about four years
He has a guy there it's his chance to pin him down
Eddie can't do it
Because all of the information that he's been saying about this guy for years is all lies
So it just fully demonstrate
That Alex
Is
Full of s***
Likee flounders
It's super embarrassing
Has some relevance to some of the stuff over today because it's another instance
Alex
To the fire
But it's another instance of him just not being able to hang
It's like
You have put yourself
From the position of the guy you are Jordan
Do not not you
Right there is
Steve Kerr's The Bel-Airs kukoc
Yeah but
Examples of it's like the buzzer is coming down
Bill Ayers domestic terrorist embarrassed
Receive another instance of
The clock is winding Alex
Feet to the fire back to the wall
It's the bed I'm very excited about that
Over April 5th and 6th 2009
It's just
There's a lot
Start with an out-of-context drop
From today's episode
I would ask
Check out yourself
Because the biggest problem
Mostest
Is speculation or rumors and on my site
I love that
I would like you guys to
Who are listening to this
Is
I would like you to investigate I want you to call these sources
I want you to find secondary sources and I want you to get quotes on the record
I mean he's trying to present it as like
Take my word for it like I'm some sort of LeVar Burton
Reading Rainbow.
Panicked as well
Reading Rainbow that's a boy
Rank speculation
So don't just believe me cuz I'm saying
If you don't come out looking good
And this episode
You come out looking
Particularly bad
Now we're all the time
Here's the first.
Is there's been some bad stuff
That just happen
Their bits of murder
Alex
These murders
Because they kind of
Volcom
There have been a lot of horrible mass shooting people killing their old families
Spoiled rotten
Because you couldn't learn to speak English fast enough went into the place where
Debowler
Yesterday in Pittsburgh Pennsylvania
I wear this at Richard Andrew
Pulaski
20 something year old 22 year old man
Waited
M-43
To come to his mommy's house where you live
It's always you guys live with Mommy
I mean I don't know what the deal is with him
Point is is that shot
Two of the cops is Mother Weidman to the house
And then
He waited for more common nnn shot three more killing another one of them
And the mainstream media has certainly enjoy tying me and let me tell you
Raw Story
The Pittsburgh Post-Gazette and others
Because it's friends and family say that
You learned all submarines by the way
He warned of a plaintiff
Application
And I'm attacked on the newspapers
He goes off in another folder
Not me talking about your revolves around
22 year old guy who killed cops before he was taken alive
Coincidence
I assume the color of his skin had nothing to do with that I see no reason to believe he was he
Started to have a discussion about what motivated
His mom for telling him that he had to get rid of his dog because the dog
Peeing on the carpet they're always mad at
Started to get domestic violence they always call the police about this
Was the precipitated the shooting
Richard's friend Edward perkovich
The idea that Obama was coming to take everyone's guns
A large team of a documentary released a month before the shoot
Coincidence
Richard was a frequent poster on both Alex's Dyke front door he wants posted quote
The federal government mainstream media and banking system in the United States
Completely controlled by zionists interest
An economic collapse of the financial system is inevitable bring civil unrest if not outright
Balkanization of a continental United States
Sybil revolutionary racial War
This collapse is larger the engineered by the elite powers
B b in order to make up for a power and asset grab
Summer of Rage take the words do and Zionist out of there you got Alex to a f****** to eat
Under his f******
Whether or not that's actually the argument
Irrelevant
Are entirely base
He's a Pez dispenser
He clearly believed all the things that Alex put into the world but Alex doesn't want to talk too much about this case
Really he just wants to deflect attention
That's not me
Because
Richard was motivated by everything that Alex
There's a little
Wrinkle
Infowars forum
For being such players in the endgame many info Warriors are surprisingly unfamiliar with the Zionist
So
He was someone who clearly believes everything Alex was saying but felty wasn't hard enough on the Jews
This is the conversation Alex doesn't want to have
Because it very clearly illustrates how at least on some level
He's psychserves
The conduit towards people
Getting the message of Nazis
So you have this murderer
There's no reason to had to go that way seems like
I'd like the first time
Starts talking about the
The shootings I was
God
That's awful
I should remember that
And I don't because
Which shooting is it
And it's crazy because three cops were murdered
You don't remember don't remember
But they're still there still but
That should be a big moment for the 300 million people
What you're expressing is something that I feel so much when I go back
Necessarily
Something that should be a national tragedy
Everybody should know about that
So was that one of the ones in the schools or was that one of the ones outside
The school cuz there's been hundreds of
It goes to show like that
Feeling that Everyone likes to blame on Trump
Has been pervasive in our society for
Longer
Trump
Concerta
Human
Self-defense
What else is a joking about that she'll the pain of all of these things
You can't you can
Can't function
Yeah
Vicky's going to blame Obama
And the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette
And association with the shooting
The fatal shooting of three police
This is ridiculous they also attacked
Because we are delusional
You are descended
Kill some cops
Barack Obama
That sounds right
I think that this also illustrate Alex's
Incapable or unwilling dealing with
Horrible things
Things that people who happened
A white pill
He thinks he's being hard on him but he lives with his mommy
These guys pathetic
Winner winner
People
Three young Muslim girls walking to the pool supply store
Animals
Just want to be in the Marines
For coming to get it that's what happened
And right I mean that's a big angle that Alex
But it's all Lotus
Semi-automatic handguns and rifles
And a psychologically test all Americans own guns
And to have an attorney general who Lobby last year
Talk about Eric Holder
Having
The lobby before The Supreme Court
Eric Holder didn't argue in front of the Supreme Court 2008
With a bunch of people
Doesn't necessarily protect
Individuals right to own firearms
Outside of a well-regulated militia
People make
About
Tation of the second
Directions
Decided Amicus brief with a bunch of people it wasn't like
Supreme Court Justice
But that's the image Alex wants
Mr. holder ghost
Right
Earlier right there you heard Alex say
Obama's trying to push
To have psychological
Testing for guns
And only because I think this is a very this is very important
Here is Alex from his interview
Patrick bet-david
In 2018
Saying what you think
Good gun
Control
I believe in the 2nd Amendment added criminals or any guns regardless
But I do think with mental-health other issues
Background checks probably good if you
Call prescription right now you're taking Prozac whatever it is some of the medication list that we have
That is either for bipolar or whatever you know things that we just talked about
Those folks can't get a gun you're okay with that
Here's the thing 30% of women are on those drugs about 15% a minute
And it doesn't sound right
Don't act like
People that are on those drugs
When the insert says I can make it be a killer
They should be looked at
I think if somebody has been
And is almost drives this be a database and you shouldn't be able to fire
Alex's own definition of Alex Jones is a gun grabber
Psychological
Testing for it
If you are at your Aunt psychiatric medication there should be a list
Need to cut through a lot of the bulshit
Because what Alex Jones is doing
Is perpetuating
The exact
Kind of fear
That made this guy end up shooting
He's going on Aaron blaming Obama
Hotel
Cesaro all that stuff is actually really good of course people
Mental issues
He's just he's a monster.
Is
When you boil it down his argument
Obama is coming for your guns
And that's what you get
You know if you told
You're going to get
Dead Cops also which suggested he's justified in a way
A little bit
Perpetuate
I guess the idea that this guy who killed these cops
Wasn't optional
You know the idea that he was afraid of Obama taking his gun
That was exactly that wasn't based on a propaganda narrative put out by the right-wing and now like Alex
He is actually justify these letters
Should be
He's mad that everybody is like
Connect
Because of the optic
Problem right
That is messed up you minimize it for exactly the other reason that you would expect
Copper cops
And it barely gets any news coverage they want to play that down
Real quick I need to stop
Here because I listen
Do all of his shows
Haha
Bring up
Illegal immigrants killing
I hate that I
Keep saying illegal immigrants just because he
You keep saying right
Right
People aren't
He's presenting the idea that
He covers be stories frequently of undocumented immigrants killing cops and just doesn't
He doesn't
He's given himself some sort of like
A backstory of every other day I talked about an immigrant till in the car I don't want
And that's not
He is in this case
Because they don't want to get the police lobbies upset about the open borders
Sure California where the tent cities are
They coming to take people's children they take their winnebago's of the insurance is down
Point of order
Robbed
Undocumented immigrant Mexican
You got to leave those immigrants
Hey teacher leave those
Mnm cops or even below
1 cops killed by illegals
But also it's big national news
That guy's reading habits and what he was reading
So he's real defensive about that
Because
On some level whether realizes
He's a propaganda outlet that is
Doing exactly what he insist
Everyone else is doing and this is one of the unfortunate
This isn't it
Inevitable
Yep that some people will respond
Do you know whether it's by
By virtue of Tristram sort of chemical imbalance
Experience
Incorrectly or whatever
Because of
The fears that
You create now in the same way is that like you get it you make a shotty seatbelt
Hundred thousand people will die but six million
These companies do that
Send whatever
Does the same thing which is like
This rhetoric is super dangerous
And a bunch of people are going to hurt other
But the rest of them that don't are going to give me money
I think that's what he has to do
Setting aside money for the legal funds for the people that they're killing as opposed to
Fixing the problem they're doing that mass of like
Well it cost us this much to settle a massive loss
As opposed to a process this much to actually not
Kill 1000
And as a corollary the same thing is true
It's more profitable to run that risk exactly whenever these instances happen
Might as well
The one that blew up
That is true
Clips
Yeah I'm watching these young listen
Watching these episodes I'm taking notes
This is one of the only times
Go look at my notebooks
There's an hour
Not good
Alex starts taking
Call
Probably the most
Sing f****** call I've ever heard on his show
Talk to Mark and New York Mark welcome
I'll try you doing I just want to thank you I picked up a short way that's how I ran into you
And then I picked up
The Obama Deception
I cried most of the way through it
But when I saw your face I saw two things Alexei so emanuar man's man
And I saw a father
So I can tell you
What was Sean Hannity's and everybody else I don't know what they think when they look in her mirror at night before they put their kids to bed
But at least Alex Jones cuz she's not only a man he's also a father
Oh God oh God
Know how to emotionally connect with Eddie
You said maybe build up this massive emotional wall of life
You cried during the Obama I don't have no no no no no no
Why is your first thought
You got to call your work some s*** out or you got a like
Deal with the fact that your ex-wife has your kids
You f***** up is not what I would have more and Alex's icon
Exactly the same thing
Over again because the words not making much then
And that's proof
You know I saw your film and ice
Cried through it and I thought there's a man
And like you said the same thing over again
This is trouble I want a documentary
Market New York
Trying to take anybody's
What okay
So we watch
The Obama Justice
What
Would make you cry
Also consider multiple
Focus documentary
No
So he's eight
Crying on new stuff all the time
I can't imagine that being your response to it I could understand
Through it I was Furious
Wanted
Nothing like that I would ever understand
Ryan
The country must be that
Black people
I don't know if you responded really when I told you that I cried through a lot of
Review Andy Daly
Review like you thought that was that was a little bit weird
I don't think I had timing I guess in retrospect now I disagree with my whatever okay
You experience
Incredibles
Yeah there's a tragedy connect
What could be
Of the character of forest
Right I think they're possibly like
The Warped version of that
Experience Alex as the narrator of that documentary the guy who
Trying his hardest in a tragic exotic struggle against
Triggers
Emotion
Now that you bring it up there isn't a little bit of a parallel
Go between
Andy Daly and review and Alex Jones Show
Destroy all personal relationships in
Service of the show the image of like
They're being a point where they could have been saved
Gotten a divorce for the show that your life would have been completely same with Alex it's like maybe if you hadn't joined Trump
Maybe if you hadn't gotten involved and the river
Never ending cycle
That up but if you
Then you know what
Yeah you you're still divorced but look at how much better everything is okay no you didn't do that
Alright if you stopped
With the Sandy Hooks
You're seeing you could have changed things you could have gone if you'd never met all these
Yeah it's kind of Alex's kind of like a
Emotionally interesting Dumber version
But it's equal a psychopath
Yeah
Noah
Anyway
Whatever you think
So that's the end of the fifth that's all we're going to cover their
We move on to the sticks
My friend
Is
What I
This to me
Is exactly why we play the game
Yeah we we find like
All of this is worth my neck report stuff comes right
This is equally exciting
Because
Your minute fishing trip Alex had to cancel
Spoiler alert
At a time
To cover Glenn Beck
Forthcoming debunking a FEMA camp
And so
April 6th
Is it Monday
That's the day that going back is going to be
FEMA camp
He's run out of time to create a video so he has to do it live on air
Right Alex has the ball
He's open
You know it's just on you
Get the ball in the hole
You've been talkin about FEMA camps
Entire f****** career
All you have to do
Is coherently make your point
And you have won the basketball game
That is all and I have no idea why I thought
Tragic embarrassed
But it's even worse than I thought
I thought it could be I thought there was a chance
Stumble and fall in like
Or just save eggs dolphin
He's him just rambling about nothing and sayings
Number of specific instances of things
And they're all pathetic
Put up
Yeah but you could just be a dick to Glenn Beck and call it a day
I wash it
Something with lunatic I'm sure he was
F****** stupid about it too it was pretty little bit further down the road but
Lamest thing
My life
We'll start the episode
And Alex is going to
Introduce
He's about to do
So he has to do it today it's not like I'm going to do this
Almost is using language that indicate I don't
But I also know that if everyone's going to speak
Need ground to Glenn Beck
I can't let that happen.
After you can't
I'm pretty sure actually Alex does have mold
Glenn Beck's
Predictions about what
No way.
Based on
The possibility
That a mole at Fox News
Has told him what Glenn Beck's
Because like
He does make
I stuck an absurdly specific
Prediction about him
A Amtrak station
It is one of the like popular internet videos
So for him to specifically latch on to that one so strongly
Leads me to believe that he hadn't
Whatever I want Market New York
Internecine Bowl between the two
Bishop campsite
Glenn Beck Kobe also
That's why you sending over all these things
Glenn Beck's not a man or a father
That's right but that's
Glenn Beck
So is that first clip I think we saw
Market
Get Wellmark marks 2019 Geo year
Marksman
Using there I think very clearly in
Cape a sense of
I have to do
And I think that carries
Next
He starts
Immediately making excuses for why it's not going to be that great
So they're in there right now
He's talking about his producer
So they're in a race
Miami Herald
Fridge training compass
You said a couple things that were kind of
Miami Herald Argus
Riedel not specific enough
Do you do is go through the database of every article that the Miami Herald
Lord knows
I do know that you do want to do that that's
That the scary things
First of all because I am a hundred percent sure
He is like
Look they're going to do it a lot in there
There's hundreds of things you have to do whatever we end up doing here
Shut up I had to go fishing
And then the second
Something is Isaac
A shifting of the goalposts
Cuz he starts talking about troops on the street
And stuff like that confiscating guns
Stuff like that
That's not the future
Can't stop I know that Alex likes to pretend that all of this is connected
But that's not the conversation to Glenn Beck
It has nothing to do with it
Debunking this is a moving of the goalposts
You artificially run-up
Is score going to make it look like
I'm making points
Make a point about
Troops doing exercises all that stuff
It's even more overwhelming
Mike stuff about his
Camp stuff
So it's it's
It's ludicrous.
The day before this
He was rightly pilloried for
Being a man to murder the troops on the streets
Narrative
Keep in mind before
There's a method to my madness
Cuz there's there's a reason I kept
What he ends up doing on this show is telling people to kill cops
You bet
Very least like
It is what inspired this guy to be a nurse position where you
Doesn't matter why
Well you have to exercise your second amendment includes
You can also kill cops if they come
Further well-regulated militia or whatever
But he's not going to
He's going to complain about Robert Reich
Labor secretary Robert Reich
Maxwell quotes
He didn't say that
Even if he did say that that does not relate to socialism
And then
That doesn't make sense
Let's
Youth race targeting that's not socialist that's what's it called
American
Robert Reich had a comet
We don't want it to all go to
Construction worker
Yeah that was it you were talking about how their needs
Not
Just
White Construction 10 he didn't come out and say
You didn't say that
Don't know why this quote
Me a quote so quote literally no one said that
He said quote
Look up
I would love to say but I still will
No
To misquote somebody
Much more oppressed
Or if they were going for some sort of ghoulish Overkill like advocating for wet
When that might be
Just so you know our donations
For next year all go to none
Bright
So in this next clip Alex
You already sucked out this idea
The exact same thing that reads
Do this guy in Pittsburgh killing three cop
He doubled down on it
Voting
Automatic
For a complete
State senator Illinois
Direct General last year
Justice department
Attorney General
Supreme Court
Shot shotgun or handgun
No firearms
. only police and military
Right now
It's in Supreme Court website
Read all of it but I read enough
To know the reality
Yeah
Disregards back today
Suicide signs
Eric Holder was a deputy attorney
General until 2000
He wasn't
At the time
Like the. Of time
No
Versatile
Was going on he was working in private practice
Because easy was
News from d.c.
There was a
Right
Yeah absolutely
He wasn't it
General at the time
At all
Alex is mixing
All this time lineup in
XYZ they're all coming to take your guns
So it's all hot
The reason
Is still
You still Fair
Myself and Glenn Beck
My Media Matters run by Mr Brock of former neocon
Long story and of course
But in the same ways that rage filled Achilles
Is an epithet that runs through
The
Yeah everytime almost every time
The epithet rage-filled Achilles
Is in its very right
I read it but most of the characters in epithets along with them
Characterizing their characters
Modern times
Whenever
Talk about Media Matters
He says
Soros and Media Matters
Soros-funded Media Matters
Neocon
And also
Knows Larry Nichols from those days
Issue
For me is that
Bring up Media Matters
Without bring up Sora
The idea that he had been
Like starting to bring up the roast a little bit right but not still not a big bad guy
It makes me think that we might have read a little bit more into that then there was
Vicky has no
Targeting of Soros yet
Defunded thing
Alright be supported responded
Bright
That's super in
Obama
Eric Holder for the shooting
I think it's even like
Amatis
He blames the Pooh
Was Mister Rogers from Mister Rogers
Neighborhood
Looking for
Material material material
Try to bolster their whole world
Going to get a lot of cops killed
Give the police implement the cops are pulling
They're going to
Oh my God
Did you just understand black people in America
The most important
I don't
I don't want to go too far down that road put it it
You just said it a very interesting point
I don't want to go
Too far down that road
You're still stupid
What is advocating
I guess the position
Self
Going
In my research about all these other weird things
I found that there is a improv quartet
Musical quartet
In the Austin area
Police chief
RAC take out I thought that was really funny
I wish there was a baby
Fusion quartet door whatever
Miac worldview
If you are the Pentatonix
Change your name to Maya
Your garbage
In this case
So specific
Those cops are responding to a domestic disturbance that this guy was responsible
Before he was the one who
The person who is wrong
There's no evidence that they did anything
Wrong in this situation
The shooting
To happen
So for Alex
Using
This sort of rhetoric
It legitimately is to
Blame the victim of murder for the actions of the murderer
Well I understand it's not it's not the first time but
That's not cool
No I don't want to be here defending cops or anything like that but
Defending them as murder victim has nothing to do with
Is David Auntie cop goes I'm on your team but I'm still not like
Let's murder indiscriminate
Almost certainly he would have
Beat her up or killed her like that is
I know we can't like fantasy book what if it's all if this then that
Yeah history or whatever
But you look at through this person
With this track record
He was doing that
There's a really good chance he would have caused
Terrible
She did the thing
Protect yourself that you could
It's a horrible thing of the only person to blame is
The guy who did it
Yep
The further conversation is
The places where he was getting his in
Information
Let him to
You could also blame all women for sometimes
See now this is what I was hoping to get you
It's women for sometimes being mean to taking us two years but finally working here
You got to stop being a little bit
Close to the real argument
Exactly
If we just had a gun ban on like
People who have been suspected of domestic violence or have had the cops called on them for domestic violence
Dispute
Murders we go way way down really would
The last two years of like mass shooting
Really horrifying because the numbers don't tell story
But if you look at their website
You can go to the
Like spreadsheets
Local news reports
About you
You go to them and
Hear the stories of what they are your hundred percent right
Like almost all of the
People
But it's a drastic
Majority of that
Violence
In that area
If Alex Jones
Preserving
The Second Amendment
All that
Interested in cata unnecessary gun murders
That is the one
Should be in favor of
F****** never talks about it
And it shows just give a s***
Even for the NRA or anything like that
Like if you're really smart
Because right
Which is there really smart
As far as that
You got credit for being monsters through and through
Because they haven't
Nothing
There's no real like meaningful legislation about control
Acceptance that maybe we shouldn't have bump stocks around and it's like
In the first
You read the articles about that bump stock ban most
Gun sales people
We don't really sell many of these anyway they're horrible for accuracy it's almost pointless product
Almost like their existence is
Purely to murder
Debate
Symbolic
Control thing more than
Anyway
We're getting too far off track
He does not give us
And if you did there will be other things that you would
Which suggested possible
Cuz he's even denying that there is a problem
He's denying
The reality of the
Situation at all
Deny the facts
This guy was inspired by who
Q word right
Basically like
And Alex Watts
Nothing to do with that
F****** fishing with his kids
Really f****** drive in 50 minutes
The episode
Alex gets
He has Max Keiser coming on for the last hour of the show
Has a good hour and a half
To do his debunked
Already complained
There's too much information
I don't know how I'm going to do this
Too much information
I'll tell you how it for as long as nothing for them in the show
Max Keiser about his fake currency for the last hour
Here is the
Alex
Japanese toe
Into talking
Wrong Glenn Beck
100 news articles
Because I can
Will do
He starts us
50 minutes
Let's hear
Actually starts the hour and 20 minutes
Broadcast
Supporters are dangerous
Regardless
We're going to expose you understand
Eclipse and news articles
Point of order could have had a production meeting
Alex Jones has
Limited
No one is controlling anything he does
In terms of like
He had a show some of that could have covered the material could have done the first hour of the
Bump Max Keiser
Doesn't f****** matter next Kaiser would still come next week or whatever come on next
Kaiser's happy to be there
That's irrelevant
Outside internet
And one of the reasons
Is there something
Does a bunch
At this period of
Career
He goes into
Overdrive
Is the term
Overdrive do not know what that
Very frequent
And that is when his show
Cheats for the radio
He broadcast on his own website
He has the infrastructure
Few more calls another hour I know where
Remembers
All that she has run
Limited time
Information
To get out there
Preemptively making excuse
Is it going to be
Now I want to say this very f****** clearly
If you only have time to get it to 10%
You better get into the best 10
10% I don't understand why
Go fuc yourself in like I can do an hour
Which is 60 minutes
10% of that
6 minutes
Perhaps the Showcase
I'm just going to have Hazard leeches what material I do
Time to get into the goods
Stop Dan if you want to hear my better material go somewhere else
To go this is Alex
Doing his big Markie
About
This is it
And it would end if he did it
Look he does have OverDrive
He can go on his own show
Tents
Read out all the documents implications the
The name the name
Devastating
Revolution
Unfortunately none of it is
10:25 making excuses
Alex finally gets to
The big FEMA camp debunking
End.
This starts out
Bad
Hour and 30 minutes
How is controlled by the National Security Council
Okay I already got to stop you
On like a technicality because FEMA is Under the Umbrella of the Department of home
Homeland Security
Stretch
There are a ton of organization
The fall under the heading of national
Bearded Barber
Because their role is obviously a
You know it involves National Security there's a ton of place departments like immigration
Services
Coastguard Customs Enforcement
All of that is under the heading of
Department of National
The department oversees preparedness for responding
Natural
Natural birth
Is absolutely something that belongs in the Department of National Security
Housing it anywhere else
Would be a bureaucratic
Mistake
The problem is
The National Security Council is not the Department of National City
The president's National Security advisor is a regular attendee of the National Security Council meetings
But it's not considered to be an essential player in the council
Cancel
Is made up of members
Like the president presidents
Treasury
The National Intelligence advisor of the chairman of the
A regular attempt but not remember
The Department of National Security as hell because they're under 6
Department of National Security is headed by the Secretary of Homeland Security
Who is not a statutory member of the National Security Council
It does is not required
These are two
Different things
Or your your argument with Alex right now
By saying is controlled by the National Security Council it's not it's in the neck
Department of Nash
Which are
Similar but not the same thing
Razee
It is
Crazy that he doesn't understand the
I cannot see why you were so excited
Go fuc yourself
You you you just had your Michael Jordan slam dunk moments
And it's only going to get worse from here if the shot on Ehlo
Scored on the opposite rim
Accidentally scored for the Cavs
Like this
Beginning part
First of all
Is even more poorly
Council controls
Presidential
The one on the right
America
And the courts are ceremonial under the present so they use cotton
As a way to basically shut up
He's talking about the
He won the presidential
Directive
He's using that to argue I've heard him argue this
FEMA under the Nash
Council
And that it makes everyone slaves and makes the Congress ceremony
None of this is
Department of Homeland Security
Like 1000
Before that
Responsibilities are handled by Hud
In the seventies as a solitary
Independent agency
Before that another run by chud's
Chard
Cannibalistic
Humanoid Underground
P-51 presidential
Decisions directive 51 also known as the National Security and Homeland Security Presidential Directive
Until May
Fourth 22007
I had literally nothing
It has to do with continuity plans
Catastrophic
Emergency
And largely deals with the national
Is very different from
Department of Homeland
Gymnastics
Yeah it makes it just
It just rolls off the tongue the right way near like probably
Talking about how power is
In retrospect
You know
We're living now with Trump as President should retract all of his open
Is president said stuff like that the groundwork
So the idea that Homeland Security
I'm sorry
51 of course
The document specifically says inspection to
The goal is coming up with a framework for
National government
Find a quote
A Cooperative effort among Executives legislative
Judicial branches
The Federal
My coordinates
As a matter of Comedy
Disrespect
Do the legislative and judicial branches
And with proper respect
For the Constitutional separation
Anna Powers among the branches
To preserve the concert
No framework under which the nation
Capabilities
Three branches of government
To execute constant
Responsibility
And provide for orderly succession
Appropriate transition of leadership
Ability and support of the national essential function
During a catastrophic
That clearly discuss
Branches of government
And separation of power
It's Section 5 in
It even goes on to enumerate what are considered nationalist
There must be preserved
What do you think the first thing listed is
Quote ensuring the continued functioning of our form of government under the Constitution including the function
Separate branches of government
It's section 92 even stay quote
Each branch of the federal government is responsible for its own continuity program
88 the way Alex is treating
This story now is if I heard all of what you said
And then
I was like
Stanton would like instead of Comedy
So this whole thing is a joke Dan
That's how you know what they're really
Is when they write comedy with Amy
It's legitimately that level of misunderstanding
It's locked up
He's trying to say that the executive branch
Is absorbing all of the
Power Inn
The legislative
Judicial subordinates
I've read.
Congress's ceremonial
The actual text
Preserving these branches of government
Preserving their separateness and are.
Delineate
Get out
Very specific
Ptd 51 established a new position
The national continuity Corden
Who coordinate with Apartments about their continuity planning
This position was designated specifically to
Exist quote without exercising directive Authority
Meaning they can't make any rule
Right
It's a coordinate
Are you doing that
How about you
You do that
Okay cool they don't have to get involved with each other's business because that of course
Would defeat the f******
To the federal government
Responsible for its own continuity program
Just going to decide yours for you but we are going to say you better have one
That's what this document is doing
You what
Some sort of Mastermind sort of Ozzy man who's organized
We need to be prepared
The document also lays out the responsibilities of the secretary
Security +
And none of them are
Build
Most of them are like assef local readiness
Response
Tastrophe
And stuff like
Conduct red unisex
Code
Taking your gun
Also spoiler alert pb51 was really just an update in the PD 67 which is
Issued by Bill Clinton on October 21st
Which was Excel it's just an updating of HW Bush's PD d69
92 which was itself an updated as National Security director
Which itself was an update and Reagan's and sd55
From September 14th 1980
All I will say is you guys got
Your f****** numbering
That did not work out right
So wait so president under the new president the directive
Number reset executive orders
Well we should be on you need a coordinator e1244 right now
I don't disagree with you does make things a little confusing but
All of this stuff is to save that
There was
There's a sense that
Need to know what's going to happen when there's an emergency
We got that emergency happen
We don't have time to make a plan
No.
Before you
Prepared
Yeah I read all these things that I've read the argument
People like Alexandra Patriots and stuff make them
Because they don't take
You do need to be
Ready
Like
Hey
Worst case scenario someone sets off a bomb in Congress and
50 senators.
Leave some
What do you do that
We should have a plan in place
These directives that have been
Sent down since
At least 19:8
82 have been
Convey incent
That we need a plan when something happens
Even if that thing is
For unlikely
Cuz if that happened
We are fuc
But that's what their deal
If you are
Caring for something
They say
You are f****** planning on doing it Alex
If you don't prepare for something
Your fault
Prepared
That's the way when either way
Food that'll like go bad in your attic
And then blame you if you didn't use it
Right right
See this one
See that's what I'm saying the government
Cuz they want it
To happen like it doesn't matter it's a lot of nonsense
We're like
Less than a minute in Alex's already misrepresented the idea that FEMA is under the national
Security Council
What is the Department of Asheville
Security completely lied
About
The reality
T1 and the history of it all that stuff so
Like deep Waters
Alex is
He's out of his
This is going to be
Like legitimately he is
The guy
And that is
That's your first
Minute
Sad
Susan Evans right after that first minute we think it's worse than even I think
Also books
News articles on the subject
Is there so much
Show many Congressional hearings
Start
But I will start
Going over the fact
That
Supporters should be arrested in the army
Good good
I don't even know where to start
Where I will start however is
Bitching about this guy
Glenn Beck sucks
Bad
Sign
Now that's not
That means
You got
Nothing
I'll just give you my emotional experience
Of listening to this episode
FEMA camp
Pronged
Response the first was excitement cuz I like
He's got to come correct
Second one
This is going to be
Which you did
I kind of did there was there was a
According Byzantine
Both of your Bronx
When we
Do the first hour of the show
About this Alex
You are like me
College
You didn't prepare for an exam the night before
I'm just replacing Donkey Kong Country will see what happen
He's living in this in that space of like well I didn't prepare for this so if it goes well
I didn't prepare
He is but he's not presenting
Problem
Of course he's not like he's wrong
That like females under the national
Security Council
I'm like
No
And I'm like
Oh really like
Worried
And then it was like where to start
Glenn Beck sucks on like
You have nothing
I was
Blown Away studying him for
And I was even shocked
By how little he
Recognize that this matters
Like this is a historical
The day Alex Jones
Had to talk about FEMA camps
Any subs
Definitive way
And he's like
Glenn Beck
Motherfuker
If that's where you
I know you could have totally legit like
Push it back
I even wanted to get your Kohl's
Information that I wanted to lay out but you know what
I just got so busy
Defending White
People from murder
I was very worried about
About who
Competence I think is what I'm looking for yeah I was worried about his ability to actually
But I didn't think
We're like an hour and 25 minutes into his show
Next Kaiser's coming in
3 hour mark
Do you got a good
You know our
25 hour 30 in there
Maybe
Our
With commercial take that I don't know what you're going to talk
I don't know I don't know how your
What you got
Barb
Photocopies
Miami Herald
When they had pressure home
Hearings dealing with Shadow government
Martial law
Herold Rd
Wants to talk about FEMA camps
Fonzo
Reagan aids for the secret government
And it's about
Iran-Contra Affair
Either were or pretend to have been involved so I don't know what to do with that I mean
Is that what you want to start with a misrepresented article about Trucking Oliver
North
Has Oliver North doing
What's he up to these days
He's running the NRA
I know that Oliver North
No proposed that Rex 84
Use some of that talks about that
Martial law
Here it is
The only way they can pass this bill
Is by creating and sustaining a panic atmosphere
Miss fear is not justified
Many of us were told in private conversations
Did we voted against this bill
On Monday
And a few members were even
Martial law in America if we voted
Sparta
Through The Obama Deception this is Bradshaw
The house number
The show in clarified
Talk about what's real
This is
This is where your
You're coming with
Here's proof proof of a proof of FEMA camps
A congressman said
Something
Vig
But it's like
Interlake
What Brad Sherman was talking about was
Consequences
Which was about like the idea they're like
For the game of telephone one guy says
This is bad Alex
Nose that isn't
Proof of anything
What do you even weirder is that
The very situation that he is siding Brad Sherman for
Incorrect about is the situation that Alex is
Everyone should be in a
In order for these things to occur
I'm going to create a state of constant panic
In order to stop
I guess
So I actually f***** up
Candy flip
Apologize
Because
Cuz at this point Alex Jones brings up Army regulation 210 dash 35
Disease civilian inmate labor
For program
So he brings that up as
Real.
Apologize I weigh
He's got talk about it later
But he starts talking about how this is
Slave everybody and
Who is who is not
Regulations
Into 10-35 with
Plane from 2005
The place where they would take several prisoners
And put them to work on Army base
The reason for this was that it would be cheaper for them
Quotes
As well as
Crowding in prison
I want to be clear nothing I'm going to say is an anyway advocate
This program or saying that it's okay but I am sitting out
It's quite frankly a gross extension to convict leasing program
Keep slavery around without calling it that Nan that I'm strongly against
However Alex should have no fear of this program being used against him
Infection paragraph
The document lists
The source of inmates that are eligible for the program
And getting out of this program
F****** easy
They don't accept any sex
Offenders and violent
The Flight Risk
Anyone who's been quote involved in drugs within the last 3 years
Even drugs imprison anyone incarcerated for selling drugs anyone who's had a Vonage
Give me problem at another facility anyone who committed arson
The list goes on and on
No because there is another qualification about like being part of a criminal conspiracy
The reason they aren't interested in anybody who fits those descriptions is because this is about getting cheap
People who fit those described
Have a potential to make
This is a gross
Evil program
Which I have
It's absurd
Can anything other than abusive Financial arranged
Yeah they just one place
Birchbox
What's further
To the point
This
Document from
Isn't about starting
It
Clear if you read it that it's been going on a long time but this is what program is this
This program is like
Is literally them spelling out we want house slaves we don't want
People who are going to be a flight
Well
Naruto are the part that's difficult for me
Zip code for me is that I can't quite
Figure out exactly
Because I feel like
But at the same time about in the document that these people who would be used
Wouldn't be allowed
2 Cummins contact
I think it's like digging ditches
We have cotton plantations
Something like that
Custodial work
Cuz you're not allowed as one of these inmates they go into 8
Quarters of the
I think it has to
You just like
Really shity
Yeah yeah
And of course
I'm against it
Angle on this should
He is protecting the rights of the
These prisoners
Ice human
Not that it's
Think about this very real thing
In the way he's talking about it
What he does
Is make
A good portion of the
Opposition to it
Complaining
Searcy theorist
Yelling about a real thing in a fake
We need to legislate forthright
Fasteners
And also you should see it as an extension of the thing that's going on at the actual prison
You know this is that this isn't something that you still for into
Just what incarceration is
Like it is a
The f*****-up thing to learn that like
The Army is
Using slave labor from
We should really get on this whole like the 13th amendment was a good
Not
The fifth
Is that like
Alex
Perpetuating this idea that they're just going to
Prison so you can get into the slave program
That's kind of the argument
Inmate labor program
And even if you
The worst about the
The program
Because they don't
We got to marry man but I hate to relate this to buy playing civilization but like I love having a
The Builder around
The weights are realtors and over and over again
The idea of incarcerating tons and tons
The people in these
Labor program
You would end up with
An excess of labor at that point interested in that
4 hours
Pacifically
If he was
For some reason by some miracle charged
With probably
Manslaughter charge
That's a violent crime
Fillmore and I guarantee he would have a quota management
Problem
Afraid of being put in
Do the civilian labor program
I would say if
You get arrested for somebody
There's a fee for this I will say that
It's crazy this is so stupid
It's really like
If you want to talk about the substance
Tissues in the real world about this
You have to talk about prison
You have to talk about like the underground
The fact that this is like one of Alex's
Those big pieces of
I mean
It's as close as he gets to real
But it's still wrong
It's not
It's not correct minimizing the real problem which is
Slaves are still around
That's what he's doing he's like
Hey they're going to turn you into slaves
Without ever saying
Hey we already have slight think I've ever heard Alex a convict
Necklacing
But I don't think I've ever heard talk about reality
Those
It just served
Continue slavery
People people are becoming more
I think that's a positive
I hope so
I think
I think we're getting
Dealing with
But I still
Long socks
Episode whenever
Real that the Republicans
Clearly the point like
So many Republicans everytime they pull out that like we're the party of Lincoln
Where are the party that freed the slaves
It's like well you guys wake up everyday
Slaves man
It's malicious app
It's not OU
A party we don't want to appear weak on continuing slavery
Democrats
Alex talks about that a little bit
Beginning of sorry that I did
B
And why whatever he was
Was full of s***
Any we'll talk about it later
And you'll see some
So now at this
Glenn Beck
B*******
Zoe
Had his Pro
We're getting hundreds
He forgot something very important
Says the president is a dictator
Oh four point
It's just so much right documents
About parents
And so we've got all of this year
Look
Makes it so governor
You know they they're just serve at the Wyndham
The president American history
Pretty sure if a
As somebody who is
Just a small amount of
I'm pretty sure that at
Any point in
The president can
You're fired
Right
Governor
There's language
The president can send out National
State of emergency
If martial law is declared
Which previously was up to
Governor
Create a very weird set
If there was
President
Requested National Guard troops
And the governor said
Knox
Interesting situation
Every time
That's a good present
Question
The governor pullout National Guard troops
They have
I don't know I don't know if I sick but my point is that I think
Generally
If there were like
Or if there were
A horrible natural disaster
Yeah the present
Word to say
I would like National Guard
The governor would always say
Bypass that step
Is not going to Funk
Emotionally change
That much would have a little bit of discomfort
With that
Maybe
Maybe there's something worth retaining and saying that the governor in present
Coordinate on that
Maybe you know what I actually
Ceremony
I am concerned about how norms
Violation of so many political Norm
And
Because imagine imagine for a moment
Trump
Having some sort of effort
Having some sort of temperature
We're going to send Arizona's National Guard to the Border
Imagine that Evan
The governor of one of those dates is like hey
No we can't do that
That makes sense
I want to keep that one in place
There's a middle ground that makes the most
Give me the president not doing it unless it is a necessary emerge
Requisite
Middle-ground is coordination
The president for the governor should necessarily
Have final say on
I think it should be some sort of
Quorum thing
Where we balance
Respect
Responsibility
Sovereignty of the state
Reality of the situation
Four other states
I think there is a middle ground that
Is
Easy to preserve
As for the most
Of life
Who is just directing National Guard troops anywhere
Governor can be like
No I do we can't we
We can't be doing
Whittier adult an adult we can't be doing this
Send
If if
The president
Is so bad
Control
And the
The governor is like no Nash
Guard troops
That President will just send in the army
The point of like
It being
Controllable by the governor
Yeah that's
That's true for the United States versus New Mexico
Situation where there's a
Crazy f****** governor who is not going to send the next
Guard troops
Even though f****** earthquake
Just destroyed
Right now that's where
Brady's coming at you know that
Private sector comes in
Fixes everything
Cars for kids without a front for
It's complicated and I don't think I 100% support
But I also
Believe
Reddit
I've read that
I don't think
That figure
And I think it is specifically about catastrophic
Emergency
Right like they do talk about like
What sort of emergency
It would be relevant
Cause
It'll be like
It would be a huge
Like let's say a meteor
New Madrid fault
Extreme enough for everybody
Pretty Lights
You like to eat something
Hanzo's levels
Fox
And I don't think
Streamlining who's
Is responsible for
Is necessarily A
Because in
That whole thing about
Like you have to do preparation
Before the event otherwise the preparation preparation
Yeah everything is good in talapoin
We're past that point
We all need to be working on the same page
I kind of understand where that comes
Know the things
The show has really doing the show the shows
Doing the show
Really given me far more appreciative
Is the literal language
That
Players to have to write or or these kinds of things
What it is like
Yeah this this conversation we're having is
One of such specified
Then if you
Buck up the language like a little bit
Then you have some
Place for Alex Jones
What you're talking about
Come on there's layers upon layers there's like Alex at the bottom with just
Wildnout
Knights of nonsense
Misunderstand
Zipline
A pretending that everything
Sing of the secret code
Understand
And nuance
Even better
And it's just unfortunate that
It's just unfortunate that Alex
Yeah it's another way to put it
F****** dumb
The next wants to make
Gibson tours
Religion
Of course of course
He's trying to make his really don't know how that has anything to do with FEMA
He's going all over
If you need
The broad spectrum in order make
Good
He has to get ABC
In order to make point B
Because point B is
Or non-existent
That alphabet
They're not
They look fine
You look better
When all of them
Some is greater than the parts
That's it
Stinks
The clergy Response Team martial law
Pacify the secret FEMA program
Tell him take shots
They're paying on the television sets
Sounds creepy if your problems with Romans 13
F****** Bible
Cuz it does say that all authority on Earth is destined by God or whatever
Bring up the Bible that they gave to Slaves prior to
What were they ripped out all of those Passage
Images about being free and all that s*** the ones that was
Entirely about submitting to Authority
Pastor Walt Mansfield who came out and became a whistleblower by the government and list
Pastor is to indoctrinate their parishioners there's no official confirmation of any of this
Who I don't trust
Alex fields
About any of this
He plays a news clip
KLM
Google clergy response
News 12
Just Google clergy response teams
Send me all the
I think it's from Louisa
But if you find if you go and listen to this horribly.
Local news
Clip is playing
The pastor
The guy named dr. Gerald Phil which is an awful name
Dr. Darrell cooperville
The deal is but dr. tuberville quote serves as a Chaplain for the Shreveport fire department and
Sheriff's Office
He's a government employee
None of this proves in any way that the government is going out and trying to
Unless your pastor to turn them against he is the chaplain for the fire department
Sheriff's office in recruiting pastors
Pacified the fire department
Dick the interview that they do
Really scary
Yeah
FEMA programs
Dude
Like
What else
Shots because
Walk YouTube
The only interview in this whole very poorly
News
Production
Is
The guy who
Works for
I've tried to find any evidence
Like Alex talks about the clergy response
20 something thousand
Preachers across the country there is nothing
Nothing
It is kind of
You hear somebody be like
Don't believe the Bible
Alex says that a bit.
The only place where is the scripture that's like
Even the devil
Can quote scripture
Or there's that one
Yeah I got you
The only sure has themselves covered coming and going don't they
Response Team stuff is a loadable
There is nothing behind
If anyone can prove it to me I will change my position
Champs
Response
Exist
I will only believe
That it is
Actual
Who are Gotham
Employees
Like this track
And stuff like that committed volunteers
The government already
Who's server role to make sure that
People don't
You Crazy Russ
I will go so far as to say that it is a show by Dick Wolf
That is as far as I will go
I would like to see that show
Find Bowser can come to
This stuff
I just think it's terrible
Yeah cuz
Whereabouts
3 minutes into Alex's actual breakdown of the
He has a proxy
20 minutes total to talk about it because Max guy
That's a hard out on
Proving my point
I don't think he's proven his worth
I don't think he's proven his
Everyone please feel free
Free to go listen to Alex
April 6th 2000
The 9 episode of
It's not too hard to
If you want to debunked the idea
That I'm not bringing up every substitute
Facts about
Go for it I don't give a good luck
She is said so much nonsense
Back
Obliquely reference
He said the Miami Herald article in the 80s and I said I can go on
Spent all his time doing stuff
Stuff like that
He's done nothing
To prove to me
In any way
FEMA camp
Absolutely
More important
Isaac
And II
And probably
Maybe but there has to
To be some overlap
Alex Jones
Definitely
Hasn't even
Improvement
To those p
That Glen
Nor is he actually rebutted anything that Glenn Beck
Really
Could
You want
The most generous to Alex
What he's done is
Create substantiv thing
Like the inmate labor camp program at
But he knows that Glenn Beck won't talk about Glenn Beck
Make me like you never touch that
Not like
It's good it's good for
What I'm saying is we're 40 minutes
And he says this is also
Problem
Go over
Title
Here is the text of HR 645 National Emergency
Establishment
We'll run
Knightley movies
Well it's not that bad
40 minutes
Debunking the started an hour and 20 minutes into his f****** show
Of news that saves FEMA camp
That's not good cuz your s***
Before this says HR 645
This bill that involves the clergy response teams and nightly movies8 f****** doesn't
Andy died in committee
It was a builder's super unpopular this dude pitched a couple times before
FEMA camps
I'm going to say it
It should have accounted for the future.
Who's going to watch The Wire
We need nightly
Homeland have a chance
My favorite show ever Foothill stable
Yeah
Nonsense isn't in the bill
But the reasons it has never had any
Retraction is largely
Because of the
Problems
You need to repurpose a bunch of playwright
People could go in an emerge
Correct
F*** that me up
Demonstration of lack of preparation
The fact
HR 645
Alex doesn't know that at
He should know that
I'm talking about your health
But it wasn't
Yay
Never went anywhere
That is what he comes in first with his
This is the build its going to do it not recognized
Volume
Unsuccessful ping pong
It's not good and it gets worse when he gets to his next article in here we go
Hundred
In the stack of
FEMA camp
It's labeled FEMA
Wall Street Journal homeland security contract
Free 1000000% FEMA camps in the United States
Okay
This is a story about an engineering and construction company being awarded a contract to support ice facilities
Also Alex fails to mention in the article that in the article
We are also have this contract
2002-2005
Because if it is about
Weather going back to at least 2,000
Course
It's all this is about
Creating
This is.
This isn't this isn't real strong atrocity
You could be useful
I like you.
Also let's be honest
385 million is
Nothing's what it would require to Cree
FEMA camp
Control the entire scale altamed
Drop in the bucket
In there for dinner
Hayward
ER has now been given all this money in order to
Champs.
Contract
The time that you
And it was about Isis
Second
About these
Contract
That are going around
The prove that FEMA camps exist
Here's the New York
Halliburton subsidiary get the contract to add temporary
Immigration Detention Center just like
Martial law
Halliburton subsidiaries
Now the bigger picture in that clip is that Alex is saying that
Rex 84
Ruby Skye
Immigrants come again but it would really be a plan to make martial law
Remind everyone that in 28
Alex said
Trump is initiating Rex
Before
Because it was acting
I thought it was about martial law but it's really actually about the immigrants
Crazy games
A hundred percent
It's all about
The ghost white whiteness you could wait you can see that demonstrated so clearly it's
Especially when he's talking about the exact same thing
He's talking about
I have the secret knowledge
That it's not
Really about illegal immigrant
In 2018
When he sang the Trump is putting rx80
The action
He says
Look
The reality is it appeared to be about locking up the Patriot
But it's actually about
Making sure our borders are so
Whatever
Nonsense it's really
I want him to be
Better
Do you know what that is thought that I had repeat
Yeah I really I really did
Like
Look
Whatever
Intubate with Alex Jones I'd probably lose
It would it would probably
I want to respect
I could use a monster
You really bad dude
And I'm against him like I
Play my wife about being against him
Better
Legitimately
Prove
You have one objective
You go in
Nose-to-the-grindstone
Adjust
F****** do it
And this is the outcome
It is disappointing
Know this whole thing reminds me so much
Much of an argument with my
Any argument where it's like
You're mine
Family
I want
To love you
I don't want to
If you're going to be
The thing that you're doing at least to the level where I'm not
Comes down to
Necessarily with your fam
Handle this level of
Yeah
I thought
Alex
Oh you poor bastard I thought there was a chance you poor back to the last
2 years of episodes that I've been listening listen to the right episode
Maybe he had a lot of fucken gas in the tank
He has to prove
I'm going to be in trouble because he's actually going to prove you thought he was going to pull
Drop a hammer
I did I really really did
Howlongtobeat
Think that he was going to be there was a party
O'Reilly's liars and frauds
Like all the time if you want to like I think there's an impulse
Polite Society
They just don't want to push
Who's back on
Your conflict
I mean
Don't be afraid of pushing back
Stuff like this because
This is the day
Yeah supposed to come correct
Pathetic
We're still in the Alex's stack
Another one
Also
George Bush
Doesn't sound right
That was the internment camps
I mean I'm not cutting sudeste with the same way the Germans preserve f******
Like instances where he
Says
Like
Good points for react
Nothing specific I can look in
Alex is actually correct
That bush
Reserve internment
Park services to restore and pay
Search
Preserved
A reminder of how the United States
Turn down some of its own citizens at a time of fear
Yes 100%
Yes tournament to Historic Site
Museums of the National Park Service
At the time bushes Finance
From WWII already served
The plan was just to
This is not
There's no f******
Piece of this at all that is bushes
Trying to reopen
Right
We can all learn
At least super valuable where you wish they were publicized more so more people
Diamond be like
American not being that great isn't
Indication that
You hate America
Or anything like that
In order to make America
As good as it
Again
Those sorts of
First order
Horrible things that we
We've done we need to
What I represent a references earlier but the slave Bible there likes
4 copies in America
This place really really damning and imp
Important piece of his
Because you understand
That and you say they were against slavery
You know
That these people
Went into the f****** Bible
Self-important
Remove
Every path
About any kind of free
Every single part of that Bible
Mention baby you shouldn't be a f****** slave they removed
And gave it to slate
They use the Rangers
Purpose
Religion as a weapon against freedom and equality
The weapon against
Everyone being people
Religion
In order
Just own up to those things
Celebrate
I don't mean celebrate like Horeb understand
Jesus
Denying them just
Thumbs up if you want to say how great your f****** Bible is then you also have to
Except that there are people
Always
Alter the Bible
To make it do what
They wanted to
The simple a workout
That's what I texted or not
Bible do
Jesus up sorry
Ashok
Jordan
We've seen some things
Is that Alex has brought
Receive
Call wise but yeah you're giving things a lot of weight and that's it
Alex has to work there are work just substantially like that's
We've seen Alex use a lot of ghosts very clear
At the beginning of no substance
But I do think he said
Fayetteville civilian inmate labor program is a thing
Conversation to have
You having his
It was called
Civilian weird were slaves
Tdd 51 is a real thing
These news articles Miami Herald article article
Like all this stuff is like
He's lying
The government
Oh that's
Executive orders
Actually
Probably
It tickled me more than
Numbers
I've ever discovered America
I thought I would go over
Executive orders
President
Testing emergency preparedness functions
Okay
And this is just one of 11
Thousand
Supervision
You can go read that if you
You'd like to
So this is an executive order from JFK who I thought Alex was the last real president
The Federal Reserve
You're using blazing the public you put out
Put in executive order 11000
Really nice of him to make it a nice
Even number
Yeah that's great Alex half
In his conception
Mississippi truhitte wrong about it
Coup
Put on executive order
That was going to
Federal Reserve which being murdered by the evil forces under the sway of the Federal Reserve
He put out an executive order
Athens Enslaved the American public good with abet the rough with the smooth or whatever like this
Is nonsensical
Also disorder was overturned by Nixon's executive order 11 490
Binding today
What is 11000 + 1
Around 4 11001
Also has been no vaccines executive
Even if it has been overturned and all that stuff
Even if it were still
Today
Do anything
Even in emergencies
Situation
That executive order 11000 was
Instructions
Use civilian
Power that was available
In a crisis
Section 4 C
Laser
Create
Incentive
For people to join the civilian labor force
Quote
Develop plans and procedures for wage and salary compensation at death and disability compensation
For authorized civil defense workers and as appropriate
Measures for unemployment payments
Re-employment write-in occupational safety and other protections
For the civilian labor force during emerging
This is about
Non
Government
Like non-military employees in this
Is not
I'm going to get stripped can script you a ride military government
Employee is like hey
We should probably pay people in
Gas there is that but it's also how best
To use the resources
Does that are available military
People during crisis
That is literally nothing
Executive order
A lot
About like
Using
Civilian
Power in a crisis situation
But understood correctly
It's not talking about like
All the civilians
To do that
It's not like it's not like taking shaking down your apartment building and using you all to dig a ditch
About non-military government employees billions
Women during World War like they were like okay well
How about you guys built
To do that no
Encourage through
But there wasn't
Conscription
This is all like
This is crazy
First of all
I know but I can't
I can't get over it the idea that Alex
Is just throwing this out without bringing up yet
Executive order it's not like
He didn't do that
Like an executive order
He has all the control the world over what executive orders he puts out
That is part of being
President to do with it
Wasn't too is that
But it's also way before then this is nonsense man from up from a like
Fix proper propaganda
Big problem
Yeah because they undercut so much of the other propaganda
I need to put in the water
He's not talking about the Federal Reserve nonsense
He can imagine that all that stuff doesn't feel like
Yeah really does
And so for him to believe
The JFK was such a
Threatening president
The globalist
Who are in charge of the Federal Reserve
Call Sophie
It just doesn't they got the whole they got the whole back
It just doesn't
Makes I wish it was none of this makes sense
It's over 9000
Yeah that'd be great
I got back
He also talks about a couple other executive orders
10990 Weisgarber to take over all modes of transportation to control on highways
Defense authorization act and others
Executive order 10,000 995
Emergency alerts
It goes on like that
Quite a while
Let me ask you a question real quick
How far into Obama
What you mean when this episode
Recorded so where at
January 20th
I it's not about Obama
I know but essentially what he saying is that
Obama has
Accelerated these programs
S450
What's years
And most of them aren't already been on.
Like executive order 10 990
Executive order didn't allow the Takeover all of all the roads and s*** like that
Cancel to overseed
Civilian federal government employees
That's why I was order 11 6
12 in 1971 titled quote occupational safety and health programs for federal employees
Know that photo that was for
Powder before yeah sorry
Apologies executive executive order 10995 that he brought up
We'll take the Takeover of the
About emergence
Broadcast
Trump is forcing people to get cell phone messages
I've never gotten one
Yeah yeah
You're fine
Fall back
Also nothing contained in this order Shelby
Jurisdiction of
The Federal Communication
Checks and balances even in that executive order
Also that exact
Order was revoked on
Executive order 11
But here's the bigger picture
Four-door Nixon but Nixon
Manma
Executive orders
Insult
In order to confuse and annoy
A little bit
Yeah is actually give me a window
Who's getting the info
If he's rattling office
Series of executive order
Does that suggest
But somebody else is already
Compiled
T-Series
That suggested
Somebody has already put together a list of these executive orders
Suggesting what Alex is already about to say you can look up who has
Compile this kind of list of orders before and what
Their motivations are. I assume you've done zero research at all because this is
Not really r-mo
Alex's literally reading off a chain email
No
His wording about what executive orders is literal
Exactly word for word 121
One from a
You can find on factcheck.org
Does any research capabilities
He's literally on this episode reading off something your grandma might have said
Like this is ridiculous
Because diesel forward forward forward
The government coming to kill
Like this is embarrassing level
But yeah
Executive orders
Google
I figured out why I was trying to figure out
Like I don't I don't believe in executive order put out in the seventies made all
Road
Under the sea
It also seems like the
Why haven't they done that
Like why has it been 40-50 years that they they
Had control of everything and then been like
Forcella
The snake news
How much slow-playing do you need
Like that's what I'm saying
So I looked the executive orders
Three of them that he said
How can I be right back checked out
Dot-org articles
Yay early 2000
Time frame
And it weighs a similar time.
What do you mean by that
Early 2000
What time. Are we in
This
Has a list of executive order
And descriptions of what they are
The
Are not correct
They don't
Alex
Literally
Is reading off
You can you can
But it's
It's crazy for me to try and describe what I mean by this week
Because I'm not going to
Play that clip
I was as I was
Hearing him read
Is the next like
Oh my God
It's almost like a strip
He's just now
God dammit
Maybe what we should have been angry at the
This whole time is Alec
Texas grandma
No cuz she was soft killed by a vaccine
Why do I know that
We should have been angry at
Off of his me whatever he was growing up
Anyway Alex reads a bunch of
Executive orders
Where's which are all spurious and they're all just
He has done no research
He hasn't read the executive orders
If he had he would know that most
Shazam don't stay
Sammy Sosa
Executive orders
Now I want to get more versus the strawman argument
I'll stay with you
Unfortunate
Is that like a I've covered these exact
Active orders now we're going to get to the FEMA camps
Yeah
This is all supposed to be about the FEMA camps
At all
Continue to forgot that this entire episode
Every time we do it
Okay
He has got to be focused about this one thing Ryan to do this
Are you for real this is what the episode is about and honestly that mirrors bikes
Listening to
We're doing the FEMA camp episode right I understand if you want to talk about
Right
Gunn g agree
It's
Not
We're talking about a funeral
Oh now I'm interested
Has he ever
Focused on one topic
I mean he's trying
No I mean but like have we ever
Well we're two years in the closest was that episode that disgraceful
Oh yeah
Then that one was like
Cuz that was just the way for him to ramble on about 10 million different other
Said he was pretty on point
You stay
Close to the harbor
My mind so much as
It's one of the times that it's really stuck out
The show Almost
Entirely about
Yeah
He tries sometimes
Episode
Argue for the ban of Muslims
Like I think he tried to do that
We failed
Cuz that episode is all over
You know what I think. It reminds me of my
Hey I've changed
I'm changing
Remind remind me of my favorite moments of 2018
Hearing him say
I'm a big fan of dead down to Grand Prix
Might have been the hardest I've laughed wow like just listening to a show
So I think that does deserve it if we're making a
2018 Mount Rushmore
That
Bill Ayers is in there
Mount Rushmore
So
Like I just think
This is really
I feel like I've lost a little bit of my interest
In talking about how bad
Mirrors
My experience
I came in guns blazing
Pens blazing is like
Take a note
45 minutes
I'm starting to talk about
FEMA camps
Boo
I don't not doing him saying things I disagree with eyebright
It's it's just
What I
The reason I'm deeply ashamed that I forgot that clip about the
Inmate labor program earlier
Is because
When he gets back
From break
He says I've covered these executive orders were going to get back at ya
When he comes back from break this is what he brings up
And I thought
This is the white flag of surrender I have no
Civilian inmate labor camp program Army regulation 210
If you only heard that is the first time
Chinese bring it up right
Explain why
Not know that stuff
But it's not
This is him bringing it back up
Half an hour later after he's already talked about it yet
It's new information right
He talks about it
And just
This is the big piece of news
If not new
This is to establish
Prison labor camps
Representative
Policy statement
Governing Provisions operating civilian prison camps
Installations
He's just reading the headings
Yeah he has no ability to
Have a conversation about what
Chris Pratt
If you have
Don't have the information
To have a conversation about what is
Right back
That to me is
Incredibly
This is the second time it's been brought up
In terms of this
This whole FEMA camp
Big news
It's not new
Is 4 years after
Yeah of course
And
That to me is
Real f******
If you have a car like a propagandist
Like
Or even pestova
Probably
Generally speaking
Wade into Waters that they don't know something about
Right deflector
That's not what we really talked
Yeah that's a part of it but also it is
You'll never pin me down position
On whatever it is
Prepared to talk about not saying I'm going to have
Republican debate
When I See This sort of behavior
From Alex when I see him have the
Labor camp program
Document
On camera
Like and he's just reading the headings
With no no
Awareness of what it's
And about yet
I just see a shower light ICA
Loquacious
Yeah I like it's just someone who's
Good at
And doing somebody
No one is forced to
To do this
No one
His foursome
To sit down
Enforcing to proved FEMA camps exist
Piece of evidence
That he brought up
Understand
He doesn't know how to have a
Is deeply depressing
He's trying
Through this
Is we get to this point
Use the bunker
Yeah
Throw whatever spaghetti
Narrative
See recently this is a new one
Urban training at Arcadia in April this is going on
Practice writing the local gun shop
This is for domestic operations
The only way you would ever have that perception
If you read the Infowars article about
Because that's not what have
An exercise
That one
That was such a bummer like that was a bummer
To the point to the point where you're like
Man
Come on
Just leave that one out
Leave nothing less than nothing to it
Happened to
Weeks ago or something like that
In the timeline in 2009
We covered like
Like this should be a piece of your mythology
If you're talkin about FEMA
Champs
You have a
50 year span to get your information from
And one of the things
You're going to throw out is Ally from
Weeks ago
You are f******
Dead in the water
This sucks
So at this point
Done his
Like this is it
Done with call Quest
Exploded in the fire of pre-emptive debunked
I was thinking about
Eclipse from here
Debunking
Was guy from popular
Alex
You can love me again
Call Vina debunked
Owners of opposition are everything
Did some
Articles about
Ideas about
Physic
Naruto
You're wrong about 9/11
IRobot
How many versions
Loose change
Is it more than 5
Cuz it is
There's a lot of information
Sorry about that one Popular Mechanics
Ran a
Debunking 911
Lincoln welder into mechanics
How do you ring a minute I thought so
Construction
Fall at Esquire the academic
I'm way more interested in Reading because I assumed that it was very close to like a
Bodybuilding
It's just for mechanics
Instead of somewhere in the middle
There's a lot of s*** articles and stuff
There's also some
It's a magazine
Against
Lucci documentary
Do you have it
Do you think
They were wrong about 9/11
And then in the same
Breath
Being fine with doing what
He did
About 9/11
Loose change
Had to
Doing what
Their movie was
Because there's s***
Proven wrong
I thought you meant like a nap so I thought you meant in a nap
Distract sense of life
Oh you made loose change but other people have made the same documentary
You mean that there were literally six
Different versions of because Jim kept being proved wrong
Yep gacha
I did not understand that Dillon Avery
And I was involved as well.
Versions of it because things are like
That can't
I appreciate
Very clearly associated with
Legacy of 911 truth
I'm not going to say the Popular Mechanics
I'm not going to stay there
Right on all fronts
But I'm going to say
With them over there
So Glenn Beck has this guy
Exxon
F****** boring
Alex is fairly close to
Predictions that he make
It's about like the idea that they're going to go to
These these FEMA
Some stuff like that
This is Mark from Newark playing
Totally text step 3
There is like there is that Colonel of like
I think
If I were out
And I didn't
A mole at
Yeah I would probably
Adjust Bank online
She has to do a TV
He's not going to
King Soopers
Say 4 hours plus whatever discretionary time. In order to broadcast
The reality of the situation
Just going to respond to the most
Popular internet
What are the most popular
FEMA camps
I wouldn't
I think if there's any
Threat
There is just enough
A necessity
To do
Right there's no there's no threat
Episode
He could have run a whole long list of like
Glenn Beck
Point and then I'm going to deflect away from it and do that I would argue that
Necessary
It makes way more sense than to
Preemptively be wrong at not wrong about his predictions about what Glenn Beck is going
Stay
Preemptively
If I were his like advisor I was like his wormtongue I be like
We got to stop don't worry about the
We got to stop giving him advice
Even even in 2009 we got to stop
For so long
Don't even worry about this put on some
Some sunglasses
Just be like
Get drunk in studio
And just be like
Hold on 28
2018 Alex
Take The High Ground of just
Being cooler than him
Can't prove your point
It's been demonstrated because they're not true
Part of that problem
Serious problem for your argument
Don't try triple Lindy
Land it that's that's kind of the argument I'm
I would make
I feel like you just invalidated cool
I feel like Alex
Is now the Jamaican vibes
Bobsled team
And you are ruining
Here's the problem with your metaphor
Those people
UPN a bobsled team
The reason no one said that it was absurd to think they could not be
Because they
Have the goods they could run there were like
Wheeled cart all of the relevant skills
Possible
I don't
I think that Alex just
The good
I know that I'm just like
Here's the problem
Yeah what's the problem
Took my problem is like
I think that I think that
Real life
And all that but
There's so much more in all
Cut out all the stuff
Just
Ransom
Yeah
I just
We Have Heard
Like literally
We've heard enough
And that's why I'm getting really
What about this
It's because Alex has done an hour and 20 minutes
Of talking about his
Defensive
And all we've heard is him
Moving the goalposts
You know mentioning
Executive orders that he got from us
Fear chain email right we've heard news stories that are about different
Not about
He's talking about
A couple of oblique references to the Iran-Contra scandal
We've heard the citizen
Pavilion
Labor program
The different cops
Having
None of this is real. The fact that you're putting together
Damning indictment of the fact
Is going to come off as though it was
In such a way that it looks like I'm wrestling with that right now
A hundred percent
I think that
If this was your
Look you have done
This was your moment
Suddenly betray all of our trucks
It would be a real real coup d'etat
The only
Phasing f****** turn for you if you would he'll turn on Hollywood Hogan
Folding pocket aces for two years of the goddamn World Series of Poker
Lego
Yeah
Kevin Nash
People like wrestling references and I haven't
Bring this up
For me I honestly think
This is maybe a like
An episode of our show
But this is a varsity level episode of Alex
Perez needs to be
You come correct
And I don't want anyone
Like I know that I am
Coming back with you articulated perfectly
I hacked
Distress
I'm not
The stuff that is not included in the clip
Is so boring
Stupid nonsense
Of him just Randy
Randomly referencing dumb s***
That isn't specific all the stuff like document
So we get to this point
And Alex says this
Which
Pink
And I've gone over most of this together lot of other
Gotten into
Association
New York Times Wall Street Journal
Brenton Wood martial law
He's shown you the New York Times and Washington
Postel
Article is his only reference to Congress being
Threatened with martial law
Jim Hoffer
In Hafiz
I'm showing you all the documents when they're getting the space ready for Marshall Lauder National compulsory service
National service
Defense department civilian expeditionary Workforce
Directed 1404 point
A7
This is just
Department events
Directive
Representing what civilian
It's a non-military
Employees that work for the
Department
Vacay
Drafted
Essential Personnel can be made to go overseas
Working art
Aaron Lewis
Freak
Call Jessica
But also
If you don't want to
It's a job
The part of the
Department
Yep do it's not forcing you into a
CID
First of all
Is a misunderstanding
Civilian
Events
Are you kidding me
The f****** idea that
To create something
Is the army
Of our country
The biggest most-funded army
Yeah in the world
We're going to create a
Times that Obama's hold on
Excuse me colonel
Foxface
I'm not going to do your f****** dirty
I quit
Really how it works
I think it is just role-played exactly okay well I mean I could still use
Paycheck though so like
Can you resend me your best
Personnel
Positioned slightly
Essential
You have to take a pay cut probably
I mean
Principles do demand that I
Move Department
Is that cool
Oh okay
So he's not on the level
Okay well then can I
Go back to my old job
Yeah
Sure I'm not an improv guy
And that literal one.
I think what's really interesting
Sing about that last clip
Is that you can tell
Beginning of it at
Like right
I have done it
I've made this clear I've shown you all this stuff
And you show anybody
His pride and how spectacularly wrong
Is
Admirable
In a certain sense
Cause of how bad
Something
Slim
He has brought
Nothing
So here is the last
Alex makes it close
I think that this is a
But I got surprised to hear all
Because what
Talk about that murder episode
And how that relates to Alex
Talking about the FEMA camps top you are so good at bringing the hammer
You can read
Army regulation
Right now
I did that
What do I get
I get The Raw Story
It says
Prisonplanet US troops in Homeland
Silver is Mankind's oldest natural antibiotic
I left
It's not my fault it's your fault
He's what is all comes
That is what you trying to express
Even when
Debunking of
Glenn Beck
Supposed debunker of the FEMA camps
It's still just on some level 8 defensive like
I don't want to feel bad
Did not expect you to drop that
I didn't expect it to happen
So what just happened was this entire rambling
Nonsense
Nanja bunking
Somebody else's
Was really about him justifying himself not being the cause of the murder of three
I mean I don't think it was meant to be
But
Like that to me was
Like much more revealing than anything red in the axles
Yeah
Cops
Like maybe the
Keyboard apps
Control a lot longer than we realize cuz like that
Hilarious because that's a Wipeout
I imagined been like 15 different guys who have worked
And every time
He's like okay
I'm going to let you train the next guy
I know you were
Resigned
Stay on for another couple weeks
Extreme the next
And the entire two weeks has been being like
Okay so he
What year is it
This one is
Whack
Do
Block Rocker
Curvy
Pausing a lot
Block Rockin
Give me that he's failing
Rowan
Everyone listening
There's like a flowchart guide
Looked
John with the clips
We're done with his like
Whatever it is
I mean I don't know
I don't know what to say about this like
Write this is like
Hate to use our
What is own cosmology
Colonel Travis at the Alamo
Cloister himself
Mobile
Yeah but himself into a bubble
Like his
The only evidence
He was able to
Provide
Veryable
It's all
Nonsense
It's all s***
Or misdirection
The idea of the civilian labor
Kroger
Real and that the conversation we all should
Buckingham
But the
He's not having to write
Conversation about that
So even the things that are true
AR
Miscues
IComfort
You failed you failed
When
Dismount
The laughing
You say
After this arambol
Break
Yeah
Parting shot
It's not my fault
It's your fault
Yeah that's sort of
I don't think
I don't think that that's where it
You was trying to do this for at least
Like trying to do
Like I'm going to
Debunked
I wanted him
F******
Because I wanted
A good
Gladiator
To meet me
I want
I love this pic you wanted to test yourself against the best
I love you
And I love this
I love what we do
I wanted
This episode
Alex Jones
Nose to the
Keystone right
He is just
Working is
Trying to make sure
Did you know that he is never been lying about FEMA camp and it's all f****** true
From the jump
As soon as he started talking about it
It's like
The National Security Council and the department of national security problem
Is
Just miss representation
Why like I wanted
Even if you got off to that pic
Okay
Fifa.com is ruled by the National Security
I would have
Forgiving it
If the other things he was saying we're like
Some sort of
Proof of his cancer
It started bad
Middle bad
Nick finished bad
This is like a bad
Comedy
Shut up
That you go to
Iraq
No
Goddamn point man I was going to what
Wrong that's not the right way to do things but Thursday
You know like that's what you wanted Alex to have
His motivation
Play Sublime
I get it
And we can have a more robust conversation about that other than
He's wrong about this
He's wrong about that
It was so easy
The show that
The only thing that
I think if we look back
Marginally interested
Governors
Having power over the National Guard
Which I think is a really weirdly specific thing for us to be like
I have conflicting
FEMA camp in
Well the separation of powers is
Civilian labor camps others like a hundred percent.
Alex you're on the wrong side of this year
Are they talking about
Crazy to me
It's crazy
I know I
I recognize this as I'm saying
I know
Did everyone listening
8D
Deeply deeply
F***** up for me
Bestowed
You like it so f***** up
I know I don't know why
Keeps
It's crazy
It's crazy that I still hold out hope
It it's behind it's it's it's that
If there's some there's some part of me that thinks there's like
Stop
He's going to tomorrow he's going to get it right
He's not Alec
Idiot
Do you think racist
And that's never going to change
I think it's
He so often
Talks about topic
Text that we're alike
If you would just
If you would
Cuz it's not
It's not far from his narrative it's not it's if you just
If you would just turn it from like this thing to like not even 180 to 10 degrees in the
Direction
All the sudden Gap
Everyone's having a conversation about
Slavery
Which is what
We still allow
You know if you would just
It's not a lot it's not a
Close but instead you're like
Safe
Harbor Freight near me
Jordan
This is our last episode
And I'd like to say thank you
Everyone
Listen to our podcast
May this year
End of
It's completely
There's a lot of people who are on
Bored
A year ago
Who are still there
I love you
We appreciate
You so much
Interview jokes
Look it's crazy
How much
I appreciate
Everyone is awesome
It's not to me
Is it people have warm
2 oz
Because our show is some
Looking stupid
The ideas
You and I sit around
And I appreciate that so very much
Does
I can't
This year
Without
From
You all
You make this all work
Worthwhile
Because if I were sitting around
I'm just researching
Anyways to talk about him
Deeply depressing which you would do without their shell
By the first three months of our show where almost nobody was listening
If we had never met you would still be doing freezing point but it would just be about Alex
You would be gone probably if things have gone pretty well you would be gone
And I would be talking to
Hulu app
I appreciate it
This is this is
In some way
Reming the year
Thank you to everyone
Thank you for listening
Thank you for
Changing my life
And a very
Specific way
And
I have gas
You gave me gout
It because of Alex Jones I have
Gout well I should also
Vapors
What is gout
Also I'm hanging out with
The Whispers Gaslight Lake
Uric acid
Here's the deal
Everyone out there
Romans
Countryman
We will be back
Next episode button
Until then I will say
What is a nihilist
Alright
Okay hold on
So we have
Which you were going to release
The wiki
Pictures of
Honestly by the
Sing a goddamn Wiki
That we have covered
Elisa Lam
You have accomplished something
F****** incredible
And you refuse to take
So I will get you earlier but
No it'll never
Accomplishment
This as this comes out
It should be
Live on knowledge
Tomorrow
So
In honor of that
If you want to find us on Twitter
Go fuc yourself go to knowledge fight.com
If you want to find us on Facebook I'll see you in hell because you need to go to knowledge fight.com
Never killed a guy
I don't know
That's true
You know we probably had time to 1
Oh my God
I don't know what the fuc
Aw like
When I was like
19 Not ranch like
I don't know why but
Would just hang out
Anybody like oxalic descended from the window hobos
Very funny
Call Dad
I like
Ended up being weird
I was very
The deal with it
I don't know how this happened
House
Where I was
I didn't know where I was
Really drunk
I ended up in a
I'm smoking
Blunt with a guy
And he starts telling me about how he
Accidentally
Like this guy
This guy was trying to kill him
And he ended up having to stabbed
That self-defense it was terrified I understand that
You know it
Think it was
Defense
So we're already
Prettiest like
Camiguin twist in the back
I had to kill a what
What
Turned into a terrible night of my life
Experience was
Right
I need like also I have a radio show really f***** up
Affected
And he only did it because
It was murder diaper.
Necessarily
The story that he told me made
Tire Center
Really struggling
Doesn't care about
Artifact
Leak transmission is Alex Jones
Holding
Alex