Alex
Starting off
Terrible hiccups
At my instinct
Was to say Happy New Year to everybody
Call Matt I cannot get
Dick
Yessir what's your favorite
What my best New Year's tell me about your
I don't
Great news
Me neither I can't think of any that stick out in my head
Super-awesome
Remember
They're all just
You know various amounts of booze With Friends
Yeah it's usually
Do you make a movie
The glory of Youth
Especially since I've been like
Over 21
Yeah I think the only New Years that I really remember
Because the rest of them have been an absolute
Was when I was like
Chicago
I was at Columbia
We just
Actually
When
Like we went all over
Morning
One of my friends
Peed on the subway
Hell yeah
I remember distinctly everyone beans
Fine with it
Of course it was 4 a.m.
To go you got to go
Glory Days Of Youth kind of music
I've got
I think one year was like an open bar thing
Exact in Columbia
With me and my friends never would have gone to an open bar for like twenty bucks
I remember I left
I believe a couple times to go to
Fortnite but I'm pretty sure
But I got into a little altercation with the
The DJ
I don't like going to the club
Hey could you play
Could you play some Highwaymen for the first thing was I think they're playing music too loud
And I let him know that
Too loud
Everyone everybody
Okay cranky old man shut up
It was too loud had a little bit of that was like
Your lawn as well
He was playing music that I thought was
Just real bad
I'm so I
You play something better
Faster
Wow I got something to blow your mind
Alright another shot
He's looking over at me
What was it like
Okay
Remix of The Mamas &
The Papas California Dreamin
And I was looking at me I made eye contact
I went like this
Thumbs up
Did not get kicked out for probably should have been
That might have been one of my New Year's
Rewrite their Glory of old
ER shows
Okay
Answer what I wanted to do today's I wanted to mix things up at
An episode
Is possibly
Could be depressed by this
Okay alright
Episode
A fancy free weird
I got to give a shout out to
Knowledge fight
First I'd like to say thank you to Jeremy
You are now
Anime
Secondly we're a little late on this based on the name
Appreciate it all the same thank you so much
The Christmas fish
You are now a policy wonk
Thank you so much Chris
Mysterious enigmatic Christmas special
Next one
I don't want to talk about
A goofy trolling prank
But I'm going to go ahead and allow it
It is thank you so much
I appreciate it also very much
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
I don't want
Thank you so much
If you out there listening
You can do that but
If you
That's an interest
Thought to have
When you're driving at work
Or chauffeur
AR podcast
Five stars on the app
The strange not to have to just be like
I want to support
The first
There's a little bit more work I need to do and I realized
How much better would it be
If it came out on January 7th
The formal anniversary of our anniversary
Dot-com
In Celebration
Anniversary
Light
I don't know if it's positive
In the show is positive
Wacky Wednesday
The place where we
Fulfill time travel
Talk about the Project Camelot
Any of these
To do
He's Electric
Highlight
Guess
More about what they're into what they're about a boy
Today is one such episode
You every time he's been on
Stop Marty saxer every liver if you've ever told
Today we're talking about
You don't even remember who Lionel Lionel the guy who hosts the 4th
Flower for Alex
And he's one of Alex's long
You've been around since about 2011
Late 2020 early 2011
You still there today
The 4th hour from time to time he's still a very regular Gaston Night Show
In particular
And so I thought
Michael is
A guy
Do you
As soon as you hear his voice you will remember and remember how much you like him
Now it is
I do
Ton of clips
Supplier on Alex's show because the first one I found
Good enough
To give you a taste
Lionel
So here is a clip of Lionel filling in for Alex Jones
In the fourth hour of the Alex Jones
Alex Jones so glad to be here when I get down to visit I got so much to talk about
Hi I've been thinking
Which is the dangerous single one of the worst part about this is what I want to talk about
Do you remember who I know
I love it
A little bit
There's 25 million things
Everything was really getting me
Charged up
Do you know what last night open try this English you know what open last night there we go on Broadway
That Broadway by storm
Do you have any idea to repot
Not
Familiar
Lot of Harry Potter know who he is and what it is
Story that is
What is it about
Don't believe in Black Magic I don't believe in any of this stuff
Irreligious
I don't speak and I don't speak French I'm not saying the French people don't exist because I don't understand what they're saying
I'm not saying there's no religion
Any of that stuff no matter what
Isn't it
Funny
That right now
This
World this Society of ours is being so contaminated by anyone
Beat beat beat
World of Sex
Human trafficking
Open the light
Who believed in symbology and letting you know
Everything that they do what hand signals an Instagram
Interesting I think it is I just want to give you that
Park it over there
Just make you say
Bat
No I think it's terrific people can say whatever they want I don't care about it but just think
Wizard
Warlocks
Magic spells vehicle does that scare you
Maybe maybe not
But isn't that interesting because you know
The more that I think we as humans
Elevated beyond the more I say I see it we've never really evolve
We've been like this
Since we first
Call Dad
It goes on for a while
Write this in Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles being on Broadway
To do with the weaving in like it's a distraction for kids magic
I don't f****** know
I struggle to find
He's a religious
Into the weeds
What are you talkin about
Nothing
Weaving empties like soda
Pizzagate married
The hand gesture
In reference to
Picture of John podesta
It's very easy
Understand what's going on in
Call Hot nonsense
But that should give you a disorder
Place where you need to
For this next clip to not be surprising at all
Let me make this
First of all
Unequivocally
Clear
Limpid
Pellucid I want to add clarity
No ambiguity
Listen and listen good
I stand with q
I stand with the Anand I stand with
These brilliant
Decoders who
Just
Breathtakingly I'm saying the word too much
Brilliant
Is Bletchley Park is our own
Project Enigma it's our own
Cryptographers it's it's brilliant
I don't want to provide this because
You're still folks coming around Shane what the hell are they talking about what is kill who's cute
Who's fighting
Harry Potter Harry Potter book I don't want to get too into this
Either because there's been a number of requests from people that we do an episode about qanon
Do it but one of the reasons
Is there a
There's a lot of other great
Resources out there okay
People who have
Been following it much
Close
The level of attention
Seems like I could bring to it
Is not merely on the level
The number of other
We dive into at some point
We'll talk more about it
He's a huge qanon
Somebody burned his f****** face or ass as soon as possible
Every possible
Adjectives
Justin Long
Series of synonyms appearances
Intelligent
What's going on here
He is irascible annoying
Necessary
This out and make it clear I want to delineate
Exactly how silly
You need a thesaurus silly three times
Real name is Michael LeBron
Lawyer have graduated from Steven Universe
The College of Law
The smallest
7.2%
Some contacts
According to the 2017 legal resource
This group that makes would make sense
169 best law school in the country
University of Detroit Mercy
Less than 50% of the 27
19 graduates found work
Law Firm
From this love
67.2 is not
A good person
For Barb
I was just going to ask
University of Detroit Mercy
I would go there
The trial lawyer for a bit but according to his own bio
After o.j. Simpson got arrested decided to Rebrand
I can't stress enough vets and he's owned by oh he wrote back
The trial of OJ
Made him decide to
Become a media personality
New York VHF station called PIX11
In 1999 Lionel got his own show on court
Irreverent satirical look at legal news
It was canceled
Before 2000
Very short-lived
TV show
Largely radio base
Interesting in April 2017
Report with Sam secure on air America
Siri been a fixture of the network literally since it launched
And this was a huge
According to many sources
Replacements
Crazy big backlash
The Boston Network
Katana subscribers
The writing's on the wall
Green Brothers and early 2000
7 Replacements with lion
Truly.
That was the point where I was like
It's hard turn to the right
He began appearing on Alex Jones Show
On a fairly regular basis
Right by
He also
Kept appearing
On that Savage
PIX11
And let me tell you this
All of his reports are still online
Today will be a number of
Local New York
What kind of commentators in 2011 and onward
Amtrak
Change
Who's that happen
In the course of
What is rhetoric
His worldview over the
I'm going to bring you
One of the earliest
Videos that still available
This
Is
You know
He's a commentator he's got druthers got to complain about things
Enjoy
I should have I should have probably won't do he have a theme song
Fiesta Mariachi inspired Pizza
Observer New York in this country must be the exercise capital of the world
Ifitness
Obsessed with Fitness commercials and bad
Shuffle my favorites
First the Russian kettlebell
It's a recycled
Choosing
As in the case of a perverted human behavior exercise product for the name of a place
Russia suggests hardcore
Cleveland
Next
You stop it
You will see houses for rent
Humiliating and threatening the human reproduction
If it looks stupid
It's Been Everywhere
High quality exercise sick
Color
What is it
Tired of noxious pitchman who screams at you the whole time
Why does God make sure he's in great shape using methods you know never included
Never have fat people around him
You were selling dreams. Reminders
Imma cut this one shorts
We get the point this is essentially the grind my gears from Family Guy
Exactly
Exercise equipment
There's a hacker
But like
If you have a position where you're on
You think you would make use of that time
Like really
If you're someone who has a
W
Your time talking about how
Exercise equipment
That's well
Like well-traveled
Maybe you're not
Maybe don't have a lot to say
I don't like
Exercise equipment
Rich
Maybe a week or two after this
He comes in with a
This one this one is going to burn
Court will decide whether the government can ban them
Rather video games
For any reason whatsoever
Weather
An answer is yes
Non-Stop
Something very very wrong there
Violet
He said the repetitive
Sure
Corner of the world
Just worried about
I sure as heck would prefer any activities
As opposed to the video lobotomy
I took holiday game is on Wyatt
Game
Supermax
Where aliens are killed
I think he thinks that all video games are just Space Invaders early not realizing
Really compelling narrative structures
Staring at a computer
Ulta
Also yeah
But you know the most social drug out there is
You know how when you get high
You do sit around and
Chinese food
You go out with a lot of friends and you get your
You get your jollies
20%
There was even a
The kid smokes marijuana
And then some
Quoting drug
Psh
Anyway
Aculate my thoughts precisely
Cyborg
One day
Try to interview for a job
A kid I'll bet never shakes the interviewers hand and if so what's that creepy squishy none
Chelo's
Because he's never used
Enjoy yourself created sense of entitlement
God only knows the amount of medication prescribed
Gamers Paradise
Paris look at me
Games for fun
Games make you happy
These are games
Mind-numbing graphics
Has he ever played a video I don't fuc
No sew
Describing just being
You can already see if it was hot
Fundamental
Problem with us doing
To be funny I know it's not going there
Unfortunately we're going to have to drift into
Construction of
Honda
He's trying to make you
Even though he's trying to make them in
I think he's against video
The end of that be against
The idea of legislating against
What is this
Manifesting
Shaking his fist
The parents who allow their kids
Become
Melissa zombie
Literally
It's all just
Exercise equipment
Video games
To the cyborg
The take is that he
He's not even doing the regular take
You just like that you think violent video games are bad
Pac-Man make you unemployable
Grave
It's got so much arthritis
Bright
This next one is nuclear
I would like to take this opportunity to describe a subject of great annoyance
Again
Problems
How bad can my annoyance possibly be
Play frankly
Now where was I
Backpacks
Big purses satchels bags over the shoulder
Or fixed attached or suspended from the back
But it contains face like a subway car
When is this important
Inconvenience
Inconsiderate self-centered Ingles
Center of the universe universe
You are merely permitted to wallow in their world
Maybe it's me maybe I'm a superhuman sentient
Until
Yes I'm sure Paul like backpack that I might straphanger
Justin screams of someone yelling
Look Bloomberg
You want to pass the law that actually makes sense
It doesn't
Specifically extinguish get another civil liberty pass Lionel Richie
5 years of hard labor
Wearing a backpack or a statue
Or bag or suspended via shoulder strap that touches intrusive or
Subway passenger or anyone
How much are clothes
Find who's incredible
Horrible
Tucson
Check draw the human idiot Lottery position
Systematic disregard for
The devolution
Ivar
Proud Society
As you see
What the f***
So if I understand correctly
I know that's serious.
Let's the crack of this conversation
All of them
Is why our society is falling
Part of the comedy like that's in big hard labor
What is hacky washed over B
Go to any open mic
This requires no creativity there's no point of view no perspective whatsoever this is trash
Ranch
I am struggling to remember why the
80s comedy
And I can't be killed
Possible
So high
No f****** backpack
On the train
Where would they go
Like I knows it like that part about like hard labor
But if you even think about what
What would you
Like to make a rule
Like
What kind of a nightmare fascist
They're like no backpacks in public
Compass
Directions
Break
You know people are going to get around
Smuggling bag
Exit
You know they're going to get
Through the
Security guard
You know what they're going to hide the back
In a bigger bag
Look I can never catch him it's nice to be
Considerate
The people blue line to O'Hare
Back from O'Hare
But you can never really be that upset by
People with luggage on the train are you going
I'm furious with them and they need to do 5 years hard labor
You should never have taken
I'm pissed off
Well now what you're really critiquing
Complaints
A train
I'm not being able to afford
Punching down issues you know you know
Comedians never punched
Doubt
Dislike
There's no there's no way to really put a finer point on this
He's not this is an area
Perspective
Peoria
It's interesting
Because in these early
Days
He
Heather perspective
Kind of cranky old man
A little bit
Decent
Analysis every now and again
It might surprise you
Next weapon would absolutely completely non facetiously
This next clip is a little bit surprising
It is rare that I don't care about something I have opinions about
I mean everything
That I can say the following
I guess birth claims namely that he's at the president
Wasn't born in this country
Or
Fishy about the story
I can say unequivocally
And that's all because if
Here we are halfway through his first term
Okay Donnie
Maker cake
Splat
You see maybe it's the prosecutor in me but call me Waikiki
I want this thing called
Make Your Case
And something's fishy in exactly cause of action
No Maybe.
Certificate of live birth
And the country
As per usual couldn't care less about this
What exactly why the industry but I love the fact
Eddie's driving msnbc's
Chris Matthews
That's not a very long ride
Anything that makes big red and yellow produce voluminous and prodigious pools of saliva makes me high
Happy as far as being the same
Your fire
Your claim so far
But you're driving Chris Matthews
And I love that Sophie
The hardball dude
You know and I know that if he had Chinese out Sarah Palin
No it's true Matthew
I was true
I personally hate
Who think they're funny when they're not let the leprosy that tops my list of stuff I load
It's leprosy and people who think they're funny
I'm going to leave that there for a second let him finish the quote but that is a crazy 12 of things you're mad about
A joke
Have been used
And from here on
Give me the subject matter is absolutely and thoroughly exhausted
There is nothing new novel or vaguely unique about anything of relating to or pertaining to that
Please
Okay
All right with that with that
Blistering
Non-tech
I guess for someone who ends up
Becoming a qanon expert and Alex Jones
Devotee regular
Isaac Isaac I think the idea of him saying your is back
Donald Trump
Please shut up about this unless you can
Improve it
As far as
You being in charge
Birth certificate
I think that's pretty
In the general population
But in the population of Alex Jones
Of the
I need proof
I think you was great
Yeah yeah crazy transformation
Here's my question
Clearly
These people who think they're funny
You said as much
Also has
Transitive property dictates 30 months
Just another example of
Sales humor
Just yet another I can
Is interesting
World
Is take
We're not going to listen to
Do-it-all like
Against globalism for the Federal Reserve and stuff like that cuz it's like
It's what you'd expect
It's not an anomaly
It's it's like
Okay yeah
Should we waste our time
Confirming that this guy
Who loves Ron Paul and all that
Believes the things that anybody
Who loves Ron
Not really
It's not worth our time
What is worth our time
Is this
Blistering
Surface of the Sun
Level take
Said he's got about holiday
7 in 10 Americans will celebrate
Halloween
This year Americans are expected to Spanish
Google total outlays by consumers expect
Billion dollars
Is that a lot
Dollars
I don't understand what you're saying numbers
You live in
Neighborhood
I don't know
Statistic in this context
You know somebody's getting that
Text everybody on average
$380
Consider this
Was like
That's just a lot of candy for a lot of kids
Or spend so much money
Crazy house decoration
Bump the average
Pagan ceremony
And demented group of psychological adults
It was nothing more
Costume
Translation
I'm nothing
Just one night
Modern Vintage
Halloween celebration
Translation
Bisexual
Hypebeast
Arena Lumberjack cap
French maid Halloween
From you always do that
Box
And it consisted of a mask whose eyeholes didn't match up in a way to the orbital radius of a child
Boston affect blinding you
I did was hold on with the foot
The cable
Flame retarded
Super Edge
Flame retardant
The same thing with
Oriental
Call Raghu
Vase or something like that or not
ABC
Retarded
Universal
Bread preparation
Retard memes
You delayed
Souffle
He's not being at all
Scoring a point
He is
Accusation about these imaginary PC
People
He's not quite.
So far
Is that he's not even like an old crank
Where is like it
Who's better back in my day I think he's just more like
I hate everything
Except you and Ron Paul.
Ouch
Because of the consistency of the polyester torch fabric
Ventilation would not exist
Add hyperthermia 17 within 10 minutes
Stroll
You put on this thermal blanket
Like I'd worked for you to get anywhere near an open flame I'll fix your mask
I did make it wait until that night alone
Knocking on strange neighbors doors
Hearing the stories of kids
Running clip Diablo
A razor blade
Damage
Stuck with me to this day
That was Halloween
Baptist
Demented garbage today
Trick
Coming
As you see fit
Comment does UCF
Become his goodnight
Good luck
I don't like you
Talking about the idea of razor blades
Remembers
The people laugh
Come up with cuz I've watched
Pretty laugh but like it was a big
And I think it's cuz it's a holiday like Halloween episode
Studio
The holiday
We get to drink at work
Watch this
If I was if I was
UHF
Station
I'm not doing great
If I was there and I saw this
Hilarious but not because of what
He was often will last
Wow
Happy Halloween
Yeah
I don't want people to laugh
Be like
You take a job
Yeah
Lionel start
Have a flight transformation
Can trace it
Around 1
Alexa
Start to see a little bit more
Weird
The stuff that were not covered
I wonder if
He doesn't like him
Know that
Fit right in
The real deal with Bill McNeil
Basically
Lionel is living a news radio pit basically
I want
You're going to hear it at least six or seven more times
I think what I would do
If I was going to punch up here
Play the theme song
And then do a light
Round Table
Him with any topic
How do you feel
How do you feel about that
Get it get it in and out within 2 minutes
Amigos
If you wrote
Washington helped bump this up
Page-one rewrite
It's just the whole thing I recast it I probably take it out of PIX11
Not a great environment for this sort of thing
Perspective
Do everything
Certain amount of
Showmanship
Appeal
He presents
And there's a little bit of that
Beyond
Like I said as the real action starts
You start to see a shift
I can save it this summer
Many of these videos
You know we're like something I like it and I don't
Is it telling me that everybody thicken it
Aw
Isn't depressed
George Bush's Cajun point
Listen to me carefully
Look at me
I like him
Kim
I don't know what happens to a president
Ran for president
Stiff in the mud
By the way
You know what happens when a lawyer takes Viagra
George Bush has qualities I like
Okay first now here's a
Which was a cattle episode
Pronouncer
Nuclear
He said parents wanted to put food on their family
I know that scared me too
I'd only imagined them on the secure phone reading the nuclear codes backwards
He's got me doing
People swim
Barbara Bush
And a miscarriage in the fetus in a jar
Love to table difference
I don't like his honesty about drinking suggest that he's a dry drunk know he's stopped
24 years ago
That's admirable his Society with the Charlie Sheen to Lindsay Lohan's spiraling out of control
Never chase women
Compromise National Security by
Opening himself up to Blackmail playing hide the panatela
Worst president
That was Franklin Pierce hands down
As a president
But I don't kid yourself
Obama is exactly the same as a man who would be
Almost as much as the 22nd Amendment
That's
For someone who ended up as a qanon
Conspiracy theorist
Find it very strange
Very weird
Like the idea of like even if you saying
I'm not saying I like it
The president but I like the guy
He's falling into
To the same store
Trap
Now that the W is out of office
He's a painter
That's falling
Where is before
Which Bush's was over all of the war crimes
Committed he has every reason
To be like f*** that I'm not
Chicago like the guys
Cigarette
Because Obama's
Definitely for I mean definitely for non-race relay
100 +
When I look at Obama
Cusseta Georgia
President
What is a person I don't like
Finger on why
So far
Overwhelming number videos
Put out about how George Zimmerman is
Donald Sterling
Westboro Baptist Church
He doesn't like them but they're Crusaders
I was all nonsense
Exactly like Alex
Yeah yeah yeah more understated
Reports
There's a temp
Dozen
Wildman
It's pretty watch videos about Zimmerman
So you're the legal take on
Although there are a lot of other legal case
It'll come out that he could have spent that much time
You know what's weird is
The more I feel like when he
He was 9
He Saw My Cousin Vinny's
This is this is
Groove about 34
You know you talk to that last clip about liking w
I feel like that's a little hacking
If you're serious commentator
You're probably be above that
But then this next clip made me even more can
Concerned
The Chinese book in my time it's a bookstore
Entitled
In my time
Is that understood
Coerced
Presidential
But trust me
But Angie Grace Sundays he will discard well that's no
So real quick
We have it the beginning
The presentation of
You sang to me
It's unconstitutional
Do snow with boring name
Let's see where this
I didn't either.
International image
That being said
Play mr. certitude in his decisiveness
Lip
RoR
Hi mrs. refusal to equivocate
When you get the decider made up their mind
Bush hamdan
Stanford
Probably perhaps
You've got to give
He's scared that
Just like you wanted
Mr. Potter
Believe me
And it comes in handy
You know
I wouldn't do that if I were you
I don't think Dick Cheney would appreciate that
First NASA tell Joe Biden
44 President Obama's going to read you the Riot Act
As long as it's
Love it
I don't care what you think
He was being interviewed about
The horse you could even get it out
No big deal
Vice president
I wasn't
Whatever
Play Store I mean finish
Jumper cables
Rihanna
Hey juicy
I understand he's trying to be funny
I leave a tiny bit of
This is all satire
But I don't think it is
Because the talking points about Obama and the teleprompter Arkham City
Ineffectual
He's consistent
Bucky's Express
Underneath a lot of that attempt
Is something that I believe you sincerely are
The world is afraid of
Which is not
Should argue
Is there a serious
That's not good analysis
That is very very bad
When stupid people used
They were right
Do things without any kind of
Pre analysis
Whatsoever in
Just kind of
Really get s***
Done
It was work
Millions of people killed by Stevie worried about like or phrase efficient
See if its efficiency towards a goal he's again
Like what is that
That makes
Victor's internal inconsistent
There's so many of these reports
Because I think they're
Like an attempt to
Interesting
Temptress Vaughn
Points that are very poorly thought-through
And that is exactly what you'd expect
Mike just
Well of course of course
With that kind
Dumb
Look up
To Trump in your life
It's kind of interesting that
Sing right now
Is of course just
Picture reaction
There is a certain part of us that
You know
Like when people
A certain part of everybody
Oh now we have somebody who's
Just going to find
Not we have
To constantly be vigil
Just going to
Yo
Cut through all the b*******
We all want to cut through all the red tape
What do you play
Statistics
Cut through it
Done it does exist all over the
Feeds into
To each other from both sides
I just think
Easier is it was the order of the day
Because at this point
The election is already
Paul's not going anywhere
The Ron Paul Revolution
Have some sort of an idea that
Ron is going to
I'll be the guy
Hands up retiring
Is it
Potential
Here is gone
You do when you're lying
Basically just
Libertarian-leaning establish
What is
You hearken towards the strong
Strongman
Because
You're so dissatisfied with Obama
It's
Easiest cheapest
Route to
Having a position
So that's what he does
Is that right
Do you know that that's the
Position
He was into
Consistent
Globalist
And I will say
Videos
Put out about
Defending
To be on the right side of that
Apartment today
Like fat shaming
I think that those things
I couldn't get my I couldn't get a handle on that
It is a position was
If I was going to
Gas without
Any knowledge of what
He said
A little bit of a vocabulary show
Greek mythology exactly
He's doing that thing where he's
Stronger
So I wanted around
If it does feel like
I mean you've already pointed this out of it earlier
You're projecting
Lame
Comedies bad
The perspective is
You talk about
Now I want to say
Overture
Romanticize
Cast of
Of course liking bush
Like that
4 second
Forgotten
You still is a man who knows his
Mayor Bloomberg
The subway
Cry-Baby
Power
Necessary incarcerate
These practitioners
Who insist upon wearing my existence
The backpack
That's just a huge oversized Sherpa like lawn mower size bundles that people strapped
The rules of football backpacks
No problem
Stop
Please
G train
Intrude
Crazy
Nobody is keeping it in the news Dan it's got to stay in the news cycle
You got ahold
I got it but he just ran out of time to get the report together for that and forgot he'd already covered
What in the f*** the same script
Different synonym
Even at this point when
You started to take this
Pivot
I mean
Conservative
Nonsense
The train
Back on just
Keeps going that direction
You'll see in this next
Stuff that is just
Independable level he's taking attorney now
Words
These
Weird
Globalism and Ron Paul apologetic
Like soda
Positions that are weird
He started
You say things that are like
Presentation was a distraction
Caracol
Horst Ortega presidential election
Bacon is irrelevant
I mean
What did did immediately talk about
Because it was something they could
I just said we Parson reverse-engineer
I just you need series
Ryan's app
Distraction
Trying to associate
Idiocy
Rodney Ryan to gopong the Angelika
Seriously
Facebook
You're a typical National League
Stove
I'm an American League true blue
What does that have to do with anything
Here's where the argument Falls Apartment PDX there exactly
And the other one difference between the National and American League
Your attempt to minimize reductio ad absurdum argument falls apart
Dumb dumb
What kind of
Nationally
That's where we are today
We've distilled reduce the argument to person
Bumper sticker Playbook argument
The World Monetary systems are on the verge of collapse
We are on our way to end
Tomorrow
I told him
And yet these
Giving you
As you speak
I will
So what are you doing
Really important client
Because he's covering it
Right here is like
First of all he's not taking into account
Can cover multiple stories simultaneously
Employee
Can't get the bigger thing
Good examples that he's talking about here like
Economy collapse
Stuff like that
He is the one who is guilty of not covering those things in favor of talking about.
To dismiss this
Todd Akin
Legitimate rape doesn't cause pregnancy
These nonsense
Now the bigger issue is
Conflated with
Like the tea party and stuff like that
Isn't
Irresponsible because he's a member of the Tea Party
The other thing is that his
Statement
Weren't condemned by the
People on the right
Maybe a couple people
But generally speaking
People much like with Nazis
Just started like
That's sort of the thing
He was a member of the House of Representatives like it is relevant
It's elected official with a
These are when they're this
Misogynistic
About both of your shoes of abortion
Great it is very
There's no point in talking
It's not like he has
He does
I should tell you that
I got bad news about the house
It's very
It's not a distraction
This is abstract
This is this is distracted
You from
The idea of
What today
I'd like what
That every person
It's not to say that every
Conservative
On somebody
You probably up till that
Didn't say anything like that
To be a normal run-of-the-mill considered anti-abortion
It gives you what you
Just be like at least a couple other people who
And that's really f***** up
It's also really f***** up have you apologized
Lost
Claire mccaskill later wrote a book
Most
Yeah
Nuts but this is
Going out of their way
Interference
In Subway
About conserving
Who do things that are
Really horrible
Just political
It's it's like
And this is
Sing that I think a lot of
White people
As they get older
Like they ride them minor in
Inconvenience train
White supremacy
Oh you bet
It's not going to be
Owl
And of course that's why why
I need to break away from
Natural
It's all about the bass
Everything else is
Distraction
Clearly
Of your own show
Also everytime it
If Eddie like photoshopped
Take the Lionel theme song
And just
The Zelda
Villain bad guy
Make a video of
Vinyl dancing with a mariachi band
That's all that goes through my head but I
The next
Clifford
Chaz Bono going to explain to him
Information with Chaz Bono
You know what's interesting
He said please
You don't need to because
The end of the clip
He will invalidate everything he said during the clip
And makeup
What the fascination
Being amusing words
He's just being
Intentionally obtuse
As an interest
Chaz Bono
Female-to-male gender transition
He doesn't miss gendered
Of this elk probably would
Hero 2000
Sexuality and gender identity
That means
I'm starting to get sick
She come around
Heineken
I guess
Baby I get bored easily
He gets bored easily
He did over
Videos about George Zimmerman being cool
Maybe
I'm the only person
Who actually couldn't care less
This isn't one of those
There are more important issues lectures I'm a fan of pop culture
But the question that I like
That I know you would ask on faces
You want to know that my friend Judy Gold at her new one-woman shows
Why is
Chaz so fat
Reconstruction
Accurately Construction
That I want
A pretty straightforward
Pun
The guts encouraged part I can't emphasize
There are transgender
Glitter lyrics
Brandon P nothing comes to mind
Give Jenny Craig
Who's
Carrie Fisher with her ezt electroshock
Okay
Isn't that interesting there at the end talking about how like
Your chats has a large
Platform as a celebrity
The clip with such an invalid
CID
Sick and tired of seeing Chad Bono route
He makes clear that he understands
Very valuable
In small-town America who is representative of
Make
Making them feel normal
For him to pretend
The keys like I'm totally
Fine
People I'm not against that at all
But f*** this representation thing
Edwards
I don't like it
Because it doesn't affect me
Because for the people
It's actually very important
But
People being fat
I don't understand I really don't like
If I were the segments
Producer on the show and he submitted this is
I would be like
There's internal problems yourself very least
You let make
We're at the end
Do you know exactly what
And aware of
Figure it in pop culture
Trans rights and acceptance
You're pretending
Perhaps Perhaps the end of this undercuts your point
I would
Go to a page-one rewrite
Recast
Embarrassing
Pramod comedy
Perspective
From a human perspective
From a point
Perspective
From a
Writing
Everything about that
Bad
Yeah I don't know
So that's interesting that we have Chaz Bono
This is his take
That's great
His take on him
Super awesome that a trans person
Coming out
People find it inspirational and
And we are talking about
Insomuch also helps normalize trans
Comfortable
Ever made you feel comfortable because finally
This pop culture
Is being transmitted
Making them feel more comfortable with the idea
But also
Jenny Craig needs to again
Like I really can't
Understand
Like where his
Because he does have a number of videos about how bullies are bad
They're committing a bad thing
To bullying
And the idea that
K2
Bad
Would be not a difficult argument to make what he's doing there
It's a little bit
Also
Feeling uncomfortable in their own skin
Afraid of coming out to there
To his parents
Afraid of
What do you think that person
Idea it
It's just them
He talks about Chaz Bono
Who's differences
You notice how immediately after
Right-wing group
This is dangerous
Absolutely are
First expansion
Singular sick of it
Message
Right wing watch
Particular
Politico
We're giving Quick Remote
What Charles Manson orchestrated the tate-labianca murders
Cuz he said
A white supremacist or a fallen left
In addition to Independence
Democratic and Republican Administration
OneRepublic
Domestic terrorism
Islamofascism an oxymoron
Empower
Right
Malicious
Are the danger
The more that these discussions go from the Norway
His support of the English Defence League
Similarity to our tea party
Conflation and expansion
Then leave to some weird kind of transitive property application
Our political
That's exactly what's happening
Whatever
Don't let the heart
That's what you're doing
He won't even stay a brother's name
He won't even acknowledge that talk about the real way
And if you want to if you want to hear more about
Episode
Anders Breivik
Is that
Lionel has never read his Manifesto
Understanding exactly what motivated
To do the things he did
Because they are so close
Do the same
That do inspired
Malaysia cinta right-wing AT-AT
Pity party
Anti-muslim sentiments
In what motivated
I do understand what you saying in terms of
This guy is representative of all of us
Point well-taken is affairs
We can have that conversation
What it's like a brevik is indicative of
The mainstream of
Conservatism
But
Why somebody did something
Is irrelevant a I'm afraid of looking at
Because it will
Unveil Andrew Steele
How
Pancake disease
Anti-immigrant
Thinking
Left
To their own devices
And take him to the
End up in
Why don't we
You killed people
The end result
Of this line
Just is
He's a crazy person
His motivations that doesn't matter
It is almost like
Terrorist
Matter
Cuz they're crazy
They're just nuts
You can't
There
Manifest
Play the same s*** that I say all the
SB
Terrorist
Because there's Lomb is so horrible
Or conversely with this world
Cuz they don't even want
That's all folks
Or whatever
Something like this
This clip
Is interesting
Because he's talking about Anders Breivik like this
Yeah after he talked about Chaz Bono
This is actually more akin to the
Avatar
Don't associate
I will take no ownership of the idea that
This is very close
I absolutely will not look
At The Logical
Conclusion of all of the stuff that I say in
Because my doing that
See you that it would inspire
Motivation
Eco-terrorists
Like for sure animal rights
Terrorists
Important to look at their motivation
Understand what
I have no idea
Motivated by
Principal
Maybe
To Pharr Event
This is just a shutting down
Because of the fear of what it could
Like you live
What's under there
I think it's sad I think it's a very
Cowardly
Typo
A place to live
More or less
Which is why I wanted to cover this stuff
This is more like
This is the career that Lionel
Living
This is what you put in
Large chunk of
He's creepy
100%
Quite frankly
And at the same time
Qanon
Knew that this
Is the guy who you're now all like
Take a step back and
Think about what you're
Like
Your intellectual Heroes
Whitwell
We all get very bored
Ibloom
Thousand
Sealed indictments coming and everybody wears
Hillary's going to prison bushes
100%
Bush
Sick and tired of exercise equipment absolute
Swear to God
So
Oh yeah
Actually
You say it is best to get for listening to
Too much of this
Early on
Lionel had that video
You was talking about
You show proof
About
His
That Obama
Wasn't
In the country
Election
No
The well on Trump's birthday
Donald Trump is my new hero
Never really been a fan before I give her
Only person who really knows and cares
Being sad
Maybe he's driving.
Dairy
What I saw CNN permanently comatose
Wolf Blitzer
What were the subject of death
Berrington
President eligibility specifically
Estimate natural-born
Release his birth certificate
Who I swear died in 1978
Wolf spiders
How to remember
Ever see anyone ever
Any embarrassing
Think about it during the Clinton years
Paddle
Watching Vince
Obamanation
Snow Queen
Or really anyone in the media
Why Trump crazy
For he's a racist or whatever
Solutely mandatory
Presidential Scholars my
Recall that there were questions
Real
Prior to his election had spent some time abroad
Did the 14-year residency requirement apply
14 years cumulative
The Raven questions about John McCain
Requiem
Parkade and historically recondite article to parsec
What do you still want American citizen
Bad hair or not
And I love
As you
Not a lot of laughter in the studio
She has a job.
There's a couple of
Important
Declared hair jokes dead
He did two of them
Maximum
By your own rules
Jokes
You have transgressed your own rule
No second
Nothing really changed
In terms of Donald Trump's birtherism
And the intervening
Years between these clips
Nothing on the ground had changed
And
Nothing really
Perspective
In the first clip use like
You have no evidence
You got to stop at SoDo I'm thrilled you're making
Chris Matthews
Right what's motivating clip is there wolf
Blitzer is now mad about
There is no subs
Different
Except for
I don't know what it is
I have no idea
But something changed
Completely flipped
Disposition
On something
2 point where he's like
It's like Trump is questioning the birth
You made a video being mad about them questioning the Versa
Like I what you're condemning your past
Self without calling yourself a I would know I was even
Stupid
This is indicative
Absolute
Something behind the scenes
I don't know what it is Ron Paul's retirement
That alone could
Account for a great
It's something and it's
That's all I
I don't know.
Because
You just sound like
He's getting crankier and let's
It doesn't seem like he's enjoying himself at all giving
If you listen to a bunch of his stuff
She doesn't seem
He doesn't have a lot of
She said that earlier
Should be right
Pillory
For your
Be funny when you
So there
Hans
These are the ones that I thought
Overtime
Of Lionel
Career at work
Yeah now it should be noted that
Here is
First Energy
So this is his last clip
That we just played
Rvhs
So
2 years prior to that
Isn't super important necessarily
Play for this
This is before the re-election right
Pyramid
America.
Rin that place
I think this
It should speak volumes
About why
Tangled
There is not one show is not one day that goes by
Number 12
Where are the mainstream media where are these narcotized
How many hours
But if you want to run and listen to local media news
In front of everybody in full View
Those are the stories
You do it
So
Pickaboo
Ill about you see is infected
Thrombosis
Christ
I am
You see here is
Someone
It's hard to say I actually have very strong
Elizabeth etics
Con man
Okay
I think he is marginal
Something usually hack
Very large market for Paterson
Well I mean
Even Beyond him if you just go to rike Road
Because they're on the right
And middle-of-the-road stuff.
Kind of boring to anyone
He isn't very
What
Unfortunately this is
But
Is the white
Baby cats
Catch more fish that way the lowest common denominator
Troglodyte
Talk radio is blank
Tibet scam after
Realized
Law is hot
Flirting
Interested in hearing these legal opinions
And stuff like that I have a log
Degree from a bad College I'm going to
This game
Leestown Tatnuck
With the word
That I can
Do that
Be charming and
You got into that
As you got it
Local access
News does hackey washed over warmed up comedy
Regine
I wouldn't be surprised if there is an echo
Moonlighted going to open mic
In New York
And just writing down friend
Not equality
So he does that
Not working out all that
Gets involved in Aramaic
Maybe in some ways responsible for hair America falling apart
Because of them turning their back on Sam Cedar and making it
Sunday only
And when are America falls apart
She's kind of life
I have a talk radio show
Makes a pivot
He interpreted
Yeah at the time that is
Anti-obama
And in some ways
Glorifying
Bush
Anti youth
Now you still has the Ron Paul background
Already
Bear
Him to start getting involved
Absolutely
Weather
It's because he recognized
Or whatever
He becomes radicalized
He starts to go down harder
With Alex
His video city starts putting out on you
YouTube r
More hardcore
From him and a news Studio.
To him in his office
Apetor a bit more extreme
Track
You still look
These numbers
Videos that he has
Of him doing this
Hundred
Yes
It's minuscule the number of use these
Ever got
And when he started Broadcasting
Videos on
Still only like
They've been online for five years yet
As soon as he pivoted to
As soon as you started doing
It's now in the 50
Thousand hundred thousand
He took a
Massive jump
And I think
I think it's the pass
I think he's always been looking
Better
Cod battered
He found
What's going on
The dude who is just always been looking
Keep jumping from
Trying to
Find it's like somebody
Trying to move their way up
The corporate ladder
Pretending
Trying to get up the ladder or whatever
But I think
Probably
Is that the latter leads to
Position on the lower rungs of the ladder
It's not that hard
You can have
Poorly thoughts
Through hockey positions
And maybe still Coast
Through
As you go higher up the ladder
Become
Like
Malicious propaganda
Congruent
So I don't know I don't I don't know I don't know how
This was an attempt
I believe
Wholeheartedly
It was I want
You're on something
You could just laugh bunch of out
And still have some
Hey this is all stupid
The laughing
So I think we
A small point
About how
He is also
To start the new year
I feel like we missed last
With RC
Secretive 22nd
Thank you all for joining us
It's been a great
Of year so far
It is
I will soar on Twitter
Absolutely we're on eyeliner
Leave review, review
God I could do that all day
So
Hertz
I love it so much bad and it's so annoying
Good
So much
Icarus
Humorous of that
I'm going to show you as soon as
According to the video
Fake yelling in a bowl
If crazy
Everyone looking up
No good
Next time
Until then
Indeed
Don't think I've ever killed
True
I think I think the chances are Slim
Technically
And that's all
Alex