Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages
Yes sir
Stop stop it stop it stop it everyone
A lot of positive feedback from the light
Chrome last episode
After all memories have gone I will say
As my last
Lie. Lie
Did not expect
That sort of response from people but I appreciate everyone that loved it that's great news I hadn't already
Already heard that song Right 20 years ago
I don't know. With a Lionel behind
Somebody would have liked
Picked up on it and it would have
Spread like fire
In some corner of the internet
FairPoint
It is now
Are Marching theme I guess I don't know
I guess his associates theme song
We have
Episode
South Alex
Told Rodger Stone to get in touch
Throwing a hatchet
Ended 28 Jean on beware he's at at the beginning of 2019
Like to take a moment to take some folks who've become policy wants
So first of all I'd like to thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Second
You are now a policy
I'm a policy wonk
Next Alexa
Thank you Paul
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Courtney thank you so much
Your walk
I'm a policy wonk
Finally
Wondering how how many
Suddenly this entire episode
We have a backlog and I feel bad we need to get some
For the longer
Donate
I'll be standards. You know I I'm sorry you don't get to hear Alex say he doesn't want to hate black people
I'm sorry we don't get to hear him say that he renounces Jesus Christ
That's the way it goes sometimes
I'm so finally I'd like to say thank you to
You are now a policy
Thank you very much
Weather in
Our listeners
I've gotten actually a number of messages from other people
American from some other country
Enlarged or Swedish contingency
PS2
The Growers Swedish Ranch haenow stop it
Private lives of our listeners
Are they really sweet
Also
I don't want to
If you have
If you would like support the show and what we do and because of our website knowledge fight.com
Really a big deal
Absolutely not a big deal out of the time for people who are
People donating
When there are a lot of people
Come together
They donate a little bit it makes a massive difference
So much
It's
I can go to
So that's great
You have a productive level
When you only put in 78 hours of the hours are still a bit of a mess but we're close to a
Basic entry level salary
This episode is f***** up goes all over the place
Contact drops
From Today Show
Business
Need to start
Stella h
Probably
Is January 2nd 2000
I'm close to that just because of how much time I spent listening to his shift
I listen to the first
Cuz I thought like let's get this
Real New Years on Earth
Are you going
Bulshit deconstruction of how afraid he is
The China
5G Wireless technology
Alex
Part his ideas about the FEMA camps about this but
I know he's going to do it again
We can do it then
I don't want to exhaust the listeners so I understand
I checked in on the 2nd
I found
Interesting hours
Jumping all over the place
We're going to start
It's about how Muslim
Outta control
My friend is January 2nd 2019 2009
I'm your host Alex Jones will be here for the next 4 hours
Call Joseph Watson with big breaking news guides at the bottom of the hour
Bombings firework attacks rates
Nearby bars for City
It has been vomiting uprising
There's just done as an exercise of dominance over
Coming up
The slaves in this context
If you're missing
Display
Are the white.
The people of the West
So this is this is crazy
Already
Tell him to
Hold the brakes
For a little bit
Because I want to starting to your claiming the Muslims are terrorizing everyone
Totally forgetting to
To cover what the weather for the rest of the show
Man was arrested after he drove his car through group of immigrants shortly after midnight on New Year's Eve
Including the list of those injured by the attack were four year old boy a ten-year-old girl
Turkish descent
He was a German citizen
Quote
While being arrested
Independent
Clear intention to kill foreigners
Interior minister
For the state
Herbert Rel
PA
That was a clear active
Xenophobia
There was another car attack on
This one in Tokyo
Twenty-one-year-old Captain Hero cast
Drove his car through the Narrow Street leading
What was really important run
You are a lot
The injured 9 people
It was an act of terrorism but it wasn't Muslim
Alex
Protest
And you refuse to even defend his axe
In the name of protesting something
But he thought was way worse
That's kind of interesting
It's a little bit interesting
I mean marriage covering
The back are attacked the Muslim stabbing people and stuff like that
Seems like this might be something relevant to fold into
The conversation
Guy who went on an attack
Specifically trying to kill immigrants or if it's this guy was protesting
The death penalty
In Japan
Except the problem is that he wasn't a political terrorist
General
He was protesting the death penalty as it was specifically applied to members of the album called
Who are executed for their actions on March
T95
They were doomsday cult believe that they were the only people who were going to survive independent global war
A building Bala after everybody else
Who killed a bike
But they work this kind of like let's wait and let the war happen kind of called
They were let also go kill people and see if we can help this war start kind of
In 1990 they fielded a number of candidates for office but lost
The Freemasons
It's for their failure
In response they began trying to harvest botulism toxin in order to prepare chemical attack
To trigger a war between Japan and the United States
This was unsuccessful
Because they did a really shity job of harvesting the botchling
L I was in a state of disorientation
He began to make his doomsday prophecies more specific
Can you publish the book
I called declaring myself
The Christ
Interesting Lee he began to outline
Who exactly the enemy was
And though he previously list
Freemasons in
Now he was warning of a
Conspiracy between those groups
The Dutch and British royal family
Which sounds weirdly familiar to me
I don't know why
I can't I can't think of why but it seems I feel like we touched on this at least once maybe one
This is this is this is a race
Thought that I'm having
Feel like you can't be anti-Semitic
I feel like you are you're on the wrong side of us
I don't I don't like that thought it's a weirdly races
They attempt to the number of chemical and biological attacks in the intervening years
Edgeworth anthrax
Luckily the strains of Anthrax a required we're not ones that hurt people
They were responsible for at least ten confirmed chemical weapons attacks
Late night
But the one that got them in the most trouble with the one on March 20th
At the peak of morning rush hour five members of The Cult released sarin gas in the Tokyo subway
Killing 12 people and severely severely injuring 50
Seymour complication
Attack
Surveys of the survivors found that many of them still suffer from
PTSD
And 20% feel unsafe
Publix
47 survivors have been certified as disabled
The reason I lay all this out is because there's a bigger world out there that I would want no part in touch
The attack in Germany was clearly an anti-immigrant attack.
Call Alex
Cuz rhetoric
The attack in Japan was carried out by a young man with protest
The death sentences
The carried many of the same beliefs
Enemies is Alex.
He can't wrestle with these ideas without pointing out some
Problems with his own message
And how he chooses
Deliver it
Aggressively stirs up hatred
Fear of the vague Muslim attacks
CiCi's happening everywhere
It's very sad
Realize
60s
Yukio Mishima the incredible
Novelist
To the prime minister's housebroken with samurai sword
Installed
The emperor back
Supreme leader in order to get rid of all of the
The foreigners who
This is kind of a
Later version of that
Alex is going to
Muslim
Throwing fireworks
Some stuff like that
In reality
On New Year's Eve have a lot more to talk about if you want to look at
Like other events that have happened
Or as important more important
I'm just saying
You're not looking at the big picture Alex you're looking at your narrative
Your editorial position is anti-muslim
Hey there for the only stories that
See fit to cover
Are these ones that
Integrate
Do that editorial position
Right now I think it's lame
And when I first heard that I was like
Well at least I'll get to learn a little bit more about this about it
But at the same time
Episode where we're going
Talk a little bit more about events
The new year
Promises out of the gates
Linking up with
Trump and Putin and others
Public Schools
Pedophile agenda of sexualizing children
They're putting a place around 2nd Amendment
Whoopty s***
The idea of like
Getting their own Second Amendment and stuff like that that's just
100 not centered in Brazil very clear lake
Bolsonaro
If I played Alex's game I might just refer to someone
NBC news headline
Panaro targets minorities on first day in office
But even that isn't enough to tell the full story
Jerry bolsonaro's
Fascist
Be incredibly worried
Because bolsonaro is very close with the oligarchs
Agribusiness
Miss World was strongly against the idea
Protective
Indigenous population
Responsibilities involved what lands are protected
From the Justice Ministry to the agriculture
The clear track record as opposing native
These arguments on the sub
Nope
Protecting
Bolsonaro
The program that isn't he
Interested in reaching the agribusiness
People
And the native Brazil
Version of Brazilian Society
Is this being done to I don't know the hours for absolutely
The flip out
And I don't need you to predict
I've heard him constantly go on about how FDA regulations on Amish sold
Cheese are an attack on their self
This is also add retina all this stuff is also a direct attack on environmentalism but regardless
It's being done to help big business
And will likely lead to the genocide
On contact
The tribes in the Amazon
Summit so many of them are literally uncontacted
We're not supposed to
But like the one a****** who
Ground situation
As Bi-Rite would like to call it
Bolsonaro also remove the lgbtq community of concerns and responsibilities
The human rights
Ministry
Become
The new human rights minister is an Evangelical preacher named Tamara Salva
Who believes quote the Brazilian family is being threatened by diversity policy
Oh my f****** God I hate
Journalists are happy
There's so much more
Critically dangerous
We're going to watch the game
Human rights disaster
Play out right in front of our eyes
And now it's going to Delight
Because
Behind the human suffering and Terror
The stock market went up in Brazil bolsonaro came
The widely popular opponent bolsonaro Hedge
What's a socialist
Bolsonaro interop seem like friends really all Alex
In order to
Be like grey
Because Alex
Much like Jerry bolsonaro
Is a monster
These people are terrible
This is a really really really important
Brazil to take
Because just
What four years ago
The right-wing
Installed Tamara who is barred from f****** running
For the office
He was given
The Supreme Court just
Brazil
Sanely hard
They elected a f****** out now fashion
Facebook for years
So in case it is never going to
Descendant
Let's let's hold up pump the brakes there
All of this supported by the oligarchs
Who controlled most of the f****** media
Getting involved too and like
Just all our
It's all a complete mess
It is indicative of of like
Things you need to look out for things to keep an eye on
Cuz it's going to get worse
It's going to be humanitarian organization
Support in order to
Mitigate the damage that's going
Because
These communities weather
Lgbtq
The folk Inn
In Brazil
Whether it be
Basically just destroy by way of claiming that they should
Like all that stuff
Never seen that
Group of people
Claim that native
Assimilated
Ultimately to amass
Types of genocide
No
Don't have tons of case studies
Alex
I feel like
Revealing himself
How to not be
Good
Compiler of the news
Complaints about
No no
Bric-a-brac
I think they had multiple Seasons dedicated to it
Abyss
Intimidation
Really big
Something really really big
That I'm going to tell you about
Ominous storm clouds
We'll break it down when we come back in just 60 Seconds
Newswars.com tomorrow's news today
That is almost as hell
He used the term storm
Intentionally
Qanon.pub
Black Emperor
X-Men fan
This
He's going to culminate in Alex saying something
I do believe could have legal
I think that he might be
This is on par with him telling on-air that he told Rodger
The contact us like this is like
Alex is getting real sloppy
Some of the stuff he ends up saying about this big story that you got
No
Hannah wants to go to
What's go to jail
Because where he's at right now all he's got left his martyrdom
I think he want
Get tried for something and win on
Free Speech grounds
Or something like that
Deeply enough
But fall back on like I was just saying things I want
Something like that
We can get caught up in
The courts
Like have his opportunity to grandstand
And stuff like that knows you knows the track is on now
Leads to diminishing return
It is show just falling apart
I don't know I don't know I think there is a chance that you really think
I'm not going to give too much away but I think
He might actually believe is true
Would you mind actually believe
The stuff you say
We can't get too into this without the actual contest
Visit
Oh yeah recalled when overdue
Hesitant
Without telling anybody
First Security
Concerns
Or something
No that's bad
You don't like it when people just don't call and show up at your house
Actually not if their president and I am
It's weird
Diplomacy there otherwise
Essentially sayings
Push back on because about another problem
Was Trump's visit
After Alex misunderstand
Those Critters
It is mind-blowing
You can't version of reality
And so often I don't even respond to it on air anymore
Because it's so Brazen it's so ridiculous it's so insane
Photos of Obama going into warzone
Some of the trips coming up and wanting them p.m. to shine
His autograph
Military code
I call it the chicken
Shu know what T dimension
How do you get so low that you're trying to figure out the
Army soldiers
Kind of sounds like
Stuff you and your guys do all the time
We have a way with words the chicken shot dimension
F*** it I'm Gore Vidal in this b****
Do we all live in the chicken
According to Alex yes absolutely
It's good to know that they're going through the dictionary of
I think they just realize we have too much fun
Kier is specifically that when Trump win over and visited
The Rock his people put out
Video of him
Taking pictures with soldiers
That's
The soldiers who were captured in those pictures
Were members of Like SEAL Teams that you aren't supposed to know where they are
Are there with the president
You're not always with you're not supposed to know there in a rock
Very
Specialized teams
So the issue isn't so much
Like
You put out pictures of himself with
No one really cares about that
In the past
Presidents would have listened to their advisors
And been careful enough not
To be on camera or if you are
Keep it private
Keep it a private picture for that soldiers when I died
Don't release pictures of people who are in secret
That then give people
Bulshit remember whenever Obama leaves that picture with him and Hillary Clinton and they were in the situation
Watching SEAL Team Six kill Osama bin Laden
Yeah
They just revealed where Seal Team 6 was
Picture Show
Hillary p
I don't know I remember him releasing the video of him peeing on the Wailing Wall
Just she
ALEKS syntek
Understanding why people
Concerned about that
I don't know I'm not a military guy so I don't really fully understand
How big of an infraction
Can this is
But I read stuff
On it enough
To knows it like it is
This is a breach of protocol for sure
But I understand
People
Stop him you know like I don't know but someone's to blame
I don't in terms of things about Trump I don't really care about this one for
Particularly
And not because I don't think
Could be severe understand it
If I fully understood it then I can talk about it more
I just air on the side of the
People who know what they're
Well the simpler one is the first thing he started with with
A lot of a lot of soldiers
Clamoring for Obama
Autograph
However
Campaign materials
Not good
Right
That's against the rules it was ghosts of Obama to bring like
Wheaties boxes with himself on them to autograph
Average rookie card primitive time
Come on man you didn't play pro ball
You know that's not great
Misrepresenting stuff
It's still kind of like
We're getting into
With too much
Behind him
Denigrate
The Fantasticks
Right I just
Wonder
Toast
Were they more excited
I don't really care
That's 10 to me I understand I don't really care
Y'all like it's just
Go down the road of like
Well who cares about protecting these people whose
Specialized
Yeah but
I just don't care
I don't know
Really important that everybody and even the FBI released a report
I lured out of military and police Personnel are white
Out now
There is no
Speaking of the military
Would have sent
He gets into
Complaining about Mitt Romney
Kuzma
This is Mitt Romney had some
Words about
Withdrawing
Afghanistan
Ineffectual stupid words to make him look like he's a valuable critic of the president
The same time supporting literally
Put your own f****** face
On top of that she let him drive it
You f****** garbage
Criticize
What you talking about Afghanistan
A little bit
And I think
That he says something
Things that I take
Is already
Taking out of the 44 billion dollars a year
44 billion dollars
Horses out of Afghanistan how much lithium
Herb for batteries
Guess how much
How much of a b hundreds of rarest mineral
Sickly stabilize the railway and stabilize the highways and stabilizer
Tricom
Just like we always do that's globalism
And Trump knows that
The minute we pull out of there
LeBonheur Al-Qaeda are going to start blowing the Chinese faces up they already are
I'll be there on problem
Chinese Bass
Instead
We guard
Flip flops
That is
Weird
Wild Things
Criticisms
Our various Wars I don't think I've heard him specifically likes
We should get out of there because they are going to blow up Chinese
We're just there protecting the Chinese mineral interest
Or something like that I don't think I've ever heard him say
Stuff like that before
Say stuff like that
What is profoundly weird
Also
I believe that the number is closer to 95
Percent of the world
Rare Earth
Minerals are
But extract
Goodbye China
Near-monopoly on
The industry
Extracting
Rare Earth minerals in China what they have control of it
R2 just stop
Whatever problem
Knew it would be a problem
Is very mineral-rich
50 year old Sophia
Copper deposits
2010 more formal survey found that all things considered
There's likely a trillion dollars worth
Mineral resources in Afghanistan
2014 Afghanistan
Billion dollar contract with a Chinese state-owned
Coppertop
Their biggest iron deposits
I can find no evidence of Alex's 44 billion-a-year number
And honestly considering that one trillion dollar debt figure that's 9
And the fact that China is
Play when it comes to strip mining
I find it very unlikely that that number is active
I just can't
What time does she is actually a very
Political question
Which is what is the right
To do in terms of Afghanistan
Obviously as it stands now since
You can't rewrite
Do nothing is
The very badass
Because what would happen is most likely that
I wouldn't just start working too
Peach
That's an absurd idea
Suggested Alex Banks
The Terrorist on his side
Which is hard to square with his constant rhetoric about how Obama and Hillary created
These terrorist groups and they just do their bidding
I thought Hillary and Obama were in bed with China
Why would their terrorist armies attacked
Chinese address
If we withdrew from the country
It's all globalism up top for terrorist
In the past
You don't f****** remember whenever I said it was their fault it like that
It's crazy
Because if he
If his worldview is
Consistent then
Up top is the globalist
And they're controlling the
Hillary and Obama and controlling Puppet Master
These terrorist groups
Attack each other
Especially
Extracted minerals and making money off it
You would understand if they fought against each other
The appearance
What is ostensibly
Your conspiracy no longer makes sense correctly
Play here's what his worldview says is going on
That he does not see his contradicting
The globalist control both the check comms and through
The terrorist
Moana just Obama and Hillary
Trump pulls out of
Assuming
Terrorists will attack the tricon
Even though the terrorists are controlled by the globalist by a proxy
And the check comes are controlled by the
Globalist
Entirely
The goal
I don't know
The most likely outcome if we were to
Withdraw and everything
These terrorist groups with Zen
Start
To take over some of these
Very lucrative mineral businesses
Industries or parts
So the government
You know that
Much more becoming
Realistic outcome
Unfortunately
All of us withdrawing
They were better plans
Could have been put in place to
To begin with
There's a number of them
What would make more sense for them
To destroy the street
Because they don't
Don't even have engineers
Continue trying to take over power and then take over the contract with the Chinese operation
China has a very specifically like
Non moral foreign policy and terms of like
Especially economics
But there's that are
Perhaps
Against or morals of the world because there's money is Money Baby
Sure
Time is doing and what I'm doing
Is employing a strategy of soft power in a
Afghanistan
Country's debt
Are constantly working to ensure relationship
Friendship and cooperation
Many experts have noted that their strategy includes
The belief that
Should the country be listed out of abject poverty
Many of the problems that precipitate terrorism with ceased
Exist
Whether or not their intention
Whether intentions are pure is a separate Quest
But I think it's safe to say
Bombing people indiscriminate
Is the one that we use in for a really long time
Of course you have to worry about China City
Human rights record and their oppressive
Investing in the natural resources there
To be an evil plan it seems like a better strategy
Because they aren't
I mean I'm sure there's some exploitation involved
But
They're doing isn't
Necessarily stealing all of this.
There's a mutual attraction stuff
Take copper from the country
Which
In-N-Out
Like it
Corrupt system
So that works well
From out of the
Have arranged
And based on the resources that are available Afghanistan they could end up
Becoming a very viable country could be a very stable
Affluent country
Based on what is there but
Because
I've added
It's the sort of political situation
What
Intuit
Time immemorial
Okay so you're saying that
On the one hand we have a merry
That has since
We killed Millions upon millions of 9
Include all of the damage they've done to the economy
Right
And then you have China that was like you guys have a lot of
Valuable stuff
What if we paid you for
And then when your people are pissed off and getting
You'll eventually have a thriving
Economy
Then you'll recognize that we were part of the party
From the very
We forgave your debt in 2004
Founders strategy
Operation
I have no idea
But just
Broad picture
Is it seems like
What we have
Pierre is
About to is it believed that
A e v
Mister Steal your stuff
Kind of operation
And they have all these
Like 44 billion dollars that they're making a year
If we pull out and
The terrorists start attack
Do you think Daisy
Hey run back to base
They're not like if that is what Alex
Then us getting militarily involved
Killington
It doesn't but that's what I
That would probably be the natural
Is give up this way
4 billion dollars
You're there making
China doesn't have a history of invading countries
And the only one right now.
Twisted in is Tibet
Add make
You sure that everybody in Tibet knows
And there's other issues for why that is
They don't have a long history of
I would assume and I would hope
And I would
Think that by now
Global
Community would recognize
That
And Afghanistan is a
Bad idea
We've got
Examples
And only making
It's true
Implied by Alex's world
It wouldn't happen
No matter what
But
The reality on the ground is what it is
Alex
Talkingshit
Quite frankly
The big news
And even in this
I think Alex is stepping in a big old pile
Not quite
Pictures of big enchilada
One way to classify information
Declassified
Very skilled hackers
Sorry having information Missouri
Release all the 9/11
On the clintons
You want to rock and roll baby you're going to rock and roll the actors have
18000 pages of the stand-down
911 bulwark.com and it's all about to be coming out let's stop right there
What the entire New York
He said there were bombs in the building
That's a few little tricks
Wild Ride is sort of
Meeting with the general
Before the storm Ernest to big qanon
The storm
Reclaim
He wants to take over that space
In a whale
Now I know
This story is going to
To break what's
The real chick
That you are his
Quote hacker
And they are the ones really saying 18,000
No not so much
It's it's a little bit bigger than that
In terms of
There is
Come out about
We'll get into it more when Alex
2000 page
About the 9/11
Insurance policies
Regal
Cases
That have come out of
Prove it
Second
In that clip I think it makes
Perfectly clear
That he's implying he has advanced knowledge of what's in those
Hack documents
Which no one should have
Because they're equipped
Know that there have been decryption key
Is that have been released
In order to show like
We have something
Right
But I do now hackers got them legally right
No but have no info
Information
And the fact that you can
Implying that he does occasion of
Being in touch
Grimes
Oregon zip line
Play F1
I'm leaning towards lying right now
Suggest that you have some
After we get to the end of this I'm not entirely sure that I can land on one or the other
Based on his actions later in this episode
To be f****** hilarious at the other place
I don't know what's going to happen I believe the documents
We get to that
I just
This is where the episode
I'm like yeah right this
Kacchan sometime
And yeah we know you're afraid of Muslims it's right
Three girls in a pool supply shop fireworks
Around holidays
New Year's Eve
France
Oh my God
Youth shooting fireworks
Cars
Right
I kind of perked up a little bit
Alex's mad Chris Cuomo
Maybe. Chris Cuomo Governor Cuomo
Mario
About
Eclipse
Contact was weird off
About the radio interview
Okay
Preemptively say like we have a far more democratic
Situation there but they're not going to investigate
Nobody said
Anybody who's investigating you
That's
Speech that he gave near Ellis Island
Talking
I think the contacts but I can
And honestly
If I could do this all over again I probably would have gone and listen to the whole speech
Who sings just admit
It seemed to be something about the idea of like
Trump's relatives
Immigrated
Kira nerys
The presidents
Immigrations great
But
No matter the case Alex is going to play a quip
And then
Alex says something
That is
Raising literally crazy
Frederick Trump
Germany
And that's why we're closing
Trump's grandfather
3 months on Ellis Island quarantine
On record
That's interesting
Turn on record
On October 19th 1885 16 year old Frederick Trump arrived at Ellis Island
The thing is at Ellis Island as we know it the single we know about the one wears an Immigration Center run by the federal government
Exist until January 1st
7 years later
What was known as Garden immigration
Which is run by the state of New York
The federal government had to take over the operation after a ton of inside
Unnecessary death
Reports of state workers feeling indiscriminately from
Immigrants
And overall just outright
Corruption was found
Castle Garden was
The first immigration
Facility in the United States
I became American
That's over 100
2000 / gear or 400
The story of trump being quarantined
For 3 months
Categorically not
Immigration records to my timer very precise so we know exactly when you arrived
I'm going to Blair's 2000 book
The trumps
Three generations that built an Empire
Explicitly lights-out help me hours after
Frederick Trump
You met a german-speaking Barbara was looking
Hiring assistant
And that Frederick began working
Day it stayed for 6 years
Three months
Episode
2014 we heard him lie about Ellis Island and the idea of it
They are all these people were turned away because of
All all the stuff
Just trying to
Already
False narrative
Ellis Island
Being exactly like
Immigration apologize for
Detention Center
Like he's trying to present this idea but
You're mad that these kids are being held in camps but in reality
When that's not
True
If you look at the history of Ellis Island
A few people work
And how quickly people got through
And we're just now you're American
You don't have a good case to change your name
You don't have a good case to make though if you look at the reality and
You try and use that to ended
Some sort of like it's always been this way but immigration
You can make that Arctic
And that's what Alex is doing
Internet service
His purpose is on the second level
Because I need
Trump
Trump his whole life has come from that
Really
Careful
Immigration
Some stuff like that like even the guy
Who's being a monster to Mexican immigrants and South American immigrants
Like himself
The product of
The rigorous
He's as much a victim as them trying to make them stronger than because they had to go through it now
Presidential it's only if only
If only we
We quarantine all of these
For 3 months
Become president
Right
I think all of their off
The story about Frederick Trump
Hundred percent
Very clearly on Recker
He got through immigration
And it wasn't
Castle Gardens
Ellis Island
Which is the second point that I want to make
About the idea of why Federal
Or coughing
Because run fix
Debit corrupt
As evidenced by Castle Gardens
The reason why Ellis Island
Had to be taken over by a federal organization
Point taken
Rights of the States Federal friction there is
Just one other point I want
Highlights
Is the story about Frederick Trump isn't
And the only place you probably could be
We getting it from
Is Maybe
Associates
Trump
Something like that
That don't match history he's just making this stuff up
Peacock
He was a Nazi
Tested for diseases
I mean even does that funny voice about 12:00 to try and
You don't talk about that
It's not true
Better directed at you
Talk about that
It would be hard for him to have talked about a live at
After
By the time of his speech
He would have added that
Why don't you try to track that down possibly about lecture
Trying to find possible sources
Where that story
Compromise
Like
Impossible
Exclude the possibility that
Yeah I do think that's why I picked
Yeah
In the course of the
Years that I was Island
Castle Garden were open and all that stuff
I'm certain the probably there were in
A really long time
Coming into were held for any amount
Very very small
Maybe Rodger
Alton
Flight 42
The bigger issue is just it's not true
What even diseases would they test for
It's in the 18 f****** 90 what are they what are they what testing procedure
Can stuff it take sponsoring
Be like
Like we talked about
Episode that I condition
Indicative of a really
Aegis
Could do visual test
Body
I am back door
Nope
No f****** get out
And that's why
QuickBooks
You got legs
And I forgot
I crawled up this f****** boat so
It's all lot of s***
It's nice to see Alex
Because even that
Innocuously Frederick Trump with quarantine for
For three months at Ellis Island
Isn't service of whiteness
Like even that bit seems so disconnected
From Alex's
Pictures of the editorial position
And therefore all the
Cover
Are these instances of
A Muslim
Running over someone with the car
People running over people
Tutorial position it just seems like
Truck Trump has undercut like a
Dismissal of the concern
Of immigrants who Alex
Classifies as
Right and therefore us courage and a menace coming to him
It's Bryson
Well of course they let Frederick through he was white
But I feel like that's underneath
How do I instead of
None dare call it
Conspiracy
Alex had just watched
Fievel An American Tail
Do you think we're being an entirely different universe
Possibly the very least he wouldn't be anti-Semitic
I tried watch that
Not too long ago
It was crazy
It was it was
First of all episode
Crazy
Like just from a content and then second from like
You forget how rudimentary animation
The cartoons from like
The newest Modern
Like Toy Story Middle Ground
Of like that like early 90
Golden age
It's pretty good but it's also like
It's really weird to look at
Fantastic and also.
Lot of racial stereotypes
Tell me about Jews Coming to America
It's a mess and then they move Western
Let's not go too far down this
Critiquing of cartoons roof
What we're Alex
Add a story
He wants to cover
He has another story wants to talk about
Uncle says yes that's true last week we're going to ignore National sovereignty and ignore the vote
200 officers
Of the German military because they were planning to overthrow Merkle for treason
Yeah the German tried to overthrow Hitler too
Wish they would have
Okay
So
Alright
Feet
Clips
Was
In the larger World sometimes States have
No compromises
Sovereignty
Describe
Giving up some of your sovereignty
It's not like saying
The EU Army is going to rule over you or anything like that pretty much everything Alex lies about
Talking about
Compromises in terms of
She was talking about how
Parliament is the most
Piece of these states
I tried
To find this
Story
And I I don't know.
He's talking about
No one is interested in overthrowing anger
She's already announced she stepped down as Chancellor just doesn't like her
Is going to waste their resources on a very dangerous coup attempt
That would be nonsensical
Better
500 or maybe you just wanted to overthrow Merkle
Let's play this out okay I'ma group
John Leguizamo
That's how it go
Like if you are a group that wants to overthrow Angela Merkel for the things that she
She's staying for an hour
Send
Wait it out
Starbucks
It's like no it's like a movie stupid
But there's a chance it won't work like if there's a chance you die on the way to the movie maybe you wait for me
There's a good chance maybe you get it on Netflix
So I can't find any indication of what Alex is talking
I can't find any articles on it on even on Infowars website
Bring up any story
That seems like he might be covering
There was one story about that was about 200
Police officers
There was that being involved in a large Mafia operation
Breaking up a mafia
In the 200 officers when arrested they were the ones
Doing the arresting
100 number
Possibility I don't think that's it
However back in October
Arrested
Performing is far-right Terror cell called Revolution
Which Angela Merkel
But they weren't doing it from Raider position
Ethnostate
The name Revolution submits is a reference to the city show
A city that
The aftermath of the stabbing
It was done by a migraine
The protest has deteriorated into Bob violence and Nazi salute for being deliberately
Following these protests members of Revolution Shipmates began attacking immigrants with glass bottles and stun gun
Pretty regularly
In what prosecutors have described as practice run
Further planned larger-scale attack
To come
They plan to attack
With assault rifles and high-grade weapons
For October 3rd
The day when Germans celebrate the anniversary of the country's reunify
Application
The message could not have been more
Clear that their primary terrorist motivation was to undo that that unification
The police interceptor
Communications
I've been watching the group
And when it became clear that this was their plan they made their move and arrested
The conspirators
For they can murder tongue
Of non-white people in the interest of
Pushing their goal
These men weren't anti-globalization
They were literally members of the neo-nazis
And it's easy to see where their motivations came from
Here is this is the story he's talking about
Arrested for trying to overthrow Angela Merkel in the last year so I'm guessing what he's talking about
It may be misunderstanding story maybe not
I think that's kind
I think I'm a good job if only
I think it was one of them got arrested
Previous to the 6 a.m.
He beat up an immigrant and then there's like
Arrest
Are arrested in the United States
We never really heard about it all that much
I think is
The media was like well yeah I mean there's a black present
Of course
I think it was me and I was like
I I would I would guess
That Obama wouldn't want to give
Creed 2 out
Like threats against people who were around
Probably saw no benefit
Like what do you do do you encourage
To do this do insight
Before him what good is that outcome for it so just don't talk about
Quiet lyrics
Breakup Lots where
And just move on where is now
Anytime there's some sort of admittance cool threat against Trump
You got here about it
Installed
Those LED
And it just added constantly updating list of endeavor
Just the names
Just going alongside there
Be nice that there are probably more people who conspired again
But this is the only thing I can come up with that seems to match Alex's story numbers are right but
These are Nazis man
Like straight up
Big Lake it's not it's not a stretch to
To say that
They are people who beat up immigrants
And had plans right to attack
Politicians
And citizens with assault rifles
On the
The celebration
Unification
Bringing a white ethnostate German
All the traffic
Read Nazi salute all over the place
Like that sort of thing that Alex
Depending on my
It shouldn't surprise me
Somehow it still does
Like if that's crazy but he's whitewashing
Because it's so easy to see what the real
It's just not kind of amazed
I'm still
Like we're so normalized to it now but
Kind of
Still become Nazi
Especially
After the 1st
World War whatever everybody
Droid Germany and left everybody so f*****
You know you're like well and nationalist far-right movement is going to arise whenever
Still people trying
Not well I think
You're looking at the wrong
Axe throwing
Generational differences
That there's probably a lot of people who are
I've been taught that like
And do any kind of thing that's adjacent
Do not forget
Is absolutely forbidden
Like you know
There's a certain oppositional-defiant necessary whatever is the most rebellious thing right
Identifying with Nazis
Is the thing that their culture.
The most
Forbidden
Good reason to think that up
Rebellion could be
Dabbling in knock the idea it's not the
I mean
I think it's easier to become a Nazi in Germany
Then it is anywhere else
Because it is a place where they've dealt with that that guilt
Yeah as long as they have
Underground German bondage video that was actually just a guy putting on a Nazi
So you know it
Taboo
Yeah I don't know I don't know how to
Talk about it more because I'm not German
It's like that
Anybody can deny the Holocaust
It just seems strange to
Deny the Holocaust
But at the same time
Actively trying kill
Cool
Or immigrants
Aren't you the
Very proof that the Holocaust
I don't know
I don't know I think
I honestly don't know how to like
And that sort of line of thinking other than that
It seems obvious he like a
You guys there's six
You're trying to kill emigrants
None
Politicians in order to help put in your idea of a
Excludes imagine
Six guys imagine the entire country
Immigrants in
You might wind up with the Holocaust
Maybe you're maybe the Holocaust
I don't know
Anyway
They have their position
Position on minority
Call Dad
Alex
When is next
He starts screaming about how the Muslims
Are winning
It is the bunch of tax that are attached to the right patak's
The firework attached you don't want to keep track of
Because
You don't want to do any work
Get into
Islam related or immigrant
Sing like that
Khan was talk
About what
Or something
She wasn't flexing on people like he was saying that in a modern society
Sometimes there are risks
Then some of these risks are
Like let's say the security apparatus in place can't catch ever
And it's a part of
Like a large-scale urban life I live in Chicago if there is risk
Everytime we walk down the street
At night
Yeah
Think you might get mugged
Acosta me
But like I accept that as a possibility
City mugging as a crime
Real
With the world as it is
NRA's entire policy might as well be an organization
I'm saying
Get used to it
Well there's that work as a frayed of
The realities of
Modern
But their answer is
Priorat protect you
Makes a lot more money
On the day after a match
You bet so they kind of
Find outfit that I agree with you
But the only reason I don't like that
Because
It seems
To put
Actual guilt on them as opposed
Abstract
Let's not do that
Attacks
And the end and the mash raping and grooming and government allowing it
I can't anymore
I'm just becoming numb to it their wedding
London
All the specials are going to be over
Another reason you can't keep
Because he would also have
Howmanyofme
Compare
You're the one I want to do anyway
Because even in Tennessee
You just keep talking about the
Knife attack
And every time that we
Delving into
Those Waters talk about like how he always screams
And we go over the statistics and talk about
Reality of who are the people who are
Doing
It never matches his mirror
He never wants to get in
The reality
Individual
Problem for him
Rat reality really sucks up his marriage
He just wants to yell.
Scared of the idea that the Muslims are winning in the
The specials are
Strange
Assuage
And then he spends all of her
It's time making people
All the time
It is just
But it's a strategy that he learned
In the ninth
Is working for
Fear of financial
Collapse
I meant head
Comes in and tells me about the gold
Write like it doesn't work on a one-to-one level
Because he's making people afraid
Of Muslim women
And then selling them
Pills
I don't like
I have Ted who selling you the thing that's saved
You from what I'm making you afraid of
It doesn't matter what are you selling
If you buy things for me I will continue to exist
And I'm the one yeah yeah
It's a really pathetic
Business model
An ugly
No matter what he says it's the best thing in the world
It's still a bad day
Fallen trying to say is that the far-right is take
Taking over in the United
Nazism is on the rise hate crimes are going out of control
We have T-shirts that you
We don't have to
We're bad at this
To talk more about the most
And about
Is b*******
Cars in one town
We can even
Here's the key
This country
Was one of those lobbyists
Tactics
Reversed
I guess
It's cancer
Non-white
Making neighborhoods
Cancer
There's a story about these burning cars
99 burn cars
Which
Every city
I don't know about that
So just reply because I was just talking about car burnings and I want to illustrate how easy it is to headliners
However you want I present you with this news story out of Goldsboro North Carolina
January 2nd
Police investigating what appears to be a hate crime after a Goldsboro North Carolina families SUV
He was set on fire
Because their daughter who is was dating an African America
The girl's mother said that while the family slept to the cars were covered with swastikas and racist language in a third car was set on fire
In the aftermath of daughter had to stay with family out of
The family had to wrestle with the idea that their child is unsafe
Because she decided to date outside her
Go ahead look into recent arsons in the United States there's plenty of them
There's Victor Nelson Rosado who I was arrested on December 30th in Midland Texas
Right now it's his backyard because he said a woman's house on fire
Charged with felonies
Fergie been arrested for twice
4 twice
In the past
Officers that Rosato had previously / for car tires and vandalized
How about Loretta Bailey for Manchester Pennsylvania
A burning down her house
Right after she had broken up with him
The weather
He started out small just vandalizing her truck on Thanksgiving
Did you get a protective order against them
Ultimately this didn't work out because he just kept avoiding the officers were trying to serve him with papers
Have any burn down her house
Or there's this guy in Hialeah Florida side on New Year's Day 2019
Before you did
You see his girlfriend and recently separated from it but she didn't feel safe going to retrieve
Possession
So she called the police to escort
Over there
Which contact to make sure he
He knew what the situation was and everything went smoothly
After getting this update that the
Police on her we're coming to get her possessions
East that is house and car on fire to make sure that she
You couldn't reclaim
Her possession
Then there was Nicholas Cole the twenty-year-old guy from Albany New York for September
Car on fire on New Year's Eve
What time
Or there's George husky of York South Carolina who is dude turn self into begin serving a 90-day sentence
Receive for domestic violence charge
As well as a charge for illegally carrying a pistol
We went to turn himself in he decided to enjoy his freedom One Last Time by burning down someone's house with diamonds
They survived
After that list
The point is
The arson related incidents that have happened to the United States in the last few days
A whole lot of domestic violence which as you are estranged
Real strain
Kind of a
Pattern
A further point is that yes there were fire in France
But the way out is reporting the story is intentionally racist
His headline on Infowars is Eagle set on fire in migrant heavy Paris suburb
Which is meant to imply that
Migrants are committed this mask
Some sort of a terrorist
Because the wires would you say migrant heavy suburb
Unless you were trying to make
Someone
Afraid that they're going to come burn your car
You look at yourself to figure out whether it's
Relevant
Information is out there
The Story Goes even further to make things explicit this quote is a perfect illustration of how
Integration has completely failed that's a f*****-up sentence
There's no primary sourcing in this article
An account called
The intelligence Fusion
Which states cars were set on fire
Editorial
And connect the stories he's just decided or connected
So this entire article the only primary source about the 99
Is the street from the intelligence
3 million illegal immigrants
I don't know who I glanced over their Twitter feed
Maybe
People who are doing work like it
Yeah I don't know enough about them to
Give any kind of decision on them
Pjw certainly are getting beer
From January 3rd 2019
Flowers are placed on vehicles in central Ferndale Michigan
White supremacist groups
Flyers at messages regarding
Take back America
Or there was a tweet from January 2nd 2019
Quote in 2018 Chicago stardrop inverters for the second year in a row
With 100 fewer murders
The 2017
Police Credit Investments a data-driven
SportsCenter
For the drop getting better in Chicago
Chiraq
Write the intelligence editorial position
No idea
I don't know it would take way too long
Figure that out and there's such a tertiary piece of the story that I'm going to
Actual primary information story
Cover the Story 2 end credits
An actual French source
Which includes the line
Quote in the lot some Vehicles were most likely burn for insurance
This is something that comes up over and over again
From expert
When we look into the issue of vehicle Burns of Europe in particular
The vast majority of them are the result of insurance
Alex is every reason to know this
But still perpetuates the idea that this is the work of some sort of
Group of Muslim immigrants trying to
Terrorize the public
Which there's no evidence to support
Even on Alex's own website
This is a pure expression of Infowars editorial position
Demonizing immigrants Muslim
And of supporting White
This is a 0
You know
You know what I just
I just thought
The way Alex
Earlier
These immigrants coming
They lower property value so they
Take over
What are you actually just said
I know the races of a property values in that just
Anyone there
Lowers property value
Doesn't matter if their houses the same or different it's just
Virtual white it lowers property
Valleys
You understand how racism
You have that you have what it takes to be woke
What is indicating
Jump on that
Wait didn't you just
The problem doesn't seem to think that that's a function of systemic racism and a
Corrupt
Industry
Yeah he's doing but he even more at like this
I bet there was more before the feeds cut in because it starts very
Seriously
Is you coming back
Mommy's going to help out your testicles
Liberal
Hoverboard
Holy s*** I don't know understand
I want to be clear before this he wasn't talkin about like transition
He doesn't ask for this
He's just
The spirits
I don't know why you
It must have been a conversation
Or something like that blood into the show
It's so weird
Buckley we want to break right Buckley
It's such an interesting stray bigot
Connect to anything covers in the end the episode
You should know there's that big news
These 911 hacks.
It's coming
Yeah for it comes
Alex's got to throw one of his longtime associate
Radon
Going on for me to do it
Alex's with Rodger in the Rodger Stone vs Jerome corsi battle
Doesn't know if we covered it on the shower or anything like that but
Jerome corsi has
Talking to Mueller
He's decided he's going to sue
Mahler
Can't tell probably not great
Initially
Jerome corsi
But now backstage
Rodger cuz he has no other social media put up on Instagram
Really ugly picture of Jerome corsi
He's there wasn't it was just a picture of course again his makeshift
I don't care I really don't care
I don't think it
I honestly don't even know if it's
Like
I don't think they might be doing a professional wrestling
Possible in order to both distance each other from each other's whenever they're being investigated
They look at how Rodger left the Trump campaign
Trump fired
Yeah that's another thing I think if you look at Rogers career there's a lot of fake
Publicity
Or whatever
I don't really care all this is is a zero
Jerome corsi still Jerome corsi
Rodger Stone still Rodger Stone
Still Alex Jones I don't give a fuk they don't like each other
Neither
I'd come on you got to pee vages this is Twilight all over again
We have a strange I'm rooting for them both to go to prison have a strange romantic
Triangle
I assume that Alex is Rodger
Rodger 100%
Him the f*** out
In this situation Jerome corsi is the werewolf kid
References for the rest of the night I'm holding myself to everybody
The werewolf was more nurturing
Or like was a better guy I think that was the story
Houston assholes
It's my understanding that the werewolf
What's her age
And a decent guy
Empire was a decreased
Statutory rape
Being Bella
The werewolf and Rodger bigger vampire is possibly accurate
Never seen Twilight that is a completely accurate metaphor don't
Don't come at me I just I just don't care it could be a fake beef
It could be real
I really I don't I'm not Charmed by this I'm not interested slightly interested in the ideas
The situation is Alex
Is decided to be like
I'm doubling
Triple and quadruple
Between tarsier
Stone
You think so
Man man
Birthstone
Bisquick he's quick on his feet
Deseret Book
Jerome corsi is one of those guys that if he hit
You're up
George Foreman still got you never lose the you never lose the right
He's a guy also has a lot of endurance in the ring
30 * in Casper 10 whatever
But I think Rodger is the stick and move
I think quick enough
Rope-a-dope
Accorsi Toulouse everytime
I just don't care
We started talking about how the Vegas attack
Yeah Alex threw him under the bus
And was like
I think he's still doing CIA operation
What are the other things that
China King
Told me in the past
That's not going to work with him in the future
Time literally everything is part of my world
Alex is now throwing corsi out
And being like horse easily
Weasel he's trying to get Rodger thrown in prison all this stuff
No point going to do the work of being like
I've used him
Course he used to work for world
Storyworks for me yeah yeah yeah
He's a huge part of lot of lot of my fears about it's crazy that he doesn't
Bitter like
Friends thrown in prison Maybe
He doesn't care at all about that
Because he doesn't
Yeah I've never considered this
Like whenever they all know there
Playing a if they thought any of this was real
It would be like
We need to start analyzing what
Toxic information visit now toxic person brought into my world never does that
Just like with a cop
Every investigation has ever done
Then comes into question you got it you got to review
Is
Like
Wichita Rejects
Quit right
Because
I don't want to be the token
Nothing I can tell yet
The problem with the
Vittoriale shift
That was happening
And if it were it would be
But
How it must
Fields
Fired for
Infowars
Like pechenik
Is literally no longer ago
He's fire
Because
Infowars
Your nuts
Even after he after Alex stop talking to show up on David Knight show
The junior varsity roster I didn't know that you don't get Alex's publicity promotion
You don't get that
But you can still have access to David Knight
Or maybe you'll show up on the War Room everybody has access to David Knight
Leo zagami
You keep them in the likes of the baby
Right
Have access to the
The show that people actually listen
This is an occasion to visit
Smells like pay-for-play
Because otherwise I don't talk to them
Don't trust them don't let them on any of your shows
Write a little bit of money for them to appear on this show or what
He's like that
I bet we could get on Owen Shroyer
Combative
Probably
Gmail
Could probably get us
Are free
Globalist Alex
Jerome corsi
Alright
S h of the first live show I've done in 2019
That's news to me
I actually didn't realize he said that
What you mean
That the episode that I've started
Listen to on the 1st
Where the clip show
And that makes me makes me feel confused
Here's two things
I'm glad we didn't go over it
DLS possible
Whatever the case it's weird I couldn't
It doesn't speak highly of his contact
January 2nd 2019 Emmy host
Alex Jones
Are you
Guess you don't talk show host Michael Savage
Everyone try to hurt them
I would like to have Job Corps sheet for
1617 years and he's a smart guy
What time he's had the number one New York Times best sellers
About Obama's birth certificate
Swiftboating
Fart by the Koch brothers
Yeah you do we have to pause there because Jerome corsi
The show is specifically talks about how he was trained by Edward Bernays
Propaganda
Describe the process
We went over there
I don't I don't have people on misinformation
Steve pieczenik before you throughout the show you always talk about how he's asiop a guy he's in information Warfare
That was your lawyer
Sleep well.
Probably more often
Really funny to hear that halfway through
This episode when he said the trumps was quarantined for three months on record
Idalis
100 cars
First city in France Got burn
In the password
Per City
100 cars burn
Alsace-lorraine region
Who gives a s***
Altitude
He's thrown cursing under the bus
It's going to be it's a non-binding so
Much like Agenda 21
Non-binding
Yeah this is nonsense I don't care
We got into this and we're like
Look at this
Rodger
Course you're fighting
Bean something
That would be kind of the equivalent of Alex getting into palace intrigue
Of the Trump Administration
We got to get Kushner out of there you were still in there fighting with each other
Working together
Doesn't matter who gives a s***
The only possibility
But I see as being interesting
And I see no indication
Of this being forthcoming
Is there as they start to fight
Each other
One of them could reveal something accident
Yeah like the idea of what they were doing
Lead up to the 20
Like that idea
These people who work
Coordinate
With each other in some way
That's
And as of yet I have
But if it was talking about the prisoner's dilemma as being a possibility
Interest
Right because Rodger Stone and Jerome corsi are both well familiar with
Game theory in a
Decided that the best way for both
With a public appearances
Yeah I think that's entirely
It may not be I don't know
But
The biggest thing I can say is
Is GHIN I don't
Well I don't
What are they is it like you're lying
No I don't think so it's more of a
Rogers allegation is Jerome corsi
Was willing to lie about Rodger but not about himself
With the special counsel
How he knows that now or what he's basing that on I have no idea
Documents
Text Sid
Come out
Between Rodger and
Emails
Rodger and Coursey about
Like we need to get Ted
Mileage to go talk to our friend at the Ecuadorian Embassy and stuff like that
Coordination
Between the two of them in the relevant time frame the WikiLeaks
Because we don't have all the information
We don't know what it is right
For us to speculate but like
They were I could have been anybody in the Ecuadorian Embassy dance
They were up to something
It doesn't really matter we know that Alex is taking response
Telling Rodger to coordinate
Is also a unit Floyd
Hayman actual employee
The Washington
Bureau
Without starter Washington branch
Infowars
There is there is a lot of stuff
Disconnect
A harmonious whole
Would require us
Jenny Lee
There's something going on
But who knows
Beat
Could be
That Rodger
Were conspiring
To f*** with that
Entirely possible
Call Larry
God that would be the greatest possible that the two of them were
Incapable of getting in touch
Or something like that
Look who knows like I said
Avenue DoubleDown
Irresponsible to speculate too much
With what we know we know that Alex has a lot of
Trip big news
Always
Correct
Or at least
Way more than everybody else
A big news story
Is about to break
Right now
Story
That I have to be careful about what I say
Fisher
Which you're not going to be
This is incredible
Super incredible
World we live in where things are so volatile
Sommer Ray
Heart attack
Hello
Go to the next break and come back
You son-of-a-b**** teasing
He talked about the idea
These hackers have these
Documents
So you think
He's doing the same game that he always plays with
Just tell what the story is but what
Yes he said that he's going to be
Judicious about it
Yes be careful
Keep that in which place do what you said
Suggest
He was not very good
If he's Napolitano
If he's
Being careful I can't imagine what willy-nilly Alex would be like
I'm just going to talk about the story already
Because
This is the best way to
Leave a hacker group of hack
Calling themselves
The dark Overlord announce
18000 pages of emails
And disclosure agreements from hiscock which is an insurer
Lloyd's of London
Another insurance
And Hooch Blackwell
A law firm
Regarding
They dropped the encrypted files for download
Aren't really all that damn
Did this group is
Bitcoin
They will slowly release more description
Information
They've even invited China
Russia
Renovations like Isis
To bid to receive
Documents
What you tell you that they're definitely
Really cool
And clearly have America's best interest at heart
It's a classic cyber blackmail operate
Then there's no evidence as of right now that anything
Singing those supposed 18,000 documents actually
Prove anything
In fact Lloyd's of London and husch Blackwell both
Confirmed they review their cybersecurity
And there was no evidence that they've
The other one
They had been
April
But it's unclear if
To do with that
Whatever the reality that story is remains
But as of right now there is no reason to report it
It's coming through sit 911 is a
The dark Overlord has a history of cyber extortion
What they do
And the representative representative of the
UK National cyber security Centre points out
Quote
The volume and sensitivity of the data Maybe exaggerated to maximize
This is what extortionists do
They make perceived damage to make the idea of
The perceived
Devastating
Whether or not what they have lives up to that expectation
From an article in Forbes
Experts agree the material the dark Overlord claims to have is not as game-changing as its theme
Ian Thornton dropped the head of cybersecurity at AmTrust in
International says
This latest incident sounds like
Cybercriminal bravado
The fact that the firms are named
You know what terms like hiscox
You did refuse to pay the rent
So this is kind of just a pressure tactic from the dark Overlord
Force the ransom
Okay so you think
Herbs
This guy would seem.
It suggests that these companies
I've already been
Contacted by the dark Overlord
Okay
Scott is what cybersecurity
Studied
The tactics of extortionists
I'm so everybody
Who's actually
Official
Yeah this just seems like a patterned of the dark Overlord has
Because
Or a person
For a long time
They'll eat the season of Orange
Is the New Black
Before they held it
It's not like they don't have a can
There are other instances
Them not having
Good of stuff
Extortion demands
BART map
That they're still around
After being an operation for
For so long
And Betsy bomber Wild
Good enough to escape
So far
We don't know how long that will last
Because they have so many publicized
Failures
Suggestive
Probably have
I don't know it's possible it indicates to me that it is obvious
Play more than one
Because I
The character of the different things that they've done over
Have been so different
It's all extortion
But
Having the doors are not having the good
Gyro
Different
Probably some people who
Operate under that moniker Who You Are
You got it
YouTube is the New Black
And then their people were like
They don't have all the
Who have
Like things
They hacked from like a
Hospital
It's not as damning as
Covid-19
9/11
They have
They're presenting
Bring up bring down this corrupt system
Prove that 9/11 the false flag and all this
But it could just be that they have the
These
Like these insurance
Like they could very well Insurance memos and stuff like that
Trump
Long protracted court case
Don't demonstrate that 9/11 was fake
But might be embarrassing to
People are by Peter private business in the streets
No one wants that but
It's the over-promising
You hope will get you
You your extortion
To consider about this
Which is a red flag
Because right now Bitcoins going through
Aren't you know that
I have not heard anything about Bitcoin for the last year
I assume
Most people who work in like cyber FB
Understand that world
Would probably want their money
They probably want it
Through
Another unmarked bills much less traceable
Yeah
Through PayPal
And there's no specified amount which implies that
Amount
People
Previous contacts
There's alot going on here
It has the look of
Someone who
The dark Overlord
Extortion Opera
So you have that
I-95 on top of that a history of often over-promising and
Then you have asking for the money
Bitcoin which makes if the dark Overlord is a
Group
Then what you have is probably the Lesser part of that group
Or maybe the week or part of that group because they're asking
Bitcoin
As opposed to one
Other
More space
More protected
Less price of
August
Protected there Saturday
There's so many
Yeah there's still money
Not as like Bitcoins the one that took off because of
Became like out of school and came
Well because there's a lot of fraudsters outbound pump-and-dump stamps
There is that which led to bitcoin
Prominent
But there's so many other
Use there also
But I was reading about that like
We are now at a place where Bitcoin
Can possibly
People in intelligence
Could trace
If
Really wanted their money
If they were they part of this Elite hacker
Yeah they would know that
For sure I would never want
So there are red flags and questions about
If I had to guess I would say yeah they probably
I got ahold of some documents there over-inflating what they have
Because they want to make a
Bunch of money
But also our
Not
The best cyber-terrorist
In the world
I don't know
But
If they have
If they have AIDS
Prove 911
I really
F****** public service
You could possibly
I strongly disagree only be
Because of the mean
Because of the extortion part I agree with that
The other governments in the terrorist
Their Public Service is
BMI
I'm calling your bluff
Are public
Holyshit 9/11 with a
Were someone to be a benevolent hacker in Seattle and come up with that information
Through channels that could
Be like an actual
I don't know what would it be like
It would be unprecedented
That sort of operation
That involves like
Really committed
Principal journalist
Be interested in that somewhat
Unnamed
Hacker or Collective
That is looking to enrich themselves in offering to sell the
It makes me think like
You probably it's
Probably a scam
Probably a lot of
It's trading on
Conspiracy
Theory
I just
What what are your hand on the other hand
I like the other hand the biggest problem Woodward and Bernstein
Really encountered with deep throat is not f******
Selling the information in the first place
Rich's fuc
Good okay I mean they did okay
They could have been
9/11 was fake
Cabal
No One Ever Knows
They've like 911
What in those.
Tricked by this again
You get struck by this a lot
The
So did the Schrodinger's cat
And
I'm thinking I can take I can take a loss on this
Right
Like how much could they possibly be asked
How much does a
Possibly be
And even if it's not true
We spent 10 million we look we look foolish but it's like you have like
I don't know I'll tear
Yeah is too big
The Pod is too big
This guy bets
Like 50
The Grand at you
You got
I don't know
$1000000 in chips like I shouldn't pay 50 Grand I know I've lost
But whatever
Exactly it's no matter what they're asking for
If it is
Then yes China or Russia was made for it
Destroy America
Trillian
Of the United States
American
Influence
In places where they speak influenced
Greyhound
Yeah
Hannah vishu
But like all of them are important in their own way
Because they're all.
How like
If you just critically
Think about this for a second
There's no way this is real
Yeah there's no reason to suspect it's real because
It's been put out by
Cyber extortion racket
Who are known for
I'm still like it's
Just it's interesting that this is Alex
Is big news
I thought whenever you started talking about it
It was going to be some sort
Like
Hooray for the
Yeah
I was never
Prepare for this
This is
The most
I hate how I always say every
Everything is like a superlative
You got a lot of superlatives over there
2 years ago doing this Alex keeps blowing my mind
Like when I was listening to this there's no way I could have
All right so crazy
Zerohedge article zerohedge.com up on newswars.com
Rochester story but how
Systems
I'll release the 911 info on the clintons and the bushes
And has come out and said there's more than one way to declassify
Illegal spying on me and how you find the Taliban and Al-Qaeda
And now Isis
Goodyear
Cropped just us intelligence agencies
And then have the cover story that they're putting a ransom out of this company
Situated bring attention to it and then releasing
Cuz they released
What happened
They'll get payoffs
Because you cannot relations to dammit
Are you interested
Because
Okay YouTube the most f*****-up thing
Worst way
To cover this story would be to say
This is Trump
So what are you saying is this
Trump won
To release
The 9/11 is an inside job.
You bet and one Law Firm
Because the lawyers would get in the way
So instead
He is worth Congress leaders of Congress
Why do lawyers in Congress Hotel
Right right
EBay
What does if JFK was an inside job tomorrow Trump
Simply Be
It is because and pony show like 6 months ago
He's about to be classified
You can't do that with the stroke of a pen
Political politically
That might be the best move
He just revealed the JFK was an inside job
I think even I would be like
Hey Google
I mean I'd still
Think he was a
The bigot
Dick cuz he is
Is for him to declassify JFK documents that proved that the government was behind it and
Prove it 911 the government was behind it
Advent him die stroke of the pen
Without publicly globalist kill him
Because then we are
Everybody have to go like
I don't like on his life it so if he loses in 2020 it would his last day should be that
Trump should release the America has done all the inside job
Instead he is hired a group or perhaps create how to create
PetSmart
Story so he convened release the 9/11 was an inside job
There's a lot of problems because of real-world problems with this narrative.
Alex's embarking on this I would say
Because he is very
Siri sings it like
This is
Not
Clear Advanced knowledge
Your Bitcoin Ransom not met
Will be providing conspiracies through r18000 secret documents
From fat
Kids Cox Toms and others
Overlord
Wonder who that is New Year's Eve
That would have broken into the computer systems
Construction
Ugly
She says that I would only marry one person yet but
The parallel Construction
All of these Becky hacker
In order to parallel Forest
Release of the document
Okay because he already had
You can spell it out in the next clip
But they can't do it themselves
With doctor
Turlock
Construction
Of this hacking narrative
These hackers have done this in order for it to be
Deflected onto that
For their actions
Which they need to do
Because they're good people within the intelligence
His knowing laugh is in
The qanon
His knowing laugh is
I wonder who these people are obvious
Government
Right now
Actually knows
Who these guys
Buddies
Thinking it's
The government
Right
Good people within the intelligence
The
What is a narrative
Absolutely
Dumb
So let's
Listen to this next trip real quick where Alex is spelled it out a little more
Collective
Overlords
To the computer
Of the law firm files
He always said that though it doesn't matter
I know never forgot but of course the president's not involved
Hahaha
Omnipresent everybody else release everything now just
Take me to crush them.
But like
Extortion group
On the internet
And they're probably
Spectacular
You know like it's generally
You have a lot of ways
It's
Pretty early on by turning one of those
Right but you had to find that dude first
If you if you if you are
Make steps
If you do that like it's in the same way
Lloyd's of London
Good security
Infrastructure and we can
Either that or
Yeah
The problem is to
Switching
Like it's far easier to
You're playing often
You get the first move
Bright
Then you switched
2 defense
And you don't
It's far easier to hack
Is to avoid
Right but if you are a collective of hackers or even just one
Talented
You don't
Doing the offense
To stop without
A good defensive position
Magnus Samuelsson
Listen
It's irrelevant
It really is
Because
Viktos my position
Situation
Who I
I've read talked about this
Exposition
That's what I
It's probably the
And the fact that no one seems to be
It would have been paid for immediately
Or you would have possibly
Although at the same time only leads to worth extortion
Blackmail
Cuz generally when someone
If you give in
The first stage of the blackmail the second
So you just take me
Serve the real information is far less damaging than the ongoing
This is
Nonsense
Absolute
But
Problem
Alex's narrative about it is that it's good guys
Intelligence
I don't know
Possible
Nope
In a hypothetical world is possible
We're living in Alex's face
So if that is
That is
Phraseology
Insanely illegal
Alex
Is implying that he knows about this
Is thrilled about it
And
Trump is in on it
If it's not true
His Radio Show right now is
Implicating Trump
Innate
F****** national security issue
These people are offering to sell this information to
To f****** Isis
Trump is behind
Trump
Isis
I mean
I think
Really what was going on here is Alex doesn't
Liverpool grass
He heard that someone is offering
911 factual information he got a hard-on and then he's giving it a scam
He's starting to
I think probably
You might still be in touch
Rodger
Just doing this
One of his dumb ass holes
Who talks to Bhai
Has created this narrative for the good guys
We're doing this because
It fits so much
He's by movie reality
I just everything that he lives about
Let me just say here's my other
Kind of
Thought about that
Is that
As much and as often as he
Tried to jump on the qanon
And like
Use that to bolster his credibility wants to own it
What is qanon other than
Q is Trump he's releasing all that
What is my
Most of the
Flexeril
It's always been in them
Embracing of how popular
Qanon news on the
Internet but never wanting to get in
Position towards
Quite Frank
Is the idea of like I don't want to get involved with that involved
Makes you afraid
And get you into
Lower myself to run
Exactly I'm the ring
Towards the next clip
Because I think
Doesn't know what he's talking
I think it's
He's talkingshit
He's found these stray variables that
And some wormtongue
Is Whispering
Yeah I'm sorry I interrupted you I just wanted to make sure I wasn't clear on that because
I wasn't yet
Jordan
No I'm
Less than rare
It's medium frequency
When you interrupt me there's a good point
Other episode
I just think this is the Mazda that Alex doesn't know the situation
She just has a narrative
Because he's
Overlord memes
Asian
Overlord
But he doesn't seem to recognize and anyways it's dark Overlord is a organization that has exist
Like
Snot
He's acting like it's somebody that popped up now with something
Referenced earlier
The ideas
Like Trump
Created this
Extortion out
Fit as a
Cover or whatever years ago right might be
To go to as his defense
But that's for anybody
This is an entity that Isaac
And he's trained
Yeah
It's a dark but
You flip the dark and I
Which is the qanon
Justification 100%
She wants that world so bad
Not being
Like yells all the time
Original qanon
Yeah yeah
For sure
It's the
Tried
For the fall
Rafter Oregon
In the middle of the Fall
Pride comes a lot of places
Threat
It is it is the full contact
Because where you do not have the full context of his
Timothy pettiness
Is need to get a tent
Combined with the fact that
Qanon is far more popular
If you didn't realize that you think
He was coming up
With a completely normal
Conspiracy
Where is within the full context we realize how pathetic
Bulshit
You could very easily see how we
Is just a few understand dark Overlord is
I think you could
Well they can't find it with quick trudel search but I think what you add to it from our show
Xqc
Even if you take
The reality
Qanon out of the
You do have
Consistent
Friends of Alex internetworld
He doesn't have sort of ownership of
Fortune places
Reddit
These communities
He's not like able to dictate the
This
You know what you're saying
Used to feel about the mainstream media
Resentment
He doesn't control the narrative we don't control this
And even As Trump was coming in
There was so many times
Jim and Owens
Troyer do you like
You now the mainstream
You don't control what
We're talking about
There's a snake eating a
In some ways
In terms of the Ulta
Alternative meat
Did Alex not recognizing
Ternative stuff
Is also out of
He also doesn't care
Control that
6-9 months ago
So whenever he's
Qanon
First point
Is that right
Mission he's never stopped
Trying to
To take exactly what qanon is talking about and make it his
Of course
She knows better than them
The thing that bus
Most infuriate him
Is the actual Anan part of
Because if it was if there was a head
Like
Glenn Beck
He would not be trying to co-opt second.
You'd be like
Bulshit
This guy is not the guy
Stick with me the fact that it's an honest person
The mystery
Allows the space we're in
Kitano
Because he can't own going back
A little bit
He insults
Institution
Necessarily
Idea behind
You just try to
The coop
You behind it right
And appearance of elevation
No no no
You guys
Qanon
It is
You know what's strange to me
Is
Well actually
Because the best move to fight against
Qanon is to actually go into the
And how it's
Facebook from
These things trials are weird character on Star Trek
Long history of being full of b*******
Of course
Do that I guess if
Discredit
It's a trump positive
Trump
We're here to attack that
Recalling to a question
The others
And furthermore if he starts
Debunking
Conspiracy theories
Instead of joining them
But right
Story
Like
Big fish
I think we already know what we
We think
You're welcome
Disagree with
If you want but
Extortion
Disagree
Okay we kind of Welcome to
Oh well we kind of see what Alex is take on it is
Only if
If like
When guccifer
Started
Come around
No one really understood
What it was
Yeah but
Navigation start
To happen they started to trace the
Vpns
The logins of
They found that it were didn't like the jet Gru offices right
That's when it became like
Okay
This is a
Cut out
I'm not saying that
This hacking operation
I have no idea
But I think Alex is
Playing with
Fire unnecessary
Because
There's a chance that it is a cyber extortion racket
You just lying about it
Gooddata
No consequence for that
In the world we live in now
Especially its
Really risky to associate yourself or stories like this
Turn out
People are able to
Frosty's
Keebler able to trace
Find it someone Acts
Accidentally didn't sign into there
You got the laptop where the hacking
There is a decent
Chance that it could
You are now associated
Sing yourself and telling a story
About something
F******
Is it possible
Like I don't know
I want even overwhelming
Because if there was not over 16 that information will come out
Because if there were not suggesting that there isn't some
Hacker the best
There's ever been who at Seibert
If you're talking about
Actual 9/11
Approve
Every
F****** hacker
Within the Chinese government
You break at every hacker in Russia is going to be
Trying to break
Every hacker in the United States
Everybody's
Ever had
Would be
One guy it would also or a.m.
It would become a
Bidding war between plant
Cut out of
All of these
Like everybody would want it no one would want a bid on it has various
Lakefront
Where you at like launder weird cryptocurrencies
Through and it would turn into a trillion f****** dollars for it we never hear about it
They were the single greatest hacker in history
There's a 10% chance
Pull this off
Is there anything less
All the world
Because we're recording this on Thursday night
Another bird
The end of American civilization
We don't know how the story is going to
Play out and it'll be interesting
To see how it does
Because they're real decent
And it'll be a nothing much like the antifa Soros document
Which hours will just later bring up as proof of
Writings without ever having
But I don't know I don't know
As a human being as
Go on
But this proves 911
Very small
And if it is
If it is
Well we got a f*****-up Time ahead of
Greatest whistleblowers
Of all we
We have
Snowden we have mayonnaise
Reality
Have these people
Their move was
Secret
They're moved within the
End
That way
Heroically
Attention
I'm from the
That's why Seth rich is such a
You would fit that mold
Who was The Whistleblower
I'm at front
But
Again it's alright
As it relates to 9/11 we have next clip where Alex talks
Visa vie
Trump was not involved in all this he went on television
There were bombs in the building
He probably should
Real quick
Did Justin interview on 9/11
But he thought they were
Well
What do you mean
Isn't 9/11
She wasn't back then
Terrorist had bombs on the plane
Because he was
The Iron and Steel girders
If you live in
It's about the penetration to the building
Who's talking about how the windows were so narrow
In that World Trade Center
Building
It was because of all of the
The iron
He's talking about how the building was built from the outside
The structure of it
They couldn't have wide windows
Do you talk about the idea
Is that a plane was able to fly into it and penetrate
Those steel beams
He suggested that there were bombs
Not
That there were bombs at the bottom of whatever to breathe
Increase the impact in order to allow them to
Penetrate those steel beams
Whatever they were representing at 30,000 miles an hour
Oh you bet that's a possibility buttstocks
People
You can't it seems like if you're flying
Really really fast
A lot about
You know what
Maybe
One time
Because Trump is a real estate
Even though he's a
Complete failure in a pile of
And he doesn't pay his
He has some
Engineering
Are some engineering knowledge
Just know more than you
But not more than Xbox.
Expect
Flying 30,000
Mph is a pretty good penny
I'm not sure that the speed they're flying put yes absolutely it is it it does seem like it
Equivalent to a box
We made it
Indicative
Thought that there was some sort of
Yeah
Also invited
Interview hours after the attacks
40 Wall Street actually was the second tallest building in downtown Manhattan
Replied and it was actually before the World Trade Center
Has the second tallest
But now it's the tallest
Also for fun just to be Petty even after 9/11
40 Wall Street West butala
Manhattan
70 Prime
So Trump's building he was bragging about what even before 9/11
Hours app
The tallest
And also also
Definitely not because he
He's a f****** psychopath
Also fun fact about 40 Wall Street
He only bought that
Because of Ferdinand Marcos
IHOP Philippines
Yeah
Kia
Embezzled
Millions and millions of dollars from
New York and 40 Wall Street
Another building
Disrepair
Rehabilitated as the Trump building
Event for years
Hanzo
Tons
Criminals
So many people
Not people necessarily
The business is that
Have been house
1040 Wall Street
Have been
Indicted
It's crazy
I don't know if every building in New York has that
Kind of batting average I don't know
But their batting average
Looks
Bad also Trump University their address is 40 law Street
That's so much like a haunted house where is likes
Fashion
Have existed and the f****** infiltrated everyone who
It's hard not to look at it that way
I think this means I
Superfudge
Weird is that Rodger Stone
Through black manafort
Brookstone
His old Lobby
Group
They used to do a ton of horror musical called black man
Before that they like before Ferdinand Marcos
Avoided lobbyist for Marcos
For this brutal f****** dictator
Who embezzled
The habit I don't know if you know this
Of like taking political
The middle of the night
Dismembering their body
Disfiguring them and s*** and then leaving them out in public
For other people to find as a message about what happened
Kind of like that as a message what happened
If you watch who's called Salvage
He was doing that while Rodger Stone was a lobbyist
And it's interesting that
He took this
Panin bought 40 Wall Street
Didn't work out and then Trump ended up buying it
I honestly don't
Like 121 connection
Rodger Stone
Definitely
I'm not trying to prevent it
Conspiracy were like Rodger Stone was absolutely
Interesting
It's so interesting if that history is
Coincidence
Is
Just at least knows each other
Just shy
2 hours
Listen to this episode before like eclipse
Like if I keep going
Through this episode
We're just going to
Kudos
Whatever
Worse than what you saying already
Implying
More complicated this narrative
And so we end
Alex celebrating
Some sort like he's he's delivered this narrative
Perfectly
Businesses this is McStuffin victories made of the president has nothing
Things you do why does release the documents
Through Congress themselves
Packers are going to release it now
I'm vibing on the song
That's good vibe vibing on that song
I just
His bums me out not not like cuz it's a bummer
Because like
I don't like just I don't like to see
See the celebration
It's Transit
Like I I know
I've listened to so much of Alex's show that like
I can't even be happy
For him like
I knows it within a week
I know it was in a week
Because just going to become a
Another like little
Narratives that didn't
Workout that he will go back about whenever
To reinforce another Point user
I jumped
I just
Bummer
I think
It's something we don't talk about it
Generally
Never as explicit
It felt like
What we talked about
A little bit already is
This is such a
Pathetic attempt
Through
Yeah
How to put it it's just
I leave this called
Because I
I own one level I'm super happy about the idea that like in the same way that
On Christmas Eve
Alex
He told Rodger
Go to talk to song
Yeah like that
Par with that
Like he's revealing that someone told him some
We correct
This is the biggest crime he could
Someone absolutely
This isn't his own analysis
That summer
In this life
Though which is
Which begs the question of who's telling him this b*******
Behind
That there's someone
And I'm not sure who it is
Absolutely
Like
There's two ways this
Is possibly cancer
Yeah
Actually probably
Three or four
Play out
These people who
Titan Collective
Get arrested
That's one
Possibly
I most likely
I see that is kind of unlikely
Maybe someone get arrested
If someone gets arrested everyone
Sure that's the way I can collect
Possibly
I think you're I think you're right General
No one pays the the f******
Ransom
Just fizzled out
A couple of more
Decryption key
Show other documents
Anything about 9
Right or
China Wok
Which
Wow
Which I think is more like
They approved it Hillary Clinton
Was in the World Trade Center in
The only reason that
She lost the presidency
Was because she died in 2001
9/11 Hillary Clinton
Number for Silver Fox
Drake quotes
40K
Precipitated
Attacks because she needed
Which could
The exact
Necessary
Ritual in the
Linda bloodworth-thomason they did a witch ceremonies
Alright
Provide
Required to have in order to lose the 2016 election
I don't know
The elevator was slow
She could get to the base
Number 7
Something else
I don't know
I don't think
Any lakes
Other than propaganda
Like that's the only thing
I think we can clown on stuff and we can we can have fun
But like I really don't think
I see a lot
Of the world in
Failed attempt
Like narrative
Who gives a s***
Yeah but this to me it just thinks of
It's yes
Something's it only
Exist
Provide fodder
For people like Alex 100
These people do
They're not doing it I don't think
In order
To be of service to Alex
They're doing it cuz they want that extortion money
You have two teams working sort of out of
Like
They are
Creating
That which Alex needs
They don't give a s*** about that
And they'll disappear as soon as
The money isn't
There
That.
The only two
I have on this
Here's the worst part
Against
All of my better judgment against
The worst things happened
I do
He's been so depressed
But that's why he's been so miserable and kind of like
Look this is garbage
Not going to go anywhere
Glad you got a
Living on a Prayer
He's living
Before that Rush of the of the narrative
Because the
The world is
Is so bad
Is forced to demonize Muslims who threw a firework
Shirts and stuff like that
Or
Lion
Make a hero out of bolsonaro
We shouldn't he's absolutely amazing hero about a racist
Rapist
Fascist
Monster
Yeah
Literally stand
Analysis career
Yeah
Butt wipe
People aren't in place
Have to do
Those things because everything is so bad in a real world
Play Store
This is what's so weird about the world is like it's bad
Forever
Yeah like
Lgbtq
Everyone is everyone
In general are having a bad time
Yeah
Alex is also having a
As evidenced by
Desperate he is
Right you'll happy about
A cyber expression group
They're doing great
Hero his narrative
They must be
Proof
Of my grand conspiracy
That I have been putting
4th and
The qanon is
Can I must now reclaim
The fact that you
He's very
You're not having
Funny
Yeah we could all be having
Fun
We work toward
Right
I don't know I don't know how to put a button on there
I'm delighted
Equal level
This beginning
Right
Here's my butt
Here's my brother
Dark Overlord
Happy New Year Dad thank you Happy New Year.
Is Lionel this is not good
It's fine I think
I think it's good
When is Hebrew
He's bringing this
The beginning of the year
M like
Way off on
I bet he's big story
Is this
Cyber-espionage
Asif razzaq
Actually
Hey extortion racket
Yeah
Kidnappers
Extortion blackmailers on the net right now they would have been kidnappers in the 90s
Windmill gifts
Austin was making movies of Eric released
Yeah
Whether you be a man
A woman
A collective
Or your pronoun
Is different
This was a bad idea
Because once you start a fire around and
Proving that is
Inside Job
Even if you're lying
Lot more people are paying attention
You if you're going to cyber store
Keep it on the low level
The car
The consequences for playing this game or a little bit
More than
Probably
To reference
Stick with the mid-level terrorist
Do you know yet if we got three Hots
Hostages will give them to you for
90 grand how about that
What do I do
To get you out of here with a hostage
Like going to a car dealership
Conspiracy a superpower
What gives
As a power chip
Is unbelievable
As of how that gives you
The world's you don't get to choose the next superpower
There's no there's no ways
Get to choose
Who is the next
Ascending
You get there's no way if you can
Improve
That 9/11 was an inside job
That you don't instantly become on the planet because
Does what you do
Is that you have that with will destroy
Z Super
You know what I'm saying
Instantaneous
Destroyed
When they find out that
F******
Gdubs in Chinese
Orchestrated
We'll talk about it
Alex
Stop talking.
Yep
Anyway
Beck
Griffin
Secret information that these
Who's supposed inside
Patriots
Right
To know that
Consistent
The only consistent
Career
Is knowing laughter presages
Him being the most wrong
Could ever be
I'm falling ass backwards into
To a criminal
Underscore fight we got a Facebook group called go home and tell your mother you're lying
That's right
You will be releasing the wiki
Every episode every episode
Because there's a part of me that fun fact
Fat women
The 7th comes
You'll say it
I'm not back
January 7th the most comprehensive
What other adjectives
Match.com
Sanely comprehend
We only
Has ever done this
If your
False modesty
Shuffle Spotify
It's only it isn't credible
That is to say
The only things that will be
Recovered
When we launched this
Are the things
We've know about
Auto Show we haven't covered a great deal of Alex Jones
So what
He is a full compendium
Everything Alex Jones
We haven't covered
He's in tire
We're so
Did you just Robert
There are no known Known Unknown unknown
Robert Gates
Rumsfeld murdered by
Roving band of people
Whether known or unknown
Launch into
The website
The wiki and all that stuff will cover the
Formation that we are
Are able to cover
For what
I do
And I think it's comprehensive
But I don't want to oversell it
And say like
Cuz I know you discovered the Boston Bomber
In that we will that will be there once we cover it I know that I don't know
It's frustrating to me
Look at houses behind a paywall
You can go faster
The information there will be great
The only reason that I push
Next
Episode
We all have our anniversary episode
Oh man as you know what is already on that show said let the never do it with her
Like we would do a
F****** sound
Quit
I'll save the dark Overlord is a hack
Collective or individual who knows
Extort
Right I don't know if that is everlight anyone to
To commit suicide
For fear of the extortion writing like that committed
Probably not ever actually physically killed
One guy
And that guy
Alex Jones
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work