Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
70 *
Remember the most
Junior year of high school
I mean he's a math teacher in high school
Right you had
He had little catch
Which phrases
Is about like about the reality
Piece of this
They always
When we look at the hypotenuse
The realities
Is that the length is based on the other length
I don't know what the reality
It was his way of saying this is what you need to focus on
Missed a bunch
You're not going to pass
This class is
Well the reality is that I don't really care
Get out
So that was that was what
A real life
He said in the Moment by getting into stand-up comedy
Career was just chock-full of
With me
Being overly
Gifted in many ways like a capacitor
Super easily write essays on
Stop I didn't really know much about the family
Just be
Just the worst
Not coming
What would you mostly Layton breast
I wasn't a bad ass I guess you could get that image based on
It's mostly mental illness
Cool
And I would go to
School
Hello neighbor
The Listener spider educational background
Great difference
That I got inspired to do
We go along but Spurs 11
It's pretty close and our donors
First of all Rosie
Thank you so much
You are now
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Taking time out of your very busy schedule
You mean the schedule is riveting
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Mark
Thank you you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Jon B
Do you make a Sloop John B
You're about to
A genuinely was John B thank you so much
Fruit Loop vodka
I'm a policy wonk
Today
Jordan
Review yes David I get these emails sometimes
End up in the wrong folder like sometimes
People emails
The people have donated to the promotions tab
But then also another thing that happens is that if someone
Has an account that maybe
Be someone else's name is on
That other person will get the shout out
We we made a mistake
Oh s***
Thank you you're a policy wonk but in honor of our mistake
We are going to make you an honorary Texan
Someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much
I don't know their husband her husband's name
As I understand
Yeah I know ma'am
Patriarchal bullshits
Go to our website
Play.com click that button supports we would appreciate it
Hey Jordan today I
Different Road
Is the owner last episode hard about this idea of these hacks documents
Approve 911 extortion racket
Alex
The hypothetical content of those emails
Ownership of the space
Reclaim qanon
Until I was I was
Ruminating on that and I realized you talked about
Produce Loose Change Final Cut
On the Forefront of 9/11 conspiracy theory
Quite frankly
Talk about how
Claims
He predicted
All right I want to go into that a little bit
I'm trying to assess exactly
If we want to give him credit for that
It's sort of up in the air a little bit
Are we going to
Credit for have
Actually
Applied an owl
Is that
Function the way it was
I'm not sure even if that's how I would phrase it going to say just taken is
He predicted 9/11 because he says
So
Today we're going to start
On July 25th
When Alex got on air
And dig what he says
Is him predict
He said that
He's projected
Here is from Alex Jones is
Hello ladies
Join us
For this
Wednesday
Fest
1 broadcast
The global terrorism
Important
Information I'mma put the call out
Call the White House
What about things up
Martial law
And that we're aware of who the terrorists are if you pull this
This can stop
Larian right
By the White House
Terrorism come from
Boogeyman
I want the White House now
A big part of the solution
Terrorism
Call White House
You know Oklahoma City in World Trade Center was terrorism
Airliner
Marshawn
If you do it we're going to blame
Terrace
We know who to blame
Planet
So most of the subs
Of him predicted 911 on 25th
35th 2001
Does bring up Osama bin Laden
Just bring up the World Trade Center
You can talk clearly from
Contacts
He's talking about that as an example of something
Texas facts
And also you can tell us about blowing up airplane
He's not talking about that in the predictive
Capacity
To blow up airplane
Write a future
Beyblade never have stopped
Hublot
I'm not I'm not going to take
Because there are a lot of specific
Specific
Who's going to do with this is where it's going to be your anything like that
More more substance than you would expect from Alex Jones
You're missing
You didn't get it
It's numerology
Letters
Mathematics
It is interesting that that is not
It is interesting to me you know
It sounds a lot just like any Alex show quite frankly
In terms of like screaming about the government
Preparing to Stage Terror attacks
You can choose almost any day of the week
Alex is going to have said something similar.
It still would have made the exact same amount
He did do it.
Videos everleigh doesn't even
Crystal clearly he sing
The Boogeyman
Of some sort
The 2nd
Second
There's also
Reconsider
So he also is comparing
The idea of some terrorist attack that's to come
Larry and rice tags
Fire
Which is an important thing
Keep in mind as we
We go along
Interesting
There's another guy
The conspiracy world
I don't know if you've ever heard of Bill Cooper
I do not know anything about Goku
Well let me tell you a little bit
Derek bill
William Cooper Bill Cooper also first name Milton William
Musically
Gucci near the paranoid militia broadcasting world
It is absolutely an early $0
There's literally no way around
From January 1993 to the time of his death in November 2001
Bill Cooper distributed his own of the time
Then later on a weekly basis
He covered it all
He dabbled in UFOs and mystery religion
But more importantly the world he was also deeply
Interested in the idea of a one-world government
He was a staunch defender of Randy Weaver the central figure Ruby Ridge
It did frequent episodes about hello Oklahoma City and Waco didn't go down the way the government said
He covered the difference between gold and silver as hard money versus the idea of soft currency in paper money
On a March 11th 1990
3 show
He didn't episode about the internet intentional devaluation of the dollar
He covered the Federal Reserve and how income taxes aren't real
Derailed on socialist
Spread suspicion about the
Council on Foreign Relations
And trilateral commission as far back as 1990 when Alex was 19 years old and still years
From ever being on the radio
On February 18th 1994
Episode
Bill Cooper interview Sheriff Richard Mack
A central figure of the
Susanville Sheriff's movement
If someone who go on to be a freak
There are a lot of overlaps
Between cast
Including Aaron zelman the president of Jews for the preservation of firearms
So it was an early sponsor of Alex Jones
Really gets to the point
All this is to say
If you look at spiritually at the stuff
The bill was
The world
Alex wasn't a big
I probably was deeply inspired by
What do you nationally syndicated or was he around the southern Market
Show but it was
You know it made the rounds
Very big deal
You wrote a book called horse
I don't know if this is true
He says it
Number one most underground Duster
Computed book
In the world
In all of history
Because that's no marketing numbers on there is no marketing and nothing really behind him or anything
It's a very very popular book in these world
Who's doing that since
The New York Times number one ranked on Reggie's
Bestseller
Sure why not
Books
I don't know I don't know how you quantify it but it is
And here's the part where I should probably just
I don't know what time about Bill Cooper
Yeah I'm going to learn a lot more time
I don't f****** know a whole lot about it
I know a lot of it matches up with Alex
And then there's a lot of stuff that Alex
Drive to
Yeah yeah
But
Bill wasn't too that
The course of his career that the militia Patriots
Interesting UFOs
Question
Alex is a huge fan of like coast to coast and George Noory
Turn off
Music I'm sure I'm positive
Alex love
When did Alex
Who died in 2000
November 2018 November 2000
Fairy shot to accompany head twice
Okay
Charged with bank fraud
We're not going to f****** fulfill that warrant because we're afraid of an armed standoff
Come out of his house
With a
He would commonly tell people to
Be quiet right that sort of thing
Cuz I knew you had weapons cache
Coyote running videos only did this because he had
Reports that
Threatening
Local residence
With weapons
Go through with it
So they do this
He shows up at
The car they announce themselves
Police officers
All right. The best way for things
Clear that
Didn't believe
You've been arrested for the
Tax evasion
And all that
So he had already made clear
Email to friend
Too long before it all went down
He had said I'm going to take as many down with
Suspect this is probably what's going to happen
His house
Or something like that is a real
Nono for the police
I'm not idle I never liked it when the police kill anybody
Luther Wright
Cuz I understand
Yeah it's the number 2000
See the way that you
He described his
Radiokorea
More like he had died
Because he was a
Precursor to Alex Jones
Apparently he was
Just like
A sovereign citizen
Like a regular sub
There's no way you can
Keep your job
With a warrant on you
Play themselves well he wasn't living on the lamps
Uneasy truce
Trouble
Execute the warrant
The people around
It almost doesn't make sense
Do okay
Now alternate
Alternate Theory
Alright he predicted the
He did but he got it right on
He said almost the same
Something is Alex
The government realize
Is that
In order to
To prop Alex up who is an operative of the CIA
Isn't it always
Government control
Control
He's too nice to Israel according
Stormfront
The reason that they left
Alex a lot
With the Takeover
No bill Cooper's I understand
My magic.
Reality is both of them could have continued to
Suggested that sword
Perfect which is
Unhinged
Untethered
Criticism of Alex
The system he had them take out
More like what you're saying
Conspiracy theory web
Cooper ENT
More about him as as
Spoiler alert the entire Archive of his radio show is available
Wednesday character because all of his shows are online
We can know
That on June 28th
2000w before Alex predicted 911 on his show
Bill Cooper
Show hour of the time
After the anniversary
Play Kiss From a Rose
Of the Oklahoma City bombing
We were bombarded with anti Patriot anti-morsi to anti
Who's panel look that people believe
Are the Constitution for United States of America
Anti-American propaganda
Airbnb Timothy McVeigh occurred once again
Prior to
And immediately following
Look cream thing occurred against a word extremist would use over and over and over and over and over and over and over
Over and over and over again
How many time
Now we're being bombarded with messages that will, Bin Laden is planning to attack the United States
America
And Israel
And I'm telling you deep a
For a major
But it won't be on, bin Laden
It will be those behind the New World Order once again
Want to take
The Gardens and the freedom away from the American people because we're the only ones left in the world
Who can oppose
The destruction of freedom in the world
The implementation of a one-room for solitary in socialist government and that is the goal
So you have basically he predicted
Specifically
Preemptively
Inside Job false flag narrative
Already before Alex is supposed
New Theory
Alex
Got his hands
Spawn
Sumerian ritual
Okay
Leadville Cooper out
Look directly into his eyes and
Soul
And that's why
911 he lost his
And
Spoiler alert after 9/11 Bill Cooper
Necessarily
The police
Very much so he's had several
Play Don King character
Chicken standoff
Sound
A little bit later
2001 episode
You'll hear bill
Layout almost
Entirely with Alex's 911
The Narrative will end up being
And you'll hear a little bit of a similar
To Alex's
Months later prediction
But he makes about
Hitler could not have ever come to power absolute power in Germany without the right
Stag party
Hitler was a socialist
Social engineering
How to get the support of the German people
I need dirt bike Burning Down The reichstag
Well
In our country
It would be the Capitol building
Brickenstein
House of Representatives
Somebody were to go and burn down the Capitol building today
They would use that as an excuse as Hitler did
Round up all of the enemies
How the new world order
Which would be named
Both of you look me
Florida prison or Instituto
Declare martial law
I talked to Absolute and total power the surface
I wonder what
Karma bin Laden
Target Circle close to me
You know if it doesn't materialize next 2 or 3 weeks
It will eventually materialized because
They haven't succeeded
Getting the garden
Out of the hands of the American people nor have they succeeded in taking our freedoms away and practice been
Great Awakening
Backlash
Against the Market Common
Naki
Did somebody steal his thesaurus
But you can see a little bit of Alex even there
-
Bombast
Explosive Showmanship or whatever you want to call it
Calling these people
Now there's a there's a little bit
50mm of
Are there doing these terrorist attacks
In order to
Bring in
New World Order movement is gaining traction and that's why they're going to have to do this
In order to
Cut it off at the pass
Or whatever to Alex's version
That it's almost impossible to imagine
Listen to this episode
And that a month later
Your credit a little bit kind of my big series
In terms of these
Very paranoid man
Quote predicting
I don't like that
You turned every
Things that I believe
Into a lie
Because even his
F****** Origins
Everyone
Every Every Little Feather never happened pretty much
Everything Supply behind everything
Totally
Completely dismantled
Does man's mythology
Subway
Was very helpful
And now I see no getting in
Little bit of this.
Giving a shout-out
The other thing
One I don't like that he had trouble reading
Constitutionalist
I think that was for dramatic effect
He sounds
Super good at his job
I think I think we listen to a lot more episodes
Do you have less of that
He's not is he secretly right about ever
I can say no
Interesting
A lot of episodes
The show where callers call in
And he'll push back on
Alex.
Complaints about Alex Jones later on
What is the idea that Alex just listens to rumor and reports it is true
So he like on his show when someone calls in
Tennessee Department of
On the streets
Or something like that
Where is Alex Wolff
Turn that into
The Bill Cooper knows a lot or is right about
No
He does have more of a measured approach to broadcast
Which is why he was never going to become a
Successful is out
Already
There's other reasons why Alex
Pay the taxes
A bunch of that does hurt your ability to Syndicate probably assumed is active
Lawrence
I'm telling you
Give me a job
Dude we're going to have to
We're going to have to garnish your wages before you start
And also turn you off
We should be having this interview right now
He would have been perfect
Alex
Richard Anderson
Yeah but I think based on the
Reality
Through the years
You're wanted
You could do that if you're sad
Even more under
He's the number one most
Best selling Underground
There's a little bit of a beef between Alex Jones and Bill
It exists within the Patriot militia world
This is really
This is Drake
I don't have a good grasp on Bill Cooper but I do have a grasp on Alex Jones
It is interesting to see
Disfigure
Come into His
This world is such a demonstrable
Alex is wrong kind of
In the same way in the sentence
The first part
Is it looks
Pretty clear
That Alex
Number one has to be a huge fan
Of his rate of the hour of the time
Yeah
Almost certainly stole that 911
Now
Along the line
This has to be after Bill Cooper was dead
But I'm not sure exactly
Alex get to call about Bill
Asking
About
What do you think about Bill Cooper
What did you think of Bill Cooper
Never try to attack him
Put me on that night
He thought I'd never heard it show because I didn't look.
In Aliens and all the stuff and I've tried to never attacking but people resurrected old tasty out of them and stuff and
Okay alright
Well
Or whatever I mean
His
It's a no too much but
From what I understand he believes that Eisenhower met with aliens
Episode
Not too far off in terms of being like I was a little bit
Not
We haven't listened to a lot of it has sounded correct on everything Sophie
Is in reference to Uber after
The whites
UK episode of the show
Together
Very out of line
On Y2K
Of which we covered on I think our second episode Alex
Like
Episodes of time about how f*****-up Alex's
Hold on
So somehow will Cooper
Inspiration for Alex
His progenitor
He will
Send timer hours
Yeah it is weird isn't it
It is interesting my working theory on a Tuesday Alex hero-worship
Bill Cooper 2
Disposition
Is malicious stuff
Salt
Become a bill or something like that
Batman started
Interact
In some way
Hatfield didn't like Alex never lost lyrics
That's my hilarious
There's more to this called
How do you spell sorry for Bill and he really let him set them up and
And I ran out there and help them killing
And distractions her I don't talk about flying saucers and
All that stuff man I'm sorry and football team
Sorry for Bill
Okay thank you
Never caught the guy customary custard everybody
Is that your answer you like that answer
I believe me I know you're putting
Uber to
Falling down drunk
Okay
Needed help
IRS
Newark
How triggered Alex
Brings up the name Bill Cooper
Issues are intense
And all across the board but don't you find that interesting like the color just asked what do you think of Bill Cooper
Very different is he launches into that with no help from the college
And even halfway through the colors like Alex I believe you I trusted you know like interesting I'm
I'm on your side still defensive about it
And the reason for that
Is Alex
Is f******
Totally lying
Absolutely
Categorically
Totally lie
Bill Cooper has been on Alex Jones Show exactly one time
In 1998
Yeah
And when he was on
It did not go the way Alex doesn't
Absolutely
There is no indication that
He cusses at all
Who's on the radio for over 40 minutes
Not including commercial breaks he's probably on an entire hour
Of Alex's show
But here is how the interview start
Hello
My friend just called and he's got an Apache over his house with camera pods and infrared taking
Play that on our TV show just wonderful
Call around my unmarked police car
Openly taking photographs of this wonderful isn't it
So you see already this is how we like almost
Friendliness
And then immediately starts launch again
Impress belt just called in that has a black helicopter over his house
There's a sense of that
Just another manifestation of the
Nazi gestapo police date which is taking over this country
Practice
I talked to you this week
44 years old
He doesn't ever anger you
Well course it does what angers me most is the stupidity of the vast heard of American people out there
It's also Bill Cooper is one of the people
Noted
Popularising
Him to thank for that
It seems like the person who's more unhinged has
He's screaming about how mad he is and then there's a long
Don't you ever get mad almost
As a way of like trying to find the common
First memes
Heather think they know something and they don't even know what planet they're on to tell you the truth
Simple Thing by private bank print the money and enslave everyone
Simple things like Clintonville
Transnational Asian
Will you book Behold a pale horses
Well now and almost everybody that has
Any know-how bond any of these subjects
He's already plugged
You claimed he hasn't read berlioz
Stupid
He knows about that book
So he's already
If you look at the exit very clearly
100-percent lying about this interact
Ben 10 years prior to
Track to Lil
Well after I wrote it over a. Of years back
Beginning in the early eighties and continuing up
Into about 88
Senator I believe in 89
And I may have added a couple of things in 90 and then it was published in December 1990
December 1990
How many copies are out
I love you have no idea bendy number one underground best seller of all time with no advertising what's the weather
River
Amanda
People sell it on the street corners in New York City had to take it off the shelf and then
New York City bookstore because it
Everybody wanted making it the most stolen book in their inventory
The most stolen book in their inventory
I'm around here
Basically an overview of what Behold a Pale Horse
Tell the public and now it's
Even more incredible that so much as what you've written has come through in the last 8 years
He's
You giving him Prosthetics status yeah
Have come true
This interview to me
Knowing Alex isn't
From his work
I hear an insecure Alex
Alex in 98 wasn't the Alex of
You know the mid
Delete 2000
Liqe
He's not the same broadcast
With the same status in the world
He wants to be a part of
He's a hero in that world
Totally
You like the way he's asking these questions and you heard it twice
Almost
I was at 4
There's a sense of reverence
Minuscule and I think it's his way of covering not really knowing how to interview this guy that he likes a lot
Yeah that's the sense that I get
It's exactly like
Edith exactly like so many of the times to see Alex
Does daddy issue show up like what the John Birch
Oh I'll give you whatever you want please please just
Give me some sort of
F****** there are remnants of that
And you could make the argument
Like Alex
Future from
The color glass.
You could
You can look listen to that and you could say
Well that's not Alex being insecure and Reverend
Sure fired
That doesn't track with the way he's lauding
The way you think that your book all these things
Been proven true in the last 8 years
Keep calling him sir thank you for being here
For sure
Elizabeth
Much more of the interview itself
Because it's 40 minutes and it's mostly the
And more
You know
It doesn't serve our
Too much
To go over that
Find the whole thing
A what
Heard from bill which was interesting
Based on
What we know about the
He is like giving those stock
Like he doesn't believe
That there's a Blackhawk
He doesn't he's just like maybe there is maybe there is
Exact part of reinforcing this
Noahsnoah
I think that's
Probably
And I think
You just hear a guy who's doing the radio
Any plane is rolled
The end of the
Where Alex
There are going to be absolutely amazed
A couple times and it is a lot of good information people see and I
Hi I do respect you and
And I
I certainly hope that the FED do back down
Because I know that the revolution in this country we've had a couple of them
T1
And that's it the whole thing starts I know that I'm on the way
Website
And actually before that
Cut that clip terribly before
To stay over another break
I love the idea of
Kick him off the air isn't true
They'd already run over the time allotted for their interview and he was asking
Stick around later I'll stick around but I've got a plug my website
For the weekend can't you stay one more day discussion
With the collar about Vale don't track with reality
At all
Start swearing Alex
None of that is
Defend themselves
That is a hundred percent
Is that what I
I was really hope
Hoping for a repeat
Okay
Interesting Lee
September 11th
Gentleman who put out their words
So Bill Cooper ends up dying
In November
Thought before he died
On the 26th
For September 2001
He puts out an episode of our of the time
Titled
Alex Jones
Liar
This is cool here is the first clips
Tower of the time William Cooper Good Evening Post
Probably get started after clear up a little
Discrepancy here
Who did the last week
Beginning work email about this and receive One telephone call
Apparently somebody call the Alex Jones
Broadcast
I didn't have me on the air ask him something about me
Alex Jones Eddie and have me on the year
Before
Several years ago
And had to cut me off the air because of the foul language that I you
Sony air tonight I'm going to tell you Alex Jones
You are a bowl
Face
Miserable
Thinking little
Howard liar
Don't say that again cuz there's no mistake about it you can all tell Alex Jones that I said there
He's with me because he does
Alex Jones
You are bold-faced stinking rotten little coward liar
Feels good
There's a piece of this that I kind of decided to do this episode
Partially because of
Alex's weird 911 stuff last week
Yeah
Prediction but then I also really wanted
Adjust
Take a
Tikka sort of
I don't know it's almost to walk
A little bit for an episode of just like we get to Cooper telling Alex Jones
Go f*** himself interrupting everything
And especially you
I want to listen to all of this
Whatever I said that
Was the precursor for Alex Jones are showing ours
Really right on well
He was kicking ass dude what we're doing now and Noble
Where are you hope that we
We get a review on iTunes
But it's not like every episode of his show is about exposing the b******* of the hour
Like you is one episode here from the 30
18th of September next I want to listen to that
Biological attack
October 9th
There's a lot of like
Most of his show it does appear that
Is crazy conspiratorial nonsense
Okay and I will try and
Make a real-world corollaries
Alright Year from September 11th
New York attack 9/11
Number 8
Cheetah 10 episode
I really nailed that one probably
Let's try this one owls from the 14th of February 2000
The guardian
Owls of Ga'Hoole
Abundantly clear and I think I have already
I don't know a ton about Bill Cooper it's nothing that I'm saying
In any way
Ice cream that I
Cooper has been right about everything I'm certain if I listen to a ton more of these episodes
I would find
Hunza problems and probably incredibly late
And probably really scary dangerous
I am certain of that
In the same
I can say I'm interested in his interaction intersection with the world then we cover bees ivy
Did Heathcliff
Clearly his
And clearly
It didn't work out for Alex
And that's pretty funny
Broadcast
Kerry Cassidy
It's hard to tell her YouTube channel probably started
Butcher project
Before that
Board mean that it started in November
2001 when the
Bill Cooper
Was was
Instead transported
Into the body
Films made by
Hours
Kerry Cassidy is a fan of Alex Jones isn't that point
William Williams
Nearest
Okay
Air raid siren in Menlo Park
But I'm also glad we don't have a theme song
I don't want to get too into the weeds because like I said I do have some
Some very strong reason
The suspect the Bill Cooper
If only
Vacations good indication
Drawings
Pictures of red flag of some, I mean like from I mean like
His work
Don't know enough about it to be conversing
So this is one of these weird
Before we started the show.
Your place for me to be in because
Cuz we're covering a topic that I admittedly don't have a good handle
Like I only know
As much as I know and it's
The world I know
Have a hold on a tiny piece
So I feel out of my depth
Variance
Insecure but
This is
This is more like
Teaser episode 4
Text timey wimey Wednesday
Bill Cooper
I want to know all about Bill Cooper and about how he
I'm absolutely certain of that
Is there a Monday episode that I should say
That
The one of the big reasons
In addition to last week Alex re bring up 9/11 all that s***
Hazzard episodes
You can call out
I was only on the Alex Jones Show
Years ago
I didn't know who he was
When I didn't the realize little liar and a coward and a
Tapetilla
Bulshit artist of the year
Biltwell 14
Broadcast that's when I was doing guest appearances on broadcast years ago
I was not cut off
I did not use any kind of foul language so ever
He treated me very well
Track
For the whole show
Totally true love you in Texas
Know that that's true because you
Heard the broadcast
Who Alex Jones was and what he was doing to the truth
Cowardly liar and can't April she really is
Israeli tiny calls me
After that
I've always refused to appear on a project
Absolutely refused to lend him any credibility whatsoever
Bye.
Broadcast
Very angry
I believe everything
Alex
Like I said probably wrong about just about everything
Morningside Alex wanted me to come back on
Three times before the cock crows
Is that you said about
You can get away with appearing on shows that
You don't support
A little bit
Like with that you know that that have idea because I don't think you should crucify somebody
For appearing on a show that asked them to
To be on that you don't
Like
Know your episode of punk
It was weird I got that was just
Timberlake
The only reference I have for Punk
The reason I'm thinking about this is like there's
Tons and tons
Cast of Alex Jones Show who have been guests
On Red Ice Radio
Red Ice TV
Yes I'm out right
White nationalist
Know what it was
And got asked
To come on
As like a
To show there's some listeners
Everybody's got a
You can blow it every every
I should have done that
Later realized
Turn on red eye sport
You do not know the character of the show
If you're able to learn the character I'm just saying I'm just saying
I'm just saying
Inside
So I believe all that
I think that's a bills probably
The idea that Alex wanted to back on said no and I do
Think there's nothing
Nothing terrible about it
And how he reacts to
Situations
Exactly what
Exactly like what Bill Cooper
Alex's
Exactly
Is acting like everything good Bill Cooper says was 10
Hundred percent correct
It feels like
All the things that we would have
Just listening to Alex
Oh yeah
This thing here
Infowars
Used to have
Video up
Alex is trying to
To bury this part of
He hear that Bill Cooper is right about everything
Siri can only go so far as
He's right about Alex
Yes that doesn't mean that he's right about other things
God knows
Should have seen what I ate yesterday
Call boy
Pennywise
I'll tell you who's never even
Untrue certainly certainly
He makes his chili homemade
In his talk with a collar where he's lying about Bill
He says the bill edited up videos of me
You was about to
Calling Alex Jones wire tuck
He brings up why he did
I'm also we do him for the lying-in-state Coronavirus
Bulshit artist of the year
To your attention
The lines under the feet
A rumor that he spread
Over the airwaves
Better not good
How about AR Presley not good for Melissa
And Patriots
Broadcast you ever did
Garner
New Year's Eve
What year
The New York
Bring your beer 2000
What you went completely out of his mind
Queen
Intercontinental
Ballistic missile
With multiple Warheads
After United States of America millions of people who are putting their children and their
Borinquen their cars and heading for the Hills
So right there on
I think it's
Really important
The point out that what bill is taking issue
So personal
Offended by this
It's Alex has no respect for
Effacing is operation
Reportaj
Entirely on rumors and
Conjecture and hearsay
The second Bill recognizes that
Alex
Have an effect on the
Go hear them
He's taking
Yeah it's strong issue with the idea
People heard them and got into a panic
That's part of his negative consequence
Yeah
Who the f*** is Bill Cooper
Recognizes
Responsibilities of someone in a position
Or like
That is
Don't get people in
To the place
Hear your life
And that's important
Yeah I can we try and bring it up but it often gets buried in terms
Except for whenever people talk about Alex
Visa vie
Getting Sandy Hook families harassed
The human element of it is so
It's not ignored but it's
It's very rarely
Made
A big part
Yeah
Stoneberry
He's got Alex Jones's ideology Dan Rather
It's it's like
Call me in the
Saying that everybody is going to
A little incongruity
In the Deep
Boring
And they're coming
To murder you
Zombie
The hours of time
Go to shows it like
Few not boring
Is much different than having a boring delivery
Stephen with his
Terrible delivery
Get well soon
Nobody needs to lie about me
Sometimes I am irritated
Sometimes I absolutely will not suffer fools and am just as rude as I can be
Alex Jones
Next time somebody calls your broadcast and ask them about me you tell the truth
Lots of fruits that you can tell about me
Don't ever lie on me buddy
You off at your uncle
I will chew you up I will
Put you out for the lying stinking rotten little coward that you are
It's a lot of the main points
Yeah I will I'm going to give him a
Slight
Look just
Studio notes
You were doing great
It is a little bit weak
You off at the ankles it's kind of like
It's on gratifying as a threat
I don't know yeah you're not wrong
Now
Redundant
Forgiving others
Studio notes the idea of life
Never be said enough quite frankly but
Yeah
What's interesting
Is that called we heard
From Alex
Talk to the caller Bill Cooper
Bill was Devin of 2001
Bill put out this episode responding to a caller
Calling into Alex
To show
And Alex responding.
Exact same what do know that at least
From 2001
Onward that's been Alex's
Sort of
Rewriting of the interview
Area was like
Do you feel that
That's true but I think it's because it highlights.
What's so important
About his own self
Mythology
Yes
He is a coward
Bill Cooper
And I don't mean to say
Admirable
He is the one who
Clearly was willing to
To stand on
Whatever principles no matter how dumb
Or backwards
A f****** cop
And got killed
Rather than own up to the fact that he's got to pay taxes
Like that's not a good thing but if you look at a propaganda
You have your principal
Yes
Good or bad
You present yourself as believing in
And with Alex
Alex
Position
And all of those things and we've said
According to your own principles
You should be against the
Just be
Like fuk about other than believing that the government was coming to kill
Plane
What's up
Ideologically
Consistent as he was
Hughes crazy cancer
It does appear that way again
It's hard for me to say
Is that it is that there is a
He wasn't deviating that
Did the clip show
Supposed to just
Doing the beat
So that's the thing that gets me as far as
As far as the conman non-con man level
Recognize that the beef
Yeah you know but they don't do
Specifics about each other
Clip show
Not generally
Alex was shooting all over the bed doing the Glenn Beck
Expose
But Bill f****** did it man he went straight for the car
He sells books
Episodes that I've listened to a number of
I listen to a number of them and he doesn't ask
For money
Really
Like the car
Isabel
And there's even a
Call that I heard where this guy was talking about how he doesn't have a lot of money but when he does he's going to send Bill some
Have all the air time
Like not mentally but she's like haha
Alright well thank you
Florida
It doesn't seem like he's motivated by the sea
In terms of
Things that are true for his own enrichment
Primarily motivated by
I want to know more about Bill Cooper
Open episode
Open up way too big of a Vista
You know like the horizon
Two large
What's the name of this Tower of the
The time alright well
About Alex
And it was knowledge
Alright so now we just moved Cooper
Legit
Only interest
Really in as much as he is sort of a
Prototype
Precursor to out
And someone who seems to believe that much more than Alex
And Alex was able to use
A lot of fields good for in a lot of the world that bill was right as the window dressing
Camouflage
For him to sell Ted Anderson's gold and all the other scams
Approach to cover and more
Let's just talk Bill Cooper for a bit
I understand about him but
Enrich our understanding
Early Alex Jones
Alex Azar
Like a lot of that you can't find on the internet and man I've been trying to
Males have been returned
No idea
Cuz I can't find
These early days Alex Jones episode
Super easily there's very few
Resources
No
But this does give a window into
What that world was like
What is this
Formed
Into what he would but
Abundantly
The Logical endpoint
Alex Jones
InStyle propaganda
Who actually
The Logical endpoint for an Alex Jones that believes what
How do you say
Is to be murdered by the cops
Like that's the reality of it
Simply by his continued
Existence
We can surmise that Alex Jones because we have a case study
They're saying
F******
Just a tiny bit
Because it didn't have to go that way
Because
Bill could have continued doing a
Exactly what
You was doing if you wasn't
Threatening local
With guns
And stuff like that
It wasn't just
His presence
Threatened that he was going around harassing
And Alex
I don't know
Book fair
He doesn't have an outstanding
Warrant for bank fraud and tax evasion that the cops could act
You'd have to be a new
Moshe
For the directive
Bill Cooper
To commit suicide by cop
He didn't have to go that route it's not the logical
Propaganda
Just like the Superbowl
It's a logical endpoint of abrupt
Believes this load of stuff
And also likes to threaten people with guns
I don't want to give him
For his death
Beat like being like well
We are saying that it's like
You believed it enough to get there
But
Really precipitated it is him being
F****** a******
And also
Gone pee
Ms like if the cops come for your guns you need to be prepared to kill the cop
Present
Weird
To see the parallels between so many Underground
Like Comedians and musicians who
Everybody's like I should have been more a bigger than Nirvana
Bill Cooper
And I think this is one of the reasons why
The difficult episode
For me to do is like a lot of people
I thought you know exactly how cute
And then there's a lot of people who listen
No quitters were built
The showare
We're giving an introduction
Sort of tooth
As another topic
It will come up over the course
Podcast
End
That might be unsatisfying
Metaphorical mudhoney fans or whatever
You don't need because because what you're expressing isn't
Truly
He was cute
He's very big
But obviously
Commit suicide
That's probably one of the reasons
Is lingering
Poni
Computer stuff after that
But
He's not a miner variable
He is someone who was
Very important
To this world
Piercing propaganda
Banana.
You want to you want to bring a button
No
It's all just
Like what I've been expressing this
Entire time at what I said
I don't know a ton
I want a gun to learn more
But as we're doing the show
This episode
It's not
To give like
Peterbilt
Uber
Here's an interesting incident from Alex's career
Cooper
I know you're Furious that you're conversant and not a PhD in the subject or less
And I just have to make
It'll happen
We already know that
Who's lying
But in this next clip
Fill your hand first tuition what else is what else is Alex feeling
Truck delivery companies
No building kill nog
On bills show where you talk about Alex Jones is a liar
Yeah which again
We don't need a backup to prove
It is the case
Bill take some calls and they all have his back
Music near me
Yeah I heard it
1992 did he hear
Thank you for dinner
Alex Jones is a miserable rotten little
Howard Lebow Facebook
Boring
All these people are no better than to mess with me because I don't take any crap
From anybody
I'm not afraid of the whole national anthem for the entire government gestapo what is my helmet
Aljo place that I would ever be afraid of his cowardly little rotten butt
Pretty think you're near
Said about the Alex
Archived on the internet at one time and I did hear that interview
And I wasn't thrown off the air
Interview I ever did without it goes as soon as I found out what he was doing and who he really was I
100 times in France
I've always told him to take a hike
Appreciate
So
Interesting things to wrestle with
Is that
Bill is right
Like he's on your percent right
The circumstance
B
He's also probably
I think he's probably worse than Alex
In terms of being really extreme
You're insane
Banality of evil
Alex is an impotent
A small cross-section of his audience will end up doing terrible things
Just get lulled into a
Learned helplessness in by Prada
Nature of the scam
I think the people who listen to
Whatever was serious and focused and likes when they're talking about a subject
Directly talking about it and then when they're done talking
You know like how I f******
Serial killer is goddamn organized and ready
Alex Jones
Prince Humperdinck
Bill
Is Christopher Guest
The torture in
Christopher Guest
Don't give a fuk
He's just going to do what you can
Twilight
Apparently everybody was out
50/50
I don't know I don't know how to your right or earlier I don't know how to put a button on this and there is nobody this is just kind of interesting
Snapshot
Ideally we'll build on more as time goes on
But it's a Snapchat worth looking at even without brand
Context
Cuz
We Now understand a little bit better
Where Alex gets these ideas
Which is worse it on its own
And then beyond that week
Hear someone call
Which is always fun season we're introducing a new villains and we're f******
Course your first step
Going to get closure
Nope
Season monarch
Or not we could
As time goes on I'll probably go ahead and read
In the past but go ahead
Jump down that f****** chimney and see what's inside
Stihl M5
Thousand dollars
Jumping-off
Both both
Absolutely
Eric Cooper
All right we will not see him again
Get well soon
Ultra.com
Underscore knowledge
Underscore fight underscore Bilko
World
Correct
Over there
Can we die
Technically
I don't know if we can say you didn't kill a guy
What specific incident
It does seem that way
Technically probably
Tequila guide
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color