Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We are back forget another episode
Drink a little bit of wine
And discuss their what's going on
Play Chubby Checker The Fat Boys level twist
Alright
Fat Boys
Nordstrom's in particular
Not at all not at Iota except I did just turkey what you watching
You tried to get me to watch some
And then David
Appeared
F****** demon from beneath the the boring
Sixth level of hell like the world's most boring hobo
Coming on TV
Yellow tongue
Because Alex said
Promoted online
He's about to drop a
Pizzagate
If we wanted to check in on what that was
Watching
So far
No bombshell
So we will monitor
Keep you up-to-date
Nope not at all I'm still standing by my former theory that I espoused of Life podcast
You got threat
The lawsuit
I'm not sure that anything that he says
Is today
Play Shake by beliefs
No he was definitely he's definitely serve some sort of papers Maybe
Subpoenaed
Truck hero
Yeah but anyway
Loft
He was way more sugar
Episode
Generally what we do is I take
A Day in the Life of Alex Jones
And I play the
We discuss
Incredibly wrong
About everything
The entirety of last
This week this is unprecedented
But Alex's
Promoting
And
The results
Of my
N2y Alex Jones
I feel lucky
Pasta no
But he's just being
Alright have to know
About 30 text
Trivia over this past week
About how in
Your research is
Wonder I wonder
Court document
What is
Wrong with you
Decision
This is now this is eventually just going to turn into wishing well on
Thing is I'm thrilled
I know
That's one of the problems I had an amazingly great time reading up on all this stuff
I found is like legitimately
The horrifying
There's individuals that we're going to discuss
You probably wear of maybe one or two of them
Sure he's going to come in the mix
Liverwurst Franklin delanor
Roosevelt
I think it's an accident but I'm not sure
Possibly
There's a guy at least one who
Going to come up
We all know who he is we heard of them before
But then
Search that I did
Really highlighted how much
The worst of a person he is
Okay that was not fun
Reading some of the
The stories about him
Because
Can think about is you
First thought is o.j. for some reason I don't think that's right
But look
I know I'm doing too much
Teasing but we have to start out her episodes as we
We tried
I'm out of context
Text drop it is nothing to do
Call
No yep
Yep
Anyway
A lot of people over 50%
Yeah
Alright
Here we go
Let's get to it
Skip
Alright
Cuz this is going to be in 10
Alright I don't want to sing let's get down to business
This Is How We Do It
Bi-Rite
The party's up on the Westside
You know what eventually I will make
Just because I love pink and I don't know that one
Pink Lana Del Rey Carly Rae Jepsen and died on Mount Rushmore
F*** you okay okay
That's fine
He's pitching this entire game
Zombie song
I like the Orinoco Flow
Or that song
Sweet November
Only time
Look what we got to get out of bed
Exxon Monday's shows
The pieces
We're going to be talking about
Okay
You're listening to The Alex Jones Show
Monday
Dragon
Cam
You can see it's been there since yesterday
Afternoon
Documents prove surveillance of trump
Project
Now we got
Inside Sheriff Joe Arpaio
Call Casey
Kohl's
Infowars.com
Years
Last night
This morning
Document
Wendy's
No because when he's saying more that's that click
Careful more he's reading
The link
Eminem Eminem project dragon is a second link
He just did
He doesn't even know what he's reading on the page
Rhythm of that is
Banana Trump
Surveilled more project Christopher Walken
Doing the show
His lack of preparation
He doesn't know what he
Actually
About to talk about it all
It's infuriating it drives me incredibly insane
But
So we have the
This clip
Done there's more
What we have already as the introduction of the theme
Who is come out
Who has a ton of documents that prove
Donald Trump
Is being surveilled
Will learn
But not only is Donald Trump
Being
Surveilled
Bethany was just
Right
Alex Jones
Michael Savage
Other people's families
And this
Just just other people say Hansa folks
Note
Although Snowden does get clocked out a little bit in this episode
So minor compared to what this whistleblowers bring
Alright we're going to dig into every single element
I will
If in the next
Two-and-a-half
23 hours don't end up with everyone who hears this
Realizing that this is nothing
I will
Commit Harry Caray
Verbal contract
Look it up
The only way to go about things honorably
At least come out and say it wasn't true sound like we got them
Federal Marshals and Topping
And for a week the media ignored
I also called the phone numbers on there
Right now
Trump family
Again that's him reading the link
I'm not figuring out outside
I do remember
Yes where we go to make the movie with The Rock
Can Steve Carell is that right
I don't know
Yeah with
That was the old one
They made a new one
Steve Carell
I don't think the rock was in it I think I can play at 6
So on Sunday of last week
Infowars published they
Believe
Claiming
A database
Phone numbers
An address
Right
And Alex has said
These were my old phone numbers this is correct
These are the phone numbers that I have for Donald Trump
These are real phone number
But as We Know
He doesn't know Donald Trump's phone number
Code for the prize you keep saying that
He's claimed
But he has multiple phone numbers for Trump
It falls flat for us
Thompson different area
He has he has these things that he published
What's up
Parts you know like you don't want to
Bakery don't want it even if you don't want to
Hunza people
Klipsch off parts of phone numbers in Wenatchee
They claim that it was a part of a massive index
People who were being spied on
And this is from this whistleblowers
Now
The problem that we have with that
Is that is
Completely unprovable
All of this information
Could Have Been Gone by someone who has
The minimum amount of hacker
Skills
Added willing
To falsify.
So keep that in mind as we go for
Struggling
Anything that Alex posted
Does not have to come
If you posted on the website
From
Like an NFA source
It's all very easily accessible information
Like a lot of information is
Mara Lago
I could Google that
I need to print out like a part of the phone book
I don't think he did I think someone else did and sent
22mm as evidence of Ali
Okay
It's not the white papers it's the white pages
Nailed it nailed it
You think about all day
So this is basically the construction of what
Is going on
They building the foundation of a lie about
Eli's
Alex
If using whatever information that he got as evidence that
Spied on
If using it as evidence that he was right all along
Right
So on Monday he has an interview with
A guy
Mike zullo
Okay
I'm in for what
So you come back for one last job
Is he is away from retirement please give me some used car dealer
Cars I can tell that's what I found in my
Flight b a
The research
About Mike zullo
Necessarily
Alright care about more is that he is
What former employee
Cuz he's not out of he's not to work
Anymore
Sheriff Joe Arpaio
He was a member of it and now I think it is time
To deal a tiny bit with Joe Arpaio
Racist
Garbage
Pile of
Human foxy
Earlier when I said when you look at him
But even what you just said
I did not know
Get worse
So we're going to get to it and
Is going to make the argument
You think the devil can't go lower but there we go
The devil also like
You know cheats
The cards come on
Zulos point
Which is
When
Joe Arpaio was being
Court
Making the necessary changes
Insisted that he make
Based on findings that they had racial discrimination
In the Maricopa County
Police force he didn't follow
And then also didn't default telling him
There were times he was brought in
2008-2010
A problem
He was held in contempt
Arrested
Left leg cut off
What should have
In this court case
I don't like
He's right legs
Yeah exactly
Argument as he was being
Because being
Surveilled upon and why
During that investigation
Cuz I want to give an accurate picture of Joe Arpaio is
Let's get down to it
Pages
Subway
One of these
Is disqualifying
So get ready
Does he say grandpa
No
Maricopa County in Arizona
Joe Arpaio
The houses inmates have not believed that they deserve to be inside
Great Arpaio literally described the city as a quote
That's good
I like his willingness to embrace
His monstrosity like didn't even bother to call it
If I could burn you I would
I would totally do that
Blind as I can
Speaking of burning these inmates
Please don't say anymore after that on July 2nd 2011 temperatures in Phoenix
Degrees Fahrenheit
Arpaio measured the temperature inside is 145 degrees Fahrenheit
Some inmates complained that their fans near their beds were not working
Heather shoes were melting from the
Cheese's during the summer 2003 with outside temperature 10 degrees Fahrenheit
Arpaio said to complaining inmates
Hit 120° in Iraq and the soldiers are living in tents and they didn't commit any crimes
So shut your mouth
Which is
Horrible
How do you do that
How do you not have any empathy
In 1997 Amnesty International said arpaio's Tent City Jail is a quote
Humane alternative
Inmates in suitable jail facility
People get mad when you leave a dog in a f****** car
This dude is literally burning people alive in the Desert Sun
Tent city is criticized by groups
Human and constitutional rights
Implicit in it
Formation
Yep you at
You wouldn't do that
His argument is that they're criminals and who cares
Committed crimes really bad argument
One of our relations actions was a requirement that inmates wear pink underwear
In order to prevent it
Released inmates
Which of the stupid rationale
Most harmless thing I've ever heard anybody
He claims that he has saved the county
$70,000 into effect
Mankato
Sent more advisor
Customized boxers
With a Maricopa County Sheriff's logo
Goat
As a fundraiser for Sheriff's Association
What's the spike
Arpaio
Declined to provide
Accounting for the money
He basically use it as a promotional tool
So so it's so
With his financial
Close
Together in arms illegal immigration policy to help enforce immigration laws
Posse Posse
Gets worse
This included
Steven Seagal and Lou Ferrigno
No that's better
I am comfortable with that
They have guns
I know that
That Posse is
Immune to ninja
That's the first thing we know about that party and then
If anybody
Gets really out of control
He's a big green guy
You would not like me if you're illegal
Especially not if you're a God
Even close to the tip of the iceberg
Routinely abused child
Another contaminated food
How hot is it
Endanger their help
Denying them care for serious Medical
Mental Health
And keeping the packets
Now that's before they've been middle Medieval ages what is f****** happening before they were charged
That's before they were charged
Pretrial detainees
No you should treat you awake
2010's
Constitutional rights
Vivian Maier
That should have taken like 20 sack
Under Arpaio the Maricopa County
Multiple times
In September 2008 the National Committee on Correctional Healthcare accreditation of Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
Office jail for failure to maintain compliance
Are providing false information about such compliance
Does that mean people aren't allowed to be
They're not supported by these medical associations that are in charge
I'm sort of keeping
Track and making sure that jails
I think that's
I love though I love their life-saving ability
Like enforcement
Capabilities but they do have
Like
When do the finger go to a Goddamn pizza restaurant
Beings to save other human beings lives
Liberals are
Maricopa County
Are unconstitutional
Play work on it but these are just
Is places
Although most inmates have not been convicted of a crime and are awaiting trial
F*** you
What
It gets worse
Where is Egypt worth
Come from it gets worse
At least
Ted Bundy was on
Monstrosity
Like I would much rather
Like he's a sociopathic
It still allowed to roam the
The streets like you just figure it out
How to f******
Turn it into a money you like
Turn being
Ted Bundy
8 *
Arizona
That's fair
Here's another one for
Under Arpaio the Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
As many as 75% of cases
Navigation
As I grabbed
During a three-year period ending in 2007 more than 400 sex crimes reported
We're providing police services for El Mirage
Arizona
The Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
Failed to follow through on at least 32 reported child molestation
Jesus f****** why
In all six cases
Many many
We're illegal immigrants
How do you
Not care about
I don't know
Hey 1999 undercover Maricopa County Sheriff's Office deputies arrested
Then 18 years old
And charged with plotting to kill Arpaio with a pipe bomb
A local television station
A broadcast
The Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
And local television stations
If they think they're going to scare me away with everything else
It's not going to bother me
After spending four years in jail awaiting trial
Seville was about 24 years awaiting trial
He was about to sign a plea deal that would have sent
The prison for twenty years
Although he maintained
He was initially unwilling
To take a chance on being
To even longer
If you work
However
The former head of undercover investigations for the Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
Based on his review of the case
He felt the civility been in trap
Although it is all but impossible to prove in most jurisdictions
Attorneys eventually discovered that the Maricopa County Sheriff
Detective
I bought the bomparts themselves
What then convince the bill to build it even though he was not predisposed
To commit such a crime
On July 9th 22,000
America Copa County Superior Court jury acquitted Seville
The Boost arpaio's re-election
In 2004
Siri
Maricopa County Jail in Maricopa County
Billion dollars in damage
Joe Arpaio should have been hit with a f****** in 2008 the suit was settled with Maricopa County paying
1.6 billion dollars
Little bit less
You should have got
Billion dollar
Yeah
I am
This is the hardest thing
I am against the death
Penalty
But your pale should be f****** killed
He's
There's only there's only one reason for the use the public Trust
To such an he's abused them
CIA
Like there's no other
Hey Jordan
He's already dead
This is the producer
It can't justice department Constitution
Latinos
And retaliate retaliating against
Critics
In a report
The department concluded the Arpaio oversaw
The worst racial profiling in US history
It 2015
After after all Arts
If you get labeled with that
In 2015 Arpaio was charged with
Contempt of court for failing to implement a court
Required changes
I to his police force regarding
Racial profiling
He was also found to have destroyed Evan
A f****** course
He's also publicly promoted the Obama birther
Up to December 2016
He was quoting
Getting a birth certificate you found 9
Points of forgery Obama's birth certificate
So
A2000
Mayor Phil Gordon called the federal investigation into federal investigation
Immigration enforcement
Arpaio's office respond
Fight demanding the mayor's emails and phone log
Arpaio also had his critics
Maricopa County supervisor
Republican
To properly discuss
Disclose Business Center
Stapley agreed to a 3.5 billion settlement in his lawsuit against Arpaio
Thomas and the county for Folsom
Multiple times
A suit for it and
He's cost the county
So many millions of dollars
Because of these illegal tactics
But he's undergone
4 * has like a runoff election
In twice
Drop the mic that hit failed both times
Really
How could this country have elect
Trump deeply entrenched
Illegal operations f****** racist
I love s***
Yeah so you know he's a racist
Is bigot you the awful but it not in jail cuz he argues that he gets results
Wow you committed all the crimes he might be soon
He should be dead
His argument is that he's Gruff but he gets results but that's not an argument in a case of law
But also listen to this
In 1998 Jordan you're under arrest
For terrorism
Excuse me I believe I get results
Commission to study by Arizona State University criminal justice
Professor meriel Griffin
Examine recidivism rate
It's based on
Conditions of confinement
So basically like beforehand
We'll come back supposed to be
Before him and after him
Under Armour
Observe between those offenders released
A1989 290
Those released in 1994 to 1995
So what you're saying is that he is both
A criminal
A monster
And it's offensive I get results
Does not actually
He's a f******
How can you how could you not
Prosecute
Like there's no
That you could not put him in jail forever and ever and ever
And all the lives
Believe in reincarnation
Nation or ghost
Just so that guy can
Be tortured every moment
For the rest of f******
I'm giving you all of this information because the interview that Alex does is with
This guy's close
Okay. Waterford
Do Alex has our property of Europe
F****** monster
We can
Determined
We're talking to a f******
He's an evil man
Here's the situation
There's a lot of really f***** up stuff that you can find out about the history of Joe Arpaio
Maricopa County Sheriff's Association
I just got a
F****** bullet point list of
Absolute
Alderman
Monstrosity
Upon reflection
Me and Jordan have talked it over and we've decided
For us
To necessarily be Broadcasting
I I think
I think you should
On your own
In
Mystical place because
In a row
Overwhelming
It shook me
A good place
Start
About that you want to go you can find out more about
The depths of the truly irresponsible and evil police work that he
Joe Arpaio
Presided over
Everyone can
Convicted in the nerve
I genuinely
I genuinely believe that
Is the sword
Give a moment of silence
Let's get it
We will wait for seconds for you and they will kick right back at you
Interview with Mike zullo
That
One of the higher-ups of the Maricopa County
Former higher-ups
Does it work Alex
Does a lot of vampirina
Accomplice to every single thing the Joe Arpaio
Implicitly signed off by
Supporting him
Still supporting
Also Alex does a lot of sort of
Opening presentation before he gets to the interview so I can play a couple coats of that
Documents for surveillance
Federal court
Decorated Sheriff patreon
Monster murderer
To try to make up garbage
Yours truly
Isn't that just special
Not particularly
Nope
Shipping
I think it was the Red List
So the argument
The Blacklist
I don't know that's why I
Arpaio was
Spider
This is
Absolute utter nonsense
Why would you need to the secondary argument that he's making is come out with all of these
All these people
One of
The necklace from Mission Impossible
Get The Blacklist on James my reference
A little bit further down the line
And make sure
In a second
This is where he connect
What's going on
The Arpaio spying situation
To what we're going
We talkin about later
That involves Trump
Involves Alex
Is the guy named Dennis Montgomery who is that nsa's CIA
I swear to God
Have you seen the movie Zodiac
Yeah have you seen any movie where somebody has a giant
Pinboard with string connect one thing to another
Because it's on your goddamn wall
This one's real simple though it's not a
I assure you this is not
Line string that's all we needed for this basic
They ignored it
Arpaio even harder because
The Whistleblower
Information
So connect everything there this whistleblower question is this guy named Dennis Montgomery
Dennis Montgomery on him now or later
Let's go with
Okay here's a fun one
Dennis Montgomery music video compression noise filtering business called
Intrepid technology
A video
Compression noise filter
Like a 1998
Business started out as a tool for the
Casino industry but eventually they sought government
In 2014 Montgomery was revealed to be working as a confidential informant
For Sheriff Joe Arpaio
He claimed that when he was contract
For the CIA technology
The government contracts as he was doing
Documents
The prove the conspiracy
Against Arpaio
Basically the department of justice under Eric Holder
Was working
With
The judge
In the case
Unopposed
Racial profiling
I had the document
Sprint just called
It's not just called
Get like doing conspiracy
Well I mean
Is it just like
But I guess I mean
You can't man
Conspiracy
Wiretap
The judge
I mean I also do
On the table
I don't think it was also
We know how bad do Joe Arpaio is
Gila monster
Publicity stunts in this 2000
Claim that Montgomery
As the result of Montgomery's investigation is quote
Junk
So even arpaia fixed
Yep
Come on Alex Jones
It's just talked to
Alright so he's a vampire
Mark Mike's
Zillow
Who is arpaio's
Again
Tears that we
Heating up
In elaborate
And super long introduction
On-screen know Jerome corsi
If somebody's not looking uncomfortable while Alex Jones is introducing somebody I get real bummed out I'm not joking at all
Trokosi is hanging out
Between Mike zullo
He is there as like a third wheel
Okay
At this point Alex dropped information that shows
He doesn't have
About the situation that he's going to be
They're the ones that got the documents
The contractor
Wizard
He doesn't know what to talk about unless this information is sitting right in front of them
Cuz he doesn't know the situation
Of course not
He only knows if he's reading Awesome piece for wet meanwhile yells bodies teleprompter free
He only knows
If his staff
Is feeding him information
Let's recap what happened
Key Alex
I had published
List of people's phone numbers and addresses
Just leave from
This Montgomery does Dennis Montgomery
I just did
Willits recap what happened yes
And Trump
Play with invisible
Of documents
That Dennis Montgomery has revealed
But he hasn't
All that proves the James
This is going on and Trump is being f****** Railroad
It's good
This
I wish you was on a railroad
Pencil Thin Mustache
What
Once again I want to use this
Just established
That Alex
Is specifically
Talkin about
And Arpaio stuff
As being the exact same thing
What about butt
In the mix
Papa's infowars.com
Bombshell discovery shows targets
Project
Here's a Larry klayman article
House intelligence committee
Mass surveillance
Where the 47 hard drives over 60 million
Talking about Snowden
Necessary
Also known as hard drives
3 by 5 floppy
They claim it's actually 600 million.
Walgreens
The issue is that no one really knows what's on them or if they're even real
This point
Lead time you couldn't process 600 million documents
No
McDonald's
Cell 99 billion
10 years
Alex is proof
But all this is real his phone number and his old phone number is
Along with
Donald Trump
Phone numbers
Which again we have
Suspicions whether he actually knows or not
The only evidence
He gives at any point
This stuff is true
Super stoked bleached show
Obama
Right on truck
Alex Jones
Sheriff Arpaio
.
Showtime
Nothing on this
These phone numbers
By the phone number
Private
Apartment
These are the numbers
Miles cell phone number
Mi private office
Numbers
Real
They're running around saying
World Trump
Defective
Phone numbers
That nobody could know
Chew it like
It's dumb why would you even have an office phone
You know your office phone number
Hit the nail right on the head a lot of the stuff is
Conceivably public information
But even Alex Jones cell phone number I guarantee I could find it
Tiny bit of hacking ability I could find his phone number
Really easily
Based on all of the places that you would have dropped it if you ever went to college all that information
And is really easily accessible like
A bunch of your ear a dresser
The community
Wichita
Two cell phones
A lot of the
I don't think real
Be that as it may have these things you end up
Filing information places
A lot of your private information is much more accessible than people think
Tons of news reports about this
Work just
Mid-level basic hacking
Individual
Let's not even the most evolved hackers
Are able to find
Tons and tons
Private information about people
You can get f******
Courtesy calls on your cell phone
Yeah they're just telling your number
Like if you ever gotten a call on your cell phone polling you that's because somebody told your f****** number
You can easily
All that information
It's super easy to find proof of an essay CIA database
Is is cockamamie
It's ludicrous
It could have just been
AT&T
Yeah absolutely and I mean if you really want to go
Get down to the wood like the bottom of it
Is that people are selling information
But that's
Anyway
It's not illegal to sell out
So here we go here we go Alex is
Again reinforcing his own
Sort of narrative
But doing it in
Incredibly
I've got to get this is
He says
In terms of
We have the proof
Headlines headlines
Is all day long with Ant-Man edited until right before
He says that you say these that don't say we have all the proof and then he says we have all the headlines
To say we have all the headlines
Perfect you look like a
To the actual zullo interview
That unfortunately as tells the story
You start to get the pictures that he actually doesn't
Lititz
It's really unfortunate
The title that I gave this
They don't know what to do with the information
We really don't know what is going on
We know that we made
Every endeavor
To bring
Mister Montgomery
Disinformation
Federal authorities
Like I said earlier
We contacted Larry klayman for his assistance
And under the direction of Sheriff Arpaio we brought
Mister Montgomery 2
Judge Royce Lamberth we used to be the head of the fisa Courts
And when we got in there
The Dilemma
Involved
Mister
During his tenure as a contractor
Where do I live
In Michigan
Illegally
Executed a search warrant on his phone
And I was all there. In the trial I can find no evidence.
FBI
That poster problem for us
Because the only other place we could have gone to at that time would have been the Department of Justice and I believe at that time it was still at work
That was a problem
So here's why it's a problem for them
Because
Not
No
All of this 600000000 document
Is confidential information
So they can just go to a lawyer
He stole all this allegedly
From the NFL
It is it is a problem
To take it to the Department of Justice wood holder is
Willing to process
But also
This guy
Mike zullo
This guy who keeps coming up Larry klayman
The two of them
Can't know anything about what's on those
And if they do they've committed a crime
Admit that they know anything on it
Their Evonne are
Committed
Is a pickle
That's really tough
Have to believe that they're lying
They haven't looked at any
All know
I think all they're going on
Is what
Acumen
They are telling Alex
What Dennis Montgomery has told them they say
Sarah playing a big game a telephone here
That's the Alex had on the other day
Like third hand knowledge
That where Michelle Obama says the word honky
Really wish that were true
Sirhan
Hoverboard
Third hand
And arrow
That's
Problems
Cuz they can't make an
All they can do is speculate about what possibly is in this
Nation based on what
Dennis Montgomery is told
Everything Alex Jones
Loves to do
We've already established his investigation to try and help
Joe Arpaio I was called
Joke by Joe Arpaio
So
That's one p
Can't wait to
Let's go
I tried doing it now we need we need to let it bills
So at this point
Zullo is going to
Explain what happened
They took the
Information to the FBI I'll let him spell it out
Larry klayman was successful
To talk to the FBI
Which he did
To clarify
With Larry
Is
Mister Montgomery Broughton
A sampling of some documentation
Gave him what is known as production immunity
Again
This is based on Montgomery
They wouldn't have done that though if he is
Sonos document 600 million documents
Be in the country
Like
Goodbye
These documents
They let him leave and then he just has been living his life
There's Montgomery at this point in 2017
Is like 65 years old
He's not some sprightly
Edward Snowden
DC Young and like
It's a fun whistleblower image
Citizen 64
No not at all
You get in your head this idea cuz Snowden keeps coming up that he's like some
Able Body
Yeah
YouTube
Usually art of seven-year-old dude that he actually
Steve
I mean we can talk all the s*** we want but I do believe this guy actually does have some hash
Capability
But that's only because
Occam's razor tells me he
In order to fraud
We create the document
That have been sent to
Infowars
Alright I'll stall that out a little bit later as we go along
He's knows enough to forge
Bulshit
Gotcha
Let's talk a little bit more about the FBI
And he brought in I believe it was like 600 million Wrecker
What
He provided them that information some time goes by
And they called him back and they get alligator in testimonial immunity
Information
Not necessarily
Again it comes back to you like a lot of that stuff is
Fairly easy
Need to find
Google
Some of it could be Google.
Freaking Google
No not bad at all
I know a lot of people who are in there
No you can't bring
You can't be
Classified documents only Google
At this point to another
Fart sounds
Like it might have some Blake
The most boring person to listen
Jerome corsi still around
Good point
So he's going to get into this and it sounds scary but don't worry about it
I'll be right back on the other side of a 620
Personal information on 151
Identify
That were alleged to be theirs
Because those bank accounts it is suspected
That they are actually fraudulent transactions
Had
Accounts
Speculative real estate gas and oil
Stock plays
Coronavirus doesn't
And
Derivative
Things
What is he
Those are
Sugar
Futures
I don't know
Actually really unfortunate
Specifics because I can trace back exactly what they're talkin
Fabulous
Find a little bit of an article from the news of Association in Phoenix that was covering the tree
Montgomery was investigating snow
Who was the lawyer
Who is
The judge
Joe Arpaio racial discrimination
Okay
That Montgomery
Was being a
To investigate
The judge
Which would be very illegal
Really illegal
That
Who is actively opponent
People who speak out against billions of dollars of lawsuits
To be filed
Because of his dictator is behaviors
Any movie from the south
Northern California are 80 movies
Arpaio insisted
Encourage Montgomery to investigate the judge
Instead
Arpaio insisted the informant was investigating bank fraud
And the judge was one of 150,000 alleged Maricopa
What county
Now that 150 is important
Because that's
From the number
That this guy just reference
As the nsac I-80
Allegedly included Donald Trump
And Alex Jones
Do they live in Maricopa County
Possibility
That that
They're Reapers the repurposing bulshit information
Bulshit inform
Right
Wow that's
Well
We should recite
I think that's a
Very important
Climate change
Exactly
So Arpaio
Hattiesburg
Arpaio in Montgomery had this bank fraud thing
That was cover
For him investigator
This judge
There was trying to
Racial profiling
What is not actually invested in
Striking him down
You scaring the
The prosecutors are more the issue
But he's
What have you
Kids with that that fits with the kind of paranoid personality that we're dealing with
Because he doesn't believe that
It is never
He always believed this one guy
All of the Power
Cuz he's a guy with all of this.
Lutera
Dictator who can't understand that
He can understand that laws are real
Order that the Sheriff's Office
Turn over documents relating to Montgomery Montgomery's investigation
These documents include timelines and flowcharts to allege conversations inclusion
Between judge snow the doj
Burlington
Which represents the plane
MK
Christmas on Friday plaintiff's lawyer question about Montgomery
Montgomery was looking into judge snow and would personally interested in that Pro
Both
Earrings
They didn't ask Montgomery to make those.
Sheridan testified earlier in the hearing
Then he told the detective and Sergeant working with Montgomery not to pursue the investigation
The judge
Article goes on to explain
That I want to find
It's f****** hilarious
Young who was employed by Covington in Burlington
This lawyer young who's employed by Covington Burlington showed Arpaio
I had received a fax
Text from Montgomery
In November 2013
With an early version of a timeline showing event
In the Department of Justice
This is racial profiling case
And the racial profiling case and judge Snow's Court
As well as information about alleged wiretap
On the back of the facts
Arpaio use the typewriter to make some
Traveling through time right now
Handwritten notes about possible connections and hand wrote on the same f***
Do you have wrote about
About possible connections between George snow in the law firm Covington & Burling
Piazza Berlin
If you drew his hand at church
These notes mentioned that former Arizona Senator John
Worked with the law firm Covington & Burling
There's no mention there's also mention
Judge Snow's wife works there as well which is not
True the notes read
Snow's snow confirmed by US Senate
Keilon Judiciary Committee on June 26th 2008
Obama takes office January 2009
Judge born 1959
It's all crazy nonsense
Handwritten
Scroll virology
Transportation manager
Making a
Together
All of it is
Desperately grasping at straws and clearly Montgomery was not working on a bank fraud case
He was cover
That he used
Note also noted quotes
Wilcox's husband
Envy 150000
That's the people that were allegedly being bit
Being targeted as well as the number of Jehovah's
Make it into heaven
Wilcox refer to for Maricopa County Supervisor Mary Rose
Text husband Earl
Arpaio said it was a reference to him
Can we just talk about how the whitest names in a row you just
Earl and Mary Rose Wilcox
Arpaio said it was a reference to him being among the 150,000 victims of bank fraud
That note quote
Totally floored Earl Wilcox
Who is in the courtroom in his own name in the documents
Automata in the gallery
The wilcox's are vocal opponent
The Sheriff's Office had to Rose Wilcox
If you want a civil suit against the county
For the baseless charge
So you get a sense of what's going on here
Arpeggio is
Acting illegally all the time
Super all the time all the time
And
Montgomery
Was
Confidential informant
In quotes
Who is actually doing
Pretty illegal investigations on his back
That's the flavor we've got right now
Promise you
This is going to develop
It's going to be a rose pet
Blossom
I would prefer
A Bloomin Onion
From TGI
If you want to do a roast battle that's fine
Okay at this point the alleged
151,000 people
Include Donald Trump Alex Jones
Alex Jones is old office
And what have you
His private office
This number is old cell phone number
His mom's birthday
His sons
Mitzvah
His great-grandmother's
She's a slave I don't know
What's being alleged now
Was used
Years ago in this court case
As
Information
Of all people live in Maricopa County
Zorbing
Victims of bank fraud in order to cover for an investigation
Intuit federal judge
So that's what's going on
Alex
It's possible he doesn't know that
All of those words you just said are more words than Alex Jones can understand
Right but you should have boiled baby Alex Jones
Understand headline
Alrighty
You built
Gathered evidence
It's for that research pretty ugly
You put a lot of work
Bedtime
An effort into
All of that points to only one possible conclusion
That you can then if tablets
Is reality even further
Where do you think
And that why
Alex Jones Woodstock
He wouldn't eat just part where you said
Sears
You know where he would stop
As soon as any like indication that he's not totally right
So here's the next it's Mike zullo a game getting into how they don't actually know
Right now on the
Inside of Alex Bean
Because he's in it
I think
That it's possible
I think that is pretty strong and
Here's the problem
Later,
He's going to do is
He talks to him and stuff like that
I believe that there is a vested interest in Alex
I don't know if you
If you
He's super willing to be
Alex Jones is always super willing to be
That's true
Truly horrific
Nightmarish
Pile of garbage human being
In the same way that he want
How to suck up to the f******
Alleged
See Jesse James
We got a lot of ground to cover so I'm going to skip the
This next clip because it's about it earlier
It's basically just
Azula repeating
In different languages
Don't really actually know what's going on
They don't know what the documents say
80-in
Next clip explaining
Some of Dennis Montgomery's pedigree and where you come from
Evidence of by argument
That he is able to
Discover
People private information
Through Tech
Employee on his own
As opposed to Batman who just
Hangs out in the butt
Well I I don't want to go into too much of what he said
Actually mr. Montgomery in this is public
Pfister Montgomery was a contractor who developed the
Hacking software
That could penetrate
Firewalls
A computer's breach them
Take over as the administrator and remain undetected for about an hour and a half
And download whatever they are
What's the time frame
Play movie exact location
We can mask up for an hour and a half build something that only lasts for an hour and a half
At 4 because it's a lie
I think it might be alive
But I do believe that he has some hacker
Done some research
And figured out exactly
What
Dennis Montgomery was doing when he died
The subtitle of this episode is
So I told you about Dennis Montgomery
1998 founded a company called etrepid technology
Thank you we're going to burn him
Like I said it started out as a casino tool
Eventually I started targeting Sino industry they started branch
The government
That's right around then
Dennis claimed develops software that would analyze barcodes that appeared on Al Jazeera
Any used these Dakota
Information
To predict impending terrorist
This is what he developed
He's a
Student
The Kabbalah is that what you're saying
He's just
So he's out there
Planning
The terrorist attacks through the barcodes
To predict
A terrorist
I kind of make sense
On a horse
At that point
The gentleman named Tom Ridge
Was Homeland
Security direct
And that it was legit
The information gleaned from the software to raise the terror alert multiple times
He went so far as to evacuate public buildings
A call for flights to be grounded
Based on interpretation
Of barcodes on Al Jazeera through Dennis Montgomery soft
It is
Very real living
It's so real
Like you know
Is it in the Kabbalah where it's like they put certain letters of each
Weird stuff
The end of the world
It's exactly the same sort of logic
Because I don't want to ruin where this going to go
I don't want to ruin
The entire end of the story yet
But a CIA agent who was involved
I'm like the implementation of the technology and it being brought in
Quoted later
The meeting where they burned
Information is being this is so embarrassing
Kia
Hold on
I'll just spell out the rest
Activist story now because why not
There's no way they could have killed JF
People bite
Stupid
Such incompetence considered
Immoral
You want to arrive at in someone gives you like
Confirmation possible version of of your conclusion
So
This guy
His software used
To make Terror predict
Is it
What is it what is it even look like
This is 2003 levels
Alright don't put them in and this is back when you had to use
No
Rudimentary flash drive
We're using or you let's call it Windows 2000
You've noticed
Windows
Well whatever
It's Montgomery let's call it Windows 95
I don't know if it's like
MLB The Show
So are using
Base window
Our first GUI
And
This guy
Put in a CD
That analyzes barcodes on Al Jazeera
Rightfully so that means he's
What
You got screenshots
Takes in 5 minutes
To download each picture of Al Jazeera
Can you pull up a command prompt and it looks at it like
Does one of those like
Best software had to bend
Same level of Technology
Where in the World is Carmen
Without rockapella
That is there's no possible way that was even
Real software random number generator
Here's what happened
Alright a little bit
And they realized I was just making
King s*** up
Yep and I know that
Not only
These barcodes on Al Jazeera
He just made even that part off about it
So the FBI didn't is a conman of ridiculous
Csbi did a counter invest
Navigation to Dennis Montgomery history of fraud
He had
Gambling problem with VTEC
I CIA agent like I said was quoted as saying that the whole thing was quote
His former lawyer
Representative
Actually his name is Michael Jace
Which is weird cuz that's my son's name
It's not the same guy as far as I can tell
That's also Michael j.fox
What's up I think we can rule out Michael j.fox was basically the
The character in The Secret of My Success
A lawyer described as Montgomery is a con artist
And quote a habitual liar engaged in fraud
Defended
So that's the guy
That's the guy about it somehow
Like
Can I just get like catch me if you can
Memories in my head
What is there a movie
There are too many movies where our secret service in our CIA is in our intelligence
Community it comp
When there are so many more stories were there
Right right
CIA
Stupid that deserves our public interest
We like to create
Feeling safe feeling a lot better
Jordan
51 really great
Yes you do
Sew-in 2006's governor
I accused
He claimed his own business
Casino chips
And $100,000 in cash in exchange for favors
Said that
Committed
Valentines
That was his like
I committed a crime
You're corrupted
It's not great for immunity beforehand or did you clear
So he claimed he claimed they gave him all of this money in exchange for favors
Rite Aid Montgomery claimed that he had emails from Gibbons
Private email
That he was he was not lying
Gibbons said that the emails were fake
In court
Computer expert testified
That he must challenge the authenticity of the emails
The court case was thrown out
An 18-month FBI investigation concluded
They cleared him of all charges
18 months
A US
Ethics Committee investigate
The charges as well
And found no wrongdoing
Now why is this case super important
It shows has a liar an idiot
And willing to
Falsify documents
Super well there is an indication
That was
Borne out in court
He has
Fraudulently created
And so now we're citing his documents
Who's going to be a hoax
Give history
Has been shown
Create.
You know you committed crimes you if you accuse that dude
Committing a crime
Also
Oh yeah
Happens
Montgomery's off the hook for bribery
Cuz he didn't do it
Or making false statements
Actually a trial he would have had to
To testify that
And testified that then that would be
He would have perjured himself under oath
Maybe he trial
These claims
Initiated and that he never said anything on turo
If you have committed a crime
Yeah so this is the guy who's the root of these
Fake
Database that I was Jones exciting as evidence
Himself
Entropic being
Spider-Man
Clear at this point
But that is not
True
Absolutely not
Have Kik
Morass
On that story than anyone has ever kick
I promise you it's not.
That's nothing expose that you just did no one will really ever hit the news
Do you know what the reason they're complaining about how the FBI is making no moves on this stuff
And there's a media blackout
But that is why the media blackout
Look at what was the
Yeah YouTube
You just kicked it
You just kicked your ass you kept all the answer the story
Again it's not done
We still have to get to Larry klayman
Seriously
This is amazing this next
So we're still in Missoula interview
And Jerome corsi who is been silently apart of this the whole time
But then
To try and vouch
For the situation that's going on
And I want to play this clip just
Little another side argument I want to make right after
Bikes
We would work on this for days
Couple of weeks
Is used car dealer
Speaks the truth it's carefully
Put together
Here's why play that clip
He's desperately trying to provide credibility for Mike zullo
REI
But
He doesn't realize that if you look at the history of Jerome corsi
That's a liar vouching
Sing for your credibility
Would you actually
Jerome corsi
Laid out a book
About Obama's birth certificate
He was also a member of the Swift
Swift boat lettering
Boating
Yeah
He is that so when he comes in and
This guy is honest as the day is long
To me that means
Oh we just both have the same propaganda goal
That's all he's saying
Anyway I'm looking and being like dude I love this guy's lies
We have one more again
Spelling out
Very clearly
And very overtly
But he doesn't know anything
There's no information that he has
He even let slip that he can't even confirm that anybody was ever wiretap
Which is kind of unfortunate for the outrageous claims
Plus I'm Sheriff Arpaio
Account is
The timeline and I'm going by memory
Understanding is
This alleged wiretap
Orange seeds
Tell us more about what occurred under 8
Withdraw
And at the same time
Individuals that were
The Clearblue a civil proceeding ensued
Hey this is talking about Covington & Burling
Again this is
Earlier
But
Let's be clear
Alex is trying to say that like you don't have DNA testing can't prove it
The duck the expression is if it walks like a duck
And talks like a duck
Going the other direction with a duck metaphor
Starting in the middle of forest family
Hold on one second we're going to need a blood
Hey son f******
Improve it
Prove that's a duck you son-of-a-b****
F***
You and also it shows that Alex Jones has a higher standard of proof about like what is a duck
Anything else we talked about on his show of evidence
Is is is glaring
So we're going to leave Mike zullo now that is been
His timing
As it works
I don't necessarily have a ton against Mike zullo except I found
Evidence
In an article
He's part of the
That's enough from the Phoenix New Times I did find an article about the case
Against Arpaio
And it's interesting that Mike Zoo
I was called to testify
Invoked
The Fifth Amendment
What a shocker
He pleaded self-incrimination in court
Which means
I mean you're not always guilty when you plead the Fifth
But in this case it does seem to imply
If he wants to go out there publicly and talk about how there's a railroad in case being done
It seems if you're in if you're in court you'd want to provide the evidence than Ingo
The kind of means that you're
Afraid of what might come out
Anyone who is under any kind of Trials do not say a goddamn word
I agree with that
Whether or not
Do not say a goddamn thing
Let It Go
Until you
Sodus Point
We transition
Stationary go to how Alex end
This gentleman who's come up a couple times
Larry klayman on the Friday
Episode of the shop
Meanwhile throughout the week he was yelling about this evidence
Everything
I'm saying is correct
This whole time
Hazme bababababababa
So that is why reclaiming his guests here is the introduction of how he brings him
Into the
Show
Larry
The clay man
Exposing 4 is fine going on against the president against Congress has been in the news for years
The CIA
Here in just a moment Larry klayman legendary Larry klayman
He never was the verdict
We can't prove without a little bird
This is extra Market
When were
Devin Nunes
No he didn't
He got it for Larry klayman
Larry klayman
That's what Alex just said
And in this interview
Larry klayman
Cypress mulch
Larry klayman would have talked to him
At all
The only word
Speculation
Episode
Because the history does bear out there is
Look I can't
I can't prove it
These Liars are always lying but
Larry klayman telling of it he had been trying to get this information
The devyn Nunez for quite a while
And succeeded
So
All feels like anime
I wrote it on the back of that
Paper airplane the directions
I have been doing everything I can to get this
Information to Nunez
Again that's Montgomery not
Clayman
But
Establish those are the only Farms
The communication that Alex Jones
Is okra
One thing that's important to lay out here is that Larry klayman
Montgomery's lawyer now
The former lawyer called him
Habitually engaged in fraud
Yes now
Larry klayman is his lawyer
The two of them met
Through Joe Arpaio
When Joe Arpaio was being represented by Larry klayman
Dennis Montgomery was the confidential informant
We're having a wonderful romantic comedy
We take a break from all of this information
Reduction
Alex Jones realizes that you got to pay the bill
The only victory
First off where was first reported by the products
First off you're crazy we have the best
Organic fluoride free with soil silver and
Surgeon
Matt manufacturer the biggest manufacturer in the country
Tell you who's our private labeling but this is iodine
False or attitude
I think you might have just breached his contract
That's not that's not fair
To Tom's of Maine the contract says you can't say who made it
Whoops whoops
I've not review their contracts
Certainly don't know why
Alex Jones
The full-on vial of Larry klayman
I'll be back
Bayou
It would take too long
Everybody knows who Larry klayman is
No one knows who Larry klayman is
And he doesn't go over his bio so I will
Would you like to know
Would you like to know some fun facts about Larry klayman
Owen Clements behavior in the 1992 trial in California Federal Court
William Lehman from his courtroom for life
Hold on hold on
Hold up
Five years later in a separate case in New York
District
To issue a lifetime ban on the attorney practicing law before
Well Danny Chen sounds like
Have barred him from practicing law in front of them
4life
Claimant has written about his dealings with do that
If you're a judge
It's essential
It's essentially an extreme version of holding someone in contempt
Absolutely
Do you at least get
To say he's out of order
Claiming his feelings of Keller in
Claiming that color
And was quote obviously drunk
I don't believe you
The best way in 2017
Received from a woman facing criminal charges
And she accused him of not providing legal services in return
The Florida Bar Association
The matter
Small portion
He was reprimanded by the Association
It it was just like hey
Dude
He's filed at least you don't have to pay
He has filed at least 18 lawsuits against the accusations of racketeering
Two bunch of s*** about Benghazi
In the wake of the 2016 shooting of Dallas police officer
Claimant filed a lawsuit against
Former US Attorney General Eric Holder the Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan
Matter movement
Alleged
That led to the shooting
Play Man amended the complaint to
Include Dallas police officer
And Hillary Clinton and George Soros as defense enough I mean this is super weird but I'm reading off
Your screen
Former San Antonio Spurs star Tim Duncan
I don't know how he got in there but he is part of the
Autograph
That case
It was just
A poet was
And all of them
What nobody could stop you a lot to get disbarred
What even is being a lawyer if you can just
Is anybody paying a also James Carville Cajun
Call Tim like a jackass
In 1998
Swimming suits mother for $50,000
Reimbursement for medical care provided to his maternal grandmother
After claiming brother told Newsweek magazine
Clayman
The Clinton White House was responsible for the magazine
Nope it was your brother
That's a stretch
Got to stretch
It was on
So he's just a
Into October 2014
Claiming it secretly allow the Ebola virus to enter the
American-Asian race and Jewish Christian religion
Any other possible
He was involved in that
Love those lies
15 claimant filed a defamation suit on behalf of Dennis Montgomery.
I think he's media hora
Yeah well yeah
Lawyer I know but like what did he do he's probably a sleazy lawyer I don't know who.
Listen
Probably I wouldn't be surprised if he's Better Call Saul type of guy
DuckTales a little bit with
Defamation lawsuit
The author of the book
Call pay any price
Green power in the endless war
The lawsuit alleged describe Montgomery is quote
The Maestro behind what
Former US officials
Believe was the most
The Labyrinth
Susan American
This is that software we discussed earlier
To be able to predict
Salad bowls
How do you get too good of a con man
Man that you can just make that s*** up
It couldn't have even looked like
Like that's the thing about computer I don't think I don't think you would understand.
Road effect erodic software thing but because
People don't have that computer savvy they're willing to be
Like you're just like
This is why we can't have old people in power anymore they don't even like
Can't do it
They don't even live in the world we live in
The DNC hacking was not
Some sort of cop
Implicated movie Hack
Quick tan
Like that's all it was
Like there's no real hack
Can going on like what
People think it is
Sophisticated
That's really
But again
All of this stuff
We have a
Power armor
Let me get through I Larry claimants bio
There's more
Well you know what Alex was right in saying
That he did not have time
We do
Clayman
On behalf of
In 2016 a federal court
That lawsuit
I was appealed as I as I understand
Appeal
I believe in Marine Le Pen
Prime ministerial candidate
You can
And we'll call her effects
That's a great lawsuit there's two sides of it is
She is
Legally a fascist
Yes but then the other side
Just findings was that
You can't
Considerate definition when you're in
A political
Sphere
Just describing someone
Political beliefs
Isn't defamation
If there is
Credibility
Larry klayman filed at least three lawsuits
Claiming that Obama was not eligible to be president cuz his birth certificate was fake
Okay
He tried to defend
As we all know Cliven Bundy is a crazy person as is
The judge ruled
Clayman
Headband dishonest history of discipline
And he had no clearance or standing
Go to assign himself as someone else's lawyer
The one that mean
Cliven Bundy
Did not want his help at all.
M2
I would actually go the opposite direction where the judges like
Jesus man you said you were
More than you
I'm a victim
2013 claim and declared it a conservative rally in Washington DC that quote
This President is not a president of We the People he's a president
Whoops
That's probably rare lyrics
Barry race
He urged the crowd to begin a quote
American nonviolent Revolution and demanded the President Obama quote
Put the Quorum down
And figuratively come out with his hands up
Weeks Later
Put the volume down
Weeks Later claim and sponsored reclaim America rally
In Lafayette Square across from the White House
I was calling for the president's removal
Claimant stated that if Obama did the first American
Nonviolent
I can't think of one of the violent revolution
Obama did not resign conservative
Whoops
Considering that now all they talk about is how there's a shadow government
Anyway
Millions to occupy Washington DC
Hollywood between 130 and 200
Also
They're going to talk about this
Princeton a little bit
He won a court case
About
And varied and
Klayman vs. Obama
Where
He was trying to
Contestant
Collection
A phone and internet metadata
Good
That's a good one
We can agree
Like a lot of that stuff is
Pretty
11 delete
It's pretty f*****
A lot of police state
In front of a judge
Did not laugh
Here come the judge
Did the judge
If you're a jerk
And you Google this
Chicken guy wouldn't
You just be like no Get It Go
Go go
The judge would
Play Brew
I'm out of the courtroom
The Apollo
2013 and US Federal
Richard J Leon
He ruled that book collection of America
Telephone metadata
Constitution
He had insanely
Legitimate
Concern
About
Call
This program could violate people's Fourth Amendment rights
Unreasonable search and seizure
Stop
And then actually comes
The ruling
Cuz it wasn't
Before
But
He ruled in favor
Of
Clayman
Whose last name is strange
Alright
The original trial was held
And the judge agreed with the argument
That metadata collection
The 4th amendment
Was to say Isis
Spend my judgment
For six months
To allow
The government to appeal
That you be made
That any
Metadata collection
Regarding strange or claiming
I have to stop
Every
Bit of information that had been
Had to be destroyed
He stayed his ruling for 6 months
Allowing for appeal
During that
6 month
They can still collect their medal
No
Yeah yeah
Change for the next 6 months
If the government doesn't respond then the ruling stands
Respond
Basically
The appeals court found that
Because the program had been ended they didn't have a responsibility to rule on the
Legality
Of the Fourth Amendment claim
Secondarily they found
That
There's no
They could be provided
They claiming or strain
Actually were spied on it
Or hands or meditate
And therefore they have no standing in Port
To bring the
Even
Do the government
Collect bulk metadata
Premeditated
Was collected
They're kicked out
And they can't represent
The entirety of
Part of their argument was the bear Verizon customers
They collected Verizon
Metadata
The thing is
I told on the government admitted that they collected
Business
Through Verizon
Like Verizon business
Individual
You and I
Cell phone owners
They collected things through
A different
Part of Verizon
This is
I don't like that I don't
But I do think
That based on the law
Based on
I'm telling you
I read
These Court decision
Yeah I know cuz you're a lunatic
And I don't think that they
The decisions were rocks
I think the appeals court was right
He didn't have the standing
But at the same time
The conclusion is correct
The metadata collection isn't on
Reasonable search
So he was right and they probably stopped
Wink wink
In a lot of ways
I just don't want all the information we can find it has stopped
Based on
What were afraid is actually the truth
Larry klayman is right on that count
He's wrong about everything else
Yep his claims that he beat the NSA in a court case is wrong
He had a case where they agreed with him or they were inclined to agree with him
Suspended judgment
Anyway
Let's get into it
I'm spent most work
I think any human being has ever done
Here's where this next flip is where
Larry klayman
This clip
Larry klayman tries to do a little bit of a dance or he has to be sure that he has
The information
Beyond Sunday
V up
Mother fobs other work Weathers
Publishing things have been out there in federal court
Showing the Trump was being surveilled
CIA whistleblower based on income for
Montgomery system for a long time
Shepherd
I apologize that was trying not to implicate himself
So
Yeah
Larry breaking down
He sees as Montgomery's
Whatever just let's get into the meeting Botanas
Unclassified Chaser involve dinner
That really is a Rosetta Stone
A while
Bulshit
And also
Also on this episode
Some guy
Who's nickname is Esperanto
I don't like any of those words you just survived the Benghazi attack
Content
Esperanto is the hero of Benghazi
And is fairly reasonable but also pretty aggressive
And at the end of the interview you said like
If people are afraid arrest
George Soros
And they're afraid
I'll do it
I'll go and I'll do it
So Alex later uses that
As like
George Soros
That's not quite what he said we should arrest him
Marine
You know that's what he's like he thinks we should be arrested
You ready to go do it himself
They just being held back a real Marine
Do we know that
He's a real dude
Oh he's a real dude I can't remember right now he's going on Alex Jones
I can't remember his first name
Seems like a pretty decent dude
But they also he has probably been kicked out of only one quart
Never allowed to be there
He's had William Richard
Larry klayman on
We had a lot of gas
Recently
He has to man
He's scrambling
You scrambling also you can come here he's losing it a little bit
I don't know maybe next week I will be different you know this this week
You started with the at the end of the week
Recovering right now you're listening
I already did his big
Pizzagate apology could reinvigorate him a little bit
We'll see
CIA contractor
And
Over 600 million pages of information
Again went the only evidence we
We can find of him being
A contractor at all is
Creating that software that analyzes Al Jazeera
Questionable weather in that capacity he would have access at all
47 hard drives or 600 million
Document If he if he
Did they have all those things
Crazy and he must have been going way outside of his way in order to
I mean is massively illegal
It's all good
Is Larry klayman coming in
Much like Mike zullo
And
Really trying hard to make sure that people don't think that
Chicken committed a crime
And what he told me was on there
Was that there was
President Trump when he was a businessman
Oprah
The only time that he could have
Possibly had access to NFL
Is around. Of 2003
Discredited
Prejudice the FBI's investigation on him and found to be a fraud
There's no way he would ever be able to get any sort of clearance after
I'm listening
That al-jazeera
Did work
Trojan Horse
Enterprise
Consider this
Right
Like
I'm listening
Are the
Which is the acronym Avengers
From the very beginning
Like from the very beginning
Because the al-jazeera soft
Montgomery
Pinpoint
Every level of government
He is at
Chile
The guy who
See the Occam's razor
I don't like
Ubly have information
Stolen
The early 2010
He's working with Joe Arpaio
And he has this database of Maricopa County
Victims of bank fraud
Which is now being repurposed
As people who are being spied on including
Alex Jones all this s***
600 million sound so f****** made up
Where do you get 600 million.
Like genuinely
What
What area of the government other than maybe that bulk
Metadata collection
System
Close to 6
100 million
And even if it was about meditate
Point-by-point
GPS
Location of that kind of
So where would you
600 million.
And it would be like I said from
14 years ago
Is it is there even that much information in the f****** Library of Congress
In The Archives of all the stuff
I'm made of
1 kajillion
Jillian
Important point is that Larry klayman is coming out as a lawyer
Being on Alex Jones
Discuss this
Wyoming
But he only has secondary knowledge
He has no idea was actually in these documents
It is illegal for him to know it.
Exactly
Rodger Stone
Repeat that
Yeah
If these same games that are so it's propaganda
Even though
Right
You got six
100 million documents
You're not going to take a look
Come on man
I don't know
To make sure that it's real
Be so scared
You don't I probably run away that's why you don't buy my drugs
Scream and run the other direction
As everybody knows
You take your Coke
Pinky
You put it into the
You make sure that
The kokusai quote
So
Confirming
But he didn't
Discuss
With Devin Nunes
Come forward with information
And that's what we've done and we've
Has has
Coming forward and then some
So either all of this is just
Fantasy world live there's a possibility
And that's where he shot and that's very confusing.
Nunez is acting up
The house
Intelligence committee chairman
Destroyed and if he is acting impact on this information that has its roots in
Someone who has a complete
Call man
Nunez himself
Came on again it said the document showed no indication of wiretap on Trump Tower
I think all of this I think it's as like a zigzag of
I'm shook
Because there was that thing that came out the other day
About
Flynn
The inner of the meetings that he had with the Turkish ambassador
About
Extraditing
This goolingoo
Aw
5 to be extradited
Erdewan believes that this cleric
Was responsible for the fake
I'm pretty sure
Totally
So he wants this guy extradited and United
Does not believe the appropriate
Flynn was being paid
To help expedite the
Dick came out
The meeting
Between flame and
And the Turkish Ambassador was also attended by Devin Nunez
He was also there
Really yeah
So now we sit with the information might be.
Because now
Maybe
Flint
Yeah at this point on Sunday when we recording this it's still not sure
There's indications in
Sources
Anonymous sources are indicating that he might have cut it
A grain of salt
But maybe this is
The possibility
It's possible it's not proven it's not definite
The only part
It's hard to swallow about him
If you look at all of this s***
Everybody would go down
Yeah
The entire
Get taken down
From
The bottom not everyone
Empower
Big a deal as we think
The truth is probably somewhere in between
But the reality is that like
All that stuff
It isn't
We can't prove
We can prove that Nunez was in that meeting with flame at a Turkish Ambassador attacked doesn't look good
Newness is in the
Convulsed
And newness has given Handy's
With a little bit of prostate
Disappearing the night
Before he went to the White House
Meeting with somebody
Like there's a lot of stuff
Real f*****-up
Yeah so
Government should be shut down
My thought nobody should be allowed to do anything
My thought is that I don't think he was meeting with Larry klayman that night
But some of that stuff does relate to this
I probably actually meeting
With Larry Flynt
It's possible
He's one of those guys who I don't care if he's alive today so I have no idea
He's done good work
The Great
Is essentially that a lot of his stuff
Nunez's Behavior
Walnut
Singularly
Motivated
Montgomery information
Pretty clearly I think on this episode
Bulshit
Or the title take
I think part of
His behavior was
What's pi
Clayman
And Montgomery
Also the conspiracy theory Community is
The flame does a lot of
Like on the Block
Why are people investigating not Montgomery
I just did
Suck it even more
Kind of even more interesting
Is that
The Conspiracy Theory blog
And yet at the same time
It's hard not to look at
Get reality and go
Kind of conspiracy is happy
Opening
Confluence
Idiots
Happening
The same time
Weird coincidence
Almost as likely as anything else
I think he
Justice like like
Like with the Montgomery
Those idiots believe that s***
Like it's just as likely
See what's going on right now is that everyone
The f****** conspiracy
Football
Russia
Bring up for a while and I'll just
Deal with
Go to slightly
Alex Jones
Is b*******
I don't want
Paint with a broad brush all people who believe in
Conspiracy theories
It has the same
People who are very smart
The idea that we would be
Entire conspiracy communities
By attacking our
Is unfair
Make that assumption if we're not clear
There's a lot of people who also believe Alex Jones full of s*** but believe in conspiracies
There goes there are
Chemtrails got a cam
Sure there are not stupid crazy people in that world
Unfortunately there is a lot of stupid
Crazy people in that world
Yes absolutely
So this next
Is Larry klayman explaining why this is a matter of
Immediate importance
Do something that has to be dealt with Now or Never
Exactly like how we need to
I will file three court cases about
It's bigger than yours
His life is
Come forward
Could just die from a brain aneurysm
I'm dead
Any moment he needs to be interviewed
Now it's just trying to create a sense of immediacy about it
It's also trying
Create sort of a tragic
Sekiro story around this obvious liar
What possible reason
I'd like to interview
That's a good point, Robbins podcast
I meant be here cuz I got a lot of questions
Perfect
First date
Bistro or movie
Bistro
You don't have it I legitimately think I flashback to
French classes
I think my brain just like snack before midnight
I love that movie
Anyway Richard linklater
Slip into talking a little bit more about Montgomery himself and brings
Bijo Arpaio situation
You on Montgomery and
People
We have
It's so easy
Successfully
It's so easy to destroy his credibility
All it took was like
Couple Google searches
Again Google
And just
Couple like just read a couple artic
Like it's not that hard you find this guy is
Is a massive
Snake oil field
And if you wasn't
Being used for
Propaganda purposes I agree with you
He would be fun
It would be fun it would be like
Is he going to make it there's a there's a there's always a part of me that's going to be on the side of the guy trying to f*** with
With the FBI I think that there also is a narc
Could type of that like
Down-and-out two-time loser gambling loser
Kind of guy who just like last for
Whereas our culture we're all in Grain to pull for that
Like we all want to see the little guy
Strike out against
The system
And it's unfortunate
That this little guy striking out against the system
Is being used propagandistic Lee
To support the cyst
Yeah yeah
It's like we all Robin Hood and they all wind up being.
Robin Hood Robin Hood is working
Before the sheriff
Turns out
Yeah that's it that's all
Murderous monster
You know what we got to get back to
Sheriff's being
The most
That f****** nonsense the sheriff's movement all that stuff for another day
The hacker
Who wrote the book
About that involved
Larry klayman as lawyer for Dennis Montgomery
Sue this writer
Was unsuccessful
The case was thrown out of court
Of course so now you coming
You failed
Somebody's going to do tonight
Obama's immigration
That didn't happen
Which is why we're proceeding on a separate
Sympathize with Surfer file
He's a great man
But I was just talked to him he's staying out of this
Getting out of this is a great bed
I automatically wish
You lose
You do not belong in this world you want hundred percent
Or you're not at least you're not in touch with your own Humanity
Alex
I'll talk to her
Our personal reason Arpaio said
Montgomery's investigation was
Junk
That's a good reason to stay out of it
So now I want to bring this back
Phoenix news article that I was talking about earlier
Right
Play this out
Again Robert Young
Is the lawyer
That's trying case
According to reports
Court in 2014 to outside experts
Experience of the nsa's evaluated Montgomery
For the Sheriff's Office
And concluded that Montgomery was quote
A complete and total fraud
Young brought this up in court to Arpaio
At least by November 2014
You knew Dennis Montgomery was a fraud
That's a question
It was
Putting it lightly
Arpaio said
That was putting it lightly Arpaio said noted they have been working they been working Montgomery
So we decided to stop paying
Young went on to present email records showing members of arpaio's team we're still in touch with Montgomery 4 months after
For that into 2015
What a law enforcement officer have to be incredibly stupid to continue working with someone known to be a
Complete and total fraud
Young ass
Our attorney John Masterson
How can you say that
Okay technically that is
I'm going to go with yes the answer is yes as humans is a fair question
Probably
Younger
Reminded Arpaio April weather
And never brought up
The timeline
Begin where the faxes
With the weird type writing on the back
Or other documents Montgomery had made
That included judge snow
Quote I never thought you asked me the question Arpaio said
Do you regret not telling him those things that April young a
Quotes in retrospect
Maybe I should have brought it up but it never came to my mind at that time I'll talk tomorrow payos
So
Really not
Really relevant
Admitted in
The disguises
Complete and total fraud admitted
After an essay
Investigators evaluated his hard drives as a fraud
Real pain fast
You should be allowed
How to prove in court that are paid
I think it is
A legal imperative
The only reason I disagree is
It's irrelevant
Like that
If you were to bring a court case specifically designed to
Approved
That it's relevant
But because it's a
Contempt of court case
It's irrelevant to the matter at hand
Dismiss are you an idiot
Which I still love that the auto in the eventual death penalty
You probably shouldn't unless you're in Texas
At this point
Play music
You should ask
I don't think
He doesn't deserve it
I'd like to see a court trial though
I don't want any violence to happen to him except for
Sanctioned
Because of his ex
Don't believe in the death penalty believe that again I want to be clear that me and Jordan know a ton
One more news on this podcast
Please look into Joe arpaio's history
Based on what we wanted
Not even
We had to edit some stuff out
I nearly cried
Painted we had to pause I had to go outside and walk around
Just based on how bad to do this
So please look into that again Arpaio the monster
We have to get back to the matter at hand which
Judith interview with Larry klayman where he at
Insist
And then beyond that
He goes to lay the blame
And all this s***
On people who are no longer
The current predicament
Is the Fault
Of people who have not been
Involved
For quite a while
We'll check and I don't know what's going on but I don't know why that doesn't happen
Are we clear
Generally agreeable
Should probably be aware that there is a
Not
Sometimes it's manipulative sometimes
It goes both ways sometimes it is legit
Sometimes it's not
There's a very
The message the message
Important is that
Intelligence community
People a lot of the time
But sometimes
I mean
You should look for evidence
You should look for truth
As opposed to
Or disbelieving
But things are said to you
Take things as
They come to you
Look for
Heaven Allah
I've realized
Legitimately
That was the
Smoothest you've ever been
You're right legitimately I'm getting to the point where I'm realizing that if I ever want this
Does it take off I'm going to have to start mimicking some of Alex Jones's behaviors
So I'm going to start
Look for
You dumbfucks
Are really awesome and they're really cool I don't think that you guys already
Maybe a couple
So I don't know what is assuming we have like
But I got to assume there's some Dum Dums in there
This is why
Cuz we've had a we had a rough podcast
I have just learned more about Joe Arpaio deal understand where we're coming from
Inform he's lashing out hypothetical
Wednesdays Wednesdays is band therapy
Anyway he blames Clapper and what
I think
National
No longer in office
Flapper is not
Yeah
Got to get rid of them
John
I think the example that Alex keep going back to is that
Who's gone
John Brennan
Who I was
When Trump got elected
In between him
Being sworn in
He said that you should watch
You should be careful about
Things he says
I mean
Avocado
Message
I get I get where Alex is interpretation everything like a boy watch your mouth
I don't like the way you said that
I know that.
That's the one talking
I get where Alex takes
Umbrage
But I also would understand how anybody who's in the intelligence committee
Is the steak
Of the president running his mouth
Are you can piss off foreign powers
Accident
Well you didn't even
Service you can do these things
To install foreign powers that are out
Deep
Build Alliance
And you can insult them
And you should watch your mouth
You should be really careful what you say
Diplomacy
We have a
Department
Hayirli devoted
Diplomacy
And there's a reason
You feel that
Department
People
Who actually is
Been quoted as saying he
I didn't want the job
And his wife
Do it
Yeah and then they have not stuff that
Everybody
Confused
Frustrated
North Korea
Rr4 about you
Like
It's strange
To be still
Stats with domestic
Policy
When we are
Get out of Syria
Killing more civilians than we've killed in
So long
Repeat
Non
Like it's not even defensible the variability
Terry Target
Offended so many of our allies
So many countries
This clip is Larry klayman saying that everything in the world
Essentially is Obama
I'm certain
I didn't he's talking about all this information that Montgomery has
Looked at from before Obama
Great I'll take your word for it later claiming guy who is
Clearly
Incredible
Originally above Obama Soros
Obama
In other countries in the world
Other countries executive
Super unfortunate
I had a pajama example like
Brazil
Recently had a coup you no other country
The ones where they hold their leaders responsible Benjamin Netanyahu has never been held response
Possible for any president
Literally not allowed to run for
Is legally barred from running for the job
He currently holds
Doorly illegal
Uses these two countries as an example
The president needs to be held responsible for bulshit
I think
It's the FBI buying software based on Al jazeera's barcodes
Yeah it's right up there
Italian cuisine
That's the last clip that I have for Larry klayman Centerville
If you want to know more about him and you want him to
Speak his peace
Checkers
You probably have
I didn't look into that
If you want to hear his
Entire argument laid out
I will link it on the website he has
That just lays out his entire argument
About Montgomery
It's all lies
But at least
If you go there it's basically all the stuff I cut out from
Cuz it's boring and a lot of it was covered by
Mike zullo
A lot of it is just repetitious
Here is a fun
Claim it doesn't say anything
Because Alex
Trying to
Really desperately make you believe
The people he has on his show are real
Manchester
Not Sesame Street
Claymation
We try to get it right
No you don't but sometimes
Fake Pizza Gastrology
Peju
Yeah so I mean like your guests
To ninety-nine percent accurate is legitimately don't know how you would quanta
Supply what for
Percent your guess
But I know that if there was
99%
Ambitious
Ninety-nine percent
I think the most
Respectable new sources that I trust
Have maybe 80
75%
Amazing to me
Like I said I told you on the last episode of and reading foreign policy
And a lot of 0
A lot of stuff that I've been reading in the area it seems looked into
But I still think they get things wrong for
From time to time
Of course it's every Citizen's responsibilities to take in
Media and news
Evaluate
That's your responsibility
It's not the media's responsibility to your right every time
When they're wrong it is the responsibility
To own up to
Exactly correction
And to make sure that everybody knows that
Which place is like the New York Times Washington Post
These sorts of establishment Institution
Do on a regular basis
Do as
It's unfortunate because this weekend again Alex Jones
Came out with his
Apology
Nope he never does and this is not evidence
Density does
Cuz even
Package Within
Throwing other news organizations
But hey they said it we're reporting
What you wanted
Yeah and if they had done any do diligence they never would have reported any of this
About
YouTube
They're not about
Episode
Just kind of fun
This one this one
Has been he wasn't on the phone during the claimant interview
Singing
Zip-a-Dee-Doo-Dah
Slightly racist Disney song
This one is
It's a good song though if you take the racist part out of it
Oh my what a wonderful day
Anyway
What's an autocrat
Tar-Baby in El Reno
Drunk horse he was
In the background essentially for the entire Mike zullo interview and then once Mike zullo gets off the phone out
Jerome corsi has asked for a little while
This clip
He says this clip
And it's one way of looking
And when I explained
I'm also powerful
Either from high-level leaks or house
What shows you are really On Target my friends
What his everything we write
Everybody
That everything you write
Nobody looks
That's how I'm Target
Right everything Paul Joseph Watson does everyone loves that
Yeah you're you're like
Conspiracy theorists conspiracy
Terrace
Even if
Wonky
Conspiracy theory community
I realize that
Well I mean
So far we've
Seen that Paul Ryan's walking this is wonky
Absolute gym
It's perhaps broken
Generally I like to try and come up
For something that
I really sums up
Appealing
Nothing
Next time listen to two-and-a-half hours of us talk
The last 5 minutes
We'll have a good clip
Give us light
Information of everything we've got
Monster
Liars
Everybody involved with the Alex Jones Show is all of those
That's pretty much what
I think you did a good real brief summation imma try for a little more
Who is that
Joe Arpaio
Complete monster
He is
Of racial profiling
So much
He is absolutely
Terrible he was not being wiretapped by any information
Is publicly available
Deserve the death
He had a confidential informant name
Montgomery who is a proven liar
History of fraud
History of Troy
Set up people with fake documents
Clearly
His lawyer Larry klayman
Is a complete islamophobic
Has Pride
Multiple times
Frivolous lawsuits
Against liberals kicked out of 2 quarts
Forever for life
4life
Not allowed to be quiet
So these are the characters that we're dealing with
Alex Jones take
And information about an alleged
Wiretapping
Project
That's been going on that allegedly have his phone
Numbers
Montgomery
Could easily get that information
Very mild hacking
Which he is shown
Through
People
History has shown that he is capable of
Can write Bass
Epic software in
Yeah
So what we have here is Alex Jones either willingly or unwillingly being
Tricked
Bye
Pastor Joe Arpaio
Crimes against
And probably deserves
Probably could get you a good deal on a Hyundai
Amazing
Probably
So Alex Jones
Alex Jones
Do research into any of these things
He is
Truly
What percent trying to lie
In a way that we do stay only in the way that we've always had that kind of spectrum
Fourth
If
Alex Jones has done
Research into these
We're one hundred percent
That he is
Flying ant
Pedaling a false narrative
If he is not
Which to me seems
Who's the more like
Situation
Because again all of the work you've done
All of the research you've done
Seems like something
So far beyond anything Alex Jones is capable of
It hasn't taken me that long though exactly
Even more
To be honest
We're not getting paid for the show I have a nine-to-five job is generally at 8
26 job
I'm at work
A lot of my life and I can't be
Spending time researching
I have not been tearing my hair out researching this
It's been pretty easy to find most of
Disinformation
It fits within the Alex Jones and what
We know of him
That he would not have
Even the most
Cursory of
If someone comes to Jerome corsi
And says I have evidence
The Trump is being spied on
Jerome corsi is going to write up an article
And Alex Jones is going to
To just implicitly believe
But no matter what he's not going to do any research
Recite any of that work
And because
Jerome corsi
Is
So
Someone credit
Nicole
He just brings this b******* into the house
So
Tumi I fall on the side of Alex Jones
Not
Mafia.
In this particular
That's interesting
Willfully misleading
People in the way that
He would be
If he had done
In any research
Do any of these p
Disagree with you just don't
White turkey
Ocala
I think he willfully doesn't do the research because a part of him knows that if he did
He would invalidate his unbelief
Your objections
Thank you
Groups
So
Realistically
What week what we end this with
Is
Trump was not being spied on in the West
Narrative
Who's pitching the entire week
The idea that his phone number in Trump's phone number and all that was part of this database
Is absolutely
Retrieve
I think firmly established
It's like there's a
Web
Things it's built upon it by the week on this
Do you have multiple interviews
With people propping up this one
It's complete
Has confirmed
And Trump was wiretapped Nunez is it least incredulous
Prick
In some way
His behavior was altered by some of this information Nunez I would actually argue
Is on
Evil side
Is on the evil specs
Hybrid
Lie especially if they order to protect
In order
But
In the same way
Use wagon to what he
Thanks won't get
Torn down
If you were going to
Lexus
50/50 horse race
What's blank
Who do you think you would rather
Hit your worst to right now
Paul Ryan or Donald Trump
Proof
Sophie's Choice
Really
No that's that's a no-win situation I don't hit my horse to either but if I had to choose
You probably go Trump yeah
I'm still
Going to go with Ryan
I would go Trump but
Real
Just because I don't want anything to do with Paul Ryan
Once every couple
Isaac
I think Trump is a traitor
Yeah but somehow I think Paul Ryan
Absolutely
So that I would go I would go with Trump
But
More about a knockout
Your survival
Who's the
Mcusta
More money
Gyros
Play I think Ryan is going to
I mean
And then we go back
To the
Healthcare bill
I would have booked
Or the whole Healthcare
I would have said that
Ryan
Outmaneuver
Cuz the healthcare
Was
The most
Unpopped
Nothing
Ever introduced into Congress
Yeah and he
Still put all of his
Maybe
Just maybe
Idiot
He's not a walk
He is definitely not like historical smart
He's gone it's also interesting though because I don't I don't know really
Research article about how
Trump making a hard sell on the health-care bill ended up losing them
10 votes
Negotiate with folks
Negative
It's possible that Paul Ryan maybe could have pulled it off without
Blustery tactics
Look
Either way we have one more clip
Is just great
Let's play
Get some dessert on this
This is absolutely dessert
Okay
NOW Foods
Richard Ramirez
Alex Jones showing his true colors God that felt so good
Start Society wanted for months now
Let me ask
Let me answer a question for me
Would you find us
If you were looking for
As you can find us as knowledge
Would you take donations at patreon there's a link
Knowledge fight.com
We are welcome to do that
You don't have to
I don't give a s***
I'd like it
Stafford Auto Racing
You can also subscribe
Uber review
Do you know that that pushes our ranking
Kings up or something
I'm going to give it thank you to a friend of
Thank you Brian Burger
What's up baby
You left us a nice review on
And I think everybody we want to like it really it really does
Part of something
Maple River shirt
Like
By the way
Remember when I was complaining about someone leaving the four star review
Yeah I went back and checked
I think they changed it to a 5
Sorry that I believe you
I'm so sorry
You get overly defensive
Way over Lacey
Sincere like sir
It is it is true
Sincere feelings
Really feel too but I have a
Don't even
It's hard because
Feeling like part of the reserve
Or whatever it is
It seems very few.
It's hard to try
Like looking
Protest
In Russia
This day
You see those people who are
That's real Brave
Far more than anything I
I can imagine
Cuz ever just going
It has a very real possibility
Truly does
Mastiff
Warm
Making wine
In order to
Shuttle all the protesters into a building
Like f****** road
Like it's redic
Dojo just
Feel like
I am at
The very low
Putting the
Smallest amount of what I can
Because I'm soaking
Confused about how to
All we do is
And all we can do is
Encourage people
Call your representative
Do everything a
That's that's a small thing
The ACLU I forwarded any other cause support
100%
You can that's what we want to encourage
And then beyond that also and I'm guilty of not doing this all the time
But like
It does go a long way just to be nice
Important
Further
Bailey
Is important
Try
Try to see the humanity in our fellowship
Only way to be nice to
People dad I will tell you this right now it's
Thalia Vega
Great review of knowledge
I'm glad you got that cuz that was that was my point
Twitter knowledge underscore
You can email us at knowledge
Gmail.com
Also
Last episode
Nice shout-out
Super awesome thank you very much
Anybody else who wants to write it please do we need help
If you do want to write anything about us
You should definitely mention
At the end of the article that we
Are a couple of
Just in Ohio
Policy wonks is that right
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color