Google
Introduction to this episode because
Some of you out there might be
Asking yourselves
Wait a second
Alex Jones's world
Looney Tunes right now
Crazy out
Control
With Donald Trump threatening or worse
Suggesting
You going to declare
Emergency
About it
Yeah it is crazy
An unfortunate this episode does not cover any of that stuff
The issue we have this
Because of our schedules we had to record this on Monday
Before the cycle of Alex Jones is coverage
Trump's actual speech
Play itself out
So because it's our time
Striction this week
I decided to just go ahead with this wacky and then on Friday cover all of the
But everyone is probably very interested in hearing about that
Alex's
Being a real
Dickhole
It'll be worth the wait we will have the episode for you on Friday but for now please
Enjoy
This episode
A little wacky
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work
Beverages
Alex
Jones
Danielle
Who's your favorite Spice Girl
Spice Girls
Probably
She's the one who like athletic gear and do Kik
Reverse engineering her name about that
What are your defining
If you ask the child
Like most people
Dudes that I knew who had the
Crushes on
Girls they would go with baby
Eric Reid
Ginger Spice
Normal dude
I guess the
Scary Spice
Like married to
Murphy
I don't know what your thought I have a lot of thoughts that's why I haven't thought about them in a very long time
I also
Ask question
I don't know who are you
Later hits after
Wannabe
Your affair
And the meat
Some of our donors
Dreams thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Brent
Also thank you
You are also now
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Brian
Next George thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk versions of the Bible
Brett so far you are making connections
Finally likes somebody who donated a little bit of an elevated level
Thank you so much you are now attacking
Democrat
Natalya brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
If you are
Hell yes
Interesting
Project Camelot
Doing over there
For us to go go see
She doesn't have any good episodes
Through the archives
Irrelevant to our interest
And maybe something will be Illuminating about
And I happen to find an episode that April 2016
Weather
Dr. John Waterman
Find
Well what's the introduction
Find out if he's a real doctor or not
What I'd like you to do is give some of your background
For people that haven't
Familiar with the Waterman files
I believe it's another shortwave show
And John does a show
Weekly
Maybe your daily I don't know how often you're doing it nowadays John you can fill me in
I I do want to say that he is that he was trained as an intelligence agent and decided not to pursue that
Aware of what
Intel agencies are doing
And he was also a
Head of one of the militia groups and tell you more about that so John go ahead
Alert
A very curious about it myself gas type
But it is interesting because John Waterman's not his real name so it's not like I'm going to be able to find
Kuhio I can't figure out who he is and it's a fairly common name there's enough
You know if you'd if you Google
John Waters
I am a doctor of biological medicine it's basically alternative drug therapies that I
Naturopath
It is
Which is a bad start to this interview
Meaning of not a doctor not a John Waterman
Open camera
The number of people who may know him
So
Whatever it is it's all just
A little bit
How do you became train
Isn't intelligent
That's my second career and
A fellow that sin became a very very good friend of mine Frank Shin who's now gone
I was who recruited Lee
He came to me when I was doing clinical work and
And said I'd like to
Have you checked me out so I did came back and he said that
I need some more help and so about the third trip into
Me he said the
Take you out for dinner
He's like a recruiting him Migos
Text message like I want to make you an agent or whatever and then
Yeah you get to train and all that she's involved in a bunch of separate he's like no medicine is my true love
You're a naturopath first of all
Big red flags
With this story right off the bat of course the person who could confirm all of this is gone
Giant flag
Might be something
Super consist
SeaWorld
Be very suspicious
Part of someone's backstory can confirm all of this nonsense that I say
For more information
Baby saying that you
You're sorry for
My lost
Well
Condolences
You've not
Trying to frame this as like I got taught the ways of
The agent
It was Mexico explained he was in the ship
I don't understand
Keep going to say that he was involved in like
The investigation of the Oklahoma City bombing
He says that the movie Spy game is about human this guy Frank
That sounds right fright the Robert Redford
I'm not making
You don't look like Brad Pitt
And I was
Several places across the sky
Involved
Domestically on things like helping the rundown Joe number
John Doe number to the Oklahoma City bombing
Rebellions like the chapas rebellion in Mexico that the revolution of Mexico.
High-level stuff man
Like
John Doe number 2 at level clearance
Call Danna foreign Revolution
Origin story is
Intelli Opera
From
Juicy later on
I don't think so
Isn't that another convenient
Xvii
So they are going to
Who is working in a clinical setting
Mysteriously
Right
They went a few Thai
Feel like the first time they were like he was going there
I don't know if this nature of have is good enough for the side psyop send
Go back again
Go back one more time
He thinks that we are
Because I didn't recruit
These worlds
Weather movie
But unlike those people
Inspiration for movies
Selfie
He's an inspiration for a movie
During the revolution
Many other
In the world
He says he's a pretty good I'm Robert Redford I said will you lucky duck
Step point
Is this is not a joke
I started getting all upset
And he says hey
You never would answer
He just said
Hey you did very good cuz you're
Your Robert
If you're not Robert Redford Brad Pitt
I said you're serious
Conversation still friends right
It was Conversation Over
What it was
Waterman
Get to be Robert Redford the guy on the other end of the phone is like the middle of a fight
F*** you you son of a picture Prospect
I have a lot of concerns about
Credentials
The future
In 2016
The Earth was going
There was a vibrational changes that were happening that we're going to alter our DNA
Didn't expect this to Robert Redford tell him about possibly
And we receive these messages
And or
An interpretation
Anda
One of the things that
I want to say that you know
The evidence
Was even Paula Violette talked about it
He talked about
Superwave
Possibly headed our Direction but aside from that
It we're going through an area space where this is going to happen
And
The DNA is supposed to be changing this isn't
He's kind of like a Reclamation of the 2012 - chocolate
Prophesy funneled into
Vibrational changes happening
I just saved my favorite favorite
Favorite part
My favorite part of every Project Camelot after
Is the guest
Or carry
Just saying
Haha or right
To the single most outlandish ridiculous pasta
Simple thing that could
Resetting there just like yeah of course move on
Improv game
The gravy always off
An area of
Wednesday
And
I don't know
What you're looking at or what evidence you're looking at
But
I can tell you that it is raising the vibration of the planet and and the and the humans
Now there are some people who won't be able to handle the vibration to
And don't go the opposite direction
From what I do it'll be a bad we have to be compatible
With the
Well we could say the frequency that
Compatible
Dissonant with
You will become
You will actually begin to
Offer it rather than flow with it is kind of like those
Movies like we see with Dune flow through you fear is not of your
Problem just let it flow
You're going to another words resonate
With it you're going to be much better off than trying to fight it
It goes on to explain like
More examples
Could have just brought up Kenny Loggins
Cut-ups
Surprised
You want to do
Do you want to talk about dude
I don't need to I don't need to
Everyone everyone knows
Bruno's
And how dare you
Butchers
Frank Herbert did not write a lot of good life
He was a long writer lot of line
Not a lot of good end
Sphere from the Benji
In the entire book
Are you sleep
You know it's some people
Compatible with
I wonder if there's any differences between those sorts of people who are compatible and go to art
I don't know I don't know what he thinks
Immediately after he said that
I don't know what you're talking about and I refuse to even address this
Set the sky
Animosity towards
This isn't really what this interview is about even this
Idea of vibrational changes and all that stuff
Secondary to
I believe
Her big issue on this episode
Earthquakes she wants to talk about earthquakes that are coming because she recently
Come into the possession of a map
That should wear a lot of recent earthquakes were
And she hasn't
Just like a map
Ring of fire if it's involved
Explain
Which we already knew
There's a very weird
I'm going to find a map to show everyone is on Iris
It shows you the entire
What you call that
The Ring of Fire
And you can see that
The United States is actually on the west coast right now
Kind of empty of earthquakes very strangely
Eastside
It's got a lot of it
And again I think this is
Manipulation
So whether they're trying to build the energy and then cause
A huge earthquake
Let me just say that Sean David Morton reported on my show that that he knows someone who
He's an older Israeli man who can't lie correctly predicted
Some things in the past
Remember that Sean David Morton is the con man
Who got arrested
Conspiracy Cruise
Tens of thousands of dollars
Such a hero of our time Lil weirdo
Why she still listen
Doesn't come on man Cruiser here that he got a rest
Including the 2008 crash
And he's saying that in November of this year there's going to be a major event for the 9/11
Recently Sean sent me a text saying
It's going to be an LA quake
I don't know I have seen
Where we seen a major earthquake in LA
There are going to be major volcanic eruptions as well
Now how much of this is natural and how much is uno humanly engineered
Because we have a secret government
And I'm
Illuminati
To have a program an agenda they're working
And
If they if it doesn't happen naturally
They will stimulate it
So so this is really important
She's talking about
Control
She's afraid that the
The Illuminati the government or the globalist
It's all good
But you also do need to recognize the behind that she has the exact same
Conception with
Slightly different character name
And more
Yeah
The cabal
Ruling the world
You do you see these
Indications
Mort what I want to say is if she
Is precognitive
Picture
She shouldn't keep having weirdos
That are so like
She should have seen that any page is a racist Indian
Baseball players on the planet
What
Now
Look I'm just saying
We have to believe one of
Two things either she's not
Precognitive
I'm enjoy being around these sorts of people home and if she was a psychic
F****** with us
Aside for her
That's not what I was thinking and then
That's the message she wants
To put out into the world
The two of us she has been
CNS coming for forever
That happen
A lot of precogs have predicted a large earthquake in LA
Oh yeah
I wonder why
Earthquake
Bidmc
Predicting a large one
Too far outside
Central Missouri
I don't know man
This is wack
It's not nearly as bad as what about to happen
Cuz Waterman
Wants to get in
Do you like
Something
He's got he's undergone
Vibrational
They're happening
Andy has a story that he wants
Tell Carrie about it
And this
Is nuts
The changes that are occurring on this planet
Is that I was
Literally
In a very serious State I was
Bleeding
Without
Being cut I was
Abdominal pain
Passed out
Emergency room
I can't find anything they did
They did x-rays
Cultures to see if I was
There was not a thing they could find
Until
Serendipitous event where I fell out of Texas sent me an e-mail
It said something about
Acronym acid
So I got
Interesting
That isn't
So you just had to s*** really hard
No.
The coronal mass ejection
Very close by the letter
I think that anybody who actually
Probably,
What's better diagnose
Whatever it is
Unlike
Try not to pretend
And then
Bringing up solar flares
Better talk to my doctor
Interesting
Who is Doctor
He talks to somebody else
Somebody called me and said I think I know what it is now this is a remote heater
I think what's going on with you
Coronal mass ejection
Ted come out
And I started with my emergency room Vic
And for some reason
Out of the blue
I became very sensitive to the
I mean extremely sensitive
Or there was literally something happening
But I have got a calendar where I can track because I
And
And tell you I'm extremely
To a lot of things I can walk out on a day
For there's a lotta
Higher levels of it I can't do it
In November I have become very yogurt
Higher vibrations this is attacks of some sort so everybody
Has been helping had one
A remote viewer
But remote heater contact me
And I'll ask me permission to work on me I said your ear
Happy Grape
They call me back said I can't get anywhere because you've been attacked
They're blocking everything
Troy start having to really
Investigate
This potential about
Warfare
If he's making this up how do you explain the remote healer telling him that he's being attacked
How's that might be a scam also
Olives
And I look
If you want to believe what you want to believe
Stop believing it remote Healers
Victor even one either one who is like
Okay Adam
Billionaire
You'd have to like
You would have to vend assume that they wish ill on mankind
Well
You have that gift you better never stop working because you are the only one you know it's crazy
The insurance
Doug cover
Play weird part of Trump's hair
Crazy but they do recover remote
I just think like
Yeah when your condition is
I'm sensitive
Solar flares
That's exactly when you need a remote dealer
I love that little
Max where the remote healer tells him to
He's being attacked
Feeling isn't working
An investigation
MLB remote healer back and he was like who exactly the remote I will tell you that for another 15
Literally outside of that what is the investigation
Now I'm afraid of the Sun
I guess the only thing is like staying indoors during a solar flare I guess
Maybe
Google
You know we assume that it's some sort of a solar flare thing
The culprit
You know what John Waterman has the mother
I think I was being attacked I think I did somehow get poisoned fact they did find some
Poison
I'd like to take you back to 10 minutes
Seems very contradictory
Moderation in all things
So
I don't know how
Jokes
Everybody could be remotely.
So it was a very expensive very interesting
Experience
Mid November
Thank you John I'm very happy that you that you made it through and you survived
I I had my own attack
Definitely know where you coming from
Look at that the information and what happened
And it was a it was a descaler attack
Steelers score
You know people that are out in the public eye
They can go under attack by various groups and course the Illuminati are going to concentrate on those of us
Can influence others
Because of what we're saying and what we're putting out there
Information wise
Powerful
What's the Illuminati
Is there energy on people like
Waterman
Got to get John watermelon finally Illuminati I'm thinking
Not a doctor John Waterman out of here
So they're the ones who are they
Interstellar in
Intergalactic
Interdimensional Steeler attack
I don't know
Something bad I don't know
Twitch
He is describing
The powerful
Mind-boggling
In his world there are both remote
Steelers
Yep sure there's a car dimensional
Well you know I go outside
And they can be anywhere
Hey what you going to do
You're not a real man
Because
A real man
Creeps behind the curtain and he sees that lovecraftian Eldritch Horror
His mind he keeps on fighting
This terrible otherworldly
Awful
People who don't have the good strong stuff
Turn tail and start working with the Illuminati
Or
Recall
Shut it
It seems like
If you have on one side
And then on the other side you're you look behind the curtain and you see the Illuminati has remote healers and remote poisoners
I see no evidence that the Illuminati is remote Healers
We only know that miss being good guys
World so far we've only heard of them as being on the side of the weirdos
You're losing I think it's implied they do have one but it only be poisoning people
Interdimensional scalar attack
Steelers
We got the earthquakes that obviously the Illuminati are going to
Precipitate vibration and stuff like that that are that are causing John Waterman to ship
Yeah so we got all this
But
About halfway through the episode Carrie finally gets
To like what the bread-and-butter is
What you want
Spend most of her time talking about because Johnson
Himself an expert in
Couple of top out now
I have one question that has to do with
What
You were talking about with regard to FEMA and where they're deploying and then I'd like I know we're going for lunch
Time but I'd like
He also addressed the financial meltdown be
That was part of the are some subject list
Topics are two of the main things that Alex Jones covers on his show the eye
Coming Financial meltdown
Former Intel agent
Financial crisis
That's correct I too was a was trained by Edwards
Fraction
I'd love to have him confirm bedroom
Fremont
Exocentric
Go to Alex's.
We have this guy
Supposed expert
Some variety
And here's what he has to say about
That's the thing I actually think
FEMA is more about
Populations that will be on the move
Riley Reid
I think they're kind of
Let's say you got a
A bottle and everybody's down in the bottle and everybody has to go through the bottleneck to get out right
You're putting FEMA right there at the bottleneck
They're going to need help
They're getting ready
Emergency Management agency
Emergency response
Actually accurate
Conception of the camp
Is there to cut off the flow of people
Which is
You know just because they're not clearly specifying
Became pastor
That is the exact same idea
Evil female organization
Operating
Because of these crises
That the Illuminati is going to
Perpetuate
The solutions they already
Cutting off bottlenecking
Is my wife
My wild
No no I make perfect sense but I promise you there will be
As we get
Through this there will be you'll see
Crystal clearly why this is important
Can I ask you a question
Why is not a doctor John Waterman
An expert on Fremont
Because he
He is a Former Intelligence
Is red a blogger
I don't know I don't think
He talks about like
Sources he has
Anonymous Vegas
I got to listen to that
Yeah so we got that
FEMA camps.
And then the other subject
Talk about was
Meltdown of the economy
It's coming, and you know what
You can say that Carrie
Is just coming out of this
I don't know where but no
You should know that 10
Carrie new
The financial collapse is coming
Right about when this episode.
Henry Deacon Overton around 10 years ago
Old Camelot
That
We were going to it wasn't going to be one set of
Circumstances that was going to happen in the future
And they and he even they even told us
2016 + 27
These are the years that we were told about
10 years ago
They said he said
That it was going to be a series of things that would all happen at the same time
So it's not
Major earthquake
And that's where I want to get into the financial talk now because
You do have some knowledge in that area and there's no doubt that we're having
Or being hit
Financially and there is a plan a plan complete change in the system
That is supposed to have a deadline of the end of 2016
Camelot were told this by not just one with
What do you have to say about that part
What is
I'm going to meet myself
Where we can begin talking about this is that
The dollar
Has been recognized the US dollar
Economics
Weapon
Economic weapon
Of War
So
It should surprise you not at all
To know that
His blog
On December 4th
Teeny posted
The Federal Reserve Act passed by three senators in a unanimous
23rd of December 19th
Cool
Okay that's awesome
Guys look
The waitresses
System is currently in
Instituted there will be another financial crash that's
Literally how it works
It's now they change the rules
And they will not change
To ensure that every now and then there will be
This is predicting an earthquake in LA in order to
The closet collab product
People who
Super duper rich
They don't feel the consequences.
So that's why they have no info
Change those rules back to red
There were protection
In place
Yeah please nonsense we've got this idea that he's putting forth it is
That you have
The dollar
Is
Of some sort
Clearly believe it was set up in 1913 by the
Cesar menotti bankers
Right
Precipitate of financial
Meltdown
Irresponsible by going with these dates
Pretending she's known for 10 years there's a deadline
Do you were wrong for
Subaru Outback
Even just a bad prediction all those horses you had were very wrong
Pizza Buffet
In his
It is decided
Ideas that be
Because of the fee
Fiat currency
The dollar
It's going to cause this
So it shouldn't surprise you at all
But he's also
Into hard currency
Is anything that is a threat to the dollar than is an enemy
The powers-that-be
That's it
Bottom line
Gold and silver
It's an enemy
So they controlled by
Having
These
Training
Worthy
Rothschild Illuminati of the world
Made sure that the value of gold stayed down
So the Rothschilds in the Illuminati were suppressing
The price of gold
Alex Jones
Gold constantly talk about Eva Global is the price of gold
So buy it now before it's Skyrocket
Gillette stuff and when the economy falls apart that price of gold
It's exactly the same
Exactly the same
Hi I'm not a doctor John
Suggesting that you buy
Please feel free to buy as many not a gold bars as you would like to buy from not a doctor
It is interesting message approved by
Not anybody
I think it was a decent radio voice but outside of that I got like
Almost everything he seems I'm qualified to speak on
A lot like these
Paranoid
Conspiratorial
Typed
Community people
The head of militia
Where to go
But who knows
It was called the United States Army
It was called Dan
The world
Cool
He has some other more specific
Advice to give you
And so they opened up an exchange
The term for
Federal Reserve money
What about the blood bank
Sperm bank
Those are actually
The $250,000 worth
I know that
Utah
I think it's the only state
They made it
Used gold and silver
In order to pay
For like God.
Stuff like that
So that got changed and so there's a
There's like Exchange
In Utah around
Gold and silver market
Get that is much
Different than it is another state
That's what he's talking about
Central Fiat money
So they opened up this a group the first one that's open that I like is upma
Hey that's abbreviation
Dot-org
If you go there
You'll see some videos of the Secretary of
The Attorney General
Talking
You'll see a CEO that's running for governor by the way who runs Overstock
Overstock.com
Almost no doubt in my mind that he
He's getting money from
BMI million-dollar the United precious metals Association
He later says he's not getting
Means.
Getting paid by um
He has ads for them on his website
Third
You hear the way he
Presented this is like the one that I really like
Snn talks about
Go to the website
General
Upma
It's all real credible stuff and you should go there you should go check it out
So we've now turned
The corner he right
When do the showare
You starting to spread fear about
You know fiat currency at a coming meltdown and stuff like that
But to anyone paying close attention
Are you only doing that because you have a financial interest in upma
Because it seems like you might he's running the game that Alex and good by himself
Really aware of it
This is exactly like
Peter Schiff
It was on.
Do you want on and was talking about how great goal days and how
The markets unsecured and stuff like that
Peter Schiff
Also
I want to plug my gold selling
Also the way he said
Upma
Their website that is a man whose
Given a sales pitch of the path
Featherman who's in natural path.
Because it feels I wiped
We get to see you like I think that this is almost
Exactly like how Alex does
Maybe not as bracing like maybe doesn't
Take a turn off quickly
Is an insanely irresponsible level of fear-mongering
That
Precipitates and leads directly into
Him bringing back up
Upma in house
Coming up
Through June
And July
You're going to see
Very bizarre stuff I believe
In our financial banking sector
I think you're going to see
Some of the
Big Banks
I think you're going to Vincy at the end of July
The beginning
Hyperinflation now I've got some numbers
You saw this
Late summer early fall
Numbers
Go to the grocery store
On Monday
Buy groceries and when you go back
1 days. Of time
Your groceries are going to be 9% more
Kg to lb
Meaning of weeks
75% increase in your food
Have to choose
Do I pay my house payment for my car payment or do I
And this is where we're going and it's going to be starting late summer
She go to upma.org
You can kind of set you up and I hate to say it
Bank account
But this is not a bank
Okay
Dollars in there
Gold or silver whichever you want or combination
So it's basically a place where they buy the gold they hold it you have like a debit card where you can use the amount of the gold that you have
Huron gold
Put a nugget in there in there like this
Operations like that
In the golden silver
Precious metal
Dismiss the idea of like they have
V until I got to hold it for you
Yeah but there is a lot of stuff like that
I think I understand a lot of it is kind of
Be careful it's all on the up-and-up
Abigail
You know
Clip and I can't hear any other way than a sales pitch.
You put $1,000 to get you to sign up for an account.
Say you have $1,000 in
In United States dollar
Gold
Where somebody else gets to hold on to it
And then they give you
A representation of
That you can use in the form of a car plastic not paper so it's not Fiat
Discard
Thank you for your fake name
I just
See like this is a scam
Run Ontario
He's abusing her platform
That's true
She wanted to talk about earthquakes
And maybe
Some stuff about financial trouble that you're out about 4.
Sister's going to
But it's clear that
Steven chica
Until like in the mall
A little bit this is like
She doesn't get mad at him or anything like that like she doesn't
The cheese like
At least
Suspicious
Okay
Like there's a little bit
Cuz I'm I'm listening to it now
Like if I were casually listening I wouldn't
I've noticed that the very obvious
You know I would have but I my perfect
You are already in that world and you have no reason
Conn's on you all the time
Be passive
We listening to
I don't have a financial intra
Tristan upma
But I know that you're right
So far you have been right about
Seems like everything
And even write about it he's right about this next prediction that he makes I got to be honest I don't like to
To give it up till really
No
And they plan on running this country have a revolution in fact
I have a lot of information saying they were probably
The second American Revolution
So
Could be playing
Introduces American revolution's coming around the Republic
Budget plan
I have a lot of secret people telling me all these things the revolution is coming
Grape
Didn't happen
Outlook
Look
In a world where there's remote poisoners and remote Healers
I have group of remotes
Occasional Financial Times readers telling me
American Revolution
True
Play
When did the Republican Warren is in August
I think so I don't remember exactly
Summer
And that's important
To talk about
I got information more information about the economy that got
Some very interesting more research about certain groups
Red flag
And what they're planning to do
With this kind of stuff like DNA
It's been very enlightening even to me
If you were going to say this is going to be a very hot summer politically hot
Financially troubling hot
Every in every aspect
Like you were saying it's not one thing it's multiple
Summerville it December of Rage baby
Contested
Presidential election happening politically hot
Emotional
No s*** man in the year of a presidential election how could it not be
Notorious assholes
Or like maybe one other summer of presidential
Where there was a summer of Rage
A lot of them probably what about what about
Sure
How much is
Yep
What about 2004
Summer of Rage
These people say
Is what these mean it very specific
American Revolution
Going to kick off an acrimonious
We're not going to have a great time
Temperature going to rise
Look at that is a zero
Make it
Be saying nothing
When you say summer of Rage in this sense
You mean it
Any particular context
You're only doing that service
I'm trying to sell this
Some groups
See
No that's where we need to probably start having a copper
Yeah
Some groups
Not
And suggest that I
No. Seems like a bad guy
So the red flag to me and where I was like
Website the Waterman files
Whatever issues you have buddies like fake credentials and stuff
If you check out their websites
Problems jump out in Media
From a blog post on December 28th
Is WWII came to an end to purge the German race from the planet
Zionist took over Germany called second Israel
Niche
Zionist agenda eversense
Ever since the end of World War II
Compounded the media are part of the mines
The people with a German Nazi
Propaganda
So the German military
They think it's a
The fascist regime
Here's the thing
Waterman believes a lot of the same stuff as Alex does
Is bigotry
Take this post from October 2020 Ryan
Bistro that would better come out
Quote Jewish Hollywood continues to lie by a plane hit the Pentagon
Over and over like the live the so-called Holocaust
Analyze
California criminal politician Adam Schiff
The Jews will continue to support the anti-American attacks on America
George Soros
So he is an anti-semite
Have something we can to find him even anti-semite
Not a John Waters
Explicitly arguing that he's trying to resurrect
The Christian country in Russia
Taking control away from
Jewish Bolshevik
Which is why the world hates
Tim so much
It's all just a result of
Do the Jews control the media
And hating the fact
The simultaneous the enemies
Infinite and the enemy is always losing
Conundrum that they always have or it's like
All the Jews control everything and they're telling all of you
But also the Jews are f***** over at every possible turn like
I don't understand
What are you doing
What are you doing lyrics
Vacation
What Jews do their thing unless it is really which case
Different stuff
It's because it's because it's so historically a part of our alexar
Collective Consciousness is a piece of History
Existed
You go back you know when the blood libel started
Wetware r1800
Part of bike Pub
Looks like you for a really long time
And we've come to a place
In our culture
Especially
The people know about the Holocaust
Things like that but they don't realize a lot of
Hatred was built on
I don't understand a lot of the stuff
Free dates
Even the rise of Nazism why they chose
Scapegoat
Among other skate
People don't recognize
Shortcut
The people who are lazy and bad
His maid
Forever so people like a waterman
He just doesn't want to do the work
She doesn't want to
Understand
These are
Grapple with
The greater complexity than one group of evil Zionist
Right
For me is this
He believes almost exactly the same things as Alex
You seen it over and over again throughout this episode
And even post
Bitter you know against
Please things similar things to Alex
In-N-Out f****** 100
Punch Adam Schiff
He loves Putin because he thinks that he's resurrecting a Christian
Country which is
The Peace of Alex's rhetoric
All of his stuff is there
And also
Fancy sandwiches
And one of the reasons that I believe that this is
It's because he
He perpetuates the same narrative
He's almost
To back up his argument
Zerohedge.com
At least I did on his blog
All the same
Communist narrative
Foundation
Waterman is he's an unrepentant Day by semi
Because he understands what
The point of
The propaganda is
Even if some people try to be
Explicit about
Alex Jones
Using
Anti-semitic propaganda
Whether or not
Stone up to the fact
What's behind
I'm someone like John Waters
Lake Asbury
Clearly illustrate
Yes
Of the world's structure
And what have you write exact same sources
Historical trends
That lead from the
The past to him
Lead right to Alex
The only difference is that Alex
Couches is rhetoric with
It's not the Jews at
Hate it
Heat
I'm part of humanity
Stupid so that's all awful but just to make you feel a little better on a review
Imma post that you made on Christmas Day
28 trillion
If you thought that your Christmas was kind of weird
Consider this
One very good stores the personal friend spends a couple hours each day investigating to high-level Brinkman
We've met in Costa Rica during a trip by this bright tireless person
Is direct connection
Certain qanon members who work closely with JFK Junior
Bush family is in turmoil and Hillary's face charges with only the timing endowed
Not the process
And most excitingly said John F Kennedy Junior will return to the stage at a grand event
Jennifer his father's killer is George h.w. Bush
You don't know that the party qanon
Now the Trump is
Is j.f.k. jr.
Later
The problem with ever really talking about qanon stuff if they have this
Makes fun of
Thank you and I'll be there like that stupid
Stupid s*** there's a bunch
It's just
Waterman
Diva qanon geyser
Complete weirdo gleaves almost all the same stuff is Alex Jones or also
Anti-semite
Gary
She's trying to
Wind down
The interview
He's like I want to play you something that I made
Not Bank
I kind of thought that might be what are you doing I really had a hunch.
Shoot the Moon
But instead what it is is a long
Welding music
Kind of
Islam
There's some swelling music behind it and people saying
You are.
His little speech
But he gives
About how your
We are in this together
And I think that gives us hope
I feel like he thinks he's taking over her show
He's doing overnights now he's doing like your long overnight radio
The most important thing
We are not alone
You know cuz if we were alone
Holland
And we're not alone and there are many people
Jerry
This is the awake
We just need to
Understand we're not bickering
It's
Not time for us to
Shades of our color it's time for
I want to get rid of the mess and you and I are on the same page
You get this done and get it over
So
Knowing more about him that message is no longer inspirational
If you don't know what he believes that that message could easily be heard as a message of unity the idea of it's not time
Shade of our colors although that doesn't play there is a time to talk about that and I don't like that
That could fault hit your ear the same way at Alex's we all bleed red blood at out early.
Purple blue red
Doesn't matter
Bigger
Evil that we need to face and that is this the system
Or whatever
This is a message of unity
Unless you're Jewish
We're going to f*** you up we're all in this together except these Jews
It's crazy to me for us
So many levels first of all
The little bit of awareness about
His worldview
It brings into
Focused like that
We change what he say
I meant second
He doesn't know anything about him
She allows him to give this message
A show
That is an Aki with sounding
What is actually deeply anti-Semitic
Because even says remove the problem or get rid of this mess and just take care of it
Just get paid
Done with it or something
Figure out the Omega
Fix for it
Figure out
That one
Problem solver
To figure out
Find lynels fedoras
Weather because she kind of believe similar things
Certainly heard her say
Not so wonderful
Cool things
Foot like
Whether it's that or just because she has no idea
She's talking to and dozen
Prepare really for shows at all
What she's done is allowed someone
Slick enough
To not make that a part of
Is Public Presentation
Be deeply Abby's Medical
Give a message
Attacks on her own show
Bridget
Crazy to me
Like what
Alicia Cara
Better
You can't do this
You can
If you care you can't do this
It also proves you're not a
Tango.com
Goddamn
Yeah it's just
It's nuts to me
Minut scale
I think it's illustrative
How
People who have ill-will
Not always just not
But like people who have ill-will
Like they're very adaptive
It co-opting
People's messages
So you know you have somebody
Like this Waterman
You knows that if
If you'd like
Immediately
Hey Terry
Jacuzzi
Equal bad
That's not going to be an interview.
Not a doctor John Waterman in here that
That's a strong state
Got to go
Probably knows enough
To know like a problem
So she wouldn't continue
He's quick enough to know that I have to mind my P's and
Choose when I'm home
When I'm on my way I can f****** say whatever I want
Shitpost all day the only thing that I can
With a hundred percent certain
The carries audio
Much larger than his
And he knows this
Who's the best way
Can hopefully.
Over to his worldview
By being on the show
Being careful
About stuff
People come check him out
Get red pill
Yeah yeah
This is how this shitt goes
I don't know if I could
I don't know how I would do that
I'm not that far
Hey
Whatever you're doing right now Joe
Do better
Goddamn
I believe that
Everything where he is
Whether consciously or unconsciously
Tool by which
People with ill-will attract
Themselves
At Joe's expensive
You shouldn't be
Signing off on Lotto
He does
The guys
No
You would hope
You would you would hope that somebody who managed to help make Newsradio the f***
Greatest
Sitcom of
The 90s
I would know better
You would help
Did somebody who has
Dick was on that show
Don't don't
Place
The murderer
So this is a little Adventure
I don't know if this is
Hugely important
Discuss
I think there's some connective tissue in there.
Play important whether it be easy
Project Camelot world
Connecting with h
What's more realize there is
There's a lot of connections
The connection
Between people who espouse exactly the same rhetoric is Alex
But hide
There are
Somatic nausea
In order to be more socially accepted
People like that you
I always appreciate these
Because there's so many
I swear if you
You were casual
If you were not
Really
You paying closer
You didn't have
Conversant in this world already
You would listen to his
Interview and be like
How old is just a looney
I know you're still no big deal I think that through most of it
It is so much.
You guys are always
Interconnected with
And there's so many different
Version there so many
Different flavors
Indigo
These guys can get away with
To a certain audio
Somebody from Stormfront
Maybelline
The exact same s***
As Alex Jones
Of course
Throwed off
All this way
Somebody on Facebook
You like you know
Who believes all the same s*** Alex Jones does
Isn't going to stay at the same way that
Stormfront
Right
Presentation
But it's the same s***
It's so hard because there's so many degrees
To give people
The benefit of the
Yep
Has proven
Is that you should never trust
Anybody we're all in this
And nobody knows what's going on
And the summer of Rage
The last thing I want to say
I want to say is that like
Just answer the funny wrinkle
John Waterman
Yeah you bet
So what you have there to is another little
Paracosm of these
Halfsies
These messages and all
Credibility
Themselves is attack
People who are exactly like them
You know in the same way if it's okay
Text Bill Cooper
Mexico
Does about him
This John Waterman
Attacks Alex Jones
Perversion
Right
Stratford
Write your own stuff like that that's another piece of this,
Crye-Leike
Only makes
Both
Party stronger
Which apps
Infuriate like David Duke
Where you like
Alex
Stop pretending you love this guy
Yeah you loved everything he stands for and you loved everything he believes but you
Push back his followers can be like
Alex
He doesn't hate Jews but both of them
You both keep both galvanized our audiences a little bit using the other person as their
Hope to siphon
How do you all go out for drinks
The next episode but until then
We got two apps
We do have a website
Dollartree.com
Upp neurology
.
We also on Twitter
We are on Facebook
Like that
Dan
I would guess
Based on the fact that not a doctor John Waterman
Is not a doctor Norwich on Waterman
Some bad medical advice in the winter
But one guy
Definite
Probably
Also
Iteknic
Alexandra Thurston color