Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work
Hey everybody
Yes sir I
Play Super Mario RPG
I know it's Super Mario
Dear door
I don't remember Paper Mario
You I don't know
Oh really are fun as hell.
Fell apart
The crumpled up and thrown in the garbage
It was just not all that fun
Color the world
It just was not
It was really good liked it alot
I don't know what else do you like to do I heard good things
Play that game like 15 times and I
There's the awesome Games Done Quick Marathon going on right now
It's like a massive either unkind of me it's all about donations to
Nonprofit in the
Sites that does all cancer
Like that and I love that game so much and I found out that somebody was speedrunning
And I was like
I've been watching
I've literally been watching a guy play
Super Mario for the past 2 hours
Go to the game that I was okay at
There's something gratifying something you play very sad
Reflect on that
Before the show started playing Hollow Knight
For the recommendation on that one
I like it
I'm not good at it end up wandering around places for a good 20
Supposed to go
Turn the music up
Just delightful
Gameplay fun
Video game podcast
Correct Cooper episode on Monday
Waterman not doctor Waterman
Alex Jones
And the world of Infowars
Be going over is a little bit of
Snapshot of the life
Of Alex Jones in 2018
There we go
We're going to be going over January 8th
Vat19
And then his live broadcast that he did that evening
When Trump was giving his speech from the Oval Office historically when we've gone over show
And then there's a live broadcast immediately after that
That light broadcast
Is drunken and angry
He seems a little drunk but don't get your hopes too far up on that it doesn't go for
But he is a little bit on
Then it'll be interesting to look at
We have to give a shout out
We would like to
Give a shout out
Do a couple people signed up and are supporting shall we appreciate it very much
I'd like to say.
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Policy wonk
Next
Christopher
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Christopher
I just came out that way and I apologize and thank you
Next
Bridget Bridget
I appreciate it though so very much
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
Jesus
Thank you so much Ian if you're out there listening and you're thinking hey I'd like to support this show what these Gents
Acknowledge
Appreciate
Now
We get to our business at hand and one of the reasons why I was a little bit reluctant
To do any Alex Jones
This week
Was because they are
The 2009 stuff hit a little bit of a little bit of boredom on Alex's part back
Eventbrite
Want to get into that and then
There's all this talk
Trump's part
In that world that's pure
About the idea of trump
Declaring a national emergency
In order to get the wall made out in a particular way
But I didn't know exactly how it was going to play out
I kind of got the sense that all of this was Much Ado About Nothing
People getting all worked up in
Who's going to be
You know kind of disappointed
Since I got but I didn't want to cover it until we actually had content to go over
And so January 8th is Tuesday shows no a week
Done that before this episode
I found out
F***** up
This mood is
Pretty f***** up to be to be seeing this
All that
The first years now.
Text Rob from
Gavin Newsom ladies and gentlemen you better believe is it
He is the devil
Read message
Yeah
Music is the great Satan
I wouldn't bet on you know what that's a good but now that I think about it
What respect is reasoning is that he's flick
Comer in the Democratic world
She's going to be the one
Trump with
And so that's why he's labeling the devil
Like I said
He knows the Trump is going
Going to be giving us
Speech that night
First clip you start to show
Very clearly indicate
He knows what he's going to do
Privately and the globalist
Are crapping themselves both publicly but also the look
On their faces
Set up beforehand
Sorry Squad
Subway news today
He is making it very clear
The Trump is going to declare a state of emergency
But he knows it
Seems already tonight
All the globalist
Crapping themselves
Alex
Now there's some contradict
Historic rhetoric.
I want I want us to put a pin in that until we get through
Because I
We can have about that later
Disservice
Jump the gun on it but it was listening
We are not not notice until it's very obvious
To be excited about a president declared a national emergency
Is
Super excited
United States
Other branches of government
Unilateral action
It seems it seems like
Counter to a lot of his beliefs about the power of the executive
You should understand that it's coming from
A deep
Place in Alex's
The end of his personal struggle
The end of this turmoil
His battle
In many ways I believe listening to
That wants to
Where's the state of emergency
It's game over for the globalism and finally Alex Jones
Not have to do this
Here is eclipse
Really leave me towards that
The joy is a God-fearing person
Smiling over
Closer to God
He's crazy
Now we just think you're weird
Increase for myself
Intellectually what I understand is just
Little shells
Good job
Because there's been a total shift just the last month
You talk about bolsonaro
Talked about everything we've done
Has a choice
Of what decision I want to make to be seduced by the globalist
By the high-tech
But War.
I didn't know the Antichrist
Thunder
Like a gopher
This
Pretty f*****-up
It feels a little apocalyptic
It feels like you saying we're getting our bearings together
For what will be the grand final battle between us and the globalist
And the people who are on our side or people like
Bolsonaro in Brazil
It's it's
Weird
A little weird
For me quite frankly
To come to this place
Having as much of an understanding of Alex's
Look at all my
So weird
If this is how
It's shaken out
It disappoint
Really really bad especially with bolsonaro having
It's really
Something that everybody should be aware of
Right now bolsonaro is going to do more damage to the climate than I think any single person
Possibly
Well once he
Declares open season on the Brazilian Rainforest
Being cut down
Werefox
It's a very on
Undoable
Yeah that's concerned
Human rights question
Windsor
Deeply in Ford
It's the pits
It's wild
Battle
What you failing to recognize
That when you look at the conception of
It's final.
Envisioning
Is it no matter what happens
Really
What if he loses
Declared a national emergency
Bargaining chip
What I want
The wall
Emergency
Launch launch
Glacier Skyward salad
Either way Trump wins
And sued for peace 2 years ago anyone
What do you want me to still have your wealth and you still want to screw the country over because you got some spiritual
To defeat it
With the Devil
Trump
Don't understand
Exactly
What effect declaring a national emergency
Privately
Well declare a National Emergency privately between you and Claire the power of
Yeah yeah
Qanon
To trying to convey
In order to drive
The Democrats to heal
Or whatever
And then when they don't you
He's going to tonight
On January 8th
Openly declared state of emergency be like I tried to let you guys
Just do this on your own
That's what he's
Build That Wall
He's going to
National Emergency
In order to build the wall in Alex's
Pumped about it
He loved it
Is is Alex super pumped about the years-long legal challenges that are going to come from
From this National Emergency
I have a long history of being
Look this is all this is all wack
It's all very well
Is this
On this episode
This is not about politics
There's a deeply religious field
Whether it's talking about the sword of Armageddon
Air Force
Or this next clip where he just can't
Like
Stop quoting country songs in order to demonstrate how right
With God
The mentally ill narcissistic
Froot Loops
The fill their hand
Stand the fact that they can't make this run
Like the old
Redneck anthem
Country Boy Can Survive
Cuz they can't starve us out
Make a shrine
These old boys were raised with shotgun
We say grace we say Amen
And if you ain't into that we don't give a damn
Which is
We'll take the lord's name in vain
Not perfect
God
Shop equipment
Call wife
That's why I know that
Save a Horse Ride a Cowboy
Beer for My Horses
Yeah I just it's a weird mental state
A little bit dumb
A little bit to demonstrate
He's in a very
A mindset that is
Tonight
It's going down
I got to talk about the end
Of the road
I got to talk about how right we are
God
But the amount of it
He's being very apocalyptic
The first half hour or so this show even
There is nothing here but preacher
Like this is almost a televangelist kind of thing
7 steel shelving
Broken
All the more scary that also includes
In fact I'm not scared of the Loveless
I'm scared of overheating and getting too aggressive
And just being as wise as a serpent peaceful to do
Goddess cubes Vengeance to wash
Time for vengeance is not yet
Thank God
What
Time of Vengeance will come
Vengeance is good
Saith the Lord it's mine
Quad
Soul
I guess
I don't like him
We come back up
Good luck
Bucked up
Weird
Revengeance
But it doesn't
Is fast approaching
It comes through and it will come through us
His righteousness
He's perceived
You're not even real enemy
Quite frankly
Hillary Clinton speech
Really wish somebody would get him a Bible with like large print so maybe you can read
Cuz he seems
Very uninterested in what the Bible said I would love it if there was a Bible that was Rewritten
Then maybe he might start to get better
It does go back
Do you like Alex has a very like
Weird
Version
Drive to
I don't think it's fair to
Call Main Street
I also don't think it's fair to call it in
But I'm really even
Leggett
Touches of gnosticism in there
There's touches of like overemphasis
The Old Testament
Which is no tragedy
It's just weird if you're a Christian because of the new
Christian in your rice
It's strange
I don't I don't understand but it's it's a bad place
Alex announces
He's going to
Trump speech live
Which at this point
Clear any mix
He knows what's going to happen
I mean the decision yesterday afternoon obviously we're going to
President trumps
Live Oval Office Speech at 8 p.m. central
9 p.m. Eastern 7 p.m. mountain 6 p.m. Pacific
National Emergency to shave America
Shuttle infowars.com
You'll see live coverage
Of that and
Another some band on Twitter
Tweet this image out so you can retweeted
So the people know that is coming up tonight
You thought there's going to be an ad
Having problems
And also it's clear he saying it repeatedly we know this is going to happen
Predicted
Somebody who lives in tomorrow's news today
You're going to be real disappointed that
Knowing what we know we know what happened
It is important to focus on this
This is Alex's editorial position
Entirely
This is going to happen tonight we've predicted it absolutely going at
We're going to be there covered
Zoe starts yelling about the dumb s***
It's pretty obvious
Yelp
Literally
They don't just lie they organize the line
They put out the talking points
Briefly Define
That are 50% off
Chris is the Christmas sale still going on 1000 Days of Christmas sale going on
Well into the next 3 years
Stuffed it look beat the thing here is
Tonight circuit that's an old backup situation
Was about Cinco de Mayo
Intentionally wearing American
Can Flags in order to
Recall exactly
Who is Kaizo
Spy fights
Cathay Inn
Instigate
The school has
Bi-Rite
People to wear certain kind of flag
On days like
It doesn't
Free speech
Or
Whatever other rights
It's exactly like saying you can't colors
Like when you're when you're co-opting the American flag to be a group of people
To commit violent
It's not an outright
Conflagration thing like this
Yeah that's the first thing
Second
You hear there is
Alex demonizing
Circuit
With Ally
Which is him
Complaining about
The Judiciary
Complaining about the court
And how they're really bad
Then he talks about the media
And how the media is really bad
Yeah hold on to those thoughts Hellboy
Come back on
Start complaining about how Mark.
Has been thrown off Facebook
Like a petty little move there as its way down the
Important
Honestly I think it would happen
Is that
If This falls in one of the every hour
She has like five
Minutes that don't go out on the radio
With some Tuscaloosa Channel Loretta doesn't matter
Reports their report by Mark.
In one of those no-man's-land but it's really important and what's going on here
Story behind it
Mark.
Being a
And you deserve everything that came to him
Has David he got thrown off Facebook
Because of something that was deemed
Here's a little taste
Of Mark Dice
Report
Houston
Girl
Antonio Brown
Sexually Jazmine Barnes
Here's the thing
Of Mark dice's report because why would I
Why would you
Crazy man
His delivery is insane
He looks like a lunatic
You'd like constantly
Like weird movement
We can just listening to the audio doesn't really do it service
Seems like a lunatic
Aesthetic style that he's going for
Maybe he knows that him just sitting
Is it good
YouTube something like that no one's going to be entertained by his dumb face
I watched Mark Dice videos spice to say it deserves every label it's getting
It is race
It's inflammatory
Pile of s***
From quality
Alex is playing a report saying that he's been kicked off Facebook
Mark just got suspended for a short time
I just got a little time out
So what I want to say
These f****** snowflakes need to stop exaggerating the repression
Number one
He was a real point I wanted
Works Chief complaint
Be that these
Black lives matter sjw we're only interested in the story because they thought it was a chance
To attack
But the same is true of Mark Dice
He's only interested in the story because it gives them an opportunity to defend white people and attack black people
You understand that are you saying there's some sort of irony to it
His only point is exactly what he's complaining about in these supposed other
Just weird
Seems like a bad starting point position but whatever
Also
An added problem is he has no idea what he's talking about
7 year old Jasmine Barnes was killed in a drive-by shooting
And family initially said the suspect was a white man in a red truck
This turned out not to be accurate as first hand accounts off in Ark
An official from the sheriff's
Department of gone on record saying
And this was a case of mistaken identity and
It was nothing
Also
The Killing
Also black lives matter activist
Just blindly blame White
People don't forget the story when the narrative didn't
That's what Infowars does
In reality Shaun King one of the leading figures of the black lives matter movement is literally responsible for tipping
Turn off the police that the shooters were Larry Woodruff and Eric black Junior not a white guy in a red truck
Because what I'm saying is that a prominent figure in the black lives matter movement went out of his way
Nerd help police find the actual Killers because he cared about the truth
Not just scoring points making
I don't understand
No he stopped caring once they found it once
John King received
The tip from one of his confidential source
He found out that it was two black men
And so we have corset on it and never told anybody
Complicated
Because after a mugshot was released of the original suspect
Posted a picture of a mugshot
And ask followers for Morgan
Information on
If they had any
There's absolutely led to some unmerited attention
Probable harassment
Being played
Directed towards
But it also literally led to the tip that solved
As shown put it quote
Estranged
I'm not sure we ever would have found the man who killed Jasmine Barnes
Have the initial conclusion not been so wrong
I was brought into the case to track a potential hate crime
Something altogether different
But I don't know that anyone would have ever come forward without the outrage
I don't quite know what that means or how I feel about it
But the initial outrage
Misguided as it was his what eventually helped us find
The Killers
So
If you're a white supremacist Outlet like
Infowars Mark Dice of the Daily Caller
You can focus on the part where Sean initially post
Send a picture of the wrong person
I made a mistake
Good faith and just ignore the later part where you followed through knowledge
Was inaccurate
It's all the game these assholes are playing
They simply don't give a fuk
About what's true
And people didn't
Forget about the story or the Tappan
Funerals on Wednesday
It was packed to the rafters
No one who is upset because the suspect is black
The people who organized Justice for Jasmine to Rally in Houston
I'm just calling it off now that there isn't a race angle to it
What's going on here and what Alex is putting forth in his defensive
Mark is deeply trouble
Cuz later in the video Mark starts throwing around some
6 about shooting
Alex starts doing some more of that too in
The statistics version of saying the n word
I'm what
No context that are solely meant to creative
If your
We've got over the murder stats
Manipulation
People like Alex can do to make them
I shall do whatever he wants
Fitness World
Just a small example of it
The 2017 the FBI's data shows that only six
51% of murders were even
Of the people
I haven't
You kind of have to also ask yourself a question of
Is it possible
That partial Target
Policing
Can Americans are black people
Are responsible for them being over-represented in the arrest
When 39% of murders aren't even
There's other issues possible vet
So many black people
Because they're only looking for black I'm not saying it is a piece of
The conversation
And there's even
More that we don't need to get a generalization as all of that
Play the fact
When you want to have a conversation about
Those are important
As opposed to
Just being like
Blacks kill so many more people
Statistic I'd like to share with you that Alex and Mark Dice have no interest
As of January 6th of this year there been 6 mass shooting
United States
7 people dead
In less than a week
That does not
Feel good
Also according to FBI
I think there's a more meaningful number to look at 3
Comparison
Queen band
And women
Cuz there's a large gap between different races and ethnicities
Justin Shearer bulk numbers
It's fairly close it's not
It's not
51% 49% or whatever it is
Have breakdowns at
Closer than these other parameters
A representative sample that can be used
Conclusion
2017 2932 women who were the victims of homicide
Of them
1733 were killed by men
That's a 90% of rocks
Conversely of the 4806
The two men who were the victims of homicide
Only 515 were killed by women
Which is about 10%
This is a statistic
Sickly very important
Information
That's very relevant
Again
This Loops back to
To the 6 mass shootings already in 29
Well most of them are still being investigated in
Information hasn't been made public at least one of them is definitively domestic violence
Situation where a man killed his wife
A twelve-year-old child then himself
Which is unfortunately a tragic pattern that we see
Play out over and over again
And that in turn Loops back to
Tulare Woodrow
The man arrested for shooting Jasmine
Floyd prior arrest for assaulting a family member and plead guilty in 27
13th of trying to choke a woman
The more pressing conversation
Have about murders in
Arthur up about masculinity and access to guns
The rest of it is irrelevant
Shadow puppet
People like Mark Dice now it's Jones used to justify there.
Deep-seated racism
Lambda buckshot
I'm so grateful
I was because we had that
Conversation of the past were there pulling out some rates bulshit
And so what wind up happening is we're like okay well if you want to play the race bulshit game
Great here's all the bug that
Goes against your butt butt
This isn't that
No that's not what this is you
Absolutely f****** nailed it and
It has nothing to do with their b*******
It's f****** dudes
Yeah
Subset of
If you look at it just from us
Statistical point of view
Do you have to wrestle with
The fact that
Almost all murders of women
Are done by men
A very slim number of
Murders of men are done by women
So what we need to do is convince women to start
Kelly Moore
Girl
I don't know it's stupid about this conversation
Intentionally
It's funny
Point out that Mark.
People only caring about this because they can demonize wifey
Black people
Then when you get behind a little bit
Every single piece of
It's f****** stupid
They're facing wild assertion
And misrepresenting
And that's the game that Infowars played
Because they are white
Francis Outlet
Of course
May he rest in peace
Also got an update tonight but better
I guess but he is a mess
Suspension
From Alex
He won't let him come back to work for a month because
Just want to
Being overstressed
You know what we got to go.
But it is cool that is like at least
Do we want to talk s*** on it but the idea of him
Can't come back to work
Keto salad
Your workers stand with labor even if that labor is f****** races
Exactly
So speaking of boring
Not cool
Naturalnews.com
He is a real dick
It seems to me
If I had to guess
Let's be really interested in Trump declaring a national emergency
Thanks
I think a lot of it relies on articles that Mike
Adams has written
I think he's done the legwork
Work on a lot of this
And Alex is just thrilled that he doesn't have
Too much work
Mike Adams
Ideas to the Forefront
And I'm taking that mostly
Where am I going
Preferably.
How is
Not only
In favor of an ashen
Call
He outright is calling for an authoritarian
Okay
I'm going to go
I'm really going to take a hard
This is a hot tub
I think that's a bad idea
And we should not
I'm with you on that I have reasons for it but I really don't feel like I should need to know
For that
Coming in here in just saying Trump is
Is great there for
He should be our dictator
Good reason for it
Doesn't
But he tried to make a jet
Justification rationalization
Use every Power of the executive
In order to defeat the Deep state or we lose America
Should declare martial law used the powers of the National Emergency to defend
America martial law and Rebellion
So this is going to be sort of the way that they get around
The complaints were making at the beginning yeah
Idea we are already already in this state
Declare this National Emergency
Start taking people's asses
In order to
All of the stuff that's been done already
Right right right so if I understand correctly good lie
Their argument is
We've already been in martial law baby so he better declare martial law
Find out where martial law started for explain why they have
Started
And be like actually always been going on
But here's the thing
Mike try
Mike Adams
Try
To pinpoint
The beginning of
It is not a good Ark
Iraq
Also the clip starts out
Really f******
Matanzas research
Obama
Tucker Carlson
Emergency override
Crucially I was going to repeat it again it's March 16th
I just posted a few minutes ago it's called The National Defense resources preparedness
Order it's on whitehouse.gov
In the opening paragraph
Himself as the commander-in-chief of the Armed Forces of the United States of America
Indicating
That he had planned
To use military force
To seize control over all resources in the country
Was
Absolutely
Wrote down his literal title
That's interesting I will get to that your
First things first Mike Adams
Search East most of the time doing things like lying about science naturalnews.com
Tom Segura
The Parkland shooting
Mike Adams is a no nothing
Piece of s*** of the highest order at can't say that strongly enough this guy is the worst
Executive order it's number 13 603
We can dispense with the idea that Obama released in order to declare martial law by declaring an emergency
Dear whatever the f*** they're too
All we need to do to understand what this executive order
Is about to realize
It was just an updating Bill Clinton
Executive order one
2919 four 1994
And even that was really just a refinement of the defense
Production Act
In order to help assure that the United
States had access to necessary materials for defense
Like aluminum as the Korean War start
Extension of executive order 8248
39 by f
Dior this is all just stuff that is fine too
Refined
Over the years we've been in martial law since
The 30
That's the wrong way to look at
Exactly what you
Is right there
Production
Jordan does his research
Government are almost always either building upon something that a predecessor.
There's a few things out right introduction
Wild new ideas
This is all about executive order was necessary updated Bill Clinton
Executive order and its really easy to understand
The old executive order needed an update
The Department of Homeland
Security did not exist in 1994
Existed
Independent agent
At the time I organization
Some of the language
You fixed in order to
To reflect the changes in government bureaucracy
That's almost all of the changes that were made by Obama
Executive order
It was just
Clarifying this
Different than they were
What would it have been
18 years earlier
So in response
In response to that
In response to the updating of line
Include these organizations
That were previously not included
And said we will overthrow you
Unless you do this
And then
Just
Didn't and they didn't
Hazelnut
Scotch
She's going to bring the military
Nonsense
First of all the order actually
By saying quote
President
United States
American defense production Act
And it's Mandarin
It's ordered as follows
So my clearly read the paragraph
Commander-in-chief
Has parts
How do you miss the part where explains that this is in relation to the defense production Act
Really skinny
That poorly or is he
It's obvious
Like it this isn't easy
Nelly misleading people they understood oh well this is just really
Let's go read the defense production Act of 90
We can understand where all this
From
So in reality this executive order and its predecessor serve an important role in making sure
The various departments
Government
Required an
And Ari
Powered by the ACT
Executive orders
Contracts
Make sure that the country has access to those
Materials that are needed
Beyond that because of the some of the language in the bill that's about spending
Consistent
The 1980
Emerging Technologies
Technology and independent
Research
Oh and just because Alex and Michael
Complete f****** idiot
It should be pointed out that on June 13th
2017 Trump
Invoke the defense production Act
In order to shift funding towards Franks
Movie quote space industrial base
A year before announcing
Space horse because he declared martial law in the thirties and then Trump
Finally seizing upon martial law
I really don't understand what is the f*** that they're doing all the stuff they're talking about like Trump is already
Foundational
This executive order that really just
Just a couple
Yeah cuz the goddamn Homeland Security Department 94
Even knows more about this news to f******
Clowns
Executive order that they're talking about as being evidence of Obama like setting all this up
State of
Did the Claire his emergency in order to undo
I don't know what good that would do but it sounds good too
This National emergency order to stop
Duration of National Emergency
And if nobody
Because there's everybody
Uses
Truly insane amount of power
He often does so in order to
Give the power back
The people dance
Key executive like
With with so many kings I remember them like dissolving Parliament to remember when they dissolve parliament
I can't think of a single inch
Listen to someone sort of trying to
Create
Pure into that being what they're going to do and then going
Bad
Africa just defined popular
It's a lot of bulshit but this is what Alex believes in what do you put in for
Real good notice they don't have more to talk about
They really do
Anyway that they do
But they were specific about executive order
Obama 2012/2013 14
15/16
To emergency
Those actions are still in place in operating at only under law
National Emergency
That's why you see the guy
Belligerent
Resources preparedness March 16th 2012
Obama put under martial law in 2012
That statement is written by Mike Adams
Vic should carry any other weight then this is the guy I'm talking to you
Actual state
Tanqr
Some sort of like
Research Mike f****** Adams
Hiiraan.com
Said that he's a researcher which is why
As a researcher
It's a bummer
Just a
Because In that clip
That we just played
Alex Express
Mentality
Really don't like
Comply in order to fight back against
A dictatorship
We must create a dictator
The best he's got right
Add that to me
He's thin everybody knows that in order to
Because that way you can defeat the imaginary one and we know which dictatorship is better the real one
Remember how great dictatorships are is compared to real dictatorships are really awesome if they're doing
Horrible things
Do you want a lot of people like that
So there is that
Is this next clip Mike explain
Put under this martial law
12:30
Reason
I didn't think that history was going to go the way it does
And then pay close attention
To what Mike is describing as what
He wants to
Because
I can't
Tell you how
F***** up it is
Shakira
An adult
These powers that Obama in
To president Hillary Clinton this was the plan and Hillary Clinton
A people to arrest which includes you
Myself as well
You weren't on that list you'd never be on anyone's list Mike
A 90%
I would say higher than that
No f****** idea who Mike Adams 99.99 no flakes
Really need to stop exaggerating their oppression
We were all supposed to be arresting a shutdown when Trump won the presidency
These powers to President Trump
Has been reluctant
Hillary Clinton
The Deep State under Obama
The power to destroy the Deep state
This is why they are so terrifying
This is what it's all about
Trump only
Operating
Inside universities that have become terrorist recruitment centers the mayor's
Focuspower
And then restore true Liberty and National Security
To our country
What we are demanding
Now
That is a perfect description of
I mean it's so insane that
People would especially
Being like
The paranoid guys be like what we need is
A strong
Executive evoking emergency
Powers in order to root versity the military
This is she's describing authoritarian
Bribing
Creation of a fascist so that was a great idea though and Chairman Mao did it
Awesome idea
How many other times has this happened it's always worked out really well for everybody
Great job of doing
Would you like me to give
300 more f****** examples to Mike f****** the child India Adams
It's nuts
To hear something like that
Especially after all
Apocalyptic nonsense
Earlier
Like these things
Supposed
On the show are really f****** scary
Because it's not
Like
Stuff
You know like this is an adult
Who has a platform
Legitimately being like they're openly
Encouraging
Authoritarian
At this point
They're demanding
And that is not a good sign
Up to this point
All I've heard is it okay if
We get the go-ahead
To kill all of our political enemies
Tells us to
So that
That is the start
And then
To finish
Is
We're going to do this in order to set up an authoritarian fascist rule
All the Browns out
I really don't think that's how it works
It's not
Oh absolutely
Manufacturing but this idea of illegal immigrants
It's coming at like this is to all of this
That's what's making
Which is another really important
Before we get into that
We need to
Really take a look
MC Abyss
And see how bad these ideas Mike Adams
Is espousing
On the show e.r.
Isn't he says something that's
It's the appropriate the military it's a constitutional for the military to defend the borders and also
Posse Comitatus
It prevents the military from acting as police on the streets of America
But it does not prevent military police
From pursuing
Enemies of America who are on American soil
Appointment
To arrest and seek out treasonous
Traders us soil there is no restriction against that
Because
Military police operating on us soil and domestic
Law enforcement
A hundred percent
Play against the Posse
Comitatus Act
What Mike is advocating for is literally how dictator Shore up our
We've seen it a hundred times
Simple example you brought up earlier after his stage
In January 2016 Turkish president
Called in the military police of his perceived enemies
Within nine months 110,000 people have been to
Approximately 50000 of them were arrested
Manufactured cool that even created that was a real coup and of course it just so happened that hundred thousand
The people who were his political enemies
I've got a hundred ten thousand people 7463 of them are members of the military
Terry / 10,000
Police officer
2575 or prosecutors
Judges disagreed with
Some even reportedly members of the
Journalist
179 media Outlets were shut down
Between the stage
To in the end of
The reason is important
Is that these people who were the
Target Savard wants Crackdown
Are precisely the people Alex and Michael saying Trump needs to go out
The entrenched globalist in the military and police forces
The globalist judges on the 9th circuit won't let you have a flag all the mainstream
American people
In a very real sense I mean this with no exaggeration
Alex Jones
Have now embraced calling for an outright authoritarian coup under the stewardship of their hero Donald's
This is a very different and much more
The beer situation then we saw a few weeks ago
And the massive escalation of the
We feel great
About what
Now
That being said I don't think that's necessarily
Translate to the real world
I think there's a very small section of Alex Jones
Audience that will be
U-Like severely negatively affected by
Right I'm just because Alex
Advocating
Mike Adams.
It doesn't mean the Trump is going to do that I don't want anyone to get that idea
But because we were show that
It follows out
You know we tracked this sort of
We know that this is been something that he's into for a bit
Yeah but the way their overtly talkin about it
He's a very marked
Change
It is very scary to
The idea that they feel comfortable
Because
They believe
Trump is going to declare this match
National Emergency
They can wear it openly
That they can say
It is a good idea
The military police Roundup potential
Political enemies
That is really f****** scary
Because that means
Did you shoot ever goes that way
They're going to be the
First people
Cheerleading
Of course
They're going to be the people who are on
On the radio in Rwanda
Right now
Oh my God now that we know Trump's going to do it I'm so glad it's finally okay for us to say that we need to
Have a racial cleansing and that includes
Hey if you're a white person but you support those races that we don't like guess what your race-traitor you're one of them
I mean it is it is a like gentleman speak kind of mom
The map drops
If you been meaning
For a long time
It it's just
I can't I can't legitimately can't imagine
A scenario wherein
Even if someone had like less politics that I agreed with
Advocating
Military police
Conservative
Even the alt-right
Even Nazis
But you know I'm saying like even if I heard that there's no way that I would be like
Triumphantly
Ikea
Imagine getting place and what you realize when you see Mama
They don't need to
Get to that
That's their place
Yep
There are there are so many times with
So many of the rules in the Norms that existed within Congress prior to
Baby
Mitch McConnell
Dumb f*** face
Time machine
So many of these rules are in place because everybody kind of implicitly got
That if we change these rules
For us
There will be a pendulum swing back
And those rule changes that we
Can then be used
42r d'etre
The pick your spots first democracy and Republic
And with these guys there is something that is
That is now explicit
Which is that
When you talk about one side or the other
Only one side is
Literally using these rule changes
In bad faith
To harm
It does seem
It ends so so they kind of don't care about the pendulum swing
Because why would they know that if the pendulum swings backwards
They're not going to do to us what we want to do to them well and they also kind of understand you do you swing a
Pendulum hard enough
It just gets lodged it broken or whatever you know
Even if you use a pendulum metaphor
One Direction
You end up with broken political system that doesn't
Fix itself it doesn't swing back the other way
The exact same thing about and screaming
Talking about 4 years right
Is essentially the same thing that is the dichotomy
John Waterman
Wednesday
Kerry Cassidy
Please show and on his own blog
On Kerry Cassidy show
That's Alex
A year ago
Not bringing up that he hates
The Jews
Just being like certain groups certain groups
He talks about how it's
Exterminate
Blah blah blah
I'm not saying
Metaphor
A year ago there was the couch nastua there was this
There was more of a
It wasn't this over
Right now
Is directly calling
What brings
He doesn't give a
Never gave us
It's it's
I mean
Yeah caring about the consequences
It has fallen
He does not care about any of
We could talk about how like
You know earlier in the year we had like him saying that rex-84 is
Posse Comitatus doesn't matter send the military to the border of this.
We can talk about all that stuff
Most people look at that and they wanted clown on Alex
For being a
Right
And I'm not interested
Not necessarily I don't think we have been
Metal though
May be pointed out
From time to time
I think
The people mist
The point
What it is
Is those were always
Performative aspect
Of what he
Was doing
What he was doing
And is still doing
Is defending White
Defending
The status quo
Of a
White Centric
Chauvinist
This normative world
Yeah those are the insta
Fat weird liquor
Vaguely religious so long as it justifies whatever works out.
What he's always done with all of these narratives
Is prop up an
Apologize for
Terrorism
And now he's abandoned
The mask
Of caring about tyranny because
The guy who's going to bring in the Tyranny that he want is in favor of all of those things he's a f****** chauvinist
The racist
He doesn't like
And he's a rapist
Skateboarding doesn't want to move right
Does alarm in the military or whatever sprocket is surround himself.
Who cares about
Litigating it personal
That would be had
So
He knows that
Dinos
It's a small Revelation that we've already made with
If it is
He is comfortable now
Because his guys don't
To protect
If he wants protect it
But it's just crazy to see that it is
Not just about
These little things
It's about everything Noah career is based on a lie
We talked about it on a previous episode where we were discussing that kind of hypocrisy angle
And it really isn't hypocrisy.
Is
I'm afraid they're going to do what
I'm afraid they're going to do that to us
That's what I'm afraid of tyranny
Not because tyranny is bad because we're going to get
Literal comeuppance
The right kind of
Is grapes good in the wrong kind
Exactly
It's that it's late right
I think it's worth it just little. You're having that
Discussion
Because I think it's a people who aren't
Understand it
What
Does
Misunderstand
Anime
Oh look at this you're a hypocrite cuz now you believe this when you said that
It's a much more Salient attacking
Getting much worse
To say
Oh what this does is it reveals that
You never cared about that but would you care about
And what was motivating your rhetoric
That's motivating it now I think it's a holistic
More
Reasonable
Way to look at things
I don't know I don't know if it helps anything but it's reality
And it's so important that over and over and over again to make this point is that Alex has the weakest link
Lincoln this right-wing propaganda chain
So many people in this right-wing propaganda
Pretty much support
Caldwell Parish fair enough
But but
In the right-wing propaganda so many people on Fox News
Smoked would say
Not in the same words
But in a far like in a far better couch language
Essentially the same thing
Let Mike Adams come on and say the military
Police as a constitutional role.
Potential enemies
Stuff like that
It is directly antithetical to
So many of the very ideas
The freedom and it's the sort of thing that has always LED down
Pastore
Centralized
Control oppression
And all that s***
Tucker Carlson wouldn't have Mike Adams on to stay back.
But
Trump did do that
Tucker Carlson would defend it
Probably not allowed to
But so far allowed to do that
Be as weak
As this Obama's executive order put us under martial law Trump is just
Yeah that's
Petexec
Like all that stuff is so easy
The track down
It's not even Alex's normal stuff or it's like
If you got to go
Eco science
Yeah yeah
Gone down a little bit of a road
I'm not mad about that
To remember
Is it Alex's certain
Uno's
Tonight
Emergency
East County Clare
We know he's going to do what he's going to do
Throughout the app
So earlier
We're sort of bucking at Mike Adams talk
I'm about like who is the America
You're talking about
Exquisite
You know he's just kind of makes
We reach real America and real America supports Trump
Supports a declaration of a National Emergency if that's what it takes
We are in a war to the claret
Disassemble a tablet
America and this war on America has been
Going on since 2008 model h
.
Nothing that makes me feel better about Alex at the time for vengeance isn't out
Because in this clip
A mere hour after that he sang the globalist of drawn First Blood they're fair game
Which I think
You could interpret as in being like
Kind of feels that way it
It's really f***** up and then Mike Adams
Why is that a 2012 dumbfucks
Is it just because of Obama
I don't know if you noticed
Did you notice that could be part of it
Oh we're in a war now
You're I don't know I don't know what you wanted I don't know what you want to call it if not
Let's call it Christian Bale
Colonial
White identity
We have been fighting a war
In this country
Since it started
Applebee's
It's been against
Women is Finnegan
People of color it's been against every possible minority that isn't White
It's been a good f****** Catholic
You guys
And the only fightback that anybody has ever had is been like
Guess what we're making your life better to you dumb f***
There's been a shifting of alliances people who have not been on
It's not like a consistent one group throughout the entire time
DxD
Like
More or less history of
Exclusion in ink
Struggle throughout the
The entire time
You can kind of boil stuff
Minimizing
Real serious
Like chattel slavery
That was driven by exclusion
Include
Catholics in the Irish
Stop lights
Exclude
From the group that's allowed to have access to
To power exact
Power access
Influence money
Capital
All that sort of stuff
Insta edit even talked about like worker
Explosion
Has always been
Sort of.
Define line
Of what
This
And Alex's
Exclusion
And I don't know I don't understand
How anybody
Looking at the past
Through history
Kim Kim
Honestly think that that's a good Gamble
Like I don't understand why people think
That would work out well it always is
Exclusion is always wrong
Even though it sometimes
Go back to that Ebola episode that we did
Wrong things
It's just a a sort of
New jerk reaction
But if you ever start
It's the wrong thing
It'll be looks poorly
Alex
I mean f****** Apes that have destroyed the one place that allowed us to exist
So
Of course we're going to continue this right because we have these f****** Apes continue
Wake me up there not good
My dad is God bless you great job is going tonight 7 central eastern for
Emergency
How old is going to end
Call man
She's so excited though
Yeah but they're excited because
Authoritarian
Resume he's in favor of being implemented
It's crazy to be obvious
Like what
Mental state
Pieces in here
That's what that
So now it's funny that you takes
Tour for the last
Hour of his show and talks to this guy who runs a site called Black
Pill.com
I don't know if you saw my God
If you agree with him
Particular format
I think it's
Different
We're just real quick I don't mean to
Dismissive
Complaint although I am
I think also that genre kind of
Itself out I think that's why you
Remakes of all of the like Dave the
So you just be all these remakes that the people who explored those ideas
Really well
I know that they're probably examples of newer movies that
I'd like to take on
An interesting Twist on stuff
Smith making a red state
Directions
Red-state
Also
Who did he think started
Lego who does Hebrew
Post-apocalyptic movies of the 1950s were started by conservatives
Do you think the f****** Godzilla was started by Conservative Business
The greatest
The world is f***** up movie there's ever been
This is a minor point
I just I would I would bring my rebuttal
I don't think there's much more interesting
Territory to cover I think we've done the
Society falling apart are people going to get along are they going to fight that's why Survivor you can only watch like three or four season
How many seasons of it
I have more tolerance
Theme song
Maybe I also kind of enjoyed Jeff Probst
Really certain charms
My buddy Nick
Had the best idea in the world
Getting on Survivor
Kidnap Jeff Probst make him the authoritarian dictator
We go to tribal
We all vote
Jeff Probst
I got the first love you like
Alright guy
Keppra
Hey we're still doing a show can we get can we get the producer in here
Would they redo it
But they might
My point is
Tunica gift the funny guy
Is criticism so far
His soft pitbull shepherd box
I wonder what your problem there is
Anything about
Normalizing
Real quick
First is the
Is liberal propaganda flytrap
People who identify
Is lgbtq and interracial relationship
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
What's what's next
What's next damn book I love a nice
You know I look
I can't come up with the genre
What the f*** you liberal ideas liberals convinced
Captain Kirk to kiss a black woman
If such propaganda
That's crazy to me
If you want to make a point
I'd encourage you not to
Cuz it makes you sound like
You don't want races dating
I like
The old movie
Where you weren't
Going to see kind of interracial touching
Unless it's violent
Whiteman
And white women
Kissing both of them within their perfect gender roles
Have to turn this culture into something that has more
Flavor in everything I just want
.
So from that criticism I gathered
Like just from
I meant second from a
You're apparently against interracial relationships of lgbtq
Brooks brother on Syfy is
So
To talk about how like all the bad guys are
Are white
I just did the jack off motion
Website.com
But you want to blackfield
Dot-com took me awhile to find the page
You look at it
There's problems
Give the Articles and videos he's made with titles like quote no white guilt
Or quote why they want to replace you
Which literally argues
The people in country
Trees with more oppressive governments like Argentina have lower eye
Accused
Exhausted
The powers-that-be
Make everyone closer
In order to install
Government
Beyond that
We spent a bunch of time covering her Pizza
Is totally real and of course the Seth rich
Conspiracy uzalo
Do that naturally
He's a good fit for Alex's a fellow nut
Unless you want to bring up one of the posts
Somebody year ago that he made
Particularly funny
Which is just titled quote Bill Cooper warned about Deeds
Years ago
Did Alex
Cuz he loves
Encouraging
Racial other
God creating
Depression-era
Throughout his work
That's what he's doing
That's the entire purpose
Anyway I don't have much
Perspective this guy think
Kind of sucks
Is interviews actually really boring
But
Sandra Bullock
Is a an
Bird Box
I didn't know that cuz I had
Haven't seen it
Do you know
Something about Sandra I don't know anything
What's that
Do lizards that's a running joke that we
For a while
Delivered poorly
Bring it up because
Take this opportunity
Really just
Custom swing
But she is a monstrous pig total PR was stabbed in the back is a psychopath
Monster
The soccer film
He knows where he's at
Neo-Nazi Jesse sheet divorce
Affected
Adopt
Did minority
Like I don't know it seems
Brick redundant and kind of overly simplistic to assume that's part of it
I know that these friends
Jesse James
Is a hundred percent
At least
Pretty cool with not
Alex
The two of them
Information to Jesse James has told him
If you know enough about Alex you know that what he's reporting autism
The guy that she divorced
Was talking a lot of s*** to me and I know secret s*** I know secret stuff from the jilted lover
If that is that is in source
Jesse James the only reason she divorced him because it's bad PR to be with a nothing
Do suggest that witch
You know what
Fan stick around a stripper
Really care
She has like real.
Inside knowledge
It's just
Just like p.m.
Without any
Got the peace offering
Whatever few episodes episodes
This just turned into a gossip
Now it's a apocalyptic
Authoritarian
For an episode
To have so much with
The most
You know you had all this really scary stuff
Clear
I don't know what you want to call him
Biggity
Richard Roeper but hate
Review of the movie was
What the f***
Man liberal
Yeah yikes so this is brings us to
The end of episode on the
Powder Elite Owen Shroyer takeover on the War Room
Gets his bearings about him
And comes back
With a live report for the live coverage of trump
Obviously
Declaring a state of emergency on broadcast TV everybody knows that that's what he's going to do
Heatedly throughout the show
The beginning of this
Episode live
Very boy
But about to
Call Nora cell
Alex frames what's going
To happen
The president
His first Oval Office address
Is it always a special dress tomorrow we don't know if it'll be a lobster.
Protection one came through
The shed
We are in
National price
We are in a national
Prices
Do we declare a crisis
Is it a bargaining chip
Is that what this is
Is this a
Bargaining chip
So the Democrats stop holding the shutdown government
Anyways
Tonight by Pelosi and Schumer
But he needs it for the Emergency because again we clear Obama
Executive order 2012
But at least a dozen more the truck
Named after that
Martial law
Dictatorial power
Whatever agency in groups
Groups 12
You've made it clear the only way Trump isn't
Staying at the national bird
It comes out in and out of the deal that exactly
Through a dick on the table
Pelosi and Schumer cowered in fear and you know that they would if he didn't
Be back out because you know they have a history of backing out of feels unlike the very person who had a deal in place to continue funding
The government and then because of dickwad like Alex Jones and Sean Hannity
Then went back on
You know you can't trust Pelosi
Where's all that great loclivin
Great Clips
Confined of trump talk
I'm going to shut down the government
He literally said it is going to be my fault I will accept
The other ones are dragging their
4 ft
I just need stress because
No
After the fact
Declare National
Just spouted a bunch of bulshit
How do you know that I didn't watch it because
Cuz I'm not watching that it was all just a manipulation of the
Reality of the
On the Border trying to make
Is listing
People who have been killed by immigrants yeah
White nationalist
Display
He was absolutely just a like
We need to be afraid of these people flooding into our country
The crisis of the Soul
He was appealing on like a
Hypothetically moral level
Like trying to
The moral
In terms of like we need to do this
He appealed to the opiate crisis and like
Truck off this would help with that at all I know who
Wrote that speech
Steven.
Surprisingly enough
Yeah I just feel that way
Now that's an old reference
So Alex gets
This next clip
I legitimately
Is soda
Disqualifying
Alex has no idea what he's
He's talking about
No one has ever used a National Emergency set Ronald Reagan
Limited one that use National Emergency to order the air traffic controllers
Dollar planes crashing faultless Kylie said
Does all 50 states
We're gone
He said no you get back to work I'll have your address
Now Congress
Here's the deal
Out of a hundred percent wrong about the story and it really illustrate
A deep lack of understanding
On the topic
He's covering
In August 1981 the professional air traffic
Controllers organization
Found themselves on strike
Across-the-board pay raises
And more lenient to the hours of their work weeks given the 24/7 nature of their job
Controllers walked out and negotiate
I'm going August 3rd wasn't going to give
Brigandine the strikes be illegal
And threatened to fire anyone can go back to work
Within 48 hours
11000 controllers
And Reagan stood to his word inspired
Even going so far as to put lifetime bans on them being rehired
Unfortunately the scabs who didn't stand
Their fellow workers
We're enough proximately 80%
Commercial Tower
And the freight industry ran it.
I'm just like that
A dick head president
Crippling blow to labor rights
Country
On full display in front of national media everyone so exactly what would happen to organized labor
The power of the government
They will be threatened and those
Fall in line be fired fine
A potentially band
And for life from their profession
Federal employees don't have the right to strike
Thursday did he should just fire them
Based on the taft-hartley ACT
This had been done previously
And most people believe that the circumstances ever came up a modern president
Be so shity
It's actually summarily Fire Federal Employees were demanding better working
But those people had never met
Many consider the event to be one of the most important in the history of uni
Boston
And the moment that ripple effect
Tons of Indus
Just those fired workers along
But at no point did Reagan declare a national emergency
How to inflate the idea of of a strike
And this government shutdown and this National Emergency narrative
What's going on which all of them are in no way related
But in doing so what are you saying is that no other president has
Has declared a state of emergency
Except Reagan
Which is absolutely not true
T3 people voted on the Federal Reserve
Emergency declared
Reagan didn't declare National Emergency
National
In effect
MacArthur
Nearly all of them 25 out of the 28
Freezing on the property
The people involved various regimes we've not like
More people were working to disrupt
Peace processes in countries
Like Belarus in 2006
Or the Western Balkans
Exactly
You'd expect to see
There's one from 1994 about the proliferation of weapons of mass destruction
There's one from night from 911 about terrorists
You can make whatever argument you want about these National emergencies for or against
Duck ready to talk about that I'm willing to hear both sides were probably very unnecessary
There might be a good hey I'm not again
What's the National Emergency about the idea of the
The proliferation of weapons of mass destruction
I also think we
We should be subject
The conversation
Have
But
You can't make a coherent argument that their secret
Or that somehow by declaring them
Any president has gained the ability to
Declare martial law
I'm not saying this to be a dick
That is literally with Alex Jones and Larry Nichols were arguing in the run-up to
The 2016 election
Did Obama was going to declare state of emergency
Evie FEMA provisional government would kick in
And then he become king
I just so no one thinks I'm making that up
Here's them saying
Call Antoinette Obama was elected we were thank God racist
Everything in and then shop
To make raised
Water issue now than the day the man came in
If you don't believe he is
The riots get activated out of Cheers Bar people don't understand when these Blackbob start run
Shooting wildly into the neighborhood people are doing this country
Call up and say please in the government and stop it protect us
We will call for the federal government to come in and protected we will call for the civil emergency
We'll be the ones asking because
Talk about years ago
Another program
Stop.
Guillain-Barre was using if you'll recall Alex Jesse Jackson
Supposed to start
Riots in five major cities
And once I get the computer forever
We stopped it by making it public one now
We've got problems
The folks all of this that's going on is about
The thing that's going on today
You have to be so careful
So very careful McDonald's anytime
You know
Will you kill somebody
Total chaos happens
All bets are off
Sitting photo
When this thing collapses they become king or queen
I forgot to mention that Larry Nichols is also a huge racist
This is nonsense.
This is been there editorial position
Forever gif
Idea that
The president
Introduces
A national emergency
Regency weather
Misconception
Race riots
They're worried about
Whatever the situation
Created
Creative Nashua
But that is
That is
Skip
It's not so hard it's not he has no idea where are all the
National Emergency
Place forever
He literally said that Regan's the only
Yep that's crazy
Look
Here's the thing
We talked about this already
The idea that this is not an invalid
This is a
What it's always been
This is The Logical endpoint
Right right
You just be a glimpse
Through this that the curtain
Or whatever and you see
The Wizard of Oz is a race
More or less
The idea of anything else was just window-dressing
It really was
Yep
So please understand
This episode
To right now
Is a direct me or the night Alex stayed up all night
Watch WikiLeaks
Anniversary live stream
But he thought was going to be the night of Hillary's downfall
All that evening Alex. That is Magic
Smok
I was going to arrive and whisked Away to a post globalist
In Annapolis.
He said things but indicated
Rodger both headed
What was in those leaked emails
Unlike did not arrive that
In exactly the same way
You can easily set Alex's expected
Deus ex machina
Trump on January 8th
He thinks
After that
Who's going to be
In charge of the
Change of emergency as then it's genocide
And
You let you much slip that night when he was watching the song
Him and Rodger Stone let too much slip
Wilder
Preparing
For Trump speech
On January
Rodger Stone
What do you predict tonight here in about 15 minutes
I think the president's I do think he is going to exercise his executive power
I do think he's going to appropriately declare an emergency
This is going to make the shift into high gear there will be
Because the president
Is bringing crime is bringing drugs is bringing disease
They favor a remix
In order to change.
I see the president
Going for broke tonight
Rodger that's what my gut tells me and my guts never wrong
So what is it Mike Adams
Earlier just
Really
Define
Authoritarian
Power
Rodger Stone
Direct
Describe
Dwight fashion
The idea of
These Outsiders coming in bring Crime and disease
Don Trump Jr with his
Sweet talkin about
Isuzu walls keep you safe
From the animal
Stuff like that
Humanizing ideas
All they bring is this horrible disease when they
Statistics don't match that at all no
I'd like reputable science
Back that up no
Nothing
This is all the editorial position of
Infowars witches of white Nash
In describing the shifting of the elector
All that sort of thing
Devoting quotient
All that stuff is
All the fear of
Loss of white
And that is what
Important they believe
Did Trump
Is going to declare the state of emergency
That will cry
Create
And it's like Bond villain
A certain extent
In Rodger Stone
Directly describes why
Nationalism white supremacy
There's a little slicker than to just save the same with it Mike
Blackpilled guy
But he still gets a little
Roblox
The idea of we're going to protect
The electorate
But not too far off from Fox News in general
But they think
Any interesting things that I take away
Is that they don't know shitt
But you know I'm saying
Like it's interesting that they are so G
None of them have any inside information
They are way off guard by the idea that Trump is just
Just going to do a speech being a dick
He's not going to change anything
He think he is
And that means that our
Knows nothing
That means Rodger Stone.
Have any inside information
Everything is posture
But is posturing
Possibility
Hope
We're living in a time where old white people
Trying to
Hey I mean
In
I guess
Is the metaphor of their conception of what they think they're doing
They're trying to take
Like everybody's playing
Everybody's having a good time and it felt
Probably don't
Want them to know absolutely
The later generations
In their argument of course
If you continue with this authoritarian white nationalist fascist
It's only going to accelerate our impending death by climate
Like everything they're doing everything they're doing is like
It's going to be awesome to live in an authoritarian dictatorship because I'll be dead in 20 years
And only my children will have to deal with the real Fallout
Yeah you're right
So
Rodger goes on
You want to talk about how Russia is a bunch of nonsense
Respond
Like a rock
Also
Lawyers
Man they're bad but they're so bad
Redemption
People were able to find out what was under those black bars
And it turns out.
He had given
Russian spy
Allegedly
Which is a cry so like there's that stuff inside paint Rodger
Years you guys ran a business together
Took over
Not good great
So
Really wants to muddy the waters
About
With manafort Don Jr
She was a lawyer
Connections
And that's all good
Deflection
F****** weird
If I bring some
Personal stuff
Showing that he doesn't
I'm actually understand
Of the woman
Fusion GPS before and after the Trump Tower meeting
You advised me to go public I haven't yet I have told the FBI info
Dollars
Fusion GPS is actually a Central Intelligence Agency
Interfacing with the Russians to trip Russian
Espionage
Ticket defense department funding
Officially tried to shut me up
Really
Associative Factor doing this thing use this
They're using Russian networks that got in the US
It really work for the left
To try to set Patriots up to just talk to them or take money from them
Didn't claim this whole
Say crocheting is real
Is that the clintons others that sold us out
Directions to the factory
Russian woman who quite frankly
She was running around trying to get the guy
I'm having sex with all these Republican
Didn't talk to her thinking she was an Asian
Cho
This is all they've got
Quite shameful the Russian intelligence
My friend
There's a little bit of chauvinism misogyny in their butt
Rogers talking about
Alex starts yelling
Maria
Yeah
Different differences
Alex doesn't have a grasp on the facts
It shouldn't surprise us
No it's trying to say
Set you up
Have you tried to reach
Repurpose that artist where you got talk to buy Russian
Like this is a this is a good
That rooster phobic
Kind of Russian
But this is something that the Russian intelligence agencies
Often do which is say
We don't even have the capabilities of doing that people are trying to say that we're doing that
We couldn't even do that at all the time we talked about how low is there
Beautiful Central Security
Powerful strategy
But again it doesn't
Approve anything simple deflectors conversation
About this lawyer who had just been
Because he wants to
Talking about
GPS
So that gives a speech
It's just a bunch of.
Is complete
And so immediately afterwards Alex realizes
I thought he was
Starts
They threatened the budget of behind-the-scenes economic implosion your name and three that does
Predicted for the shot kind of figured he was going to do it
Things change and he says okay
But the Border
There's Potential Threat of sovereignty that's real
Excuse
Emergency under law
To get rid of all the globalist executive orders has Obama crap
No I'm not going to get from a total pass
Given 30 days from now
This hasn't worked out
Reverse executive orders
I'm going to think that they ever compromised Trump
He does this all the time these like fake
Remember 30 days prior to whenever the date is
Jill just conveniently
Play forget to cover the usmca
Getting ratified
Forget that was a Line in the Sand
It's that it's b******* but that's slick rationalization
It's just so
He spent the entire days and I know this is going to happen it's going to happen
Like letting there
Watch for
Authoritarianism show in preparation for it happening and then
Yeah yeah
Admits he was wrong
But also
Just a few moments ago
Trump is going to declare a National Emergency in his gut is never wrong
I think the earlier in the episode you did say that
We predicted this was all coming
This is what needs to be done we're not fetishizing
Civil emergency charging the power of executive that's literally
All you're doing
Especially now that he is not instituted one
And that kind of suggests that we're still not going to be okay if we keep
Authoritarian
We can only ask for an authoritarian
After it's already
Happen
Compromise
He also
Is drunk
He's not drunk in the same way that we seen him so many times
But there is a bit of it
Yeah it really demonstrates
How many words is he got into say
Not too many
But
Comes in
He starts trying to make
That we need to make our support of
Really public
He's trying to make
Alex doesn't understand
And then start
To go out in public and wear our colors with pride
Because there's a big con right now there's a big sigh up on the American people
Trump supporters are in the minority Trump supporters donate raulito.
The only way if you are as my daughter narrative
Copy shop
On my way here
I can't even go to the gym anymore without
Your high school and college students recognizing me and saying how much they love infowar
Propaganda
Anton Yelchin
My oldest daughter I got three daughters
My daughter
Come pick me up
20 girls
And their parents
Pictures of
Girls over Saturday
And they were
I was like yeah I've been I got home late I'm going to watch TV show my wife
Come take photos
Yes
Like that was
Reduce this idea
Like we need to counter the idea that no one likes drop by wearing Trump shirts around
I meant
He did sort of introduced the idea of popularity by talking about
I go to the go to the gym
Take a pictures of everybody knows me
Yeah
It's not like a
It's not helping the conversation
Focusing on him
Which is also
What he does all the
Yeah it's very much that drunk conversation that you had with somebody in a bar before where
For sure that's just like this completely unrelated things exactly change the topic
Million percent from whatever it was you were talking about
But yeah
Call son
There's one more clip from
January 8th
Freaking out
You know
They didn't go the way
Clearly he doesn't have any
He's expressing
In this club
Get out loud
He's expressing where to go now
I have just shot my load
In this
The earlier show and
The ramp up to Trump
And then Trump speech
Disappoint
Didn't do what I said it was going
Everyone's going to know that
And the only
Is Rodger Stone
And so he tells
Bags
You told me two years ago band was bad
I said no so you didn't so I feel guilty
You said the general
We're globalist c********** excuse my French
Who's the new enemy
Well
Front right up until the last minute
Physically out of the building you were the first to say
Oh I think he is his job
She doesn't give him an answer at all Alex's begging
Tell me what hate
I need you to focus Mia
In a Direction
Because this is been a f****** disaster
And that's kind of
Implies that Rodgers to blame
Or Alex
So you better f****** pick up the pewter hold me he was definitely going to declare a national emergency
Now I'm going to give you credit for being right about
Righteous anger at you
To tell me where to go cuz I
Yeah
That's that
That's pretty bad
That is very much a man
Immediately recognized
I'm in over my head and I don't know anything
I thought he had an inside pipeline
He doesn't know she doesn't know a goddamn thing
Earlier in the day
I didn't have an eclipse
Episode
There's an article in zerohedge
Wasn't
I like zerohedge but it's
Yeah
Other news source
His world
Had it right
He had it wrong
He's best friends with
Trump supposed
Best friend
The broadcast
Some more
Talking about
He is sleeps at all
Comes back to work
On January
Thursday
Is how
He comes to the tail
And this is super weird
A couple problems
Constitutional lawyer really smart cookie founders
Chubby joining us
But bottom line
He is advocating his responsibility
No he can't
Crazy declaration
Trump is no longer president
She's giving up this
Power talk about how like he's going to give him some time
29 days
That's a strong of languages
Come out of him
The front
Yeah
Realtor
I think there is some sort of actual
Narrative progression
I've been wrong in the past
Just walk things back
I think there is a kernel of
Resentment
And disappoint
Because I think
When you fly too close to
To the Sun
You end up
Realizing
What your wings are made of
That sort of idea
Flew too close to the Sun Alex has white nationalist wings
Fed also fascist
Authoritarian
Too close to the Sun
Buy-in
Encouraging
And endorse
The hypothetical in action
Yeah
He did that
Because of the bad info
Rodger Stone
Pissed off about
I think
On some level he
He showed ass
He's got two recliners
And what does he do
He starts hanging out with
F****** oathkeeper
I haven't heard them a ton on the show I haven't heard the roads of town on the show I don't remember hearing it even in a
Any of the episodes
From 2015 that we were listening to
The only time I know him from Alex Jones is rhetoric
Yeah yeah
During the Tea Party Time
Proclaim that
From Glenn Beck
Yeah
Tumi
This is so fast
Because what do you do
When
That all goes bad
You go back
Asbestos
As you can tell
Similar
Spiritual verse
Version of it
That you had
It's like going back to an a
It's it's
It's like she represents the
Militant
Very
Close to violence
White
Supremacist version of Ron Paul's
Yeah which is
Closest Alex
Can get back to
Home
And that is what he
Yearns for
In the day after this
Disaster is livestream
National Emergency
And then the only way he can really deal with it when it doesn't happen
Is to blame
Threatening
Collapse the economy
But then also saying like well
We loved
Trump
But he has failed
That's the only
That's the only narrative I can see moving forward
He probably would love to
To do that
With his old riding partners
You f******
Do you think that
Kind of signals are getting away from Rodger Stones like
Palisade
That failure of Rodger Stone
Steam pretty big one
It's babe
Yeah I think I think
I hope so I don't know
I never one who likes to make predictions
I'm fine with analyzing what's be
Yeah
When it comes to that sort of stuff I always feel like
I think it's going this way and then
Look on the other
Far be it for me to say that but it does feel
Like that
That feels appropriate
Alex is trying to get away from
Whatever Rodger is brought into
It was life
I'm going to stop doing this back-channel b******* and I'm going to get back to my roots which is
White people getting together in murdering
It was better back then for his business better for all that
Facebook for that it's true
I feel like there might be a
This might be
Be the signaling of that part of the
And that we practice
Acoustic guitar
Save one more clip
Can imagine
More clear
You're a white person in Germany that's not allowed
Flipping it now
That's exactly
John Waterman
Talking about on his blog
From a week ago
About
Germany being the second days
There is no
Difference
Between their Reddit
He's saying that
White people in Germany
Are to be extinguished
Virginia to be gotten rid of
Nothing
The people who are more overt
The different word
No difference
Information
Let's f****** fly This Plane home then
DeLand
Alex Jones
Try to do some
Two-day span
But what are you trying to
To do was
Reveal
The Apocalypse
The revolution
Armageddon
Japanese war the war
Literal War
Direct
Vengeance filled War
Between the globalist
Is nationalist
Armies
It was going to
Beset off
By Trump
Coming on are in the Oval Office
Office
Pointed out
Replace
For war in the place for National Emergency and security
He was going to come
I have a backlash
But the Patriots were right
Trump's military
We're going to clear out all the bad people in that
The Judiciary in the media was going
Proclaimed all that stuff
We are not f****** stupid
So we see
What do you talk
Authoritarian power
Yeah
Breakside
He doesn't go his way
And I think he realizes
I think he has to
Because this isn't the same as this year
It's not the same because in those sober Morning Light
He is sticking
Intuit
Well there's that
That's the big difference that I'm taking away from that is certainly a different
Yeah well
When you play the clip from the next morning and it is
A continuation
Escalation of his previous
Where is drunkenly getting angry and screaming about
Text morning he's like
This morning is a
You know last night I was like I'll give him some time I'll say all of this stuff
And this morning I'm
Thinking about it and I continued
Thinking about it
And I don't think he's going to
Come back my way and that way
Means to me what I can soft from
That those differences of response
These events
Is there
In the prior event with bombing of Syria
What got him off that ledge got him back in pocket
Was the exact advise that
He no longer
Exactly
Back into the
The fold before
Is the thing that
He's like
That is what got me to say that there was going to be a f****** National
Yeah I was wrong
Public
And that's Rogerstown exactly
Yeah
I don't know I don't know what this pretends but I would love it
Because
I think there's much more
Interesting fertile territory
For Alex outside
Now yeah
How much it matters
Because it's true colors
Shown
He want
Someone like Trump
And authoritarian white nationalist
To create a state of emergency
Unlimited executive
Power can be
Express
In order to get rid of
Oakley disagree
He's with in various
Media judiciary
Mayor's govern
That's a wrap
So I mean it doesn't matter what he pivots to that's in his heart
Yet you know in the same way that we went back in
Clip from
Take the nineties when he's talking about the leaderless resistance
Louis beam
You dis is in his heart
White Nash
Nationalist
Ideology
Always been apart
Of his rhetoric
No matter how much is math
And now we also know
That
Strong desire
For that to be brought in
Through
Authoritarianism
Fascism
Strong arm tattoo
That is also probably always
I don't care what he does
Although just
From a
It wouldn't change my feelings on it but I got to be more interesting to
To disentangle
Yeah
Cuz because
Of all the stuff we've gone
So much of that couching of his real authoritarian white Nash
Similar
To so many people who are left
Engaged
They're talking
Come from all of these
These people who are less engaged
Probably
Don't have an intellectual understanding of the underpinnings of their
Talking
Which are
Of course right now
Giving them the benefit of the doubt
What they're doing is
You know this is my team that your team I'm going to go with my team no matter what
And
It is really important
It responds to his rhetoric and this is going to come
From left field for me
You should talk to the people
Not engaged
Who say things like this b*******
Jordan
Varian side Jordan
Because you know my family
Zoe really and f****** consistently similar to Alex
And they don't realize that they're white
Like
Republican
It turned into the same thing and they didn't
They didn't know that it was the same thing
It's a frog in a
Kind of
Raising the temp
Not realized
What has
The thing you felt comfortable
Conversation
It's it's
Got to be something that we have to actually communicate is that
If you are a disengage Republican you are inexplicably
A white nationalist and you got to figure out
How you got the
Do you have someone like Steve
Who's in office
You can't swear that
With nationalism
Become a bat
Damn you can't square that with complace
There's no way to
You
It's not
It's not okay
Yeah I think you're right
Should have those
It's possible.
Not appropriate
Going Pizza
People up first
Siding on the wrong side
Because you might get your ass kicked if you pick the wrong people
Still conducive
Conversation too
Tacitly
Supporting
Supporting viola
Minorities
People with
Gender expression
With medical condition
Did people look down on
People
Lesbian bisexual
Violence
Call Dan this was a
F****** Journey
It was
Episode
Terms of our cover
Valex Jones
It's really a
Illustrative
To give it again
Vista
Strings
Together but but
Is pretty clear
You know I think
I think what you see
Not forced
It's an unforced error it until it is absolutely Alex Jones
It's embarrassing
And pretty f***** up but it's also not
We already knew this stuff
He's just dumb enough
Next week
On Monday but until then we'll be back with probably a lesson
Not sure about that
I'll be back though and we will be calm
Waitering accounts Henry Twitter it's like
Knowledge underscore authoritarianism is great
Cam'ron
We are on iTunes the name of our podcast on iTunes is knowledge fascism
That's correct guys has been a lot of fun
God
We
Do we have anybody who probably hasn't killed Mike Adams bad Medical
Advices for
Blackpilled seems like a real s*** head
That's true but you just has a bad film criticism
Bad ideas about race
Technically
That guy's Alex
Alexandra Thurston color