Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Jordan
What's your favorite Brendan Fraser
I don't know
Monkeybone Monkeybone
We ruined a man's career in that man's more than one
Container underground career the moment you discovered Coke so almost entire Studio
Expensive
I worked at a movie theater when that came out
It was one of the best
It was
Billed as like
Aside from the director of Nightmare Before Christmas
Except
That's right
Like everybody came into the theater
Like opening night
Cubone weather like
I'm real excited about for this 2-Burner I got bad news
Remember how good the director did
Nightmare Before Christmas
We're not going to start giving producers all kinds of credit for
Amarillo
Like five years I never saw anything like that again like
Universal
Anger coming out of a speaker
The f*** are you there for the Phantom
I might have not been working
The theater at the
No I was there for a very short.
There's a huge mess
Hopefully you were fired twice and rehired
Anteater
Delirious more disappointed
I think so experienced
I don't remember hating
Sorry my finger Brendan Fraser movie it actually watch The Mummy like
Batman 3 hours ago
I would say
More disappointed by
I expect
Go to be disappointed by it
The expectation was too high
We're going to be disappointed
Everybody mad
Monkeybone
You knew that going in
Visceral
Rage
Loved it
The inverse of that was like on the open
Midnight for rollerball movie with LL Cool J
A big group of people dead
No one ever came to worth
Cedar dressed up
There were a couple people
Big group of people came out
They were so cool
Remember that as Lex Luthor the reverse of the monkey bone thing
Exuberant
Holyshit if we could go back in time I would make a documentary called roller ballers
And it's just about those people who drowned in the
We were the junior varsity theater
Anyway Jordan is a show where I know a lot about our correct
Interesting 2009 episode to go over 82 be a map
Mercilessly
He is I've been trying to warn
Qualify
Do a little bit more of that
We do something I'd rather do
I don't
So first today I'd like to say thank you
Next up Morgan thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Let's find out
You are now a policy wonk
Is actually an ancient Sumerian and
Gilgamesh both hattaway
Okay then
Next
Finally
I don't know how to pronounce this next travel
Technical difficulties
Supposed to show
I do that by going to our website knowledge fight.com
Oh yes please
We're going over the span of April 7th
We're going to go ahead
Through the 7th
Because it is
He just talked to Mike Rivero about a bunch of bulshit
How many interviews the lady
Whose son was
The guy who got decapitated on the Greyhound bus
And it's gross
Expletive
Perkasie and stuff like that
Piece of it where Alex
It's a gross interview and it doesn't seem
Fit in with anything that Alex talks about
Novel piece of his
Right he's not trying to
This guy out to be
An immigrant killer he's not trying to
There's none of the normal rhetoric except for stuff about like
Demonizing mental illness
But it's definitely not worth going
Through that jump in on the 8th
Because I think the 8th
Is one of the most
Important
But we will have ever covered
Terms of our entire podcast
Hey before we explain why
Here are a couple out of context
Text drops from Today Show
In the first one
Kind of describes my life
I think
Goodbye
More you look into the abyss Abyss looks back at you
That's dangerous
Rhetorical question
He doesn't want to dance
Weird mood on the 8th
Your own radio show is to just
Ask a Giant like
Does anybody like me here
Anybody anybody hear it all
No yeah well see that was in response to
That whole
Jaguar assertive in the response to a caller calls in
Overdrive extra hour
The show
Calls backed up and wants to talk
So the first is a guy who's
This entire episode you've been talking about this article in the eight
AP about how Obama is admitting that they're doing chemtrails
But if you go look at that article doesn't say that
I like you and I want
Help get your message out to my friends and stuff like that but you were literally saying something that isn't true
All them to go check this out they're going to see it that's not true that's hurting
So f****** defensive
So that leads
Wow
That's why you weren't over
Oh man that's so sad
That's so sad.
You're you're a great man you're doing great things
I don't want to
I love you
I'm out of that love I tell you that you are lying about this b*******
Change it
That way when you tell the truth I can tell more of my friends and they'll tell more of their friends
That you're right and it said he throws a tantrum like a little baby
Is there word not the rest of this episode I would like to just listen to that whole 20 minute
Because Alex just
Do you like
Are For Less just like
Why I'm right all the time
Awesome
But
Jordan today's episode
Is going to
Tubi
Big it's going to be very important
Byb
I need to make one
Very
Caveat
The main substance
Today's
We've got a lot of
There is going to be
What episode did I can tell you what's going on
Speculation
I want to give that warning ahead of time and we will do our best to call out
What is what
But I don't want to mislead anybody
Who's listening
As we go through it
To think that we have a
Affirm conclusion
Or that we're directly say
Right
We're not right
We not
I don't know I don't know how to say this other than to say
Alex Jones
Parlance
Seminoma closure of the parlance
Will point us to this
Aeon gut circumstantial
No
We will say our gut says this is probably true but we don't
Because we can't
There's got their circumstantial evidence coincidence
Together
How those things
Lead us to the conclusion
See that this is the conclusion exactly
Totally clear lest anyone
Wrong idea
Because a lot of his stuff is
Is pretty important
Copper
And at the same time
Really f*****
Here's where we start we're going to jump in about 20 minutes into the April 8th
2009 episodes
And the reason we're not going to listen to
The beginning
Is because it's just a continuation
Mission of Alex's
Random
Random fun
Be blamed for shooting
About the idea that
That newspapers are pointing out that the guy who did the shooting
Was a regular commenter on his rhetoric
Yeah but you look at the comments
Mets
That's sort of his defense of Our Truth
You can see how
There is an argument
Make it so
Because he does like
Just doesn't think you hate
Right
Complaints were
Which is
Not necessarily indications
The guy was against salary
Text B weird criteria
I think you're great guy I think you're right on most
But you just don't
Turn off so we can talk
I'm sorry
I'm sorry you don't think that's a win-win for me
So that's most of the beginning of the episode
And then about 25 minutes and Alex says something
Directly attacked by George Soros
Diasorin
Hardcore people
So
We have Alex
Not only
That he's being attacked
Pittsburgh shooting
He doesn't want that
Beyond
He's adding in Soros today
Which is something that
We have never seen
On April 2nd
Alex brought up Media Matters
He said that it was run by David Brock
Doesn't mention Soros at all this is a new piece of rhetoric
Being introduced here
George Soros runs Media Matters
April 8th April
Mirror days
After
Alex Jones
Talked about Media Matters
David Brock
No mention
Up until this point
Tolerance
3 mentions a caller said something
Talking about Soros so far
I'm not sure and I think that's an exploration that I will drive this afternoon
Quite frankly
But I should say
The point out that
Like if it was just that
It was just Alex being like
I don't think that I would be all that interested
Necessarily cover
Bring this much to the
To the preceding
But unfortunate
How expensive
Pretty much the in
Entire show
Taking swings
Okay in a way that I would describe as over
Like Ethan saying
Here is another clip between he's in overdrive
Super famous
He's going to blow up
And the George Soros
He's trying to destroy
Because that's the Final Fear
Didn't mention Soros by name in that clip
But that's the external context
He was talking about
The for the
Started
About to become very popular and much more he's going to see a rise
His stature
Confidence
Concrete
Statements
That does not sound like our usual both
He doesn't begin it with and I don't mean to brag
I've been holding back some kind of super strong guy and I've been holding back my popular
He says I'm about
To become super
Pivots to saying that George Soros hates
I mean that's specifically
Like a lot of Bragg's
Place in life
Position it's always
The present day
Not I'm
About to be
Because I'm stopping holding back yeah yeah or whatever
Anybody was holding back was this knowledge about George Soros
I think that he would Clearly say that on the episode
Revealing besoros is
Which probably would cut off most of my criticisms
Because that'll be like
I don't believe you
But at least you're making
Everything
He's doing it
In such a way is it
It really just feels
Unnatural
It feels like a drawing
Shift
Mechanical
Different direction because
We've been spending months and months listening to
His walk through 2019 never talked about Soros
Rothschild
You know any famous Jews and that this is
Of a departure
It's so much
And we're not nearly done
Like
Quick question
Do we have any concrete
Kind of like
Range where the
Soros being the big battle
We're going to get into all of that
Throughout the course of this
I'm really trying to make this a quick episode
It's a little more complicated than being able to eat solid released
What when you get into the
Complexities
So there is that
That's a very ever ever said
Annoying
I'm going to wake up in about
3 a.m. this morning just be like
It was a great and I hate it
His history
Axl Rose
I was reading today
So he was reading things that Soros said they were going
To do for years
Now that's
You know
Actually what's amazing about that is that in rewriting his own history you see the first draft
What do you mean
I'm still angry at the invitation is Never As Good As the original
Soros's writing
And stuff like this for
4 years
What's led him to be able to
Nobody knows
No that's
The way you presented
Not
Eonline
His own
Aversion of his
Especially considering either means
Started looking into Soros
That all of the stuff that he has been studying so far
Has actually been
Introducing Soros
World
Like I would say if she got on it was like my research
Sound
But instead
Pretending that all of these things are
About
Every episode up till this point
He's he's in media res
Restart
He's hitting the ground running
Yeah
Weird that I have to stress like we're not going
To listen to
A lot of the stuff on the 7th
But it's not like I'm hiding
Yep talkabouttd
I'm just a little defense
What about the idea
Showing all my work
I highly doubt
Still in high school
Now is you know talking
In about
Right and I think it is probably good too
Point this out
He's making a lot of wide-ranging
You just a tiny bit
If that was what you were saying he's reading Services writing
Forever
That's not really implied by what he's saying these documents
Soros
Holy
But I just want to
Totally clear
Of course
So it's a wide-ranging
Weather
IMS
Documents
Takeovers
Or
But he's already thrown around.
To be there
The Media Matters bar
They complain about Alex
He's trying to
Deflect criticism
Themselves
So there is that as a sort of
Motivation
But it still doesn't
The question why is the tap
Absolutely
The question becomes
Complicated
See how far rain
Complaints that he has
I can make a $200,000
Free
Take showers
Seems like you
You think George Soros who spent his own hard-earned money to put Barack Obama in the pacify the left
I don't know
Bacares
Hussar
The Obama Deception
Is that what you say I thought you said
I didn't realize it cuz the way that the center
It's kind of structure made it sound like
Does Soros talk about us like that
Sting the last I spoke
Which he's actually talking about
Thesaurus talked about the Obama.
Rose doesn't put out the documentary The Obama Deception okay
NetSpend
Somebody's got it
Grammar
Attorney General
Firearms
Real
You established George Soros Finance people
Does anybody
Robin trying to stop
I like
I don't have some romantic
So he's saying the Soros is going to precipitate a Civil War by
You people these funding
All of the people out there in the media that Alex doesn't like all of these people
You know pushing the ideas that Alex is opposed
Soros ownership of so much
He didn't give him ownership up before
This is a drastic
Departure point
For Alex
I don't know how much
Keeps this up in the episodes after this episode
Is a very harsh document of
Alex going
Real f****** hard on
We're going to try and contextualized
The media landscape
50 seasons
Which is there zika
Controlled
People on the left
Can I control people on
Wearing
Like Rush Limbaugh is in charge of the
The right
George soros's
Charge
Find out about another media organization
His own devices
Air America
Lionel is I don't know
Thoros wants to put Lionel on Airport I don't know
Theme song
Who gives a s***
The power base
Yeah
In the world
Amanda
Explicitly
Text clip that cirrhosis
George Soros Foundation
Other weird name for a foundation
Implantation
Hi I exposed the only conclusion I can draw from this
Is that
We're right around season 3 or season 4 and they realize they had to introduce
You have a situation where
Like I don't know
Negotiating salary
Rothschild
Propaganda
Robert Downey jr. hadn't signed on for The Avengers the whole thing could have gone crazy
Could have
So even exploit
About a whole bunch even already on this episode
Is the idea that Alex
Of guys
That he likes
Rothschild's Rockwell
What have you
And it's next clip I just regular horses
I believe
Is Alex Jones
Initiating Soros
Into that group
What can happen if Mexico collapses
There's Dead Cops all over the place military all over the place
Marching around going to take people's guns in the middle all this
Breakdown of society
Is George Soros and David Rockefeller a zbigniew Brzezinski
Benedict newborn is brazinski
Leave starting an amaryllis little bit
To cause the Civil War
Lendup
Blood in the streets
People's guns
Soros is now high-level
He has he's up there with the elite of the globalist
Before
Like a tertiary a****** but Alex
Alex
Which position on how Alex's
Describe cirrhosis
This point
I would describe it basically as like
A guy
Is to Frankie
Annabelle
He has been like
Was talking about how
The price of oil going down
Be bad for Russia
Videos applying Soros
Evil plan
Then on this show he's absolutely doing
Yes
Specific complaint
About him
I can track
Like this one
George Soros
I'm having a very good crisis is Soros
George Soros went on to say it is the culmination
My life's work and has been very stimulating
At the club
These major sites attack including Media Matters
And he's coming out
Vicious attack
Pittsburgh Post-Gazette
Oh my gosh Alex Jones had the white supremacist after him actually the cop killer
Disagree with
So that's the thing I was talking about earlier
Attractive
Press conference
Just read the headline
There's a bad paraphrase
Quoting out of context
In a way the culminating point of My Life Works
But he's not talking about causing the crisis or even
Just to question
Prior in the interview
Sores that indicated that he doesn't
Too much of his time focusing on the minutiae of financial sector
At this point
Student focusing on Paula
The interview interview
What sort of policy
Twitch Doris reply
The financial crisis and how to solve it
Wendy's
The culmination of his wife
He's talkin about all the writing
Exploring how the theory of reflexivity
Teresa
And you could be used
Sfix
This is absolutely 100%
Interview or intentionally lying about it
To quote quote about him having a
Enterprise
This is really more about how he predicted
Crash and better
Also
He warned people of what he saw comic
You publicly predicted it wasn't like
He kept the information to himself and profited off
Also hear really funny line in that interview about how the mainstream Financial experts had predicted
Three out of the last seven bubble
But he was better
Cuz he predicted seven out of the last three
Poking fun at the fact that he had wrongly predicted bubbles multiple times
He shows that great aplomb
Zipperhead
Is that in that interview when he's asked about solution
He literally advocates
Greater restrictions and regulations on selling
Which is one of the
Instrument to use to make
Make his money
He's advocating for a solution that is opposed
His own self in
There is nothing in this interview
That isn't
Indicative
But he caused
This crash
The crash part of it outside
Being sort of
At least in some ways evidence that the
In the market
Is something
Which has been hit
Interviews I've read with him he cops
To like
Yep I'm I made a mistake on that one and I wonder things
They're dear like if you make a mistake
Holden
That you put forth
Be just because it was your plan he should coach an NFL team you know what I'm saying
No references on my car
How much about my friend Kyle Erza's from Kansas City don't worry about it
But my point is that I think that when you
Read actual interviews
George Soros
Most frequently
Is a humility about himself a sense of humor about his own position
Any place in the world
He doesn't
If you actually read his words
All the books that he's written
He doesn't fit the
The picture that the right wing
Media puss
Course not
No
Easy to present yourself well in interviews and still be a dick
There's plenty of examples of that
Do that
I don't
I don't know I need more evidence
These people want to really demonized
More advantageous to the right for him to
Forthright
Self-aware
Somewhat humble and have a sense of humor about himself
In that then he becomes such an easy target to attack
True colors you can make up everything about a guy who is humble and self-aware
Tunics that but it's interesting that most of the stuff where he's actually caught
To like
You know I was wrong
Red one interviewer he's talking about how he tried to set up a
Foundation
Former soap
Hrblock
And we're pushing for reforming X Direction
And he got pushed back from the
Realized
He was going about
Because he wasn't taking it
Local customs
Greater culture
Of that country
And so like
Wait till he was ignorant of something and then you learn more about it and there is nothing
Is that
But I've never seen
That I only see
These lies
He intentionally
Nazi collaborator
Core stuff like that
It's never a never seen
TV like
Diversion conversation about
Conversation
It'll be interesting
I don't know it's
Crazy
Alex talks about how you calling for
Thesauruses
Andy says something
That I think
Red flags
I have George Soros who's having a great time
Many other nations
Kenzo doing that
That's an interesting thing for Alex to say
In the time since Alex has been talking about George Soros
Used as a scapegoat
Whenever there's something happening
In the world that runs
Counter to Russian
For instance in 2017 Macedonia was in a little bit of a
This wasn't the whole story obviously but a piece of it was that Macedonia was in the process of being brought into the
You which is bad news
Because Macedonia is home to the very important to know
Reply okay
Congressman
Text Allison about how open Society
What's romantic Discord in Macedonia
Control
Much of this was based on information
Being put out by a group called stop operation Soros
From an article in Politico
Quotes the Macedonian politicians in an Allied group operations
Denied any direct Russian role in their effort
One of the founders of stop operation Soros cuz
Noticed a virtual Army of Boston troll posting about Mass demonstrations against Soros
That never actually
We happened
Also in 2017 Viktor Orban prime minister of Hungary
Began targeting Soros and blaming him
Described as an invasion of immigrants
Which were precipitating
A great replacement
Shifting the
It should be noted that Orban is not a cool.
In speech that he gave at the valve 80s summer
Free University
2014 he literally said quote
Constructing hungry
Illiberal state
A non-liberal state
It does not reject
Principles of liberalism
And I can list a few more
Ideology
Central Elementary State organization
So he's not so much
Graduation
I don't suppose graduation as a student
But some sort that is not a real raspy
Do whatever you want
Work Rihanna
Freedom.
We like freedom but not as an absolute or a central idea
Let's pump the brakes on freedom it's a good fourth priority
We can agree that without
Freedom being fundamental lights.
Freedom
It's not
Diametrically opposed
Open the central
European University of Budapest
And pay for scholarships
For promising students
College
Which ironically was a recipient of a 1989
Goddamnit we can't teach the evils
The Aurora Center is a charity organization in hunger
Angostura
You've been here
Giving them some fun day
The guardian
The Aurora Center was set up in 2014 and act as a kind of Coalition of the
Housing the offices of non-governmental organization
Network on Jewish issues
Romo is lgbtq rights migrants drug
The proceeds from an on-site bar and regular
Go to sports
And the center's initial funding
Skateparks
From Soros
Last month
A group of far-right activists
The face the outside of the building
Spray painting
Stop operation Soros
On the pavement
And Plastering photographed with a red cross stuck through it on the doorway
In 2018 orban's government literally stopped Soros
It's literally stopped
Which great bailiff is called figuratively stop Soros
Literally
Restricted nongovernmental organizations
From being able to assist immigrants in Asylum
Solsource with
Withdrew open Society from the country
Central Europe
University Audi
Which is a US
Accredited universe
So cool
You see these are pretty good indicators of the sort
Scapegoating Soros in the more recent
But it doesn't help our purposes here because
After 2009
What we need to do is find out who a Zagg cover
Toys R Us
Positions before that
So we can see who I'll just talk
It should come as no surprise to anyone that the only relevant country Alex
Can be talking about is Russia
From November on November 7th 2003 article
Templar skladman is for staff to leave the Moscow offices of the open Society
2000 it by us billionaire
George Soros
At least Thirty men stormed the offices
These computers and documents in the rain
Which began late on Thursday
Who's playing the doors about open Society
But that doesn't explain why they took what was described as
Have documents after their rate
That does Justice
I didn't pay my rent for awhile in my landlord
Two dozen camouflage mesh to steal my computer and then rummage deny you access to
Your server
What this is really about Soros and open Society
Yukos oils
Yo McHale
Khodorkovsky
Oscoda or
Go to RC Willey
Clear instance of corruption
Temperature
His political opponents was definitely one of them
An educational program standing up
Since founding internet cafes were normal people communicate with the outside world
He was arrested
Jailed on trumped-up charges ultimately about 10 years in jail
International outcry led to Putin pardoning
After which point he wisely headed out to
UK
Okay offices and made it impossible
Country
In that time.
Throat was very clear about his opposition
Government
The quote the New Order in Moscow that is emerged out of the chaos of the night
90 is very far from an open Society
It's an authoritarian regime that preserves an outward appearance of democracy put Power from its control of Russia
National
National resources
It uses those resources
Empower
To personally enrich the rulers
And exercise influence over its neighbor
Both in Europe and the former Soviet
But the idea of an open Society is difficult to suppress and I have not given up hope
In the. Following the 2000
3 red express is hot
George Soros
And his Democratic initial
Flaming
Is Putin Zone aggression
Be at the Georgian war in 2008 or the annexation
Sora
Interesting Lee on February
23rd 2009
Which is
I don't know about a month
Before the episode we're listening to right now
Really seen close together
It was very overt
Message about poop
Putin's Russia
Here's some Choice pack
Europe cannot afford to resist Russia
Cannot afford to not resist Russia's geopolitical aggression
It needs to be unified at any chance of success
Europe needs to pursue a two-pronged strategy
On the one hand protector
Against the Jeep
Russia
On the other it must be
Replace the rule of force
And geopolitics
The pursuit of democracy
Open Society of international cooperation
Strengthening and supporting the former Soviet republics
Would serve both prongs
Unified
EU policy towards Russia
In the op-ed Soros advert
Unified energy policy
Europe-wide regulatory Authority
Which has precedence over National regulators
Eddie europe-wide distribution
This would deprive Russia of its ability to play one country against another
Because a concession
National distributor immediately become available
Customers
In all other
Which is
Reflecting the reality of what
Call Demian picking them off one by one in order to
Royal Reserve
Is it relied on
Those
How long has Putin been in power for now it's going to be 30 years
So it's dark over on New Year's Day
It's almost 24 years
The article for the European Council on Foreign Relations
The direct attack on
Political and economic status
Good Rush
I don't see it is very likely that Putin would not want to respond with it
Information camp
Very much in line
With the strategies
That Russia uses General in terms of infer
Warfare
We have juice
Before this episode
To where Alex starts talking about George Soros
George Soros himself
European Council on Foreign Relations
Position picture definitely
Work
Against
Newton Centre
Crystal Lake
Two-pronged strategy would be
Those vulnerable
Enterprising
Russia of 1
In terms of manipulating the oil supplies
To get people to turn on
Bugs Bunny episode
Daffy Duck has just put up a bunch of arrows
All over the entire Forest
Every possible Arrow everywhere
You pointed directly at Bugs Bunny's old
Kind of see where that has Bugs Bunny
There are a lot of arrows
Have I have a lot of thoughts
It does but there's really no way
To make this
Any direct
Playing but we can talk about
That rabbit is
No no
Pictures of Walmart
I've already made
It isn't
Hayirli reasonable to accept
Entirely responsible
It could just be the timing
So I guess now might be a good time to talk about
The answer the question you asked earlier about
Was doing
In the early
Demonizing the open Society
It's not
Just
Popped up out of nowhere
Hitler so there
George Soros Pacifica
He spent his life in a large Fortune
Democratizing
Countries that those death
In perpetuity
Rise to power again on New Year's Eve
But it doesn't
Predate him being in
In the KGB
He was a foreign foreign intelligence officer
8:35
1891 reaching the rank
Lieutenant colonel
You may notice
Is right around when the
Sell it which one you decided
Politics
Finding himself a fast-rising star in
In 1992 istvan kerska
Was a radical nationalist member of the Hungarian National Assembly
Do hungry wasn't part of the USSR it was a country that was militarily dominated by the Soviet
Union until iron
In the 50s
Democratic
Takiro haven't been arrested at the
Attempted Revolution
Against Soviet occupation
He put on the appearance
Being a democratic Crusader critical of the Hungarian power
He was employed as an informant for the Hungarian Secret
He's literally control
Insisting that the Zionist
To take over
In 1992 he accuse Sorrows of being a puppet of Israel
So that is it from
Do we have this example of
But he was actually a snitch
For the people he was pretending
So you got that
Okay that's one
Jim's Blanca hyper nationalistic stream member of the National Council
Ventricle
Slovakia
He was a real s*** head things like the following about
People from hungry
These robbers murderers and those who erect these ugly to rule
He's Hungarian parrot
Traditional bird
Tyrol
Houston to Laredo
Culture
Yeah. He called the ethnic Hungarian minority in the country a quote tumor on the body of the Slovak Nation
Anxiety attacks and level Budapest
If they attempt
Teach us the Lord's Prayer and
Everett
He called Joseph piso quotes one of the greatest sons of the flu
Fun facts Joseph Pisa was
The president of Slovak Republic back when it was a client state of Nazi Germany
By August 1942 Tissot at 8
Live in the Slovak Republic
When the Vatican criticized
The deportation
Peace out himself a Catholic priest
Before becoming president replied quote
There is no foreign Intervention which
Should stop us on the road to the liberation of Slovakia from
Motherfukers direction is real gonna kill the Jews
Army liberated Slovakia
Democracy
He was hung on April 18th 90
Love that guy
But you know who he didn't like
George Soros
Completely cool legislation designs
Doctor tail freedom
Empress in the Czech Republic
The accused figuratively kill Jews Act
He accused opposition of being part of a plan by George Soros.
Destabilize the country
We could spend all day learning about the various authoritarian Nazi sympathizers and
Extreme right-wing
The last decade
Example
I think they demonstrate my point
Since the fall of the Soviet Union
The Boogeyman
Who's trying to take over the counter
Is always
Used by people who do not want democratic ideals
In their country
Cirrhosis spent millions and millions
Dollar Tree
Imitation of liberal democracy
In countries formerly under the rules
The Soviet Union
Because that is where
He's from and because he knows how important
Does democratic ideals
Here's what
Crew lyrics like LeBron building a school in Cleveland
Irony of the world is
Traditional Republican foreign-policy
The same parties it is now under the sway of these
Narrative
You see a pop-up even in Fox News
The president
Yeah
Is very close to this anti-social Rosemary
Put traditional Republican foreign-policy is a Honda
Percent line with what Soros did
In the aftermath of the Soviet
The GOP Rusev Oak
I'm opening up country to Liberal democracy which inevitably
Leads to an open market for the country
And all that other s*** they f****** love
But because there was also in favor of liberal ideals
Like rights for all people and not hating immigrants
They've given up all principles
In falling in line with
With Jam Slaughter
And other sucking authoritarian
To push propaganda
Very positive spin Wichita
Not how I said traditional you should not have said that
Going to hide behind that
Saudi Arabia exist
Undoubtedly
Don't care about democracy so much as the open market
The part of what
Well I suppose it is their ideal in those country
Because there's already and they're not playing
So they would just like to
So if they were so if it was a Greek democracy
And they were playing ball
In the same way that when South American countries
Authoritarian
I think
Seems so far
Little bit of a deconstruction about how
Historically so much of the
Criticism of Soros
Smith Falls
To putting forth his
Europe
Early on
Empower
He his
Soros ads
Color Revolution anytime
Do you sort of threat
It's a Soros thing
Prevailing
Place that
But
These are fundamental shift receive
Take place in a relatively
Short. Of time
A Alex
I think there's no way around
I strongly suspect
But the only way we can
Can tell if there's
The only way to tell
Is it we need to analyze some of the context
And see what was going on in the world
In April 2009
See there's any clues that might tell us about why Alex
Begin this all of a sudden
What company and then they bumped up there
Sizing on Alex's show on the gcn network
Got a meeting with
Here's what we're going to do
Will buy all your goals
But let you run the place
I have a complete ownership stationary clothes
It's very close actually do station stealth
Through for that because
The Russians were trying to
Get diamond gusset to replace their theme song with the tetris
Months
That is why no one knows how big or small
Relations between Russia United States Lily Frost
In the mid-to-late
Early 2009
There's a matter of Bush's plans
Install
Stick missiles in Poland
The Czech Republic
Things that Russia made very certain
Act of aggression
Their ambassador to the UN Vitality chickens
Imposter
Impossibly to reply
Their own metals
I'm here with that exchange of
Threat
Russia pack the separatists
Asia and South ossetia in August 2008
Between the state of Georgia and what the rest of the world
Russian
In the to Breakaway
It was a coalition of the willing
Sure of course on January 6th 2009 Russia
Ukraine precipitated
We are crisis
Of much of Europe
Adapt
The winter
As we saw when we listen to that episode
A almost unanimous
Welcome Center
Alex's position on that crisis was that
Ukraine shut off the gas
There are a lot of flare-ups
And people were rightly concerned about what that would pretend between
You're for the relations
Tomb Raider
Hours
On April 2nd 2009 the G20 Summit occurred in London
Which Mark the beginning of an increase
Chris efforts to repair the strained relations
With talks between Obama and president of Russia
Earlier in March Hillary Clinton
Famously posed with Sergei
By holding a proper reset button
Send a message
The two countries
We're putting the past behind them moving forward
NES
Almost
There are good reasons
This is possibly an effort being made to live in a more of a balanced world
And put the Cold War mentality
Behind us and let it die
Public perception
In reality the relationship
Was not getting better
Part of this is due to
The fact
Italy prime minister
The time in medvetta was president
Everyone knew that Vladimir Putin
I'd never really stepped down from power and was really running
He be president from the start
Until May 2008
We became pregnant
Until May
Became president
The Russian Constitution doesn't allow for more than two consecutive terms
Presidents
So Putin and Medved ever engaged in what's known as a
Democracy
Became president
And again in 2012 he made Medvedev Prime minute
When he was elected president
With 97% of the votes
Is my day was very Democratic everybody
Protest
Clear corruption
Is doing
Or just trading positions in order to
Retain a Stranglehold on power
People protest
Points to their protest
Clear signs
Things like call the revolution
Being carried out by
Internationalist to Lake George
Somebody is fomenting
It's almost like to rhetoric that far-right authoritarian dictatorship
In order to demonize
Reasonable rational protesters
Has become de rigueur for
Far-right nationalist politicians
Who just so happened to go under the same
It does seem that way
What's interest
Is like weed
Lesotho
Historical hatred of
Zoroaster
In 2009
Raptor 2009
There is very clearly
Soros
Putin are at loggerheads
Receive
The sort of tension
Between the United States
And Russia
Where
Do you know
Or aggression would not work
The outward appearance of trying to make the relationship better
Is information Warfare
Since 1970s
You be in the foreign intelligence
It seems like specializing in product
It seems like
His move
Pretend to be
Having
Let's make our relationship better talk
Trying actively undermining those talks
Through demonization of
Both Obama
Creating this because it's important
What is
Country is doing ends
Absolutely
I think that's there and I don't think it's
Crazy
To look at that
The connection
Step back and say
Looks bad
There's a historical piece
The present
Pizza Hut in 2009
But none of it is to say that Russia told Alex
To do that
Of course it's
It's just
So much
Even then
Even had as far as like a let's prove it
Even had told Alex directly
8 different people and a video chat I guess
Apparently according to rush
Here is are is my question
With this
Like
Which right-wing propaganda
Utterly dominated Russia for
And then
Metastasize the way that it has
Worldwide
And to see the way that you do like
It's always going to be the fact-checkers are going to be on the defensive and they're never going to win in the same way that
The Russian hacker
You can have a great
Defense cyber security system but it's never going to do
The people who are spending all of their time
On the author
If you don't like white person
Black enchantress like Rodger Stone always
Exactly
Is there any idea way that right-wing propaganda is actually defeated in
Like is there a way to win
No
Speculative question
I really don't think there is
I think you can have a little
Deconstructionist
Win
For Austin our listeners
Having a more robust under
Understanding
What's really behind them where there's true
I swear there's.
Is great
Wrong word
Effective about proper
Target
People where they live at Targets them in their weak spot
Parts of how the
Entire
Of course
Grown up
The early
Days of advertising
Disinformation
Tied together
It's become so effect
Practicing
Understand
They in order to get a bad message
Supercross
You're not implying
Whether it's the Jews are evil
Yeah
Kind of have to give a secondary
That you attach to the other message
Trojan Horse
You're ever going to be able to overcome that
With reason logic
Our truth I really don't you realize that the conclusion to draw from that then
Is not we should be battling
Evil right-wing propaganda with
Reason and facts and logic
Ensure
And should instead create
Are evil left-wing propaganda I think that's a
Things that are called liberal propaganda
It's always things like
Appeals to
People's rights and stuff like that
Done with the liberal propaganda of interracial relationship
Yes yeah
Accused of being liberal propaganda
I think there is probably like
Some smaller-scale versions of
Like left
People who are
Use manipulative tactics in the same way
I think if they do exist they're very unsuccessful
They don't make a difference
No one really looks
Have we considered
Turning ourselves into a Consulting business for
Left-wing propaganda on the show like seven times at least I know bunch
Really putting that out there
Actually really be interested in
I think it serves your consultancy business
Not true at all not true at all
Listen to Ed Gazette
They wouldn't get me
Really be interested to know if there is like a Russian analog for our podcast
It would be way more brazen
Absolutely
And get them to
Couple things
Because
We've done some of the
Offshoot episodes that we've
Weak now now
I want folks to know I wouldn't do this willingly
I want that on record
Look what he did
Are first in 9/11 Inside Job
Bill Cooper we don't have to just say
Alex's
Innova
Over wearing a switch
Just fun so go f*** yourself
Stop Alex
Emmett next flip
This one
So Alex is really still pushing The Obama Deception
It's the Silver Bullet
I appreciate that our listeners
A number of
How to box
Something like that
And asking them to
Make me
You feel gross
Listen to this next clip
Listen to what Alex's of his audience
Because this is
Souvlaki
Gross
I want YouTube
Infowars.com
430 hours
A million 200,000 views high-quality for free
Heading out to everybody
Buy the DVD and support.com
So far okay
What's a little bit
Asher
Financial thing here is
You know by the TV remotes
Help get the word out of it goes off the rails so f****** hard
Can you go by 1000 cell all the jump a jet ski you don't use whatever out of the garage
That's crazy
First of all people to sell in order to buy a DVD
Multiple boats
Give them out for free
Garage
In Alex's defense he's not
It's not clear how many hours he wants them to put it
It's so much of an ass
That's so much to ask if you like it
Please tell people about it
Fire copy and helps
Support what we do
Sawyer jetski I want every policy walk
2 by 3 million
Download every episode of our podcast
I just throw them off the overpass in a f****** right on 94 I want every car to be hit with
Your garage if you don't have a garage
Work
A little too aspiration
We're telling people to bend
Hey you know what quit your job get them
For the garage get a better job so you can do with the abuse
Yusuf we are asking you to do to support our own ambitions
Oh man
Do at this point Jordan
Interesting Lee on this April 8th episode
Guess we've met before
Short story
Just saw a in 2018
The guy who started Oath Keepers
You're not
Are you
Are you aware
Of what's going to happen because I'm sick of you drawing these f****** perfect parallels on a day-to-day
It's part of what I was talking to
The show about how uncomfortable I am
Really just texted you like
Weird near like I'm fine
I'm just trying to talk
Through what I'm looking
This is very
So Stewart Road shows back up here on
Alex has decided to go demonize George Soros
I think that is probably
I think it's almost certainly acuenta
It's interesting time
But it's I think that that doesn't mean
Aldo
If I need to if I've made a big decision
I need to work it out comfort food
So he's just made a big change
In 2009
He's just made a big change in
I think you're probably right
I think that's dirt road showing up in present-day is much more indicative
I think so cuz I don't think that
Know each other very well
They'd only had one
Interview
That's it
Probably talked off are a little bit you can even hear from
Their interaction that they they aren't like super tight
In the same way that they will become
Maybe it's like a
You know
You've had a long run you just got out of a relationship
You text your funk buddy
And then they come on your show
When she gets real weird
And in this interview in this disappearance
Stewart Road
He's trying to
Remote
Publix
Of the
Is it going to meet at Lexus
Concord
And I'm going to have a big ceremony where all these
Police and military
Reaffirm their oath
Perfect
Course
Yes so after having a
Conversation
Alex has a
Division
Shots fired
In the American Revolution began
We're going to be staying there that's her first public meeting as of keepers
Right there
I got to stop shooting by the end of April
McRib
It's the final solution
It's the solution
The problems
He is now taking on the oathkeeper
Probably
Maybe Miss ascribed was the idea that Alex glommed onto
Keep her calm.
Yeah
Exist in any large
Stewart made his first appearance on the show
The responses from being on a
No we can have two weeks ago
Moments
Alex has The Oath Keepers founder on The Oath Keepers at the same at the time are pretty much nothing
Has The Oath Keepers founder
No it just this one time
So all of a sudden
He gets a massive response
A lot more people want to join the
He staying in contact with
Alex loves
It's kind of a symbiotic
Gotcha
Was the
This is a way to reclaim the Patriot energy
The world right now
Through Glenn Beck
Through
They make it
Myra
My version is this Persian
The other version
Counterfeit
Witchy spells out in the snow
Who's definitely an operative
Definitely enough
Serta Vanowen
Keepers are apart of
Party
Scoffing
Glenn Beck
It does lead 12
Did they might have
A slight external
Motive
I can't really step my foot down on on any direction on
Probably not having all the information I know
What's the roads an hour to talk
I want to kill the middle class
Well from Alex's rhetoric we know that that's what he believes
Okay that's a little bit
On this episode
I want war
Russian Revolution
Right now
Tomorrow
Call George Soros
Headlines
Not where's that article
Where is that
Damn can you think of somebody right
Who has absolutely
Somebody who has engineered
Number
Somebody who is
Operator can you think of anybody
Nope
Somebody who made
On the
Grounding
Maybe someone who said that
Eugenics
Is real somebody like that
No nobody never loved
And they would never become the president of the goddamn United
So what we have here is Alex
Like that is a strong into
Right there
Alex
How to put this other than
Feel like someone told him something
Appear to be any kind of
Real
Like I've known about Soros forever
That guy
Cuz I like I said
Repeatedly
Episode
There's ways to present that in natural way which is
Like I said my research team dug this up
Yeah or a look I overlooked an element
Any of those sorts of things
Does all the time and then
They're trying to create a socialist State and destroy the middle class
And give it to George Soro
He's adding it on is an addendum and it seems forced
To do say that this is the culmination of his
Up until this
It wouldn't George Soros is this guy we've always been pointing towards the Rockefellers and all this
List of information all of these schemes together
The other version
David Rockefeller is too old
And The Heir Apparent is Sora
Yeah
Still talk about the tradition of hating Soros
And how this is still popping up out of nowhere but it takes away a little bit of the sting of the
Coming out of nowhere
Is it in
You either than with a natural
The way people
Present information
Because you need a contact for it needs doing this with no context
I've listened to
Every episode
Put out
From
Late 2008
To now we're in April
Every single episode
You consider all of that time
It's probably 5
100 hours
Of his broadcast
And I can say unequivocally
With no reservation
With no
Exaggeration or anything
That this
Is
Not
It's it's not normal
Yes very abnormal
Anything other than
I am certain that someone told her
Something
About cirrhosis
Or be like
Hey Soros is your new Target
Yeah he was staying up
Who would cover Trump speech
We heard him turn
Who's the new enemy
Yeah kind of a thing that he does
The focus is energy in a certain direction
Cuz he's not going to do the
She can't read not going to do any but he can't read last Cliff he said where's where's the headline
Where's the Hat
Where's the information
Interested in
Title
He has he has
Nothing
And
I
This is where we get
Circulation
Suppose one of the other big
What other big factors that I'm considering with this
This is
Soros is
Speeches in February
Apologize
This is April 8th
It seems like if there was a direct
Connection
That would be a long. Of time
It's important to remember this
Now that that connection could have been one tweet that was sent out
Andover a day every single human being
Who is in the circle
Would have been connected
Did to it more likelihood of it being
Powers
OSHA
Much more protracted
This person talks to me
That's
Influence
Steelers going out
Exactly
Because
Is German
Thai baht
This point
Encouraging
Blow up militia
Houses with Angela Kaley Cuoco
It's not I read the article it's just like how he got a really
Gmail
Or I think was a comment.
Is blog from a guy who's in the militia
About do you like hey man different America
Was vaguely threatening
This comment doesn't writer.
Was very much like
Animal
Appreciate that
La Quinta
In this combat
You're on this side
You're brainwashed you're in dr.
We love
Your dad because of us
This guy this post daily Ghostwriter
Was talking about
Do you think
Second
These assholes
Out there cosplay
Are going to actually have
Impact gun
United States Army
Do you think that
Possible
Are going to go out
Closest thousand run into an arm
Do that absolutely
Victor
Be able to
Peter Stormare
With the war of pointlessness
Gyro
Rhodes is presenting it
This guy is
It's like it's a classic misunderstanding that these people in the right terms
Creating her own victim
Look
You don't have a chance against the the
Biggest yacht in the world
World history
It's a nonsense
Director retention
Places where are we
Actually
Have a way to change things
Democratic process
I like I like you have I like us having to note that militia member
Rotate
Grammatically well well,
Like this song
Text Salinger is the noncommissioned officer in a militia
Ghostwriter
2 Stewart Road
Whatever
What you doing
Represent
And I don't really care to go over it more than we already have
I don't want to listen to him
Jim talked for like 10
It's about how they want
I kill our children
Stuff like that
Right but the real threat that he's
The real threat that he's getting from the Daily Coast writer based on your character
Conversation of what the writer said was
You're calling us Cox
Issue with you is you're saying that we are ineffectual bulshit
We're not capable of doing any of the interest
Near Stewart's
Compliant although when the article is just
That is Alex's complaint complaint
I mean like psychologic
No he's just using it as a pet
Piece of propaganda
Because he knows what the
Give a f*** about that I like are you willing
Go to war with United States military
Knowing that you know if you do
Just going to buy me
Your house right with your wife inside
Which was trying to draw parallel to what country
Literary aspect to it
In terms of what the guy at the coast was right
To kill our family
I don't think you
He's offended by the idea of them
Being called
Airsoft
But Alex
Whenever there's something about it absolutely
They're calling it while I think in the articles I cute
These b****** would be out there
By with bombs going
Military bases
You brought that up but it's Alex's
Not Stewart
Stewart is
Reserve military man
But
Board motor
Interested in the mission
Creating the idea that all of these people on the left
And these media figures are lusting after the idea of killing our
Which is more important to him
Been preserving his masculinity
That is actually really fast
Text talk about
Your instincts
About all this world
Or so sharp but they're just about Alice
And then you say that I can't get hired as a consultant for evil
Broad-spectrum
I do
I'll bring you on
I need you to starting salary that's well below
Maybe that works
They're talking about this article and I didn't bring this up for no reason I brought it up because the next clip
Alex is responding to
2in talking about how bad
Said something about Sora
What's the score of the human Americans that are
George Soros
Wow
Everything goes back
Soros
Literally every
Ghost Riders
Runs air America is a charge of Media Matters
He's trying to demonize Alex
Across-the-board
He is in charge of writing a bunch of stuff about the
The IMF and how they're going to take over everything
It's like what I was just doesn't impression to somebody who takes the Rosemont
Just fun
When I was listening
That first of all stupid
Hazmat oppression
He just sounded like him
I really think that I should have had this thought
Before this
It was one of the first times that I realized how bad that rent would sound without the music
The pressure of an out
Like the commercial out
Oh yeah ok Google
And then without do you like I know it's going to commercial so I don't have to say anything after it
You just be lost without a map
We have
We've touched on that before in that field
Lego
You got to give it you got to give the man credit for knowing how to
Two sides of the same coin
Giving him his props as like a broadcast
The realization
Is very similar
That like
Be so pathetic without
You playing Tuesday
Recognizing
Music brings to the table
Because like you hear that
You're dumb and you believe in
You take away that music
That France
Real week
Yeah
Jordan in this next clip Alex's.
More stuff about Soros
This
Continue to try and undermine black people right now
Oh my God
George Soros propaganda
Please publication
Come out the right way
That's cuz they have malicious
That's George Soros propaganda
So that's an interesting position
And this is something that I
Can't make more clear
Especially
After that clip
Alex has not said any of these things in the past
When you talked about the demonization of his
Weirdo paper
Militia
Family
Like the time
Talk about this
Who's one of my Akron
No but the Viagra Port is
Perfect example of him
He should have brought up Soros
Came up if it was a part of his
Bring up the spiritually on some level
Hear that sort of thing about
And stuff like that and don't understand what he's talking about
That's
Let's not give his listeners
That's dirty
But it's a
Exhaust fuel
To the miac reports
Through a
Attack on George Soros
Yeah I can do that
The opposite
What's more important
Is that windy direct attack on the miac report happen
There was no mention of
Single
Freaking out on air about the idea that they're demonizing the militias and
People like Ron Paul supporters
Chuck Baldwin and all these people
Save the world
Not a single f****** word about George Soros being involved in any of that
So this to me
Is one of the most
Example
Wind report
Came out which
He's a powder monkey
When were talking about
Like it
Not
Super far connected
Very,
It's very close together
And when he's going
Through the
The fake avian
Influence
When he's doing his FEMA camp rebuttal about Glenn Beck
All those things that have been in very close recent memory
Not a single f****** word about George Soros
And on this episode
50 + mentions of him
Bmd
Physically involved
With all of these Evil operation
It's suspicious as f***
To go from no mentions
25-man
No I probably would be very different episode
This is an addition
0 mentions 250
Is a very different from 0 to 50
Do that but you need the ramp that takes you from zero
Without it it's just
What
You can't make that jump
And that's what Alex is doing
Jump Snake River
Without a rock in without a bucket
To get over there
Gap
I never talked about Soros
Even though I talked about the exact same
About now to the other side
Is that where
Weird we all hate sora's right guy
None of the work
There's none of the con
Me and the sincere
If you could just present
As
My guys
For two days straight
They were sitting at their laptops and they did nothing but research and they read all these documents and everything
I still have the same
Suspicion
But
It would not be as glare
This is too glaring
It's too much
It's a bridge too far for me
Yeah
Suspicious
It's pretty crazy
Alex reveals
On this episode
Not only does George Soros
Him
He also hates
Well yeah but that's
Hopping mad because we are the resistance
Spirit
That clip wasn't so great but it's a context of it is him talking to Stewart Road talking about how like
He's hopping mad about what we're doing
Enemies
But that sort of thing
And he's trying to bring
Like Brie and my family here
Because
Wasn't doing this before before he wasn't talking about Soros
The interview
This is so
Unfortunately this is probably a
Herculean task of research
No
Researcher would ever be able to do I know I can't think of any researcher
Who would have the ability to kind of
Go through just
All of the right-wing information around the time. And see where
Slow-roast popped up
In most of the place
Like at this point
And it's not good at not much
There was the
Dating
Bill O'Reilly report
When he did a report about George
Soros being super
Westfield
Double back on it
Yeah
Coldwater
No and I don't know what to make of that
I think that there's a
Possibility
That was an opening Salvo of some
I think it's possible that that's what it is or it's just bill needed a story
Came up with something wanted
Riders
It is impossible for me to really sort out
O'Reilly's
Loretta
This is before
A little bit
Bill O'Reilly and Bob Odenkirk
Sorry that was Dennis Miller thrilling adventure hour had just started
I don't know what to make
That part
Like that
Is
Question that I tried to
To wrestle with
Episode
It would be really
Easy and very convenient for us
Define
April
This is where Alex is getting it promises
Because then we could have
We wouldn't have to have the larger conversation about it we would have to have the conversation of where the source got it from
Or more importantly if there was a
Of s*** around this
If there was around me
That's a whole different story
Exactly
Cuz
Bill O'Reilly
F****** show
It was a one-off
And then you get to like
What was it 2010
Soros the Puppet Master
Yeah
Alex is like
Soros
Just a middle
Mix
Is weird
This is weird
I don't like it
So in this next clip Alex explains that all criticism
Basic
He probably is just going to help
Best friend
So he's essentially ascribing
Criticism
Misrepresented
It does exist
So he's just saying it about me probably
Which I think is a cowardly way if you hear bad information about me there is suppressive purse
So anyway we have one more clip
April 8th
This clip
It's your road
I recommend the people find out about the
Tea Party
Nearest
To them
There's going to be
We used
Radicalized
Make fun of the idea of
But it's literally
Yeah absolutely it's like people who are
Weirdo
Craterian
Conservative
Tour gravitating
Towards this
Anti Tech
Party thing
We go out there this opportunity
A captive audience
That we're going to
To f****** radicalized
I know he's doing that to mock
The mainstream media whatever but he knows that that's exact
What he's doing
Okay so we're going to
Turn into a
Terrorist and then you're going to go to it like
You can put it within scarecrows all you want but that's what you're doing so it doesn't matter how you say it
The Somerset
Putting this
Eating because you're not doing this again
So Jordan at this point the show kind of
He has a
Michael bagner
His name's actually Michael Patton
If you want to spell it
Craigslist
F****** ever.
Or on the internet at all
This guy
How is he
It's bad
Ba
Speaker backpack
You've got to teach a constant
I don't know I don't
What the president on the libertarian ticket
Michael Jordan
I tell you
I lied to
I'm sorry about the
But
The structure of this episode
This is not the last clip from April 8th
April 8th
I lied to you about nothing
Happening
April 7th
Did you just f****** Inception
No I didn't it's just how the narrative
How's the playing out of this
Nation mosque
What I'm about to
At the beginning of this episode
It wouldn't really matter
But now
You're really really does
That you sound like a benevolent race from a Doctor Who episode where you're like
You guys weren't ready for this information yet and now we have brought you to the
The point where you can handle
The idea of life
I'm not I'm not trying to tell you what dishonest story
Except
April 7th
Really f******
Bored
The part that I'm about to play
Also kind of bored
Until April 8th
This part of a
April 7th
Part of this 10 minutes
Just amazing to us
One of the fairest interviews he's ever done
And before you say anything I want to make clear about 1
I don't think
The pyramid art
I don't think that the tankers are guests their Putin Stooges
That's nonsense
We simplistic and Rusev ovik mindset
I don't believe
I absolutely don't believe that
I think there are
Believe that
Reality
Abundantly
That being said
The network is stay.
Most
Like it's the best interviews ever.
Berenstain Bears
April 7th episode
Or
He launches his
Soros effective
Didn't see an equation word on RT on April 7th
So there is a there was an interesting
I know I know I know
So
Here is where the interview starts
Alex / listen to the artist
Please
What is strong decorative
He's not mystery
Representing sat interview at all I watched the entire thing
I was thinking about like completely out of character
I was thinking about pulling
Clips from it and actually did record all of it
What alexplayz my
Oh no that's pretty much
That's pretty much
So we can listen to Alex
Like
Introduction of it
Clips from his show
Indicative
So here he start
Cuz a lot of folks watching The Prison Planet.
The world audience Erdos
Archie's in Austin Texas catching up with radio talk show host and documentary filmmaker
Sitting down with us today
What does Christian in several months after Obama stepped in as president of the United States
You make a documentary calling him a deceiver why
He said he wouldn't hire lobbyists all he's done
My power lobbyist
Every level of government
Head of the country over the oligarchs the international bankers
Alex Jones
The repeating narrative
Individually
They're just people who he
Has deemed
Some of them
But not all
Fasting
He's at the interviewer asks
He's a Deceiver
Why
Rehashing of the Obama
Deception air
About this that's not good to start out with
In this next clip
And what you say is that the American government is a puppet of the New World Order is that is that right
Absolutely I am a patriot
I believe in the free-market I believe in the red white and blue
Constitutional rights
And everything that the supposed government is doing
Is the opposite of that
Okay
Cool
The interviewer started by thing that you call Obama
A Deceiver
And this next clip Alex literally says that Obama is a fever one thing that I really want to point out
Really want everybody to be clear on and I think everybody kind of
Those people who say they're into the Constitution always a constitution
Bill of Rights
And really never talked about any of them other amendments passed
No cuz they really don't like those amendments
Like popiah AOL
I like those guys
The everything past the
Or whatever
Most of them take everything past the Second Amendment and none of the Constitution
Yeah
Alex actually
Recalls Obama a Deceiver
Right
How do you say Barack Obama as
American president President Barack Obama is the deceiver
He says one thing
Does the opposite
And that's the only
Sing that is constantly Barack Obama
Building self
Vampire establishment
But really he is completely
And paid for
Body scrub
Here's the next
How do you see the future of American politics
United States is corrupt
That has been used by International Banks in the global crime syndicate
To expand their empire worldwide
Okay
Ukraine
Is one of the people who are like
Free with Artie
Where Alex list.
This interview
I'm out on
April 6th
2 days before
The episode is on April 6th
2009 two days before the episode we listen to.
If I was going to make a prediction based upon introduce this clip I would guess what
No mention of
Alleged that the Bilderberg Group from the world who are they exactly
The number group is the Queen of England
The queen of the Netherlands
Is Rockefellers
It is the Rothschilds they write books they brag about it for years ago saying
He wants $12 in US dollars
And they're these incredibly wealthy powerful families
The play with the nation
No mention of sore
Not a single man
Weird
Today's earlier
Just two days earlier
So so you would you would suspect
Russian media Outlets
I want to talk to you about this
Cuz I have a lot of field
Yeah
This is very interesting for a number of reasons
I think you're are super not out of the norm for things he normally says
He's not waiting outside of Israel
What is the difference
Feel when it's being presented on the state
Media channel 4
When Alex is it Obama's deceive
It's not saying that he's a liar
That's things that Russia is right not to
Proposed
In the talks between Obama
When I was says that you asked the US has a corrupt Empire
Croton
Georgia
What's going on in Syria
And that the US
Response is simply an expression of the
Yeah it takes on a very different
Feel in that
Contact
But all that is good and well but really interest me about this interview is
Who is interviewing out
What
The interview was being done by a woman named Anastasia
Who is the prominent journalists cigar teeth
For a while
In addition to being a reporter
She's also the daughter of Vitality vitality cherkin
You may remember him from earlier as Russians Russia's ambassador to the UN
Who sang the Russian
Miquel
If the US put their radar
Republic
We're
Been a prominent member of Russia's Foreign Relations team
Representative
Do you win since April
And even quicker to veto UN resolution
He was the one to
DeVito 13 resolution
Many of which were about human rights abuses
A few others about George
Ukraine
3 resolution
Before becoming Russia's main man at the UN
Vitality
Having
Risen up from the US desk
To becoming the Ambassador
The Belgium and Canada in the early
Anderle
My point here is working is
Big player in Russian International politics in Florida
And it seems
We can stretch of credulity
Imagine that Alex wouldn't know who
He is
Given the fact that chicken was a naysayer with
The most the United Nation
I find it very unlikely though
But he wouldn't
He was being interview
Daughter
I don't think that's possible
The only way that it's not possible
Is it Alex has no idea about the world's he pretends
Know about
Which
I accept
Let's
Pump the brakes on that would real quick
I respect that
I respect
The best I'm going to give you a 50/50 yesterday on that
I don't know.
Now you might also remember Vitality chicken is one of
Sue died
Special circumstances
Single action
I have no idea
He really died of a heart attack is made
The media people have suggested or if it was a political murder
He's a very strong possibility that
Coincidence
Wasn't
Be home
This is just random
Like he was like he was 35
You know
No you
For his birthday
Look I don't want to I don't want to talk about
Too much because I think
There are parts of it that are Trucking
Yeah there were these nine
Who died
In the nine months
The election
Right
And they were all
Extant
Diplomatic people in
In honor of that
Yeah I remember that
Delicious
Horsey Sauce
I don't like the conspiracies to go around about this
We're trying to tie them all together in the same way that I don't
Pharisees that Mike Adams and Alex
It's about the idea of like
People who are like
MetroHealth
Cures and
Call Vic
Vehicle went
Like these are
Young people
There's not there's no reason
All of them are
And it's just suspicious
Doesn't prove
It doesn't necessarily
Daughter
It's entirely possible it's all just
So I don't know I don't know what
Cheerleader
Anything but
A lot
That analogy it is a million arrows pointing to Bugs Bunny's hole
You cannot prove bug bunnies down there
But God damn it if there weren't a lot of arrows
And Circumstance
This stuff
Really
Bothers me
Yeah it's only because
It's happening
And I always wish happy
Revelations happen later
You like
No you got to deal with it but I wish that
The store Rose pivot
You know I don't know two-month
Blindsided
Another want to talk about it we were having a conversation in 2009 than we were in 20 acres
I know
It is weird
FEMA camp stuff that was so fun 2009
I thought we could keep going
Great ride
Is introduced Olmos
I want I want a
But
I'm
I'm very self-conscious
And I'm very
It's about a lot of this
This is so frustrating
It's still frustrating
It's hard to make sense of
I want I want to have I want to be free
I want to save it you know
The guardian is right about all kinds of s*** but
I think you take we can
Hard take that
Boiling that Takis
It's it's
Unrewarding
On some level
For all these months
Waiting for
Talk about Sarah
Yeah
He does
It's also
Coincidental
Around a very
Specific hotspot
Dean Russo American religion
He was in a
Review by art
Two days prior
And a month
Before Soros did
Interview but how like
We need
Attack
Russia
And we still
Can't say
Anything
It really bums
But
Is the path of honesty
So I'm okay
Anyway Jordan
I don't know what to tell you
But will be back
Next episode
Talking like it you hate not knowing this isn't it
Furious
Or at the very least it's a thing that in order for you to know would require
Contacts
At the level
God I wish we could pretend
What if you are hiring
We will pay you nothing
II
It's parts
Partially also like
The last episode we did on Friday
That was f******
That was heavy
Yeah
Kind of an episode off
Coming back
Dammit
I'm human
I would like to walk
I would like
We're doing the show in Austin
Sometimes it's
Various
Difficult to get
You know
Contacts
Actually we have on our description on items
Variably hard to get through
I would love
For the last episode
Real
Except
Of
I would love for the next episode
The beach
Dance on his face
Here's what I'm excited
What if
Alright this is my this is my great excitement
Some kind of Philip K Dick's story
Would love desperately all right
So
Alex
In 29
Is living in an actual parallel universe to Alex in 2009
How many year
So every 2019 episode
Has a direct parallel to a 2009 episodes
The bigot in the High Castle
Guys in the middle on Spotify by preciate everybody so much this is
Episode
Will be back
We got a website called the bigger in the High Castle
Yeah
I've got to get
Flow my tears
The police band
Go home and tell your mother you're ubik
We are a group called go home and tell your mother you're not a bigot
We're also on the X
The Jesus of iTunes
You did that she brought up some it's my fault you can download
Describe Libra View
Leaving Eldridge review those are twice as I get it I get it
Killed anybody probably led people down so bad Road probably.
Like young women into heroin and I'm not throw the said they probably died as a result of
That I'm not Rose.
But he didn't kill anybody but one guy technically probably did
Arika in this episode and that guy is Alex Jones
Holding
Alex