Alex
Alex Jones
Have you ever bought a sex toy
Friend of the show Mighty DeRosa has been a lot of time
He bought me a flashlight
From doing the week of shows and
Cleveland Cleveland
Yeah cuz I didn't really get paid
The shows
The fund the ride
Through
I think we have to Indiana
Victorious baby sex shop
About getting a flashlight
For this
I can't afford this
You just too much
Curious
Whatever I never really.
Flashlight knockoff type thing
If you were when Marty was like going to the checkout and what has he he saw me looking at these
Lowrance sex toys
Make it around
What kind of friend Marty DeRosa is Astoria number times I don't mind putting his business
I have that flashlight for a little while
It wears out its novelty
Yeah the excitement of
First time around is is great but then overtime
Becomes a hassle
Like going to clean it
Google has the best bet about
I'm sure I would paraphrasing
It was my own complaints
Do not does not wear out it's excitement for me thank you
Give a shout out to
And are supporting the show
Thank you so much you are now
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
You are now a problem
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Kris Kross
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Criss-Cross
Christopher Cross
Fair enough
Elevated
You are now attacking
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean accent
I don't want
Jesus Christ
But these guys do I'd like to support that you could do that
We would a
Appreciate it
Induction
We're probably about two weeks behind
You became the entire beginning of the show
You know beautiful like 2:50
Into trouble
We've got first of all sorry about the weird schedule this
Supposed to Monday Wednesday Friday
I just
Keep up quite frankly
I'll take this one
Matter of
This is
To do our last episode with all the Soros business
Stuff like that
Sometimes
The workload is too much
Tuesday Thursday
Back to normal
Next week
I'm not defensive about it I just want to live
Not really but I'm not
Today Jordan we are going to be going over on modern day ever
Going to be going over the
Of January 2019
In in
In the year of Our Lord I'm still writing
That's correct
I get out of that happen
Episode
Alex's had this big news broke recently I have you heard something
Think about this and that is that
He lost
Little League
Situation
Where in
The Sandy Hook families will be able to
I get in Discovery
Some of his financial documents internal memos
Yeah
There's this there's this legal situation and everybody bring it up to me
I wanted to be able to address it by covering whatever Alex is talking about about it
Not talkin about it
So I listen to Monday and a lot of it is just
Complaining about that Gillette commercial
That's a 04
That's a non-starter
Not not really caring so much
Watch over that episode but
Tuesday the
The 15th actually interested
Merits talking about
And so we will
Here is an out-of-context drop
From Today Show
Donald Trump like tacos
And Obama likes like winners
I get it
Alex likes to have
Fun
Refuse refuse
Piece of his conversations
He's having where he's defending Trump getting all those burgers for
The football team Clemson football team
Get it
Cuz he likes
I don't know
We will start the show with what
Maine Marathon
Surprise anyone
Your any
Of this store
Of nonsense
I really important story that illustrates why we can't take this country back
Representative
Overboard
Adam contest quote from the New York Times
Shoreline
Vicious lie Factory
Remove words
Clearwater
And none of the media will eat
White supremacist
White supremacy
When you got a public statement
Today
I have experienced that they are times
They are
Devils
You can kind of see there at the end that a lot of the energy that's driving this is probably about Alex's own personal
Listen to every episode of the show
In the present day as I have
To the past but I don't remember him talking that much about Steve
Do it the past
It surprises me not to hear him defend Steve King
But that it surprises me to hear
I haven't heard you talk much about that guy
Defense
Bet you do it publicly
Is a bad boy
It's that it's not in my memory
The dedotated strikes a novel Court
Anything that would assimilate I would associate him with the white National
But that's only because the New York Times is taking
New contact
And putting him in that box right never
Nationalist to talk about it because he's never been
For being a white nationalist or white supremacist before because Dan of course he is never said anything
The issue
How does white supremacy
Attitude
Supremacist
Quote
It's
He talks about illegal aliens
Okay
He says we should be proud of the accomplishments of Western Civilization absolutely
Are the Japanese proud of themselves
Not the same thing
It's just it's just a Rosetta Stone into everything
How they lie how they manipulate
And how the Republicans
To curry favour with the left
Race Pace leopard constituents
Hoverboard
So he's mad
Alex's pretty bad
Really quick
P by taking Steve's
But not turning on Steve King cuz they disagree with his
Positions or anything like that
The only reason they stripped him of his committee seats
Is because Randy feenstra
Iowa State
It just announced his candidacy
Run against King
2020 primary
If it didn't have a very viable replacement waiting in the wings
Outspoken
Like they have for years
Does it have a primary challenge
Looks Like You Can Go the Distance
Costanza
Supremacist and that is why they have gotten rid of 98% of
There's a second because for years I served as a i
Immigration policy and that's
I'm so
Politicians who wanted to Curry favor with that side of the
The Republican Party
With him in a way that I
I've seen a couple of reporters described as like he was a kingmaker
Right-wing immigrations.
But now he isn't that anymore Trump is so he doesn't even function
For the right-wing
Together the primary candidates successfully without the baggage
He doesn't serve what role he used to serve
Make a list of course they're going to throw them away. It's nothing to do with his white supremacy the comments that he's making
Understand
Ignored
4 years
Steve King has always been on some b*******
But this current examples that he's going through right now
Him questioning why what's white supremacy is considered a bad thing
Then claiming that the New York Times made up
2018 The Weekly Standard reported that while speaking with
Stop
He was talking about how some local jalapenos were grown in Mexican shirt
Which conversation turned from literal dirt to Heather's metaphorically a lot of dirt
After the article came out tonight ever having said such a thing
Accused The Weekly Standard a notoriously conservative Outlet
And demanded proof. They released the full tape
Leftist lies exist without original sources because they are false and manufactured accusation
So they did
They release the tape exactly what the
And showed can clearly calling immigrants
And asylum-seekers.
Play this game again with the New York Times
I don't feel like I have much interest in giving him the benefit of the doubt
Is it possible that such an out-of-touch bigot
But he doesn't realize how old vert might be
I don't care
Because the evidence that Steve King is a real f*****-up raises a******
Go far deeper than not liking illegal immigration
I've been quote-unquote proud of the West
Is Alex's asserting
One time
Give me the comic
ER that's
And so that's why he can throw around the n-word all the
He's not a racist
I've heard a lot of those doing comedy over the years down
The US House of Representatives in 2000
Over that span of time representative King assets
Intense
Also did you know that until at least 2016 Steve had a Confederate flag on his office desk
Which was in the union during the Civil War
People like to say that's a message
Kemah go on to remove the flag
From his desk after Scott Michael Green murdered two police officers in a style killing
In 2017
Footage was found of green being asked by other police officers
The Urbandale High School football game
Who's attending a Confederate flag black students
Charleston South Carolina
Because of his racist ideology
And everybody started talking about how it's f***** up
Confederate flags are flown estate houses
King it with speech
Confederate flag calling it wasn't for the South
And saying quote
I regret deeply that we're watching this country be divided again over a symbol
Again he represent Iowa
Different different thing
Different things different
Iowa
Better if he was from the south
Like one of the actual Confederate
The argument of Southern Pride and that sort of thing would make way more sense
Bent to be doing this SB
Representative for a Union state
I don't know anyway
In September 2016 he went on a little
Condemning black people having abortions
Because they listen to people in the
Congressional Black Caucus
Same quote
They chose to have a Congressional Black Caucus
They chose to have an abortion
I would give you even money that a vast majority of mothers who say they can't afford an abortion have an iPhone which cost more
That's a cool comment
How about them welfare Queens
It does feel a little bit subtle their reason our way into this
Betty literal red flags
Benefits there was the time in 2018 with members of Austria's freaking party
The political party that was
A literal member of the Nazi SS
When asked about it
Every presently set of the group America pushing the platform they push they would be Republicans
No
That doesn't mean what you think
Spell probably
Of course this was his campaign for the
Toronto after the 14 words of white supremacy
Patriots prize no on that he supported
The 14 words
We can't restore our civilization with somebody else's baby
By the way was repeated by David in all caps
Said
God for Steve
#truth Rising
This guy is never been opened
Out-of-control Chevrolet
David July 2016 parents on MSNBC right around the Republican National Convention time
Steve King extolled the virtues of
People
I'd ask you to go back through history and figure out what contributions have been made by these other categories of people that you're talk
Talking about any other subgroup of people contribute more to civilization
He was later called on it and kind of apology meant Western Civilization instead of white people
Which is really just a perfect example of giving up
The game dog whistles rsf1
What I meant sorry I've already
Which means
Jordan a******
In July 2013 he didn't interview with Newsmax quote Forever Young
Undocumented immigrant who's a valedictorian
There's no doubt there are 130 lb I got calves the size of cantaloupe
Because they're hauling 75 pounds of marijuana across the desert
Cool bro
Steve King won his first election
22002 by whipping
Proposed bill to make English the official language of Iowa
Why
I just be my response
I don't know why that's an important issue unless you're just trying to wedge people a little bit
Drum up
Insecurities
Some fears about the other
It was it was weird
Floated that built
The Iowa City
Official sister city
Berlin
Killer with a certain subsection
In 2012 by illegal aliens
M13 more killed by drunk driving illegal
You just making up stuff
But the rhetorics.
And you can hear the same talking point
Repeated ultra-conservative propaganda video
I've definitely heard that exact line come out of Alex's mouth
Lisa doesn't
In November 2009 he skipped his son mix wedding
The cast of pointless vote against the Affordable Care Act
That one battery last point about his racism motor 2.5 a vehicle
FamilySearch
Yeah
Indo I in June 2018 he told Breitbart that he didn't want Muslims working in meat factories
Infidel Muslims are not eating
So as long as they're preparing for infidels to help send them to hell and must make happy
I don't want people doing my
Doing that with my pork that won't eat it
Let alone hope they go to hell for eating pork chops
Convoluted understand I think what he's trying to express his he's worried
That Muslims will taint the pork
Because they know that other Muslims aren't eating
Or something like that I think that's what he's trying to express
Uncle thing but I cuz otherwise because otherwise
Eat it so
F****** what
I think he's
Sounds like I'm
Call Shirley
Sensitive to
As long as they're preparing the report for infidels and help sends them to hell
Infidels are sent
Yeah you're going to the meet somehow
Even if you're not
Scary muzzle
Mozart
What he's saying is that Muslims
Are joyful
Preparing
For white folks
In order to ensure that by Vera Lynn
Code
People go to hell problem with that part
Which
About like the idea
That they're doing a great job cuz they know when people eat it
Can you get great pork I guess
The real
Pretty f*****-up
Good way to look at that
Tweet when he posted Bart article and editorial
5% of Italians
Now oppose Mass immigration
Europe is waking up
King retweeted that saying quote Europe is waking up
Will America in Thai
I hate to see her
This takeover
I hate
To see our country
Hate to see prisoners at Abu ghraib prison were revealed
Just teasing
You know how I say that
Through The Years Kingsman supporter of all the far-right foreign politicians that Alex also love
We see we seen Steve King strongly support geert Wilders Marin the Viktor Orban
He was being interviewed by those Austrian Nazi descendants I mention
Advocated the position that Soros
Was behind the grate
Westerners may replace culturally
The demographic Lee
So he has been for his entire
This kind of
His story is an interesting story
The conservative body politic
This country
In order to understand a little more about how that's
It's important to follow the money
If you look at the information to the public about Steve Canyon who's donating
You seem interesting picture
The first thing that jumps out to you is that in the 2017 2018 cycle
Do you like me
First place among his donors
But $10,800 in donations
Individuals being sent that his way from within the Navy
Which it does not make me
Doesn't make me feel great
He also got $10,000 from the John Bolton political action committee but I don't know what to make
But
If you look at his past fundraising
You'll see a very interesting trend
Name of it is numbers are pretty normal for most years
Then take a massive Spike
In the 2012 election
He goes from 1.02 million raised
Cycle
The 3.8 million just two years later
A lot of that money
Over 250,000 organization called Club
For growth
Which seems like a really fun nice name
In reality the group is a far-right fundraising outfit whose activities went into overdrive in
Least 10 billion dollars that then governor of Wisconsin
Wisconsin Scott Walker
To oppose his recall vote and support his initiative to strip collective bargaining
Protection
And crippled you know
You misunderstand their name
You think it means a collection of people who are pro-growth
What it is is a literal
That is for the growth of the white nationalist
Orthopedic back road
Notzoey
What's interest
Koch Network fun
Like Freedom partner
Gamefowl Steve King 11000
$300 in the family research Council
Suspiciously named political action committee
Clearly aren't front
On the nose
There's a huge push in the 2012 election to retain what
Seawing of the Republic
Looking party
And to not succumb to dwindling support
But definitely was happening
That point
Part of this was a massive cash
Confusion in the coffers of various people
We're carrying the banner of
People funding the Tea Party were into
And Steve King was absolutely one of the main figure
Face swelling of his
Really hard to think that's not
The case was about
Small-government Dan it had no reaction to black president
Sooner
You see that exact same pattern when you look into the money going into other Tea Party
Louie gohmert is a bit of an exception because he was a republican running attack
Pretty much a sure thing
But Michele Bachmann is another great
She raised just under 3.5 million of the 2008 election
The number skyrocketed to 13.5 in 2010 and 15 million in 2012
Who is Michele Bachmann
Top donor throughout her career
You guessed it
The Club for Growth
Who is Ted Cruz's all-time top Downer
Call Firgrove
Who is Rand Paul's career spanning top donor
The Club for Growth
With over a hundred thousand dollars from them coming in the 2012
There's a concerted effort on the part of very rich conservative interest
To ship the politics of the right to a more extreme version of
Conservatism
In the 2012 election cycle
And before but that was crunch time
That's not news
It's not even news to say that Steve King was a big part of
What is important
Because it demonstrates the sort of things that they were interested in being part of that ship
Defected it outright white supremacist was among their top guys
Should tell you everything that you need to know
About what they wanted
The Overton window to move towards
At that time
What was it what was the word you used
I suppose
It wasn't disintegration it was
Descendants
Deterioration
Raz-b apotheosis
We're talking about the same thing just looking at it
Who is mayor of former Republican National Committee spokesperson
Just Steve King has done for the Republican Party
Very very few Grassroots Conservative Republican
Actually
However
Do you Mabel's elected Republicans were more restrictionist or otherwise hard-line to strike a pose if it reads as mod
That's the kingmaker
Yeah he is the person who people are able to
Be around
Is that Donald Trump is that you don't have to
Ostensibly
Distance himself from
Steve King
Where is like
This guy says all the stuff that I want to stay
But because I can
Myself from him
I can do all the stuff
That results
Without ever being
Associated
Really you're if you're pretty far right
Card right
And you have a guy who's
Outright
Fascist
You look like you're pretty close to the middle
And that's an important person to have around
Absolute quite frankly
Explain
In some ways
Spend so much money
Keeping him around despite his horrible
And I think almost everybody
Who understood politics
To an extent
Knew that that's the role these are
And why Republicans would never take Target
And now we've come to a point where
Where he's no longer needed
Would you like a
Appendix
Is a vestigial organ of
The bigotry machine
That needed to be put in place
The machine is in place now
You don't need that appendix right so he's getting removed
And
That's that
Whatever his nonsense about Steve King being all aboveboard about stuff
Nonsense
That idea of a liberal
Pedialyte
I don't think anyone who listens to our share of that
New disguise
But I just wanted to
Really
And I think it's some of that
Important stuff
Important again to note that in the
The 2018 election
All of his wife
Supremacist views where I
WYD
Like
See them
Super clear and
You still won re-election
Buy 1/4 + 1
You still need it
Hit his Challenger with a Dumber
Republicans
They're still going to defend him
There's another option
So we have that other option
Well Steve will be out of office in 20
Yep you'll lose that primer
Any something in this next clip that I think is a brutal slippers
For the tongue
Not like saying something racist
But I bet you just as Edward Edward Edward Edward Edward Edward a Alex
He said something here
Just makes me think
Oh my gosh oh my gosh
Organization organization
Clearly
And the New York Times removes that out
You asking up there
It's incredible
The mapping white people making up the internet
Marc Jacobs the internet with their opinions
Pissing on fire hydrant
Dry white piranha
I think your eyes perked up at exactly the point about
We all know his talk
That's a weird thing for Alex to say I think it's a real bad flip up because
That implies that ideas that King 1000r talkin
And the fact that Alex leaves her with them
To the point of claiming to know what he meant to say in this interview
Seems to imply that they might be getting talking points from the sniveler source
I don't know
It seems very
Very strange phrasing
Arthur's one
But you've always been
It's so unfair to
Maybe a little unfair
Being super fussy
I could see an argument that I'm making a mountain out of a molehill very strange
We all know his talkin
Every Republican and Democratic
Never says that people who agree with him have talking point
That's a fair point always talks about how like all of his weirdo Patriots
They're just on the same page naturally
Everything
It's because they just know the truth
And they're right about everything
So for him to be saying something about
Steve
But he has talking points
It seems like
Little bit of a
Really good point
King isn't
The one
Controlling what's
Marriott points that means
That they're coming
From somewhere you didn't create the
Exactly
Does implied
I don't know
Anyway
In his next Wipeout
I'm going to go through every angle
That true
New York Times machine how they twist
Once they put out one big lie
Define someone
No.
Real things they said that's defining
Illegal aliens
Have double the crime rate of the average citizen that's it
Becomes the white supremacist
The bus and
Signal
What else is trying to describe there is basically house
He does stuff
Yeah like the idea of attaching things to people and like rating
Perception based on
Well blurring lines
And stuff like that absolute
Idea about like immigrants committing
Stuff like that
That is a white supremacist
You don't need
Latched onto him
Statistic of being
Somehow I supremacist
Things that
Is bulshit or at least white nationalist
Justin Bieber
Is it like
That's unfair
Virtual level that is
Ridiculous
It's just because the report
News like
Muzzling
Things
Some have described this as races
Can't be more overseas
He is
Indigo
Directions
Score going out of their way
To try and be
Quotes
Fair
And s*** like that
Liberal
Media Outlets don't want to call racism racism
Yeah yeah yeah
4th and he keeps a couple times now
Immigrants
Crime
Are the Oxford criminology and criminal justice Research Unit did a study on immigration
And crime
In 2017 that
Reflected a bunch
Different studies
Compiled
Here are some excerpts
Research has consistently shown is negatively associated with crime overall
Colin is not significantly either violent or property crime
If an undocumented immigrant is arrested for a criminal offense
Before a missed.
Additionally
We're such access is not available
That last part is completely obvious given the being charged with the crime might jeopardize our access to essential services
Which is entirely against
The study further found that foreign-born victims
The crimes are much less likely to report crimes against them
Because of fears of being mistreated by the police or being deported
Some statistics they found for pouring over all the data
Between 2005 and
Incarceration rate Rose 16% Among Us
But only 7%
Foreign-born
Nonsense
They started his own Hometown to be there was any pattern
Between
Using Austin city
Retract level analysis
Mansfield found no relationship between doing the immigration and serious property crime
Deposited the new arrivals might have revitalized neighborhoods
By causing a bottom-up growth among Mexican immigrants commercial Enterprises
They reviewed violent crimes
Statistics in cities of high drug and homicide issues like Miami
Immigrants were not the people committing
These crimes
But in many cases
Second generation
Brett's work
So they refine the data analysis and found the places with high rates of Financial Security
Just to say jobs and access to Social Services slower than average
Which cities yes this is effects
Poverty is mitigated by access to Social Services
And employer
Those are two things being around has no relation
To Immigrant status
What I would find
This would be such a
Interesting experiment
Worthy
Consequences
Is for misdemeanors
End end
Keno like nonviolence
Crimes
Equal 4
As they are for
Demented
Would we see a massive drop
Do you know I'm saying like
Imagine if there was a real threat that you would get to
Deported
Dollar Tree
You know like
I just you and I
How much lower do you
If the threat
Disincentivize and aspect
It's almost it almost seems like that is
More of a deterrent
The death
I don't have
You know I accessed the statistics on that but it makes intuitive sense
Like that
Kind of
Account for a
Interesting idea
Saudi studies also looked at Chicago
A 2009 study looked at neighborhoods of poverty rates in low employee
And the researcher found in areas where there were large populations of recent
The number of homicides
Priest vallon
Reinvigoration of neighborhoods when do immigrants arrive
There is there is very good
The crime goes down
When there's an inn
Influx of immigrants
City
Like when
Always been the case for first-generation immigrants
Has always been
Dude weird scraping to get buy-in
Your f***
Not our
We're trying to make it our own
Impossible
Fit into
Like when they talk about
Bastardization
It's awful all of this
Diversity and we don't have enough
White representation
Infinitely
We better
And just even in ways that are statistics
Retractable
Yeah
You can find 100 studies again to the
The minutiae of exactly how the idea that
Commit more crimes than citizens
Wrong
We can leave that here for now
The only studied seems to indicate that immigrants commit more crime comes from the prevention Research Center in Atherton
Undocumented immigrants
146 percent more likely to be convicted of crime
Then the control subsets there was used
Throw the data out here because it relies on arrest numbers for 1985
2017 in Arizona know that Joe Arpaio was busy
Police Department in recent memory in Arizona's most populous city
I'm not sure how much that skews the data but I'm sure it does
I'm sure it at least
Is a factor in it so I'm going to go ahead and say I don't accept that study
Well I mean if they just arrested for all the crimes he committed then that
30 would be reversed by a million percent
Committed immigrants had in Arizona if you just arrested Joe Arpaio
Did a crime it would Reverse by
Margin of 221
Perhaps
All this is just to say that claiming that immigrants have double the crime rate in the United States is an expression of white supremacy
It's a talking point
Of the people out there who seek to spread fear of Shifting demographics
And faceless paranoia about white genocide
Italics
What's going on
Anyway
It should come as no surprise especially based on
Start
Always lying about immigrants
It should surprise
Nobody
Immediately decide
Start season 2 of Caravan paranoid
Big Caravan is on its way
Decision
Hundreds of Honduras
Look up the Apple photos and those countries hits.
Just like they said
Hundred
Always a close shot of a woman
Weather child
Camera
And it's 10,000 20,000 30,000 40,000 50,000
Oun fun
Childish works
That's how the globalist get this job done
Another tree welfare
Everything else up here
So
That's that's that's that's
Cool you're a f****** piece of s*** feel the need to respond to that that's just
That's the that yeah
Surprises
More than anything else
Is that he didn't
I don't get why it's wrong
You say you're a
It's wrong just don't know he does a little bit but he's just talkin about the Nationalist
You deflect that sorta stuff is easier for him to vent
Like fully own that space
Coach Dave did
But Alex is being assertive
Nationalist is just
White
And nationalized not a compound
Noun like with Coach Dave
Oh man you might
With Alex
You f*** your deflector
You f***
The Caravans coming back
Caravans it's bigger than ever
Are we angry and Hondurans do they Alex's
Alex I challenge you
Without
Any primer
Tell me where Honduras is
I know the capital is
Love cap
I do you love
Funland
Names
Burkina Faso capital is
I know
Madagascar
With the antenna Revo
Fun
Yeah not that I can't get on the trade routes I've had
Between there's news that this is happening
And that is what the leftist
Mule
Machete funded by the
Shooting Hispanic pregnant women
Watch all that
Believe it and then they that go to
That makes no sense
Watch machete
Directed by Robert Rodriguez
That's cool man
I told you
A second ago that we didn't
The Robert Rodriguez and what do you know
Rodriguez
Super Why
I took care of all that
We are great in that sin
Robert Rodriguez
Do you know do you know what's really
He does not say
Danny Trejo
No
Fuckingawesome
Danny Trejo is
The coolest I mean after all of his
But he's a f****** cool
Did you know that he owns a f****** Donuts
I didn't know that
Play music
It's amazing when I was in LA he may
Incredible
Is great
Danny Trejo
Coupon out of donuts
Adult
Feel good you could have just said a new sentence
Complaints about Robert Rodger
Taking issue with Robert Rodriguez
That being in his list of complaints it's strange
Disinfect
You brought up the
He was raised by white
People suggested
You think he's a race traitor or that he owes them
To be one of us
We will
Manifesting a lot of these sort of
Text Ernest ideas whether it's insulting
Robert Rodriguez
Complaining
Sister working
These drug cartels
Spouting this b*******
Things about that immigrants
He gets a little bit of that out of his system
I didn't say that
Mark
It kinda is though we shouldn't be proud of
Yep kind of sugar group
They are alive
They remove the words are out of the quote
One word or two words
White supremacist
Surrounded
That is pure evil
Want to
Purchasing
Love The Virtue signaling today
Even voted
Everybody to say Steve
Save that shitt
House of Representatives
Representative
Garbage
Steve King was like
Yeah I agree with you
We could definitely tell me not to say that s*** in his speech of around that he met
And his response
Look let's just be clear about this the quote in the New York Times
Wasn't just one or two words in quotes
And then just
Creating a quote around it
And even Steve King admits to that you're in a second
Alex's make it back s*** up
So steep King up to the podium on the house floor and wasn't racist
But him saying these things that the New York Times
Disclaimer
His case in general is very
Convincing
So I'm going to tell you that the words are likely what I said but I want to
But I want to read it to you the way I believe I said it
And that's where
White supremacist Western Civilization
How did that language become offensive
First of all
He keeps saying
This is what I believe I said
What is track record on these things it's pretty shity
But he's not offering anything anyways any more convincing than what the New York Times
Just adding western civilization in the middle of the quote in no way makes it better
These feel saying exactly the same thing as the original quote
He's just now making it clear that he believes Western Civilization
Directions to making it worse
In the era of shity apologies this one is particularly Wild
Even says quote it's 13 words ironically that caused this
If you want
Why is 13 words a run
In what sense is 13 words and ironic number unless it's because
The topic at hand was white supremacy and that's just the 14th
In his apology
On the house floor
He's signaling to whites
Supremacist
Exactly what he said and he isn't sorry about it at all
I think everybody would like
White
Coding a lot more
Thousand words
Instead of the four
Show me 12 though
The Bakersfield
I know but
Do you need to make a Baker's like a
Super ambitious Baker, 14th
Keywords for beatitude
I don't want to
Ourselves is sort of
Editors for haggai
Supremacist
But I love
Really well well written
More than
Psychic
To put a fine button on it that even in his apology
She's making clear the what he saying
Be more clear
Defend
Steve Vai kind of using wipes
Defend him
Weird
Alchemy
What's the score
White supremacy
Which they don't
White supremacy 2
Wichita
See how he does
The balcony
They take the words
And you go
See what they did
Tricky very very sneaky these New York Times
I don't know I don't know what what else to say about that other
That's that
That's very dumb
I feel like you got if you're going to bring up Alchemy
Ogden 6 Fullmetal Alchemist
Which is weird
If we're in 2018 you better believe Alex is going to complain about the Chinese
Alex finally gets around
Complaining about something
Because the Chinese are totally ethnocentric
Completely maximum
And they know that their funding for Hollywood
Weathers race war in America in division
Execute you for that
It's on your record it's not on like the real real
It's not like real it's on your six of the eight movie houses are not trying to force everyone
Which one which one
I mean we went over this like a year-and-a-half ago when you started this.
Names I wouldn't know
Do they own you
Dan is Disney
Still American
22 the new it
Incase
You know one of the things that I'm really trying to do is highlight how Alex Jones
Really him defending himself
Because we are the same
They're very similar in terms of what they believe what they stand for
In the same way
Steve King
Existed in the world of politics to be the guy
Look less extreme next to Alex Jones in the world of media existed in the exact same capacity
Actually does and Compares himself to seek it
A good decent Christian man very wholesome I watch this because many times I've read is right and just
Mine just good
Wholesome Americana
Got to love it
What happened
I mean like
If you look at this he probably met a little further back in the third act but we know
You don't need to like
This is where it becomes almost absurd that we're doing the show
I lost
I think he's a great man he's just like me I'm good wholesome
Alright
Rope and the amount necessary to hang yourself but did you give yourself the correct amount
It's wild to me that I even try to lay things out like information
It like that
Do a 5-minute episode radio playlist
Out of the same dues this but knowledge fight
Martin Luther King Junior has a street named after
Not just 1 hour.
Classic
White supremacist white nationalist
Pinpoint
No
So bad everyone wouldn't be trying to get into white Christian
That's very basic white nationalist
The idea of like which kind of just
Try to rewrite and undo all the history of how did those countries get
There's that but even after we deal like
Just on an economic monetary level
Before we talk about that
You have to unpack his language and he's saying White
Christian Nation
So it's just taking his red and assume for Alec
What's that America is
Nation
Which is
Kind of again
A black
People didn't want to be here so bad
Why did they get on those boats
Do it huh
Come here
Thrown off those boats
Whenever I
In a legal slave trade
Miserably
Nephew flash forward to the modern day
Exploding of the Decades
The Decades of generations
The affluenza
From the amount of infrastructure
The relative security to the rest of the world the stability
That's the thing is
Built on the backs of these other countries that we
Pillaged
Exploited
Over the years
So dis ideas
If we're so bad why do people want to come here
Because of
The things that we've been able to afford
Based on
Adventurism
We're so bad
Nation
I want to come here
Why is it that when we strip behind all of South
Forgot
Destroyed
They would then want to come to where the resource
And this is demonstrative of why this is
Alex
So flippantly is just like
Come on man you got it yet to try better
And have you heard
The Africa
Want to tape
Landowner
Watch
Yeah
That's a different episode of Alex's show but yeah
So you know
Here he just had some more
Wax yet
What was no the West has a guilt christianese us it's good to keep us from killing each other
Used against us
Gilt Gilt turned into foaming at the mouth
Racist
Against white people
What is a become the majority
Chicken
Why people are being taught them
Be guilty and stand
Into a frenzy
Justice they're taking power
Gross
Pretty grab
Yeah I mean
No there's not much do you need to unpack there
It's just an expression of the
These really messed-up racial ideas that
Expresses
Yeah
Feel the need to say anything
If you listen to that clip and you disagree with what you already know I think
We're done
You can you can stop
You can stop listening now. Already
Present
You don't you don't get
Through an episode
Complain about the Chinese
You don't get through an episode without hearing praise
For someone else
Going to the highest level of Martial law under dictatorship
I'm at the world
As even more authentic
Text our yes
He doesn't
I just like George Washington TV was a colonel and all the rest of it
The Real McCoy mean I don't disagree with most of the things he's saying except I think they're bad
You know like he's The Real McCoy yes
Of power and
Shoring up his power
He's more well-spoken than Trump you bet you
Almost everybody
Direct
Comparison would be when
You can grab them by the p****
And I moved
He would prefer to hear
Bolsonaro
Because you're not attract
Rape you I guess that's what he wish Trump would have said he wish
No
Brightright
Because they weren't
Attractive enough
I guess it's
I guess it's kind of debatable which is more better spoken
We already went over this last week about the idea that Alex is really showing his cards about really loving authoritarian
Dictator types
The coverage
Bolsonaro
It's it's
F***** up bud
Not surprised
No that wasn't coming out
Anyways
In terms of his like
This episode is Aurelio for document of his wife
Supremacist
Which surprise
The authoritarian dictator bootlegging
10 diabetes
Came out really to the Forefront
And surprising at all
The present day
Becoming
He's always pretended not to be pretending like it's not
Against every
Pretends to be
Bucked up
That
Look this is
Is all white
But it is
Also
Misogyny
All he is choosing
Every every person
Who ha
A f******
Credibly
And
Incredible
And proven to have committed
Text Melissa
Patterns of behavior sort of run together a little bit
I think that all of that
Is
It's always hard to tell exactly what piece of his identities more defensive about
When over Monday when you complaining about Gillette
I think that we would have much more of a
Speak based on his
Like horrible Chauvin if nonsense
His whiteness
Descendants
Is more prevalent in
The conversation
Just just just
Really hammered home
Men
That he thinks
Is that is that is
Nothing that is
Is part of that whiteness
Soupremacy is
Absolutely
Steve King also thinks
Women should
To be subject
Absolutely Alex
Women are sexy
Class C
Abs
These guys are going home
Their Call to Arms or whatever is that they believe that
They won't apologize for
They're chauvinism the living in the world that men created
So yeah
That's part and parcel of all of the
These these dudes absolutely look at
Alex's
Argument about
Immigration
And that sort of thing
Seems to have
You know
There is the idea that a Sovereign Nation can
Can just not let people in
Big piece of
He doesn't want open borders
No you do not come in
Unfortunately because
He's a s*******
The undercut
Entire argument
Because he wants
To defend Michael Savage
Preachers preaching
Savage
You can go
Yeah where are your papers exactly
Destination post
So if I understand correctly
His
Nations
Should have sovereign
And they should be able to
Enforce their borders
Which is why it's okay for America
To keep out
Whatever immigrants
If we decide our bad
But
Other Nation
Should not be allowed to exercise their sovereignty
By keeping out people
White people
I think we got that
Ha
So some Nation
Maybe
One in particular
If you will
Should be allowed
Non-white
God
Not know how dumb
I don't know I think he just knows that
The audience
Prone to pick up on those
Stove
Stupid
Lakeview dump
Have to say like
Good Sarah sovereignty
So we're not allowed to visit
Literally
Seems like
They set their own immigration laws and
Fire right by your principles
You need to support that
It's just stupid
Who cares
This is an interview with the guy who
May or may not have stopped
Is running Breitbart
Europe
I really care he's has a bunch of stupid nonsense
Interview Alex
Long time
Just good like mine though
This guy agrees with everything I'm saying
This interview was
In no way was
Changing it all
Have to
Even say
Dank nope
Just a random
I'm shittin that guy wouldn't
I went along with it and felt really good
Now we had a great agreement Fest and it really nailed at home
Bummer
There
Almost
It's like
We've we've dealt with
Over the years
Stroop
Soma
It is it is incredibly stupid
There's very little coherence on his show anymore like
Listening
Incredibly frustrating
Because
You can always get a sense that he doesn't want to do it
Anymore the feeling of that
Camp Layman
But now I agree with
I don't want him
A lot of
White supremacist apology
And the trend has been in
In the past
More of that earlier with
Praising bolsonaro
If you like you can't make it more clear
Lowe's
Dictator
We are watching
Rebellions against the globalist very very
Very closely in
Brazilian
Emerald Isle
Brazilian out of kingdom here in Australia they are quietly
The Irishman
Watch that with a very very please die
You know
You clearly said
Which side of that battle you're on
That that
Literally made in
You literally made an evil laugh
In regards
To a large group
Engaging in a battle
Everyone who is non-white
Yeah it was like really
Dangerous
Restriction
Policies
Emerald Isle
I don't know what I think that was
Yeah
I think he just was really grasping for words
I think you forgot
I forgot the countries clearly
I got to come up with a noun or a pronoun this is weird
So
After this Alex has an interview with this guy Dan lineman who runs
Europe wards.com
Just a little bit on the nose if we if we
One of our characters
Dan Lyman Lyman
Yeah a little bit Yeah Yeah
Give us that was a great novel
But that characters
What are you guys doing
Avenue 2nd
Alex started newswars and Europe Wars because he had a Infowars
You know maybe
People work trucks
So much
So you keep it on brand with newswars in Europe Wars maybe people who see the links
Know that it's a war
Infowars
Lakes
It's not important
But they do end up talking about her
I talked about this fast food buffet
But he gave Clemson football team
We're not going to talk about that
But it is
It's only it's only brought up as a
Transition
About why Trump
Eat so much fast food
Little
Defensive about it
Guys
We get it
You like
Young love the president
We don't need
You could not
You could just we could all just not give a s*** about what he eats very
I don't I don't know if they do
They're only bring it up because they want to create this idea
Trump is under like an intense amount of
And so they rationalized
Is so he doesn't get
Get poisoned by the globalist
Which is interesting Eminem
I leave
Giving us a revelation
His own life
Visa V poison
It has been said that Trump has a lot of fast-food especially now at this point because of the the low-risk
I'm having his food contaminated which you know I don't think any of us can really
Yes I mean
Poison
And I'm so
Date
President
No certainly not
Certainly.
Arsenic
Larger question
Why isn't
I don't know maybe some people are
You never hear about
Attempt
Threat against Obama when he was in office
A good strategy
Not
Make a lot of those
Publix
So I think there's probably
Maybe there are some sort
Taste like
Again a medieval
Prior to
There already is that in place in the White House
Already
Getaround
But there's already there's already protocol in place
50s trying to rationalize away while you eat a ton of fast food
If I was
Send Viber Isis my first moved
Try and like not try and do it but just say
We've been trying to poison Impreza
We keep doing
Cuz
Yeah come out
2 president
Guess what
Little do you know we have people in all of your favorite restaurants restaurant
You know that this episode is a lot of
Just Steve
King stuff
Yeah it really is
Is it as it goes along
Morrin
Assertive Defender
Tyrants
Love and authoritarianism
Just a little bit
Paul Joseph Watson
We're working at this clip and I don't understand how this isn't Alex G
Just doing brainwash E-Type language
I need this would fit in in 1984
Trump quotes
Trump equals victory victory
I don't like
That's insanely wow
Trump equals victory
Relegated
It's just that
Play sad and pathetic and I wish I could get more worked up about it because the things
You talk about our f****** off
Yeah he defensive white supremacy
Is awful d
Apologizing for someone
And making
Really dumb bad excuses
Someone likes
I'm I'm not
I'm the I'm not super in
Interested in it
Looking at it
Wisconsin
Whatever
Deactivate isn't really that in
Impressive or interesting
It's just like flap dipster seen that coming
For this dick
I know and
So important
The point it out because
Teagan
Becomes normalized
Alex
Out and out white suit
He's not it's just like a
Dismiss
Yeah of course that's
To maintain
He said he's shifted over to the window of interesting
That's not good
The fact that
Goddamn
What
Total 30%
Still wants a white
The struggles of
Novelty
You know like
The Twitter outrageous you where it's like yesterday and then the next day
It's
It's a battle to see things through fresh eyes
See the same thing a new
Yeah whenever you see it
The present
With that
But
Hey it's important
You know I'm glad
Take a look at it
Alex is living up to exactly all of the things that we would expect
Well it would be scarier actually I got to see growth
Cuz then I'll know I don't know what would that would pretend
Just imagine
Like put yourself in
Headspace of like
This is the
First time you've heard Alex
You'd be amazed
I would start this podcast is this if I wasn't already
This would probably be enough to be like
Hello
Where does this come from
Now we know where come from
Yeah it's a sin
Furiated
H.
On Monday
Appreciate everyone
Putting up with a weird schedule this week but
Cheeseburger no
Wednesday this week
But
It got it
You know it
Mental Health
Sure exhausted
Self care
I'm working on
Tom's
Browser on Twitter
Have fun of course
Describe subscribe to download
You then like
When and left
Review every nice
Like it
Tonight
Please do it
So women
The
Fully named Man O to much about him I've never done a deep dive into his history but so far of all the times I've heard him
Probably
Just passed that guy's Alex Jones
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color