Holding
Alex
Novelty beverages
Jordan
Have you ever been in trouble for being late to work
Silver dresser
Have you been late to work.
In big trouble
Open fired for it
Habitually
Through my
What off
I can't think of any luck extreme
Examples
The 25 year-old
Dave
I had a lot of jobs I worked a lot of places and
I worked hard but
I just
Hated hated almost every place I ended up attics
I love that
My life
In terms of like
You know hourly wages
Stuff like that but
I work today
Car wash for a while but he's miserable bit about it
That was just based on the whole idea of like it's nothing like the song
I built a B Justin
I used to work at this terrible car wash at my buddies socks
Got me a job at
It was so bad I just got some
Just got screamed at by the co-worker
It was a terrible
Terrible scene
Oh yeah it was horrible
Horrible
And then you get
I was on the end of it
Three main station
Be like people at the
The beginning of a new start the washer and it goes where
Get sprayed down in a
And then it comes out
And because that
Isabella customer-facing position
You know you hand the car back to the customer and give you a tip
Humiliating
Well
It's customary to tip at that point
At one time
That deserves an app
Ice
Like how do you
I dare you
The worst f******
Arable time
Yeah what was that guy's
Might be too long of a story to tell in our intro for the episode there was a suspected
Everyone who works there knew that this dude was straight-up
Everyone knew you was a queef
Customer complained about it
To the manager
Do operation
Pacific change
In a dummy car through the carwash
The quarters and stuff like that all set up
Music
When is the strangest missing
Will look in his pocket
And if those specific
Will know that he stole the change
So he goes through with it low and behold changes gone on the other side
That change
Matters like this doesn't prove anything
I was like
Could be a coincidence
I was like 17 18
Teenage years old and I think I was like
I got to do better than you
Anyway bad time
There we go
A lot about Alex Trebek
Development
To go over here on the show
Starting
To go hard at George Soros cuz he just princess
What's the news
Demeans Soros
Ownership
So many
Nefarious plots
She brings him up
B+ time
It was
Wild
So now today
Who covered April 8th
Today we're going over April 9th
And we'll see what happens with that
See how that
Thread continue
But before we get to that
Got to give a shout out to new donors
Listeners out there supporting
Appreciate it oh so very much
First of all I'd like to
Kevin cage
I'm a policy wonk
Next Taylor thank you so much
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Next Richard
Thank you so much
You are now
A little bit of an elevated level
Sir Foundation
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites Italy
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean black
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much
MacArthur genius Grant
Little bit
You know other people
David Foster Wallace got a little more than
If you out there just like what the show is what we do
We have a little button
Appreciate it
Please
Yes hot off the heels of Alex Jones George Soros
We come in and on April 9th
Alex Jones starts the show talking about goddamn chemtrails
For about the first 40 minutes
Of the show alright I am not
You know what it is
Remember how I meant
On April 8th to overdrive. Really
You bet I think so but okay
Doing so on this
April 9th episode he's letting his sores narrative completely slip
Favor against
To do
Or self-defense against a valid criticism
I'm from one of his listeners
Chemtrails
It does not do it for me
And I'm not interested
For the first 40 minutes of the episode but
The first clip we will hear Alex make
Some
Incredibly untrue predictions about
This time I have the DVDs come in for Obama Deception was released
Before
April May
His little secret
3 days before the official release workout
You will get it on the release that's what we're doing
So we are just
Intensifying what we're doing
Interesting little add products and services that he's offering
Interesting
It's very familiar
On the 4th of July and you will have it on the release date
Does not come out on the 4th of July comes out a bit later
But he's also saying the day he's done with the Obama film
He's going to start a new documentary about chemtrails
And I'll say this
That never got made
Next Obama film is the last documentary
No cuz there was at 1 with Joel skousen
Interview about relocation
Although Jason bermas one of Alex
Does end up making
Call Jack what the hell are they spraying
So maybe Alex is a good enough
What's up
I felt like he was just asking
Where somebody's like to go to a car wash
Is it straight up that the Khan where they're like
Okay
You give me five
I'll give you these $4 to drink
Fusee with release date
He's like it's going to be out but also for some places
Another day
I think he's sincere in his intentions
But none of that happened
This is what's going to happen and we know now none of that
Kind of a little bit of an add pivot to
But it happened almost immediately after
He does what I would describe as
Like a modern-day kind of
We need your financial
Then now
That that the intent expression of like
Pause
Pivot
To the ad that is
Present day
Level Alex Jones at pivot and we have not seen much of that in the in this era
It's just learning how to use
Flex like
Eventually that that is going to turn it down
Have you found our products instead of him being like
Now I should
It's interesting to see
We're just seeing the evolution of
Receding be like
The salesmanship
Get better
He directs himself more towards
Being a sales operation
As opposed to
Pretending to be
Right right right I think that's kind of interesting will see where that goes
In terms of actual narrative
I'm telling you man
It is
90% chemtrails
I got nowhere
90%
He has an interview with this guy named captain Sweeney
Captain
In early April 2009
Captain Phillips got taken by the Somali pirates
This Captain knows the guy who took over the vessel
Captain Phillips got taken by the Pirates he knows that guys
Kevin Bacon
Straightforward
No-nonsense kind of interview so we don't need to listen to it
This is okay
It's kind of a conversation about like the dangers of sea piracy
Is Kevin Sweeney his kind of trying to make himself part of the story a little bit
Coronavirus knows the guy who's there
What it is
Presenting
The information
And I don't
In this
In this instance
I don't think there was
Coming up with crazy narratives about it or anything like that
It's like wow this is an interesting story story almost no take on it
Can skip that question
Really f****** not about that
Sue
Is he eats like a private
Fisher
He's like a privates
If you just have a boat you can call yourself cap
Is that
But he's not in the associated with the military
Was he born
I don't know I don't know he's not very clear on that
I just want to know what did I do
And have people
You can but I also don't think
You can vent
Contracted to
To do like run
And stuff like that
Actually like a license
Commercial
Sea captain
There is a line okay
He's above
Batman
So after she talks to Sweeney
He gets Tyler Palmer
In-studio ecoloblue sponsor
Techmeme school bus school bus
And in the middle of them talking about their water filter
America was talking
About it
If this tickles me to no end because
You could be so excited
Find out who this is
No
Degenerated light on
They are
There's so much cussing
They put out
You know what
I wish you was being raped their biggest fear is is that no one gives it
Coming from that
Pittsburgh Post-Gazette
Not really
Never did I imagine in my wildest dreams that marinwood come up episode
What are you I remember this
Blaming Soros Soros mansion
On the show but they're both in the context
Running
Is not accurate
I would be
Highly surprised
If Mara never got any
George Soros money
So
I would say that Alex is a little bit uptight here
He's being a little bit
Snowflake
You're the ones who don't want us to have guns
I think it's a far stretch for Alex to be saying that Marin is
Calling for him to be raped
Whenever what is really saying is essentially like
This guy is really over exaggerating
Maybe off-color joke
2009 get away with
WTF Marc Maron
In the depths of depression
WTF with Marc Maron are you about to start
Dairy Queen
Piquant
Marc Maron
As opposed to
Oh he's accusing me of exaggerating
My
So
Responding
Got Tyler Palmer just sitting there
Come on
And put my water filters
This f****** junior varsity guy on air America I don't know
What's going on here
Of Marin
Oh he's on home
But actually
Come down on
Marc Maron is
Incredibly insightful
About the people like Alex
Yeah it's first clip
He basically is trying to express
Alex
Muselk
Beer the idea that they are inside
Metallic spruce
You know what
I wish it was being raped there
These people's biggest fear is is that no one gives it
Their biggest fear is insignificant
Their biggest fear is that they really aren't that
Important
Power Mountain
So that's his overcompensation
No no
Do you want
He wants you to recognize that you
You fear the idea of being insignificant
Not that you actually are
But what motivates you
The defensiveness Invicta posturing
Is the ID without it you aren't any
Without the presentation coming to get my guns what are you
Without the
Charade the silhouette of a globalist
You ceased to have any
And Alex Cruz
Now that
Elvis Presley
On Merrick Park
But this makes
Clip
I will say is almost
A psychic level
Prediction
Set Marin ends up
I was kind of Blown Away
Based on what we know from 28
Can you then get mad when we stand up you're not
Their biggest fear is that they really aren't that important
Their biggest fear is that no one's going to recognize him
Your biggest fear is we're figuring out how much power we got
These are all distinct
And dangerous Cry for Help from poorly parenting
Who seek to harm
And hurricane the name of Jamaican Soldier
To make themselves known to pee
They're misguided
And when they are charismatic
Like someone like Glenn Beck
Or somebody like Alex Jones
And they were exploiting the damage
A people who live in this world for desperate angry and misguided
That they become
Dangerous
Populist leaders
They are the criminal
If the FEMA camps are for anybody
It's for what these people will do when they think the end of the world
There's a way to fight this.
Propaganda
FEMA camps are real they will be what these people use
Whenever they think the end of the world is coming
Is essentially they will use these
Tactic
Whenever they feel threatened
And that's what you're seeing
Fears of
It being done to them when it's not being
When their fear of being
True witch
When we now see or whenever they have the
Sort of cover to do it
Alex's
Complete
Slipping on his position about rex-84 his open opening up to the idea
FEMA camps for
Immigrants and asylum-seekers in
Some stuff like that
Marin was a hundred percent right on
If FEMA camps exist
It's for them
If
Crazy when I heard that
Goddamn
So
You're very wise. Your career
So we we about all that I found interesting
In this episode
Cuz the rest of it
Dogshit he sits down with George Humphrey but Alex
Unexplained
At the beginning of the
I'm having George Humphrey, and because we didn't interview on the documentary straight
Shuffle timer
Really terrible
He's talking about a coffee shop and a third of them are Democrats
Third Republic
Dependence
Everybody's talking about
Is it complete horseshit
Where is this is inside like the five corners of this day Rocksmith
Like precursor to like that you know
He would constant
We tweet about being at a coffee
Coffee shop in overhearing liberals they like
Formula
MC George Humphrey
It's just
This washed over b******* about like
I'm out there
Cific anecdotal
Redman whatever
Trends Wiki
I don't know if you noticed
Alex has an interview with Rosalind
Peterson
Who is a chemtrail
I don't care about that
It's real stupid
A couple years after
Rosalyn
She said I literally have no evidence of chemtrails I have no documents
Nothing
Just a thought
Two years prior or whatever
As soon as I found that interview from after this
She said I don't I don't have any
Is it b*******
One of the most
I've ever
So we saw on the 8th
It's almost like he's forgotten that he's supposed to be talkin about Soros
Just bring him up a couple times.
I guess
Which
And also
Somali pirates
ISM play
On the 9th
Pirate stuff is pretty on
It's pretty normal
Oh s*** Are we going to get with soros-funded pirates
No okay but that would be great Musical
Could be
Put the
You could knock me over with a feather after I heard this
Compared to the Gilded domesticated westerners
Battle
Fantasy movie
Waterworld
U.s. Navy
Just people are unbelievable
Army Rangers
Wow
Your Love
Is a crazy pivot I don't understand
Hugo
No
You got to give up. I give it to you
Holyshit
I heard a lot of Alex's like
Weird
Is it all those guys
Nut to me
And then I thought like
Okay
That's probably just weird phrases
It's probably just a Sebring pot
White supremacist
This is what in relation to the Pittsburgh shooter
This is it
This is him just being self-defensive about the
Relation
So real quick
You can even here in there that he is defending the Pittsburgh
Because he's coming for the guns
Not that he was acting out of paranoia
Through his constant
Exposure
These narratives
So he knows that they're coming for the guns it's something we already covered when we talked about
Alex's dealing with Tesla
It wasn't rational decision to kill
He knows we're coming for the gun
You got a killer
So that's f***** up a defense of his
No no I didn't make that guy killed that guy
1/10 killed
Instead of 9:10
Right right
Ancestry
Involves
Yeah it's bad
At 90%
The face down
AK-47
So he's a good guy
What
I really don't know
Wearing a flower outfit
They really don't want that so they never satisfied.
Okay so we drifted too deeply Mr a kind of territory there
The way we are exposed to
Do you like this
Yes
These women are supposed to be that way at least
Rational
Desperately need no fight
Then he goes on to say positive things about the arrow
A net positive statement
Just because you're giving lip service to not liking piracy doesn't mean that you're not in good things about
I don't like the target
I love the way they do it
They got a verb
Because you saying these positive things
About
Somali pirates
After
Comparing them to
Do the Pittsburgh shooting
It is kind of a language works
With his classic denigrating
Pittsburgh
Computers mail. He's all alone he's fat he lives in his mom's basement
Desperate
The cops are coming for his gun
Just like these awesome badass hardcore
Somali pirates
And that's what is just like
But I love the whites
Supremacist shooter didn't I
Oops
Alex isn't taking into account like possible other variables
They make a f*** ton of money
Most of the ransoms are paid
You know they take over bumper boats and because
Insurance
Stopping all that
And the difficulties of trying to get
Get the boats back by 5
Absolute must Molly Pirates
Or epitome
2 problems
A function of a economically depressed Somalia
Where there is a Outlaw business where people are very very successful
I think that it might have more to do them with that as opposed to being attractive
Pirates for their gun
So you're saying that
These women who who are with me
Cartels they aren't attract
To the brutal
Vicious nature of the
But instead
The large sums of money that these guys
And the way we are supposed to
Too much into sort of misogynistic ideas if we say
Whether you're attracted to the brutality
To the money but I don't think
Necessarily in any way offensive to say
It's a
Incredibly impoverished country
These are people who have
Some sort of inability to pay
Provide secure
Situation
Anomic
And it does make sense
The people Woods
Steve m
More attractive partner
Then someone who
Is a broke fisherman
Socioeconomic
Parallel
I don't really know or
Yeah
This is
Real men's rights
Realreal.com
Coming out
Defending the Pittsburgh
Shooter praising the Somali
Pirates drifting in
Massage
Just
I don't know what's happening man doing everything possible to
To say out loud what he
He really feels
I love that Pittsburgh shooter
Absolutely
Fighting viciously to keep
Keep the real part of him inside and it
It's not going
Just like them Somali pirates
Great
Shooters but they are a lot
I do love you can drive drunk
Pittsburgh shooter was motivated by these ideas
For your guns and what do you know Alex
Reinforces exactly that idea
Tellez tamales
Cruisin for a Bruisin
VIP for buying guns
Isn't evidence that the government's propaganda
Is not working
It's evidence that Alex is is
The idea that the government is trying to put out anti-gun propaganda
It not working
Is evidenced by gun sales doesn't
But the idea that take your gun
You should get more
The propaganda is working
Just looking at this backwards
Sideways and wrong
Child support
The reason he's doing it is
Force them same narratives
Is it leather
Shooter down the path that ended up
Murdering
Officer so that's real cool
I like that
I say facetious
So I told you I can't talk much about chemtrails
Yeah but Alex does bring up one single
We talked about
The past
Be fun to make sure that everyone understand
Understand
Inability
I have been consistent
Through the last.
Warrior terms the testing
Or is other people call them
Terraforming
Technology
Actually it doesn't say anything about
He's talking about
Prohibited
Activities but
Petty
Can we talk about this
Before but just because it bears
Consistent
His stupidity is
Yes there are these exceptions
In paragraph
But the exceptions
Begin subject to subsection C
CBN
The prohibition in subsection
Hey does not apply to a
I carried out for the following
Subsection C says
The Secretary of Defense
Only if informed
Consent to the testing was obtained
Each human subject
So the exception
Or actually
Enclosed Within
Kunsak thing
The consent is imposed upon the exception
So Alex
Just doesn't know how to read
This is infuriating
He's a very
Yes
So
I just bring it up every now and again
Yeah
I forgot
A little bit let's just make sure that
Just cuz you can
Say a lot of words in a row
Does not mean that those words
Correlate to the paragraph
To which you are
Meaning of anything close to what you're
Describe
I'm so happy we got through that
And now guess what
Pirates are back
What
Good
Yes you can you can help it. I'm watch the film
Cowards
Not like
I don't understand
Neither do I
Because I scrambled on this I was like okay is this an indication of something that means more than we realize
Is there some world power that was aligned with the Somali pirates
That maybe Alex is being
Gowanda Subway
They're only on board with them
Russia was even bombing them
Somali pirate vampire
It was it was almost one of the most
Probably the most universally opposed
Videos
I don't f****** know what he's doing
I think
He's just making sure
Devilish
So I can put him on a ship
I don't think we fundamentally misunderstood about the Somali pirates
We're doing
New York Times
The guardian among other Publications
Tyrus
Their only motivation was money
They're committing these crimes just
Extort The Ransom money from the ships there was no grander political statement
There any government and work fighting for freedom
It was just a criminal racket
That's all it was
This is super interesting
Because what else is done in his head
He's transformed this Mafia activity into something
Grandeur
Summit Fitness
Community
Give me work so cowardly
But that's all it is
Just his fantasies
No
It should be noted that there were side benefits
To the Pirates
The primary reason
The crime
Because they scared off a ton of fishing boat traffic local fishermen were able to boost
What are the real help the local economy
Additionally the ransom money the Pirates received was in
Refused into local
Community which in turn began to help them flourish
None of this excuses
And none of it was a reason
Cuz there's inflows
Somewhere
These people are in these
It's interesting it's not
Exculpatory or excusing them
Anyway whatever you have a
Economically
Exploited by others
And then
Part of that economically depressed regions like holyshit
Right right
AIDS
Go to the
You have to give it up today
It's just more complicated
Although his version
Weird sure
About Pirates
He seems to think that they're the same
Who fought the US in Mogadishu in 90
But that's absurd
Mogadishu's on the south coast of Somalia
Which is between the northern coast of Somalia
NFL statistics
Years later at the
I sure there overlap like a couple of the Pirates were veterans
But it's crazy to think that it's mostly the same
Seems to be conflating
Is mine
Because
Mogadishu was an embarrassment
You when there's a possibility
These are the same
Somalians who
Maybe that's the only Theory I can come up with
But that's not good enough.
On the Blackhawk
Grew up in this is what
16 years later
So now he's grizzled he's going to be played by
He's
This is exactly the same Catherine
Tom Hanks
So he's he's like
And start our own piracy business
Try to build it up go to the North Coast successful for a wire
Enough attention
People finally Crackdown on as and straight-up murder
Yeah that's because I said that most of it was
Surrounded
That doesn't mean that all of it
Like most hot
Is a geographic
Kind of weird to assume
I do I just picked it out
I don't know what he's
The association with embarrassment
Alex
Like Outlaw assholes who killed
I don't think you're wrong
Sweeney on again
And here's how he introduces him
Thank you Alex great being with you
What
I don't know the craziest thing I think I've ever seen
Not just that they were not just
Give it up to him now we're at
Howard wrestler people
Because I think that he thinks that they're locked
And some sort of a
Like
Nationalist struggle against
The globalist
When it's just
Totally
Chemtrails
This next clip I think brings it into a little bit more Focus
Interesting
Because
Alex
More crime in this
Next
Very strange
I think another reason that he
Is respecting them
Is he thinks that there
Real terrorist
All of these fake terrorists out there and stuff like that
So I think that he thinks that there are noble enemy for him to fight again
And therefore you got to give it to him but I'm still going to fight you
A great warrior can only be killed by a degrader warrior
Really really
F***** up that is not is not reflective of reality
At all
And you destroy
The first
I would like
The restriction on Merchant vessels having a weapon
You taking off and have it be a requirement
They have
Either armed guards on
Board for train
Cruise that with weapons onboard to high-risk areas
I would also like some kind of mechanism for trying
Is this is also bogus
Because they had no they didn't know what to do with
Right now yes and I'll tell you why
How do you
Vietnam
And I was in the Army just after that but
We have a heck of a time deciding who was
The good guys
Say we have
Floating base
But even then
Delete a few weeks ago the Indian Navy
Via tide fishing vest
And they killed off work
It's like
I think personally that we need to have a defense
Especially the part about no you don't
Killing
People who are pirates which is evidenced by what happened
Response to that
She knows about
Brings up that Indian Navy taking out the Tie Fighter
Alex
Before he even says before Sweeney even said that Alex knows what story he's going to bring up which means that Alex is aware
If you do just indiscriminate League Obama going to end up killing
Who were the wrong people he doesn't give a
It will your bum and I'm out
It's like that
You can see how deflated with
Bring that up
Come on
It's so weird
Millwall I'm saying is you can't figure out his position
Take a main economic
Not just illegal act
Regular activity and just blow it
And destroy the area
Get rid of all of their whatever fishing
Community does exist there whatever economy
Does the air
Pirates
To eat so you should
Destroy all food sources around the area as well.
Douglas
Horrible
I can't imagine he hasn't thought that through
I don't know
Narrative
Complicated
Because on the 9th
It wasn't weird
Lens interview with Sweeney it wasn't weird he wasn't saying positive things
Amazing
It does kind of sound like also what he did
Started talking about Somali pirates
Little excited
And then spent the rest of the night Clips in every possible
Immediately like
YouTube clips in between that chemtrails
And I'm telling you
You got to give it up
It is very possible that's exactly what happened
I mean this plays out over like
The next
Waze like app
Phillips was held
Evolve
I thought I used to
I honestly wonder if he'll be mad that
Took out
I wonder if that will be his approach
They should have pulled out swords
I can't wait to find out cowardly to shoot a man from Vista
Could you look up in the eyes Dan never gives you what you expect
On some level you expecting Soros
F****** doesn't Eddy Deb's like tomorrow
Don't know what to do anymore
Fat fat
That's the kind of Alex
Out-of-left-field support
Yeah
It's it's like his
Ability to support and love white supremacist is restricted
Because when they kill people
Transfers
Because their Romance
Exercise murder
Give me some of that
Somali pirates
Alex
Complains more bikes
You just got to give it up to the that's okay
Now Alex is going to
Complain more about
Pittsburgh
He's going to blame the Southern Poverty Law Center in the
ATL
For feeding his name
But this clip is
46 seconds
Long
In the beginning of the clip he's going to blame them
For doing that
And by the end of the clip he's going he has no idea if they did that
This is quintessential Alex Jones you need a sound bite of how Alex Jones
This is it
It always is
I don't know
Amor amor
That needs to be investigated
He made a direct accusation that the Southern Poverty Law Center
Said his name to the media to associate with it
That's crazy you can't do the
They did that
You can't do that
You can't do that I don't know if
Every single time you say I know this
Because you do I don't know
So
The perfect like
Distillation of Alex
I know it but
It's true we should look into it
The standard everybody was
Oh man
Crazy stuff
The MacArthur Foundation
Probably
Now Alex has another guy
No
The situation
I should also tell you
But it was
Meandering nonsense
I don't know
Because of the
Interview with
Developing
Weird crazy add pivot
Stream sell all of Alex's stuff that does include the gold
There is a little bit of
You were
Alex uses Bob as a setup to bring in
Pirates on the brain
Somali pirates in their economic
Alex
Another guest
This is a really
Syngas to heaven
Because
He's not an
Okay
Mr. black right now mr. black
Complete the interviews even gracious enough to do with us
Are there in your offices
Talkin about any
His offices
You better
Begin because I was accidentally found himself a credible guess
Oh no William black
Black is a professor of economics and law at the University of Missouri
Kansas City into the deep resume in the world of science
He played a major role in mitigating the damage
It was done during the S&L crisis
Which SE
Re-regulate
I thought that was when they hired Janeane
Oh I got it
Dick ebersol
I have to assume
Has no idea who Alex Jones is
I can come to no other conclusion as to why he
He agreed to come on
Because as we will find out
Shortly
He doesn't agree with Alex
At all
So here's the first clip
We're discussing about how the banks are a bunch of
Fusions erotic
Control Federal Reserve
No but doesn't come up really
Because
Is not an anti-federalist
Kia
A guy
It is very
These Lending
Incorrupt memes
They have both
The same sort of
Idea about what
Problem is
His talking points blacks
Just with
Scholarly aplomb and what-have-you
The idea of what is going on
Is socialism
President
I guess
Arrangement
Comparing either of these
I don't think that
Misuse of the phrase
Really diminishing whatnot
The economic system is
I think the best way to describe it is
Boney Kapoor
Terrible system anybody was ever
In a nation like that
He already in the earlier the interview Alex tried to characterize
Hyperinflation
That he's afraid of
Republic
Hyperinflation in Black disagree
What does misrepresent
Yeah that there but
Two important things there
Start that music
We got the sound bite he needed and then we're going to move along we got it that's great
Second thing
Alex and necklace
Very clearly demonstrates
He is aware that the National Socialist
Just called themselves social
So
Every time he tries to
Represent the idea that Hitler
Go fuc yourself
There's a level of like you
You know it Improv
Or like if your
We are playing a character in a scene
You have to adjust your level of intelligence like aware of X Y or Z
Like if you're playing some sort of like Backwoods character
You should know about Noam Chomsky
Even if you do as the actor
Alex's
F****** up his intelligence
He's f****** up what he should be aware of
According to how he presented his worldview
He shouldn't have your awareness
But Nazis just called them till social
Yeah that's true
I think it's probably partially because
Excited
That William blackett saying a lot of things
His
Description
The market is going to use them
Rice crackers
So how do you feel about the Federal Reserve being
Voted on by three congressmen
I got to go
They agree about the description of the problem with the bank from Lending
Crisis
But I think almost everyone
About that stay for the politicians
Filtercopy
So they Grill the
But if you take a look at Black
His public statements
You'll see that he's not at all on the same page to Alex
One small caveat though they are in agreement
Prices on trial
And if necessary
Alex probably lesson
Call for Samara Lee locking up bankers
But the two guys definitely are on the side of
These people need to face consequence
Who's not
Tobias
Agrees on that to themselves agree that they caused the problem
Right or they wouldn't be reticent to admit it or not
Here's one piece of information that
Everything you need to know
In the 2016 election official economic adviser for the Bernie Sanders campaign
The same Bernie Sanders economic positions of the u.s.
Collapse becoming a totalitarian hellhole William black is Bernie Sanders economic advisor
Crazy
Really blacks pretty far-left dude
Especially from an economic
Is testimony before the Senate Judiciary Committee regarding the financial crisis
Could not be more clear in its point
The failure brought on by deregulation
And not enforcing the regulations exist
Glass-steagall
Deal but what was worse was how the Clinton administration
Quote implemented the
Which was hostile to regulation enforcement
We were instructed pursuant to that initiative
And think of the industry as our client
That's a mindset that destroys effective supervision
He goes on to spell it out saying quote
The 3D
Deregulation D supervision and de facto decriminalization
I returned with a Vengeance in 1990
Expanded over the
The most difficult aspect of the current prices to
It contains was it roughly 80% of non-prime loans were made by aunt
He's not subject
Direct Federal Regulations
Primarily mortgage
All The Regulators needed to do
Preventic rice
Was-band lending practices that were rational only for control frauds
Engaged in lewd
Consistently refused
To do so because of their anti regulatory ideology
Do you have
Effective Financial regulatory cops on the beat
Are essential to our ability
Please prosecute Elite white-collar crime
Economics is very
The game
Argument is very simple
Engage in what he calls
Control fraud
Pioneer
Which is the idea
They take their
Fusion
And control it as an insult
Frog
The cheap way that this fraud was done
Was in the form of
Call Milan
What the industry calls Liars
Where the lender knows that the recipient doesn't have the ability to repay the loan
And assist them in lying about their ink
According to Black's testimony was nearly 90
That's a lot
Yeah
It's complicated
Institution that's engaged and stated income loans
Clearly doing so.
Tomato frog
It should be on everyone's radar
Because of deregulation and deprioritization
The Regulators were hamstrung in
Which led to what amounted to a
Decriminalization
Control fraud
In the large Finance
Institutions
In that environment there's no incentive
Play by the rules
And doing so is actually a great disadvantage
Which increases likelihood
Behavior
Come on dammit
The problems that William blacks on the financial world where all things
Taken care of with regulation and Regulatory follow-up
Which Alex
Would not be insane
He also advocated for tying
Professional compensation
Quotes demonstrated long-term performance
But you're something else
Unless the John Birch Society
Instead of paying Mortgage Bankers
S*** ton for doing something
Immediately
And then dump
Later
Long-term performance
It really boils down to In terms
What is positions
There were these for the regulatory where The Regulators were
Treating their the people they were supposed to be watching over as their client
As opposed to be collected
Because during the
Look at these
At these
Situation
Outside of Toronto
Politics
To blame
Extra wires
It's foolish
Because you just need to deal with the problem as the problem
The problem is.
Fusions
Taking
There
Durability
Turn themselves
The big deal and the way that they do that
Chief way
Was through these Liars
Research into this
These stated income loans that he's talked about which 9%
They were fraudulent at the direction of the lender not the lendy
It wasn't
Massively
More
Traveling
For the person giving out the loan
Course
Lie about your income in your ability to pay back the right
Because they were lying about
If the security of these loans
Create
A blossoming
I want your
Grossen
Wow you approved for this loan
If you give this is
Is your gross income
You give just a little bit more is your gross
They're going to approve you for this life
To get this I need
I don't know exactly the words
Probably felt
Test
Judiciary
Find distillate
A lot of what
Lot of it
Thumbs down
Regulatory failure
And a need for stronger regulations
And enforcement of those rigged
So
I don't think Alex
I don't know if Alex knows what William black is about
Outside of having seen
Do an interview with Bill Moyers
Talkabouttd
Now it's probably just a
Surface-level things
About
We must believe all day
Globalist stuff and all that other
Doesn't know who he is
I'm excited
That interview for the
Cuz maybe he will have figured it out by the I don't know
Yeah obviously
Based on the way the Alex
From what I've heard and can gather from there they're like
The Voice
Alex probably does know more about
Then
Just
Like a surface-level
Belief in his globalist
Just because he's
He's clearly trying to get
He's sound
He is not trying I think I do
In an actual
Discussion I think Alex knows his resume
Is a credible dude
She knows I don't read
I don't think he's
Like what
Specifically involved in during the S&L crisis
The guy I really I really don't think he does cuz
He does
I guess it wouldn't serve as interested all to debate him
Because William black so much smarter than
Maybe he's just trying to exploit
No matter what but it's hard to tell if it's
It's born out of ignorance
Or Malik
I'm not sure but
It's fine interview as far as it goes it never gets hostile or anything like that
A number of points where black has to
Clarify
Stuff like that cuz Alex assertive
He is constantly trying to lead him down the path that
If you need something
He just comes back to regulation
And stuff like that
Fairly regularly without
Without making them super over
Which I am not sure why
Could be because he doesn't know about Alex and doesn't want to bring up regulation
I'm not sure
He brings up what happen
Depression
Isn't important
I think our Mantra should be
Not a penny
Until we have
Cora investigation started
Cora
What's the guy
Billions prosecutor
Broadcast
The Great Depression
Find Alpha
Anthem
Wall Street
Fat cat
Every step of the way
Eastbound the widespread fraud
Lead
Yakitori
50 years
Work so successfully
In America what happened to Charles Broad Street
Finally
Got enough
Vertical juice
Get rid
Aftermarket
Right near the end
So you bring up the Cora investigation
Interesting. Right after
Dunking on them
Embarrassing them to the point where they had to resign and stuff like that
Verity
What was the name of the bootlegging movie with Sean Connery and Kevin Costner
Do you remember that one
Dammit I just cuz that was about
Breaking up
Bootleggers
Socorro
And it just
Didn't have enough action I don't have any Gunplay
Wrote like like that was the other guy
That Will Ferrell
The pecora investigation
A buddy cop
Perhaps it's
Find
Sing is it interesting
The system worked well enough
Aftermath of the Great
That be conclusion of there the report of the investigation
Dexter go back
It talks about how like
Lace out all the causes
Feelings games
We're being played
By Banks and lenders and
Stuff like that
And then
Seems like
We don't really have recommendation
Because they have already
Taken care of over the course of this investigation
Because by the time the investigation ended glass-steagall it already
We passed along with the other banking
Reform bills
Did system
Even work better
Because during the investigation people like
Over starting to learn stuff we better fix it
It's just another symptom of how broken fix our problems
The problems they were like
Instead of being like what what if we just rode out the investor
I just saw where
I wonder if we could Coronavirus
So we can bring another
Years
Is much money out of this is
Responsible
The important things
Number is that
When the chorus
Ahead and win the S&L crisis
All of it was about regulation
Regulation
Markets that
Falling into
Negative patterns
So
For Alex
Sort of
Like bread and butter and everything that
Kind of comes down to regulated market doesn't seem like that's something that
Alex should be
Into but
Expert
Enough Alex
Him to sign off on this idea that
The collapse
Plant
That's okay
He tried to lead him down that road
And we'll see how black
Response
You're saying
He was against it
No I'm not saying that I'm not I don't know the Congress
I'm telling you
In the trade
Everybody knew that if you made something called a liar
It was because they were fraud
Overwhelmingly
And I think it's going to produce
Horses paid not to know
Right
Sneakers don't go in front of Congress
Play Count Congress
Financial derivative
And everybody
Wall Street
This is the greatest thing
Since sliced bread
Right
Everything's going to be wonderful
Adidas
Because we have it
Can't compete with a German
Universal Banks
So we have to get rid of every protected we never put places
In place the United States
Mukbang
Complete
It's like a little bit
Narrative
Is Maury real
That's a tough thing to yell
That's a problem for that is a tough
He doesn't get to demonize the politicians
Stuff like that
When it's easy to demonize them as just be
Willfully composite
Because
They look the other way
You know baby
Some people had misgivings about looking the other way
Had a suspicion that something bad could happen of course no one was
Having
Having him on there it's really interesting
It's that late I was definitely
An attempt on Alex's
Hard to get that sound bite
But because black nose thing
Understand
He's like well
On the part of people committing the fraudulent
There's more new wants to it now it's not it
So it doesn't get hostile
Interview
Amanda to go there
Separate Ways
And then Alex gets back to
Complaining about the
Very
Itachi
Subject
Even if he wasn't attached to it before
What kind of people were just saying
Lego he's attached to it he could have just not said anything
But now that he's
You like
I'm going to talk about it all the time
Between
He's only doing that
Is the media
He needs to fight back
Against
Explain
They say you want to murder cops
Cops murder
Collapse
Mha
You know what your cocktail
I mean
This is psychological warfare
They need it to be wild
Why do they come out in November
So I don't know who that Al-Qaeda members been killed
X
Pacific
Let's talk about chemical Ops
Ali Hassan almost
Who is the cousin of Saddam Hussein
And also God who authorized
Use of chemical weapons on
Records
Attempted genocide
On June 24th
2017 guilty of crimes against
Is execution was postponed
And then president
Was hesitant to find the Executioner
Over political
This was allegedly all cleared up
On February 2000
Chemical Ali
This time for quick play no role in The Killing of between
Shi'ite Muslim
During the Revolt in southern Iraq that followed the night
91 /
Persian Gulf War
He was also sentenced
The death of third time on March 2nd 2009
This time for the assassination of grand Ayatollah Muhammad Ali
He's also been
What's the Death Punch
It's not like
He's been
He's been sentenced
You don't need to retract it because he wants it
Almost blue.
Confused because he's an idiot me can't read
Instead of getting to the bottom of where is confusion stems from
Proof of immediacy
Pathetically childish behavior
Chemical Ali was executed on
January something
Exact date
But that's the time that he died
All the other times are Alex
Just misunderstanding
Different trials
That he had over the course of
2 years
It's real stupid
It's real f****** stupid sentenced to death like you walk out of the courtroom and then you
I don't know
In the interest of total fairness I should point out there was a Reaper
The chemical Ali was killed in Basra on April
6 2003
They wasn't that reported it
So that's the only thing I can
You think over that's still only one that four times about the four times he was sent
Absolutely
So this is Dad man
B dad
That b*******
Alex has a breakdown about how
Shut up conspiracy theorist
Is a weird metaphor
The floor
I don't know who's who in this medicine
Now it's a mine
What's going on or what
Dammit you still my screenplay
Where they at
Reminder
Prophecy
And you have no idea how bad this is going to get
That was a protracted metaphor
We're good guys trying to help everybody metaphorically stupid stupid
I can't believe that he imagines that he is
Goodbye
I can see that delusion but the idea
In his house
Flash my metaphors like
Please stop doing this politely
Is very bizarre
Can't you tell if this is a self-fulfilling prophecy about the Pittsburgh
The Pittsburgh shooting happening is a self-fulfilling prophecy because
Of what all of these gun-grabbers are doing
So again he's trying to justify the actions
I'm complaining about people who sang
He's advocating
For this
Please himself
As the true victim of that crime
Alex
This is your fault for putting out that much
People who sings like this guy
Sensationalizing that miac report
Making guys reinforcing now paranoid world
Against you because the mic reports
Conclusions are correct
Existed
If you hadn't put that
So who's really at fault here
About the very things that he was complaining about previously
Mystery
Yeah she's a how many narratives if we go through
15 state
To keep our bearings about it
We've got to get to something
Concrete
So we got to we got to get on
Actually exist
Like Desmond.
Need to find
Find my constant
Alex bringing up
An actual thing that I can look into
Turns out to be
Document
Council on Foreign Relations
No one's ever wanted to rule the world there aren't Global Elite
Relations in literally hundreds of documents
Justin last few years
May 1st 2008
David Rockefeller
Well then
That's a reference to one of his sponsors
Home game
Home game gorilla
He was just doing a plug for them
Plush gorilla toy
Easy to do a little product plug
Subtle
Is a
Address
The estimated value
It's a scam
Yeah
But this document
Institutions of global government
Governance program
Title
For someone like out
You actually read the document
First thing to jump
The first paragraph literally say the program is funded by a grant from the
Foundation
Organization I have literally never heard
Also it specifies who's running this program
Who's in charge of Usher
It's not David Rock
This report at all
His name does come up but only is like
Foundation with
Doesn't doesn't
So personally involved in
As is always the case
Does about
You're out of a title that includes words like Global governance
In reality what that refers to
Do here is not so much the creation of a world government but the idea of managing approach
The issues that aren't isolate
Country RV
As the document
Explain
Quotes
The program will take an issue a area approach
Focusing on Arrangements
Governing State conduct International
A meeting for broad sets of challenge
Caltrain transnational threats
That's including terrorism for proliferation of weapons
Construction inspector
Diseases
Protecting the environment in promoting energy secure
Three managing global economy
And for preventing
Responding to fire
They going to explain the variety of approaches that they are
In each of these figures the program book
Consider whether the most promising framework for governance
Is a formal organization
Universal membership
EG the United
A regional Regional organization
Or a narrower informal Coalition of like-minded
Or some combination of all three
A narrower informal Coalition of like-minded
Breezes basically description of a lion
This is saying that it's possible that it's them
The best equipped
Respond to a crisis
But in others
Perhaps just countries on the same page
Will be back
That seems counter to the idea that this document is about establishing a one-world government
If you read the whole thing about global cooperation
Not Global governor
Governance is the word they chose
Which sound similar to government
Man we got a
Figure out how to
Yeah I'm probably a lot of people don't understand
What people with bad wheel
Jerome guys and got them
Just call it though
Happy Funtime hour and it would have been
Fine like
Book
One of their
Yeah probably
I can't believe how
What they're describing is just what the world is interconnected
You thought that you could just be a place by yourself but it turns out
That if there's an earthquake in Tokyo that can affect your s***
So how are we going to deal with all of this the best
Is it going to be through Us in Mexico being like
Let's fix this f****** Canyon earlier all of that show
It's what are the best ways to diagnose problems
That aren't just yours
Is very specific
About this program
These problems
And approaches
With a broad spectrum
There are multiple
Paradigm
I guess
Organization
They're being looked at
Does
The possibility that
Itself is great
This is not at all advocating
Nothing to do with it
I mean like
Hundreds of
I mean
Whatever
I don't care that's the one you specific
That's okay
It's just the same thing he does with new stories
Read the headline in the eye
Coda
She called back to Somali pirate hideout in great
Now that's done for the day
Amazon you was a very reputable source
Measurer
Informed
Who ended up becoming
Yep this is just I can't get over this
For a fact
Alex responded to
Delete down pads
And then
Gain credibility
To his
Attached
To William black
Yeah
Now he's callers
His listeners
Maybe don't
Let's just go to your phone calls right now as promised
Alex
I'm getting kind of frustrated here and I was listening to that William black interview with you
And I went I watched his Moyers
People got to go back and watch the third segment on that
This guy is
He's holding back
You know you you are a true Seeker
So
He's pulling a Glenn Beck
This is what happens when you internalize narratives like Alex
What you do is you exclude people with actual expert
What to use on issues
And because they don't
Fall exactly in line with Alex's ideas but the Federal Reserve and that everybody crash the economy on purpose
They are now Glenn Beck
They're controlled opposition
When in reality they're Towing
Studied
Approach
To why what happened
So what you do is
You Poison the Well in more ways
One like
You ruined your own ability to look at
And then you also
Create
I don't know if you call it an Oppositional defiant
But you create a hostility
Towards people
Who knows things
Who don't agree with
Do you have it you have a built-in excuse
S4y the world.
Conform to your expectations
And that's super Dave
It always has the same endpoint
Is cannibalism
Anytime these kinds
Situations
With this
Oh we get rid of all of the the liberal
We don't have an enemy
We don't have anybody to
None of it means anything because all that they do for them
Is the desire to get rid of
Who created
And from that perspective that
Just like a piano
The right
Just thing to do like in terms
That that delone is enough of an Argy
To be like
Exclusion
It's just it always will end up
Become like it's a piece of paper that's folded over
We got rid of all the
You're never going to
Is a fractal always
That's what his colors
Because of the rain
Sad
Somali pirates
Bananas
It's weird
Strange places
Take your claim playing
Your flag but
Respect
It honestly I think you got to give it up to these tamale pie
Apologist in the world like Alex Jones what the f***
You know what that's where we use that's where we've gotten away from our Roots which is apologizing for somebody
Anyways
I find this more interesting than the Soros
Is a story that needs
Play out further
It's like
There is nothing I need to know more
That to me is a
Juicy Alex Jones f******
By virtue of the show that we do and who we cover
Unlike
Script
2Cellos where it's like
Jennifer like Breaking Bad whenever they have an episode that setting
Entire that the bottle
Episode
Narrative
No cuz it is even like that bottle episode cuz they're still dealing
The Pittsburgh shooting stuff
That's sort of the
And then the flag is
Support stop buck
Anyway we'll see how I have been reborn in 2000
Got to give it to him
List of Ali fights
Whatever here that's very weird
Website knowledge my.com
That's true
I have squatted on a cup
I got
I think your hand. Cam.com
Also
Just remembered if someone sent me a message on by personal Twitter
Forgot to check I saw like a notification
But I didn't check it and I apologize I will get back to you I never use my personal Twitter
I probably going to just
Get rid of it cuz I haven't used in Forever
Think that I'm ignoring them
Yeah
I just feel very
Tell your mother your Somali pirates
You got to give it up to us for name again
We're also on reviews
Describe Jordan I don't know you know this I recently checked in on our reviews
And a bunch of them Knotts Bill Cooper
Everybody go follow through
Vac
I don't know
Doesn't seem like he's ever killed
Good
Marketplace
Help to re-regulate the savings
Pretty good guy he's ever killed anybody
Documentary with a guy who has
Alexandra Thurston color