Alexandra Thurston color
Taunting somebody opening tones
I don't know what it was
Indeed we are.
I got nothing for you right now
Today
I usually come up with a question
Right off the top of my head
I usually like to dig dig out of a ditch with your question
To ask myself
I'm just testing you
Auto partner in this and I will not
I will not Bend to The Winds of a interviewer
Affair I'm no Somali pirate
That's true
Sing show ahead of us excited
To what we're going to get in
Time travel episode
I'm very excited
To the topic at hand
Which will explain
Thank you to couple people
The first one
You're now Apollo
I don't think we did that
Anyway most questions
I don't remember what we were talking about 5 minutes ago
I'm a policy wonk
Also
Very much codeine
I'm a policy wonk
Next
And finally
We would like to thank you so much for taking your donation
We very much appreciate that honor of your generosity
Your support of the show
You're now a technocrat
Start until you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much miles
Go to our website knowledge.com
Now before we got down to business
Too much
The show isn't going to turn into Delilah
Song
Request
Four people out there on your long drive
Where I get a nice message from somebody
Anyway I can
From Grace
If you wanted us to know that there's a policy wonk out there by the name of Bruce
Who's having a birthday and we wanted to take a little bit of a happy birthday out there Bruce
Listening in your support
I hear you got a podcast about UFOs
That's pretty that's pretty fun
Send me a message
I swear to God
Underwater base
No it's not underwater the Dulce base oh yeah that's how it is
New Mexico
Delfina explores
Hey Bruce knows about that UFOs
Selective
Third letter of the alphabet
Oh I see what you're saying
It's been polished
Too much
God bless you
I hope all is well
We are getting into this time travel episode request
I would say
Back to step
10 / 20
5th 2011
It's always a fun game
Try and figure out if
If you have any idea
Might be that someone would send me back to
Okay so this is 925 11
Correct
Y9 1111
The 10-year anniversary never forget two weeks
Years to weeks
Street
Things to say about Occupy Wall Street
The dis
Coming in I had no I've no idea
According to their own website Occupy Wall Street
Quota people-powered movement Spire by popular uprisings in
Egypt and Tunisia
It aims to fight back
The richest 1% of the world that are
Of an unfair global economy that is foreclosing on our feet
Based on that
Alex Jones to be against
Since the uprising is in
Neither were globalist false-flag uprising
So that this is just another one
On the other hand
Well Occupy Wall Street was the Federal Reserve
It definitely had the
Appearance of being a
Community of people who could be red
Build by the info Warriors
And become them
Themselves
So maybe Alex
Since it could serve as a pipeline to him
On the other hand
The beginnings of Occupy Wall Street Grado publication
Adbuster
Which is definitely anti-consumerist
A pretty certainly
Anti-capitalist
So that seems like
This is so infuriating when you know the answer of what
Is going to happen in this episode
Possible for Alex
On the side of the people
Good feels like you would have to
Occupy Wall Street
Against his principles
Weekly ignore it so he doesn't
I have to side with the
Are we doing
They were literally protesting Bank malfeasance and that's one of them
But primary branch
December to same time ignore the part that what the protests that are diametrically opposed to his world
You truly have a gift for Ryan's boyfriend
Does Delta protest good for that proposed to his worldview it's really important stuff
Redistribution
Come forgiveness
That putting restrictions or limitations on Bank
Putting restrictions on excessive
Executive
Substation all these things
Evil goals of the globalist
A+ Michael Moore was in Fault
What I'm getting at
That
Proposed episode
I have literally no idea what I was going to fight
Any slot on the roulette wheel
In choosing a specific date to go back to I decided to choose the temperature
25th 2011
I chose the date because they'll Occupy Wall Street
Began on September 17th
I thought it was
Probably likely that Alex would be slow to hear about it or talk about it
Cuz that seems to be his friend
Somali pirates
September 24th at least 80 protesters were arrested
Police roughing up protesters
Who are peaceful
Corralling them with a large net and a video of Officer Anthony bologna
Female protest
I felt if there was any day that was going to be the day that Alex
Talk about Occupy Wall Street as a positive or the negative
This was going to be the day
That he was trigger
Then so we jumping
On
25th of September
It's not
I don't actually know like
You you're pretending that I know a lot even though I know what the
Clips are going to be in all that
I don't really know that much
We don't know where you actually Lance
It's it's
We'll get to it
It's hard to say exactly conflicted
I'm going to tell you ahead of time like this is probably going to
To be one of these like
Preludes of things to come
IFixit Occupy Wall Street
The entire span is where I'm going after
Yeah
Of my fill
Of Alakazam
For me once I get a handle on the Soros stuff all that stuff in 2009
I believe that looking at the entirety
Positions on it
I think it'll be that would be a
Fitting next investigation we get here
Sweet at all
Just know
I know what
Coming in the clips
But I don't
I don't know big picture what's going on
Subway
So he has a Sunday show
It's only a two-hour
I thought that would be
Be better
Bored
Yeah
On Sunday
Genesis
Add
It seems
Very possible
Sunday episode
Lemoore me
Yeah so
We jumping
Restart with Alex
Bragging
Infowars.com
Thank you so much for joining us
Infowar
Cool you know what the only thing that I get whenever I hear that kind of beginning
When he's like number one on global shirt
And stuff like that
Remember When
The Academy Award
No
Next song
Doe Boy Fresh
Estate
Yes that's the way you
It doesn't sound like
Chamillionaire
How long is Chamillionaire been around
It's just a Being John Malkovich
Rip they just
Okay people going into the little duck
They're just like doing a music video
Keeps flashing
Video
The reason I bring it up is the song starts with
Academy Award winner
But they were hyping up that they won the Academy Award yeah you're really not telling me on this song
Or this album
Or Three 6 Mafia at all the next angle they had after
It starts with
36B
Number one ringtone
Of the Bragg
Put the song
In that era consistently open with them bragging about something you want to hang out
Three 6 Mafia syrup
Yeah
Give me Schoolboy Q
So
I thought that was funny but it's just kind of like
Standard doesn't tell us anything
Think about what's going on
So
Chamillionaire
Turn on chameleon
Yeah
It is yes
Okay
And Billy Gunn
I was I just wasn't sure what do or like was his name
I like
Hammer something like that you know like
It starts hbh
Chameleon end
Chipotle
Anyway that opening doesn't tell us that much
His career
But I don't know what he's been up to
Who knows what's going to happen
There's a lot of like in 2014
He had different waypoints that were used
And I was expecting
Find
Different Waypoint
September 2011
Alex Jones
Really into
Party
Obviously we got an information overload here
Are horses owned by the people
In the arena
Agreement obituaries
Our constitution
Are they
The Republican debate
And the Tea Party is destroying
He is now taking ownership of the
The Tea Party by the
Easter 2019
People first
So it's some point
Between these two points
Time
Keys
Accepted that like
I can
Associate
And of course he's super into Ron Paul
No surprises
This is also in the lead-up to the 2012 elections or Ron Paul's running
You know like
So true
Alexander the end game.
He's been a long time
Unfortunately I should tell you that Alex's
Rick Perry
And sometimes the homophobic
Also got to take out politically
Is just as bad or worse and that's MIT
Twinkle Toes
Tommy
The fact that he's from Michigan from Texas
And
Okay
Cheerleader
Isabel cheerleader
Really
Not the Twinkle Toes
Hey hey come on who is it wasn't
That was station that was given to avatar The Last Airbender
Text matters
Gave him the nickname
Context Matthews in Airbender
Alright I assumed that Alex Jones is describing both Rick Perry and
Mitt Romney's Airbenders
The Firebender wasn't pillow biter
Okay more about the laser
How does it relate to
Dune
Avatar The Last Airbender
In much the same way
Goodbye
Episode
Be about something
I am about the Somali pirates out of nowhere
The same way I'm expecting to hear something about Occupy Wall Street or I'm expecting Alex
Keep talking
About Ron Paul
People are waking up
The game
Listen to the who songs
Zipless music
But finally
That's what I'm talkin point of his stock in 2009
He just goes on a TED talk about
Man
Look and you know what
This is one thing I'm not going to Folsom
All right it is a lot to put out for hours of content
No totally
So I guess
Yeah you're driving to work whatever it was you thought you were going to talk about that day isn't you're not getting it up
Forever whatever reason
It's just like I who song Baba O'Riley this here you go
You fill your time with what you got to do
I guess but
But that's what shock jock
That's what like
He lives in the world of high-stakes
Espionage and governments
He insists on doing like 20 minutes on importance of Won't Get Fooled Again
It's crazy
Like to the point where it is next cook it starts with him reminding people
They are bring up who are you
I should put a clip of this song
I love that
Soccer
On television
Doesn't shoot video
It's a side issue on a side issue
Okay so if I understand correctly
The train of thought is
The I got to remind you who is the who is
Band from rabbi
That's correct water 84 Hap's the most famous rock bands of all time
You are on this planet and you have not heard of who song
In the top
Rock songs of all time
Probably have
No no
Oreilly.com
Wizard
Oh get real aggressive and then you ran out of gas slick
Quadrophenia
Like they're kind of a big deal
Let me remind you my Target demographic
Let's start there
Next.
Now that I've reminded you who is I'm going to bring up
Unrelated Personnel for Robert produces ran into Robert Plant watches
You should have your Adderall this morning
Conversation
Secondary revelation.
Pick up on
But I think it's actually super important
No
This point
His producers
That's truly a Papal
He hates those companies
Kia use using
Products
Another producer
He couldn't have cared about those like an apple narratives back then
New Edition to it
When was Samsung
Bent
I'm sure he's still
Uses Apple products
Monster
Who cares
He prefers Simplicity over
Well how many holistic healers have we had on the show always tell a story where they like
And I had to go to the doctor
What time are you like
Alex
Dramatic reading of lyrics of
Make a claim
What is not true
Constitution take a bow for the new Revolution
No no
By the way I can confirm from Bugs
Whatever
Pete Townsend the guy who wrote all the songs
The album that won't exist
Music has always suffered from being tied to any kind of political or social even spiritual or religious connect
I suppose the who were rebellious and I for a while we were
Tubi
But that wasn't really
I think we're just reflecting what was going on around us
So
Also Won't Get Fooled Again with originally written to be a part of the who's scrapped sci-fi rock opera Lifehouse
They realize they should just let Tommy stand
So they abandoned Lifehouse
Put the song on the album who's next
Also the song wasn't really even about the real world
It Was Written was that rock opera
And when you actually look at the lyrics
The kind of inspire app
Together Poster Revolution
Criticism
My criticism has described the song as one
B creams Defiance at those who feel any causes better than no car
Rallying cry to
Have no position
Like defending your right to remain silent
In the face
Is there a lion
Probable
Prog rock opera
It was setting the dystopian time when rock and roll was gone people repressed
I'm giving Bland entertainment people kept a secret knowledge
Rock secret but alive prog rock
70th cocaine obvious
Wehelp 12
Tons of other concept album
Deltron 3030
Alex could not be more wrong about the who
Art School weirdos revolutionary sentiment
Even as it relates to this very song
The song revolutionary
But that was never the interest
They were
Largely
Just like
And you can see it in
Career like
He's gotten more involved in like the Philharmonic
It's crazy
Electric
I do too I do have you ever heard of
I've not
Maybe
I will say that I like
Concept album
Perfect
Immersive
Experience of like this album.
Me a story
Along with music
It's great but have a really boring conversation
Certainly do
Tire rack
You know he's doing his misguided Ted Talk About The Who
On some level
Well it's only because it's not interest
Is that make sense
It's out of place is weird
It takes up a large chunk of the show
At least 15-20 minutes song
That has been out for good
Thirtysomething
Like 90s hip-hop from St Louis and the surrounding
Let me know about the members of
I know I I know the city Spud was in prison
I get it that's why the first album was called free second album was called City free
I understand I know about aliens
Lead
Zeppelin
Freak out no idea
Holy s*** you don't even know that there's a California hotel
That you cannot
Was worried you get any
Oh I was also worried
It's just nuts.
Why waste your time
You're in the middle of like trying to defend Ron Paul about like why he's running for president
Wall Street happening
That should be either
Summon your super into or super again
Yet you've got to dissect
The goddamn
Although on the other hand perhaps it makes even
More sense
He's is Ron Paul and Occupy Wall Street
What song could be more fitting than apathy from
Lyrics because
Wall Street
We Won't Get Fooled Again
Perhaps putting off having
That makes more sense
Good bit of time about that
Commercial
Commercial that I've never heard before
It's one of these rare in
Lake
Messed up,
Doing the voiceover
Commercials that he's done
For like
The Israeli
Tourism Bureau
Right those are packaged commercials that are sent over and
Please play DMX money off it
This one he's doing the voiceover for
I'm here to tell you today that
Modest Proposal
There is a new food company out there Revolution
What if what if what if
What if he got onboard of soylent real early
Not breathe it's not free
Eltingville
My ear really weird because
First of all I found
3 kg
Haha, specifics to be lacking
Figure out what
For the one I found out
Alex
Did the voiceover for it
A very wealthy USA 2011
The crazy part is
I can't stress this enough
URL for time
Also it's not
The only thing that
The call to action
Should be towards the action you want
As opposed to call to action which makes me want to go
Well what the f***** up with end of America one.com right I can't go
Return of the Jedi
Is the work of a guy named Porter Stansberry
Which Alex is very keen to not say his name in the commercial very wealthy American is
That's Porter Stansberry
The f****** con man
Alex is not just running a commercial for him he did the
The voiceover for it and he plays it four times
During this two-hour episode
He's pushing
Or at least
He's getting a lot of money
Which
Is a fraud in the reign of most of Alex's gas
He spreads fear of append
Collapse advises people to subscribe
And also advise them
His credibility was based on the
The claim that he has
Do you predicted the collapse
The Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac
Problem is that the only evidence of this prediction is him saying that he predicted it after the fact
In a funny turn of the best prediction
Stripped
Was fellow Alex Jones Peter Schiff
Who stuck his newsletters
2006/2007
To the woodshed
Another man's car
Respect Peter Schiff a little more not much but a little
There's a conman high Council that got together and sensor
Peter Schiff
And there's also a possibility that like
He was working against
Peter Schiff scam
So maybe there wasn't
Yeah maybe like a
Cut it off at the pass
Newsletters
Advocating for
Where you buy your gold and silver from
Enjoyed seeing these Alex Jones podcast
Supporters
It does prove that they can research
Did you spend two years
Looking at this guy shift and then
Real world information
Just emphasized whether or not it was
Valuable
Have you thought about doing that before
Did you spend that time in
Instead of research
Sing the truth
So
Like
Operation going
And we would have passed out long ago
But instead
In 2003 the SEC filed a case against Porter Stansberry for sale
Direction to subscribers
An investigation found that he just made up the source
In 2070 was sentenced to pay $1000000 in restitution to the people
Frauded
He tried to pull a First Amendment argue
But the court rejected conduct undoubtedly involved deliberate fraud
False
The sentence was upheld by the force
Circuit Court
And the Supreme Court refused to hear the case because why would you
The episode that we're listening to 2011
Years after Stansbury was charged with intentional fraud
Here Alex is doing the voiceover for the commercials for his new fraud
Alex has no
Fucken moral compass
Didn't know that
You didn't even need the definition of the word on
Unscrupulous
It's not like the idea why you even words to describe unscrupulous
Tell that story 11 and stay like
2005 3006
Before he was charged by the
Prodigy
It's too good
Camfrog
I always like to check in where is monetary resources are coming from
Great to find out the 2011
No more ethical than the other point
Little bit
Beyond wanting to talk about
Who Alex mostly into Ron Paul today
F****** super in
Why are you saying
When's unfortunately
Why do you guys keep insisting he can win
Ron Paul
In a row
That is a Republican
Real Republican
Now this is a misrepresentation
Because I don't know if you remember this during the Republican iridal this one
Mitt Romney
Announced ahead of time that he was skipping straw-poll
He did not
Engage at all
His campaign
We are only focusing on caucuses and primaries
Lee straw polls
It it will be a waste of our resources
Sew-in
The first
What came out
Mitt Romney was
Because you put no effort into
No effort into
Involved in the process of it at all
Incredibly
False hope
That Ron Paul had the goods
Go the Distance
Any f******
These these
Indications of
In terms of his defensive
And if you know anything
Think about what was going on you would know that that
Is a
I don't know what is
Hollow victory
Yes.
Yeah exactly
Cubeatz
I hope you
Orthoscopic straw-poll
The primaries that started happening
Admit Rami just started
Could be
And the toy
Arizona 2012
Sure they were all like
There's a black president so obviously people
I hate black people
Platform
Let's pickle I got a Mitt Romney
It wasn't until Trump really show them that you can let your race
Six Flags fly that they realize that a run pulp
You could be elect
Did now before they probably couldn't afford
Galvanized
A big gun for recessed we would have had a one-term Obama
Newsletters
Stuff like that
You might have seen
Acceleration
And where we ended up for you
Years later exactly
Just sort of a broadside into reality TV show old man
Boring
Order
Yes and also his brother
Free People
He thinks the three
So it's just all wrong
Paul defense
There's a lot of cut out cuz
Straight dogs
Justin Bieber
I don't need to hear that honey
We will hear a little bit more of it later but before we do
We got to check in with
What Alex thinks about The Highwaymen
Does he want to sing along with me 2011
Year are we not going to find out how he feels about the highwomen
Just plays all right along with it
Not bad
Two terms of his Impressions that's not bad currently
Easily his best impression
That's a good impression of this depression apparel
Exactly still better than his impression of
Show me information
Anyway
Like I said
Most of the show is about
Defensiveness about Ron Paul
And if next
Elementary
It makes my head spin sometimes
In every
And Hunter Johnson
Who wins all the spontaneous
Double double
Formula 1 racing
And
And their car is picking up steam running Gray
That's the
For the Jack Daniel's car whatever it is
For the Chevy car
I think I'm more at one of those three can make a car
You're more apt metaphor would be like
Okay so you're doing this race
The guy who has the
Best Buy
Lakeway fast
Her car wasn't
The first two laps
Do you know your car is going fine
Running out of it doesn't have any more boosters on it doesn't
And so what you got here
You're doing fine
You're you're going around the course but the guy who has the much better faster sleeker car
It was better at driving is now in the race
He's gaining on you
But his Rockets
Yeah so there's a legitimate way to look at it
He's in third then
That's a great position for him to be in
At any point
But he's only in Thursday
Because Mitt Romney
Is game
I remember this
No one no one
Conversation
A tiny piece
But no one really believe
It was
Mixture of
After anal sex
That was that
I just
I think his metaphors are
Keesler not dealing with reality
He's
Fetishizing
The idea of a volcano
Court
To be expected
It's interesting to see that there's so much going on in the world like
Legitimately
The day before
80 people who were peaceful protesters
Were arrested
If they Occupy Wall Street
Violently pushed to the ground roughed up
Pepper spray
Algeria people
Rihanna
Really, really close to Kent State
You think that you've seen these young white women being spray
I'm going to start my show
Talkin about
Atomy that I think is a strong indication
Doesn't care that much
She doesn't care.
Mike little I don't nobody cares more about Ron Paul
He's really pissed off
The people are saying
To the point where you can't do is show
Ron Paul
He's here
He's presenting
I've gone back and looked
Some of the
The primaries for
Cuz it's kind of relevant to like trying
Can figure out Alex's
Political
Trajectory related
Especially turning
Later
What are things that I noticed is that like
The only reason
Is there
No one f******.
Even his supporters didn't think
But in 2012
Because Mitt Romney
Participate
In the street
Earlier in the primaries
4 years of the
Tea Party
Galvanizing movement
More engaged at
Necessarily
That was sort of growing
Farther to the right
You're weird
To the right
The GOP
That energy
When
Intersect
Mitt Romney not
Beginning of primary season
This swelling
The appearance of massive grass
Success
2012 was a heartbreaking
Experience
Actually bought it
Because there was
The perception that he could
The beginning of the primary season
There was an idea
Army base on unfortunate
Didn't
Alex's
Presenting the side
That he's being screwed
Based on the
The fact that
All that momentum
That was gained by Mitt Romney not being involved in the campaign
Sort of dissipated as Mitt Romney in the campaign
Alex is trying to also
Help
Oh no
But I think his advice is bad
Don't ever try to call Ron Paul I think I am
4 minutes
Give me the floor
First of all I know rajbhog
Here's a great strategy
Demon title
Again
Works
Be a whiny dick
That works
For Trump because it was at I know I'm being I'm being
Just seen it before
Okay
Only
Rock Quarry
Ever hit a f****** homerun I don't believe that for a second foot
Publix
Available now do you believe that Republican shirts
R naught of the box scores
But think about this for one second
Don't you think a lot of Republican voters would change their vote
Wussies
Don't you think a lot of the people are the most delectable as
Republicans also have a history
Like there's a lot of
I think so I think
People
Jim Jordan can hit a Dinger you think so
Hours
Challenge
Even Romney's got wheels
He was a governor you probably wasn't welcome
Inside the park homerun
Budweiser
Work at the park
I think this is
If they had just shown video of Mitt Romney
Running
He would never won the GOP
Navigation to him try and run they would look at him and he would look like a baby duck
Like Ron Paul
I'm in the house
Has been there for like
Texans nineteen
He's been married
He hit that home run or something like that
No one's ever keep playing tonight
The f*** out of here
Sasha Cohen
Facebook
Unless, nobody else up here I've won most of straw polls I'm coming first second third
Play what the fact Rod Paul's version of the facts
Speech therapy what Ron needs
To do is like
Just be up
Witches entry at Somali pirate
On that level
Also in terms of like what we know from the 2016 election
When he's in support of Paul
He keeps saying R&B aggressive be an a******
I won't do it but who runs well NBA
David Alex just ask Ron Paul 2
To disguise dad
And both
Generations
Can't follow through with it
Eventually one
Real defense
About Ron Paul
These
He's pissed off
But he's so likeable
He's present like out
3 right
Every time
The top three
Is always the best
And I will robot
On the other end
Horse racing
Which raisin is the closest he's come to the lake place show in end
Exacta box call man
Number it's always
Is the Final Four
We're in the West in the NBA another LeBron and that was it it was LeBron versus the
Nothing
Depicts reality
Nonsensical
I could come up with a better one like the Olympics
Gold silver and bronze
Be a result
The three people who came in first second and third
Are the people who get rewarded
Bronze still win
Become the gold medalist by coming in
The only time that the top three
3 or import
Horse racing and
Of the Olympic Games
Your only important
Arkansas
You just described
Betting odds
Bright Olympic ice skating
Does that mean that there's a
It means people
Games
Who
But I love the idea that
The top three are the
Contenders
If the top three were contenders the Washington Nationals won a World Series
Would be like the entire
Just a foundation
Sports
Is it raining
Macron feel better
Amazon needs help
Checking in on 2011
Yep
And it's interesting
Some of these
Congruous
Things that we talked about
2009-10 man anytime like
Pops up I like to
In present-day Alex
Not into a Ron
Does not like A-Rod
In 2009
He was pro-rata in 2011
Romney and Rick Perry
Weapons material
Dozens of countries have weapons
Iran
Start World War 3
And go along with the police
Crazy
First of all Alex's doing some sort of
High-ground racism
Argue
Growler run
Sort of
You don't like those three girls in Nigeria
Wild berry strain I don't understand
Thinking he's doing let alone what it is he is asked
Solidly pro-iran
Against
Demonizing arawn
That's interested colonialism
Which okay
I guess
Yeah I know
Tehran Falls
No I mean not just that
The idea of advocating for a country to get a nuke
Is essentially saying
If you want to have a conversation with the United States you better protect your neck
Like that's what he said he's like
Iran should have
He's just missing the very idea that the capabilities of
They have will ever produce
Or have any
Potential to
Material
Threat in the way the people who
Make them a threat like Bill Clinton Mitt Romney they aren't that
Which is
Agree with
Within a few years
I'm not sure why
Because I mean Obama's president
In 2011
Everybody
Everybody knows
My principal
Fine with that
Cuz if he before the deal
Before the deal he is like
Spread
We should all keep it that way
Nobody makes a deal
That will help.
Hard not to feel that way
No I don't know cuz we're just taking a snapshot of 2011 we don't know where
Builds to REI
Yeah I know
We get a random acts of Somali pirates
We're not just playing team sports
From some principal place and they're actually is like a tree break
Supposed to
Like moment words like
No this is to
Imagine what that is
No clue
There's at least at present
We know that we should
Give Alex
Which credit bureau credit
Anyway
Gets really defensive about Howard
Supposed to just sit here and be calm and talk about
I want it to stop
A sucker
What's going on
Call
Cool
More loudly
Protest
All of the things that
He is
And has proven himself
He is in the present over
Powder
Yeah exactly
So we can
Yeah yeah
Our friend
Just on this time-travel Adventures
And
Thanks Joshua
Look Joshua's great
Joshua
17 Clips October point
Not talkin about Occupy Wall Street
Finally Alex
Get to Occupy Wall Street
And let's see what his angle is
See who his expert on the streets
For Occupy Wall
Casino
The week-long demonstrations
Are there New York 120
I don't know a bunch of articles about it.
Is it allowed
Wall Street
Luca Brasi wasn't even a New York one
You got a man on the ground
Fuel tank
I don't know what the time frame is
I don't f****** know Mandy was just over there getting a biscuit
U7
I don't know
Just lollygagging
He's not a serious
Person is not Luke radowski is not a serious person
He was hanging out New York
Oh my God what is this
The Occupy Wall
Everything is blowing up
And tried to get
Get some after the fact
He was intact
Actually engaged
Who were there
Portland
Resetting Revolution either
Neither is Alex
None of these
People are
Now
The important thing I think he
Alex
Wrong
The way you presented
He's
Hour and 40 minutes
I hear a bunch of these people are at
End the Fetters
Please end the Federal Reserve
That's not a cure
That wasn't a big deal
I remember Occupy Wall Street they were very insistent that there were only three members of
Congress who voted for the Fed
Fred Wayne
There might be some people and maybe even like
Contingent
Some point
Federal Reserve System
But it wasn't a central tenet
Of the
Ows
Movement it really wasn't even from the
It wasn't a destroy the Fed
Absolutely
Alex Jones
Ron Paul
Those people
And the sad type
So Alex is imagining
These people
Protest
Against
Who are just dumb, you don't realize
Is minimizing the
The entire
Right
Maybe
A lot of them are
Exactly
Like what
Maha
Is my remember that long list on the other hand
It's it was it was intense
Alex
In the exact same
Zigzag
Pattern that the enterologist episode is
Episode
Think he is
I don't think
I think that he
Mad
The police are
Yeah
He likes it they're making fun of the bank
He also likes the specific people who are being oppressed
Arby's
There is definitely that there is actually pepper sprayed
He's a man without a country in this protects
Might as well be
Somali pirates
You can't help but admire
80s it is interesting
Specifically because I remember the way your mainstream right way
Outlets covered this
Which was peor like
Rose and they were like definitely not reacting because there's a black guy
Presidents and their freedom they were like
They're just protesting because they want to overthrow the government
Do you get that I appreciate Alex for
Waffling
I guess that's a
I think it's a more sinister
And honestly
If you will
Will be in activity
Willington
Like he's against the idea of these protesters
Just got to rest
But he's also still denigrate
Clearly not on board with what
By Wall Street
At this point
Which is not getting
Pretending
Understand
Even do little child little communist
Alex we would prefer dinner
I understand that you're mad
Your boss communist
But I know better I know but look
You don't think he's your boss but he is
He's paying you so
This whole time he's talking about the Narwhal
The number of Sorrows
So
I think that I have
September
Fifth 20
I don't think
Is a s*** about matcha
In the New York area where do they converge
Liberty Plaza by City Hall
This is America
New York
Mad
People who are gathering
He's telling all of the
Info Warriors
New York to go to
China Wok
In 2011
Grizzled Detective
Just about to retire
Training Young Buck
We've seen this
What else is present in here I think
Is a
A perfect sympathy
Occupy Wall Street
I don't know
Entirely
But I'm
I'm going to guess
He hasn't talked to me
Because
He didn't seem to care
Much
The day after a ton of people get arrested and depressed
Peaceful protesters getting
Jammed up
The protest
Seems like something
Beats
He spent most
Stupid show talking about
Like dissecting
The Who
Like all this stuff
You spent
Is that much time
That shitt
4 min
About
At all
The day after
Probably one of the most
Like if you really look at the
Of course when the police came in and took all the tents out
More of a
Encroachment
This was one of the biggest
Early warning
Shots of like this is getting serious
Alex doesn't give a s***
He just I don't
I don't think
Before
I bet he will
Because you think he'll give a s*** later because
Clip
From Hammond
Go down there
Because I think he thinks
Co-op
I honestly
We think that is his position
In the same way with a tea party
In 2009 that we
We've seen when you talk
It's about like this tea party is a place where we can
Find people
Then we can educate them
The Federal Reserve and all this year
Views that Occupy Wall Street
Movement is like
Hey
Look maybe some of them self-identify as commie
Cuz they're f******
You don't know who their boss is
But we can red pill those
Pictures down there
Figure this out
And then before you know it
I honestly think that's probably the position from
And I don't I don't I don't think
A Warrior's all go down to this park
Let's let's flood
We got Luke rudowski
Across town when
Action HEPA
He's somewhere
He's around
I don't know I don't know I find this to be a very dishonest
Who live in New York
Luke rudowski
Is around
Start looking
New York
So they could be anywhere
There's a small space
I find this to be like
On a journalistic level
From what I would expect from a
Terrible
D-11
I understand that
Heating the banks
That's true
Mister B's open
No matter what
Positive or negative
Whatever the
He should have
Rock Solid position
This move
Like the people
Like occupying zuccotti Park
Houston
Have a ball
He should
Either
I understand day one
Not knowing what you think
But a week in
They can start on the 17th we're talkin about the 25th
He has a week from
The day before the show
Yeah everything to play out
And get his bearings
Figure out what
Think about it
Do you think anything about it
Except
Maybe we can twist them
Opportunistic
The rebuttal to so many arguments
When we
About
Changed his principles in the present
Well in 2011 following his
Stated principles
He will be off
For occupied
Not really
Not really because they're
Very left
Looks like William black
Yep
Like which are against Alex
And they did
They did do that but the Occupy Wall Street as a movement
Was not
Centered around like
We're going to send these policy proposals to book
In the same way that the
The Tea Party wasn't a movement that was built around were sending policy
Proposal
8 something
The idea of a group
People non-violently brutal this resistance
Exactly
Play this version.
Didn't mean s***
I don't mean s***
Now
Lego news
Tumi
There wasn't any shift on
Principles
Ever know the principles have always been
Nazis in the White House
DoubleDown
I honestly
Everything I can
Until
Alex eventually ends up
Viking Auto
Occupy Wall Street
That motherfuker
Because I think that he
He thinks he can co-opt it the same way I think
I think
I think it'll be an interested I want to do a full investigation
Because I want
You stand it better
I want understand the past
You don't want to know
Hey on the 25th he was
Dismissive
Of it but also thought he could
Co-opted
Right mid October
He's a fan
I want to understand
Progression through the
And I can't do service
To that until we
So I think they are next vest
100%
Be walking
Through
This
It's not that long
It really was but
I think that you
Alex
Really
Really changed
And I think that
I think
A very
Interesting
And robust
How little he cares
When we do that invest
Let's all agree
Where I say
My predict
Is Alex
Dismissive of Occupy Wall Street
Then says they have some good point
Ventas they're good
And then very quickly says they're Eve
Event
Present himself as the real version of it
I would bet a lot of money on that
Progression Bakery
Maybe make us suspicious that like
In the present
Not I'm the real trouble
Are you sure this isn't he will he'll be like
Look
We didn't leave the party
He could pull something like that
French
I don't know a lot of options and
The same time here
Has nowhere to go
Fascinating human being
Yeah I know
I don't think he has a real position on it
Many meanings
He's for the ID
The ideas
People are being
By the police
Wrightwood also jump
He's in a real
Difficult
Evolve
Clip
It's just a little
Icing on the cake
Most
What episode
And about how much Alex wants Ron Paul to be elected president
Most of this episode was the thing that we talked about
Terry tertiary
Both of Us episode was actually about Somali pirates
So
Alex gets a call at
The show
Styxhammer
Are you f******
Exceptions
Invalidate
About Donald Trump
You and I and most your lesson is all they are gold doesn't count I meant Ron Pauley tonight Skype
But does he have a standing army
Afford
Air Defense Artillery.
Keeping working if he was to be a
And I'm running we win exposing the whole system
Illustrating all their dirty tricks
You have this position that
Can fix it all
This one
Lifesaver Vapors
A president before 2011
I don't know
Joshua I appreciate you setting up on the time travel
I don't think that we found
Position about Alex Jones
Occupy Wall Street
You will certainly
Find out more
Indeed
It's so weird when we do the time travel episode
Because unlike
With 2015
We don't have like a f****** sticks week exploration to why it is
You thinking this s***
Right now
Time travel episodes
Crazy because we're like does this mean something does it
I don't know.
I don't know
Like Panera to give it to every episode.
Between
January 1st 2011 and December 31st 1
I knew that he was mostly just talkin about Ron Paul's
Mother things that I didn't pick up on it
We'll figure it out radical
We just figured out
We'll sweep that up
Get back to
More exhaust
We almost certainly will within the next six
212 year
It will be next
So I
Block this been fun
Do we have a redo, feel your hand. Com
Type it in and
Take me to what
Good thing
AltaVista
GoDaddy
Navigator
Real-time Navigator ww.w
Nowlin
Kate
Https
Yeah
Cayenne now this right with a k
Of course
Knowledge
Right
Ross on Facebook
What have you all day
Good stuff
But for now
Who among our cast
The characters to
Has not probably definitely
Lucrative
Prove it
Ask me to prove it
You can't do it
Bradley Cooper
I will say that much like Bradley Cooper probably haven't killed anybody
Same is true of lucre dowski just an ineffectual propaganda
God bless him
He's never killed me by
Anybody who has almost probably
Quickly killed again
Probably totally
Allegedly
Himself he said his
Themselves that guys out
Stop
Alex