Alexandra first in color
Jones did you come prepared with the question this time
Wondering where we are at
Insurance
About the Carolina Reaper puree
My parents
In a little Christmas package they sent over the
Yellowbird sauces from
Austin company
Most of them are trash
It's too hot but it's pretty bad
Joseph Arthur
I think we could have gotten
Honestly I think
Adventurism
Beginning of April
And getting a new apartment one of the things I'm going to focus on there
Is building a little garden
Inside my apartment
Grow some peppers
Make my own
Kind of hot sauce
See if I can figure that out
I added stuff like like grow from
Explorer that and then also
I don't know what that is
August
People outside of Chicago
How do you describe it sort of a relishing kind of thing
Is a condiment like oil
Celery carrots cauliflower
Nearest exit
It's too busy
But you could narrow it down to like two
A really good
Explore those things once I get into a new apartment
That'll be fun
Get into any business today
Car Wash store
Monday episode
In the group
Show sketch
About car wash I did I did
And I want to be very clear about that because I
Constantly question myself about like
Am I remembering that sketch
February
I have to second-guess my memories
Categorical certainty absolutely
Not just a misremembering of that mystery show sketch it really really terrifies me
Remember the feeling of being in that car wash
You are adult the writers from Missouri
He wasn't from Missouri I wasn't really sure that sketch
That they've done that before
I worked at that car wash
I'm pretty sure that was in the 90s
DIA to do the I don't know if he was that hip I just want to make sure that
People understand
That really happened
I don't care anymore
You missed out on a secret friendship with
With your boss who turned out to love
Really interesting
Going to be a slightly different present-day episodes
You covering the Spanish
Going to take
The first
Some people who signed up
Michelle
So first of all you are now policy walk
Play band
You're now a policy
I'm a policy wonk
Journal policy
Xtaren
How much
Aaro
Neither
Somebody who donated on a little bit of an elevated level
You are now a global it
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomizing a bucket of poop
If you're out there listening
Yourself I like this guy
Pepper Farm
I want to dance
Sport the show
Also by the way
I just learned today that Alex Jones Show.
Redirect
Our websites
Present day
I don't want it I don't care about the prison
Ever since Alex's
Cards about
The idea of trump
So you can just act like
A dictator
Care much
I don't
It doesn't charm
Whenever I listen to the shows like what what do you think you say
Play choose anything that's happening
What do you think his angle on it is already know
So f****** predictable in the present-day that I could do this show without listening to his show
Radio host
Supporting Charles de Gaulle
Sure
Comes up on this episode
From Covington
School
Native American settlement
Cancellation of the colonialist attitude that we've had towards Native
Americans for sale
You're being going you know exactly what he's had about it
When we go back to like 2009 we're seeing him support Somali pirates that's true
What's the address
Uyghur
Expecting to find X and Y
Will you look in the present day
Exactly what you expect
Define novelty
Ctuit
I'm not saying we should recuse ourselves from
You know paying attention
2/8 ft
He just is awful I can
It's an awful boring
Formulaic
Neo-fascist show
That's all it is
And it sucks
It seems like
Episode
About the present day we should have
Each episode
Here's what Alex said for this production meeting on here while everyone
Still have to listen to all of it in order to get those many glimpses which is
Incredibly on satisfying for me cuz now the request of our show and more of his
The ratio ends up becoming more work for me for Less
Of this
And already
Today what we're going to do is mostly go over the 23rd that's Wednesday
23rd 2019
But there's a couple things that happened along the way over the course of the
This week on the 17th
Important
We're going to talk about
He's going to open up account
Nation about whether or not it's even appropriate for us to cover Alex in the present anymore
Interesting conversation
Conversation
Looks like when we get to it
Here's an out-of-context drop
Destro folks
Captain America
America
Those guys
Cobra Commander
Does g.i. Joe
We start on the 7th
And
If these are going to be some tripe
Thanks
We're not going to cover much contact
From 17th and 9th
They're mostly going to be Alex
Descending into
Personal loan
The whole thing
Destro Age of Ultron
Really
Deuces
New Slang
I'm introducing that into the
Modern vernacular
Dead friend 33
Dr. Infection died
Linebacker
Wouldn't
Hot dog
And I really bad whatever you wanted to ask
Thaddeus klunk Alex's
Yeah this is never going to work
Bocornya hot dog
Rappers that would be able to work
Corny hot dogs
No
Fatman Scoop
Is a shout-out guy
Hot dog bone Bone Crusher out there like talk but I was never scared
Remember who else Fatman Scoop work with
All right you're not up on current Hip Hop
That's fair
Master P
Master P probably worse
Just give that rhymes with Soldier way2go
Alright
Yeah
Talks about how he
Deal with the
Can't do it
I just telling you right now ladies and gentlemen
Civil War
Running around bullying and threatening
Because
Always talks about the global
Make a deal with the Devil
Really counter to pretty much everything about all the time
The idea that he can't make a deal with the Devil
Will be important later
Is a little bit of a setup
Punchline coming later
In order to
Do well
No it's it's something else entirely breakdown
It came out about Cohen
Payments
Two people
16 election
It made it reflect or appear
That more people believe the Trump won the debates
And they did
That is
It may have been
Raped by
This outfit is
The Drudge poll
Of trump
Performance
And it's like the story I believe
Alright
Whatever we'll see how this shakes out how about that
Everytime I saw that one like
You know who else can influence
A bunch of dudes just clicking a bunch of times it's
But yeah
I don't think it's fine but I also think it's like what let's do
Let's see what more there is here
At this point
You are the Q and I have enough
To go on
To have a real Firm Stance
Cuz he's predictable and defense
Right I think my biggest problem with it
I want my villains
To be super
I don't want them to be pathetic
Losers
Do you know what I mean
I do know what you mean you're not going to get what you want
Big fans of Alex Jones
I know it's a reference for license.
He's doing is he's doing an imagined
Dialogue
Between Trump
Chicken neck
What are the reason
I think the biggest reason I'm
Including this clip in our in our little brief glimpse
Of January 2nd
Demonstrate
Submental
Problems
On Alex
They're not uncommon or unfamiliar to us
But I think they're more important today than they have
This is not our business
Action Mitchell
What
Never heard of
Chicken craft
Just I mean
He is expressing
Huge but just nonsensical
Two-sided
The socratic debate
What's going on inside his head
None of it's based in reality reality
And all it does is
Freedomtoons
Weird I'm the only person who's a real man anymore I don't I don't know it's just
If there's something going on in his brain
Both
Parts of transfer policy
And blaming
Other people
Foreign policy
And also blaming it off at me. This is what happens when you don't know anything
And this is what happened
You have a super predictable editorial position
But he doesn't have any new watch doesn't he has no George Soros might put it reflexive
Respond defensively
Attack whoever is not on board
And it's pathetic and boring
But I also I also
I think there's more going on
Because if he's
Specifically talking about
Not supporting our allies
Trump's unilaterally and also reverse decision to pull troops out of
Siri
Absolutely abandoning our allies
So he's against
The foreign policy of the people that
Supposedly
Puppet Master
All the counts everybody
We're done and said
Okay I guess and then six months later like 2 months later very quietly
Yeah
Alex's version on that is that I can put his foot down and then the meddling globalist
Just didn't listen to that effect
Do you want
We know from listening to as much Alex Jones as I have
I'm telling you about it childhood
Fraught with
Nonsense
Fictitious
Clearly
Fight the things that we know that
To be very consistent are
You know had some feelings of alienation
And at the same time
Discovered none dare call it
Conspiracy
The book by Gary Alan when he
He was 12
Except the course of his life he saw through
The you call it
The conservative
The Communist Menace Among Us the conspiracy of the elite which was that
Manhattan
It conspiracy on the shelves
His parents were mostly cups
John versus
His childhood very consist
Discovered
Depending on the time
Cities told the story
Very consistent
I have heard other accounts
I found it in high school
He says 10 or 12
On a very regular basis
Which makes this next clip
Incredibly impossible for me to believe
Intimately obsessed with abusing children and chilling
Compare
I agree
I am not in their system
Almost
When I was about
I was a
Okay
And I wasn't killing people or dogs or anything that kind of sounds like
What is the country where I grew up I've seen the Dark Side of the Moon
And
I pulled out
$15
I was definitely there
Boy it's a hell of a drug
Contact
I got partially seduced but never gave over all the way
What
So far from the satanism
So far away from these people
Super far
In the spiritual
But all the crap in the rituals.
Aleister Crowley went
I think
I think it's his first of all potion
Doing is just trying to give himself another piece of the you like hero's journey
Yeah
The sort of moment of doubt in
Seduction by Darkside and stuff like that
No rights
A 12
Crowley
Probably f****** talking about
Crowley was a f*****-up dude
I'm sure Alex
The Crowley traveled the world from like the late 1800s early 1900s
Scared to venture far from the Western Shores
He attempted to climb K2
Never been scaled at that point
He took a spiritual Quest To The Logical extreme
Traveling to Japan
Sri Lanka India
Egypt to seek out instruction and knowledge
You can say the Crowley was bad dude and I'm not going to argue with that point
Pretty much at all or much
But you can't live a life of curiosity and exploration
Strictly opposed to
Alex read none dare call it conspiracy when he was 12 and it blew his mind ever since
What are
Whenever he's gone to visit another country he's only been to verify the pre-existing beliefs
He brought with him
He's a pathetic example of a mind made up in childhood which Crowley was the opposite of
I don't believe Alex a story about being a Satanist from the age of 12 to 15
I think that's just him expressing
Deep guilt about forcing women to get aboard
But assuming he's not lying and he Siva Crowley scene
Let's guess what Alex was up to back when he was 12
Sex Magic
He would almost certainly have been into sadomasochism those that was pretty prevalent in curly sex life
Most definitely would have been on the receiving end of sex with men since they sex intercourse with a large party higher levels of
Crowley Sex Magic
And he was famously bisexual
It was noted as the passive partner in those encounters
He may or may not have been eating cakes which would make the menstrual blood or semen
I don't think Alex has any idea who else to Crowley was or what he stood for
He just knows that he's a good account name to drop I was going to say
Like I was for Crowley's just
He was incredibly f***** up
Really f***** up stuff
But I also
What do you eat with El Ron Hubbard
The red lady
He is somehow to me
Strictly opposed
Crowley in that
He was he was just like
Sex is crazy let's do all of it
Like Aleister Crowley
You don't know that I don't know.
Nothing is more sex magic than shoving something down your pee hole
I'll let you have that I'm not going to I'm not going to push back
But
Harry Potter
What I Hear here is Alex desperately trying to give himself some sort of like
Appeal to
To expertise and knowledge about these
That's what it's what all these assholes
Everybody who has The Stolen Valor or stolen
People on Project Camelot pretending they were CIA agent
Captain Mark Richards
Piece of their past
Employ in order to give themselves ownership of and
Like there's knowledge that they have that you can't possibly have and so you should just listen to them
It's a manipulative tricks
Furthermore
Here's a question
For his
It's so so if he's in those
Richard he's not doing the ritual
He's going to do that means
He's just doing the Satanist
Number 2 for 3 years
I don't know
Once you're in your head
For three years in your formative years
What kind of cookie even
He doesn't even know about the problem
Something like that
Reacting to that emotionally
That's not good at art
On the 17th there's not much else I want to talk about except for this next clip
Where Alex
As hell
I think it's only important
Because we just had the news come out about this
Supreme Court DACA
Fry's
Think that we are
We're entering a dangerous time
Uno's
Going to go with we're entering a dangerous. Of the
The exclusion and
Erasure of trans people from Publix
Visibility
Knowledge
You know what I mean
Awareness
Place in society
And so I think it's important to see
Be the kind of rhetoric that Alex is putting out into the world
About these sorts of
Issues on January 17th
Smart
We need to get a full shampoo
And says you are going to
Schmear
And the nurse
No it's okay
Hospital
You know what
The dog
Maybe I was wrong
That sounds like something that he
I mean this is
It is his way of
Trying to
You think he's doing is taking extreme
Isn't doing a reductio ad absurdum
Same logic
Absurd extreme
It's not
That story that he's telling about this nurse who got fired
From the UK hospital
Like you probably reference from 2017
Requested female nurse
It was a woman nurse showed up in the exam room
No it was fired over it
The patient after work
I don't know if that's even
Appropriate
Beware the story stop
It's also possible that he's referencing a sensationalized story out of the Sun
The Tabloid
About how Public Health guidelines were reflecting
Screenings that were appropriate for their.
So if the story was about anything real it was about the bureaucracy of the health administration
Not other entrants
It wasn't about trans pap smears as a
It was about routine reminders that are sent out to everyone
Bot invite them to take care of their health care
There's nothing malicious or weird
In that story at all
Do I can find no evidence that this is a real story I can find other stories that Alex doesn't want to talk about
There's a case in 2015
Went to e.r. where the staff
Because the lights
Instead he was carrying wasn't.
Up-to-date
Quote they came up and she's like that's a girl that's really a girl
It wasn't business-like at all I was a spectacle I was a freak Show at the Cirque
It was definitely to draw attention to
To the fact that my outward appearance didn't match my identification
Ethan Cicero who author study on trans experience at hospital
Expressed this experience is all too common
And in fact is a threat
Same quote
From a safety standpoint I don't know many people who would want to be in that position and stay in that environment
People without receiving care
National Center for gender equality found that 19% of those surveyed had been denied Medical Care
Because they were trans or gender-nonconforming
And a 28% of reported postponed
Do discrimination
The story-telling is not true
What that story reinforces is a status quo that is killing
And I mean that literally
In May 2015
Fourteen-year-old Kyler Prescott committed suicide after hospital employees
And staff would not stop calling him a girl
Tyler was at Rainbow Children's Hospital in San Diego
Depression
It was on a suicide watch to begin with
But according to his mother
The staff refusing to stop misgendering them called the downward spiral
Quote they were making him worse
They were completely traumatizing
The staff knew the situation
And one employee even said quote
Honey I would call you he but you're such a pretty girl
That kind of why I don't care
About stories like The Wanderers one from July 28th
What is contract terminated at UK hospital because he's
We refuse to accept
The hospital policy for burns
People by their preferred pronoun
He can claim all he wants that it's irrelevant to his ability to treat a patient
But tons of anecdotal stories
And actual Studies have been done that clearly show that this is not the case
And the keys wrong
Also that story about David Mack arrest
Cannot possibly be what Alex is referencing all the details are completely different
So that doesn't even track with his
Almost certainly made up story
So I just might my point here is that with Alex's doing
When is
Ever
Issue is always
Is the reverse
The reality
Do you want some man going into the women's bathroom
Little girl might be
Well
10 is infinitely more likely to be abused when going into the men's bathroom
Correct
Was it is always
The reason
For this
Protection is sexual abuse
Ward train
The reason for these protection
They're always
Because so much abuse
Abuse is living
Ward's
People and they try and turn it into somehow there
They're firing people for not wanting to continue to abuse people
Like what the story that I can find it even
Comes close to Tracy
Track of
A trans woman nurse
To feel
Bad about that
Because the woman was uncomfortable with her
I don't know
Victim-blaming behavior and that's that's what you
Expect
It's not like hey look at Alex
Taking the weird turn it's right on course
Just
It needs to be
Be pointed out
As
That what Alex is doing is reinforcing the world
View that
Is one of
Did not get a pass for that
And we won clip
It doesn't let Alex off the hook for anything but I legitimately might
Serve as
Application that we
We can't
Talk about Alex in the same way in the
I think he said something that reveals
Stroke on air right now and it's close to that Bible
We see clear evidence of
Like real substantial
Mantle
I go to 62% oxygen always have
Text Becky
Most people die at 60% oxygen
What's the weather
So that's extreme
Wow so you got some serious app
Big deal
Incredibly serious
He doesn't want to do DMT with Joe Rogan
Is beyond what's treatable with normal procedures
And you have to sleep sitting up
All that is really sad
Somebody who suffered with Sleep Disorders earlier in my life I'd never wish that kind of thing on anyone
At the same time it really starts to clear up some Quest
About why Alex is the way he is
According to a 2016 study from the UCLA School of Nursing
People who suffer from sleep apnea show significant changes in their levels of two important brain chemical
The first is Gaba or gamma amnio of butyric acid
Studies show that people with sleep apnea showed significant decreases of Gaba which is involved
From higher brain region
Regulate emotions and physical functions
Such as blood pressure and perspiration
UCLA describe Gabba is a chemical messenger that exist
Keeping people calm
Functioning like a break
People with severe sleep apnea like Alex is describing has significantly lower levels of
Simultaneously
The study found that while Gaba levels are low levels of glutamine or significantly elevated inpatient
Sleep apnea
Glutamine is the opposite of Gaba
And works as an accelerator
Glutamine levels are high
The brain is working in a state of stress
And consequently doesn't function
As efficient
Paul Macy the lead researcher of the study said quote
It's rare to have this size of difference and biological measures
We expected an increase in glutamine because of the chemical that causes damage
And we've already seen brain damage from sleep apnea
What we were surprised to see was the dropping Gabba
That made us realize that there must
To be a reorganization of how the brain is working
If Alex suffers from sleep apnea so severe that
CPAP machine
About it
It's a very serious condition
And you expect to see wildly out of balance levels of Gaba and glutamine
A company that
And you know why
That's very
Clearly explains his behavior
He doesn't explain his bigotry
Out-of-control Behavior
It could all be the Public Presentation of brain damage she suffered because of his sleep apnea
Obviously this doesn't let him off the hook for anyting
Since we can see this terrible beliefs
Real stupid
Behavior
But if this sleep apnea developed over the past few years it would definitely explain the
Flagrant inability
He has to control his emotions
And his out-of-control Outburst on the show we're like
It was legitimately could be
Result of brain damage caused by his severe sleep apnea
I don't know how I feel about that
But there is some good news
They've also found in these studies
Studies strong indications that the brain damage caused by these out of whack
Chemical level
Camp
So it's actually start taking this seriously
We get that surgery the doctors
Recommended in
Going on the right path
He could be back to being a run-of-the-mill interesting racist
In no time
It's possible I mean a lot of this
It gives you a window into like okay
That doesn't sound like when he just make stuff up
Pissed off to have to
We talkin about it.
It gives you a window and that window is
He probably has diminished brain functioning and
Wheatley
Way out of normal range chemical levels
For these
Sort of restricting and accelerating
Yeah
It explains so much
Yeah it's too much like
He's on
Adrenaline all the time like every single moment of his life
His brain is stressed out
Exist
You can't excuse
But it is
It is one of those things where like if you've ever had anybody in a traumatic
Car accident
Personality
Suddenly
Really rare
Completely
Like 180
And who they are right it's almost always in
Acceleration
Expansion
Of those terrible character
They already
Inhibiting
He's always one of the fascist but now you really want that
Yeah maybe on something because of what we do you know parsing out the clues that he provides
Getting context for the things you say baby's brain chemical imbalance
He doesn't have those governors yet restrictive
Regulation of emotions
Some stuff like that
So maybe he tips
And more because of it
Analysis how often
Drops
The quiet part loud in the past 3 years is compared to
Yeah it does
I don't know I feel very weird about that because I don't know where that puts Alex on my feeling
About this present day
But I feel very conflicted about it
Like if if what he's saying is true
Balance does exist
And his behavior does
Match
With what studies
Shoshone to behavior someone
Who had brain damage from
Severe sleep apnea
Yeah I don't know how I feel about that
I don't know I don't have an answer I'm just conflicted
He saying is true it sounds
It's right
He's over exaggerating it but this is like a
I need to get through this obvious fact and we just need to move on and we don't need to worry about it but I don't I don't know why Alex
I about something
It's not in his character
Dale sings
Enhances
Important
Citicards
Play
Fuel made up
And the reason that I
Get more seriously
Because what
His behavior matches
The outcome
That would be
The results
The most
Compelling piece of evidence
Right again like I said I don't know
Based on his face and how many fights are apparently
Like all of this stuff
Is 8
Probably right
Right
The only thing about it is
So much of what we talked about regarding
Could be attributed
Any number of drugs
Conflicted
So for now my editorial position
He was f***** up is f***** up
We're not sure why
I'm going to I'm going to call myself out on it a little bit
We talked about him in the future
Then we might be horrible
But until further confirmation comes
I think
View the father
She has kids
He needs to take care of that so like my feeling on it is
As entertaining as his outbursts are
I think
The greater good is for
Listen to the doctors
Get that neck surgery
You have millions of dollars
You have good health care
You can do that
Don't keep sleeping sitting up I don't know I don't know what the Infowars
Insurance package
I'm telling you I don't think he threw Alex
I don't know. He has a dream self
Anyway
I don't know man
Real serious curveball for me
Yeah that stuff
To the 23rd
Where will spend
The bar time
For today going through
How Alex enjoyed Wednesday
Start Spotify
About how
Declaring emergency
Didn't happen
We went over on pants episode
But I hate
How could you not have been wrong about flowing
Because of the shutdown
Declared a national emergency
No
How predictions wet
We told you but
Convoluted nonsensical idea
I told you a sunspot was going to destroy New York City on January 12th
Vincent just backed off
Troy New York
Bright
Prediction
But
You come down
Alex discusses
Trend
This seems to keep happen
The seems to keep well
President
He can use the military funding to do it
I told you that
Situation
We will because
You mean your immediate response was right maybe Trump is backing off at the last minute or maybe
He's a f****** con man
Who's bluffing with all this stuff
Maybe
Everything you want him to
Is such a tremendously bad idea
Even if
To the point where he's like
This is
Not
At Altru anybody make me look like
F****** a b**** I don't want to do
Information
Downey Police Department of Maricopa County
We went over is complete the whole story
Absolute nonsense imagine the idea of trump coming out with
The public
Can you imagine if more people than just us
Talked about the dentist Montgomery
It would be able be opening Pandora's Box never wanted to
That should give some in
Indication that the story
Doesn't have as much legs out
To contextualize it all he wants as like
Trump keeps backing off
But that's not what's going on
ABC's
Lying to the public and then not
Not
Falling through because he knows it
The klusterfuk
Is because
Of course he feels like
Betrayed by the
Publicly
Right
But
He does the same thing on account of he knows
He's lying as well
So he knows
He's going to be
Roundly
The president
The f****** present of the United States
Everyone's
Not just
Do any of that ship without
Definitely essential features in there
Modus operandi
Is that they don't follow through
Because like
What is like a consonant
Classically is out of town by the time it comes time to do whatever
I turns out you can just
Move on
The new cycle in Tucson
Something else or
That's true
Yeah it distance
Be spiritual version of leaving town
That's what Alex is describing when he says Trump
Follow through
The same thing
Is it that when Alex tries to prove anything
He's leaving town or episode
Proving white Wiz
That Trump should have
Declared a national emergency
First I'm going to spend the two hours of course bitching about why everybody makes
Feel bad all
The tighter the last 2 hours
Someone else
Some headlines
Caller
15 minutes
Organic a proven episode that he has moved the goalposts
Pretended to prove other things
Revealed
So that's going to work better than a hot dog
I think we would have a better chance hot dog is what I call
Map
A lot of narrative
Perpetuating
Present-day artists
Predictable
And here is Alex talking about the kids
Bob from Covington
Stockbridge
Where it's like are they bad or are they good
Fairview bastila whitewash
You white piece of crap
20 minutes
The poor wonderful
Lambo Vietnam Commando
Elder
Wampum
That's not good
Avengers
It's real bad
I don't know why you were acting in a very racially insensitive racist
Undercut
Are you picking on these races kids doing races I'm doing racist
What are you doing is he's trying to pull this weird sleight-of-hand trick
The Native American guy with the
The word yelling stuff at
This entire story
End cuz it guess what what whatever you thought
Is pretty much right
Seeing the details watching all the
If your takeaway is that those kids
And particularly the one who was just sort of smugly standing in front of
That the dude is that they were at
Like really
Inappropriately
You're right in terms of like the kids
From Covington
Text that were there
But you came in with the drum
It's trying to Defuse The Situation
And then those kids started antagonizing
You actually watch the videos you can tell that the black Israelites were actually
Calm down by
And do you throw kids in the
Have you were not they've been beginning
Antagonizing
I would hate to be in the picture that is
So
Closely related to
What was the name of
Of the first
Blackstone
Screaming at her like
Yeah
To be that it is it is the sort of thing where the Optics of it are
Really
Resonant
Captures
I don't know
The kids
Mixing it up and arguing with
She's black is Ray
If you want to point the finger at somebody pointed at them
You know you could have but instead Alex
His take on it is
That this Native American is cheap swamp
To go to college campuses and get upset
About people dressing up like Native Americans
He has his whole like
A strange
I mean I understand that over doesn't pay that
I'm just saying
Convoluted narrative about
Behind it
I suppose my biggest frustration
And the reason that I did
Pay attention
Because
There are already so many
There are so many of these pictures
Ferguson is like any number of these pictures if you want to find them you can see a picture that gives you a perfect and
Capsulation
Of white race
I don't like these stories because
Clearly we have not been able
The focus on
Any one of these
For a long enough.
To do anything
So is operative
Frustrating because it's
Like f****** guys
We got to pick one and then never
Ever
No no no no no
That's why they've done
Cuz I have one thing to say
Right
Focus of Messi
Whether or not what they saying is true or not
One so much
Let's talk about how those kids
Are awesome
The places where Maca is cool are better
Explains what he means by better
You know what
No
Are we still
I don't want that
Square all day
Is it
Drug addict
Weirdo
Pretty good
More
You're drunk on air all the time
This is nonsense
Drink on the job
Call Mandy real Square Alex
Like if what he saying
That's where people are working 12 to 14 hours a day
That's what I work on this remember the beat
Pictures of the future from like the 1940s and 50s number one was always like
And because of automation only work 3 hours
Where's the date
Standard of a good place is you're overworked
No not good
He says Old Glory flying at the Statehouse he means the Confederate flag
I would say no I do not think that makes for a good place
Courthouse
Head covered in Bible
Yeah
A place where you work 40
That's the real
Trying to be like
Farmer
Maybe maybe
Farmer Farmer might be what
You go home
For 2 hours
Sleep for 8 hours
To that that is entirely possible
But what he doesn't fail to recognize it
Working 14 hours a day
Uber drivers in jail in Confederate flag-waving
People working 12 hours today
Alex's
Fear about this Caravan 3.0
Because we need it again
The right needs
Season 2 of
They needed again I'm not sure why
The government shutdown
Make sure that
Democrats somehow look bad I don't know
Cuz there's not another election
I'm coming up for another year
Shutdown negotiations
Because the
Is the Democrats don't want the wall
A build-up fear of what the wall
Disappointed
For the same way
But Alex's
Mexico is going to let
People through
He says
Trump should do something
Very scary
Everyone
Be terrified by
Understand
Associated Press
Mexico
2 degrees
We will allow full-on invasion
Now you know what the regular response is a dash
Sure
Start a war
Let them know that we're not going to have Mexico
Running a territorial war against the holy s*** out of the truck
And take the capital so fast
What points great we've been doing in ground Wars
You take Mexico City
I don't know install a government you like
That's what happened
And installing government
Overthrowing governments right right right right
Broken clock is right
Global
Yeah yeah
It just wouldn't hear stuff like that
And that is like
Back to me
Did you
Sleep apnea
E-40 war on Mexico
Troops to Mexico City
But that's only because
What
How far out a line is this with everything he's reported to believe
Well
He hates regime-change
Afraid of these immigrants and refugees
Asylum
When they make it to our party so fucken afraid of that
And what's behind it
I think if you really break it down
Is the idea that
He's afraid of demographic shift
Is afraid of the idea that white people
The power
It's so fun how much right-wing rhetoric
Relies on Mexico
You know it's like
Hey we're going to accomplish something is like Mexico
Right
Forest
If that's
Control of it
Do all of our work for us
Everybody knows that kind of flippant
Partially
Because he has such
Like fantasies about the sound
I think there's a pretty decent chance
What underlies his disrespect of Mexican sovereignty
He's just kind of like
Play I live in Mexico
Might as well
But in the
Text Alex
Expresses
Ask about Trump
Tom and
The closest get to criticism
Because the Trump isn't doing a good enough job
It turns
The protecting Americans
Yats
Jerks
Okay trip
I stayed up late last night so I had happened this morning
A container have a package
I'm already past infected
I tell you what I'm feeling right now
It it that is not a good visit
Uninhabitable
You should buy
It is right here
Is actively working against like
Hey guys what you're seeing for me right now is I'm out of it I'm out of it because I took this product
Which is the new products available on the store.
This is bad
Hilarious
Yeah it's very buddy
If it works sketch it would be brilliant
Food Bistro
Infowars store
I didn't
Which is also attributable to what he said
Not be able to sleep
Product
By saying how tough they are to deal with
I don't understand this world
Breezy
Banana
Yeah it's pretty nuts
Is there
Regardless
Costs that are going on
Not just Financial cost
Button terms
Programs that are being
You can read about where people are having to sneak into
Cultures alive
Research they're doing
And stuff like that
Like massive Fallout
That we won't understand
And that was the last time we had
Even shorter government shutdown
We didn't understand
The damage that was being done
As it was happening
We do understand right now
The people who are being affected by it not being
Paid and stuff like that
We understand that
Yep it's it's heroine
About like all the stuff that we're going to discover that we
You just didn't realize
Got f***** up
In the in the process
And what's
Super important
To remember is that as much as this is
Is Trump being a giant baby
Every Republican
In elected office
Save-A-Lot
Maybe a few
Is a giant
Trump is an idiot
Trump doesn't know Trump is trying to win a fight
Trump is not aware of how real things work he's a
The f****** moron
Problem
Put a ton of members in the Senate and the house
No.
F****** well the damage that they're doing
And they're doing it out of
Cowardice
Two twins get f***** over
Because they don't want
Get
Blowback I don't want to look like they're breaking ranks
And then
Exactly
Because all of these people are
Cowards probably
You still giving him a little bit
We're on or on getting sick of this guy watch
ZR2 this time Alex follows up
Bikes at expressing a plan that he has
ProTech
People need to call the White House
Could they take the form letter
White House peaceful March
President declared emergency
He was but he backed off
How crazy is it
Alex f****** Jones
Three talking about going across the country
Peaceful march by the way
Where he tries to encourage the president to express
Executive powers
How quick like
Not a few years ago whether it was Obama or bushes term
He would have done the exact same thing or maybe pretended he was going to
He would have said he was going to go and protest Bush or Obama
He's not doing nothing I need
I need
Create this Authority
Once he does
I-10
Via media figure
Yeah pretty much
I am going to go to the
And have a peaceful protest
Declare himself King
I'm destroyed
So I can get back on Twitter
Eunos
He believes that
Trump
Executive powers
Will allow him to
To create this sort of world that
Which
We understand
Engaged
What does rhetoric over
Is a white
Authoritarian
Do you think there is also a bit of a
Obviously in the world we live in now
He can't
Really be
Successful
So
Install Jose
I guess dictators
I think about this question
Then Trump is thinking well of course I'm going to keep Fox & Friends
It's got to go
Talking Friends
Alex as his
I think you can install Alex in a media operation
His brand of
Media
Much more protected
Words
We heard him talk about it about how Obama put in all these executive orders that he can't name
Doesn't specify
And one of them is this vague idea of
Controller
What
If the government
Has the authority
Authority
To take over the
Comedian sound like
Alert system
But he believes
Is it just a warning
Tornado watch
Get to your basement
Hawaii
Apologies holy work
I think that there is
He has this misguided
That should
These
Give powers
Alex
To have
He would be able to then overturn all of the things that are keeping Alex down
Trump can get an executive order to put them back on
Right right because he believes that those things
Things that are keeping
Social media platform
Parts of government
Coordination
Government not his treasured
National
So it's all based on
A misunderstanding
Of what's Happening
Is willful
But also
Sophia lucky
I don't know
I just want him to take over
Sarah Huckabee
His life would be so much
Booth that be crazy
Anymore you might as well put Alex
F*** yeah everybody would have a great time
And make it make Alex feel so good
Give me a much-needed win
Second source of income
To get that neck surgery
Which I bring back up because
I think this next quote
The demonstration on January 23rd of
Exactly
Is glutamine
Excessiveness overabundance of this
Stress hormone
Deficiency
I believe
Frank
Full demonstration
This is why it makes me uncomfortable
I still like to laugh about him
But this is why it's
Kind of a comfort
$9,000 cars
You talk about Maxine Waters
Husband
I don't like losing
How much do
That's a really bad at
I mean that's not even it
Hahaha
Either that or he just
Did a lot of Coke
People save that shitt
Yeah or or
Could make someone laugh
That is right on the line of fake
Psychotic
And almost Primal level of like
If you hear somebody make that noise
Yeah I'm going to Play It Again Play it again
This morning
That's f****** good Joker
Yeah
Listen I think that there is an element of its fake and there's also a part of it
Define the line there
Flies like someone who
Yeah
You hate yet
You hate to see this
Yeah
Scary
Doing that as an actor
You heard that he's going to call
Bring that energy
Yeah
Terrifying
Yeah yeah I'm uncomfortable with all of that
Sew-ins next clip Alex
Business
Chief wampum
It's not good
I want to get into a New Mexico called the Covington element
Shingle Christianity
Crap
Why
Demonic snake absolute bottom-of-the-barrel Democrat bill
Garbage
That's terrible
That is just terrible
Terrible
I think
Keys
Really channeling
Andrew Jackson trying
Finish the Native America
Do you know
The like
Cuz it's legitimately like
They did
On purpose
That was their main reason for
Destroying that
And he looked
So
And his interviews that happened afterwards he wasn't even mad at those
Just kids
But you didn't demonize them
Snake which is why UK
Can't demonized
That's one of the rules of hell did you looks like a demonic make which is also
You know
Between the ages of 12 and 15
I don't know whenever you say somebody looks like
Demonic
Whatever
That's usually you're trying to
Use code
I always
Get the sense that whatever
You're relating someone's
Appearance 2
Demonic nest
You're generally I mean you're talking about their physical characteristic
And
It's 8 to talk to wiggle away from that cuz I see that guy and I don't think he looks like a demonic snake
He looks pretty nice
Looks like a guy
Nice about it
Is that
Normally
He uses demonic
To refer to
That's true
You know like you can call built up
Situation
Using that
Trigger
You felt up to
Reply to this guy
So it's not better
He's in a bummer of a place even
For him because when he would really love
Is to go after the black Israel
I don't think you understand that part of the story
If I was giving if we were doing
R manga
Nationalist
They're black
Melissa
Picture was the the black
Israelites
And the white
Assholes
Of course
It's right to go out
After them
Long series of reasons
Parentheses
Mainly because
But because
Pictures of
In Vietnam war vet
Soros operative
This is bad even for
I think that's one of the reasons
Scope of the situation go after the black Israelites
Is that
Like anybody who knows anything
Knows that
They
Thrive on antagonist
Is there a hangout Insidious
East Coast
People on street corners
Hope it's a notary
I can't provide if you want to learn a little bit more about them
Go for it
But also there's a good
Where you at
The black National
What's that
You get a little bit of an insight into how they operate
Be here in Chicago like I got a ride
There is a little colonel of that in what they do there
The way they operate is
Enticed
People in
2 watt vape
I don't know if you had this
Is Ian go to college
Which belief
But like when I went
Ouch I'm sorry I don't mean to disparage
Fine
The necessary University Missouri
There's a guy who's come to the campus
She would go around
Country number people who were listening
To their campus
College
He was around
His main base was at the creek
Got a ride
Susan Missouri and he was always on
Mizzou
His whole thing was just screaming
Powderhorn
How they're going to hell
And what you would do if you would attract a large crowd of college kids who are mostly laughing at
Keywood Gallatin
Intubate
And
You know what
Here's the thing
It doesn't work
Big picture
Does work
In terms of like
1000 people are going to laugh at you and maybe someone's going to take a swing at you
But you get to use that guy who takes a swing at you as an example of why you're right in your repressed right
And the people who come to
Maybe one out of every 5000 people
Do you encounter
Is going to be Extreme as f***
And it's going to be a good
Recruit
The people like people like
The black Israelites
They are
Operating a very similar
It's at Broadneck
Everybody
But the people
You do get or going
Soldiers there going to be an acolyte
Yes that's the reason
Do they get along well
Excellent.
Is
An offshoot of
Malcolm X
Malcolm X's Church
Extreme enough for them
I couldn't love him
Because his words were so smooth is he still alive
Branched off of the
Create decipher
Percent Nation Nation
Gods on Earth
Where is conception
Is the black man is God made up of
Which one Parts arm leg leg arm head
Which are
Especially
English
Don't spell it that way
He believes that the black man is
Existence
Mutually
Respectful arrangement
Fat people in pop culture kind of believe
These beliefs like the
Among other rappers
The rizs version of the 5%
Is almost
Reform
Five percent Nation
He takes a lot of the racism out of it she has
In later time I think if you went back to like
When 36 Chambers was recorded it probably
Handsome
Mitre
I might know too much about them
The reason it's called the five percent Nation
Because they believe that their 5%
Population
It is aware of the
Truth and helping wake up
The rest of the
85% of the population
Is deaf blind
They have no idea what's going on alright then there's 10%
The 5%
Keep the 85
But don't have a clue asleep
That the 5%
Is that the black man is
In the more reform versions of
These days
It's more
It's not really that important what race you are
Is Maura self-empowerment thing
Like the 5%
You are a god
Misogyny
Perform Brett it's great it's interesting
To answer your question
Five percent nation is an Islamic group
Black Israelites
Which are more
Assertive
Ohiopyle
Israeli
I'm sorry
Absolute black nationalist
Which
Seems like it would be common ground
I don't from what I understand and I could be a little bit wrong about this
What I understand
Don't see eye-to-eye
Catch up the by percent Nation
Oh bummer
You guys would have
At this point to talk more about
From Covington
The Covington boys
He says something
Square
I don't care
Or
So
Two of those years at least
Asia
His whole timeline is fun
School is awesome
Must be great
School you can go find
Pictures of
Bunch of kids
That's great
School
You bet it's crazy
People who looked into the
Their talk to others
Student
Who go to that school they fall into
Problematic
Very
Singularly White
Valedictorian
Gay who is like
This is
He's a former Valley
You always are available
Sounds right I didn't graduate college
Zoe
Alex
And what he does is
Appeals to
He's built up as a
And because we've done our work
Followed out
We know this is a lie
So Alex is already without talking about the
Specifics of the
Situation is it
The black Israelites who were
The provocateur the was the Native American guy was drunk
Is black Israelites who were screaming at the kids go back to Europe
Necessities
Suburban is actively trying to
Diffuse the situation between the two
Hardee's in fighting
Provocateur
Is how you go to
2018 Bugatti
Which one cause martial law
When the police
Are there any
Starbucks
Authorized
These are the documents that he found on 4chan that are
Completely
These are the hit contract
This is this to me is where like
But because of the show that we do it never does
Like the conversation
Sing like that
And all you have to do
Where does your narrative go if those aren't
You haven't proven that they're real
So where do you have anything to stand on here if they're not real right
No you don't
This day all this falls apart
This idea that the guy
Is it provocateur falls apart
He's even now throwing into in those documents
That wasn't part of this before
You know that the initial thing was a lie
So you can add a hat to a hat
You can lie on top of a lie
If the antifa sometimes uses
This guy was using a drum
He must be logically sound
You can call
Clearly confirm that if a uses a drum
Then by necessity if B uses a drum
Despite there being no connection between them
They must be
Is the protesters
Used drums
This protest
Drum
Possible
Southern work
Breaking news
Important
Caracas is basically falling in Venezuela
President here has recognized
Crazy
So has declared himself president of Venezuela
But the president Nicolas Maduro
I have no interest in litigating the presidency of Maduro because I sincerely
What's going on right now is a coup
And Donald Trump has expressed that he recognizes as the president of Venezuela
All options are on the table in terms of dealing with a situation
This could end up being a very very serious problem
Because you know who recognizes Maduro still at this point
Russia China
North Korea Iran
Turkey Mexico in many other countries
There's a ton of oil in Venezuela
It's not like the world is just going to agree to disagree about who the president
And this could very seriously blow up into a geopolitical crisis
Now that Maduro has indicated that he's going to cut off relations with the US
It is given notice for diplomats to return to the US
Because of our schedules this week
But just before we started recording
Indications growing that Trump will not withdraw diplomat
Because the president
He recognizes didn't
Ask him to
This is a recipe
Before an international incident
He said he would withdraw there were indications that he was going to make that statement
Right before we started recording
Absolutely I mean that could Spark
It's like an absolute
I don't know what the situation is cuz
For the last hour and a half
What you what you see
Is the recipes
Before
Real f******
In trouble
Because it's not an isolated
Like I know how bad Brazilian
Like the idea that bolsonaro is in power
But it doesn't have the same wedge
That's something like what's going on in Venezuela right now does
These are both
Absolutely South America
Central America
This is
Like this is Jeff
You have now
Trump
Trudeau
Also
Recognize that guy do
The present
Do you have the disease
X group of people who like that is the real president of this oil-rich country
No
These other people think
Maduro still the president of this contract
What comes
What what ends up happening
Is
Who does the military support
If it is they support
Decided that
I don't know
America doesn't agree
What is that tarnish
Yeah
Potential to be a ridiculous powder-keg
Weird conversation
Maduro is president
He has received a lot of pushback from
Amlo
People are stoked
Then he was like maduro's present
That wasn't a thing that everybody cool
Is is one of those
Things where people have
Very mixed feelings
And I have I have mixed feelings to like a man
Nonce
Has been the leader of the National Assembly
But you're not supposed to win the 2018 election is Alex's presenting
The Carrington that election were Maduro
Prairie falcon
Javier Bertucci
Renaldo a Qui Qui Hannah
And Luis Alejandro rod
If Alex wants to make the argument that Maduro is Win was suspicious
Fine go for it
We can have that conversation agree I do is the rightful winner of that election
Some International Aid organizations
It demonstrates a complete lack of awareness of what's going on cuz he wasn't even in that'll
That's nuts I was I was going to facetiously say
Of course he didn't win that election
He didn't even run
Because I thought that would be a fun joke
Nope
He didn't even run
Okay president of the Nash
National Assembly
Like Alexa
Essentially
Equivalent
Military government
Asthma
President of country
It's possible to live in a world where you have
Your misgivings about how Maduro runs the country
At the same time recognize that this isn't
Democratic cool happening right in front of our eyes
I certainly don't know what the right answer is
But it's not
Immediately recognize the guy who declares himself president is the rightful president of the country
About it
What is electrum are great idea
He can't run in Brazil anymore he might as well become president of Venezuela
Exact extradite Lula Venezuela what happened
I'm not not in a month
We're laughing for like this is very very serious
The deposit bility
Real Siri
Disagreement
Among world powers
He's very palpable
Because Venezuela and their oil resource
Very important
Of not just our world but everyone else
So
The idea of Turkey
Recognize Maduro is the present
And we
Are starting to
Tuesday like
Gaido
Where do you take that
If only
There were
Previous historical example
America recognize
Somebody is
Resident who wasn't democratically-elected
I know I know but this is happening in front of our eyes right
It's terrifying
So Alex
From now for him to
Do you like
Hangman
You hate
Like four
You hate regime-change
You hate
Democratic process
Respect sovereignty of countries
What are you doing
Like it
He has no
He's a manager
Yes no
Yeah this is
I don't like it
Makes me it makes me feel really uncomfortable
When
Somebody
Does it like endisys
This is also true
To always make it clear
Party affiliation
Not
Important
Not in our country not to me for or any
Anything like that so
F****** abandon their principles to watch things you don't like
Getting on board with this
Just because you don't like doesn't mean that this is the right
If you don't have principles and f******
You know like just say I don't
Give a f*** about what it is I put
I'm to believe
And I will do the
Which as we know from all of human history
Always
He's worked out
Great
Like I don't know how better to say go f***
I'm at yeah totally
Making those Arkham
Know that it's not good
Yeah that's going to affect
People in Venezuela
The collateral damage
Ends up
Yeah but gets
It's dreadfully unacceptable
Which is great because the Venezuelan people have been doing so well
So long
And now it's talked about the idea that they're like eating dogs all the time
There's a conversation
We had about
You know Hugo Chavez
Maduro has mismanaged
Resources
Absolutely
There's also a conversation
We had about thanks
That end in that survey
How much is that
Actual
It's not as black-and-white as that wanted to be on that
That ND
Ikea
But you know what like we talked we talked about
Please stop
Government and media talks about
And I can't
Find a moral argument
For them
Do you know what I mean
I think
Yeah
It's hard because ideologically I think
In terms of
Is there a
It's sort of like putting someone in timeout
But if you look at it just from like on paper
More like more like a child
I have is like a parent
Acting
Terribly
I'm putting the child in
A good
Like to wait someone some countries out of line
Cut off the aid
Yeah okay
Freeze accounts
And that's worth
Seems like that's the right thing
Time where
Received that the effect
People that your friends are
Which would be
Gart
The people who are in power
It only ends up hurting
The people beneath
So we should know
From
Experience
That it does
Careers that it would work
Closing borders
It seems like a good argh
Mixers
Feels like the right
To do but we have enough
The experience we have
History to know that it doesn't
Just hurt
The most vulnerable
Forget I agree
I don't know what to do with it I don't know what the appropriate saying
International protocol
What problems
Is this is still developing
And it'll be another day before this episode is out
Right
Be things that we're on our way Road as we're recording right
And so I don't I don't know
The situation
Will develop
The big point is that Alex does Notre
He has no idea
He's commenting
Flippant
Which seems to
Adjectives
It indicates initial support for gaido
Inasmuch as he saying that he should have been the rightful winner of the last election
And
It just it's
It's a pathetic
Position
Like he needs to do better
I suppose needs to prepare in anyway
And just
Without editorial position
To reveal break
So like you're in the middle of your show
This newsbreak
UTSA
Here's the situation
We'll talk about it a little bit later need to get some more details
Or
If you're someone who is starting
The History of Venezuela
Understand what's going on
You can edit or Eli's a little bit
But I was doing
Halfway think his
For solving
Venezuela
Is for America.
To take over men
Target Sports
So we have one more clip Jordan
Post in our group
On Facebook, tell your mother you're brilliant they're asking
Early this morning and I am
Recommend
Gravette don't do it
There been a couple post
Asking if
Anybody has any
Idea is Alex knows about our show
Responses that is always kind of like a
I think he probably does
I think I have some
Reason to be
That he does but
Also
Anything that icing
For any evidence that I have about our show
Could be explained Away by
Through the Somali pirate
It could all be coincidence
There's nothing to say
Rat bite
I think
I don't
I don't think that you live in a world where
There are two people who have been putting out multiple episodes
Critiquing him shoes years at least somebody who works at in
Infowars doesn't know about
I think that's an unrealistic especially with his penchant for finding every single space
Pacific critic about him the deposit
Like somebody wrote a random ass
Block episodes
Operate
There's a lot of possibilities I can't say definitively either way
But
I think this next clip
Made me
Gasp
From that Wednesday the 23rd
Because
It indicates that if he listens to our show
He listens
Early in the morning like before he does his show
Listen to this
Are you sure
I have not heard him talk about the who being big listeners
Except for that episode we that we put out on Wednesday
It happens again
Coincidence
Probably a crazy coincidence nuts man it's
I like
I like living in this fantasy world where he woke up and listen to our shows like
Yeah but who are fans of me I remember that
Are you actually smart
Are you f****** with us
I need to know
Besides
At least one of the members
Of The Who
Is big fat
Actually there's only two members that are still alive
Rodger Daltrey Pete Townshend
Keith Moon
Not a fan
Hundred percent is not as
Alex
In 1974 Pete Townshend said that he was a capitalist but his ideals were communist
In 2012 interview where he said quote
I try to stay away from American politics
Cuz I'm a bit of a neocon
I like the idea of America is the world
Police force
That's not in line with Alex in anyway
Nathan
Communist Tendencies back in the seventies and then he grew into a neocon
Very regular trajectory
For people of that generation
But the idea that he would become a self-avowed neocon
And it expressed that
He's not even
Boxed out
I think that Alex.
Just really talking about how Rodger Daltrey didn't interview
Endorsed
I think that's what he's going
Trump stupid hair
I don't know your house in order
It is not
But I looked for like
Find like some indica
Where is he close to Alex
Legitimately the only thing I can find
Yeah I'm into brakes
Because
Almost
He's dead though
Cookie phone died before that this one was from literally today
I'm just talkin about what
What if it was dead as long as
Turn on the radio
Diving
I remember his dad
I remember when it was
I will tell you this
No cuz really Entwistle
Are we going to count you as a member of The Who
Like to me Keith Moon
Pete Townsend The Who
Adultery and I wasn't go f*** themselves
I understand
You're wrong
Dad
Go to bed much like
JFK jr. absolute
The Cuban on people
That's crazy
I know I don't think we have any
Who's the problem with modern-day stuff
Has no like ability to
To talk about things on the Fly things like a coup in Venezuela
Being so ill-equipped
Discuss them right
Just one thing which
Bundesliga
You just see him doing exactly what you'd expect
You'd expect
Because like before he got the news
Trump it already said that he recognizes guy.
So like no matter what happens
She's going to side with
Gabapentin
Navigate from Covington of course Alex
What is going to
Defend
It's a that everyone is just re-signed
All of it is so
Nonsensical and point
Except
For the piece we're now
I think we understand
How to spray
And I want at least we understand
Whatever the brain damage
Is being fumigated stuff like that
I mean who knows
If it's too vague
Sweet meaningful
This I think is more real
And so I would like
B b conversation on Facebook
If you're if you're there it go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Let us know like I want to know what the audience think about
Does that bring an element
Toothache
Where is ugly
Yeah
I don't know where to land on
Ben and I do
Value
Our listeners
But I would like to
Also Alex
Different Siri
Alex has
Created seven horcruxes
Alright now we know that the way to create a horcrux
Is 2
Because that splits your
Your soul apart
According to
JK Rowling
Just getting robbed
And we know that he is killed in the past
Dogs
Humans
All of these
The split is so left
Too many times
He can't even breathe
Everybody knows
Sleep apnea
Scientific
It's good to know that there was a little bit of
Sleep apnea self lock in there that I that I missed out on
I don't know I just wish I would like peoples into it because I can't do this on my own
I can't find my moral Center
Because if I did I would say we can't talk about it
Open the present
I would just say
Like if left to my own devices
Yeah
No but I don't think
Do you want to be like keep making fun of a
That is not true
I don't like to I don't punch down
I need the conversation really is our Rapunzel
Exact
It's hard to know
If that's the case
We can see what the
The expected impairment
From the condition
And you can fit a lot of it is the part that make
18 episodes of Alex listening to me freaks out and do stuff that's f****** stupid
All just beat
Points of
His
Like the rest of the stuff is all
Boring wrote
He doesn't know
That's not a good show
For us from talking about the stuff
Is almost
Clearly
Deficiency
Glutamine
Excessive
Put ourselves in a box
You know but that that ass
Which is
Outside media
Affect
Whether or not
Has a heart attack
Tomorrow
And six months from now he's back
You can clearly see that the heart attack
But he still has 10 million viewers a night
I honestly don't think that measures into my
Where I'm coming from
Is just
Human level
Yeah
And maybe it's because like I said
Think that a large part of
Where I'm coming from my hyper
Comes from
When I was in college
Professor
I remember yeah
And he'd show videos
Class
In the like mid-80
He was just
Everything was totally
Define
Lecture
Was just
He couldn't communicate
Anymore because
That stroke and there were people in that class that would laugh at him
Fond of him as a lecturer
Add ideas
I get that he's bad at doing his job
Which is
To give a lecture
Cause of
Yeah
And I always got very very mad
People who didn't
Understand that
Prices
I look at it
Look at Alex in the same way
I look at this like
Whenever we talk about these hypothetical brain damage
Which type thing
They haven't been is conch
Like the idea of you
Express
Sleep sitting up
CPAP machine
Don't work
Yeah whatever
We need surgery
What is thick ass neck
I mean
I don't know I don't want this out
Moral relativism is fine
It interested
We're just going to keep
Keep expressing that we don't know
Yeah you know it's just a ride
Keep coming back
Who knows
Sound off
Let us know what you
I value your in
Until then
Will be back
Next
Yes we will website.com
Natural
Yep bro
Facebook present
I relapsed a brand
That's correct
But
You are listening and you'd like a butt
Please email knowledge fight
At gmail.com
And I'll send your address
We are almost out of
If you want to buy it
So I'm
Well there's your house
Your girlfriend holyshit
Seems like he's in
Brexit
Not thrilled to sex
You just picked out of everybody who's ever lived Earth on Rockstar life probably kill somebody
I don't know I've never heard any evidence
But Rodger Daltrey is killed by
That he has technically probably killed
Alexandra Thurston color