Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Yeah Jordan what was the last time
You saw somebody
Truly astonishing
I saw that too gymnast
Gymnastics
In the floor routine that was going around
On Twitter
Remember to the young lady's name but that was
Outstandingly good she's the one that was like 13 years old
Call CLA
Holy s*** it's insane the people's bodies
I can do that
Then I guess I'm a recording is on Sunday but last night I watched at NXT takeover Phoenix
Ricochet ricochet
Phoenix is alright alright
There's a wrestler Ricochet amazing flips like he could jump over stuff
Physically
Tate's bake shop
Gyros and of course everyone knows that that is already
And that is what I started playing Hyrule warriors on the switch
Rodger Stone got arrested on Friday you got indicted
People are clamoring for our take on it
And so we will get to that
Before we get to that
To give a shout out
Show possible
Nice people
Ewok
First I'd like to carry
You are now a policy wonk
Las Animas
Terrible
You are now policy
You are now a policy wonk
I don't know
Harley
You are a founding member of the John Birch Society or just anybody else
Amerigroup
Quick nut button
The sports show
Please do
Like I said
Rodger Stone
Is that
He got indicted
And being Rodger Stone
His primary brand is basically being a dick
So no one's really going to go soft on him
He's most famous for our the movie get me Rodger Stone
Fastest time in the barrel is coming
Prior to the John podesta emails being
So
Things that are so f****** easy
For people to make headlines about it's just a sea of people doing like
Mother said get me Rodger stone or time in the
That's terrible
On himself
Itaki
Becoming the recipient
I wish people be a little more creative but on another level I kind of enjoy it
He has to just be thinking like
Why is everybody being so mean to me
I think I'm a nice guy
You know what you can't even make a 40-year career out of f****** people over without eventually
Happened to deal with
That's bulshit nonsense in a global
To get with this information but I guess I should probably just assume that everybody doesn't know any
We're going to be going over
Friday's episode of Alex Jones Show
What would that have been
25th
25th 2019
It's in the immediate aftermath of Rodger getting arrested and posting bail
You got arrested at
Like 6 in the morning
I believe
FBI agents
Which I think is a good idea
I think the based on the things that he's up to and the other contacts that he has I would consider him
A flight risk for sure
You're going to want to surprise that's what I
I wouldn't I wouldn't take any chances
Took him away
Pretty soon after that him and his lawyers were able to negotiate bail
He posted a
$50,000 Bond
YouMail free
To go to New York
Florida
DC in Florida
That's correct.
You could have got Austin on that list
I need it and I think that tells you something
Infowars
Even if you make that argument there nothing
DC or New York City to close to Canada
Close to any of these arguments would hold water if Rodger Stone wanted to he could have gotten
And I think that's partially
Because
Open large
Addicted
In many ways
Now that he's actually been indicted realizes Alex
Can't really help him
Outside of
Tricking his listeners into giving him money
That's the only thing I can help
His problems are much bigger than Alex can help with now
And so it's not a priority for him
He's going to use the
Infowars Army
Or whatever for whatever
But he's not going to
He's not going to be Rodger Stone anymore
So
Really boring really fat
And he'll direct his attention on places where like Trump actually
Is listening
Tucker Carlson on Fox and Friends
Like helping Alex
The troops for their imaginary apocalyptic battle for coming
To the forest as well
There is a great moment in the in his press conference
We don't have
An interviewer asks
Have you asked
Rogers responses Park
I don't think he was trying to be funny but it's hilarious
Here we go let's go let's go
We'll get through it the best we can
We're going to be going over this indictment here bit by bit as we go through the episode
Unspeakable
Six-count indictment
Against Rodger Stone on Friday
Count to 36 are all lies
Rodger told the house intelligence committee
Account one is an obstruction charge
Regarding some message
That Rodger sent critico is supposed intermediary with Julian Assange
Reading over this indictment one gets a very strong sense that Rodger is completely f*****
The obstruction charge
To carry a 20-year sentence
Each charge of lying to Congress could be up to five years
But I don't mean that Rogers f***
Because that's a total of fifty years you could look
Be looking at
Which is
I mean he's f***** because of the in
Information that's laid out in the document
And more importantly
The information that is conspicuous in a
Absence
The text messages of emails that are referenced
Mostly but not all correspondences that had already come to light in some manner or another
Summer messages that came out Windsor on Coursey got in trouble like a month or two ago
Somewhere reported on vacuum
2018 when Randy credico
Investigator
But there are a few pieces of information in the
Take me to bring it all together
Clearly demonstrate that Rodger Stone
Intentionally misled the house until
Maybe
And gives a strong indication as to why
There's no fat in that.
Which I think is
Interesting point
Mother clearly has so many more emails and texts
Then the ones referenced in this
Is because there is enough
Rodger Stone to be charged with a crime
Have some of the other correspondences
Is may contain information related to other crimes
Particularly the correspondence
3 Rodger in Jerome Court
I could be wrong but that's my heart
Either way Rogers f***
Because this indictment lays out a really open and shut case
Did Rodger is
Super guilty of the crime scene
Another way he's f*****
Is that prisoner's dilemma
The two of them know a lot of dirt on each other and are both really bad people
Each of them knows that
The other is a threat
Typically you never want to be in a prisoner's dilemma with someone who you know is untrustworthy
And there are few people are few people in town who are less trustworthy than Paul manafort
And Rodger cell
Sodexo
Just a broad glimpse
Right what's going on
In order to discuss this indictment in its proper context
I need to give
You in the listeners
A little backstory
Flush out somebody aspect
And other
Some of these aspects of the story that other non Infowars Focus
Outlets might've
So
Alex Jones isn't the only person in our story who has a radio show
Or more accurately
On August 15th 2016 Genesis communication
Network distributed a press release
Rodger Stone every Saturday
The show was short-lived on GCI which isn't suspicious at all
I say
Field by World crisis radio host by Webster
The former Infowars Gaston
Early 2016 when he realized the drop was an aspiring fashion
Very bizarrely the co-host of Rodger Stones show Stone Cold Truth
Is a comedian named Travis Irvine
Definitely hung out with multiple times
I've done shows with Travis
And at no point could I have possibly imagined that he would end up being the co-host
Rodger Stone radio show world is very weird
Weird is I know that he was a Libertarian Dewdney ran for mayor of his
His child
I knew that but I imagine he was this far
Teaming up with Rodger Stone four radio show
If somebody gave me that offer
I would
To think about it hard because
F****** hilarious
I agree with
Cupid also you got to consider the idea might end up
Play something something you don't realize you're getting
Involved
Anytime you agree to a project with Rodger Stone you know it comes with the possibility of a stoop
Calculus
Either way
Number of this episode
The show
Travis easy
Involved with Rodger Stone
But the show it really seems like Rodger just has him there
Do use a sort of a millennial stew
Kind of thing
I don't I don't know I don't want to assume that they're related
You're back early is
Anything like that but
It's really f***** up I think he's a really nice guy
Rodger releases first episode on August 20th
Ventura
I listen to a bunch of episodes
And way more
Centration
Wall2wall Trump campaigning
Define whatever you'd like to show itself is like
It almost is like trying to take Alex Jones and make it my PR
That's the kind of more like irresponsible with their report
August 3rd episode
From September 3rd 2016
Rodger interview with Randy credico
Inconsequential much just talk about how Rodger and Randy sported some
Reform measures
That's the point
The only thing that really stands out to me
Is how Rodger introduced
Decredico on this episode
Incredible
Metaphysics
From the dead
A man who
Swore I would never
I lived
Renzi's
You never speak to Randy credico again
This is a piece of the story that almost every single report that I've seen fails to discuss
This is important
This is a very big story
And every articles that I've read
Has basically just said
Rodger Stone had a falling-out mobile
No one has pulled that thread or at least no one seemed
I'm sure somebody has most haven't seen that article
Majorities articles
Leave that question open and I am
The type of person is very curious I want understand why why the f*** did these two people who are deeply involved
He said situation about espionage
It all goes back to 2007
Note imagine that Randy was actually the one who didn't want to talk to Rodger
Back in 2007 Rodger was working for the New York State Senate Majority Leader
Bruno
Who is probably most memorable for being Governor Eliot Spitzer
Political differences between a result of Bruno being suspected
The corruption
The track is travel records
In terms of expenses
Flights
Ultimately this was a misuse of State resources and Bruno's cleared of wrongdoing in terms of his traveling
In 2009 he was convicted on two counts of what is honest Services fraud
Failed to disclose conflicts of interest
Involving
$440,000 in Consulting fees
From a businessman he was friends with
Which were alleged to be bribed
He was sentenced to two years in prison but his legal problems were solved by a deus ex machina
When the Supreme Court ruled in 2010
It honest Services fraud statute
The statute regarding
And that's his convictions were overturned
Any walks for
Legally speaking Bruno is plain but I refuse to accept the $440,000
From a friend who is businessman
That would be like
Let er Rip
Either way Rodger work for Joseph Bruno the time breaking in a salary of $20,000
And Eliot Spitzer was breathing down his bosses in it
F****** New York State politics man it is a wreck
Breathing
Rodger Stone went to work trying and succeeding in taking down Elliott
First he sent the FBI letter on November 19th
Tipping them off about Spitzer's habit of employment
This to me seems like a flagrant Act of parkour
Rodger stone is a noted sexual Liberty and a libertarian
I thought you shouldn't be opposed to sex workers being a legal or punished
That's a Bedrock of principle
Like in terms of libertarianism
I've heard him say before that he believes that button past it analyzed
Don't matter when you're at
He's a ratfuck of course that's what matters what do you think what you're doing is
Directly opposed
This wasn't the only thing that Rodger didn't is Attack on Eliot Spitzer
Previous destination to the FBI
At about 10 p.m. on August 6th called Eliot Spitzer's father Bernard
I proceeded to threaten legal action
Bernard Spitzer had nothing to do with Rogers political work
He called him out of pure ugliness and mallet
As we listen to this call this voicemail
Remember the call
Is Eliot Spitzer's eighty-three-year-old father
Who at the time was suffering from Parker
Bernard
You will be
Testified before the Senate
Committee on investigate
Campaign
Send it
Sergeant at Arms
You resisted
Tina you will be rent
Is it brought the Alban
It's not a god
Your phony
Psycho
You got it
Folding lounger back
Ketchup
You will be
Fruit
The fact that you're trying to pass
Illogical liar
Sarpinos
Their number of flourishes in the vocal pattern
F****** Rodger to
I wrote that script
Flip the script in the aftermath of this called being released Bruno ask Rodger to Steph which Rodger agreed to
Proceeded to tell anyone who is this
First Rodger said flatly that he makes
The call
It wasn't me
He was Shaggy in it
Weather
Up up
Showed evidence
Call Rogers Park
With information on the table Rodger
Anyone could have broken into his apartment and made the call but also no concern about his apartment being broken into
He claimed that he was at a live performance of frost Nixon that nights
Governor Spitzer
It shows you what Hubris in lying
New York Magazine
On August 6th to him
Old man lying in Huber
Oh my God demonstrated his own actions is amazing
Crazy is a nut
Nowhere to turn
For no reason left a threatening message
Like leaving a threatening message on an old man's phone
That's not the kind of dirty trickster image
Do you like 2% of self is B
Brilliant kind of guy
Doing those sorts of stunts
Not be pointless Petty and just abusive for the sake of being abusive store
That's the ladder yourself publicly
As the as the prior
Because you need that
You need that
It's exactly what you've always responded to the Loki trickster God
A monster he's a horrible person who's made almost all of his money throughout his career
If you look like
Manafort Stone and black
Who they worked for
It is a who's who who dated work with a lot of murderous
Dictators
In their in their rank
I know you look at the three of them
And then that water got involved with the f****** Willie Horton
Add
Slimy
Comical bad person that he likes
Resent because it is
It's easier for him to do his business
I feel like as far as
Representing
That's just
More like knowing people
Because
You is like
The job is open
You have to have
0 morality in order
Tijera
People are clamoring
But the money is Big Nicholas
Psycho
From his great hit
Mobutu Seko
Zaire
Oh boy
Quote presided over the worst human-rights conditions in a
Bouquet
Publican
Terrorized
Beveled at least 5 billion dollars
From his own country
Rogers
I meant of course another one it is
His great clients
Yeah
What sort of business is involved
Rigid lights
Define how's it going to get away with this one
With no other options
Rodger Stone blamed Randy credico
The Washington Post relates Rogers rationale
You've been on Letterman
He doesn't incredible
So his argument
Now as I understand
Broke into his apartment
Call to Bernard
Perfect
Right under the auspices of the people trying to
To be at this point for Rogers version of Troy
Right
So he goes on to say the credit goes done an impression of him in the past
That's Rodger Style
You always include a personal attack
They've somehow meant to invalidate the person
You could be
Avoid that refutes your point
Yeah
It's it's very consistent throughout his career
You hear it over and over again his appearances on Infowars even the way he attacked
People who could provide criticism
So funny
That's hilarious
I'm absolutely denying
Years
In order for Rodger story to work as you pointed out Pro Spencer force does it have two enlisted credico
Credit Karma
Is Rodger to lie about his alibi
Rodger
He blamed Randy credico
And this is why Rodger
I thought they would never see
Speak again
There's a good chance
But they wouldn't
But they did
Because in 2016 Rodger once again
Patsy
That's important
On September 3rd 2016
Rogers involvement
Communicating with a song
Was already well underway
According to Rogers indictment by June or July 26
Campaign officials
I'm not entirely sure if that's confirmed
Cuz there's multiple references to Trump officials not specified
Same Pride person
They're not saying person
Campaign official
So it's unclear being able to track whether it's all the same
So you've already telling
Wikileaks documents about Hillary
On June 22nd Wikileaks released the DNC emails
And 3 Days Later Rodger email Jerome corsi and told him to quote Assange at the Ecuadorian Embassy
And get the pending email
Course he forwarded the email that Rodger had sent him to Ted Malik
Doing seeing pop up a time or two on Infowars in the past
He's famous for the Declaration yeah he might as well be called Ted Molokai
He's a bit of a fraud himself week we've gone over him
He's not really all that important
He's not named in this
He's not like a person one two or three
Either the document
He's not a Target
Maybe he's cooperating
So
Command is delivered to Coursey doesn't imply this is an unreasonable thing
He doesn't tell him to try to get to a saint
Get in touch with them
By August 2nd 2016 emailing Rodger with suggestion
The next right-wing coordinated attack on Hillary was going
Quotes would not hurt to start suggesting HRC old memory bad has stroke
Percy also told Rodger that he expected next batch of emails that have to do with the Clinton Foundation
Almost immediately Rodger began telling everyone that he's spoken to us
And the next documents would likely be about the foundation
Almost as if he was repeating Annabella showing the things course he told him
Rodger we continue claiming that he had spoken with WikiLeaks
Until Wikileaks put out a statement in mid August 2nd not communicated with him
So his story changed to have him having talked to them
On August 23rd 2016 Rodger was a guest on Randy
Criticos radio show
Echo ask Rodger about how Rodger
In that interview Rodger told Randy credico quote
We meeting him and Assange
Mutual friend someone we both Trust
And therefore I'm a recipient of
A pretty good information
The date of this interview is important
Because it predates Randy credico ever speaking
Julian Assange
The first time that you were in contact with 12 sides with a guest on cryptos radio show
Rogers Communication through intermediaries or not
Predates the possibility
Credit
Jerome corsi with the person who's coordinating with Rodger on
Misprint blame course
The connector
It's under the bus
Too many questions
Kernel of an idea that Rodger
Credico
Accorsi was
This is why would Rodger testified in front of the house intelligence
He said his intermediary with credit and never brought up Jerome corsi
Because he needed that to be the perception
By November 2017
We claim the credit go with his gobert
And unsurprisingly credico got a request from the house complete
Come testify
He texted Rodger about it and Rodger replied with a quote from Richard Nixon
Quote Stonewall
Plead the fifth anything to save the plan
This is a paraphrasing over
This is a former Attorney General on March 20th
Second Life
Approximately 11 months
For he would be formally impeached
Much like Nixon Rodger was stupid enough to say something like that
In a manner that would be
Record it
On November 28th 2017 credico was subpoenaed by the committee
And he told Rodger about it
Rodger
Is later he would run Jerome corsi and ask him to start writing so articles
About credit card
Rodger sent but is Patsy wasn't cooperating
So he planned
Republic scapegoating
But he was going to
Initiate that plan
Corsi reply to his request by saying quote
Why not wait to see what he does
You might be defending yourself too much
Raising new questions that will fuel new inquiry
This may be a time to say less not more
Corsi the wisest person in this store
Because he's so boring a douche I think that we
Maybe underestimate how like involved in Shazam
So his go-between
How is course
Incontact
He might also be making all that up
I don't know but also could be through
Garage door
New London
I mean until we know more
Think that
Rodger
Is lying to cover this up
I don't know what course he's game
He could be making all of it up himself and funneling it to Rodger Rodger thinks it's coming
Massage
Course he could actually be in touch with a dog
Subway
It it becomes
Huge disaster for him
If corsi's in
So
Is after 10
Nixon
Quote
2 days later on November 30th
He reaches out to Jerome corsi and tells him to start writing about credit
On November 30th 2017 Rodger Stone released
On the website
Where he exposed
Randy credico
There's no byline on the story may or may not have written it
Either way the editorial Tone It Infowars flowery towards credico for long and behind-the-scenes
Manipulation
Strategy
Rodger seppi's complimentary things 42
In his statement about credit
To going along with him and his
We the fifth plan
Credit Karma
It's mostly it's a public statement on the website but it's also a message
Should you directly to the website
Use the compliments later to inflict
Further guilt
Emailing him everything I said publicly about you has been complimentary yet you continue to act like nunberg
Referencing Sam nunberg the guy who got drunk all over TV
So the next day after that article
December 1st Rodger Texan Credit Co and told him to do a Frank pentangeli
Referencing the character in Godfather
But also knows what the compression
Committee wants to
No
This is a really damning referee
The jelly was setup by Corleone
I was being threatened into not testifying
Also Frank does testified then recant after he's been threatened
He's threatened his family will be safe
So he does
I don't know about credico but I would not be quick to do a Frank had someone who like
Obviously
Like I committed a crime
Please help me cover
You bet
What an idiot Randy credico replies Rodger that Rodger needs to amend his testimony before
For December 50
The day he was scheduled to testify
I was doing this because by this point
You figured out that you couldn't be Rogers gobert
Considering
Massage when Rodger was going around immediate early August
Claiming that he communicated with Wiki Lee
He knew that his testimony would contradict Rogers
And was extending a very unnecessary Curtis
It's unclear what happened between December 1st and December 12th
Put on the 12 critico told the committee that he would assert his Fifth Amendment right
If you was forced to testify
Based on information is public I can't say what happened there
But it's really hard not to
Indictment doesn't include any interactions between those dates
Is very telling
I know legal scholar but I'm positive that Mueller has those interactions
You can make your own
Conclusions about why they're not at me
Kill you
I will kill you
Rogers emailing with Trump
Ministration of campaign
You have any news about a wikileak
And he says yes let's go on WhatsApp
Time
That time Rodger was communicating with him
Encrypted
Horrible just over unprotected
So whatever whatever the case I'm not entirely sure what all the details are I think some of that will come out as time goes on
For now
Vague threat
By the end of December credico
Thought
What time here is interesting because by that Point Fortin Rick Gates have been indicted
Michael Flynn to just plead guilty to cut it
If you're Randy credico you're seeing all these people going down mixed up with the guy who knows all of them
Got to feel weird
You're being vaguely threatened by the guy who knows all of them
And you know the guy who
Who knows all that was also one of their lobbying partners
That would not be a pleasant position
Now
I don't want to I don't want to see I don't want
Who am I
Is it the guy who I know is guilty
Because he texts
Guilty
Or
Who is
Proving that a bunch of other people are guilty
So critical told Rodger that he wasn't going to let Rogers wise about him
Began making video appearances to clear his name and tell his side of the story
Turn on April 9th 2018 Rodger email credit go to tell him
He also threatened
Mu
Just probably records The Killing
Dog
That's my dog you're holding onto and then
I'm so ready Let's Get It On prepared c*********
Right back
Humor is all over again
Which is a week tonight
Most probably being in there I'm not
I don't I'm not interested somebody broke into my apartment
Medrite they sent an email Friday to email to self
And perhaps my favorite part of the story when mother emailed back in May
They reached out for comment from Rodger
Paragraphs
Pure f******
Can gold
In a text message to Mother Jones
Credico
Stop making a threat
It contends the critical reciting his words out of context
He told me he had terminal prostate cancer Stone rights it was such a response to that we talked about it to do was pick 4
Credico says
Chicken Rogers is being like real tuck in Macon
Everything up
Rogers trying to threaten credit
Completing the stamp
Because you knew that if credico Rodger testimony was going to be contradicted
No contradictions
Timeline would fall apart in Jerome corsi would come into play something Rodger never wanted to happen
The cover-up corsi's involvement in all this
Interpretation to make sure those lies weren't realize
Turn the charging document
He's dead to right on there it's
A open and shut case
The Chrome
Plated
But here's the important thing to realize why I told you this long-ass story
Compulsive behaviors naturally Trend towards forming a pattern
Serial killer start to develop routine behaviors and habitual Liars due to
Given the information present it would be a stretch
Me to say that Rodger stone is guilty of deeper involvement
The DMC in
But the dissemination bacterial
But his behavior deeply suggest to me that he is
Is a response to early suggestions that he was involved in any of this stuff
Exact path that his denials of being the one who harassed Eliot Spitzer
First step tonight expressively
Live Match
3rd step keep lying until people don't believe you anymore
4th step blame Brandy
Be credico
If you take out of the equation this is also the exact pattern that Rodger followed when he was forced to step down from a position in the night
Africans accused of posting classified ad looking for people to swing with him and his wife
Deny lie
Keep lying
Blame someone else
An unnamed domestic
Employee you said had a drug problem
Just like you did with credit go in 2017
We all learn from our experiences as human
I generally speaking repeat successful Behavior
In the case of the 2016 campaign and propaganda campaign surrounding it
Rodger replayed them out of trouble
In 1996 2007 and undoubtedly a ton of other time that we're not aware of
In this case though it seems like the underlying crime was too big
Where is Patsy just to laugh it off
Right
That is kind of what I feel about the endive
What is that
What does in rapture
With your with your room storyteller
People are making
And some of it has to do with
I don't know
Lack of awareness
Curiosity perhaps in some reporting
And then some of it is
Is just like
I understand that I'm
Connect
Maybe can't be proven
Leave there
You know the patterns of behavior are definitely there
If you walked me into a quart I probably couldn't make this argument right illegal
Inspection
But in terms of how I
Look what's the most likely scenario
I feel very confident
That this is
And that's not to say that Rodger absolutely was
In touch with
Russian intelligence or anything like that
The way he acted when he started coming up
That he believes he might have
Right that's the I think that's as far as I'm willing
These guys
I have got to
They finally have to realize the worst thing that
To them with Trump winning
The presidential
Nobody
They were just like phuc yea
Show off my
Play skills
And then use the use that
Showing off
Spell those
To somebody else feels like the classic like
Builder
In order to Parlay
That's what they were real
Italy Italy to tons
Contract
Yeah so I don't
I don't know I think it's going to be interesting to see how this plays out
Your articles are starting to come out about Rodger
Same like
Look
I know something I'll talk to mother
It's already indications that he's like
Get out of this
Pirate
I realize that I'm f*****
Alex
Trump
A little extra because there's another important piece to
To consider and that is nothing in that indictment relies on credit or even
It is basically
Hayirli made up
Of these documents
The emails
The the
And stuff like that
If there's no like you said he said about this
It's entirely like
We can show
Is this you guys were having this conversation
Your testimony
Contradict
Therefore
You lied to Congress
Hawaiian stuff I know exactly
It it it's telling I'm sure Rodger lied about more stuff
In his testimony
Fetzer
To cover up corsi's
Involved
I think that you can probably end up
Plead is public case
That I just didn't remember or whatever
The witness intimidation
That is a hundred percent
Borne out by those
Equal standard
And
Like
Aisha
If he doesn't cut a deal like I don't I can't imagine
The way he's carried himself throughout this entire like less
Two-and-a-half years or so
Yelling about Miller everyday on the radio saying that he's guilty
Reason people would show
They were at least he wasn't
Being an a******
While they were investigating
Stone is
Everybody
I hate them
Extend the only reason that
Would get off
If Trump
Pardon
And the only reason
Is if he knew that right
Rodger Stone
And the only reason that
I know that we kind of have
Slightly
Feelings about whether or not
Pardon
Rodger
Everything is up for grabs nowadays
If you were to do that it would be
Definitely
Obstruction of justice
Oh yeah
Twitter
This would be like
Directly
Pardoning someone who tried
To derail and investigate
I don't know
And nobody would care
Because the right-wing is like
Guess what we're going to survive this
We've we've survived
So much in the past
2 years it is Non-Stop
All of the elite
Enough for us to not get away with
We got the indictment stuff
I think we were pretty
Decent on what's going on with that where
That comes from and all that stuff
January
25th
Alex is immediate response
His best buddy
The guy tells him every
Narrative
Rodger Stone
Hear it
Have you ever
I just never told
11 is time
Rodger got arrested
Its 6 or so a few hours
Assuming he was awake I've no idea
Harrison Smith
Underling
Infowars
He's the guy who found those antifa Soros documents on 4chan to make a big deal out of it
Brilliant researcher terrible on air 280
Heart attack
For a while
It was
Like I watched it
Wow
How is Alex not bum-rushed
The studio
We are in a crisis
Stop
Anything
Eddie told Joe Biggs backend broken through the wall like
Yeah I mean it just goes to show how shallow his
End of the day when you f****** spin artist in there
You got Harrison Smith
Good luck ironically the only person who should have been in there that wasn't Alex is Rochester
I like to Harrison Tomatoes trying to come
Compare the treatment of
Rodger
Two likes Olsen eaten in
Teleprompter
He tries to stay the gulag archipelago
Trips over the word
It's clear that he has no idea what the words are as reading
Embarrassing
It's so bad
And so I was
Expecting like Alex
You got to right the ship
His own broadcast like
Harrison Smith
Performance somewhat
The level of talent is so glaring
That guy is a showstopper
I give it two days before they start comparing Rodger to Martin Luther King
The letters from the Birmingham Jail
Start the show
And like I said
Kind of subdued
There's a little bit of like a
Almost focused energy
A little bit
It doesn't last
Start
Pneumonia
Kiel Alex's whole things
At the beginning of the show
I think he's aware
How many f******
Can people are going to tune in to his show to see what the f*** freaked out that
Excessive traffic coming to his website
And so all he wants to do
Is make sure that everybody knows
He's about to talk to Rodger Stone was just gotten out of jail on bail
Exclusive
And he's Furious
That more media Outlets aren't saying
Infowars has the exclusive to start off this year
Ladies and gentlemen dishes World exclusive
Criminal Rodger stone with SWAT
Images
Chablis steak theater by the
Politicized arm of the deep state
Pre-dawn raid the scene and horses
For the reporter line on TV
Your cat
Saying that
Rodger Stone
Tamara
He said I can just feel it I can see it all all the preparation everything and he sent me a text message saying
Rodger Stone exclusively this is the first interview
Stop now.
You got the
Morning Show
Great we start
Not into this interview
He is he's not Rodger Stone
The character that we've come to know
Calling Adam Schiff a c*********
Screaming about how everybody
I think reality has set in and lying is not so fun for him anymore
Because
He has consequences in front of him used to that what he's really not used to is being handcuffed
To his hand and
Into a courtroom a little bit later
Change little bit of how you're going to do business real real quick
World exclusive
And
Spoiler alert this is almost exactly the same
Ends up going out in front of the courthouse
That is out there
They're so cute
Alex's
Exclusive
Where should we start with how you were able to predict this last night of the phone what happened this morning
Your house
I want to dress this really
He predicted this is not that surprising
Recently mother requested his testimony from the house
He knew he'd lied
If the investigator is requesting those documents that means
Did they have reason to believe
This will provide
So him being like they're coming
Of course they're coming Rodger
Predicted
Pre-dawn raid
What time does
Pacification for the
Make it to my
Play One More Day
Once you were in jail then what unfolded after that
Charges relate to Russian collusion
And I actually think
That's worse for Rodger was like
Collusion at all
Which means they're charged
Pink stone with some
In order to make
Conviction
Which means when they do charge somebody with
They've got that
Conviction
Already there
So they can use
Possible
My feeling about it
Conspicuous
Yeah and not
It has nothing to do with this
But he does just on a secondary level
So anyway
Or any other illegal act
2016 election
Prepare to die
That's not true
Unintentional
You don't accidentally
Just forget the person that was actually Jerome corsi
And I'm going to uniform
Jerome corsi out of this whole thing
I don't know I understand he probably thinks of his defenses going to work
But I
As an external Observer
I think it's
Yeah this is very Hollow when you start your interview with what essentially amounts
Haha
Bad day
You might have been able to tell In that clip their Rogers having a little bit of phony
He's having some troubles with technology
Please describe what happened because your phone's breaking up with you said 29
29 FBI agents
Automatic weapons
Sure
17 vehicles in the Jean
They terrorized my wife and my dog
2 mi
Do you notice I was just describing what I like
The result of his actions
Coincidence
Depriving is exactly
People with guns
Of course
Bunch cars
Of course this is a high-profile Target
Who is involved
Something pretty messy
Not that you would expect a shootout to happen or anything like that
That's cuz you're like
Is easy
If he gets anywhere near that fireplace
Going to spin around
To be outside you can be able to write
They searched my house
Yes is reasonable suspicion
Further Evidence Fair
So like the other stuff is like
He is involved with an outlet that
Routinely
Demonizes black use their killed by police snow like I don't care
The next
Alex
But you're not black
It's
Roger's coming from is
Do you know who I am there's that sort of feel to it
Whatever
If it's necklet what we hear is
Is that
Alex
Rogers Prescott
Talk about how awesome
But you still only
You got to talk to him before the press conference
Ladies and gentlemen hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of reporters
Exclusively Global explosion
He goes on to later say it's bigger than OJ's press conference
A couple points on neck
Official event and it was indoors in a small Ballroom
Of course there's more people outside
The Florida courthouse
Where do torious process
Of course in Florida I would drive a couple hours
Great
So I can only imagine the tons of people like hell yeah
I like is actually like
Most of them think this is newsworthy or
Bigger than o.j.
Just from a standpoint
Treasure
Something that I would like on my phone video of him
With shackles on like I would watch that anytime
Sad-eyed watch that be like
We got him
Something gratifying
About that when I woke up
This news is broken
It was a tragedy
I've been in the middle of trying to work on a very in-depth
Wednesday episode 4
I was getting it already
University
Now you throwing me off course I got to do this Rogers Township
Life progresses at its own pace and
Follow it
Exclusive
He's putting off all those people out there to talk to us
Cuz we're amazing
And here Rodger just gives him what I would describe as a defense
And I don't believe
Play cheats for statements to the car
Maria
Today
Because
The go-between
This is this is journalism
Only if you're bluffing
About what the
Dightman's actually says
Alex's
But
This indicates to me that this is the direction
Rodger trying to go with his defense
And I think it's not the right
I don't know what the right defense it's not my responsibility
Come up with it
Is very soft
Here's my pic
Leave a voicemail on
Every senators
I think that's not a bad idea
Kill the dogs
Beginning of something
At Alex's
In the entire world
To believe that he
Concerned about his own well-being
Is the aftermath of Rodger getting indicted
Not just his own well-being
One of his family members
Uno
Washington Post
When does the special counsel
Cuz I wanted to work here
Fathers
Give me support
They know we got elected
Little bit of Huber's there too
I don't play I haven't found it I can't find any
Like legitimate
Sources talking about how
David Jones
Is going down
The
Hrh Infowars
Is getting together and then
Amlo has to be like Caravan of white people coming to the Border we're going to have to build
It's interesting here because this is one narrative that I'm not going to be able to release
Fully tell you what's going on
But
Article
About course
View payments
And we'll see I think this is a story that's going to develop a little bit over time
Especially contract
I don't think there's actually a really
Reasonable argument
He made that went course he went
Deep down the qanon hole
I would fire tattoo I don't know there's a d
You just got
Ani and Alex did fire him
There's a chance that Rodger and corsi we're both pulling the wool over Alex's eyes
In terms of their
Clearly documented
Interaction
So really really
Interesting
Especially in the context
Alex
He told Rodger Stone
Go get me Wiki
Glen Rogers
We've got recalled
S*** from this Greenwich time article
Corsi perhaps
Best known for promoting the false idea that former President Barack Obama was not born in the United States
Has released internal special counsel.
Alleged deal offers and published
Outlining his account of interactions
With his one-time Ally
The longtime Trump advisor Rodger Stone
Subject of intense scrutiny
In the Mueller probe
Is $15,000 a month in payments from Infowars
Special counsel investigation
As a deep state
Proceed to sign to topple President Trump
Infowars
Confirm that these payments
Continue for the past 6 months
Hi severance
Sincerity lost lost
As the websites Washington bureau chief
A job that stone helped arrange
According to both Stone and Coursey
The revelation of courses arrangement
Afraid relationship
Between course again Stone
And how the on-again-off-again light
America's foremost
Conspiracy theorist
Has drawn the attention of mothers invest
When we talk about
Alex
Bureau
Like the whole thing with stone saying we need to have him
Or maybe Alex. We need to get a present in Washington and Coursey was the one stone recommended instead of
For the job
Also interesting so much money
That's so much money
Journalist get paid like a dollar every week
Yeah I know yeah
Over 100,000
Course he would have been pulling in just from Infowars anyone on nonsense
He's f******
Cannot keep it on the Shelf
Got a copy Mike cernovich
It was free
I got
Incase
If they call something later
I'll let you know
Percy said in an interview that he doesn't remember being asked by Mueller's investigators about those payments
After 40 hours of questioning over several days
Forgotten
Quote it's pretty far-fetched course
C7osure
Quiet
I'm the guy was talk to the most I have been hushed
About anything
So
Last week from Alex Jones
Does father
That the payments would stop
According to a legal complaint
Defiled this week
So
It's unclear whether or not
He was fired in June
And paid the remainder of a one-year contract to end of this month
Is Infowars paid already been scheduled to end
This month
Infowars
Ernie Mark run.
So it's unclear I could believe either version of the story quite frankly
I know the course he's up to some s*** but that doesn't prove much money right
Be a situation where it's like
F*** it.
Raking it in
Is this past couple of years for him
I must he must have bought
Six boats out of all the bulshit
I know I wish I was representing
Quote stonecore seeing Alex Jones all said that the
Received after leaving or not related to corsi's role in the mall
Pro
Whining about being broke down
Course he declined to comment on Stones character
Position of his Finance
So
You know it's faces
Reels back
Conforth
Put a little away
Put a little bit of
That's just
Now that's just good
So it's
Interesting to me cuz this article has
Some stuff that I don't know
If I was
Aware of
Rodger
Corsi coming together
I didn't realize this and I'm not sure if this is exactly true or if it's a public story but
Here from this Greenwich time article
Conspiracy theorist
Conservative pose the question to him in 2011
Who's this guy Jerome corsi
What's don't ask why you wanted to know about corsi Trump responded I've been talkin
Corset recently published a book titled where's the birth certificate the case that Barack Obama is not eligible
3 presidents
Trump became the most public Ardent supporter of course he's a public appearances
Obama to provide more proof
That is burnt
Goes on to say
Corsi's relations
Continued after Trump's Victor
Don't suggest that they both go to work
Infowars
Of course he said in an interview
Told the post the course he was one of 15 people to Stone recommended
This possible
Of the new Washington Bureau for the
Seaside
So
Like I said I don't know
Interesting glimpses into like the version of the story that people are presenting but I can't
The truth out about this
I don't know what those paint
That's word to Coursey
I can't claim to
It's an interesting thing that I think will develop as the two of them start
S******* all over each other and that course he's indicated that he's willing to work with the probe
Mueller probe this could get really ugly we might learn a lot more in the
Future
And everyone's a liar
So for now we have to put a pin in the
Corsi payments Meredith
Although it is something I'm very
So this is
This is this is like a Tarantino
Standoff like every one of them has a gun pointed at each other's had and they're both are all going to end up
Political
Text with Alex is still trying to do his world exclusive
Interviewed Rodger
He throws it
And then
To the real world right now
Your house
Other moving in to your home looking for any obviously there's nothing
What's unfolding
Phone
Yep my phone all the time
Going places and doing things
Probably malware from all the poor and he's looking at
Website
Anyway nightmare
S***
She's not there
This is the best you've ever done was got to kill some time now cuz Rodger that got to get him back on the phone
Start complaining about his position in life
Fan Drive
He starts talking Finance
Surprised by some of these number
Oh God
BuzzFeed
It's three hundred million dollars a year
It doesn't have the traffic
Infowars
Network
Are you f****** kidding those videos
The videos about as real as it like 8.
He million views does channels are massive
People are owned by f******
Evil Bratt
Motherfuker
We shall $40 product but it's literally
Show the match
Gross $29
Gross 40
Are all the crew pay all the services
Literally
That is a bad setup you are not doing things right
Tim fruge
I wouldn't cuz you could you could
Who gives a s***
I'm sure most of Mark Randazzo's work is it shouldn't take too long
We could do could really be fit on a Post-It
20 million after paying off the
Let's assume
I mean rent we saw the studio not where it was
Boston
Even though it's a giant
But yeah
Six or seven Grand
No problem
An area of Austin
How to be super hot
It's not like in the middle of August
So I think you could probably have a very reasonable but hi
Right
Then you got to consider bandwidth
Cuz he has his own servers and stuff like that
That's probably a pretty serious
To the tune of
Maybe a couple hundred thousand a year
Something like that if he does get the traffic that he
Pretends he does
Which will suit for this
$15,000 a month
Totally normal severance pay
Of course
There's a much more important piece of the operation
You got it
If he's that is a salary that is possible
Like I'm sure he's not paying David Knight
But like
Become a considered a respectable two or three grand a month
I do I bet it's more than that I will put in
Category
Something like that
Salary range for someone like course
You got a like
You got to cut down on some I hate someone who is a big supporter of workers
I still think you're paying people to watch
For what that's about
Unless part of that is don't snitch on the game
Something like that like
Is life
Look it doesn't
Me and that the payments after
The fact of course he's fighting her husband
But maybe all of it is like
You know where up
Here's a lot of money
Yeah you don't get
Complacent or feel negative about it I feel like maybe I'll
Rytec
Encrypted email somebody with arsenic
I don't know if that's a possibility cuz of course he is not worth $15,000 a month
You can put that on my grave
Whatever I would
Hear those numbers and be like
I I can give up on my morals for a little while
Just here I can
Freelancer
3 years
I appreciate everyone who donates to our show
Tremendously
Concept
$15,000
Absurd
He's having phone problems again
It's not great
And maybe if we
Catoctin Circle
Describe Rogers
You in almost
In its entirety as being like
He's channeling marionberry
That's what I would say
It works
So Alex got Rodger back on the phone
I need gears up to
Just throw to him
And this is a little bit of a longer clip but I think
It's really important
I think it's so indicative
Of where Rodger Stone and Alex Jones's relationship
He's going to be moving forward
It also just made me laugh
So f******
You're fun to talk to you everyday your good friend
My friend
About again
John Ray
What she's going through
They're moving in your house
Squatter's rights
There's no doubt they're going in
All these phones are tapped
Nope so you better believe they are so pissed right now
Rodger there
Reporter
The show me people on the phones
What's the chance of
The most obvious thing happened
Out today you can hear that his voice is almost gone he's he's he's been up all night long
There was just one statement up on infowars.com
Check the audio
The video this right now
Exclusive interview
Immediately
Infowars.com
Denise Lucifer statement
Is it important
Mueller Ezra prosecutor sent text message last night said they're setting
Venetian wasn't
Meme somebody made myself Faith goldy and Rodger
The n word
I think they're going to probably arrest me tomorrow
Conversation
I can just see it because there's all these puppies about
How I've been treated bad Mascota mean for my testimony
I was just driving me absolutely crazy
Probably forgot the world is closer but he had a lot more to add
Presidential
Obviously I need to do
You're not
Southern Seas right now
Again. And the cellphone to Grant Smith his lawyer cut out
Rodger doing that
Call fer landline
Text Grant right now
Okay
See you notice what happened there
Alex didn't know at all that Rodger had passed
It was going out to speak
To the reporters that crowd
That was outside the courthouse
World Champ I have actual media out there.
Read my case because I am horse f***
I am completely screwed
And I need at least show
Save myself a little bit
Alex has a lot of power
In a small sect
If you're not in trouble you can pretend you're in a great amount of trouble cottage industry in order to make it
In order to
Raise your relatives
You can make your book a bestseller probably by enough insinuation and Alex's world
Because
It just is what it is a bubble
So you can exploit
But when the ship gets real
Alex can't help you
That is such a strong indication of it
He didn't say
Hey Alex
I'm going to go talk to the reporters
He just disappeared
And left Alex hanging
And he knew Alex was on air
He knew that and making a big deal out of how this was an exclusive
Disrespectful
It's a real dick the only thing that I'm really serious about
Is Raj
In order for his image to work properly
He needs one of those joint jokey voicemails that's like
Hey how are you doing
Lawyers
Voicemail
The people
Speed from CNN
And
I don't know if you watched any of this
Didn't go well
You know what is this was a stand-up outside tough.
Is Inquisition
And no way to Russian collusion
We'll get back to this here in a second but you notice how it's almost exactly what he was saying
Just talked to Alex for longer than he's able to stay in front of the f*** out of there real fast
Rogers getting food
You can see it in his face the same thing you see in a comic
I'm usually pretty good at this is
This has gotten away from me
Wikileaks collaboration
Or any other illegal action connection for the 2016 campaign
Russia
So we need to talk about these things
The first thing is I really hate to do this
But I might have to give him forward partial credit for starting to lock her up
Now
Not
But it might
Yeah
As we learned when we went over Alex's 2015 passwords accepting
Trump
But the whole time he hated Hillary
Trump as Lord and around late December 2015
He recognized
Representative
He sent Joe Biggs out to the rally in Texas
Far we have been able to
Basically weasel our way into the Hillary Clinton event
Hillary t-shirt
Photo of Hillary Clinton
Penalized
Okay it's Kishore
The independent has reported that Michael stoker is credited with starting the Republican
After October 2015
I'm pretty easy to see how something that starts
Was Hillary for prison
To be made more charitable at Redbox
Predate this field report where Joe big says
Hillary for prison
And he's kind of just doing it doesn't really cool shirt
Got
Rolling Stone was closest to capturing this in their piece about the Republic
National Convention
You can hear the disembodied voice of far-right conspiracy theorist Alex Jones through downtown Cleveland
From several blocks away
Now we're going to push even harder with more Hillary for prison shirts
How many Hillary for prison shirts we got
These creatures into the microphone
Good marketing opportunity for him
Yeah
It's not terrible OfferUp is much better
Path could have been charted
Complain about people yelling stuff at Rodger really tries
Give a press conference
On October 6th 2016 Alex Jones contact
$1,000
Are you get $5,000
You could be heard saying Bill Clinton is a rapist
Well now that I know you can afford naturally this took off
A Warrior's began interrupting use remote
We're honestly probably not even caring about the money
How to provide a focus strategy
Normalized
They were longing to express
And Alex's Bill Clinton contest it'll Realtors multiple clips of his listeners interrupting speeches and press conferences
I would say that yelling lock him up at Rogers
Could be seen as
Like rooted in the same anti-social
Impulse
I think the context
The different
Yelling at Rodger falls under the heading of parrot
As well as
From a place that's closer to righteous indignation
But Alex is
Insane
By doing something
People to do not 3 years ago
And in that
From December from October 2015
He's going to a Hillary rally
In trying to create a spectacle and gal
Hillary for prison so it is the same thing it's just
You know what it turns out
A lot more people coming yell at Rodger Stone
Not hard
Mobs but I wish I was part of that Mom
It does seem like it might be a great time
I don't know I'd need to Workshop it for a bit off the top of my head nothing really comes to my
Cut his dick off
But that's not really you got that one guy was trying to
Just a little bit Albany
Call of Duty
Wood Rodgers
To be passing out Sports
RealTracs
By the wayside
It turns into a situation where
Maybe like Rodger Stone
As listeners
Alex cuts.off at the path
He said this repeatedly over and over again
Did the people booing
Our reporters
And they're not
No they're not
Which is a very understandable as this is a liberal media
Enemy of the media
They're all in order to create the perception
He's a bad man with that
It's not true
You can trick some people
Usually
Believe it's like not all journalists
White House Press briefing
All of the reporters were just like
It'll be interesting
So I was mad about that but here's one criticism of Rodger Stone
Surprise
Fpi
They had some reason
I love the idea that look like a guilty Criminal
20 seconds
Nixon I'm not a crook
That was a weird movie
Too on the nose
You know what Alex
This is like this is like it's like a movie
If it wasn't a movie be like
Guys
So Alex Rogers
Get get it back on the phone
You still in front of these people in
Like doing poses
Call Rod
He's a man address
He doesn't know what to do right going through like these
Leica MSNBC
It's like real
Comparison about what the media is
Is doing karate
And those FBI agents who
His house
How they're trying to make him look guilty
Comparison
None of us could have possibly expected
Nope I wish I wish
I told you this a thousand times
Amish people
Weird milkwort
The government wants their property in Pennsylvania
Michigan
Scripps
Chipotle year
That was cheesy
Guy goes
Cousin
49ers
Willie must be bad
Close the gate
Create the appearance that Rodger
And Alex after work is strong good for Amish or Mennonite Farm person or anything
It's really close to that
Evil laugh about this story he's kind of making things up
The government is constantly
Just trying to make stuff
That's not even close to
In the case of these Amish
Sometimes it gives undercover agent
The agent then give it to someone in another state
Are nowhere International sales of unlicensed cheese this Amish guy is going to prison
That's bulshit
Acres Farm with rape
In the culmination of a drawn-out
Bakersfield tons
Raw milk
Which has been illegal to sell across state lines
Since 1980
With discretion
But federal law prohibits Interstate sales and for a good reason
Raw milk is not pasteurize
If there's no good protection against things like e-coli salmonella
And the pathogen is responsible for causing tuberculosis
And typhoid
Eredin the deck between 1998
2008 illnesses
104 hospitalization
Two deaths were proven to be caused by drinking raw milk
Roanoke proponents claim that pasteurization kills bacteria along with the beds
Those people are dumb
Rainbow Acres was selling a lot of raw milk outside
Lancaster Online article about the operation
$6 a gallon for raw milk from Rainbow Acres
And she was far from the only one this is a really large operation
What are the ways of these Farms try to get around with known as a cow share program
Words that have milk
Farms allow people to pay a certain amount
4th stake claim on part of an actual living cow which is the rights that animals event
Will milk production literally are 49ers
It's an old saying
You need to buy the cow when you can't get
Get the milk illegal
Daughters note Farm in Pennsylvania call Davos Miller Farms
Rainbow Acres
Since they're aware they were only on the government's radar because they were definitively Trace down and being thesaurus
Listeria outbreak
They killed at least one of their customers who lived in Florida
Outside state lines
There's also Mark north of the nature sunlight Farm in Pennsylvania
For flagrantly violating state regulations by publicly refusing to maintain the state raw milk permit
He also refused to allow routine testing of his cows
Infectious diseases like tea
He's also selling tons of product across state lines
It was received a fine of $5,100 which is nothing
He liked the other cases that were talking about we're running a large operation
These are little individual Farmers being targeted by the feds
It's big size to large businesses were being punished for breaking
Michigan case I was referring to is Family Farms cooperative
Which was a little bit of a smaller operations outside
In March 2012 their customers reported getting sick after drinking
The same Friday shipment
Fromm Family Farms milk
Stool samples revealed the presence of a campylobacter
Which indicates food poison
Notification of Amish bus to Pennsylvania
What stories that like 1 oz
In fact all of them are cases where people who got arrested because it was more profitable for them
Probably not the hours
Accidentally
Alright if those diseases
Words
Contagious
A little bit
Jacob rabe
Like
Are you f******
Except for the part of it being like
That one case that Maryland
They're still feeding these kids they don't have the right to
Adult
But you can make your own decision
If you have all the information in front of
You still want to drink raw milk go I have a fun time whatever you can do your thing
Once you start having to be like
This is what if being given to children
You're an adult
Choose if you want to get vaccinated or not
Except for the
In terms of like
The kids don't have a choice
Orchids
Measles mumps rubella
So
Apply to children
A drought
It's out.
Does make a certain logical
Center of
Then you accept the cut you know it's like it's the principle of
You're only hurting yourself word
Got to climb a mountain and then die
You're like
High-risk high-reward
Right away because how awesome would it be
Need to get on the top of the mountain
I think I differ
Milk
Whatever
Just drinking raw milk
Right
At this point Alex is furious
Because Rodger Stone went out there and got
Where was
Like what what city was he in
Fort Lauderdale Fort Lauderdale Florida
If that was
Like if I got any kind of I would start run
Corsi's salary I would have jumped on the play I would have been on a plane
Myself airline flights
I'm going to go boom
It legitimately would be like
Going to Woodstock
If it came out of nowhere so they prepared
It is the sort of thing we're like 15 years from now based on how my life is going the last few years
I would love to be able to tell people I was there
I was one of those people booing Rodger Stone
Like a badge of honor
Grandpa
What's your favorite memory what time
You got arrested
It like that but I've saved this one phone I brought my friend along and saved everyone
Alex is furious about Sirius for another reason just
The fact that like
It went that way
Which
He feels that Rodger didn't listen to
To his advice
Because Alex told him
If you go out there
Zircon a boot
Witcher 3 Alex
He said he told it to him off air
But you didn't I didn't realize
This is going to be what happened
Tara Lee
He's mad for another reason
And that again
Is that no one is recognizing that before he went out there and got booed he was on Infowars
He's so mad this little bit of a longer clip it again
Tracking the infuriate
How you getting madder and madder throughout this next 3 minutes I think it's very important
You should make it about the attack on Free Speech when they do it
Call Dave Rubin
Wonderful
Amass compliment
Rodger Stones exclusive Global state
That they don't want you to hear
Come out
Next hour
We're going to come
He doesn't do that I'm going to cut in here
Intuitive are very brilliant about
You predict that in a nun
Controlled
Environment outside a courthouse
There's a decent chance at Rogers not going to
Be able to spend things as well as he does on the phone with him
Think Bold prediction he's not Nostradamus
This is where you go Bernie Mac
You motherfukers
Defense right there
Scared
Rodger Stone 100% could have gotten on Mike and Ben like
Y'all don't even understand I pulled my s*** out this whole room gets dark
In Florida
Better
The ticket it's like weird sort of acid techno
Coming out
They're so out of control
Oneplace.com
Outside
People in the crowd
Dallas County
The crowd was steaks at
The entire interview aired
We're going to air
Swedish pie
Hear what Rodger Stone
The world ever seen
Piranha like have no Russia collusion
All of it
Bastard
Relationship
Slow motion
I'm awake
I was just say this right now
You want the globalist to win
Already successfully basically stopped expansion planter Infowars
Platform
Ahead of the coup de gras
All those little
Establishment
Is it emergency
So much of this f****** episode is just
Does black ice bear man
I mean you could see if it's Eurasian there in terms of
You just so pissed off that no one's giving him
Except
Is giving him his like
You got to go to world exclusive
He's also probably pretty pissed off cuz it's Rodger speaking
Tattoo of recognized
When he was talking to Alex
I was being treated like another Outlet friend and I think I was probably has to realize that means
Lip service enough
He does call Alex back
Let's not let's not ruin
To do right what am I going to do
Along with my dog
I don't know
Explain
And they repeat
Over
And over and over again
He's wrong
Who's in jail
Framer
Downhill
That was
Hundreds of millions of dollars of Wessex
Sodus
Put us on
Frame
Now let's look at what Alex
Alex David with Hillary
He sent out to her rallies as early as October 2015
Making a big spectacle in the audience
Her speeches in the same way
Video of now complaining about people
That's Island sauce
In the way that Alex's describe
I'm starting to think that you're going to come up with some parallel
Fremont
Alex
He talks about Mueller on the tarmac with uranium
Which is b*******
Whether or not they've also committed other crimes
I'm not interested talk about positive
The things that Alex is specifically talking about
He's trying to them
Do you think your supporter of
And his billions of dollars selling
Shirt
Bumper stickers about sending Hillary to jail
He's tried to
Frame her
And put her in jail
This is literally what most of the Trump energy was about
Did Alex glommed onto throughout that the attire 2016 election
It's something that Rodger Stone was instrumental in helping
Create and helping perpetuate
So Alex
Repeating this over and over again
Is if it's what's being done
Him
Is b*******
It is his
Tactical strategy
Now what's happening
The consequence
Of other things
Cuz they can get away with
They can get away with all of their actions
Disrupts peaches yelling Bill Clinton's a rapist or whatever that's fine
That's not illegal
That's fine
Lying about Hillary Clinton selling off the uranium
When we get to the bottom of free speech to lie about it
Who gives a s*** boring
Making money off of calling for her imprisonment
It's all under the free speech
Other things you have done
Like
Lying about
Sandy Hook families
For example
Tonight at 1
But that's another one
There are things you can't do
The chickens are coming home to
If you just have never done those things
He could do everything he's doing and no one would care
Rodger Stone head White House intelligence committee
He'd be fine
There wouldn't be a perjury charge port
Totally on it
If he had
Threatened Randy credico
Did I making it
If you hadn't done things that are in that indictment
Not anything that they're doing on a political level
That is caused
Downturn
Specifically illegal things
Alex
That night
He asked
Rex
He's like hey
Hold on a sec
Did you know
What goes around
It comes back
Really really famous and common
Called what goes around
Comes around
Justin Timberlake Justin Timberlake
How to get Rodger back on the phone
Rogers start
Done his public
Humiliation
Day is now a little bit free-er to talk
To Alex Wright
Embody
What happened after the FBI came
Listen to that he's talking about being put in a holding cell
And he even in the middle of that story
Have to get in a
Very not true plug
American
Presidents
I'm sure but I do believe that happened cuz I don't believe Rodger had that conversation
What do you think about
Rogers given credit for them and then
Pretending that he had a conversation with all of these wonderful black people in his holding cell
All of these
These people in this holding cell where black and I will draw zero conclusions from this
I think what he was trying to save might be the benevolent a race head
Thrust behind it wasn't like
Hey I was in prison cell and everyone there was black
It was to save it like there are a lot of black people who are jammed up on unnecessary
Behind it
Who was behind that is trying to support the idea that Trump
Is making
Something's right
It's not and then you look a little bit further
Illness that will happen if you drink raw milk
The fever comes in waves
So big complaint
Style blog
Lots of funny hat
Yeah it's a style Stone style blog
And worst
So it's not then
20 years
And the worst part of that is I will have
0 hat
Yeah.
How do you pair them with a
Yeah perhaps
Height
He's mad
Got
When the FBI showed up in the morning
Candyman
If they just told me
Good
He's mad about that
Make this complaint a number of time
And while he's making it this time
Alex's response
Is pretty funny
And very
Okay
Call Dad
I actually
Telling the truth
But yeah I know I would have
No
. now
He could be a Flight Risk
I understand why any law enforcement agency would be like
Works not
Oh for sure time knowing Rodger his is
Extensive history
The times he's been in hot water in the past
Runaway
So I appear to me that there's a really thinks he can get away with
A lot of moves left to play but it doesn't appear that he does
Probably is sincere in saying that if they just told me I would have shown that
How is Jonah
It's one of those things
Cuz you like
But yeah I believe
Altitude
Did you see that one of the first tweets about him getting arrested with her and Chad Ochocinco
It's so so
Rodger Stone getting arrested
I've only seen s*** like that
Such an awesome like weird cameo
Indicted interested story
In a weird right now
So fun to imagine that like for you
The years they've lived
Nextdoor
Receiver of all-time
Rodger Stone
For dinner sometimes
Good walls make good neighbors
Call Rodger Stone
Have you seen the Alex Jones School of quota
William Shake
Remember how we mispronounced it
Inspire
No
In this next clip Alex
And Rodger
Start talking about
Rogers Finance
End. Store
It's real bad for him
Real bad financially
I don't believe most of it
And then Alex
Children
Something you didn't do
What's the temp
Dershowitz you smart
So there's two things there first
How dare you
Itsfunneh
Four number four
The first is that after Rodger called threatened Eliot Spitzer
Blasted navigation was tainted from the start
Eliot Spitzer
For corruption
He said
This whole story does not pass the smell test
Is more serious than any crime Spitzer committed
So
Description Rodger a little bit of the history also fun fact
They caught Rodger red-handed lying what you did was ridiculous and stupid
He went on to call Rodger a stone
Any moment now
Who helped them cut a deal on those operations
If that isn't enough to get Alex to not trust the guy
Multiple girls toward Epstein's victims have gone on record
To them to have sex with Alan
Conveniently doesn't care about things like this
He only cares about using it as a blunt instrument
Who taxes
Two political enemies
Everything is a means to an end with him
And it's gross
I didn't know that
Dershowitz
What is the per
Participants
I'm not sure if it's been proven in court but there are multiple victims
Directed
Alan dershowitz Chiron whenever you should be like
Accused
F****** pedophile
Red Blick
It should roll on the bottom
Television news
Their policies are on that but I wouldn't
Everything
He says
About all this stuff should
Anyone being caught
Except for Trump
Of course
He loves Jeffrey Epstein whenever his political enemies are sort of related to Jeffrey
Subway it's the biggest eel in the world it's proof of
Xy&z everyday
Someone who supports Trump or is literally Trump
Absolutely.
About this is Rodger telling his sob story about how this f******
Of crimes
Committed is hurting his book sale
And stuff like that
There's an episode of his goddamn radio show
What are you talkin about the WikiLeaks
Stuff it just come out
And he's talking about
Which was the first
You gave
Assange
Beautiful back-channel source
It's a treat
The person who gave us on.
You know who else was saying that around that time
F****** Jerome corsi
You know who else is episode
Jerome corsi
Think about this
The stuff
He goes into a little bit of a diatribe
Like
His time in the barrel was constantly
You know what's really great about that
Is that I've been able to go on
So if you're going to exploit
Disorder Scituate
The murder of of somebody
Further your political
Conspiratorial bulshit
You're going to be like
I'm not going to feel any sympathy
For you when you complain about
I don't have any money now
Because of
Prime
How many
Multiply don't know how many kids he has
Your stone must be
Bummer
Man
From the Press
Holyshit did you know that what goes around
That's Justin Timberlake
He's not he's one of those dudes
If you ever hear stories about
The children of
Old school pro wrestlers
Fake an injury
Emagine Rochester
Instead of
Sports entertainment
It's like
Malicious International propaganda
Kids
I know your ages for
But
The first thing I need to tell you and I wish I could have told you when you came out of the womb
Never Google
He said that before Google
Next
Alex reinforces
You're next in the hopper
He told everybody that
Shmoney
Because
It was for cause though
He wasn't living up to his application
His contract could not have been paid out
The quote from Alex Jones is that article was about
We decided to pay him out based on
Consideration
Cast for
So many
And I believe her too I don't know
And I'm a dentist
Shmoney
Porter's
Silence some
Put him in jail
Reporters
Fine petting reporters $160,000 a year
That's a difference
Especially when that reporter is
Worthless
We've been covering Alex Jones
Jerome corsi has
Done s*** except for tendies opening that watching
I tried to come up with the map it was just a dumb Seth rich
Yeah yeah
We've heard him
Just s*** the bed over and over again
And then
Be kicked off being allowed to be on the show cuz he went to into the kiwi
Disturbed
No purpose will believe that
I haven't read any of his books but break
Like even before we put this episode out and they want more answers about the Kursi business
Because I think this is a really big
But unfortunately I regret to say we
We can't offer much on that
We will be able to soon
We will
Yeah
As soon as that information is available
I assure you we will do
Of course he episode
Although I don't think Alex will even talk about it
Of course
Turn South
Chico State's evidence property like Beanie Sigel
Another rap reference
Woke up on Timberlake reference
Like three episodes of it like Three 6 Mafia references National napping Seagal
Yeah
Jadakiss is coming up
Next episode Swizz Beatz
Drag on
That means dragon
I'm surprised there wasn't a
When I woke up on Friday one of the things that I
The Hat in my mind
First was
I woke up pretty early
I'm surprised I woke up pretty early
I crack my back
Set down
Got to work
Twitter messages
La Michoacana
I woke up early. Early it up
Aethersphere kind of Rodger is on like an hour ahead
Possible that I couldn't sleep because I knew was going on but also possible that I was just playing Hyrule Warriors
Who knows
Like what I woke up
I was kind of overwhelmed by the amount of people
I appreciate
But my immediate first thought was like
Is imallexx right now
I took me an hour or so to make an egg sandwich
Process
Just get my bearings about me
I started to dig like it
Alex knows that in an hour
He's got to get on
He knows that right now
Alex knows he has to get on it
And secondarily
Alex Munoz
Everybody is tuning a
Alex knost
He's kicked off YouTube and stuff like that
He can still broadcast
You can still live stream all this s***
All eyes are on him there is no way
The people are going to be like
Lo and behold
It was it was a raid
We were getting 50,000
Builder
RadioShack
Give me credit
For the world
I don't believe we made this point we are on
The Great
Robert Evans
I don't believe those specific
Behind
The idea that
He had massively elevator
He's going to pull out a tree
Obfuscating
Excuse-making thing I've ever seen in my life
I was watching live
There was at least a number of
Who don't generally watch who like
Thousands and thousands
More people were like
Here we go
For sure so Alex knew that
Not nearly as high as
Bring some
The focus why
He's more restrained
Cuz he realized
There are a lot of people
Watching
They have an expectation
I've got a freak out
Keep it together
Also explains why
You keep asking me
People for money right because
There's so many more people
There's a better chance
So all of this makes total sense
He knows that this is sweeps
Yeah it's bad
Definitely going to prison
He's still a businessman
I don't do this without Rodger
I don't really either cuz I I use your no like I just use a flat rate
But from what I understand like
If you host something somewhere
The traffic goes up in order for the server
Traffic
The flat rate
Be the service that I use
I just need to pay a certain amount per month
And no matter how many people downloaded
Or anything like that
You pay for the
Gato however large files are that I post
And their strategies that they host
Thousands of shows
No one down
Rocks that are
It's called medicare-for-all
They liberated syndication is figured out
Socialized medicine for podcast
It doesn't matter at all it only comes into
Play if you're host
Open your own s*** in your own servers
I got you
Fine
Do it yeah I mean the reason
Because then there's no way for anybody
Take that.
Freedom's that you're
You you so desire
Libertarian
Sure Alex has a new guy
Rodger is gone he's got to go take a shower
Got to shave his hair
All that nonsense
Comfort his dog
There's no doubt about it
So pathetic
Is next guest
Is Rodger Stones lawyer
Cheap lawyers
Okay she's okay
Chinon and Alex Jones
Do you work here
How they operate
Yeah he's a spokesperson
Spokesperson
It's interesting that Rodger Stones lawyer is named Nixon
I was really curious about this
Real I was really confused
I wanted to know if he was related to Richard Nixon sings Rodger was so connected
Richard Nixon
What does it look like
At least not closely
Neither of them has a kid named Tyler
Husbands names
When they got married
Cox and Eisenhower respectively
Nixon's daughter married Eisenhower's grandson
So it's cool everybody's Great America
There's no sort of power delete that
Pitchfork
Pitchforks by white
Pitchforks up
Hearing whenever we talk or how do we not know that
Stopboor public knowledge
Reindeer
Nixon is a part of Nixon
Is a second cousin or some s***
Rogers lawyers however
He's a bad person for Alex to have on the show
Unbiased source of information
Ucpac in November 2018 Tyler Dixon was questioned by Robert Mueller about Rogers connections
Remember all the new stories that Rogers Associates being called in for questioning
You indicated that go with Rogers
This is a problem
Because it means that if credico was not being which he wasn't making up in
30 told Mother about Quantico
And that means
Tyler Nixon is in trouble too
This isn't a lawyer trying to help his client
This is a man who realizes that he fell into the same perjury trap his client
Maybe with Rodger
Since it's clear they both lied to achieve the same end result
Which is
It might not have been Tyler's
Primary motivation
But the end result
Does covering up Jerome corsi's involvement with Rodger Stone
Visa V the Wikileaks interaction
Even if your client is even if you have it
Client privilege
Jr Direct
By your client
To say something
You still lied to Congress
So you're kind of
I'm at I'm at front there's no
Was introduced new
Because he said that
Key Witness creticos
Which isn't
Like it's one thing to say Rodger told me this or whatever
Information
I mean who knows
I don't think that
He's telling the truth
Austin Rogers
Fake tan
Knowledge of Rodger Stone
I feel like
Rodger bus at this sequence of events
Must have been
Rodger like accidentally Googling
Like Nixon lawyer in this guy came up and he was like for me to have Nixon lawyer
That's entirely possible
You don't report himself on the show if any kind of a professional
He's just throwing around the globalist to come in
He's just you might as well be like Alex's
Norfolk regular gas
He does not hear them say anything
Who's word like pro bono
Jurisprudence
Illegal words
Graduate
Be f****** stupid
Because he says this
Attacktix
Report on Rodger Stone who would be just
First I'm sure
If people have their way
Would make lavrentiy Beria
And Stalin and Hitler
And the rest of them and Barrister or
I was just a child as far as you know
I would absolutely love to have this type of
Power
Alex Jones
BTU 2 vocab word
That's not good
As a lawyer
Hey let me correct you on what it is when you think you're saying help you out of that little pickle yours
To remind you that Stalin put hundreds of thousands of people
Gulag
Rodger Stone
Being embarrassed
A charge
Almost
Clearly
That off of how they made Rodger Stone
Whatever's going on right now is
Is well within the abilities of star
Himmler and anybody else
This is pathetic level
Of of what they perceived to be what's happening to them
In order to
Convince the audience
Miss so much
Dyer
Because they need their money
They want the f****** money
It's just constantly
Give Rodger Stone legal defense money
Donate to Rogers.
About that you didn't do it just dawned on me
That's why he's lying
Pulling this bull was wrapped up in the weed I got the Rodger Stone legal defense fund
Dot-com probably
Absolutely
This is so f****** stupid
Like
The idea that they're saying
Is is still Wild
So nuts
What
Exact
Termite
But I'm going to go with
Ambulance chaser
What is it with
Right wing
F****** lawyers like
But I think
Exhausted all other possibilities
Like a real lawyer
I'm going to lose
Turn off
In my name is going to be
We f****** destroy
Alex I think they're just like
He hit his like
The resource
You talk about like the idea like
This is billable hours
You also have to recognize the
Like what you're doing it
It's a possibility
You're going to be
Defending
Alex
Against
Victims family
And the Optics of that are never good
Talking as a human you know that Alex
Guilty
He did do that
It's one of those things that you're only going to be
Just f******
Mystic on some level but those people still do need representation
Everybody has the right to a fair trial
You are not going to have a trap
Well
It's an indication I
Come to a point
Where you're willing to pay way more than you need
Because no one else will
And you're trying a Hail Mary free speech type app
And I think that's
A short-term loan like one of those like
Why is he in
Straight 200,000 percent that doesn't
At this point
This episode is no longer Subs
We have reached
The point where Alex
I don't know what happened to it but he starts losing his mind
Does he start talking about God
He's only got nothing on Rodger Stone because Stone bailed on him
Ghosted him
So Alex can't like pivot other news
What is it going to be there is no news
LaRosa's criticized
Cold
Inside of himself in
Pray
Does he also Big Sur
She's going to get far
It's pretty amazing that you
Houses done with his
Is work
Weird
I try and give some sort
Real baby
Real fun sort of introduction
He starts talking about God.
And next he starts walking talking about.
I should be at least
I complimented your instincts
Mainstream National News host calling upsetting word is Mueller's coming after you next one comment
How to cover up. Being a little kid that kids on
Motor all you guys
Jesus Christ
Salt
End of the show very f*****-up
As it goes along like
What I was listening to this on Friday
I thought the first hour was
Disaster
And super boring
Are we going over it in terms of Rogers Bland statement
The dynamic of Alex be pissed off that no one recognized
Exclusive
Pretty interesting but I didn't think there was a full episode out of that
Towards the middle
The end of the show
And Alex
So unbelievably weird
In the way that you would have expected him to
You coming to the show
And what I imagine
Imagine
He did his first hour and a half or so
Lost a ton of listeners
They're like alright whatever whatever
Alex's bringing it whatever
Broccoli
I'm talking about.
Workout
Weird right we will get to Galactic Quest
By the end of this
Quest
There's one more clip
Sort of political nonsense
Pissing yourself
Polysyndeton Mueller's people
Set us up our daughter Jedi released the big set of stuff yet
Cuz you don't have any
Close to that
But it doesn't really matter anymore
Country Organics
If you don't know that everyday
Jostens Soros or La organ or DC
Arch was America's going down
Now it is
Yeah also I like it
America's never great
He says cherry picking
And you're like
You're really close to same
Cotton Pickin which is kind of
The point
Just refuses to engage with the actual argument
America will be great
Until we get to
You know when we have
You know just
Enough equality
We deal with issues
Realistically
Those arguments Arts America
It's
Do you understand
Guilt
You have like a shame is I am bad guilt is I did something
To make between those things
And when people
Teak America for like
I don't know our interventions
Venezuela in Central America
Our interventions all over the world
We turned of
Crime against humanity into a wonderful
Stores
Are deeply deeply racist history
Slavery
It was probably
Contact leasing programs
Became
We suck and shoot
Kill ourselves in America
Begone
It's just a weed
We need to own up to
And that's the only path forward
We won't be great
Until we acknowledge those things and works
And Alex's
It just is inability
Understand
You poor thing
Ability
Unwillingness
Understand
Leaves interview like
Overly simplistic
Are still above
So now
Get to the park for this is
Okay
I'm excited Alex starts fake crying
But what triggers him to start fake crying
Is that he starts talking about
Actually cry
Which is weird
Because the memory
Of him
Talkin about crying
Leads him to
Fake crying
It's very strange cuz it shouldn't be
Memories
Super painful
Whenever I think back on times I've cried that does
Super emotional
But when I was crying it was because I was
Else
That wasn't emotionally resonant
Crying isn't
The emotionally it's a byproduct
Of the emotionally resume
Cuz that's cuz you're a human
Alex talks about crying he's reminded I should probably pretend
Promotion
Sometimes just leaned up against the wall cuz I've got
This is a fake
Washington Washington
I'm not scared
To make sure that goddamn
Country
My favorite thing about Alex's when he gets on a roll if you have nothing
The thing
Spielberg's wife
Temple of Doom level of acting
It's so bad but also it's really interesting because you know you know it's all fake and performative that
The way that Alex can only contextualize B
Fake showing the vulnerability if transitions to rate that the only way to understand
Is the presentation of that emotion
Because he beams itweak
Right thanks it's a weakness
And then in order to compensate for that you
You have to Pivot that right
And it's pathetic
It is one of those like
You understand humans
It's one of those like Psychopaths
I don't know if you
Feel human emotion
I know you know it's totally possible
He feels normal emotions it is
It's so it's so hard to say
She was fake crying in
Pathetic performative aspect
Me like
Calling it
Psychopath Behavior
I'm up perform felt like
Absolute garbage
You know you put on the you put on the calendar
40 million Metro
But not making
Gross
It's all him
Yeah no
None of that money is coming in from David Knight show
Like it's on his back
But he knows he's going to bring it
40 bucks
It's kind of like having a big set
Yeah at least
Sounds like you got to do
What you got to do
For this operation
Well if you've ever read the late night
Oh you guys are
F****** crazy pressure is insane
And like
How bad
He's living
But like
No amount of pressure is going to
To make you
This awful
It's going to reveal that you are this
Perhaps
Talk in a little bit throughout this episode about
They're going to take my dad
Because of this corsi payoff s***
He's been
I'm paranoid about this it's bad
Tyler you know my dad there they're literally you're not afraid
My dad
Nobody is off limits they will table take everything that you have
Wow
Imagine how funny it would be if they did
Just grab Alex
We find this is really what it's all about
We need to be flooded
A regular basis
Rodger rabbit
Is more important
Could have
Stole that from
But
Radio City Hall
Baby funny
If possible
You missed the
Perfect
Oportun
The perp
You say go ahead take my dad
Please
Involved in all the
Operation
Whataboutism
We know about that
Her husband
I really do
You know my mom in 25 years I've been on air 24 and a half it's gotten Matteson
God
Raspy strong
His dad
Clint Eastwood
Just imagine figures it out
Hey
Anyway
The show up time
What is elapsed
Trump Rodger Stone
Prescott
I know that in our show it's been a couple hours since we talked about that
Still
Tickled by the buoy
I will watch that before we started the show I forgot you I forced you to watch
Commercial
I love that commercial so much
In that Pantheon will be
That Rodger Stone
Getting booed
It's so like
You see that
Beer in his face
Publix
It's like somebody who's like the first radio
Level nine
Your Heaven live
Beautiful
Like you've been to it like a stand-up show new
Like 2 minutes be like
I want I want it.
AUC that in Rogers face
Earlier
Houses given their response
Sarah Huckabee
Has come out and said
It doesn't have anything to do with Trump
Can lying assholes deflection
There's like
Whatever Rodger said you know like yeah sure he's
He's been someone who's been advised many people
No big deal
Whatever
I wish
Lakes with the the narrative in
Dude
I'll be on
If the president
Guilty
I know I'm getting paid a lot of money for that like
Scream
Street
Madhouse
Drop it
Habitat
Not eat
Not it in these matches like
She does a great job
Because it's
Job
To be better deflect
No never ends
That is
It really makes
It's me
Sad for her
And
Like that
But that
That makes me sad for her because I just
The childhood that
Huckabee gave her
Turned her into
To that you know
Like
Can you
Imagine growing up with Mike Huckabee azure
Because like
Mike Huckabee
Politics are
Terrible but
His brand does seem to be like he's a good guy
He plays the bass
Daughter
Hard
So I bring this up is Sarah Huckabee Sanders has come out and said like f*** this noise that's not on
Which is a good thing to say as opposed to
Or like oh yeah working on this or something.
Course that's a response
And it leaves Alex.
F****** pissed off
About how the
Administration isn't route
To Rogers a prize
You know what it turns out
They're just Joe
Jealous
Very angry
To where you are
My brother
Ossify
I like this
I wish I would have
Did they start making
Jokes by the globalist
All of you
Themselves
It's very weird still Alex Rogers lawyer Tyler
I promise you
In a couple of clips
This will deteriorate back
To the god
But this dislike
There's all this f******
You just love the people
You're so f****** pissed off
Where is the real power
That's why they don't
Respect Stone
Thumbs up
Problem
You should go to jail
I think he might
I mean based on what I know from his testimony
Like he did get questioned by Mueller
From everything I could tell from
What statements
The credit go is dead
Like
I mean whatever
Does contradict
What is
Yeah
It's because it's cute
It's because Rodger documented it
It's his only out is
Is Mueller being like
You're just a shity
You didn't
Year you're just bad at your job
Disbarred
He could
In situations like this
I think that
A lot of lower
Wrong
People probably are going
I think he might be able to in terms of
Piece of information
Wood glue
From your quest
Has helped us figure out X wires
I don't think
The f****** Tyler Knicks
I do
I would mind
But I put my flag on that Hill though
So you still sort of reeling
Earlier
We heard him talk about
Is 40
Borrow money
Little bit later in the show
You talked about it
Some more
$5000000
Bad business model
Show
45 million dollars this year
The weather
Shutdown
Men's jumpster commercial that's the hard out
Yeah
That's a dark glimpse
Start
Darkseid
Want you guys
Go to the
Infowars
To go to the store
And I want you to buy
Single product
That I
Advocated
You not buying
Dinner Bell Corinth
I took
Half of
Packet and I got
When I was watching
I recorded it
But I did
Is it for like
On the gcn
They've different commercials been on the live
Yeah AutoZone
Hell yeah
That just doesn't sound
Circle C has
Just like doing
Real soccer
Commercial
If you take this the first time take a quarter of it cuz it's f****** weird you're going to be f***** up
I didn't answer him
You would you want to start out with a half
I know you're cool
I'll eat the other half
Will f*** you up the commercial ends with Alex literally screaming
Like kind of a
That's not a terrible sales
I got
The personnel
Stop with the person who's like
Oh s***
Are you telling me this is danger
You might as well just say do meth dealer but I want
Alex is another commercial to that I wish I could
Is doing a commercial for
The idea of toasting
#Alex Jones
It's like a 30-second spot where it's like
#Alex
If we do this
We will win
Marshalls
Lego podcast it's famous where they're like
Well we don't have a sponsor for this little bit right now but
Incredibly
F*** these social media platforms I don't care that I'm off of edit does a commercial of
Please
Use those two on those social media platforms
We get back to
To this and Alex says something about how much
Super p****
Donald Trump
His administration
Cox
And also he
Rodger Mayweather
Stitches so cut-and-dry imagine
Glad there's no Russian collusion
That is what the water but again
They're a bunch of damn coward
Wart
Hell
Yes Alex
WildBlue
I know is I've committed my wheels Edition nobody
Newburgh
That guy was the guy who published Rodger Stones book so it's kind of just a parade of Rodger Stone
An associate on the show
5ever
That's so funny
Just door
Goddamnit
But you did for troll over there
The name of your likes
Business guy Republic
I know what years I don't give a f*** with his name
Amount of research
That I can do
And in a given amount
Who is kind of priority
These bigger issues
This f****** bird is published
I don't give a s*** is interview with Alex is boring it's just the same things I wasn't
I'm sure he's probably
Stupid bucks a week
Talk about that
20 bucking minutes
Button
We got to talk about how Ally
Getting weird
Now
Next
We have one clip
And then
It's Austin
The
Cliff
Esoteric
Weird nonsense Hellyeah
Is spoiler alert going to essentially the voice of God
There is a tree
It's in the River of Life
Because that's vague
Towards the end of this
But
Before he
He does
She's got to talk a little bit more about what we learned on Christmas
About how Alex
Call Rodger
Alex
And I think that's
6 mm into
Like full-on freakout
Cassandra
You got your job back with a Fox News contributor
Pay $50,000 a year
Was that why
We don't take it seriously happened
To make it look like it's legitimate
Mike manafort
You're going to walk into that
Wheelchair
Show show
Real persecution
If America fails his test
I don't know I am tired of Alex
She's like lions
Trump
More real than the others
Only because it's like
It affect his bottom line
But I still I still don't give a fuk
A hundred percent
Like believes Rogers version of the timeline
I'm almost there
I have a special investigation
You directed yourself
Two years ago to learn more about that
I've been I've Been Told
Teasing you a little bit
Cuz I was freaking out a little bit earlier
And he does freaked out really hard
But I kind of forgot as we were going through it there a couple of those like
Substance
The clips like how I gave Rodger
This job and I told him to get
Condition
Of getting this job I hired him
Alex is going to say he didn't
Is eats the grounding aspect of but then
Clip Jordan he goes up there goes gravity
Mom's spaghetti company
Because Alex accidentally
Starts talking about why he does his
Haha
Why does Alec
He admits why
I have one skill I have
What is a crime
And I'm ready to die
In fact
Unlimited data so I can show you hell I'm inside
I just got to figure
There's no way to join them and get out of this
The only thing you can do is resistant
I told you that a discernment last-lap shows up that is fine. Right now you can't understand
Championship
Now there are those of us
But have to stand in the gap
Character side with your imagined
But I'm against
Pull himself off
Has like
What if Obi-Wan Kenobi
Was Alex Jones
It's like that the only corollary I can pick OB was racist
What if what is Obi-Wan Kenobi in
Instead of being a wise Jedi Master
Who helped
F****** the Empire would
What if he instead was a f****** lunatic
Lake Yosemite
Damn in the desert
What is a controlled opposition Draculaura Skywalker
False flag
The best Star Wars movie
You know
Is is
Is that
Like Alex is admitting operate off of
I only do this because I'm scared
Performative but I think there's kernel of Truth
Feeder
B drives
And what are the problems that I have with that is that his fear is based on an imagined
Right now this idea of these globalist
Turn all this stuff
When are you really break it down you start
Horse Woody
He's talking about you look at
Get the documents that your references realized
Look at like
Did the things that are formative
Naked capitalist by skousen
Conspiracy
Right then you realize
Crawfish it
Communist
Conspiracy theory bulshit
From decades past
It's all just warmed over
Protocols of the elders
Zion.
Worked into a
New framework
Directions and eyes in a way that is
Resonated through the
Modern
Russian
You you start
To recognize that
You start to think
Think about it
That's where Alex got the
Conception
Of these imagine
And you start to look at it a little bit
A little bit too much
I know I
I try to practice radical MP
With Alex
The only way to go
Approached him
You don't deal with
Exactly
Things you say about a literal base
Right
You deal with Insanity by bringing
Acceptance of that insanity
If you respond with anger
You dismiss it you're also never go
So when I
Like this I recognize
What he saying
There are these
Demonic
Enemies that I have
There are based on this misunderstanding
Understanding of History
Was based on
And when I sit with it a little bit longer
And I hear clip like that
I am motivated by fear
It's hard for me not to
You think about
Did
Hugh
Encountered these ideas as a
Child
You got f****** terrified
But I don't
I don't
Off the hook at all
Like
As much as that
Sleep apnea brain damage stuff like
I'm not letting him off the hook for his ideas
Just possibly his behavior is explained by that
In the same way
You look at this
The brain of a child could be
Traumatized by the eye
Of this demonic World Force
That's against you and they have tendrils everywhere
The idea of a
12 year old
Find taking a
This
Every single powerful entity is working against you
Commit genocide
All that stuff right
There's a really decent chance
Book
F***** his mind up
And you've been living at me like a
Kind of states
He operates off beer
Because of that
Child brain
Note that I have
Occasionally
Fourth on
Are we a true crime podcast
Do you know what I mean
Like two are watching a serial
We are tracing we probably killed
Individual
Art racing
Facts
Have had
With some
Like that
I feel like that is a layer
The first layer is if
Literally
He is afraid
Active layer is
This is a performance
He's not actually
But the bottom layer is
Was
Or is
Actually friend
Hiding this reality
Like a try,
Yeah because what
Do you have
Like it it's just not
Question becomes after
Like going down that road though the further and further you get down that road the more you realize
This is just been
And
No endpoint like no preparation WBEZ
Care
I think that's really fun
Volume
This is where
This
This next to clip
I think our
Sofa
I'm saying it means you a resume
Fat
Eve
Deeply
I believe it was Jesus
Who said Alex Jones would be the rock of the
I believe that
Alex Jones is the loads
Stone who holds up the
That sounds right
Like on a very basic
Level one
Icepeak
For God
Then you resonate
With God
That's
This isn't the political show man this is
If it wasn't on the radio
Is being said in a small room
If Anderson Cooper goes on TV and says
If you understand what I'm saying
You understand what God is
Holyshit entire world would f***
Can you explode
Scene
When he was on
Social media
This is
Forgot
Implies that
Infowars
Forgot
Decide which side you're on
That's why this is all here
God made sure
Platform in the last hour
Play shining we're here for you
We love you
Inclusive
Don't go with Satan
The part about like
God
Is going to provide platforms and
That's crazy
The other the other like more ground part of it
That part is even crazier
Because you can you can you can possibly side do you like
God and delusions
Maniac
He's like put that in a box
The idea that he thinks he's inclusive
So inexcusable
Okay
There is
Just from a
Literal definition
Inclusion does not miss
Sara Lee
Excuse
Sure Limited
Conclusion
But if your inclusion is only white people
Play Ura
Inclusive
I should say before that clip he did say
As long as you are awake
It doesn't matter what skin color yet
Or where you from
He was trying
It up to that that that comment there
Wytheville you like
Whatever
Standard boilerplate but I really don't think it's
The fact that he said that
That's why I didn't include in the cliff
No
I don't care how we prefaces back
Passivity is
Is so exclusive
It's the only good Islam is Christianity
So Alex is getting into the
This really weird heads
He's like
Icepeak
You forgot if you
Listen to what I'm saying
A boner
That's great
And then also God
Is made it so
There will be
Places
Where you can come
Until the last days and that's me
That's awesome
That's what we're doing
We are an outpost section
Buy guide
Which is really
Really deeply f***** up
And we have one more clip
I want to be clear this last
Straits entirely with Alex
Entire Opera
I wouldn't we enjoy these sort of like weird esoteric
Dalliance
It's important
Realize why there's
Is there
I meant also realize that Alex
I mean there's indications
Struggling to
But he's struggling
When you struggling with that are
Realizing
Created
Is on like Roblox
Is a full demonstration of like
Where is that like fun in
Interesting esoteric nonsense
Pivots back
The real world
It's the same thing when he's faking
Crying
It's always
Something that he
Marginally in
Controller
Operation
Protect into it and actually
Look at it I do it
Complaining
I really should
Looking
It's really horrible.
You see what they're doing the kids and everybody Associates
Trump
I'll do what I speak on all I'm telling you is we need your prayers with your support now
This is it
Fishes the big plush
Planet planet
Spirit
Divide those up from good for the bat
Quest
I'm just very blessed
Talk to you
How are you have a shot at you you're focused
You understand potential you have
Ashley support us
Boo
You see
He's in control of that
Sing a bunch of s***
A bunch of nonsense
It's funny he's getting esoteric
Quest we're on destruction of our very planet
The hinges on Rodger stones
Somehow
Because he's able to weave it forward
It's like yeah you have to financially support
He hasn't add pivot out of
Deeper esoteric nonsense
Kind of like I'm going to look into the enemy's mind I try to but it's it's
Maybe tonight
And he's still doing the exact same voice
He's doing in that weird esoteric breakdown
When you get that you like
You have to give us support
Financial
The battle is now
And so
I know
Break myself away from
Optical
Ideas about
I don't know just it anyway feeling sorry
Because when you see stuff like that
There's there's nothing
He's not into
Tensional
About how he's using his f*****-up
I don't think there's anything wrong about you and I
Taking time out of our day
To wrestle with a possibility
That were wrong in Mockingjay
That clip was going on I was getting back
Today's like weave
So many times
And this is he
Truly
Even while we
Gears
Secting all the
Dumb
Proving
Wallows listen if I was kind of halfway
Really
Is this all
What is
We need your
Support your like that
That's it
Is trying to defend Rodger
Obviously
He doesn't want any
Mostly primarily concerned with
Yep
It's kind of pissing me off and then as The Show Goes On
You loses
How to the f****** audience
Cuz like he's not really even talked about any Rogers
Weird f****** place 3 says that he speaks for God and Infowars and outpost
Forgot
Getting to the enemies
Painful but it's
Really just away
Continue what is the
You do the whole show
Which is try and get people to
To give him more money
Because he's making less money than
Yep so
F*** all of this
I meant to say at the end
My summation
I think
First of all
My point clearly Rodger Stone
The indictments
Pretty open-and-shut
In the future talking about course
Free stuff
Information is available
Right now
I don't think there's enough for us
Position on it
Although if I
I would bet that corsi
Is probably
Cooperating
Substantial way
And there might be a lot of information
I think
Yeah sure
It's probably over
Trusted
In that world and also
It took forever to break
Manafort
When the FBI called courses
He was like you're the FBI I will tell you
Literally everything
Right now over the
The phone I don't even
Manafort manafort
Literally has worked
Dictator
Like murderers
He has lobbied for
Gotten paychecks for
Blood
He knows that
You have done that
Rodger
Known
That's their business
Is built on
The death of people in other countries
Peace with that
Hundreds
100 and hundreds of
Thousand
And yes absolutely
Like the things that
Even just a year in in Philippi
Yeah
The specifics of what
Those people were doing
Contracted by their fur
Like if unfit
Speakable stuff
Lake Burton
Legitimately had a policy
In place where
What he would like
To do is he would take
And then he would
Disfigured
And kill them
I didn't leave their bodies in the open for people
Find
In order for them to find it
Terrified
About this is what happened
Rodger Stone
He's firm
Still were fine taking their money
Disorders like
Real distillation of the brutality
Oh people Rodger Stones comfortable work
Is it supposed as ice water in their f******
They don't give a s***
Yep like
Bait Wilkes
Protect their ass
Is best
Is there
A courtroom or smaller is talking to
They have face
People who have murdered
Thousands of people
Say some experience with that high-pressure situation
Course it is written
Bailey
Coursey Road of bulshit book
About Obama not being a citizen
Yeah like
Poses like someone who's like
I have all these contacts
Whatever
He's not made of the strong stuff
And I'm not saying that is positive
That manafort and stone are
They have been
Mixed up with people
Who
Are much more dangerous
Then even the United
Judicial
Joe Arpaio
Because you went through line-by-line
Same number of
Torturous
Murderous
F****** b*******
Arpaio is a
Truman
Absolutely
Rodger Stone
And Pullman
Himmler
Many
Dictators
Like even Himmler was just
Only one dictator
Call Marie cell.
Because
Rodger Stone
Images like I'm a f****** dirty trickster whatever
And I think that it's so important to draw a line
Like
What is the fun image
And the reality
Because it's different
It's different
Like he's like
Like back when he works for
Bucking Nixon
Re-election campaign
Impatience
The Democrats
Do a fake dinner
You like that sort of stuff like okay
Cool
You were also involved in Watergate
Let's do it it's cantankerous
That's not who he is Benson
And it's not being who
Has been
The f****** age
I mean there's a ton of people who are involved with Infowars that we could do an episode that would be like
Gave
And just because it's
Knock the most
Pressing thing ever
Wow we just got to keep
Process moving Roberts
Yeah
Histories
F***** up things that they've done
We will do a whole episode
Is that he is no joke
End.
Him as if he's a monster in a fun way
Well it's
One of those things
Kingswear
And this is
Is the hard part of
Your morality
If you want to go with
When you talk about the dick
Haters that they suck
Sure
Tortured
Hundreds of
Never
End
Shouldn't
Have happened
It should never have happened
No matter what
But somehow there are people
Truly done enough
Deserve that
And they will never
Ever ever
Lego
I don't care
I don't care as far as look Rodger
Stone
Deserves
The worst
Of what
I hope he gets a you know
Federal Prison
Where are the states
Survive for the rectum
Is life
So Jordan we're at the end of episode we're done
I don't I don't know I think
I'm exhausted I don't know how to summon this up
Rogers screwed
We'll see what happens
Corsi stuff will play out over the next
We'll see I don't know
I would like you to some this up because
Okay
Bestest on this up
As well as I can
Stone is 5
Corsi's
Everybody's
Somehow
Alex
Not f***** in the same
What
And I think
He is broke
Go to prison
Like and I think that is both something
He is jealous
As well as something
Sulphur
Send it
Place for him
So for him
Do an epic
He is watching
People become
Murder
In their own mind
In a real way
And bumped him out because he is a martyr
Steakway
But he's not getting
Exclusive with Joan Park so
His bottom line
Interested
He's concerned that no one's giving him credit for
You got arrested
I wouldn't
Come on the podcast doing emerge
Episode
Hey Jordans on the phone hey Jordan has gone
I've been doing interviews
F****** 40 minutes be like
No one is Rekha
Two Georges
But that's a weird impulse
It's a
Perfectly logical impulse
For their religion
Kinship as both of them being Psychopaths
Because Rodger
Was on the phone with
And then
F****** bailed I don't get no with no like Da Costa.
Baby
Alex's on errands
We should take
Mustang
Give me
He says hey donate to Rodger Stones legal defense fund
Twice
Infowars orbit
Million
And most the time to donate stones
Fundies also then
Into like we also
It's two parasites
Sucking off each other's stomachs
Untenable like unsustainable
Situation
I don't know we'll see what happens
We have done this episode with the amount of
Information we have at our disposal
Google Now
There will be more in
Information,
Future that may color some of this stuff but
For now we we
We've done
Will be back
But until your hand. Com
Lubbock
Thank you again.
Are we on face
Facebook we are there
Members there thank you guys so much
We're also on I-25
Download
God it's so many posts in the group have been
We started listening or I started list
Nothing from the beginning and now I'm losing my mind
Big Show
The Turbo Force of
It's too late in the episode to say this but yeah
Be careful with even our show
Employees is so toxic
Sick that even
Contact and all that
Humor
It's still if you listen to too much of it
It will be painful
Here's a here's what I would say
Do you think stone is kill the guy
No I don't know how man I feel like a
Strangle the dude
Or at least
I've been his lawyer Tyler Nixon
Anybody
Seems like
I think you may have taken the identity of the real time
The guy who are the Eisenhower grandson who married
But we can't prove it.
Gildedguy
That's Alex
Holding
I love your work