Just wanted to jump it with a
For this episode first stop
First piece of business
Two little bit of an apology
On the Rodger Stone being an indictment I apologize
It is a seven-count indictment
Mix that up
I had a little bit of a mix-up delivering information
Because the obstruction charge
And the witness tampering
DeSoto Blended
Tiny bit
Confused by that
Beyond that
We got episode here's the situation
We recorded this episode intended for it to be Monday's episode
Because of Rodger Stone business we had to
Here we are with a 2009 episode on Wednesday hoping no one is confused by that either
But
Because we got our days screwed up because this the world is crazy and Rodger Stone has trouble
Very special shout-out
I just someone out there to celebrate their birthday tomorrow
I hope you're having a great one out there
Address to send
Birthday messages out to you
So please accept on our behalf
Have a wonderful
23rd year here on this Earth
Let the episode of Rodger Stone
Eddie's on our part for that Rodger Stone
You all so much positive Stone episode now that I really do
Appreciate it
And
Holding
Alex
About Alex Jones High Jordan
What's the last time you heard of
You know those
Live comedy show in
Comedian
Sings A the theme from The Bodyguard but he puts
I can't think I can't think of any info
Listen to that I'm very glad that I haven't
I'm 37 years I blocked out
Things the only in Chicago
Songhai that I remember
Was the Iceman the Iceman open mics
He would sing a song called the best party ever
You know the song called the couch cows that I found really affect
Is lazy and not funny videos about being overweight girl on the couch
Worse than a fart song
That's as best I can do to fulfill your interview
But we can do
Is think some people who signed up
Next
James Garner
I'm a policy wonk
The group
There hasn't been a raptor princess
People
It's tough to become a specific about what that actually means
Barely intentionally so where you donate above this amount and then you get
I don't want it to be more of a spiritual thing
Above and beyond
What could be considered
Monetary gain
Like that
Tritonlink
I just know I feel like it's kind of shity of us to not be specific about what it requires
This person donated on it
The show we can call this Criterium at
Everybody wants to hear the drop so let's hear it
Someone someone
Set me a bucket of poop
Call Tori
Control
Abused
Joseph Stalin
Stop.
Welcome to McDonalds may I help you
Really dark
Click the button that says
Please do thank you so much
April 12th
Took me 10 minutes of listening to the show to realize oh this is the Chuck Norris interview I've already heard
You do it be really fun because we've seen so many times to do a present-day episode and then we go back into 2009 and itself
Hilarious
I don't know who this is Rodger Stone guys Rogers
Years after the point in 2009 that we're covering
Face on his back there's no way I would ever hang out with that guy
Keep this for me in the future if I ever
Rodger Stone
ABS this is actually I think it's going to be kind of fun
Maybe a little bit
The 13th is a nature
It always is nice to remind
People that on April 8th
Alex
Real hard on Soros
And then immediately started talking about how we like Somali pirates
What who knows
I'm so we find ourselves
You're on
The 12th is a Sunday
Monday
I'm kind of expecting to
Somali pirates
I-80
At least
Listen
Don't talk about tomorrow you can't be that guy hey man you might not have a grasp of the story
You should you should probably
Let It Go
On the 13th Alex
Somali pirate stuff because on the 12th
The story came to a head on that Sunday when he had the day off the best of episode
You should come in
Was not
One way or another either they car
Sort of Valerie kind of narrative words
Yeah that's okay we got this guy's free from the clutches of these terrorists
You expect something
Nothing
The day after Captain Phillips is freed
Nothing zero lose to though
What is it what
Even fighting again
You got
No real Soros talk to speak of
Nothing none of these trends
Continuing at all
Everything is just
Everyday Is Random it's like it's a different show
There's no sterilize aspect to it
There's very little continuity
Is it anything to the point where I was second-guessing myself on my
Did I miss label these episode is this from 2010
Or something like that
Double-check
Because it's so
Ingress but like I said Alex
Sunday off
On the 12th and comes in on the 30
Out of context
Very very relaxing actually have two full days off I didn't do
Any word
Saturday or Sunday
Well it's not really true I only did 45 hours a week
Research
Saturday night Sunday night but I don't really call that work so
Call Schiff
The cover today important broadcast
I'm just amazingly important news and information
Okay so I
No chance
I mean you did take 2 days off whatever Centro
Four to five hours of studying on your the f*** out of here Alex
F*** out of
So
What is
He starts off the show with
Is
Bird flu
Right but
It's confusing to me because the narrative hasn't developed at all
The exact same
That we heard any Baxter Pharmaceutical
Narrative that we heard
So here is Alex jumping back in
People dying
Bird flu in 18 countries mixed with the vaccine
Directions being injected with live Birds
That's why they got
Bird flu
Mixed with regular human
Fulbright
He's just hitting those same points about that story all over again
And if you recall much of the information about the story was based on
Supposed there was written by Paul Joseph Watson
On Infowars
Why not just keep
Likes o this is
They have dipped
Talk about it
Backup
Like a timeline
Just doesn't
To be relevant
Russia
Mystery Theater
On PBS
Research Saturday
Play on the backyard
Play in the sandbox
Playing with cars on the floor
All sorts of evil things like that
My family going up my email
So he's responding a defensive about someone
Bring up got to bring back up
Is actively working for the opposition
Not talking about it
Absolutely negotiates with
Trolls
Of The Message Board variety
Alex can trace back where this criticism
From
It's another
Gcn talk show
Okay let me look at it
So I sit there
And I listen to it
Call radio show
And I
Find talk show host
Is Mark Marek
You're that lady for calling from New York
Freaking out
1 800 2599 231
What's your address
She says
Oh my gosh
There's a truck driver he Spanish
These silos
From Spain
And it's delivered
And
Department
And you listen to it and I just know what's real I know it's not.
Another Genesis
Communications Network show got a collar lesbeth
Extravagant
Bird flu conspiracy theory
And Alex demonstrates pretty clearly
To engage in critical thinking what he wants to that is a little bit of a towel
Number of people
The show and heard this caller
Believe
Theory is Alex of covering up this stuff
So this leads to about a 40-minute chunk of Alex's show where he's super defensive about that
I do however
FedEx
He had no f******
Conspiracy theorist
I've no idea what was going to go down
Could imagine
In the
Find a word I can mispronounce
Emagine
About listening
To Alex playing that caller
He doesn't really have much analysis other nuts
And does you wrong and I know that
I know but my version of stuff is the right version
And so it's
The fry on this
You're lying
These disease silos or whatever
You know you didn't mean
From Spain mean from Spain
You didn't mean
A Spanish man
There's bigger fish to fry
But before we get to those big fish
We need to know what we need to know once
Something I don't know I don't know if we
I have ever considered
This way but Alex
About to tell us why he's successful
I'm successful
In reaching people on this radio show
Hyperventilating isn't reason I'm successful myfreec hasn't reason I'm successful no it's because
What can be proved
Bulshit
Bat
Is a
F******
Only focus on what
That's unfair rude
Nothing to say
Especially so strike and force
You can't be that can
Convinced of the thing you know
You're not doing yeah it is weird especially where this episodes going
To go like
Report
Can't prove
From Alex Jones his entire career there was Sable
This episode
I'm and he brings up one of them
He can't prove anything you saying about that
Homeland Security documents
Read the document in about 20 minutes
And I was sure it was real because paragraph
New realm
Dafont
100 series of federal control numbers I've seen on documents
But I went ahead and emails I went ahead and called
I went ahead and called the
Infrastructure protection Fusion Center numbers on it
Talk to the watch captains that I had it
Broken the last 12 hours
Classic Tech
I could we want to wear
Superman
So two narratives on the show
Both of them have been the result of people bullying
Which isn't good that doesn't seem like a good way to go about
I'm so there's a DHS Department of Health
Security.
Is reporting on
These folks and he's proven that it's real
Looking for this next clip and then I'll address that
Call the FBI phone numbers confirm
Yes
In Missouri and talk to him and I said yeah that's our report
Are you noticing anything that seems really strange about the way he's speaking
Infrastructure Fusion
Things about
Yeah I would like to know more about that
Call the FBI
Exist
Department of Justice
Which is a separate government body
From the Department of Homeland
Insecurities
Actually have phone numbers on
But they're all dhs.gov
Email addresses not FBI email addresses
The FBI doesn't factor into this at all the only place the FBI comes up is
Is in a footnote
The desert people should report potential terrorist activity
DHHS FBI and says the FBI's phone numbers can be found on the FBI's website
Alex is clearly just making s*** up
Female bows
Those those addresses that's entirely possible
But that you could not have called the FBI
From this document
Actually just to correct myself a little bit
There are some numbers for
DHHS
In that footnote about call them
So there are those phone numbers
Was more that I'm making is that Alex
He's staying
He called the FBI and that's absurd
I wonder if you could like
Google Hangout
With the DHHS
Baby eats one of those email addresses
Actually has
I don't know in 2009 probably.
So you might be asking yourself
Alex's confirm by calling the FBI
Whatever
You guys know this document
Sure Alex go the f*** away
What
What is it about
And I have confirmed its authenticity
And
.
Hardcore
Off-the-charts long pause hardcore
What do you know Alex Jones is editorial line is backed up by
Secret document that's been released isn't that amazing
Every single thing you find evidence that the government people with guns it's strange
Knows how to read
Turns out he's not a reliable source
Let's just
So if it's a little bit more about this
You are the number one federal government
That's what
Document number 18-025 7-0 999
And you can call the FBI up right now note is there.
It's not their document why would you call the FBI
DHHS
Report
Is called
Current economic and political climate fueling resurgence radicalization
And it's not a document or anything
Sing like that
It's definitely a real document is for official use only
Which of the designation
Documents that the relevant
Government
Have a reasonable expectation
What cause harm to an ongoing effort should the information
He made public
You can think of it as something akin to like an interdepartmental equivalent of like
Attorney client privilege
This document is any bird sitters then Alex's take on the miac report
But it's
In both cases Alex's mystery document
It's not to describe legitimately dangerous militia and extremist activities
And because a lot of it is stuff he's pretty models description
He gets defensive and screams about how the document is secretly about him
It's not
There's nothing in this document
To suggest that the authors of this reports American
As their main enemy
For fucksake literally says quote
Both right-wing extremists and law-abiding citizen shareablee that Rising rates
Make the purchase of legitimate Firearms a wise move at this time
That's a weird thing for people looking to demonize gun ownership to say
Legitimate firearm
Law Abiding Citizen
That's not that's not what gun
Demonize others would say
Mysteriously that passage is absurd
From all reports
The strongest statement the document makes
About Gunn
Is this
And I think it's a measured and reasonable stay
Weapons rights and gun control legislation are likely to be hotly contested
Subjective
In light of the 2000s
Court decision
In. DC vs. Heller
Which in which the court reaffirmed the individuals rights
Keep and bear arms under the Second Amendment to the US Constitution
But left open the debate the precise Contours of that right
Because debates over constitutional rights are in
Deeply-held some
Fear but vastly the Virgin beliefs
Violent extremists
May attempt
The Coop use the controversy
Happy as a radicalization
That is very
Correct
Not
Editorialize
On my way
This report also could have been called
I think a good name for it would have been
There's a black president these ships
Are going crazy
Well let's keep an eye on it
Everybody's buying gun
Because everybody's going crazy
There's a piece of that in terms of the
The stuff in the
This document that motivates
But it's important to point out that this does not mean in any way that they're applying to Alex or anyone who shares that world you are terrorists
Or even extreme
I would put it to you this way
I believe strongly in animal rights
Which is a position that I share with groups like the animal Liberation Front
If I were to report about how extremist for animal rights believe that animals shouldn't
Be tested on
I wouldn't think that apply to me just because I agree that animals shouldn't
Is very Elementary stop in the idea that Alex
Not to get it could be seen as proof that he's dumb as a rock
But he's not
It's very clear.
To create the image
A repressive government
It's going to turn on the noble white gun-owning Christian anytime now
He's doing this because he needs to
Create an anime
Fruit
Which is ironically a large
Part of what this report is about
Using the threat of the government
Guns as an Avenue to radicalized
Well not necessarily in the case of Alex
Info Warrior fold where you just give Alex money
This report is
About Alex
Because here's the deal
Sorry I didn't mean to interrupt you based on his response
It says that right-wing extremists are using fears of illegal immigration
Radicalized
But it also goes on in April 2007 6 militia members
We're rested
For various weapons and explosives violation
1 open source reporting
Alleged
Conducted surveillance for a machine gun attack on
Hispanic
The report says that fears about the election of the first a
Can American president were being used by extreme
But it then says that it's talking about things like how quotes
Intuit
In the run-up to the
Extremist appear to be in the early planning stages of some threatening activity targeting the Democratic nominee
But law enforcement intercede
You can be a racist gun-loving New World Order figurine Christian identitarian
And the Department of Homeland Security is not going
What to give a f*** about you
They start caring when you start committing
And planning terrorist
The text and that's what this report is about
Alex isn't doing that he shouldn't take it personally
The fact that he does take it so personally
If 6th grade so much drama about this
Kind of leaves me with a science
But he identifies with and supports the goals
Of terrorists
Status report
Is actually about
Because I was about to say that I feel like one of the big reasons that
Feels like they are talking about
Just a regular gun-owning the America
We keep going back to
Like
Every time he has one of these new document proves all of his
His b*******
About how the government
Stop anyone who has a right Lena
Every single time we just get more and more indication
It's like it's about you Alex
And because of your response
You're clearly indicating that
You identify with
These like it's very clear as you read the document it's not about like a blowhard on a radio show
It's not about johnny-come-lately who's got a gun
They don't give a fuk
Militia members
Of which Alex they don't even care about militia members they care about militia
Remembers that planned violent attack
It's clear
It is very
Very clear
The report is specifically about people who plans Island
If you don't plans Island
And you're not
In some kind of
Violent group
Then
You know you shouldn't be
Offended
In fact I think you have a greater
Impotent to support this report
Because you don't want those violent people watering up your movement
If you legitimately believe
All of the things
Malicious
Armed Rebellion against the United States
Their existence
Kind of hurt
You
You would say
Yeah you would think
What was the what
Supreme Court case was it
Use the Second Amendment to protect their right to
Plan violence
That's just free speech dantos DC vs. Heller
Love that too fast
Stop it for now but I assure you we will get back
Gets distracted
Mr. crappie describes what the globalist
Ideal
That situation that there were
Working
If you listen to this I think
Familiarity
Understand what the setting up here
Highly controlled
Government
In private corporate reservations
They're called shroud of National Security
Outside
Highly controlled
Compact City
Private manners
Plantation
Outside
Image of Allstate
Don't have it yet
They're very close
Be afraid but
He always strikes
Those are whatever
Okay if you're talkin are you trying to describe
Is that what he's doing
I don't think he's describing
Is anything different
The situation
Living in isolated
Nice
Manners and then everybody else
Struggling to survive
But he's kind of talking about the real world but
Justin
Like
Distorted and twisted
Crazy-house mirror
He's talking about something real
That is a huge problem
And yet
He is defending the people
Who have created that problem as being
Perfect
Was there the middle class
Compare to the globalist
Okay fair enough that's kind of how he looks
Documentary
Days off
It wasn't
This weekend
America
About the Reverend Moon
Crazy
Alex has seen a documentary about Reverend Sun Myung Moon
I knew you liked that guy is crazy
Is the Washington f****** time that is owned by The Moody
That's ridiculous
He was referencing a documentary about the guy from San Francisco 100 years ago
He's also not talking about the gentleman
Columbia Missouri
When I was growing up there
Because he wouldn't stop bothering people downtown crown
Yeah I recognized massage
We need to have a cool looking
And it doesn't get worse over in that a Burger King
Hilarious that Alex
Can see that's crazy
But can't recognize them
He gets a lot of his information
We've been looking at the
Tea party stuff
Yeah in the course of
Completely forgot we were looking at a party stuff
I forgot about the questions kind of an answer
Actually I think we might
Be about done with
The band
I still think there's a lot of interesting stuff going on we see these like
Real formative block cehs
Support is really important
My acropora is really important
Slimes are the bird flu narrative
It really important to Alex's
Like
He builds
From here
Seneca's Value Inn
We set out to figure out when you started talking about George Soros
We found that April 8th
2009 episode
And then going to be awhile till we get back to it
I don't think they do
Yeah
I don't
I from the episodes that I've listened to after it I don't think
Like he was in a mood that day or something like that I don't know exactly what's going on
But I feel kind of resolved about like
When it started when it's flared up
And then secondarily the other question was
You know when did he get on board with
Tea Party
I think based on the factory cini's interviews with Stewart Road
The Oath Keepers guy
I hate glad back
Stop
Starting to feed exactly what happened there
Mystery
He decided
Large groups
You're close enough to his beliefs
Go f*** with them
The straight up
What kind of answer
I believe I do remember this reading this new story on April 8th
At around
AIDS
George Soros did cut off Alex
How old is Dory
So
When I say that I think we kind of answer the question about the
Tea party it also involves
The clips that were about to
Can I take this kind of made my mind up
This is this is what's going on
So you get the call from a guy
Who is in San Antonio
Hattie's
You got the news about the San Antonio Tea Party
Coming up
Matthew in Texas
Hey God bless you like this is Matthew from San Antonio change reported in
Creepy party update
Okay
1023 parties basically saying because
They don't want Alex Jones here
And they said
What do I got to do for creditor group and he's basically getting Intel for us
Didn't want any bull horns
Because they're troublemakers there anybody with a bullhorn
Is the troublemaker
Nannying or so Freedom will just have your own
Fox News and Glenn Beck are trying to take over the
Tea Party
Alex Jones
Is now
Taking ownership
In retrospect
Yeah
Yeah that's what he's already here in April 2009
What does the Fox News and Glenn Beck
Bright literally
Another thing to say about the
Notice how they're trying to take over
Show up at
You gotta love it
That
Piano
The tea party was large
Ashley AstroTurf
Fun
Forgiving them
Tons of money
Freedomworks and Americans
Prosperity
They came from
In the group citizens
Without a condom
Their first chairman
Was Ron Paul
It was funded by the Koch brothers
Citizens First sound economy
Had registered a tea party website
A 2002
They already had some sort of plans of trying to
To do something like this
Before
But the climate wasn't
Right there wasn't the ability to
To make these
These things
Make it make it a real
There is no reason to believe that
The idea that Ron Paul is behind the
Real tea party
Glenn Beck
And his Coke funding through forget works is behind the real Noah's Ark
Contradictory
They're exactly the same
This Is The Life in the right-hand basically
Absolutely
It's interesting
To see cuz I
To know if I understand
Finding out
If he asks
He knows that
Is the Koch brothers
Who's funding the entire
Or if he thinks it is inorganic I find I find this fascinating
Because
I mean what you what you got a movement that Alex thinks is being taken over by Glenn Beck
Not recognizing
Find it
Alex
Want
To take ownership of it
So he is
Free dating
His check
He's like
To make it look like he bought this before
The first party was on the 27th of February
And we've been going over it since then
When that happened
What it was
You did back then
Koch brothers knew what it was
So
I don't know I don't know what this means other than like
There's no mystery to me anymore
Alex just believe he's the true version of it
That's about it
It's not if there's no there's no mystery
Left in their Tea Party
Part of
Open the app
San Antonio
Okay
I didn't ask for updates
S***
Why are you giving me an update let alone that
The color is like we've infiltrated
Retro meeting infiltrated it cover
Federate flag
Whatever
Complaints about Glenn Beck
Stealing his movement movement
He also thinks
Contact
I mean I feel like I'm
You're about to say something
What
Which one
You are the fake mini charm
That these are people to watch these are people in the back
And
You got to find any man really got to stop saying fake mini charm either like it means something what does that even mean
I just hate
Fix that he's not sincere
That's part of it threatened by because it's not masculine
And he labels that
Yeah
How do you say Mini
That many times.
You know you know what you're trying to say but you don't want to say
Exactly
Answer in the next clip Alex.
He makes clear
Orgone
And you support Glenn Beck
No
Michelle
Because in Texas
Fort Worth
And how they work
I mean
This is this is where they castrate
I think I know what William Travis would have said
That's probably a big part of this big old drunk
Right left her with child because I was wanted by the police
Want to go to prison
Ended up
Running a militia at the Alamo
Cardi B quotes
So if you support Glenn Beck
You go to this event going to get two balls chopped off whatever that whatever that is
Questions
I think it is just a matter of
Thinking Glenn Beck stole his s***
I want to get back
And the BMV more extreme version
By virtue of Association
More with yolk
Keepers then
Tea party 912
Middle-of-the-road
You can hear it here
Website backup
Against the private Bankers there looting and rioting
Which is very popular right now
What's the truth
Weird
A good guy
It's the
I think it was on one of our recent episodes feel like it's going to be such a bummer if the answer to this is
Team sports
It wasn't about the Tea Party but turns out in terms of
Edwards
It was
Bulshit was that organic or were they also fun
I'm sure they got some
I don't know enough
That's that
I started this thing
Being on Alex's show as the
Alternative the more militant alternative
I bet also being accepted
So I think there's a possibility
She served as like a middle ground
And that led to what
Membership rolls
And then along with that financing
I have no idea I don't I don't know entirely
It was entirely organ
Yeah that's probably
OrganiCann
Apps
Salute like it was
It does seem like the tea party was
Fully financed
Tea party. Blogspot.com
I didn't want to buy it
Which
You're not the only reason you wouldn't do that is if you couldn't
Yeah
The cash to throw into
So
At this point Alex jump
Back to the
DHS report
He has Naomi wolf on for an interview
Considering she's a democratic
Strategist
Advisor
Contentious
Yeah that's what I'm not working
She's like in the middle of a sentence
What's going on
Answer the quarterback on the phone and then
I can't hear you at all you could hear her saying I'm really sorry I can't hear you
It's okay if it doesn't work interview m
Nothing happening
They even have like how much
Talking to they actually do
And that was it
It was more
Friendly then
Expect
Add a little bit of that is because a lot of position she was
The table that were critical of Obama
Slipknot
At this point
April 2009
You know you been in office a month or two and she had
Some of the similar complaints
Alex
Getting rid of stye
Choose choose coming from
The centre-left
I guess making those Critters
I think you could have been an interesting conversation and actually kind of dip
Interesting to see how that dynamic
Play doubt
We could just get a f****** broken phone
It's one of them it's like a similar conversation to what I would have with
I would imagine
I'm criticizing Obama for fake
And I'm like
I'm just criticizing him
I'm for real thing
The our disagreement comes. From
He is deserving
But that your credit
Or even I don't know if your family be on this side but I think
To this would be
Is
Make the same criticism
As a legitimate
And then the other side
Is exploiting
And using
Basis
Extrapolate into irresponsible Ludacris
I kind of think that's
I think it's really in
Interesting because of
Superficial agree
They would have probably both of Tears through like
Oh Alex
No do not hold on because the f****** phone broke
The reality of a conversation
My family would be there arguing
Ridiculous s***
Because there is a receipt
The best
Criticism
Things that are you are
Bingo
Difference between arguing Ludacris things in good faith versus arguing
I don't know
Will never know
Maybe until she comes back a week from now
I don't know
Tooth is DHS document
It's interesting to hear him try and discuss this be
Because he's just lying about ever
Like legitimately
Even lying about what's in the tech
Vale
It's about races
This is the election of the first African-American president
Unique
Drivers for right-wing radicals ation in
Recruitment
They're not applying everybody's races
That's not what that sentence means at all
On its face you can understand that
At the beginning of a clip you said this is inspection to you
Every paragraph start
With you dash dash
Ouo
That's the designation
Fouo means for official use only
You mean
Unclassified
Hid the fact that he's saying this is infection you
It doesn't understand that they you before the paragraph means unclassified
It doesn't realize that all the paragraphs
It leads me to believe that he doesn't have as much experience reading documents
As he claims to the fact that he says I can read this
I can look I spend all my time the last 20 years reading these secret official document and I'm
That I understand what they're saying when it's not literally what they're saying I can read between the lines
Do-Re-Mi
This is pathetic
Yeah that's
No
Alex
Flexion
He is right
They are all section
Trying to say this is the part of the document at the yeah
I don't help you with that at all
Crazy
Brazy
And I don't have experience
Like secret government document
I don't I can't trust
I just was like
If you did have experience really secret government documents you wouldn't you wouldn't be able to tell me I believe that you do
Experience
Secret government.
I believe this is an entirely controlled opposition
Situation you are funded fully by the government
This is all a
The wish
You could walk out of here
Angle
You're fully furnished
I don't actually live where is bag of chips
Sitting on my deck clearly from Iran your wallet is February
Sorry 2017
What else could that mean if your a secret government operative
Real for Kootenai the wall calendars are in effect
Possibility in February 2017 Diane aspirations
The organization
Because it is
Indication of him not having
The Bona fides
Pretends to have been willing to believe that
Read a bunch of
Unclassified Declassified
Stuff like that like I didn't understand what he was reading or he was just making up stuff about them as read them
But that's beyond
Anybody listening
Who actually does understand any of this stuff should also be like
Oh no
Alex
You just gave it up
You just you just indicated that you don't know what you're talkin
And about
Government
It also makes it hard
Makes it hard for me to believe
Anybody who
He's in the military
Or anything like that or in intelligence
Anybody who is in those fields
Isn't motivated to support Alex
Based on his
I don't understand
He's a credible source
In terms of like facts
Information
There are government
With section
Sections you if you will
So I would invite you to read this document
Every single paragraph
But if you had not read this
In particular
You would be fine with him saying sexy
Norwood
Oh okay
Arbiter
No it doesn't work
It would work
I understand what you're saying
Let him off the hook
It's an excuse
Listeners who haven't read this.
Particular
I think it's just an indication that anyone who believes that he knows what he's talking about
What he's talking about
So in the next flight
Alex talks about the idea
Dhs.gov
Right-wing extremist have capitalized on the election the first American American president Republican efforts on
To recruit new members
Mobilize against tyranny
And rodner stubborn appealed and propaganda
Attack plan
Real quick it doesn't list Mainline ghungroo
It doesn't list groups at all
That's not in the document at 11 list an email
Nothing else know it doesn't is it especially not after that paragraph
Call
About like these people this group of six people
Machine gun
That's a group of people
Right
It would come
Concern me if Alex
Consider that a Mainline ghungroo
I mean it
Did you save that
Cuz he hasn't read the document
It sort of leads you to believe that that's the point
Is f****** shity
I meant secondarily
This is a
About
Violent
Not middle-of-the-road people who like guns that are conserved
That is not what this is
Twisted in adults
The fact that I was
Does responding to his like saying
These violent groups are using
The first African-American president existing
As a source of radicalization
And he says
Supposed to recruit
Alex
You're supposed to mobilize is also what
Weekend
The little bit
DHHS
Doesn't actually
Do the research into the Tea Party
Movements
These propagandists are using a president
But when they say like these
These propagandist are using a black
Recruit
And do all that stuff
You'd almost hope they were like
Any propaganda serve paid by the cobra
You know like
The Koch brothers are there
Reason that these propaganda
Do all this
Like if the DHS
None of the law-enforcement groups are at all willing to
2.2
So much of this being the result of
Those two f****** billionaire
And other people too
Conservative
Foundation
Becomes shorthand
But the Koch brothers
And I think that's kind of wrong but it's the primary funders of
Sentence for sound
And Americans for Prosperity
Which were the biggest funders of
Like
Foster the
The only super rich
Right-wing people
Find it
With the amount of dark money that they filter through all of
Different nonprofit
Which again
Wow
We should
Really
I don't know laws
Goodnight
Mainline gun
Advocating
For the thing that this group is
Report
Because he hasn't read it or possibly
Because
Underlying
Anticipation of restrictions in Van
The primary concern
The primary concern is the fact that you're buying that everybody by
Their primary concern law enforcement guns and ammo
I did not at all with reports
It says
Right-wing extremist
Our stockpile
Klingons
That part is absolutely true
It says it is 80 Prime
Concern the primary concern
And I.
Like to live in a world wasn't the primary concern
Really paranoid
Violently anti-government
They're stockpiling weapons
Guys
Look over there
I think that's an important thing
For people to know about
Especially people who are trying to keep
Everybody send them a cop
Oh no
Broken into alive ring
Name check
Seattle
And then at no point does it say that
No point does it say that
Gone
Bad or suspicious
Send
Are the paragraph where they're talking about
Citizens owning legit
That's very clearly not anti-gun
Alex
Wheatley lying
They say he's racist
They don't say that at all
That is not
Been there no but it does sound like Alex's
Responding to the
The fact that say they say that
The black president
Used as a propaganda tool for
Recruit as them
Specifically pointing out that
He is afraid of a black
And is using
And so he has to be like
Now they're calling me a racist
They're definitely not calling me an opportunist
Right right
Goes back to my
It goes back to my first like my primary conviction
The only thing that is
Response to it
The only way in which this
This report is about him
Is how he is behaving
He makes it about him
If you if you saw this before in your life
Move Along
Hey guys there are people within our communities
That are giving us a bad name
Do we need to be on the
Lookout Ford
Or anything like that but
Hey
We need to do better within our communities
Whatever
That would be a fitting response
Defending
Deflecting
Lion
He's a lying about this report
In order to suit his
The government is your enemy
Rhetoric
That behavior
Is suspicious
It's pretty suspicious
Yeah
I would also probably
Under the category of like
Why are they talking about
Whether it's a specific person or just spiritually
Self-defense
Specs of it
I'm trying to make sure that
He's never seen
Is advocating violence
Exactly
We are still fresh off the Pittsburgh
So that's true
Depends on the show
Though it is mansion
Articles
Forbes.com
They talked about how
This
Incident is in this report
People have tied Alex to this report are go
This report is about Alex
But the report doesn't mention Alex it doesn't mention
That's something you have to
To bring to the report
You have to
The thing about
Doing this serialized over
We do a 2009 Epic
It's easy to forget
The context within which he is
Acting so petty
Twozies
Is reading that email at
React
Think so
F******
What
You mean this report
No they email
The people saying that he's not
About the Pittsburgh
Singing people timer
He's on that red alert
I got to be making sure that
People don't think that I'm
Attached
Whatever it is
Yeah I know and controlling my own narrative
I think I fixed it
I think that's a
Probably small
The bulk of
You knows that
This is going to be a really affect
Active
Is the government
And make it look like
For you
Which works out
Reinforce
Bolster the other narratives
I think that's mostly what it is
That on this next
Historical presidential election
Social programs and Firearms restrictions
Bring the policies of Barack Obama is also they're saying
The terrorist
It goes on to say
You see that
Twisted
That's indicative of I'm going to
Use this however I can
Which is not
Most of the report
What do you want
Doesn't say
Merit all right
That clip
Is like
It does not matter what
Headset
No.
It doesn't matter
It doesn't matter mentioned Ron Paul
As being like we found a guy who said Ron
Paul's name
He would have
We don't want to sell knives and even like to see this is the first step in them,
Right
They think that it's wrong
Outlaw knives tomorrow it's gone
Yeah
It doesn't matter what
Just going to use it as a prop
This DHS report was written by a guy named Darrell Johnson previously spent 15 years studying domestic terrorism
He compiled data create a new databases
The track correlation
Automatic Neo-Nazi and white supremacist groups
4 years Hammer drop,
2000's backlash
The DHHS cave and ended up refudiate in the
Report
In April 2010 DHHS dissolve Johnson answered the security
Consultancy business
Unsurprisingly as the threat of right-wing extremism is grown
From 2012 onwards
Constantly been interviewed by places like
The Washington Post
About how we tried to warn people listen
They're too focused on Islamic terrorism
And two willing to bow down
Coordinated right-wing media pressure
To do their job
Not much else is there to say about this other than the exact Behavior demonstrated by Alex in this episode
Is directly traceable
The weakening the government's ability
To deal with violent extremist
Because his feelings
He's got hurt
That is all of its manifest
If you read interviews with Daryl Johnson
Inside a number
He talks about how like back then there were so many more people studying
Tracking
Islamic terrorism
That was working on
The non-islamic the message
Snowman after if
Immigration
You know of this report that he
He put out the backlash that came from it
You get to April
And now there's just one guy
Who's working
For the DHS on that
Tire world
Of the non-islamic
Rite-Way interview it's gone up a little bit but I'll be surprised
If it has
Considering we've had an increase in domestic
Terrorist
Domestic terrorism and hate crimes
And all that s***
Recently increase the air they increase the size of it
Yeah maybe they did
But the people who run the tahs Earth
All of these tools and
You had come up with within the DHHS
Tracking
Understanding the service of a solvent
Yeah we're all
His career
Just like the printer in office space
Completely ineffective now
Is it
One of them was
Particular
Shooting spree
Lone Wolf
Shooter
You know that the stuff
Is important
Pay attention
But even if nothing
I don't think we could have done it
Anything about this guy
Yeah
When I hear something like that from someone who studies
I just hear
Expert
You know I hear a sincere voice right because someone who's trying to run a con
Or someone who has bad faith
Position
If they're being interviewed after the fact about how right they were
And we're shut down because they were right
They would lionize everything they wouldn't have even in perfect
Situation if nothing happened
This guy probably would have slipped through
Crack because there's no way to track
Attached to any
Or anything like that that's humility that's humble
If it were Alex in that situation
Giving an interview about how
He would have said
If implemented with this guy would never have happened
What would matter if that was anywhere near true
But just by
That's not just Alex oh that's so many
Also people
Experts on
Over-promise in a hypothetical path
You know you like you have like if this had happened
Some sort of counter-factual
Tractor
Resist that impulse
Because he knows what he's talkin
About
Johnson
The real sad
Picture of it is real sad
To think about how much that really did
End up causing
Crippling of tracking
Right wing
Extreme nationalist
Supremacist
Neo-nazis and that's everything
And the fact that Alex Jones
Was
A part of the backlash
That led to that
What are you doing this facilitating all of this right-wing terrorism
That we've seen
In in the last
Yeah it's really it
It's really weird it's hard to say if there's intention behind it but
I don't really care
I think something that is kind of fascinating about that
Is that Obama
Who was
At a disadvantage
While trying to
While trying to kind of
Tackle Vista
Would appear so much worse than
Saying we need to follow up on me
Because because you're more like
More at a disadvantage in trying to tackle terrorism
Because he's black
In the court of public opinion
Absolutely
But here in the sex with Alex gets back to talk about Glenn Beck
Because a collar brought about
The powers-that-be
Glenn Beck
Trey's the Patriots
For thirty pieces of silver
Because everytime I remind me to something I remember
Of the truth
Victims family
He hates the Patriot movement he hates malicious
He hates gun owners
We love you we love you Vic
Co-op
So we can destroy
Absolutely
Cargo head
Came up
That literally happened
That literally happened I was hoping update on the San Antonio
I was really hoping
5 times in a row
Hey just wanted to give you another update the Tea Party is about an hour in
Still in bed over here yet
Where was this at
Back in a bit
Here is Alex
Just would have reinforcing my position that I think
Just realize that
We could exploit
Tea Party
He realizes
That it's a
Perfect way for him to get his documentary The Obama Deception out into the world
But not just there
Obama Deception
This film is about the bankers Financial
And this film
Needs to be seen by everyone
That supports the radio show
Really is effective as Aaron on Access TV
Make copies of it giving it to people
Filmmaker
Future film
You see their MBA
Just Junk
It is
You can get
And go out and give
The people at the party
Spare the dumb people they're literally the ones that we are recruiting
Using anti-propaganda
Right
And they'll be all congregated in
In person
In physical reality go and give them copies and DVDs
Wake up
So I thought the VHS
Report was going to be
In terms of like
Alex
Specific
His narrative
But I call or calls
Sort of
Not aggressive
But he's just doesn't know what Alex's narrative about the mass Graves
Bizarre
Mass graves are piece of Alex's narratives
About
There's he's like there's all these last two coffins.
You go in Bullet to the Head
I am so just call her ask
Where's that mass grave stuff
Coming from
More like
Hissed off
Staff to answer this question
How many does a really bad job
Man I presented you with mainstream news about the mass Graves incinerator
Did you hear me
Unfortunately I did not
Well we written articles about it and post
Let me just show you again
I just had
Over and over and over and over
My job
Bring it up again
Imma show it to you again
Masquerade folder
Always listen
Going to fold is it Manila
Prepares for bioterrorism February 8th 2003
The state of Colorado
Extreme circumstances
For the use the event bioterrorism attack
When it goes into the governor's managers
The mass grave site
Generators
And how they're getting ready for that
Point of order
It doesn't go in
Governor's orders all that stuff is Alex make
Really lame
April 2009
But the government is planning a mass casualty
Is it there was an article in the Rocky Mountain X from 6 years prior
Is that 27
Then this article better literally about the government agent a mass casualty event
Put that these graves are for
You think that's what this article is about very small folder
The story about it all
This one is really hard to find the actual article
It's reference repeatedly and Infowars articles
Always citing the same quote that I was just
That's all
I found that I took that link and the quote
Search for it
Wet through bunch of nonsense
Website
And ultimately I traced down in Arizona with a Blog
Who actually links to the real article that I can take that
Internet archives and find the article
If you do read this article about you
But make it clear
Why Alex doesn't
To the whole article or what anybody
The first thing is that this has nothing to do with the federal government
It's all about the governor of Colorado at the series of eight
Executive orders regarding emergency prepared
Alex certainly isn't against the idea of having a planet
In case things go bad I mean
Any cell survival food
His problem is that he thinks the federal government in
FEMA are evil
I fixed it states rights are Paramount
Nothing in the story should have said that's
Sensibility FEMA isn't involved
It's all about the state
Government
What are the orders
Specifically talks about State healthcare workers being allowed to come and do your drugs from Pharmacy
In the case of an emergency
Lays out the rationale that
The federal government
Provide those drugs
Button emergency
People on the ground can't wait for any possible delay
These pharmacies be conference
Of course
Three of the remaining seven orders had to do with suspending licensing
Emergency workers could prescribe medications in
In a crisis
Something that would be allowed in Normal
Alex hates regulations and chiropractor friend doctor should be able to prescribe meds
So I don't see what his problem
What are the remaining four orders makes it so an emergency
Emergency rooms
To be able to turn away patients
Something that is a
Lauren Colorado under normal conditions
The reasoning is that in a biological attack
Or something like that
Emergency medical station
Will be set up
Patient will be processed and appropriate hospital to avoid making the situation
Again I feel like Alex as a Libertarian
Should be totally cool with the idea of hospitals being able to turn people away since they shouldn't be forced into helping anybody
That is libertarian principles
I don't know what his problem is
What are the last three orders makes it so mental health patients could be kicked out of their beds
In hospitals to make room for biochemical attack
This TV
I kind of understand the reason
I would hope they wouldn't just throw mental health patients into the street
But who knows
It doesn't specify what the process would be
Anything like that
Drawn carts
Is that they would just
I mean in a legitimate emergency
Someone
Who
Deserves care
For mental health condition
I understand why you would
Would you prioritize that
People who possibly are suffering from
Biological
I'll tell you what reason to get him out of there because everybody else in the hospital is Ben
Biological that's another reason
That's a really good angle on it
The last two of the orders are about easing by Burial and funeral
Regulation
To accommodate possibility that there were
Would be tons of body
The short time and some of the red tape could get in the way
Things like
The family of prison
By law they have to
Sign off
On how they're buried
Stuff like that
Be a time that you don't have
Yeah in the virgin
The difficulty of figuring out the
Your family you might end up spreading
Something
So often it's like
Look unfortunately we're going to have to burn these bodies
Germs are still there
It's horrible to think about but the situation that they're talking about is like
Real
F****** Siri
You put your brain into like
Ebola outbreak Airborne Ebola outbreak in America
And if it really sucks.
Control of the burial process
But
It's an existential crisis
It's very much like look I get in the
During the Black Plague
Gets like
We still need
To give them a religious burial in your like now you got a burn that chick cuz everybody you know is going to die that's exactly the point is going to
Get to is it like weed
Like a dead body that could be infected
Public Health crisis
We learned that
A few years back
Thousand years ago whenever people were
Catapult in order to spread
Exactly
And so
It sucks
But even here's a quote
I don't want to come across as saying the state's going to make this decision to do Mass cremations in ruin the lives of families
Marquette prison program coordinator for the state
Department set
But it
Executive order just gives up maximum Flex
Stability
So he's even saying like I I don't like this
I really
Really
Really hope
That we even in a biological crisis
We don't have to do it
Right
Like
This is only if it gets
The most worth
These executive orders have never been
And if you look on colorado.gov you can find the list of Governor Bill Owens executive orders
It doesn't even look like he's wherever sign
I don't know for sure
I don't know for sure but from what I can tell this was a series of executive orders that were written up his draft
And Governor Owens didn't signs
I could be wrong but I can't find any evidence that they were anything more than these draft
And the article Alex is referencing even says quote
Executive orders yet and there's a good chance they'll never be
This is not even just
Like we've signed this
Into
Route 8 in Toulon now
This is
Should
This happen
We will sign
We have these executive orders ready Eggman acts much like Alex
Another week in order to draft
Something I think it's possible or it could be just that they
I don't know
I don't know exactly what happened
You're two of
Billowing
Governorship looked at all of the executive orders
Most of them
Here's the new guy who's the Secretary of about looks
I didn't find anything
There was the weird one where you signed into
Borders was that
Dubstep was the new Nash
National weird 1004
So crazy little broad for Colorado to prep these executive orders
The things that they're talking
Extreme aversion
But you also need to
To keep in mind
Anthrax
Android app for war in Iraq
I don't think it's for a person who's responsible for the safety
Tires
To consider what the best way to address a possible emergency would be
Ahead of
And that's really all this is
Especially since their talk
Think about a
Which would
Of course be more associate
Going to put troops on the ground that's not going to happen
But
They can slip a terrorist in who's going to release a biological weapon we have that we have the
Gift of hindsight, we can laugh about like
Isn't it isn't it crazy that sort of dirty bomb is coming
But
Whether everybody did or not I'm sure there were some people some
Commentators who like
You guys are over exaggerate your dad you're being hysterical
But I don't correct for someone who
Possibility for
An entire States population governor.
Ears on them
Play many ways to help
Protect the safety
Of people from things that people shouldn't have to worry about
So
I get
Exaggerating
Little propaganda
Kind of crack
These sorts of things are
This idea of preparation
YouTube orders this Rocky Mountain Times article that Alex is referencing
I don't I don't see anything wrong with it I only see how it's like
Yep that's it
Yep
No disagreements here
So you then goes on to talk about another piece
Lisa Babbitt empty house about Mass Graves
It's not good either
Could you call the phone number
Article written by Aaron Dykes plan for Mass Graves confirm government surveying Cemetery Readiness for flu outbreak
Country
Tens of thousands per Cemetery
Phone number to call the state
Boring
No one video no one will discuss
No one will get into it
They won't because it's b*******
I mean this is a real doctor
Miac documents real DHHS documents
But I found this
PDF on Infowars
Like this document about the the New York Cemetery
If you go through it it's just a bunch of question it's a 5-page questionnaire
It sent out to cemetery
Better just trying to
2 gauge
Whether or not they could accommodate
Of
Disaster which again
From a public health
Makes total sense
If you need that
It is good to know ahead of time where you can and can't go
And
It's respectful to them as businesses
Like one of their questions
Infection
Anno doesn't mean something
It's actually section
Is the cemetery able to sustain itself
In parentheses Cashflow it do to a mass fatality event
Interment space and burial fees are delayed or a government reimburse
So this is even asking
If you had to like
If we needed to
To commandeer your Cemetery
Could you work for free and then we'll pay
Or would this be
Cuz if this is going to bankrupt you if we're not going exactly and it has
Fremont
6 months 12 months
24 months
2 is even respectful of
The business
Be like
You know I do you have
Capabilities
You have Wi-Fi
Biscuits
To the
Propagandist bread-and-butter
Which is that if you
Prepare for an emergency
The propaganda says you're going to
Creative
And if the emergent
Why didn't you
You should have fuc
Getting prepared for
They have
Are you coming and going
Right cuz they're cheap
Prices of cheap
I see I can read this document and I can't see nothing wrong with it I see exactly why it exist
Exactly
Bread Butter Alex is making out
I just think like
It's not
It's not reading comprehension
Like I know he can't read
And stuff like that but
It leads me to believe that because
So lazy
And such a just a reaction
Kind of guy
I think the real
Like
Insidious evil at Infowars
Is those people who write the articles
Because Alex isn't
Read the Rocky Mountain Times article
He didn't read
The DHS report
But you didn't read these things
He read the Infowars articles about them
I haven't responded to it
Suits the people like Curt Nimmo who have read the article and then the X report or whatever
Alex
Nefarious
Evil behind
Alex is still f****** evil as s***
You stupid do you think
In the writers room
Able to be the news desk
You know where all of this stuff happened
I mean
Do the writers for
For Ziva
Coming to
Tour of their eyes
Okay I've seen the layout of so he's not in the editorial picture
Absolutely
Yeah hangover or start one
So the
This probably goes
Was is not Alex's in the editorial
Talking about here this
We want to cover Alex's Talent
There's a there's an editorial room where they're like
Hear the narrative we've got that it's less like a news desk and more like of the writers room in SNL
Turn on Skype
UK
Yeah
So Alex is actively involved
Please call Paul Joseph
I need you to write an article that sums up all of this
True but that was because he wants
Have access to what the narrative should be
I think there's a decent chance it's because he doesn't know what it should be
She needs
The directions are more like Paul Joseph Watson
Who's smart enough
Figure out okay
This is the way we package it
This is the way you text
The truth of this
And turn it into the
You can sell
So you're dumb audien
I think that's probably what's going on
This is such like somebody going on the road and they're like
I brought I had an hour of material for 10 years
Can't write anymore
X Factor
Early days of his Shoney's has burned out on that
Hey I need a new joke
I understand really hard
Hours to go through this.
For five years from now when we hired
Script
So I seen a bunch of stuff here
DHS document is being used
Completely flagrantly irresponsibly
Just a mess just a mess what he's doing with this document
He's turning it into the
Which
Is it Services brand
Fairies
So f****** wrong
And then you see this Mass grave stuff
Come up
You know he's wrong about all this stuff too
It's interesting that he decides to
I wish everyday this one real
I wish everyday they weren't shipping birds with all the world shooting people are pleasantly dying
Mental block or something from
They only cover the weird made-up crap
It's
It's a weird
Saying that Alex is the luckiest man in the world
He wishes that none of this is real
And I'm here to say
None of this is real
You have gotten your wish Alex
Anyway
I think this is interesting cuz of these like
You know New pieces that we can bring
And then it's the same time because I think
Does represent mean
Tea party stuff
Hiperdex
Strongly
Just this trend continuing
I think there'll be varying levels of intensity that Alex feels like
His movement
Is operating position
That's going to be where he goes
Which
We had a we had a goal
Mission accomplished Somali pirates
Wonder if you can talk about that
Next episode
Consonant
A decade ago to now
Is the thing that I
I hate most about
It's the thing that I hate most about so many of these guys but
Alex's bike
I said number one guy I know
Who
Will directly assert
The exact
Opposite
Like so many people
So many people in the right-wing propaganda
Trying
Twisted they try and spin it through all of this stuff
Take reality and make it mean something else
And Alex just says directly
The opposite of what you say is true 104 180
Perfectly is what is true it still
Aggressive
I just want it like
So much more comfortable with 170
Degrees of spin
Address
With no.
He's trying to perpetuate
I feel like a woman from old
So we're done
Here at this episode but
Guy who wrote DHS report
Yeah he's never killed
Anybody he just tried to warn people about dudes who were going to be killing people in the news
Your future
Yep
Actually was part of shutting down
He's warning
About people are going to kill people
We probably killed somebody
I thought John here we are
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color