Alexandra Thurston color
Hi yes
Ready Player One
Sucks I've never seen that I've heard a lot of sniping about it on Twitter
Never asked me about anything that I know about you know what I mean like questions about like
You ever done this
Legitimate expert
So many possibilities
Questions
Sure Ready Player One
I hear it's terrible I'll double down on it for you
I'm not much of a move
Movie guy
I have a real movie at home
Still sort of triggers the same parts of your brain where it's like you're going into the movie theater
We are a kid you don't understand there's a projection is getting paid $4 an hour up there he was probably high
Love you
Where do you work at a movie theater for long enough you just like
It starts to become a nuisance
You associate bad feelings with
The feature itself and there's no there's no magic
Victor it actually makes you mad
Because the. That I lived
Who was the time when
You was transitioning from
Trouble film
To digital answer what they did was essentially
Get rid of experts dealing with this
Projectors
Troubleshooting problems
And then all of a sudden all you have to do is hit a button
Answer like I even have that resentment
Inside me when I think about movies
Watch movies
I do.
Sirius just like
Don't do that
We will just fire you really sad
I don't I don't
Those are
The generally Arctic commercial movie
Projectors for IMAX theater
Much more specialized
We we sort of flirted
Never got off the ground never happened but I love working with film
Like I loved it
Movies much I want
Alex Jones screaming
But if you watch a movie you don't learn that much but from what I've done I know a lot about Alex
Ready Player one and how much
Recently watched it
Big Show
29th
I assume nothing important happened in
Stuff happens.
And we will see why very interesting stuff so I got to go
Who shot up donors
Hell yeah but I also need to make an apology
We offered
I'm going to forward Gmail to our mailing Department
Because we have
Probably less button
Give us a little time
Keep it a little bit of time we will send them out
Is that I can figure out
Give a shout out to
I'd like to say
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Ready Player One
Next thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Greg
Next and finally
Spell hannes
Thank you so much
I love you
Guys if you're out there
Listening
You want to support the show you like what we do a website
And I would appreciate it
Today
Discovered that Rodger Stone have been indicted right pretty standard response from him
Pretty low-key
I've recovered
Hop it is
Immediately
I was
Kind of Alex Jones response to a crisis
Our show is going to pick up today on the 27th
Sunday
Go till Tuesday
. of time we will see a much more sincere response
But Alex Jones Rodger Stone being indicted
It will
Very gratifying for
Everyone
But we have to jump in on the 27th
And all this
This clip
Goats gets a little bit of islamophobic which is
Cool
For him
I guess
But also
Says
Are getting murdered
12/13 week
Islamic women
Leftist
Operations of government facilities
Infrastructure
Some people do
Yeah. It would do something like that but it's just people trying to kill
That's not good
He's celebrating political murders I don't know if these are actually
Murders or anything or he's just make
I don't know I don't really care care on some level in terms of tracing this down I Don't Care About Us
Covering it necessarily
Hey people are politically disagree with our getting murdered and I'm f****** pumped about it love it
So it was a clip he starts talking about some of his
His political concerns
In this
Late January
Sphere
Interesting
To be upset about
We've got deleted
Vice president
Next
Next year's news
Breitbart article
It's really just a collection of screenshotted people reacting to an article
About the possibility of Pelosi
Becoming president
Even the article that Alex is talking about every right to
Person doesn't really think that Washington politicians
Especially one as pants
12020 is fast
Approaching
It's not like they can't be tried when they're out of office
Also according to the 25th Amendment it is true the Pelosi would become president
Is Trump
We're kicked out of office or resigned at the same time
But odds are that would never happen
If they're both convicted of impeachment
But there's no chance
Those trials could be carried out before the 2020
There's also zero chance that they would ever resign at the same time
For this reason
If Pence becomes president
But Pelosi doesn't become vice president
Pencil points his new vice president then enters the presidential
Succession Bridge right at the top
If they were going to both resigned
The Panthers news
Be with them send
To the presidency that's being able to park both of them
There's zero Gane and resigning simultaneously
And they would never
Ever do the only reason they both get hit by a
Meteor in the same at the same
You know it's not like
Even if that does happen
If Nancy Pelosi
Hillary Clinton as her vice president
I think I will be fine with him
Teaching her to
Clean out there's no way that would ever happen with her
The new president or vice president
That person has to be approved by majority vote in both houses of Congress
You're never going to get vice president Hillary Clinton through the Senate
E-Z Pass through the house
Quite Frank
District is impossible as a real-world scenario
I was just doesn't understand
He's trying to bring up his old favorite anime to make her relevant again
I think that
Of your I think they all are I think everyone is but Alex
Is now starting
Realize
Hillary
Yeah almost immediately after that
He starts venting a little bit of frustration with the
He's godkin Donald Trump
I'm going to say this right now
The president
Are not defending yourself
Not defending your family
In one critical area
Cheryl
Nope
Self-help cover-up
Crimes of the clintons and other for the Russian
And other
Help deliver uranium to the Russians on the
Bones
Using vulgar as a
Hitman
Boston
Mafia 2 cheats
Other white shoe boy Robert Mueller
Luca Brasi of the FBI
He's the guy in 911
Grayed out by Kevin
Any blind ultimasaurus
PoBoy dirtiest of the dirty dirty
I don't know how dirty that is
I really care about
Complaints about Mueller
Because they also
Rotate gravitate around
Is Alex starting to be like f******
Trump you're not doing it
You're not doing
You're that
Similar things
But I wonder if that's going to develop Trump right now
And I wouldn't use the words of Ronald Reagan
Mr. Trump
Tear down this wall s*** no that was
Starting to
Feel little bit like Trump you're not doing your job and I'll protect
Country yourself
Finger Family
I'm not
Alex has another fire
And by this point Alex
Probably read that indictment
You know if you can
Absolutely
I'm so he's got to do a little bit of damage control for Rodger
He tries
Rodger Stone there's nothing there
Acting like a gangster when they're there is some of that in there
Text Art
Okay
Call Ray
Wow I really just Rodger
Reply
You just acting like a gang Saint guess what would you act like a gangster
That's still threatening
Is the best
Rodger Stone
Texting Randy credico still a problem
Understand
3D just doesn't have it in him
To really think about how to defend Rodger really
F*** it
I-88
It sounds so much like
Rodger
So
You got you got a lot on his plate you got a lot going on
He accidentally makes a couple of unforced
On this episode
The first of them
Is Vic
Completely bungles his
And I
Paradigm is a is an illusion
His shades of this all the time
What he says Global is t means Democrat
Right
Write designation
Someone with
The globalist
Almost unparalleled with people who are
The liberal side
And it confuses basically
Says that every Republican part of the globalist
Brautigan
A bipartisan group
Democrat
And then they all got lazy or whatever and trouble.
What's the point
His timeline is Sokka
Respect in terms of control
Blue
I just
Irrelevant
Because listen to this where he makes his second unforced error
I just want to
Americana
The whole system
What the f***
Alex
Our little bit of fascism
Eddie Redmayne Style
It's perfect John Wayne Americana with a thin veneer of fascism over it
I feel like most of his career has been predicated on the idea of a little bit of bleach do a whole lot of it
The problem is
When you have fascist icing
You put a
The little
Joke candles of white nationalism on top and no matter how hard you blow that
That to me is like your head's not in the game from the hip Sunday Atlanta
Gives a f*** anyone listening
Fever of fascist Isaac strawberries
Strawberry cream
I like orange
That's the way to go
Real sad to see that you know
It sure drop is kind of a fascist
It's too hot what
Brightly for so long then for him to just stay
It like
It's like when you're blackmailing somebody
And they're just like you know what f*** it I'm
Just going to come out
You lose your whole
Right
Admitting he's a fan
What are we what are we going to
I need Waze presenting is classic Alex
Does a little bit of a ferret
Which is let me that's what he should be saying
Like if you were being more intellectually honest with his audience
He would have been saying stuff like that all along
Because where Alex lives
And where he comes from
Is rampant
Anti-communist propaganda
Red-baiting nonsense
From Cold War
The people who are his
Spiritual predecessor
That's
They would be fine
With Americana fascism
As opposed to
The Communist Menace
That they built up because
American fascism would still be a ruthless capitalist system
Plenty of characterized
Business
Generation literally said all the time hey you guys are fast
Call Ross
Right2know
Is a little bit of getting right with God
Even
Too much too
To throw out there but like
When he says that it's easy to look at that is like
Like a pig f****** and
You take another step back and it's like
Oh
That's more honest
You have to deflect every single possible
Criticism
But now you're opening yourself up to the idea of like
Yeah yep these are there are some negative
Real serious negative things
Today's after Rodger Stone
He's a little bit
What is the same time
More whistleblowers under
He was
Right
Differences you haven't spent
3 years everyday flaking every criticism of Obama and then
Then what's your best friend used to be
420 f****** years gets indicted you start saying you know what Obama was real f***** up with the Drone
To me is monumental
On the nose
Well you can Austin trip on
If you if you got the
Container open maybe you're eating it with your finger and you know
Not supposed to do that
Flip your foot on there then all the sudden
You believe that Trump is a good president
That's just how it goes
Rodger
Deflecting and what-have-you at the end of this Sunday show
Alex's big criticisms
Is you're being too much about your own
Defense
Go on the offense
I need you to be the Rodger stone that attacks people
And you're just saying you're innocent all the time
Again
Is a valid credit
Where you see all this going because when I hear you want to hear
Simmons
You're absolutely right because I have been
Change the world
To do that
Unfortunately in a court of law
Prove that I was a liar
Can have our bullshits
You can help me in my real-world all I can do
You going to do with that Glee
Alex
Is audien
Games for money
Which should I get to enlist
Resources
Justfab.com
Support you you're a linchpin
They're home
System
Defense.com
But it shows that there are men out there that are willing to actually stand up
Bottle
Metaphors
Gettysburg Times
Simplemost.com
Man
It's so intense
So much we need money
And yeah I guess you do
More so than probably in the past
An actual reason
You are going
Probably a lot of present
He's getting sued by everybody and fix falling Parts best friends going to prison
Depressing
What you see here is almost exactly what you'd expect
Except for those
The idea that Alex is more honestly
Talking about Trump
Latin fascist temp
The idea that
Frustration with Trump about not standing up for himself in the country
Aunt
And
Frustration with Rodger
Although his version of going on the attack is just doing exactly what they were doing
All the time
Why won't you deflect with me instead of
Answer
Did Sunday show sorting
It is
Peaks my interest but
Really I had it I had a hunch when I listen to it
We were in for something
But I didn't know quite what
Until I turned on the Monday show
Advancing spiral
And my mind
Completely blocked
What we are about to win
Is Alex Jones
Pretend for The Last 5 Years
Okay
Why aren't you trying to deal with some of the issues of the present he's going to pretend he's 2009 Alex
Well I mean
Our framework
Trying to act like
Pretend hey
I didn't spend all that time being trumped bootlicker
That's basically what he's going to do on this Monday episode and it's completely crazy
Soon as we jump into the episode
And he gets back to
Trying to cover the topic
Trying to cover issues that are important
Before I go live
You know what
Autism statistics
Populations coming in
Butter spray
Measles measles mumps rubella
I love it
You do the research stay on our doing TED Talk
And we'll get into a little bit
I long for this version of Alex Wright
He's quite literally just white nationalist propaganda has been used since time immemorial to demonize non-white pop
Population
Nbcnews
Quotes
There's no evidence to show that migrants are spread eagle
Who directs the center for humanitarian Health at Johns Hopkins school of public
Keep migrants out
The article goes on to discuss health issues
Deeply relies on immigrants
As a recent study published in the Journal of the American Medical Association
16% of healthcare workers in the US
Reborn somewhere else
Including 29% of Physicians
16% of registered nurses
20% of Pharmacists 24% of deaths
And 23% of nursing psychiatric
In home health care
I checked out
Essential piece of establishing an authoritarian
The scapegoating of the other
It is crucial that the argument
Arby's
Defensive measures
The Nazis created tons of propaganda about Jews being lice
Which was something they were trying to protect the German people from
Even prior to that Jews were consistently baselessly blame for
Play
But even outside of authoritarian
Concerned there's a serious Western history to blame disease on something external
As if somehow admitting that we're all susceptible to
The illness would be admitting
Weakness or Sim
In the 1830s Irish immigrants are scapegoated for causing Colorado
During the Renaissance. The British called syphilis the French disease
Although the thought it was the Italians fault
And the Italians
Finger at the French
Bigotries are confirmed by blaming others
Miss wife
From African-Americans and syphilis to the homosexual community in Hy-Vee in
This mentality it best is useless
Current progress
And it works is employed by authoritarian rulers
Define out-group
And make certain that
The in-group has a built-in
Fear of the outdoor
Your
Like it
Counterproductive
You're trying to do
At the same time your demonizing immigrants
Spreading disease
You're spreading
You know you're only hurting
A Milbank quarterly paper
2002 discusses
Persistent Association of immigrants and disease
Are Futures the headline the foreignness of
Germs
Alex likes headlines
Restart the. From the late 1800s
The present-day rhetoric
Can policy explicitly medical language
One in which the line between perceived and actual threat
Is flipper
And prone to hysteria and hyperbole
They found it throughout our country's wonderful history
Policymakers
Employees strike
Pro diem medical labels of exclusion
And quote in order to use Medical
Exclude people that they deemed
Objectionable
This is the driving force behind this rhetoric and explains why the rhetoric persist
Even long after improve Healthcare all but eliminates the need
Need to be concerned about the underlined
He's all the function
Nativist
Exclusion
The real world
The Journal of the American Medical Association
Series a very in-depth study
About the connection between willful non vaccination
Outbreaks of Axiom
Preventable disease
In one instance
For which they had access to
Nation records for people involved
Outbreaks ahead information about
The incidence of intentionally unvaccinated individuals
Would never lower the
59%
Any cases with
His Highest 90s
And another they discuss findings from 18 measles outbreak
Where they found that other cases they had vaccination records for
70.6% of individuals involved
Vaccination
Which is what Alex promotes
Put the epidemiology of transmission
Was that quote
Children vaccine exemptions have a substantially greater risk for acquiring measles in fully vaccinated children
In one study the risk was 35 times that of the vaccine
Quotes
Higher rates of vaccination exemption and Community are associated with greater measles
In that community
These are literally the same thing
Another peer-reviewed study published in the public library science
Alexander the areas of high rates of non-medical exempt
Pencil vaccinate
Part of their findings
Of the 2014 measles outbreak
Would you like to 111 cases
Oakland California a city with a high rate of non-medical exempt
The vaccination
You can track if people have done it
Places with all of these automatic exemption
Always
Have more in
Dances of Thieves
Preventable diseases
It's nonsense
Sounds like there is
They're definitely tons of studies
Is the Baptist
Although there is no data to suggest that immigrants
You're coming
The country are insects
That is purely
White nationalist nativist
Propaganda
Alex Jones putting out
Has so much
To do
S*** like that
Cuz the movie Narrative of those in
Is always
You know somebody got on Apple
Playing from and then they showed up in your town
Spreading around
You say
Percent of non vax
Children
60% of the p
People who are hit by
Measles outbreak
Arnon back
Pineda children
Measles outbreak
If patient zero wasn't book
But that's part of the study
Generation of the
Contagion
Epidemiology part of it
The Narrative studies
Boredness of germs
There is an obsession on our part
Something
And I think
FaceTime
Sensitive religious tradition where
Beans that you did something
Vestigial part of our brain
Drop
Jump
Poverty
The same thing
You didn't deserve that and they are all in government
Yeah they are all advising the
The f****** president's
Alright buddy
You got you through some meat on my plate and
It's been awhile since
He talked about it for now
He talks about vaccines for a f****** hour
It's almost unheard of for an hour
Trump
He's talking about them
In reference to
His globalist
Enemies
Not defending Trump by attacking them
Attacking them for the sake of attacking them
Because they're giving you dirty vaccines
That's a huge difference
I'm so it doesn't throw in like
And that's why we got it
Nope in fact
Quite the opposite
Cover Trump
Rodger Stone like Rodger
Both of them
What's happening in Venezuela
Secret society some and the globalist and
Weather modification because the last 3 years
All the time
Holyshit
It's just I don't want to cover every facet of everything from Josh
You have though
Isn't that nuts
Anytime
Alex
You could have stopped
Well
She couldn't until Rodger Stone was f****** indicted that's true
Now Rodger is an interviewer every step of the way or at the very least he's not listening to Rodger as much about Meredith
There should not cover
More or less
Hard to prove that
See how are you and what have you
Highlights
And I believe that by the end of that episode
I still was like I don't think
He's going to stick today
I'm listening to this
You think this is the
This is the soft beginning of him getting off the Trump bandwagon
Because listen to this next clip he's starting to realize
That if they go down
He's going to go down unless something changes
He realizes that he's
Identity
Intertwined with Rodger Stone
And Donald Trump and that is not
A good position to be in right now because I think Monday
Andy realizes he's going to prison
If you try to distant
Entangle himself
It's very
Way
All the goods
That Trump has done
Versus the bad things that Trump has done
Nationalism and capitalism
Resurgence
Can be destroyed
I'm pulling into poverty
He's not
The fact that letting everything be about Trump
To destroy him
Ensenada cripples us
My duty is not Rodger Stone
Because I support Rodger
I support President Trump
Frustrated willing
But at the same time
Unfortunately
It is
To quote Jojo
Suspicious the time in Dubai
After there's trucks up dirty
The dirty ass hoe he had wrought
Getting back on track and now he knows like
I can't rely
I can't even other elements that
But I think
F*** it
Rodger
My lawyer in even my lawyer thinks you're going to jail
Not anymore Plumbing think about the predicament he's put himself in
Now and I think
It's possible that
He's waking up
From a real life
Long Bender like
Your Bender with
Is Trump Boos that he's been drinking his flagging over and over again
And along the way what is done
Like now he has no Rodger
They ought to be able to conspire on Rogers phones probably
Have the same relationship that they had before whatever that relationship might have been
But in the process by following
Everything Rodger wanted him to do
Where is he
You can't talk
His world which is
Webster Tarpley has turned on him because
Inspiring fashion
Wayne Madsen
The fastest ice
Webster Tarpley
The guy who brought us
Call me or call Larry Nichols story
Don't talk to Alex anymore because of the same
Play leftovers
The trend
Some of this long-term employees didn't like the direction
Of him getting into trumpets they left
People likely in McAdoo doesn't seem to be
Like he's lost everything
By following
Rodger Stones advice to the point he's at
And now he realizes
Where am I what have I given up everything for I got David Knight
Owen Shroyer hanging around I got nothing
This sucks I can't imagine reading any historical precedent for what happens if you
Listen to Rodger Stone
Purdue logs
Whoa whoa whoa
Are you staying
For three years
Nothing left
Doesn't happen to everybody
So I am
I found that
To be like I have my own man
I have my own identity isn't
Is Rodger Stone
I thought that was fine
I thought was interesting
I'm still
Waiting to see where this narrative
Progressed to
Clip and I almost fell out of my f******
Because
You listen to our show
About 3 episodes back
I said he was going to say almost literally
What he says
Launch 1776 part 2 we launched the global populist movement
Nationalist movement
Globalism
Would become so obviously oppressive authoritarian
That we should promote
It's a nationalistic counterpart
The Detonator
You kind of expect you to say
What is the prelude
To the bomb
Overall
Resistance
That's the point
That I'm making here
Is that
After the party we brought Trump to the party
I literally said that when Alex decides it's going to be
Easy Dodge for him when he's going to say I didn't leave the party Trump left the party
Which is paraphrase
I am scared of
Go to Country for a little while
It might be indicative to the you might be listening and we should get it
Consulting fee
Trump didn't bring it to the party
I think it's probably the
Smartest way to do it
I mean the only other way to do it would be to
Betray all of the principles that you've already been
Betrayed
Revealing that you
Actually believe
Principles that
Betrayed
For Trump
You'd have to burn down a lot or do with it
Controlled burn
But I think you get away a lot
When you're like
Yeah exactly
Where we got the idea that you might do this from
Yep he co-opted Trump as long as he
Rush like Stone has the same f****** pattern of behavior whenever he
Gets caught in a lie Alex
Alex whenever he needs to cut and run
Alex
I am pretending he was a real version of nobody else the real world
Even though I told all of you at the very beginning
Bright
Bad idea
Doing but he's fighting a gag order
Yep it's mess
Ticketmaster
As much as I hate him and I think he sucks
I think Alex is doing the right thing I don't think it's going to be enough to save him
But I think it's interesting
On one level because
It atleast is
A move
It will have consequences
That's
That's more interesting than just staying the course of letting the whole thing Fall Apart
It's also moved it says discretion is the better part of valor
You know it is next web
Alex says that he doesn't think the Trump is going down but the way makes me think that
Is going down
Precision all about Trump is not because I think he's about to be brought down for sure
Demoralizing effect
Because we're on the March
That is pretty
I think Alex is
Concern
So I don't think Trump is going down but I do know
2 people who are going down
I know both of them
The ship that they did
And that Trump was directly involved with that s***
So if
It makes you think that
He might be
I don't I don't know if you
Alex
Velvet
Kind of given up
Like the fact that he
He's doing this at all
Rogers
Specifically
The s*** that course he was involved in as well
He knows both of these
Yep he's
He turned on Coursey because he thought that was a way that
We could maintain Rodger
Rodger got in trouble is like
F*** it I got to change
Turn all the s*** head position
He has
In defense of
But they'll do longer be used in services
Defending Trump
Immigrants stop all the transphobia
All that s***
That will all still be there but it'll be
Attacking
As opposed
You know
Well thank God he still got Paul Joseph
Back into his TED Talk
About vaccines
Aunt
Some of this is a little bit to reiterating what he said before but
Repeatedly
I'm talking about vaccines
For the government mandating
Nope
Azure
Viruses or
That's a no technology
Have some attributes
To put things into your body
Not just
Autoimmune system but your brain
And your organs
Itself
Vaccinate
Pathogenic diseases
If you would like to leave the influx has
Suvarna just a little bit
White nationalist
The push the people are making is not so much about arresting p
People who are anti vaccinations I believe the conversations are more about
You know charging people with malpractice
Locate not vaccinated yeah
The kid gets me though
God forbid some other condition that's worse
A really interesting
Court case
I'd look a you know what my kid got measles
And that is
We traced back the
The outbreak of measles
When it comes back
To your anti-vax
Your b*******
Is that
Grounds for a civil case
Yeah I don't know I don't know
Like vaccines are just like anything they put in your body
What have you some of that defense
Is based on this next clip
And I think he doesn't know what
He's talking about
Just about the different types of so-called vaccines
Temperature genetically-engineered virus
Target shirt and shelf
The body
That would have been in your body
So I think what are you talkin about here
Just
Development of medications like in the research
Trial phases
One big example of that is when they were developing the zika vaccine research
They were working on
Also showed a bunch of promise
In the treatment of glioblastoma brain cancer
Until they started to pursue the possibility of this Taxi
Used to fight Frankie
I'm not a scientist I don't really know if I can speak
To a lot of
In-depth in the
Aspects of that
But from everything I've been able to look into
I think that that's what Alex
Misrepresent
The idea that some vaccines
End up having
Dual-purpose
Is also sold as a smoking stuff
It's not
It's very common the scientist
Who are working on it
Work on it
And they find that it helps that
Another like
F*** it
Let's do a memo
Give them different names
Stop
Solve one problem
I'm sure it's all good
That's not what this
We're golden
So
Suck
Lot of pivot
Law of
Falada
I need money
Kind of stuff yeah
The feeling is super different
Super different
In this next clip Alex
Suggest
He's not plugging enough
Find me say he was plugging plenty
But he thinks he's not plugging in
But the reason
Surprising
AAA Auto plugging up supports and I want to shut down
Operation
Infowarsstore.com today
I needed to check out all the amazing products
The things you say don't take
I want to quit so don't plug enough
All the f****** time
But it is interesting
It's an interesting angle because I think he's trying to guilt the audience
Yeah I think that's essential crisis in more like a
You got to make me be into this
Because everything is falling around apart around me everything's falling apart
Yeah it is
Kind of like
Subconsciously he's saying
Subconsciously
Wants to quit
Consciously
He kind of wants to quit and subconsciously still further he thinks he's already done
Well quit
Talking about Trump
All the time for sure almost fatalistic
Elementary
Of his
His performance over the last
Month like it just like he does
If you take what you saying there are literally
It is kind of I don't want to do the show I've been doing
But I'm more than willing to do a show where I talk about vaccines for a f****** 2 hours
Hibbetts The Narrative it h to
What's the difference
Totally willing to do that that would be exciting again
Yeah I bet you feel alive all over again
We could shave that soup
Beard
And I like
Be alive
Again really feel like he's fighting these fake enemies but he's got as opposed to
Is playing defense for a dick
But doesn't probably even talk to him
Oh absolutely doesn't that is probably
Like a leftover feeling video
He has from the last
Mumps
Maybe subconsciously I haven't been super into it
Because I wake up every morning and I've got a lie for the president
The president's friend no
Not getting paid that much intro to every present-day episode weave
Three months
I don't want to do this this is really boring
I don't find the present-day interesting.
Go back
Could be could be
You know they're evil
Plan
Play
Is you might think that the plan is just get you sick with these various things
But no no no
The plan that the globalists have it much cheaper and envy
Next clip
It's 40 seconds
An Alex bats for the bigotry cycle
Everyday
It's cold right now
Run for life and run for autism
We just get used to half of our boys.
At the shop kill
Hormone blockers
Killem
All those great Muslims
It's out of
Military
I don't think that I don't see the plan
Wow
Buckshot bigotry there at the wall
Double dribble
You're going to do a run for autism but you don't really know
Triple
But just how we're going to bring it home
Going to replace the boys who can't talk anymore with his great
What the f*** man
I heard that click but I just sitting here like
I get what he's trying to say but it's so
Yeah
That is a world
Now
It's all over the place is thoughts are tangential at best
Have the first hour
I would say 85 90% of that
F****** vaccine talk
Brought out the parts that are that are like interesting and we have it cover
A bird before
The other
Immunotek
15% is that
I don't want to just talk about Trump anymore
The thing that
Made me so angry whenever he opened
All these viruses and
Because I thought
You get back to the thought in a little bit cuz actually a really interesting places
He's getting those ideas
Understand
And I apologized
But I do so because he's going to articulate a backbiter
First hour it's pretty much
Vaccine
And a little bit of
I don't want to just be tied to these guys
I don't want to do that I want to keep making money
So
The second hour starts on a bike
You can't keep talking
But he does
Because there's break
But he's found
Involves vaccine
The Mueller probe
What
Where's the connection there
Very same people that have had their
Fingers controlling
None of them
Guarantee
Robert Mueller
Star General
But you know what your son or daughter in the military does
Weather in Toronto for kid to cuz they like to walk around and see your lower IQ and do all those cancer viruses
Congress
Spider
Rosenstein
Is somehow giving you vexed
Why Alex is starting to cook with gas
If Alex went on vacation to the Amazon
He'll be taking my malaria pills for
Yeah but do you understand you see what's going on just subtle Difference In that clip
As opposed to it being
Using his narrative years
Help
Defend Trump
Using this invest
Allegation of trump
How to inform and enforce his vaccine narrative
What is taking the path
It's the same street
But going the opposite direction down it
Which is I think
Importance
People trying to
Destroyed
Trunk from the inside
He's going from this like
There there
They're doing it not just
To destroy Trump
To destroy all of you
And who gives a s*** if Trump gets destroyed because they're still there giving you all those
Where is before primary
Define point but I think it's important
Considered in the large
All the things that you saying
The slight important variations of his narrative
Be very easy to miss
If you didn't spend
My bad
So Rod Rosenstein
He's doing this to us in the back seats that's wild
But
Pacific I didn't understand without
Doesn't it kind of suggested that sessions was doing it
First since
Robert Rosenthal
Roses
15 was the deputy Attorney General
Mueller probe was set up
Long ago
Worst evil
Like Alex
February
Sessions was the first guy
That Alex loves
In the Trump Administration
And that's why.
Even then how it was still a little bit on the fence about it
Rodger
That
Love Jeff sessions
In the 2014 2015
All the betrayals all of the cutting people loose
It's happening Alex's life
Cause of Rodger Stone
It's now it's so interesting
To look at I know that I've already brought up all those names
That are left of Alex
It's ironic
He's pulling
Midnight Massacre
The guy who works
In love
Is going to be
Weird I didn't know what he was talking about about Rosenstein
Because I have like I have no idea what can I say
General seti was vaccinated
He got his ex
He's growing up so in this next clip
Out
Man this is week
It's over the vaccine damage Court
It's not
Lawsuits and other courts
Goodnight called arbitration
Liability protection unless it's in a sovereign immunity strip
Sovereign immunity of the US government issue
You got to go through 4 years
You're doing great work
Rosenstein sister
Search for Children's Program
At the CDC
So
Guns
Rod Rosenstein
Dr. Nancy messonnier
That's probably
That she's in charge or has anything to do with
Green quartz
She does not
In that clip we just heard Alex just reading a tweet posted by Alan root
It would you links to us
CDC website about the vaccines for children program
Which is part of the cdc's mission
Provide
Children in low-income family
This page in no way proves that Rosenstein sister is in charge of this program
It's entirely possible
Butts
Important point out that the vaccines for children program has literally nothing to do with the vaccine Court
Also fun fact Wayne Allyn root is a con man who wrote a book in 1989 about how to make money
Gambling
After Obama was elected he took his
Is grifter the political world and started writing about how Obama wasn't
It was a secret Marxist Muslim
He's Simpson doors every horseshit can
Conspiracy from the Seth rich bulshit
The Nazis at Charlottesville
Paid actors
He also recently claimed that Mueller's investigation into Trump
Happening because mother has a small dick
And he's jealous
Trump's very large
Route is a
Sucking it
Reading at I know more about Trump stick that I do
I would prefer that iced item
Want to know anything about Mueller sick either
Right let's Let It Go
That links to the CDC paid for the vaccines for children program
The vaccine Court issue at all he doesn't have a story about this
He doesn't have any reporting
And it's word for word he's literally reading this
Yeah
Is the director for the national Center for immunization and rest
Pretoria diseases
Which is a branch of the Centers for Disease Control
Enter time there's you provided support and Leadership towards a lot of initiatives take care of preventable
Preventable diseases
In the third world
And has recently been on the Forefront of working of rising
Incidence
Acute flaccid myelitis
Yeah the condition
It's similar to polio but with no evidence
The vaccine Court
Just talkin about or the national vaccine injury Compensation Program
Was created under the umbrella of the Department of Health and Human Service
Department that contains
But isn't run by the
Government departments are off
Operation
And just because two things are in the same department at both have to do with vaccine
Doesn't mean they're run by the same people
I can find zero evidence
Is real
Even if she were involved I can find you a reason
Hazardous kasireddy the vaccine Court were not established because
Secret way to sweep dangers of vaccines under the rug
From public scrutiny
They were set up to be at to be
To be better
To help the subsets of people
Can we suffer from
Potential side-effects
A very important
They did this. They made it
Simpler for them to get payments for these these
Because these families deserve some consideration and payout but they never be able to get them in a real Court
Absolutely
To a certain extent side effects are inevitable of pretty much every medication
Human biology is infinitely complex the prospect of ever releasing a perfectly safe no wrist medicine
Is impossible
A study in 2017 showed that take an aspirin daily
3000 deaths a year mostly due to the blood
This is the case for whole bunch of medication
In case of aspirin dramatically reducing the risk of heart attack in older people
So the goal is to mitigate the risk of the side effect while preserving the benefit of the main purpose of the medication
This is how people look at vaccines
No one is saying that they're completely safe
Just that the incidence of side effects are not
Commensurate with the benefit
About not having to deal with
Extension level threat
From preventable diseases any
It's the greater good
It's not even just a greater good choice
No no it's not a 5-4 decision like the Supreme Court
98th division
First place
Evidence
That people give us
You don't like
This would never actually win in a way to high
San Jose
Do they realize it's inevitable
Course this is going to happen
These people do deserve some sort of compass
Others either week
Completely abandon them
Where they will get
We could create a
A special thing where it's like we get it
It sucks
I hate that
You I hate that some people get struck by lightning
But we're here to help
Never be able to prove that the vaccine question
Because their child
So
They've adjusted the standard of evidence required to success
All the people who bring cases to the vaccine court all their required to do is present a theory connecting the vaccine to the con
Show an appropriate approximate timeline
It show that there's not another plausible biological
The injury or death happen
It's a very low standard of proof and it's intentionally that way
Because they want to support the people who experience
Possible side effects without forcing them to actually proven scientific causation
The only other important to point out is that even in this court where the burden of proof is super low
They generally accept cases where petitioners claimed vaccines cause autism
Their children
And it ruled that the theory that makes a causal connection between vaccines and autism
He's not proven
And not appropriate in
The courts
Even in this world designed to provide relief
People who been hurt by vaccine
The argument Alex puts forth doesn't meet their burden
The cord is overseen by nine members of The Advisory Commission on childhood vaccines
Three of those members
Azar from the general requirements at to be legal parent or Guardian
Of children who have been affected by vaccine side
Three of the other members must be returned
With relevant Specialties for the court know they have to have
Experience in medical
Gaby Alex Jones
The health professionals appointed by the Secretary of Health and Human Services were specifically required not to be
Previous to being on this Advisory Board employees of the US
A requirement
These are
To do with it
These are the only voting members of the committee that oversees the vaccine Court the director of the national anthem
The assistant Secretary of Health and Human Services
The director of the CDC
And the commissioner of the FDA are non-voting observational members of the
They can't
What happened
But they can be a part of like
None of those things
Alex's
Profound
Dumb
And Reporting this base in
Entirely on a tweet from
Who gives a s***
Super nice.
I just mean the fact that
Any anybody like rod
Sister
Works in the CDC
Doesn't matter if it
It has any material effects
Just like fire
Eagle
Fiesta shoot the Moon
But she's there
But I honestly think the reason
He's going too far with this and swinging a little too hard is that
He's getting back into yeah that's like working working that muscle
All that stuff like
He doesn't do that much anymore assault
TV show for a year
Sage time it's going to take awhile is Rusty
Qualifications
If your lawyer
Has like a medical experience
If you're a parent of somebody who is the child support affected by vaccine
Or if you are
Healthcare professional who doesn't work for the government
You can apply to be on the advisory Commission
You can
I found the application
In 2 minutes it's super easy
Commissioner serve three-year terms that might be a little bit of a wait but it's super easy for you to do and I do notice that
The people who
In-N-Out complains almost about vaccine
Never seem to talk about that and I don't think that they're flying
I think they probably be rejected based on there if you were all three
Do you just get to be the court
Do you get to occupy three vote
Talk about it some more
Rosenstein
Mueller
Mother people
Billions of dollars
Roses
Is going to punish
Vengeance Belongs to the Lord
Now you understand the type of proof bottom-feeding spiders were dealing with
These are going to pack up front
Lab
All your tortured then they suck you dry
A song to you while they doing
Likespike I'm dumb time
It's Yum-Yum tight
I reject a ape look
Anything from the
Anything from these people I'm not
Scientist
Specialist
And if there is a
I would love to have it with the signs
But for many of these people
The moment they say the word Gardasil all you are doing is being a misogynist
Set up a lot of the function of but
The costume of concern
I don't want
That's what Gardasil
Complained
Fight
You
They're not taking into account
Spiders
They sing
Eddie's yum yum time
Piece of information without okay
CDI me up time
Spiders
Starts talking about others that
Verizon
Flood levels
The all these Fighters create a superweapon this tree
Frequency
Play make
Yum yum time I didn't know that
Physically
Here's what's great about the understand
Was a real thing
Web kids
No idea
Millions of views on YouTube
I guarantee that's what's going on
He's just like I had to watch the
Security
Anyway is that Cabela's DoubleDown says that Rosenstein doesn't take vaccines
He sure of it and we get to that issue
That. I told you to put it
Puyallup
I bet you all the fish in the sea
Which see mr. Rosenstein the shifter don't take any vaccines
German Elite
Communist leaders
The other things in them
36 37 years ago
Person in 30058
Hold on to some of these ideas
We'll get to that but
Really keep in mind
Couple years ago
Articles
About
Why is that important
There's no such thing as a clean vaccine
The idea that such a thing
Has been pushed for what explicit
Simplythick
Other vaccines
And intentionally dirty
The concept of a clean vaccine was heavily promoted by bought Army
Trace the Russian operation
According to Reuters
Read quote vaccine
And what do we normal people get
The accounts posting both Pro and anti vaxx messages such as those talk
Vaccine
Designed to educate
Which was indicted by Mueller investigation in February 2018
These messages
They were putting out
Of the vaccine
Were they were during the timeframe that Alex is talking about
It's almost certain
That it was a result of this
Yeah
Clean vaccines
So an article from the vaccine reaction had a blog post
About Mark Zuckerberg getting
In February 2016 provoked this response from a comment
What happened to Paul Walker
The darknet says he found out about vaccine
Walker picture was he too fast to vaccinate
So this guy is bringing up dark web
Responsible for Paul Walker's death
You get this these are the places that trim soda pops up on the internet
Whether it's through you know internet research ages
Sock puppet account
Or weirdos talking about Paul Walker's
Conspiracy that emotionally affected by Paul Wall
And I'm also
Anti vaxxer really an anti vaxxer how do I combine these two
What are the intrinsic issues we're going to run into here's that Alex intentionally doesn't ever really say what he thinks a clean vaccine actually
And a whole bunch of different
Depending on who you ask
Clean
2011 describe the vaccine
Arizona State University
The use that term not differentiated
From other unclean vaccine
Because they were tempting new procedure
Salmonella is a quote cargo ship
The deliver the vaccine
Priorities
Salmonella stimulates
The response from the entire body
Different
Different systems
That other cargo ship
Listen to
Complicated
I do
Eclectic
Killing everybody
And what if we do today
It was referred to an article about
Queen or detoxify the salmonella
Is being used in order to achieve the desired results
Made it through the further testing phases
Because it's the exact
Is what a clean vaccine
Specifically
Put the idea push
And promoted by
Control Farm
Which is probably assigned Alex doesn't
Very deep research
A lot of a trace back to
And people were rightfully concerned about them because
Bastards
Newspaper
Such as this ad from
Nebraska's Publications the commoner
4-19-19
What prophetess your vaccine
These concerns were legitimate in the late 1800s because many vaccines back then
And regulating their production was nearly impossible
So there were way more instant
Contamination
Take that mentality from about 100 days ago
Grab some cowpox
Put it in my hand and then slap it better than
About a hundred years ago I'm thinking that you're in the same circumstances
Only f****** stupid
A 2014 study published by the Journal of biology and Medicine
Reviews articles in
Ads about vaccinations and paper
Brewster 1915
The 1922 in an attempt to understand
The phenomenon of vaccine Skeptics
Where is many people believe that the discredited and retracted Wakefield study
Don't look back
Vaccination
Autism
They believe it that's been
Responsible for igniting
Misguided parents
The reality is quite different
Society
Entirely mirrors the concerns expressed by their predecessors
In the early
Because we've evolved so much
Sure
The difference is that back then vaccine
Seems were a new idea
And everybody intuitively thought it was dumb to give someone a disease to stop them from getting the same disease
Right of course
The authors of that study traced down the big commonality
The characterized vaccine skepticism over the course of
And found it in both time
In the modern time
It boils down to rhetoric about
Contamination
Distrust
Compulsion
The idea of being forced to take vaccine
And locality
The idea that vaccine Skeptics
Contempt
Curry pockets
Geographically
All of the ideas
It's fascinating inside
To realize that what motivates
Vaccination
Rhetoric
A movement in the present day
Is legitimately just ignorance
Of the fact that we haven't
You stayed the same
That reminds me so much of the wave it
Filtrete
Any kind of
Climate science
Scientists agree that
Climate change is happening
But you know what 100
Grieve it
The Earth
I was flattered by
CPAs
But
Discount
Our science
Like everything has
Built on the back
The reason
What came before informs what comes next
Silhouette
Medical science
Was less
Based upon a good
Consensus because there was no
General standardized
Idea of how it is
Is almost
Salable
As opposed to
Again
Almost unassailable also apart of science
Right
A hundred percent that is
If you read this study
This research paper
It's so depressing
To feed like
That's cuz you like to imagine that it is all just a movement
Because of this route
Of course
Going on
It's just
Intuitive ignorant
The people reinforce
With bad
And terribly large
It's the protocols of the Elders of Zion
It's those same narrative
Popping up over and over and over again with
Different anime
Wrong about the idea that diagnosis
The children
Spectrum have gone up considerably in the past
Last year's
I would guess
Fudging the numbers a little bit but I don't really care about that because what
Numbers is far more important
And that's the misusage
He's arguing in the number of autism spectrum diagnosis means that more people are on the autism spectrum
Literally nothing to prove that other than claimed vaccinations
The problem is he can't prove that
And no one has
Despite A Chorus of
The nihilists pretty well settled at vaccine
No calls
Do the onset of ASD
It's just not
No one
There's a simple explanation
Super Why the rate is going up
And doctor
Max Messer
A pediatric neurologist lays it out very clear
We're getting better at identifying under identified population
So it's not as if the numbers are rising it's more that everyone is getting
Everyone is going to the number that it should be
One of the things that experts will tell you is that diagnosis are quite recently
White
This was something that puzzle doctor so they study the demographic patterns
I found the quote
Afd prevalence tends to be higher among residents of neighborhoods where higher socioeconomic status
Is there
These residents are more likely to have access to Quality
Quality Healthcare is a large piece of
Treated as a child until fairly recently
If the same behavior manifested
Greater awareness of these invisible biases
As well as attempts
Provide Quality Healthcare for larger numbers of people
Is natural light to better diagnostic process
The number of diagonals
But not necessarily a jump of
The actual peep
People who exist on Netflix
Exactly like
What is saying is
So now you say
Westgate
White kids
What is 1 + 58
Of course
I mean a lot of that is what is behind
The shifting numbers
The perceived increase
Actually
You know free from doctors
It's pretty easy
And it's not because
Globalstar poisoning backseat
Women
And you go back
So long
Well women are
Like that was always
Is the diagnosis
So long as
Diagnosed
Male children
For forever and it's go
Your
Like at the end of the day
Willington
Sure content with the idea that women are working well or just a problem
Making the right
But all of this is to say
Alex jump
Headlong
Back into like
Early route
And when I heard him say this
It made me
Or convince
He's Rusty
People trying to be
Be himself again
Because statistically
Everybody around you
It's going on right now
Human target
Injections
Injunctions
Cutting sheep
Brian Russell
You got it
Bertrand Russell
An injunction
Bertrand Russell global
Directions
Conjunctions the court
Junction
We'll make
The proletariat
This is old school Alex
This isn't a fair quote
Alex's just take the beginning one
Paraphrase
Bertrand Russell's
Aren't you need to serve his purpose
The full quote is
Quote
Gradually by selective breeding the congenital differences between
Will increase until they become almost different species
The Revolt of
Williams would become as Unthinkable as the organized Insurrection of sheep against
The practice of eating
This has nothing to do with diet
Injections and injunction
Those words are found two paragraphs earlier
Alex could have just use the earlier saying
Actually remember
He could have just use the later send
The word injections
Which is really what he wants to talk about
Dusty had to combine the two witches
Little bit this song
Although it doesn't matter though
He's completely twisting Bertrand Russell
As we discussed when I was brought up is pathogen endgame
This book is based on lectures to Bertrand Russell gave in the early 1950s
From his discussion of the horrors that could have befallen the world
Where to operate on a purely scientific
Individual rights
This is explicitly something he does not want to see come to pass
The context is very very clear if you actually read the books
We already covered this in-depth so there's no real utility and doing it again Pastor
Just reminding people that
But I made a point drawing attention this because
It's one of so many signs of this episode the old Alex's
Is waking up for this Trump
Real baby little other way
It's more real than he's done
Other 2018 2019 episodes we've looked at where there's like a
The flicker
Or something from the past ride ever
This is so much like
I wanted a want to go home I want to go back screaming oil
It's awesome
You are a little bit off
Well we can probably pull things off if there's a world government that benevolent
Globalization
Globalist
With scare quotes
He wasn't a capital G
He's just brilliant
Call the table
To eat
CMS
It's kind of fun also receive
Rodger
Wants to put them aside
Is this
He's trying to make more arguing
About vaccine
Being bad
Iron Man
We could have done
A six-hour episode just going overalls
The mail
I would much rather talk about things like that
That are shining examples
How f****** stupid Alex Jones
And how bad
You makes these arguments
Some side effects
He's talking about like doctors who are told that they should support
Right doctors with border
Washing clothes
Got a snake
Screen doors
Okay
Holyshit
To see the argument he's trying to make here and it may sound kind of good sort of but it's terrible
Screen doors made it to Mosquito couldn't fly at your house and give you malaria
Problem
The screen door wasn't invented till 1887 which is a bit after the Industrial Revolution
It took us a long time to
How to get to the screen door
Some window screens were created before this but the word immediately
Washington
Doesn't work out there
Ignorant
The formulated from the series about hand washing in 1846 in Florence Nightingale and Oliver Wendell
But their ideas were not popular
Mostly because doctors felt like they were being blamed for contaminated
And at that time we believe that water itself was the source of infection
Along with foul odors called miasmas
It wasn't performed some formal experiments in the middle
1860s
Germ Theory a little bit more serious
The CDC didn't even exist until 1946
According to retrospective published by the World Health Organization
In the United States actual hand hygiene guidelines published
Most of the public discussion about hand washing
Terry was Donnie
Not because they thought it would protect customers that because they thought it was
A fear-based way that they could move more product
Man ignaz semmelweis
Is one of the most
Was tragic
Figures in the medical community
To really start
Applying
Double blind
Studies and
And actually
Treating scientific
One of the big things that
He did was
We're going directly from an autopsy
To a child birthing
All of Our Midwives are not
Killing these pregnant
And all of our doctors are killing me
Let's think about this and then later he died of sepsis
He was fighting against jiren
I'm so sad
Poor guy
Speaking the Industrial Revolution
Considered to be the. Between 70
60 + 18
It was a disease index
Outpace advances
Colorado horse common
Because of how easy it was for water to be contaminated
These newly urban areas and how people were living in far greater density than they were before
Communicable diseases went absolutely nuts
Is estimated that tuberculosis killed one-third of everyone who died in the United Kingdom
Q50
Because the condition
Brought out on Bybee Bistro Revolution
Serious researchers and historians are pretty uniformly behind the idea that industrialization has
I've been a driver
Towards diminished health
Condition
One of the things the most
Devastated urbanizing Industrial Revolution
It was so contagious and had a history of
Completely destroying world
Spanish and Portuguese explorers introduced into the new world pretty much spell death
For the Aztecs
And the Inca
He's a seriously
F*****-up dangerous disease
It said that an eighteenth-century
Thousand people die from it every year in Europe
And the fatality rate for children who contacted it
Was reported at 98%
Depending on what country in Europe
That's a bummer. That's a bummer you couldn't get it again
People knew that going back to approximate
430 BC
But no one really knew how to
Treated
In the early 1600s a doctor
Advocated patience quotes
No fire in the room leave windows permanently open
Bottles of small beer every 12 hours
Pliny the Elder
Yeah pull up the pants
This didn't work
Don't
How could you
You trust a man
With snide in
It's just not possible
In 1796 a doctor name
Edward Jenner decided to start experimenting with seeing if you could figure out how to prevent
Because they come down with less of yourself
That they would never get smallpox
This interaction that he had when he was younger
He began experimenting with kelp
This would eventually lead to him inventing vaccinations
Which box is the Latin word for cow is vodka
In
7th
He published his findings which were literally
Cowpox
But the community was not fast to get on board
M17 conducted to determine if having survived
Fox
Developing an immunity
Impact
He proved his hypothesis
Affect
As well
The work was far from done for instance
Set the timer for
Responsible for
Stepping medical progress
It's hundreds of thousands of Lies
The last naturally occurring case of smallpox
Recorded
And that would not have been possible without Edwin Jenner Edward Jenner
It is cowpox
Alex and talk a lot of s*** about screen doors all f****** want
But are you staying any
If you look at just
Case of music
According to a review studies published
In the Journal of the American Medical
Association
The measles vaccine was not life
United States
Covid-19 sick
Incidence of measles
300 cases
For 100,000
After introducing the vaccine
Cases
For 100,000
You see this trend very clearly as it relates to other vaccine-preventable
The science is very clear
Nobody want to talk about the idea that the vaccine rates
Can also go up
That's a part of the science because as
Because here in this path roof Edward Jenner in his
Is smallpox vaccine
Educreations you don't know if it's going to be a permanent immunization
Booster shot
Yeah or there are infants
This word
You know.
Some gift
That's the processes
So there's ways
You can twist statistic
It's all you want
But when you really get down
The bottom of it
Hand washing
Is not respond
Over that although it does help
Screen doors
Malaria and Dengue fever but the timelines off and
The Industrial Revolution is literally the worst thing you could use as an argument for
Zach bringing down Taziki's
Apples
Confusing that I get from 2009 hours
This is the kind of didn't expect to hear from him
That would be like Trump wants to stop all of it this stuff all the stuff that I'm complaining but not like the Industrial Revolution solved
Vaccines are given you the xy&z they're going to turn your kid to a mute
Trump is going to give
Restorative cures that all the globalist have been hiding
It never
Fails to fascinate me that
How
How the
How did
Friend of his
History
It's constantly like
We solve this problem you know like when you're talking about
The Great Depression
When you talk about how they in
The marginal tax
Broke down
So much of income
How many quality
And that
I led to a. Of
And then they forgot why the Great Depression
The generation that lived
Through it.
And so they went right back to all the same
In the same way getting rid of smallpox
The last recorded
Naturally occurring
Happened 50
2 years ago
Airport
I n
Forgot
But the only reason that
Hundreds of thousands
People aren't
Because of vaccine
So these vaccinate
Come up because they're like seeing we never had
Smallpox
In order to Lycra seineyard
Once you realize reality
You don't have to attack vaccines of having something
Enzyme that bad
Which is where you create
Clean vaccine when we go we go back to that
If you're prepared for a problem
That's because you're going to cause the problem
The problem happened
You weren't prepared
Always your fault
Interesting I enjoy all this
It's a lot of fun
But it's not nearly as fun
Is this next ad
But Alex is doing
I would say that there is a trend where Alex's address
The first one was a little passive-aggressive
Now they're turning into
Like Direct
Give me a people don't know how great our products are nowadays they are how much you need them
Apollinaire
Hillary Clinton
Running the vaccine propaganda Bureau and a secret
Because we got the
That's a threat if you don't donate to knowledge fight
If you don't go to our website and I will tell you what's going to happen
Right now
That tells me that you want Alex Jones
If you don't tell your friends about now it's right that tells me that you
What
So gross man
It's just it's just
Weird grossed
You know
It is a threat that's threatened
Yeah it's if you don't give me enough money to Vici
Whatever
The vague idea of whatever I think you should be giving me
X number is not a
Do you want to be raped by the devil
Joy
For the last 23 years I've been on air
Give me money in that means you know what maybe I shouldn't know a f*** you f*** you talk to Stevens are coming
Wild wild before
Sweat like threading
Threatening
Pivots I like it
If you don't we're f****** Diamond gusset
Do you know what you want you want your balls to be
Skeetos
Cuz that's what happens when you wear other f******
The end of the 28th that's the end of Monday
And I think it's really I think
Unisuper interesting way
It's a lot
There's a lot of content
Real pain in my ass
Preparing
Stretching out over this
It's worth it because
The Narrative plays out
On Sunday you see the colonel
Beginning of Alex setup
Yearning for something
On Monday
Start to talk about
I'm f****** Rodger Stone to Donald Trump
I'm doing almost
Entire show where he just goes
F****** vaccine
Like really not much Trump defense
On Tuesday
On the 29th
With Rodger Stone
At the beginning of the shop
Because Rodger
Just gone
I am plead not guilty
Got booed
Alex is not happy about that either
That's really starting to piss Alex off cuz the Optics of it are very difficult to Rodger keeps
Getting booed everywhere
Eventually people are not going to like they're not going to go like
Oh yeah there is a globalist
The people fake news media
Haha
Everybody wrong
Huh
Interview and it's exactly the same
We saw on our Monday
Where Alex is most
Preoccupied with the idea of this being a world exclusive
Is really driving him
Trying to talk to Rodger
Tomorrow's news
Rodger Stone
Giving Ashley World exclusive after his arraignment there were hundreds of cameras and reporters out front
Just 30 minutes ago when he came out
From the Giants running reporters
You're going to prison
To defend himself
Rodger
World
Exclusive
It's hard to
Square that with the fact
Roger's been on every f****** show that'll have him on
It's even harder to square that without peer in the show
Rodger said the earlier that morning
On Tuesday he been on Mancow show
Amen cow says hello
So the idea that he'd been on world exclusive you've been on Mancow show earlier been on Fox news all over the place
Promotes that he's going to be on Laura Ingraham while he's on Alex's show
This if there's no exclusivity today I think it's real
I think he's really getting frustrated
Rodger does not have other
I have a new thing can go down
When Alex got sued by the Sandy Hook families he couldn't go on Tucker Carlson
Go on Hannity
They wouldn't have him onto the hottest item in town he's welcome on all
All the Fox News shows
Go to Mancow Muller's place
Finger related
So Alex is starting to get this bike
Fuimadane him
Bubbling of like
Motherfuker
I keep trying to say that it's a
Exclusive
He knows that he needs more than I can provide him
He's going he's working
Across perfect
Is a wrestling business
Business for yourself
Roger's going into business for himself
In the middle of the match right here but we're witnessing is a match
Is there a tag team
Rogers basically
Twisting the script what they're supposed to be doing
And Alex's just like holding the bag
It's very
Very clear
I love it
Unfortunate
That Alex
Hasn't
Fired
Because that seems like his
I'm not saying he does but Alex does say something
That implies that
Done
Pieces
From the past
As if enough lumber
Is it out of the Twilight
His eyes are
Come back again
The sleeping giant has awoken
He starts to talk about these sources that
Talk about all the time
Free Trump
Paris sources we haven't heard about in a long time
Why was growing up
And I wish
The military is officers people would have been
FBI always other places
Not a pencil pushing paper pushing areas but no real on-the-ground stub
I always heard
I always thought it was weird not true
Was obsessed with
Government worldwide
Kevin Hart program
Super secret space
More influential
Got a Black Ops everybody else today confirmed as well
He's bringing up these old used to be such a part of things we'd encounter General
Where the two of them tried to sell $30 laminated
They were laminate
A bunch of b******* white genocide narratives
Real ghosts real
Career in the military services
From 1950
T22 1984
You may be asking yourself why you left the military in 1984
Seems like if you're in for 32 years you wouldn't leave unless you have to
Turns out
He had to
General mobile
1st Battalion operations manual
A book written by a guy named
It was packed to the gills
Project
For creating a class of warrior monks in our special abilities
Which one
USSR creating project investigates
Psychic Warfare
It ran between 1981 and 1984 he's the man who
Visible and walk through walls
As well as remote View and some world
None of these efforts were successful
Yep I didn't realize that that was Albert stubblebine
That was the guy didn't know that
That is because I've read that f****** book not the main character in the book or anything like that he is the guy who tries to walk
Walk through walls
So
He's really he's really good
406s for 3-years of creating super soldier
The military for that
It turns out that in order to super soldiers General stubblebine
Sensitive compartmentalised
Information facility
Which is crazy violation of security protocol
It was kicked out for that
There's no
After all of that
Considering Alex
Stop
That's repentant a park
Alex only knows him because I do with a big Oklahoma City
Part of a long career in the Air Force there from 31 years before retiring in 1978
Unfortunately that makes it pretty much impossible for him to
Involved in that project didn't start till 1993
Special Assistant to the head of the Federal Aviation
Association
But his role was mostly about the implementation of the new Jeep
GPS system
In matters of FAA policy
Not with creating
A gigantic
Alex knows that now bente Parton is dead so is
Kind of a shame because outside of
Some of the
More
Colorful pieces of their resumes
Careers that don't need exaggeration
You don't need to
Claimed stubblebine was the head of Black Ops
Some f****** military for 32 years
Being apart of
You could just talk about his illustrious 31-year career in the Air Force
Is Jordan from Chicago
I just want to check in
I will let you go
Like these are things that existed
CVS app
They're starting to make
Another one another little
Piece of narrative
From the earlier day
Weather weapons that other people have other weapons
I'm the bad guy cuz I told you first about
Neurologist on about
Is it crowded
I like earthquake
Is reporting that William Cullen. Michael Cohen
Legitimate under Bill press conference where he admitted that they had earthquake weather
If he's out there admitting
What kind of terrifying s*** do they have that they don't talk about it
Be very afraid
Sentence right
So in reality without speech that secretary Cohen gave on April 28th 1997
We're just part of a conference on terrorism weapons of mass destruction in US strata
In all fairness to Alex
In all fairness
Going bring some up as an example of something that doesn't
The full context
Let me ask you specifically about last week's care here in Washington and deal with that
Referring to a package that arrived at the Jewish service organization
To be a chemical weapon
Cohen's response was
Quote the nature of the threat
It turned out to be a false threat under the
But as we've learned in the intelligence
Community we had something called
Question about Santa
Samir sfeir here's that
Say the words
Star Wars fandom mobile
Alright the mirror fear that there's a mole within an agency
Can set off a chain reaction
Hot for that particular mole which can paralyze the agency for weeks in months
In a search
The same thing is true about the false cares of
Threat of someone using some kind of chemical weapon or biological
There are some reports for example that some countries
I've been trying to construct something like an Ebola virus
Very dangerous phenomenon
Alvin Toffler
Laboratory strange
That would be
Make specific so they can
Just eliminate certain ethnic groups and races
Others are designing some sort of engineering
Awesome kind of inspect
They could destroy specific crop
Others are engaging
Eco type of terrorism whereby they can alter the climate
Volcanoes
Remotely through the use of electromagnetic
Somatic waves
He's talking about potential weapon
But the context of these potential weapons or is examples
The False Prince that they've received
Reports about
It's the sort of thing that you can't
Not take seriously if you're the intelligent you get some sort of report about this or thing
But it's not real
Write Alex's
Profoundly f***
Well there's so many times where you saw it during the
Cold War Russia be like we have laser
Isn't that America
We will be like what we have
He likes
We have anti-anti
There's a lot of posturing political
Force you to account for something that is
Literally unaccounted
You can really hurt
Your enemy by pretending you have a weapon
And it forces them to spend billions of dollars
Trying to find a way to protect
Themselves
Part of
This information is necessary for both
What what the most famous
Story I can pick up off the top of my head is
The British spread that idea of keratin
In order to distract from the fact that they were using radar
You know like it was that kind of like
Oh it's this whatever technology you have
Yeah
Do you always want to have a
A perceived
Greater threat or a perceived lesser capability
In order to get people off you
Your Trail
It's very clear
From a contact
He's talking about
That we don't have
There's there's like reports
That are false that people do have
Like example of
In this next clip
Alex is
Just getting into
Suggest
Where he's at
And where he's at
I think internally he recognizes that he's sold out
He's really mad about it
Yeah
There's this weird giving there's a
Is pushing pole is going on inside his soul
I need to make up for having sold out
Right by going back to my roots in some ways
But at the same time
If I recognize but I sold out I can never go back
Which is again something that we talked about
So long ago
He can do this but he can't do it like me
Alex
And one of them is selling out
You would never
I will not show up
I will not sell out and molest children and partly Club I will not do it
K
Listen
Our best products
What the f***
Yep I will never sell out
I will tell.
Do need you to give me money for these products that are b******* that I sold out
I also really like this
Flat delivery of
I will not tell on that
Haddad
I will never sell out
Emotionless
Alex's
Going back to his roots
I think there's been some indications of it
I also been making case videos
Really doing the first step of
Getting the f*** away from Rodger
Yeah
Case necessarily
But I will in this next one
Start
Competition
When
Mister sinister
Because the 24/7 Rodger Stone
Because of that
Infowars
At least 10 times Rodger Stones yet
Right now
That's it.
Have 100 bush
Cost money
You don't think it's fine
But that I also
I think there's a truth
In terms of Rodger
In terms of Paul I don't think that's true I think that's advertising for him
I'm going to have to lay off right
I'm going to have to lay off Rodger Stone never going to lay off
TV
Did Paul Joseph Watson leave is the day everything falls apart
And Buckley would never let him
Fireball
No matter what
So I don't believe that
Expressing something
Unless you motherfukers give me a bunch of money
I'm going to I'm going to have to lay people off that's just the reality we are going to be able to
Radio show now we're not instrumental
Chickens coming home to roost
So like it dirty is that I believe that
But I also believe it
Is it Alex's
Is really pissed off
It's some of the donations that could be going
Are going to Rodger 24-hour Rodger Stone defense is
I got a business to run
What the f***
Painting Rodger Stone
And advertise
Legal defense fund
And now he is
It's probably the first time in the last three years the Rodger Stone
These single most
What's the reason
So Alex Express
Rates as The Show Goes On
Associated with Donald Trump
Is that
About screen time
Government
Why does my right about everything
Everything I've done for the last
Tastes like you do everything possible to submit yourself as the guy who's associated with
Rodger Stone and Donald Trump
What I do before in this thing
Remember When
This is so much guys
Remember when I used to
Be great
Definitely
Talking about Rodger
Like just listen
Into his f******
This is like
This is so frustrated
Andover
He's just over it
Beach ball
Now we're going to time
Will become
People
About the New World Order
I don't think it is anyways Alex was still committed to this whole thing
What happened my f****** time is going to be happy
Regretted stupid b*******
Wikipedia put-upon 24-hours
This isn't
Cutting it anymore
I'm done
This isn't this
Strong
Rogers
John
Of your illegal
An indictment of your character for me
And I
About this
And I don't think it does anything really positive about me but I put in my time without
Restaurants unique ability to understand
Everything I hear being put forth from him in the aftermath of Rodger Stone indicted
Just often empty nope sleep on it
Here is Alex screaming I want to go back
Roger's going to prison
Jerome corsi is mixed up in all of it
Webster Tarpley cuz I saw Trump for the danger that he was
Jakari Jackson he lost Rob Jacobson had to fire Joe Biggs over pizzagate
BMX dude doesn't seem to enter this anymore Rodger Stone was the glue holding together a fractured world
Without him
It's not going to work
Misdirection
Anymore
Trying to
To the idyllic pastors
Of his past
Not realizing
You can't go home again
Is George Weber learn to Tom Wolfe's book of that title
You can't go back home to your family back to your childhood back home to a young man's dream
Gloria
Back home to the places in the country
Back home to the old forms and systems
The things which once seemed Everlast
But we are changing all the time
Back home to the escapes of time and memory
3 years of becoming what he is now with taking a toll on Alex that he'll never be able to
Undo
Every day he woke up and came into his Studio to tie his name is reputation to Trump
Intentionally
And that is not something that goes away just
Because your friend got arrested and you don't want to play that game at
Alex is every reason
Don't want to go back to His Marvelous sunset
His better days
But he can't
Because he's been changed by the journey
It becomes Crystal Clear when you hear I'm trying to do this 2009 style Ranch
That we've seen over the course of this episode
But he's doing it with his 2019 bring
You can't do it any
I can't weave is I'm above politics bulshit after spending three plus years defending everything Republican members of
The government and literally making Democrat and Global is synonymous
He was always lying
Thruway whatever pretense he had
A decade ago to ride the big wave with Rodger
Unfortunately that party is
F****** over
Rogers signal that he's willing to talk to Mueller which undercuts literally all of the narratives Alex
About their interact
Rodger keeps going on Fox Road
Laura Ingraham
Because he can
He's a hot item
And Alex knows the keys
Old Navy
And Alex cannot go home
F****** fund
Pry
Alright
And I think it's really interest
Because I don't I don't think
Pecan
Make it work
But
Whether or not I think he can pull it off
Just based on how I don't think any
Pull it off
Nope
That doesn't mean I'm not still super
That's more what I'm really interested
Because of back two more like
Actually trying
On his show as opposed to being just a
Deflection artist
It's always better for me
I met at the same time
I don't think that we've ever seen
Play calyx in Salvage
Bridge mode
And I think that's what he's going to have to be
Moving forward
I think it's going to be slow moving ICE I definitely think
It's going to take a little while for it to really
Take hold but it's the same sort of thing that we saw
We came into
In the late summer fall
Into the winter
2015 Slow Burn
Where there was being
Introduction of
Seems
The gradual
Warming of the water
It's up to the point where the listeners didn't realize it was boiling they were
I think you doing
Sort of a similar thing but in Reverse now
And because we have such an awareness
Cursive Alex
How he works
How we operate from days here in January 2019
Deescalate
Boiling water
Not necessarily to let people out of the pot
I don't know how to work make that metaphor work honestly in reverse
Like
The closest would be out of the frying-pan into the fire but even then
What are the things I'm super interested in
And because we recording this here on Thursday I don't have access to
Much more
The Wednesday was kind of boring
Big picture
But I'm interested to see where he goes
Like
He has people like Owen Benjamin who are hosting 4th hour
And to me that's kind of funny
And not funny
Yeah but like
I don't see him
Bulldog
But if you were to get in with like let's save those people who do like Red Ice
Alex strong
Towards
Overt
Supremacist white nationalist
His
The other possibility
Is it we could see
A marked
Insurgent
To seem to have been laying low
People like Paul Craig Roberts
People like
Peter Schiff
We could see a lot of these guys who are really prominent figures in 20
15 start the show back up as Alex tries to refocus
On the Federal Reserve
The globalist it being
Trump defense
Pilates guys
Who used to be his like
His sources
You can't go back to Webster Tarpley can't go back to pechenik
But he has options
From his old
Roster
If he apologizes to them and shows
He's not still just on
Trumps
Right I think that's one possibility that I'd be interested in seeing
Cuz those people
Would take a real
The other possibility is
Afraid of
But I think would be more interesting
Amatis Alex going to
Overnight
We're just possible I don't know
That's the problem with not being able to go home again
Right because if he tries to go home to his old
Football back in the day
So trying to go back there is trying to
Create
A future that
It's a it's a warped
Diversion of the past
That will only make both parties
Disappointed
They're experiencing
I think I could lead him also
Towards
I don't know on the other hand
You could say that
Once again
An inside
Into the weakest
You know like Alex
Was so hard into
Trump
Now his
Pivot has to
Sofa
Where is you
People like Fox News where they're starting to
To to be like
Maybe we shouldn't sky and
Because they were
They were
Far more gradual to it and
Still attempted to
Mitigated
Decline is going to
Similarly slower
I don't want to disagree with you necessarily because of
Thank you Isaac
Your ideas
I think that Alex has to be
When they jump
Could go much harder Road 92
I think they could take a pivot really
And I think people would kind of nuts
The Flash
Graphics
Production design
Their ability to distract
And the fact that they're better at their jobs
Restaurant
The any of them they do an hour show that edited it's not live
The reading script
There is like
There's always graphics on the screen
There's an ability for them to make hard
Returns that sometimes people don't
Experience as being
Hard because they're distracted
Most of the people who were listening
Alex just have his word
After watching the video it's not like they have
Tyronza
You know like
Good graphics up everywhere on it like alcohol for the document
And then you get to see a piece of paper on his desk
That's good stuff
It's not that great
Ability to serve
Hypnotize
Ikea's just his word
To go on
I don't know
You could be right or at
I don't know I don't think either of us position on it
Interesting but actually think is impossible is the idea that Alex
Become a voice of like
We lost our way
Or something like that
I think that I think that there would be
Some value
Sort of like
How do you get to the
The place necessarily
But some sort of like penitence
We lost our way we had our principles
Ron Paul's who I always loved and I get seduced away from it
Could even go with his
Hero's journey
It seemed like the right thing
Do it seemed like the best way to attack the globalist
This guy Rodger Stone f****** over
He's going to prison I've seen the error of my ways I know you was lying to me the whole time
I beg of you
I'm a voice in the wilderness
Do you saying
We
Stocked up
Do you remember how great it was when the
Tea party was going
Do you remember how much life
We felt in that midterms
In 2010 when we started the game seat
Do you remember what it's
Felt like to have this resurgence
End the Fed
Text
Dies
We didn't know what we were doing we got LED down the wrong road
And I'm begging you to come back
Comeback
But I think I'll be interesting as a character
Actually say
Your best move there
We did this
For the right
Reason
Supreme Court Justice
You know like
Hey well say what you
You want steak
Deck but all of them
Get a winner
Sure
What we elected was
F****** moron
Guess what
We got to
Supreme Court Justice
We got the
Absolute destruction of the Consumer Financial Protection
Victory out of the jaws of death
A little bit
Character
What cuz I think that's
Interesting
Voice
Yeah
To embody
Astonishing
Sort of logical but unlikely progression
Yeah
I think most likely
Severe
Radicalization
Because
Him trying to go home isn't
Nothing is going to have to try and find
The new home
New home
In terms of the internet
Searcy sphere and all that world either got to go like
Qanon s*** that's
Clearly, he's not into
The only other world
Outright
Nationalist
And like
He believed
The same thing
He just
Yeah he's outclassed
Because he's still not going to be able to do white nationalism as good as
Nobody does have a bigger platform
A lot of them
And they would hero worship him because of that game
Beekeeper issue
Millions of
True
So I think there's a possibility there
I don't know it's only answer
It's always difficult for us to try and
Predict the future
Speculate a little but like
We can only go on what he saying in the present
Provide Conte
Text that we have from
Of course now
We have a couple more Clips here from the 29th
Which again is Tuesday
On this show Alex's
Clearly
Syndicated Rodger Stone
Alex wants to go back
He wants to be where he
Felt comfortable
Before his identity wasn't
Tight prom
You can talk about all the stuff
He's always
He wants to be that again
And I wouldn't take it all that seriously
Probably
I guess he's a liar
And it even made
The sort of things that
You think you're seeing
In him
You can trick yourself if you're giving like a generous reading
Of what he saying
Yourself into thinking like
Oh isn't that interesting
What sealed the deal for me is this
Interview
On the 29th
Report.com
In 2020
What's behind this idea is William getting one of us
Continue what you doing
Had on in years
He's a guy named William
Who runs this
The American legal immigration
Political action
Luciferous anti-immigration
He is a super
Keep them out
Brown's out
He wrote an article
About wanting
The primary Trump
In 2020
Alex would never
Have this person on his show
If you still had any
Interest
In being a part of
Can't imagine
Anybody who voices
Milquetoast criticism of trump
Alex
Valid criticisms
Do not exist
Or even invalid criticism
Once given
You never give time
To criticism
Trump
Without challenge
Hacking
The person who's delivering
William goes on the show
Listen to this
Doesn't mean I really don't want Trump to win the election
Running
Mary
What I'm doing right now
Wow
He feels betrayed by Trump and he'll never vote for him again
Alex wouldn't let this on his show a month ago
And even the idea that he's starting out this interview by saying
Back in line
Reposted
He wouldn't think that that was the
The promise
He knows who this guy is
This strikes me
Soft
No
The first
Production meeting
Infowars
Has had in
Like legit
This is when Alex got
Together with
Dad
And Buckeye
And they for real talk
Volume
We can
Do this any
Find me a guy
Who's going
Say
We're the most
Whatever it is we think
We are
And Trump is
Not bad
We didn't bring
Bring us to the party
Zebra
It's exactly
Alex is allowing this guy to
On the show because because it's
Yet
Introduced into the rhetoric of his show
Yeah very important
Being able to
Being able to transition
Have this
On a hostile conversation with someone who's like
F*** it Trump abandoned us
I've always been a liar I was I loved it
In the campaign
Hear stuff I love to
Here I love that and that's why we voted
Now it's unfortunate
Because this guy William Dean
Big old piece
Nose Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Alright go f*** yourself
You don't make it more obvious that you
Do you know her name
Then when your legs hurt but I like that
100%
Terrified of her
It's important
The Alex is letting this on his show
That's super
At the end for Trump because I
I heard these things
The campaign
Inspired
And a lot of people would like to
Resent the idea
He said he's going to get out of the teepee
PP
He was going to fight the globalist
The Williams
A f****** dick
He said
We were going to have white
William jeanes.
We did not let Donald Trump
Wow you're bad
He's doing he's actually doing something 183
Wow read me just before the midterm election voters
Bigotry is disappointing to me
I heard during the campaign
Rampit white nationalist
We got
Bayou
Better getting a 100% whitener
Was we got like a 75% and the response here is interested
Because Alex is kind of like
Yeah you know what
You're right
Like there's a part at the end of the interview where Alex is even like yeah you know we're all caught up on the wall but just a misty issue is
Really more important
The others got to be still immigrants here the holy s*** out
So not only is this a very of jovial friendly interview with his guide
Central Primary B
Times embracing of but at other times
I would imagine that if we were to really go back through the archives you could find a lot of
For the cycle
I think what's important here is that I don't
Alex
Really
Necessarily
Sports
I think he's using him
As
More extreme
I guess
To have a moderate position
With work
Sing away from Trump
I think
I don't know
Like I can't sum it up better than
I hear Alec
This not
Anymore
What he's done
What he's been involved in
Like you just realizes that he's reached the end
The party's over the lights of come on
It's not fun
You're there until 5 in the morning
Everything's like fun in the morning
And then at 5 you still think it's fun
Lights come on realized
No one's dancing with you party is over
All your friends are gone
They don't like you anymore because
You punch them at 3 a.m.
You're just f*****
5 a.m.
And now you got a f****** sober up
You got to go get some Gatorade
Whatever
Figure it out
Get his life right
That's all
Tumi
Compared to the Isis
This
This is why
Production meeting
Part of it this is why that
Stripers
What I'm saying is
Tonight was
Emotional Ally
Shooting from the cup
Turn off that camera
Course when they go home the next day
The people around him were like
You can't do that we got to amend
Where is this
Turn
Is more likely to Natural because
Because
The people around him
Otherwise
Instead
No no no you can't be doing this
Are now saying
How do we
Not
How do we maneuver
Exact
We maneuver it by soft
Cutting off Rodger
It would serve nobody because he wasn't
Paul Watson
Purposes for him to come on araby like
Buck Rogers down the guide piece of s***
But that strategy would be a non-starter
So the idea of being like
I would assume
We're going to work through this
Foot f***
I imagine it has to be something like that because you receive is presented on the
It's consistent over the core
3 days ago
I am f****** sick and tired of being tied to these dudes
It's as close as it gets to lick a shoot
Promo promo
Rodger Stone
Is a severance package
It's amazing how much money we're giving
Birmingham Wallace
It's not hush money to like
Like slander
That's just kind of a good strategy
If you're working with Rodger Stone you don't even know if
Can make it through
Yeah
You can make
Get through if he's probably going to be in prison soon
That's when you bail out that's when you're free Alex's
Free in a way that
He hasn't been
For three years old my God the most important
The most important thing for Alex right now
Is whether or not Rodger
Stones gag order
Not really
I don't care
Obviously I was being
Does get info
Alex
Well Subway Subway
I mean if a quarter is
Enforce them
Is free to just move on
You have to be afraid of whatever Rodger might do
I'm up to like
Cell Rodger
Out
Sing like that
I think that there is
Interesting
Plies our gullibility
Weakness in himself
Right
What's that like
Rogers
Railroaded by the globalist
Right now let's talk exclusively about the globalists fucktrump who gives a s*** about him
Like you can still maintain
A flimsy
Formative support for Rodger Stone
Panda panda
You can do all of the things you need to do
For sure
It's a but you can't do them if Rodger still has influence over
And when Rodger goes to
Prison or
Is on his way to prison
You are free
That's what that's what I'm saying
Component
Man
The moment I don't have to look over my shoulder
You can't talk s*** about
Not yet
Play like it doesn't matter if I have any obligations
Lisa be like
For my audience I still support Rodger Stone
The moment I
Don't have to look over my shoulder
Is the moment I'm free
Agency over
I don't look I don't know what the future holds
This week
Have been Iowa
Like it really
It's difficult to listen to
I mean
Certainly there's a lot of stuff I had to look into
Like a lot of articles
Studies
Reports about vaccines
Because I wanted to talk
About that
When was the Emoji
It's it's
It's tough
I've not see
Like this from him in
In a long
Long f******
Not even the night where he cried and the dirty assholes
Not anything close to that
This is sincere
This is
Protracted
December 25th
If you'd say year of Our Lord dirty as a
Rodger Stone chefs Islip the dirty assholes
Or the equipment or the equivalent Rogers
Emotional
This is subdued
The natural
Have to it
And I think it indicates
Very strongly
That whatever happens
The next week or
Or whatever
He's done
Alex is done talking to Rodger
And having him run the
The show
Back to Alec
And we will see
Do you still able to do that
The problem with that prediction
Is that the way that your predictions
Episode
Belies are
Constant truth of
We think Alex
Who's going to do this thing
World's wrong
29-28
So predictable I meant metaphorical right
But if Alex is getting back
To where he was in days past unpredictable
I'm excited for that
You know what I like about Rodger
He reminds me so much of the Somali pirates
I hate Alex Jones
The piece of s***
The monster lights
Supremacist
Nationalist
A bigot of all order
Like
The monster is
Influence in society
But
That being said
I will always prefer
Free Trump Alec
To Trump Alex
There is a distinct difference between them
Not on an ethical
Put on a I'm interested in this
Alex is free
Like I want to go back to
To who I used to be
I'm never going to be against it
Metaphorically
Politico
Stupid you are
Thank you Alex
Thank you for indicating that you want to come back
Straight present-day episodes
Alex and the present day is so boring I want to go back to 2009
To straight episode
It's f***** up to
Because I have so many things that have been in the works and we have
We have other things that like we have been planning
And they all got thrown off by Rodger Stone
The timing of the world
It works
Serpentza
What time do just got to let go and let God
We have to accept what the episodes
We do will be what
We'll talk about it at the beginning of the next episode but if
If you're still listening
Next week we're only going to have the Monday and Friday episode I will be on vacation
I'm so pleased
Forgive us but
Back on Monday but until then
Read website
I'll try.
Alright
What if you do that
Earlier this week
Episode
And someone got sassy with them and eyes are
Responsible
Super awesome I really f****** guy what is a
Yeah what a cool guy
A f****** cool guy
Weird Beauty point where two years ago we started this a don't give a s***
We're expecting
I liked his show quite a bit
Is just out of nowhere recommending our show to pee
That's very cool
Very cool I couldn't have happened without all of you listen
And especially the members of our Facebook group
Tell your mother you're brilliant that's correct anywhere else on iTunes
Cooper
If you like
General stubblebine
Growing fruit
Who's the military deers nevermind
I will tell you this
Spider leadership
But doesn't it doesn't exist
Although they do
Yum yum
Yum yum time before they before they met
One guy you probably killed
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work