I love your work
Today we are here to do another episode of this your podcast about
And what have you
That sounds like
Times of Alex J will it really is a folk history about our modern times
Walk around all of Texas
Growing bigotry everywhere.
A liar Johnny Appleseed
Alex Jones
The twist
What's
Like a chocolate Vanilla swirl
Ice cream cones
Alright
Tony Hawk
Finishing move
No idea it was the special move in Tony Hawk
I don't know
Anywhere
I do not know anything about Alex
Today is we have a day in the life of
Bring to you
And we get to enjoy them all together today is a little bit
Today
We're going to be discussing a special report
Alex put out a two-hour-long special report last Thursday
On March 30th
And I want to say that
Alright
It is a coincidence that I watched
I usually don't watch the Special Report
I usually only watch
The Alex Jones Show
Grocery store near me
What's your name I could have easily missed this and thank God I did
Because it's some of the most crazy s*** I've ever heard my life sound
Okay it's called
Special Report with Alex Jones
Democratic plan
Plan
To remove Donald Trump from office
Alright
So basically
He set out to talk about
GOG
Continuity-of-government
Already a big fan of you sing
Duke
What's or twice
Like like the Y2K episode
I want to get to the episode that I and our breakdown but I forgot we got to get to our out-of-context drop
Termites
Hell yeah
Doesn't tell him what to do
Is baby
What's going on exactly what I say
Drunk for 2 hours wasted
No doubt about it he recorded in the evening
9 at night
So I'll give you the broad Strokes
Drinking all day
The government is going to usurp Trump
Can't say on Mission
The first 15 minutes are boring as s***
Of course you get to Rodger Stone in
And they have an interview 60 minutes
And Alex loses the chef
So we're not going to talk much about the Rodger Stone portion of the show
Because quite honestly it's
Just the two of them doing like a wrestling shoot promo about like
Come at me b**** trying to flex on the house intelligence committee
To arrive around the 17-minute mark
Alex Jones
It's probably my favorite clip
We've ever played on this show
I don't know how anything
I've listened to this
Conservative estimate 40 time
I am ready I am now let me tell
Okay I love the gray fox
But Chef looks like the archetype
C*********
With those little deer in the headlight eye in all his stuff
And there's something about this
Hopping around bossing everybody around trying to intimidate people like me and you
I want to tell Congressman Schiff
And all the rest of them
Hey listen a****** quit saying Rodger and I
You son of a b****
What the f***** your problem
You get my face without I'll beat your goddamn ass of a b**** you piece of s***
You f****** cross the line
Get that through your f****** head pushing your s***
You're the people that have this country over
Cusses like a f****** eight-year-old
Discover how the word f*** works
The fact that he won can't pronounce archetypal
Greatpeople
Fix connectivity.
Does he not understand words
I think he doesn't understand how hateful
Especially his words
How do I love that. I almost want to play it again
Just rewind the podcast let's do it again
Enter a speech tournament
Pretender in high school
Send to good that clip should be an indication of
20 years
Non-Stop
Non-stop stream of invective
Thrown around like an idiot
Don't call me a Russian
I don't know I don't know if I have the clip of him saying this cuz I think it was surrounded by 9
Nothing but he is like
Absolutely not
Like Rodger stone is sitting there while he's on this
This is wild Rogers
Is a p****
Alex down the road today
August
Like a threat
Rodger Stone response is just
I don't think I've ever been involved in the campaign
Bro
12:00 Offutt Hillary Clinton a Chinese agent
Every time you're on the f****** show
He's questioned Barack Obama's legitimacy
Patriotic
For China
I'm lovely
These guys
Stupid
So crazy. Every time somebody
Finally likes
Received
What is the fair doing
They just lose their s*** and they
Can't make that
Small connection from
When somebody says this
I wonder if other people feel this way
When I say that they just can't do it
Little jump
All you have to do
Stop for 1 second
Meanwhile later on we're going to get into Alex really going hard about how everyone hates him
Because he loves everyone
Empathy argument for later
Alex
Swearing and running his mouth which is followed up by there
Pisses me off man down
Violation of Center rolls
Is is a violation of the rules I get
Again in reference to John McCain talk about Rand Paul
Rules
We would never insist
That Russians infiltrate our government
Left Emily not violating rules
Everybody needs to go one by one down that little outfit you have on air
Portasoft
It's not like we don't support the
Most corrupt
Ministration
United States
The contacts
This is about John McCain
In Russia
Interesting euthanasia
Russia on the senate floor
Against the rules
Some conservative
The question the patriotism of some liberal
Believe me the said it would being high.
Exactly right thank you should have been because she broke
So important
I really hate it I hate
I hate the calling Elizabeth Warren Pocahontas
That's entirely possible was she ever centered on the senate floor
101 watch Pocahontas 2
Gives up a little bit of insight into why Alex might be this drunk
Fall Apart
Over the past couple months
And this is just
Pure
Abject
He's hitting board sort of roadblocks and Hazards than mr. Magoo
Like he's just he's blindly stumbling through
You f***** up your your ads are gone now
So you got another
Piece of bad news
Clearly
Before this one
I'm going to theorize
Started his drinking
What I'm going to describe as one of the saddest sales pitches I've ever heard Rodger Stone
News on Skype anything's background like some soda
Floating head
What's the name of that like Bo
The guy who would give them missions on Power Ranger
V
Another one
Rodger Stone looks like
Thousand
4-channel least do millions of their blocking us
Knowing your own Facebook page going your own whatever is Rodger Stone
This is the information I don't want you to ask infowars.com live show
Infowars.com live show
Real Alex Jones whatever
Trailways Rodger Stone
We're moving forward
I just understand that I'm up here at 9:27
I'm so honored
Chubby here but just understand its people shopping and it for store.com
It was four years ago that we're putting on iodine supplements Ignacio boards everywhere
Because we have people
Basically doing industrial sabotage blockers
Because you can be used to make a bunch of stuff
Element
Okay
Restraining illegal
But you get their crystals
From Jeepers mining
That's something only
Drug companies
It's really important.
At this point
At this point we haven't gotten
To really the bad news portion of it yet
Just going on
Just become
Pretty
So powerful
We have
We had this for years I've had some of the biggest companies out there, try to buy it from us
And
They wanted us to then be able to just put in shampoo
Real Gone
It's a distillate or a derivative or
You know something else that yet sometimes like oils at 6,000 ft I get that little side shooting
Shepherd
Robert Townsend
Talking about fair warning
Selfish
8 minutes long
He still hasn't gotten to the bad-news portion of it to
He's taking a powder
Staring into
Camera middle-distance Fairfax Boulevard
Least-liked walk on and off
The screen from time to time you can't tell cuz most of the time the cameras on Alex he's just giving like an empath
Disability
Call Rob
Bullets for everyone
Falling asleep and then
Waking up in the middle of the story
Yep God exist
Is
Maybe
35 minutes
The two hours
And
I have documented evidence that he was drinking
Throughout the two hours
You treated at the picture
I found pictures and I also like playing
That made me realize that he's drinking
Is Rodger Stones video is on
You can hear him flirt
You can hear a gulp sound effects into the mic
No I want to be totally clear we're drinking champagne and we're up front about the differences were honest about it
And we're not missile lining
Every minority
What one of those two things is more important than the other but we're doing but they work together to make us in the clear
For drinking on our podcast
Secret drinking
And trying to get everyone to be scared of Muslim
I've never been drunk enough
Geologist
Most families done at military
Family business
Here is
Hydrolysis Texas
Is that
We have the last shipment coming up
About to sell out of one more shipments coming in 20000 bottles normally last 6 months
And now they found out
Fonte
I will let the mother like Rodger that and also the senator attacking Rodger
And so
They try to shut us down getting the distillate from seaweed to still DEA control cuz it's 999
Jennifer you want the 9999 you know how to infinity bracelet
You did
The globalist Soros
We don't want
Behind the scenes State even had
My people are like look leave it alone we're probably going to fix it don't make any shoe
He's not the best type of garbage
This is incredible stuff is helping her B help me
The whole backstory I will if I have to but
This may be the last shipment we get of this
Nobody else has got deeper Crystal forces
I'm still 30% off
Progressive that off
Yeah don't worry about that
XX
I don't know which side I'm going to come down on and believe
I think it was probably just a market
Turn slightly and they're going to
They're trying to charge him more
For it
Exclamation
Suppliers are being threatened and s*** like that
We do have to listen to the rest
I thought
Cut it we have to listen to rest of this cuz that's where it gets into people being threat
Why do we need
Purest
Do you think anybody would notice
Regulated by the FDA
Everybody
That comes up towards the end
Sales pitch cliff
Pretty f***** up things about people getting threatened
Homeopathic medicine
Hey we have to get the purest of
We can't get the shity
You just find growing in the side of your
Alliance Group
Yeah
Horse and carriage
That contest Rodger Stones book
Trump 2020 shirts when they like 45 bucks for operation
Today
It's not just Asia it's his Daily Caller it's it's everybody that
I wonder
In the snow
When you get Rodger Stones bucket give it to somebody that don't know the truth are you get a t-shirt
You connect to wish you and your family need to begin with
Hello
But what I've got
A really good product
DeSean Jackson
It's another big Nashville manufacturer that's one of the top
Yo you view private labeled our stuff and we appreciate you but
We just got threatened
This is obviously Larry C Johnson
Yeah that was not a
No use a discredited of rumormonger race-baiter
Horrible piece of s***
In essence
That's the shorthand for the
You know call him out by name but it will happen with Larry Johnson
He's about to get kicked out by Alex
Reset Legend
I can't come on anymore if they're threatening my business and my family this guy was a section chief
The world
Start threatening him so bad for coming on supporting Trump
He's rolling over and it's white
It makes you feel really cold
It makes you feel alone I'm not saying he's not a man and not tough
It's just like
But this death is rolling over to these people
It pisses me off when they
Kohl's
Rebecca too late
F*** Japanese girl what else
That goes to the pool
Drunk person
I've been this guy so many times
But I've been smart enough
Not to be on
Erase baiting
Political talk show that I have started
Wow I
Did you ever consider that they don't cover any new topics in this two-hour broadcast
Hotwire
But there's no reason to have done in the first place
Clearly
To make this
Sales pitch
What about using your language
He sped up to do with it
Instead of doing that thing
Keep walking
I think there was still a part of him that. Like alright we are going to cover the Coggs
Will get a lot of plugs in on the way
I'll scare people that won't have iodine anymore
Amanda Jones
Got a got a cookout
No one
Why would anybody threatened or maybe Larry Johnson
This is not good
And I don't want those negative parts of Larry Johnson
What people have forgotten about
And the fact
Judy's not allowed
On cable news shows anymore
Doesn't get a lot of bad
Publicity
Kiko's on Infowars
And all that stuff comes back up negative tweet
I'll be looking like you're a liar and a race-baiter
F*** is wrong with you
Imagine that
So there was some attention
You are the only person that watches info and whoever
I swear
Nobody else's
Watch the show
And this is just some weird kind of
Experiments that Stanford
You're the test subject
I think that's what happened
Brought back up to him he doesn't like it so Alex's ass
You know what that was negative for me I don't want to do it now it's can't handle that
The globalist must have gotten to her and Rodger Stone
Or Superman
Their Shadow Boxing
With a non-existent anime
The globalist
Edit really easy for them
Alright
They're finally they seem to be going down
Just because
The globalists have
There I on Alex Jones
In the past does not necessarily mean
They are not turning
Also this week is accused of being of Transylvania in stock
I don't want to ask this question cuz I see you
Alright
Transylvania real
Israel
You know what I mean
And you know that you know he doesn't
He does not know the Transylvania is a real place
He's a real place stinks Transylvania the country probably
He picks the Transylvania exist
Open the world
The dark lord Dracula
Excellent
They're chopping them off right in front of me
I could have sold who wants power over people
Call Alex Padilla
Kick your ass outside
Adjectives
6 ft tall
Flip flop three grades model weigh 200 lb
Diverticulitis 140 lb person I crawled on top of him
Nocatee.
All the way
He better not find out about our shell
Also did you notice that
The phrasing in there really strongly implies that he's put multiple people in Tacoma
Normally I would say
Exaggerating
This strange thing there was
Really long pause
Like suddenly
Maybe I shouldn't have done
Baby this is not the right road to go downtown
People that are
One hand
According to his story
And I don't
Disagree that someone
You should stand up to a bully
I don't think you should be proud
Strong indication that he has no ability to control his temper
He's beaten
And with the crowd
You put this guy in a coma and then
Tacoma
And that led to
Family fuk up
Situation
Is mental illness which
We don't know what it is
But if it's clearance
I quit
Every every idea of normal or saying I have
If it is also applied to him I am I mean
Just at this particular in
Begin that like it's
Real toxic masculinity
Fetishizing of violence
Incredibly stupid
Well yeah
Cox
Alex Jones
And it's not
These agencies and Groves don't reach out don't do things
For PR purposes
It's because they're risking their lives even talking to me
About 30% of the CIA
All the guys that do The Killing
Casey Johnson
Night
Percent agency
This debate
But they said that the guys who do The Killing
Love Trump
Don't you think if the guys who do the killing love because
They're going to do more to like if you really break I don't know
Sickly what the ratio of Those Who Kill and those who don't
Agency
Slow on the kill site
Okay
Although although
Ghetto it is one of those things
Franklin
Everybody
Is a murderer
Would you say maybe 50 50
I would say there's no way that the support structure is equal to
Doing the Killer
Cluding drones in the doing the killer I think you talkin about
Dirt bike 150 me the number for movies
The Killing
20 dozen
Got real mad
Elvis's Rock rages Channel Improvement
90%
That 80% because the killing for truck
20%
So then in order for all of its percent
I have to mean
That more than 90% of that 80%
I am not more than 90%
It still got to be like
70%
In order to compensate
Who cares what a map is really struggling
It is his argument that 90% of the people who do The Killing
Trump
80% of the total
Support Trump
Beans
Well that's majority of the analyst also support Trump
These numbers are fake
Be possible
Is that I talked to folks either all over
The Special Operations Command everything
I've been on the fence before
Republican
Approve Trump's wall
How is How is
Possible
How is that possible that you
That you make that
Because
It's like like
Trump
Sad
I'm going to let Obamacare fail
Intentionally
Because
Like they're not
There's 200 even
White did it in the first place if this is just a natural
Elise cowardly
Dispute
Intention
Prosperity
He talks about
These small business optimism index
Thanks
I found this
Statistics that he
Statistic
National Federation of in
Independent businesses
Small business index
I don't believe that the March 10th
But you should tell her that audio
I think it's like
Like 20-something
Statistical point
They analyzed
Of small businesses like
They're plants in Greece
Employment plans to make Capital outlays plants
Inventory
Current inventory
How businesses
And how they think they're going to be doing in the future
In February
The optimism index
Drop point six point
But it still
Really high 1.1
Actually I mean that's really good you look at the numbers around the election
Because of Trumps like we're going to get we're going to get rid of the factory have to pay for your employees insurance
Things like that that makes businesses optimistic
So it's not necessary
No employees are very very not out to visit cuz they want insurance
It's good to have and they want protection
Great thing that they
How they cannot make even the
Latest
Between
When it's super low
And then Trump taking over
When it's super hot
In the meantime
Something may have happened
Is what we can talk about
The stock market rise
This I think is directly related to
Small jumpers directly related
Where do you think it was in 2000
Back to 2000
The claim that it's the highest it's ever been since patently false
It was as high or higher is almost like 107
So
The optimism was even higher
Now there's a little bit down and like 2008/2009
What Market was falling apart
Way down I'm looking at it right around like 81
And then
There was a progress
Does natural Epsom salt Epsom Downs
Dramatically
It's it's a it's a projection of
The concept of how
And that's
It is kind of
A silly thing
Because
These people
You go well
And they think it's going to
Wilshire and components
Of the small business
Optimism
Index
Like if you look at the individual pieces
Here's where we are for February 2017
Businesses that plan to increase employment
Is it 15%
Which is down
From where
Time they took the measurement
January
Plants
Is it
3%
The business is actually concrete growing is only at 3%
Which is up 1% from January but
And I whatever
Sales to be higher down 3%
Now is a good time to expand
3%
Caters of like
Actual optimism are going downwards
So
Everybody
Does an artificial optimism
Earnings
He's lied
The people who voted for
Mobile
LV Small Business Association
Remember that literally every horrible person
Whatever
Best Westerns to all of you
Like he's like some
Protestant bible thumper
Diamond we see it happening
70 days into office
All these assholes
Killing your mouth off about
That wrote the book on
Can you speak about that continuum
Brought up
Some of the things we talked about and just
And trucks were made you know about put the Army around the house but
You know.
What does Trump need to do to stop.
It's Criminal
Not to stop major media organizing
Little Albert
That's not happening
That's not what Trump
Start by being honest
And then resign
Stop
But also
Ourselves
This is all a question
This is all set up a question
I don't want
Kevin just gloves are coming off bro
Because he's people
It's counting down here man punch me in my family
Without the
Are you
You hold it all back
No
We let them start
Cuz I don't want
He doesn't want
You know what I started to come around on a new series at Alex
Explain in person
I think Alex
Desperately want
Drop to get impeached
Forsyth
That is only the only
He
You know how we talked about how he didn't want Trump to win
I'm going back on that I think you did want him to win
But since he's one he started to realize
He's starting to realize that all of his narratives are busted
Every single
Statistically quotes is wrong
Stories that he site
Don't say what he thinks it says
It's becoming impossible for him to defend
People like Flynn
We have to bend in the past
Is it possible
Nunez at this point
Dennis Montgomery Road
Isn't
Frustrated
Canvas and already so I can twist the narrative
He doesn't know how to win
It's not that though I don't think
I don't think the winning is the problem I think it's the being
Being attached
Do this thing
This this tumor on the side of him
Is so counter 27
Growing out of it
Watchmen
I can open a beer about it
That already dated reference
Just say the word fetty wap on it at one time
Please make a video where you fix it
Trump then we could get all my God I can't
I can't imagine how he mispronounced it Raceway
I think it is
The only one who's talking about Trump being assassinated
Really far-out people
No One support
Even though the writing on the wall
Need to talk about that he's going to
Really at this point with this type of person would only hurt you
Against the person like this
If you kill them
Is for Trump to go down it
The probably pretty likely
Presents
Or I want all of his money taken away
Popper
And we bring back
And we all go
Get to throw one tomato at
Just like just like my Siri is are just like my prescription for Richard Spencer and
You got one pot
Is the punishment for treason instead of
Dillingham
Punishment
I think
The archetypical Cox account just line up every citizen every illegal
Just punch you in the gut
See now that's that's not a good idea that you just laid a trap for illegal immigrants
But now we know where they are what's wrong with you
Immigrant
Horrible thing could have backfired into a even more horrible thing
Like any of them
Rodger Stone before we get into uncharted waters with Alex Jones
Rodger Stone on Friday was on Bill Maher he was on real time
Belmar
F****** idiot
Is a f******
Staying islamophobe
He is the worst the most recent Chris Hayes
If you watched most of it
I'd like Louise Mensch is on
Largely
F****** conspiracy theorist
Not in the same vein as a lot of people like
Conspiracy theory
It fair to paint her with the same brush
But I will say that if
If you want any kind of journalistic integrity
You definitely don't
That's fair
I don't want to unpack all that I'm not going to go to bat for her
Alex Jones Show
So
Garages for Alex Jones listeners the same podcast
Who was the one who was talking about how
They're terrible
I don't know anyway that was like
This week Rodger stone is on and that's why he's got go to bed bed
And leave Alex
At this point
Alex
Cox outage
Stone to Bill Maher but then also
He's got bigger balls than
Mark Warner
But they tape it live he hates Infowars
94.com we're winning
I want to see if that gets in there so promise me you'll do that right
You got it you have my promise
Rogers town I don't know I didn't watch it
Do you know that
Piano
Pathetic
Doing great please
So at this point Rodger Stone go to bed bed cuz he's a seventy-year-old man
Should have stopped
God because I found
And how stupid he's been up to this point
Without Rodger Stone to ground him
He is
Losing it
The rest of this episode
These clips
Somewhat
Hard to figure out what I'm talking about
This is what is right after Rodger sound
Okay immediately
Nothing nothing
Nothing that would make this make sense
So here we go
Money is literally like a video game
Fighting the big boss
Money literally I mean
Why do I have a Dodge Hellcat
I've never bought in my life of $63,000 Bill
Banks around like $25,000 for trucks they're awesome
That's all I need
Looks like Ferrari makes this now and it's 700 horsepower
And it's America
That's not what her are you
Also these Clauses he's burping
What are we
He loves his whiskey
I don't want to share that with him
Because everyone I know.
I could see that
Doesn't
Drink Scotch
No
I don't remember I know the Joe Rogan mentioned what it was when he was on the road
Experience
Bravo talks about how he was drinking before the episodes
A picture of
Lucy Oliver
B
But he's done
Talk about cars
Fact that I want this
Dodge Hellcat
Challenger
Because it was you couldn't
You couldn't get a car
For $300,000
Million-dollar Ferrari that's fast
But it wasn't he one of the patch car
So fast
Horsepower
It was that was so Americana
Okay
And so anti algor but also because it was black
And just look like a regular
Challenger
Daddy likes fit into my cosmology
A race car but it is
Also what are you tracking
America
Is everybody knows
Dodge Challengers Americans
Dream of buying a Dodge
Challenge
It's in the Constitution
But I do like that
It doesn't look like it's erased his cosmology
Of things
Not appearing to be what they are
Cosmology
What I think he means is his life's philosophy
Mars in
No but I think what he's trying to say is that his life is
Predicated on the belief that things aren't what they appear.
Okay and if he was trying to say that
Exegesis
Credit than he has ever deserve
Crazy man on the train
I have to at least try and pour sound like
And I would agree with him that his life is about that but not in the way he think
You saying that
I see the hidden reality behind
Things
For the truth is like
You are not what you appear to be
You appear to be a conservative talk show host
And you're out now traven propaganda
So I kind of get it
Is that what he said
Again it might be the twin coming out to e.r.
A part of him that is desperately wanting to come clean
How far does he go
Before he actually does
Come clean
No
He finally
Fully taken down
And he sits there going
We're shuttering the door
And I refuse to rhyme that with whatever the name of the show or website
I think you have to have
Excessive lawsuits
Or something like that
Cuz it would take more than Glenn Beck
Like
He's going to flame out
Absolutely
Drunkenness is not going to help
For some positive to your question
I think the
He's
At this point
If I
If I know Alex like I think I do
I think he is in a battle
Between
Not being able to
Carry the load anymore
And how guilty
He feels
About
Selling out glass
20 years of his quota
For Trump
To go down
I think that's what he's due
Little bit
The Narrative of flip
And that's why
The next episode
Massively about pizza
Yeah whole situation with him
And I think that
I think
With Dennis Montgomery stuff
With one attempt
Triumph the narrative
Everything will be fine
You can't do that there's no legs.
So now he's going like
I'm going to be a crusader against pedophilia
And maybe
For a bit
I think buying time
So he doesn't
Have to face them
I might be pregnant again I might give it to my brother
To me it seems like he doesn't have good
People
Talking to
Because of the because of that earlier Clippers like
Low-level employees like
Dude
We can still make
Get through this
Chill
You
A little while
We'll get back we'll get right back to being in the spotlight will get I'm a hundred percent guessing it's raw
Rodger Stone
And Jerome Court
Other person in the studio
Alex Alex
Alex's talking and facing the other direction
That's so beautiful I can't imagine Paul Joseph Watson
Has any advice to give them
Right
They're still around
Eddie never mentioned that be
Some reports
Biggs on Twitter
Pennywise
Exposure
He's doing
Propaganda on
Get through the rest of this clip about Alex's
The reason I raised that is
What you got
Fog
And a house I'm like wanting to downsize
From my four bedroom
But I've got a bunch of children
My fortune
Are boosters for now
Cuz there's some interesting us old sweethearts
The same room together cuz
I don't like living in rich people neighborhood
It's just us feel good
I'm trying to find something compound something
Blue collar
And says that I'm
Stretch
I want you to be well be dependent but it's not my God
Sell my car just because
About 22 years
I don't need some really fast I'm driving fast I just need to be
I just go back to my
Ford F-150
Shmoney
Need money otherwise this on air
Kid reason ice cream
Because he was getting that
Said that on air
He's had another kid
He's had another kid I don't know when Eid but like recently
As recently as a few months ago he said
Pretty recently
Alright
Positive
Right
I don't know if that's true
I don't know
No I want to occasionally
Off-limit is 26
I think it's whatever neutral pronoun
Them
But
The idea that he doesn't talk about his kids on the air because
There's so many threats against the little sweetheart
That's weird
Paranoia
That's a gentle soul
Broken
Is not the word I would use
Drunk
Next clip
Pointers I'm not doing what I do for money
Yes
Chop my right arm off right now
Do it
Is coming
Doesn't mean
I got all the answers just I'm not out to get you
Put in pauses
These are this is how he's talking
Searching for
Threat
The normal talk show host would make $10 a year
Rossweisse
Highest
Tasty Tacos
Starbucks
Definitely
So no power
I pulled up forbes' list of the top radio host
They have a list
Yeah
Number 6
16 million dollars last year
Bill O'Reilly comes in a number 58
18.5 million
Just on his radio show
Syndication
Love you goodnight
Number for Sean Hannity
The number for
Number three
What will
Ryan Seacrest
Does he have
Everybody lies Mary dollar
Rush Limbaugh
Rush Limbaugh with 79 million
A number one
Howard Stern it's still around
Adult
$5000000 Chopsticks paid
Radio how is Alex Jones
Conversation
Even on that I can find
I mean like we talked about I can't get who
I can't get a Freedom of Information Act going for his
Can't find a list
Listenership
The top listenership radio shows
In the country is Morning Edition on NPR
14.7 million listeners
Number to All Things Considered also on NPR
14.4 million what
Number three
Rush Limbaugh
13.25 million
Listeners every week
Before
With 12.5 million
Delilah Delilah
Pulling in an average
8.8 million listeners a week
That we dropped a little
The Savage Nation
Michael Savage's show
5 million
Which is good
Still
Substantially below out
Coasttocoastam little bit further down the list of Love Coast to Coast
Love hearing area talk
All right until I realize the George Noory is like an Obama birther
California
The coast to coast overnight
And George Noory
What used to be Art Bell but then he fled to the Philippines
You just wanted to get off the grid
You wasn't being chased or anything like that that run
Play George Noory took over and where at
Georgia
He used to do like even radio in St Louis
He's just
Awesome
He talks about life
Ghost
Okay aliens
An ancient civilizations until like that
Special
Is most of the time is open line
Awesome
Unfortunately I realized I realized
As conservative as crazy conservative as a lot of people
Like the Michael Savage
With alien talk
How do you combined with aliens
How is it that you feel that way
Look I believe in
Christian
I really believe
Also aliens
Goats
Interesting interview with Duncan Trussell talks about some of that stuff
Interview
Interesting
A little frustrating
If you want his position
They have 2.75
Million
Top 20 listen to radio shows in the country
Not at all
The last 15 million
But give you some
Contact whoever heard of Kim Komando Show
Conceivably what this means because these numbers are based on Nielsen
Professional aggregate
Alex is on terrestrial radio
He would be covered by
Yeah statistic
Glenn Beck program
Include Sean Hannity Rush Limbaugh
Michael Savage
Coast Coast AM radio station
Have to
However
We dunno
You do not have to
Very public contract making is the you have NPR on the same list at Michaels
There's clearly no bias
List
I am
The fact that Alex Jones
Is not on there means that his actual radio audience
Does less than 2.5 million
People wait
It does have
A number of people who watches videos on
Directly through the website
I can't possibly end up being
Question
Do you think he's gained listeners since he's become
What like what would you call him now like a boogeyman like somebody that
Is much more in the spotlight
Just as just
The old people like watching
Cinememes
Do you think that any
As a as a
Because at now with
The world works like that f****** guy who murdered Trayvon
Will not say his name
I hope
He's I hope it gets there by 2
Whenever that happened
He got millions for his defense fund
Because
Conservators are like
I think as a backlash to this making fun of him
People who have rallied around a little bit
But
Statistically speaking based on these numbers that we have from the Nielsen rating
It can't possibly be
I'll be honest with you we know we reach
45 million people a week
The fact that we bring the amount of money we bring in
It's nothing
How the Super Bowl has 80 million viewers and brings in
$5000000 whatever
We have that amount of yours a week
Money but it shows how
Where is ninjas AR bigger
When you don't have it
We don't have the big corporations on the elite
Who know their advertising in a failure
Another putting money into doesn't bring back 10% what the effect
But their tithing
Got prop up there a lot
Nope
45 million people are watching a week is
45 million people
Absolutely ludicrous that number is unbelievable
Like the Super Bowl is
Getting down closed
245 million.
The numbers are down
So that sir
Note 45 million people do not agree on anything
Rush Limbaugh's audience time
That's impossible it's just impossible
It's there's no way
There's no what
Baby world
Nope that's not possible either
Go to
$1000000
Year
$3000000
10 million dollars
12 minutes I was only on like 20 some radio stations play nice
A billy million-dollar
Oh I'm a sellout to some person actually isn't involved
Just can feel like a big man
Call shoun uccello
He works for the system or the co made-up crap or whatever weeks Lisa satellite from Clear Channel Reagan T&T we work for
Lisa satellite
Samsung TV right there
Local companies that
Work Samsung
You can as well
Cast of crew and elixirs that make all the spots
I'm just an average guy with a $300,000 car
Just like every average
Plumber average this dodge Hellcat
Like you the average
I want to apologize because
But whatever the operating system that I'm in Gmail that plays audio attachments
Has changed
Overnight apparel and I can no longer load up clips and have them at the ready to press play
So sorry I am still getting used to not being able to give the setup
Somebody's going to
I'm a fuk
Or they're going to
Maybe upgrade your you alright bye
Everything I am at rehearsal
That's why I'm actually want to cuss which I want to do in 20 years
Her so clear
I don't sit here and say
Buy our products
I have a bigger house
To impress
People I want to live in a country
Family comes they got a bed to stay on the couch
You really thought that something was coming there right
Other than people
George Soros
Pacific
Stuff
Hello pool a car
Medicine I just want money to live just like you do
Were you don't get the money you need to live till you get the picture like today
Exactly what
That's exactly
Elixir taking away asthma
Riley has to change
Birth crystals
Takes away my
I want all the birth crystals
Don't talk about how you don't want money in your
Sales pitch
It's too obvious
Yeah it is very much is a dick
Donations to the patreon or whatever
I always walk it back a little bit
Cuz you don't want money
I don't care
Your third home
From the money
Play my shity apartment in Chicago yet my third shity apartment
This is this place
Does it matter
It's
Compare myself to him
And I mean it
The truth
Whether or not
We have been
George Soros offered
Number 3 Scott Aukerman
Did you literally have that list right in front of you number two is
Marc Maron
Knowledge fight
You f****** soulmate
You're a liar you're a liar Alex Jones doesn't
Explain what
We all know that it's too busy
He is also because he so drunk
He's going to end up getting sidetracked
He's going to miss you scripture
Again
Corner of old smokey
He's going to blast
I love it with back-to-back
They're shaming us
They're shutting down
Did you chop
Lust
Consideration people
Ar240 hardmoore
New crew and expand
Preachers in Dallas
Widow's Mite Yoshi at nothing
Chats Malayalam whatever
Then.
Jesus
I want
Better sitting out there thermoplastic wealthy
You think I got where they are
When do stocks and bonds giving nothing to nobody
Or maybe they gave something to some dumb-ass charts
Putting monkey bomb ilysm
F****** talking about
The church is the bride of Christ
Yes but also
I want to say
Just said there
You middle class and rich people
Who have all these stocks
I haven't given it to anybody
Sick that makes you wealthy
He is staying at Analog
Of Obama's you didn't build your business
Oh s***
You're right
The spirit of what he saying
He's so mad about is the eggs
Zack Same Spirit
Everything
Baby got serious about
Use the word
Literally
Can we just one time
Can we just
Get something like that
Have him looking at
Steam self
You too drunk to focus when he looks in the mirror also
This is my dream
So but you also
Done right now
You picked up on
That little parable
Paraphrase
Banana
He seems to think it was a lottery
Instantly know that
Culver's right there
VIP is like riches in heaven
No
She had nothing
To give
But that's a high priority of the church
And the good works
Is more valuable than your thousand
And it's because of what it means
Alex seems to think
The point of it is
Cuz I ain't
And
She'll be there soon
Look
That lady
Not afford Healthcare
So when she died
Oh man
Good stuff
Even if it's not good
What's the exchange rate
Who played well after brexit it's a lot less
Antibiotics
Churches
You buy water filters you're not dragging websites and all the other chemicals hundreds of
Apps to change my wife
You buy bio selenium
They're non-GMO
Forest Alabama
Everything I do empowers you
But you haven't
And the regenerative
Process of creativity
Realized
Everything
Pastor benefit me and everybody involved
Process of
Creative
You mispronounced
Is saic
I like it
Cotija
More drunk
Watching
Because he has a cup
Okay I will say this at the end of it
You look
Deflated
Like it's kind of a conversation he's having with Rob do
At the end of that
Coming up I don't want to spoil anything
Year
Off-base
I was talking to a New York art dealer New York
Strangely.
Trump Tower in penthouse
When one of The Heirs of a major
Restaurants
New York
After 9/11
Immoral
There's this place where
People would pay $59
Truskulls with Swisher rhinestones on it
Did somebody with Leprosy jacked off on
And I was like why would you spend
50 million dollars
But something so ugly and pathetic
You don't get it Alex to
Sacrilegious
The fact
$15 15
Hundreds of thousands of African Starving Children
And the fact that they gave it to some weird degenerate artist
Put a skull with rhinestones
A skull may be worth $500
And then they metaphorically
Gave their seed to death not to a woman to create life it was worshipping death
It was a death offering a death called offering
50 of 54 million dollars to newspaper
Semen covered skull
And then you understand everything
Oh my God
Oh yeah
Go and they pay millions a week
They go back to their pen houses
And they
That's why they burning I know because that was money for poor people exactly
It's it's
It's as good as killing a kid
She ripped off from stockholders
Can buy a skull covered in disease
Worship
Association
Spreading our link spreading our articles
Can Google wall Street's addiction to
Journal article
Was it a New Yorker Max
So that is so awesome
That story is so awesome
Would you like to know what you're talkin about
I just want to live in a world where
Kids golf
So
I can find no evidence of semen plays into this at all
Especially
I couldn't even find that on
Crazy blog
Like I was even looking at World News Daily
Daily Caller
Any salacious
Talkin talkin talkin about the sculpture called for the love of God
It was created by artist named Damien Hirst
Took a skull
And then made a platinum
Cast of the skull
And covered it with 8601
Actual flawless diamond
Not Alex Jones is fake.
8601 real diamond
Where to get
They were actually he did document they were ethically-sourced
Anything like that
Well
They were
Different type of
The name of the work
In case you were thinking it is some sort of religious thing for the love of God
It's based on his mom
Damien Hirst
Mom
And she would say for the love of God what are you going to do
Right to his mom's quote necessarily
On it that you bought
Legally
And then in the middle
I don't know and then he also has a
Giant pink diamond on the forehead
That sort of the centerpiece of it if you want
That's the that's the furlough
God peace
Such a bummer
Kind of
It's a little bit of a bummer because it is expensive
Is it cost 14 million lb for him to make
Because of all the time and platinum
And and the because of a labor of Alex's like
They paid 54 million dollars for semen covered skull
Sell it
Why
Yeah she ended up having to buy it along with a Consortium
We put together a collection of people who bought it
Damien Hirst ended up
Essentially breaking even for this piece of art
There's two things that I think are really into
So I don't know a whole lot but when I was looking into it
What things was the commentary that people had like critics have
What is the modern
Art
Genre really is publicity
Right marketing is really one of the most modern art form
Able to use
Is more impressive
Don't know
If you sold it
Who bought it
The second thing
Is that
Consider the genre of a Memento Mori
Design to remind you of your mortality
Observe
The skull is out of this world Celestial almost
It proclaimed victory over death
Infinitely more
Sadness
Ventus theme the diamond skull is Glory itself
I know but that's all
We'll talk man
He's kind of interesting in that you have a skull which is kind of
The symbol of death
I meant you have
Attached to it
Platinum
I'm
Thousands of Realtors the piss out of
Materialism
And money in some way
It is supposed to have some common
Know whether it's some stupid piece
It is
Any of the legitimate
Might my first reaction to that
Sure
No it's
Also I do
It's possible
Give me my commercial for the socket
I got this
Deep Earth crystals
Universal
54 million dollars for this
Nope but then the idea that they're doing it to deprive kids could be saving or whatever is stupid
Absolutely if possible he was on a yacht with someone they lied to him
It's even more possible he has never been married
I don't understand
Little yachty and that is
Turn up
I know nothing about the money
People go and get art and then burn it
That is
Whole thing that
Higher two-minute clip is just Alex
Drunkenly talkingshit there's
Nothing there there
He's pausing
Really what he's doing is just
Trying to find a way to get into their killing
That's his main goal there is to find any way to make rich people
You need to do no further work
Then just saying
The art world is decadent
Excessive
We all agree with
Most people agree
Even if you
We're open-minded
We would agree with that statement
Yeah for the most I mean like even your your important artists
Probably like
Chinese artist who is
Openly
See you making the jerk-off symbol
The Chinese artist and activist
He's basically fighting
Chinese
Horribly repressive
Chinese government
Trying to censor every
Did he make
Stuff one of the big things that happened though is
He was part of the
Chinese Olympics
He was part of the design committee for
And he was the first person
As part of that too
Come out and say
This is just b*******
Propaganda
What I thought it was going to be is very
From what it wound up being okay
Imprisoned has jailed
Speaking out against
Blackshear
More
AR
At the end of the day the bottom line is Alex Jones
But
We can't take away from
Studied
Alex Jones
Has researched
I didn't f****** know what
Do you want to know what he study
Public exhibition of what you're doing gives it
More power when you do it
So you say oh we have photos of naked
Inflight showing our walls
And where the Washington Post promoting are deviantART
I said that I said the pizza place to Media focused on
I don't have it so bad
Alpana Singh all that they should be left alone because the media focused on them
I never brought up but I said to expose the real stuff
PowerBack
Realized
Travis Scott
These people want to be Machiavelli
They don't even know why they're
Worshipping
A skull
Somebody with diseases
Masturbated on
54 million dollars to
Virginia an idiot
Want to know more about him
I just saw him
Lima Library
Let's just jump
Destitute
This is more talk about
Further discussion on episode
No
Brain would allow that apology
Exist
And then just move on it had to come back to
Just working too
The James Oliphant has threatened
Confirmed he has said that
Filled
Retract that stuff on the air about it
I'm trying to transition it into I'm a defender of the
The children
And
Barbies for me I would never say that abusive children isn't the real issue
Is it absolutely a real issue
And I support
I don't
Support what he's doing
Anyway
We'll get to that in another time
This is
Adjust a straight-up lie about the situation with
I mean I wonder what's going to happen I don't even have a court case and it will look at my lips about it though
Retraction
Because
People that we chant
Bulshit
You know a basement small was it wasn't true and I saw I was like
Contact
What the hell is this
Cuz I want it I want to let his words play
But then also did the contacting
What are you talkin about
Yeah
Threatening a lawsuit
Tickets at. Wheels
What's on the news
I don't care what's on seeing this b*******
It was horseshit
She's got new that it was for a shed
Trick Alex Jones
Or just everybody
Pedophile
Elaborately running around of the government what have you
Of course
Everybody by
Thinking
The fact that it's happening
At what place
That discredits
Tylenol over the place
I want to be clear I was watching pizzagate happen from day one
Cruising
Conspiracy blogs
On the forums
I watch developed
I love it
When were Cruisin conspiracy blogs
But I when were Cruisin together
Watched it develop
From
The colonel
4 months ago or so
And the whole time
It was all about the
Everything was about
I watched videos
He's presenting his position on it is it
Completely
To one of our friends on Twitter
Oh yeah
Have a copy of one of the videos that Alex Jones deleted about Marrakesh
Thank You album
Is it go after our children
McCain
Corrupt
Set up a priesthood to sacrifice children
Too dark.
And that is still going on today
Before before he even gets into it I just want to say I've read all the way
The emails
Is not in
He hasn't read them
Pedal WikiLeaks
Basically gone from hero to villain
On all sides of the spectrum
Every single time somebody mentions WikiLeaks
You can almost guarantee 6 from
6 months from now
They will mention Wikileaks in the exact
Opposite
About the same time almost everybody will
If you might come out
I don't want to deal with you
A couple of these emails in the
He characterizes them makes it clear that he hasn't read them
Someone is just
And he has
Embellished
Can imagine our Alex
Not at all
Are you
Pizzagate is it called
Is a rabbit hole
The pizzagates existence
100% of it
100% of it was
About Clinton podesta the basement
Comet Ping Pong what the entire investigation
It was about
Instagram page
Weird things
S*** like that it was
Dumbest speculation ever
Can claim
We're covering this
Is Ludacris
Malik
Reposted
Is any fast should I guess on Wednesday if it went out Thursday on the Nightly News.
He's talking about joke videos
Then he got fired
Infowars.com pizzagate is real
Only question is
What exactly is it
The wrong manual this is this is
Emmanuel
I don't know why the pizzeria in the one down the street
After movie
I don't know why they got rock stickers there
What's going on
Genre
Oh no
Just stop there out there
In the hot tub for your
None of that was in the email that he reference
That podesta email was just someone
Who said that
Osoyoos
Did there be therefore Entertain Entertain
It's essentially being like hey there kids
Of this
Hand for good luck
Andy menschel
We've been over there
That's my parents would say if I was going someone's house
F****** pool
There's no way
That's all Alex Jones
Fetishizing
Editorializing
He's not
That's not based in reality
Seattle
And he's already
2 minutes into this clip he's already
Venture out to be a liar
It gets worse
Negative
Series M4
Uno
Look there are thousands
There are thousands of emails
Yakattack
Nothing to do with
Even
The fake code
Other fake pedophile code
If you want to attract
Pizzagate
Everywhere I Go
Specifically
Everybody who's like
Google
All the b******* and how it works
Is it Alex's position about what he reported
Stuff is
Total lie
Real dad
I'll see you at the feast tonight I do have lots of blood in semen oh good
Worshipping
Marina Abramovic
Oh okay
Lincys
They
Jewel encrusted skull of performance art
You know like these
Sort of thing she's an artist
Christian
Pizza maker
If you want to attack an artist
Trying to pretend that their art
Is literal
You're a hundred percent missing the point
Distinction between the world of
Fart
And the world of reality fiction and reality metaphor is literal and metaphorical
Is
100% literal
And suspect
Everything is
It will tell you what
Art is not Americana
Cars R Us
Especially Ferraris that are made in Italy
It is lost
Worship
Who doesn't
The photos and videos inside these places
You got to see it all
Go to infowars.com
Where we have posted all of this information about these specific supplies
What's on their menu on this special
The March 30th
This clip
We posted it as on our
Wright-Patt
He's dancing around
I don't think you did a good enough job Larry Overton is like
You know you know that
Do something
You could get sued
Just saying like I don't want to get sued if not
No no
What
Is that
Donald Trump
I'm just saying
I would give you a different example
Alex Jones has paid for multiple abortions
I don't care if you sue me
I don't want to get to f*** you
You know why
He said he's paid for me
Whatever we say I can back up with documentation or Alex Jones own words
What you're saying is that we have
Never gone to lock
No
Nor will we ever
F*** you
Listen to Alex Jones
And then you got to see the FBI law enforcement manual
I wouldn't be up you outside
The last couple weeks
Joann
Question is how real is it what is it something's going on something's being covered up needs to be investigated
These are real Wikileaks this is real stuff going on.
WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange
Documents
I'm not going to play all of this is a guy named John bowne
The guy like Mark Dice he makes videos and I was jump
Not as good as not as good as this guy
No absolutely not
I can see him just being like a
Like a studio musician
Hey weasel
Instagram halfway in a bottle
I don't play the whole thing cuz it's in the world
Eat pizza
Another 5 minutes or so I want to play
Illustrate
You did not
They have no radar
Things that are horribly bumped now at this point
This is John Powell saying you thing
Giving
Exactly
Hillary Clinton's campaign manager
Tony's
Email exchange
I would only wear in Washington DC
Pedophiles it's like he has the Bible
Call Reed
Yeah he has a good voice.
Everyone involved
They're all illiterate
Hard
It's been done before
Pedophiles
Are using various types of
Distinguish their sexual preferences
So they have badges
Everyone on the Block
Talk about it
A Seaside to talk about
Used to have
Different colored handkerchiefs
Indicate what they were in
I meant a little girls or whatever
Meetup b*******
Tamiya hobo symbols
Yeah you're right
I hit two in my head I hear exactly the same thing
The the like local news
Your teens are having
Tucker Utah
No one's ever done that
Any youthful like
Sexual Maneuvers the people makeup
It's all it's all like children
Better sex
It's the bad bad version of folklore
In some ways you know it's
These symbols are basically like one of them is a swirl
What would it be
A spiral
Spyro
Their logo is
Like sort of a triangle
Whoosh think
Alright
I don't know what the fuc
Washington football team
Kings logo
Another one of these symbols
That's why I kind of
Big wings
Two small wings at bottom
And there's a picture
Comet Ping Pong
Menu
Ping pong paddle
Veracross
And it look
Not at all
Pike
Owls make
Handles make
If you're really willing to stretch for it
Proof
Sad video that's playing behind John bounds report
Raider image
Screen
Files investigator should be
Realized
Bulshit
Calling
Comet
What kind of idiotic
A business plan is
Is wrong with you
So much okay cuz I'm speaking to Alex
I don't know if it's
I don't know if it's BAU
I have no idea
Yeah it don't matter
Trucking goes hard
The pizza place
Yeah
Brings up images
Debunked asthma having any meaning
Has addressed himself
I've been like
Picture of a young girl
Taped to table
That was my niece playing around her sister take her to the tail
Table you thought it was funny
Tell relatives
Can have jokes
Strawberry
It's such an example of that kind of mass psychosis that is
Spell Santa
Human beings
Just like
The fuc
Salem witch trials
It's
Afraid
To find something to zero in on it
I recently actually studied the Salem witch trials
Interesting how
Economic forces were kind of involved
What would I love about it
When it stopped
I just went
Those books the future
So anyway she is very clearly
Counting song
Junk jaunt
I think it's legally Act
Cannibal
Might not be a real person
This could be an automated voice
That then Alex could be hiding behind John bound as like
Please report
I want to play Justin
Firewood
I wanted to play the end of it so I can get Alex's response
Tubidy
The report
National Center for missing and exploited
This that's real but that doesn't
Relate
Play
Pizza places
Cuz they want the adrenochrome we went over this episode
Chenoa mr. alefantis
Would have us all ignore
40 unique creative publicity
Hoarding Shadows of Washington d.c.
Is about to be open
Your front door
Dot-com
Which
Video
And Facebook is a murdered cut in pieces and
It's not
Trump
Also I don't think the size of the genitalia matters in this particular situation
I don't know anymore
And I can go out to investigate myself
I'm at the Shell controller over-the-top people
Nope
We have covered we are covering and all I know is God help us were in the hands.
I mean
Set
Absolute
100% evidence
That his Narrative of what he covered is Ally
That's not even the worst I can't find still the clip
Directly remember him talking about how someone should go check it out
Absolutely
So I can scrub the internet
Yeah it's probably in the
I bet Alex going to fall for this
More Hot Tips
Pizzagate
Because I'd like to be able to
Like I'd like to know
Somebody goes to Alex
Again I want to be totally clear
Abuse of children is very real
Problem
This is this is b*******
Exploit
Your
Legitimate
Matters for political point
It's only to make money and to demonize
Alex is drunk ramblings
Some good old rock
Return to the races
These people that are weasels
I sit here
Open myself up to it
Because I'm
Week
It's because I'm real
I want the return of real
The opposite of winter
Also you want
Or reopen maybe because it's WrestleMania weekend
I'm getting into shoot promo mode
We are not funded by anybody
We are creative types
Neither of us are beholden to the Democratic party
Regenerative power of creativity
Real people Alex
Bring it
If you really want some
Come get some
Please.
Spell herb address
Mister Austin
Prefer if you didn't
Steven
I only want you to Drake
One of those PBR
Covid-19
I am 100% confident
Get into a conversation with Alex
I mean I couldn't handle his yelling
And all that stuff
Cupcake
I couldn't have a cupcake
I don't I don't play it roleplay
On our website knowledge.com
Compiled
More than enough
Triple A
Clearly Illustrated
Multiple
Even better
I'd like to see from the love of God
Is work at the race
Family in this is Chris got to go with your family
Appreciate Marcos Morales and Rob doing the rest of her being here
Is this where Rob DeRozan
The left tells you all day how much they care about you
One of the ones that want Eugenics and does humility
I don't care what color
Your skin is
This is fundamental to everybody
If you got good music I'm going to listen to your music whether you're white
Weather in South Africa
Really
That's how we see the world right
If you got good food
I've gone in restaurants owned by
Clearly are racist against white people
Doctor
I don't need it
I think at this point he's hung
I think I think I think he's at the point of drunk or his
Restaurants
I need
Improve It On The Rain
I want I want
Hooray lashes out of
A little bit
Sit here
And tell you
That I'm
Races to prove myself to you
Everything I do
It's about two people
Because
Sociopath or psychopath I know metaphysical
That's your privilege mathematics
Everything
Does that mean in Chinese
I think that you and I might believe that
Generalizing a group of people
IFixit
You're going to need a backup
Text with evidence
I think fundamentally
Let's look it up right now
Is it
Generalizing a group of people
I think that's I made Prejudice ascertain
Only wrapped up in that
Formal definition of rapist
Is it just a picture of Alex Jones
It's actually a picture of Thomas
A person who shows discrimination or prejudice against people believe that a particular
Superior to others
Discrimination certainly in the sense that he discriminates
Against groups of people and loves them in
Certainly
He definitely
Seems to be very concerned with the white White's race
That was funny
I'm going to back him up on this one
I also don't care if you're out
Rapper
Show me albino musician I can come up with
If you have
Listen to him
Dive
Deeper
Intuit prejudiced hole
I don't just like Muslims because they've got brown-skinned a lot of them
I just like them cuz they're always killing each other
We're selling them to the bomb makers want bomb somebody
Saudi Arabia is a hell
It's like the worst
No rock and roll radio.
Insta kill you
If you get caught with sooner rock and roll if you're gay
So first of all first of all
That's funny
Baby that's right
Listen
In the 50s
Chris Hemsworth
You know what
Saudi Arabia
Just a whole country of John Lithgow
I will we go back to this present from the Sun
Dislike
Black people
Listen
I'm not racist
But
If every single f****** that you know
World
The facts
Keep on killing each other
I know we are killing them
And the bomb makers that I love and support so much
They got a
And maybe I'm the one who provides
That's him being drunk and not being able to figure out exactly like where is the line that I drop
Muslims keep killing each other
In the morning when I wake up
Am I going to have to
You know what everyone knows that I know more about
Then I was letting on
That's what I think is going on
That's why I think he brings that clarification
Much of the case whenever you're really drunk at you over explain yourself
The only
Supervisor
I don't care if you're some guy but you're a woman
What the hell I don't I don't have to get you
Five-year-old alone
Call my girl
Don't teach them about sex
I'm not here
Broadcast
Supposed parting shot
Melissa train
Clear that
Staff wants to leave
But they thought it was going to end when Rodger Stone
Oh did I do
Sitting there like
What is everybody
This isn't over
It's not no
Camellias Grill
I want to talk to Bart
We are not strangers broadcasting 2 million mg
I apologize
Let me back off
At least hundreds of people
Yeah I want to say this
Idiots have no understanding
The trans community
And for that matter
I don't understand
Degrading the way you seek by people
And you should be ashamed of yourself
Especially considering that you're doing the drunk
On the air
Your f****** monster
And
Justin balls we just understand
A little bit
We're going to get to this next
We're coming we're coming towards
I'm going to be perfectly honest with you
We're not coming towards
End
A half hour left of his show
I got to be honest I wanted to play you the entire thing actor Rodger Stone leave
It's just such scatterbrain on cell
Pizzagate
It's a skull covered in tattoos
Misunderstanding
Scripture
Racism racism is my friend we are going to get into a
Anti-semite
AutoZone
This morning
Alex Jones has the Jewish Mafia Run the World
And I went no I said
There's an Italian mafia Mexican Mafia
Dixie Mafia is horrible
Miami Southridge
A white moth
I go yeah there's a Jewish Mafia George Soros was part of it then they work for the Nazis
They said I said choose your evil
What the hell
It's just
It's crazy
I don't I don't
Does fall into a lot of
Antiques
He falls into a lot of anti-Semitic Canard
In one of the big ones is this idea that there was
Crypto-jews
Behind the scenes and helping with the Holocaust
And
Kids
You can go to our website I wrote an article about this
About the idea that he was working with Nazis
It's absurd
18 years old at the time
And wasn't doing anything
He was
Scared for his
Wife
These are killing me
It's also races
I might as well be Mexican
Cuz I love tacos
Hello tacos and their women are beautiful
That's horribly about this
Batavia races
Stats elephant
Nope can't be racist if you eat all their food and like their women but the fact is I eat a lot
Sushi
The idea that use of the tacos and mix
Can women as evidence
He's not racist
To support his idea
I didn't say
Meme
TripAdvisor play speaking
If that is your analog
You're f*****
So you gets worse you talked a little bit more about the
They know they're fake know so they cost
And they fully committed
I'll show you this tree robbed I don't think so
I know what they're going to do after this
I'm just because I thought I'd seen it all
I didn't say that
Are we even on the show
That's ridiculous
It's not
Like I said we will eventually
Montgomery we will do an episode about the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Exactly how
False narrative
Admire you
You're here for a reason
All of his
Cabal all of that is built
From the foundation of anti-semitism
He pretends he doesn't understand that is Ludacris
And then on top of that
And they were really responsible for the Holocaust
And as you've gotten into in the last
Week or so
Episode
Eventually
He's been starting to spout some
Revisionist history about the Holocaust
Super uncomfortable
Set up Hitler
What kind of things
There is nothing
Quite so Americana
Real American
From Germans
In America
Prescott Bush
History
Beyond
High school for headline
Where were the heroes
Hitler
Jo-Ann's
Understandably
Yeah
Really good formula
My bad.
Starts rambling about it
Oil stuff
I want to play
Because
Credibly not true
I'm at the same time
Isabella 10
So here we go
Family making $100,000 a month
All my cousins
Oil
15 years ago 10 years ago
And then now because of a cold
Bryant family gets like $3,000 a month
Heather's property taxes on
And then personally if I was one of these self-fulfilling assholes
About how do I make money
I cheered
Coming back
The paychecks going from $100,000
Thousand dollars
The $3,000
$0
10 -
So every expert
Looked into it
I mean you can just do some research on your own and find this out
Want to
Citations in front of me but
Cleancult
Is complete nonsense
Nope jobs are going to come back
Absurd for the reason
Economically viable it doesn't matter
The cost of coal is higher than
The cost of
Father not as polluting
Biggest problem
Automation
Is that
It is inevitable that clean energy is going
And it is going to be
More cost-effective than trying to
To prop up.
Call or we will die
People are trying to keep those old Industries going to ensure that we all
Glycate
It's like they're grasping for
10 more years of
A little bit more so that
We lose 100 Years of
Has metaphors but made
The metaphor I think it's probably been made before but it's like
Tomorrow
That sort of thing
Like
As much as I
I hate
The GOP
Trumpet
Sure
Like it's not there
Useful idiots
It's like Ryan
It's obvious
Breakthrough
Idiot
But
Pay for
Show
Like
Like I would rather people go to
Do billionaires homes
They're call your representative
Months
Maybe a year
Come back because this is
Control
This is exactly like the French Revolution
Exactly like the French Revolution
Scooter later
Slightly on the wrong side
Probably
Super Bowl
Compared to
A lot of people
Portage
Do we might
Get our heads
I'm willing to make that sack
11:30 today
But
Included
The reason I wanted to pause this clip here and then beyond
And talk about how like
Are my family
Cole
The idea that they were making
Hundreds of thousands
The dollars a month
And then check is down to like 3,000
Trump has been in office for
Do you have it there
Money has gone down that he hasn't even brought back
It could possibly have that big dent in there
Economic viability
Is b*******
If it's true the reason is because their Wells are gone through
Like if they don't have the product
I am going again
My own self-interest in my family self-interest
You just literally can't be true
This reworking its reworking the reality
We're losing jobs or we're losing money or so on and so forth
Say it like that
I one more and then we're going to get really weird
Okay
Here's the here's the last
Does weave into demon
Climatologists astrophysicists say the Earth's dying
Yeah
To survive energy
We terraform
Cliches the planet
I never seen aliens real
You got the brown.
Carbon dioxide
Hundreds of millions of years
A lot
When the planet doesn't have that cash
We have an energy source to put it back
Why would we do that
Hookah Hookah come up with that robbed
People that hate
So I can only assume that they're not
If they don't like humans
Daddy made a great point there do
I can only
I can only assume
Perfect
Logical
You have to agree
That if they hate
They're not human
That's just
Let's just say
Okay
Used to Cartesian logic
Yes
Therefore the art
If
The second premises
Implied in there is all who hate humans are not
So therefore
These people are
Human
I think humanity is a whole is problematic
The Matrix agent Smith
Is like I think humanity is it
The disease I was kind of like
Yeah you're probably right
Hitman video you can find online of Rogan
People like to take his
And put them over swelling music
But he does have a really interesting observation about the idea
Flyover cities the kind of look
Organs
Yeah there's like that
Inflow of cars going in and out of the city
I'd like
To work into the suburbs to go home like blood flowing in and out of
And then if you look at big cities like look like
It looks like
Disease on the on the
That's a super interesting thought
Compare it to
Which are if you were an alien
And this point has been made
By Amelia
Came to Earth
Reality would be you would say that ants are the actual
There
Out out out number
There are Continental
Which is
Like Mike
They are warfaring
One thing that
Really
Efficient
Yo
Like
We can't really compete with that level of
To work
Exactly
Moisturizing.
I'm going to say
3 out of the next
Sport Clips
Okay
Different way
But the other three are like
End of the night
Everyone left the party
What are you talkin about
Get this drunk ass out of your house
I said earlier in the show is what's going on now
Rob do is sitting at the desk
And Alex won't look
Looks like he's ready to go
He's got his coat on
He really has
Yes
And it's like this
We got to deal with a drunk
Stepdad again
Probably what it is
I would have to ask
This glimpse into that world
I don't know
It's so hard to
Hotel
I think it's I think it's
I have different feelings different employees
To at least
One employee of Infowars
It's just the cam
Who just
Insurance
It could be independent contractor
We're doing more broadcast and more because we're getting the sensor data
You know what
Just like that
Provide Lubbock's on the walls and a half
America
And you're up
They didn't do it on a power trip
To transfer knowledge
Appreciated
New way other people
The psychopath and sociopath
Because we care about people
That's not why
Environmentalism Augusta guilt
That
Ludacris
I have no idea
Thousands of years later we figured out they wanted to communicate with each other
Location cuz everything was orally transmitted everything was
Long lineage of cultures before they had writing
Where everything was just done in like
Panera
They would tell
Stories around campfires the transmitted information that was important to their culture
Which is the most rated
Really old religion
It's from first
Account
People finally written down oral tradition
Every time
Continue
Is always wanted
It's one of those things that a lot of people don't understand necessarily is that Homer wasn't a person
Moberly
Homer was the oral tradition that created
Carry down the books
Absolutely
Ascribed
Explain to me the people don't understand that about
Like Socrates
Describe these words to his
Minnesota
Interesting thoughts you have Alex about to cave drawings and what have you
People don't use environmentalism
Against you as a weapon
They're scared about science
Because his premise is that there's not enough carbon dioxide
The Earth is
Carbondale
So we actually need carbon dioxide
The atmosphere
F*** if you talkin because his belief is that this whole environmentalism is basically just trying
To push carbon taxes
And trying to
Shackle businesses
Put it under you
Control put it on
Falcor
Troll doll carbon
Weird world
Hubie to Humboldt even stuff that
So dumb
We don't have time and I'm a little bit buzzed
So I don't want to get into like the ideas of
Exactly why this version of climate denial is
I'm stupid
But maybe we can do that another day
You know what this particular brand
You don't might be fun
You take this
Idea
Maybe you do a dentist Montgomery style episode about that
Can do that conversation
Alex Jones for no reason
Eog's the way they got Rugrats the government
Leaving Rocky fighting some foreign takeover
Heatherdowns and kill the president major publication
Hit right in the all the Republicans that don't know how long they're Russians
Enterprise like
Whatever
Did you get that this talk about the Branch Davidians
I want to make sure everyone is listening
Do you talk
King about
Waco
I don't know how to say that the bad corollary but that is an example of
Some crazy
It's not an example of the public being like hooray
Everyone
Batshit insane even
Very liberal people
Conservatives also everyone thought
This is horrifying
What the f*** is going on
Cheap f*****-up
She don't
What
I don't know
It's very complicated
It's very complicated case
The people there
For mostly victim
A lot of them brainwashed and willing victim
Horrible person
Children
Just he was out of line.
Strongest worth
I think I might
Look
Do you know what he was
Do you know what he really was really really was
Cool the reality of it is out of stock I don't want it
Dive deep into that
Acquitted
The bigger point is that no one was cool with it
People alive
Do you know what that's like
If you put a lot of carbon dioxide
Cabernet
At some point
Yep
It gets worse they talk more about this is an interesting thing to come up because Alex Jones
Experiences
Waco
Who's from Texas
Sure
Because
Bill Hicks
The guy who everyone says
Was deeply involved
About
So it's super interesting is confluent
The things
Bill Hicks
Everybody everybody
And then it comes out later that they weren't that bad they were
Just because they they
Talked about
They could have arrested koresh at any time
You heavily armed
Heavily-armed
Still a bunch of people
They were gone
The person
As I understand it I don't I don't know all the details
I've been with that guy died
The Sun
Was supposed to take over the church
To a little bit of a
David koresh
Who was the
Lover of the prophetess
Then they got into this thing like who should be in charge of the church to do a bunch of like sort of raise the Dead
Kind of s***
It ended up
What was it what was it
Was it Elijah
Like hey
Bring all of your all of your holy man in like this
Like
I'm having to do all this
Snakes
Hey snakes
Date
Is
David koresh
His followers
The other guys
Had a history of armed conflict with people
Heavily-armed
And was not coming out of the sky
Wasn't coming out
Uncle
Number two
Yeah
Restaurants
Portsmouth
Everything
I'm finding wounded on that Hill
You know Sheriff was going to go public
I talked to Tom Eggers
Got Academy nomination
Awards and then Taylor
Blowing it out of Marina.
What does scapegoating m
What they did was wrong
How the people involved in that were haunted by what they did
And that's why I like they've done later by the seniors how to rectify that
But that was all a psyop on the military
To see if they could get them to turn into American people and also the media.
Turn us against the military
So then they would hate us and then they would get their fight
Instead we're going to love the military
He is so drunk
That
Ludacris
Yeah
Just
The most St Louis of rap
Christmas recital
For the players play
No Slam
House
What's a great Murphy Lee quote
Look
Did the Branch Davidian Waco situationism
Credibly cop
Okay.
That
Spell because just that weird reference from robbed
I can take him down
In the same way
Does immediate demonize the Branch Davidian
And talked about how
Kiwi
F****** kids
She was
Was
Guilty of sexual assault
Like he is
What's let's be clear
Kale
Occult member
He wasn't as bad as like Jim Jones
Conversation
They're in the same conversation
Full disclosure
The cult leader
He did jail time
He's not in the conversation
That's how bad calls
Just beat me a call later
Probably going to do jail time
There is some seriously bad cult leader
Almost anytime there's a scism in a church
If someone
People often another directions
Schism
Acura pronunciation
He's like an offshoot of a church
Generally
Someone's up
If your dude
What are you doing
Eclipse last
This next one
If you have any
Doubt in your mind
Ermine
But Alex has been drunk
Parricide
Please do not interrupt this
You can learn to experience
Didn't learn through
Education
Or you can learn through
Revelation
Erase memory
So there is always more exactly
And thanks, Spence
Salvage common sense
Learning
Elearn
Well
Education like you said
Experience experience Revelation which probably is the DNA
Well it's spiritual
Yeah
And you really screwing up
That's how you learn that's the one of the biggest way the best way is to learn
Let me ask you this question
Spoiler alert
For the last 2 minutes
He was talking about the different ways to learn
Estimation of it is
If you want to learn
Let me tell you about the best way to do it
Learning
At no point was
Reading
Listening
Communicating with people
Sharing experiences
The empathic of others
No chance
It just
Timmy is
Capsulation of
Someone who won't leave my
Is
Frustrated
Learn
Florida
I just said
You learn
You know what
DNA
You got one wrong
I think reveley
Memory
Thanks
Them just talking about the branch
List of idioms
What
Rob do accidentally
Hitting the nail on the head of why I started
Now they're talking about the mainstream media
The match
What he's talking about but about them
Kind of clear up some of my motivation
Every time we Face real
It's not just delicious figure it out spread the word
But it's like gorgeous Wild
Other people decide you know what I got to step in
That's usually how it happens
People get pushed so far
And at some point they go I've had enough
What's your light in the sand
How many times is our test
What's your
And being intimidated by MSM or something
She's a total coward on Facebook probably sockpuppet
Calling you a racist
First of all
Perfect
Solution of Y
I started
IWatch
The election night
Everyone who is
Was crying
Laughing
A very diverse crowd
We realize our lives are in danger
The things that Keep Us Alive
Planned Parenthood
Most basic example
Immigration laws
Can I am in danger
They were crying
Legitimately
In a room full of smoking cigars
Absolute all the tears
We're legit
How many how many times do you have to
Story up
Children
Separated for
And because
Because she
He's been deported
Families broken up
Really really
Thumbs down
Technicality
Rule
Yeah
That was it that was it for me
I watch that was the moment that robbed you just described as
When I've had enough
That was the line
Alex Jones
I could have documented it before that
Do you know what the life for me
For me was
I would love to have some sort of holy Crusader but I didn't have this
This idea you did for the ride the ride
Pieces to an anti-Semitic
I say Nazis are horrible working with Jewish Mafia
Pulitzer Prize books
SL the Jewish
They're the ones that
It's not like I have to sit there oh my God
They're the ones like
Dementia
It doesn't matter
Infowars.com live show in Fort Worth
Do you know
What a piece of s***
Associate
Get the taste out of our mouths
Weeks until
Okay I love them they're great folks
But ship looks like the archetype
Archetypal c*********
With those little deer in the headlight eyes and all his stuff
And there's something about this
Nothing around bossing everybody around trying to
I want to tell Congressman Schiff
And all the rest of them
Hey listen a****** quit saying Rodger and I
You son-of-a-b****
What the f***** your problem
You want to sit here and say that I'm a goddamn f****** Russians
You piece of s***
You f****** goddamn f*****
Listen f*** head
You f****** cross the line
Get that through your goddamn f****** head
Pushing your s***
You're the people that have his country over
The reason I wanted to play that again is because it's so f****** awesome
I just want to illustrate we taking this entire episode
I'm to the point where he's end of the night drunk
I wanted to remind people that he started a run
Started
He started
Even drunk this entire time
You are an alcoholic
We like to make fun of you but I'd like to end this on actually a slight
We just had that at the same time because we mean
Yeah you have a problem
Empathy
Somehow
You should really turn your life
We've had issues of substance
Various time
Myself
And I've known people who
Substance problems and
What is behaviors
How to mirror
Give that crazy person that you know who has a drug problem
A nationally syndicated radio show like this
It's not really ethical to diagnose
Mental illness
No but I think
Based on
The sound that we heard of him drinking
Hiding a cup under his desk
His clearly drunk Behavior
Is drunk Behavior
How wasted he was on Rogan
Pinchot
These are all indications
She has a very serious problem
And maybe some of these behaviors that we like to make fun of
We should be
Making fun of
Some of them might have their route
Since abuse problem
As much of a Monster High
Absolutely
Regret
No absolutely not I'm just trying to
Make this
Ferris
Podcast
Possible about Alex
If we are going to do that
We have to recognize
Then maybe he's not as bad of a
A person
Underneath that
If possible
And it's never going to happen
Help
We have to add
He's probably going to be fine
Good
I honestly
Buckhead
He did get help
And he stopped doing his show
That would ruin the
The show
We can transition to Michael Savage
Like there's 100 reviews
You're right
And they're all
Equally easy
Just like point out where they're lying
A****** conservative
What is a conservative
Crazy
Right wing
Yep
You deserve your family deserves it apparently you have a fourth kid they deserve it
Let me ask you a question
What's up you were looking
Find us
On the streets b****
Alright that was
The problem
That's our website
You can also follow with it at knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Underscore
Leprechaun Twitter
Bring it
If you would like to eat
Get help
Resources
People who have proof
If Trump doesn't get impeached
Also you can email us if you want at gmail.com
Did get an email recently from a listener who
Oh Ana
I mean you got to pay for shipping
But I don't know how much that cost I'm really bad at this
Autograph
Baby FNAF
Send Amanda Nunes
YouTube
And I asked
If you guys want
Npr-style there's a
So much Jordan
Has been
Delightful
Let me ask you a question
I'd love to answer
Are we
Dudes
Into power
Alex