Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones Jordan
I can't remember anything we ever coming in
Mary on unfamiliar territory
Recording this on the in the morning cuz I'm flying out on vacation
Window of the - 50 degrees Chicago
For a couple days
And because of that we have to record this ahead of time so we can get this episode out for Monday
But we will not have an episode
Just abide by virtue
There's no way we could have pulled that off I wish I wish we could have
Yeah but that we could not appreciate everybody
Little man
Call my parents kind of still at work
Vacation
Emotional word cookies
Very thrilled about that though because
I mean
This life
Especially the show is Ben
Nuts
Like in terms of
Monday
And then Alex's clear indications that he's f****** done with Rodger at the end
And even requiem
Talk too much about this but I was working on like a really big episode
Right before Rodger got indicted so it was like
3 straight days of
Call Matt Rogers
This is got to go on the back burner and I got to dive into
So I'm very excited
To not do this for a couple days
I'll probably check Twitter but beyond that
I'm not doing anything
Working
The candle at both ends as it where I know a lot about Alex Jones
It doesn't matter today cannot talk about Alex Jones
Yeah last week no Wacky Wednesday last
Project
Forget to that I got to give a couple shout outs
Signed up
Then or supporting the show first of all
I'm a policy wonk
Supportive
A joke is no good but something that is very good
I'm a policy wonk Mega Robin
Finally likes
My appreciate it also very much
So Dylan thank you so much
Someone sodomites
Black
Jesus Christ
Not really Business website
Click the button for the show
So Jordan been
A little bit of a mess
The sort of things that necessarily we liked
Recover
I don't need to hear Kerry Cassidy talk some weirdo by 5G technology
I really need to hear that I want to hear about space
I don't want to hear her talk about real science but
Libels pray that stuff there are, now.
Miss a little bit because I don't want to talk about her version of that
Delivered
Let interesting late spider leadership is involved with involved with 5G technology
How to get the f*** out of
Start a punch on those little bit
I found it
With starring
Starex
He's on to promote his new book
Wow this is busy pretty good stuff this is interesting
Search talking about Luke
You talk about loose
Alright
He's talking about how he had these licked
These messages from Aliens
He starts talking about how he had some people who he had good help editing the book
I'm thinking
If you're getting messages from Aliens
You don't even understand
That's unfair that is unfair everybody
True.
Worst
Grandma
Pretty similar
Certainly at least
Reliant
You can tell if there was a bigger story behind it
But they weren't talking about the specifics of okay
So I went back to a year prior
The first time Sebastian Martin was on the show
Wild okay sweets
I love Mia Sebastian
So I'm kind of on his side right off the write-up
Until the listeners that this is simultaneously the most fascinating and most boring story
I was a zigzag Road in yours backstory Tales of this are super interesting
But as I was going over it I
Kept finding myself zoning out
God
I guess
I guess he's talking about the honor
Okay
Cool
I took slap myself in the face would be like getting the game's getting the game
So they'll be a little bit of that context drop
Today Show
It is a problem where people put at aliens
So-called aliens on pedestals so to speak
You don't got to elevate
Concerned
She's worried that we over exaggerate
The Evolve level
Different different types
Would you get that read between the lines however you like
On the show
It's interesting. They came out
Beginning of 2017
The two of them don't really know each other
They're on a little bit of
Oh and
He's a French dude
More fun
He hasn't is one of the types of people who gets tricked by an accent
It makes it makes dumb things sound smarter to American ears reading. European
Especially French or British
It's a hack it's like a little override
In people's brain be like
Yeah that's where the thing
Some of the stuff that you saying I would
I would beg the audience to imagine
He wasn't French
If they sound
Now
Carrie and Sebastian Matt alien conference
I think they call it the alien Congress
I don't think they have any kind of actual legislative power there's no balance
There's no alien executive or judicial
Here's how they start at the interview
Hi I'm Kerry Cassidy from Project Camelot
Today we are beautiful Congress and
Texas opportunity to meet up with Sebastian
Who is here as well attending the conference
He's a very interesting man he has been out and around telling his story a bit
But we're going to Dallas down a maybe a little deeper here
The great opportunity
Project Camelot 2
What's been going on with him over many many years and
I'm going to let him introduce himself since I actually don't know him that well
Heard a couple interviews
So I don't I don't know I feel like Gary knows nothing
Considering that you saying like what
He's been going people stories
Maybe skimmed in interview
Something like that
Are you can you can
Damn
We don't do this
Would you just
Are you prepared for the show yeah
I don't have a u.s. congress
To get ready to go to the vet
Really front-loaded or schedule preparing for
The Congress
Congress
Forgot
Prepare for the center
She the
Introduce yourself I don't know who you are
So I was a C U of A
Multinational for 10 years in Canada
Struck my ears drain
First
He says he's a CEO of a multinational corporation
Or what you think he was
Immediately I'm like I don't believe anybody
I don't believe them across the board for the military
I can't figure that out
But if you're the CEO of a company that records should be somewhere
So
Hold on
However
You could have a franchise of McDonald's
In Canada and
Across the border in America and call yourself a multinational business
You going to start upright
Front office
Canada
Vizio remote
Across-the-board interviews I've watched Sebastian Martin as well as bio on Amazon in the blurb
Released book called journey and outer space
Martin consistently refers to himself as before Maceo of a multinational company
But in no instance does he ever say what that company was
Which I found very suspicious
If you just Google is named find a ton of Sebastian Martin's who aren't
Which doesn't get me anywhere
I decided to search
First Sebastian Martins
And see what came out
Which mysteriously doesn't go
Of a multinational company
Jobs listed
What is its current business City run
Distribution
The website mostly about new-age pseudo-spiritual together lightworkers and what have you
That's what he's doing
What position is the director of focus herbs
Leader whose positions could be the CEO position he always stays as a part of History partially because the entire time
Have you was at fault
Another person
We drank any of this had a higher position in the company that he did
And beyond that the timeline doesn't work out
About
You look through the other lady has to find somebody who is like a little bit higher that's a little bit
You're running a little bit higher
Thorough
Hireright
Another interview date in 2013 so neither
Of the two entries on his LinkedIn page could possibly represent
And that's just leave off of your resume on a job website
CEO of the multinational company
Please
It says it on a ton of interviews that he was in
Portion of LinkedIn
Mercury
Any honors and accolades article
About the 2012 responsibility
I don't know
But he says that his business got an honorable mention in the small slash medium business of any sector
Category
There it is
Sebastian was the CEO of a company called wet organic
Wedderspoon organic is a honey company
They sell small jars of Boutique honey for absurdly high prices
But that's not all
They also promote their honey is having antibacterial property
Interesting Lee that's not a problem honey absolutely does have antibacterial properties
But Weatherspoon is
Accused of exaggerating their honey powers on that front
In March 2015 they were hit with a class-action lawsuit for it
That's it would be voluntary
Voluntarily withdrawn in December but the exact details of why I got withdrawn
From looking at a series of court filings throughout fall 2015
It does appear that they reached some sort of out-of-court settlement but it's hard to say for sure
So what are spoon Organics base product
For $50 you can get a honey-based
Or for $22 in get a smaller tube
Territory
For $21 you can buy a 5-pack of single-serving
Honey plus Vitality which were apparently perfect for when you're on-the-go I would rather put that on
Super male vitality
They sell versions that are honey plus immunity honey plus Clarity advertising minutes
Fuels the body and the mind
That sort of thing
So it looks like Sebastian ran a small to medium Boutique honey operation
Sound like it was a Fortune 500 company in order to elevated story
Moments like this that I'm glad that I got to the bottom of the story but also realize that it probably wasn't worth it
We could have just assumed it was something like this
He was just honest I wouldn't
But he's trying to make it seem like a business was much larger than it was
Everything
Simple everything I can tell like he started it
Department
Ended build-it small slash medium size
I am going to say it's slightly dishonest
To only represent
Mazzio's multinational corporations
What is 2
Elevate his story make himself seem way more important
So whatever you say is so much more important by virtue of that
But what stolen business Valor like that's kind of weird talking about here but it's the difference between
You're being entirely made up and just exaggerated
It would be like someone just a rank
Can file enlisted person
And then they're saying that they were
Level up
Credit enough for being a CEO and not hate not being a lie
But
I also think it's spiritually a little bit.
Both stood and honorable mention in the oven
The years were the years of 2012 was when you got that two honorable mention
And then 2015 was when I got the class-action
Where water
The company in 2013
On him
You know at least he wasn't around at the show the time
You do car to get the fence
Marketing
The I don't know
Robin
Hey soon-to-be tsar2
No no no no no
That same sort of
Call Honey
Doesn't honey business only thing that never goes bad or whatever it is
Closing property
Let's move along
Traduction
Pennsylvania
UK
Yu-Gi-Oh
And
In 2011
The dream
That's that was a common dream
The face of a boy
You had eyes away before
Away from each other then house and
Cheekbones
And he was very happy
Key smiles
California
UT novetta
Since I'm not that unusual because you not see him in
Does a woman
When I woke up in the morning
I went to work
That's a boy
The face
Was steel
In front of me
And it was highly disturbing
So you had a bad day
Maybe have a
And then that face was staring at him all day I think you just meme in this case that
Couldn't get the image out of
You imagine that
You just had a face like directly in front of him like
3 ft away
Best Buy
Thinking about this boy all day
Comes home
From work after having
Head all day
Starts to meditate
Or something
It's not really clear what he's up to
And then the boy appears to him in his lips
My sofa
It does require
And I put myself a cup of tea before hands
Not renewing what to expect
Basically
Something must have happened
I still get some
With my eyes on second
Ween the Walgreens
Of energy around me
I've been stopped
And when I stopped
Ibis
Open
Andy was Beast
Boy
But stunning
In front of me
He was about
Speedway from me
How many was
Glowing
Globe energy was breakfast with Buddy
Keith was not
Bouncy was
Physically there
The casino in Shreveport
So you got this boy in his room
Cereal
Events at down on the couch
Apparently
Spirit
Just like a Frenchman
Azores
Call hours tonight
From France or is he
The Bordeaux
Empire
Is it legit Frenchman
But yeah used
Spend some time in Germany of UK and Canada also throughout his
It's before he went to the different countries
And it's very disappointing
Nope
You sitting there this boy comes and visit
But it turns out
The boy
Am I try to get up
I was frozen
Because it was going to stop by the whole thing
When I so Hammond
You must have heard me
Basically responded saying
My Name Is Earl
The oar
And I'm from the Galactic Federation
She said no I forgot
Refrigeration
But I'm guessing
We had a 15-minute phone conversation
Which is
Intractable
Weird space
I was a little bit turned on at the same time cuz I'm kind of
Had some
Sleep paralysis
Described
Paralysis
Talk about is very
Justfly contact
But I do like the idea that
1550 minute conversation
Azure
My favorite thing
Just like
Galactic Federation
Russian Federation
Carrie's just like
Bright corn dad also
In fact if you Google's or Intergalactic Alliance or whatever or Federation
Keeps popping outfits
But there's another podcast
And on the same episode
I don't think they're on it together
I don't think they're on the episode together I think it's like this guy interview both of them
But just to show there's a connection
Some podcast will have both
Jon rappoport
Zoar alien on
Cuz this is what I see happening right now
3-space
Zoar
Sebastian
CEO of yourself honey
Ends or those oars always like
I'm way up in the clock
And then they both kind of learn about each other and eventually they find out
You know
Glee Sebastian has to be like
Man I've been lying to
See this whole time
Dude
I'm a janitor
But also I love honey
Realized I got to clean my apartment
Let's trade
As if you was talking I did it again find myself zoning out a little bit what I realized I could
Myself is CEO of an international
That's true
Maybe that's not fair
How about that
What are the problems with Carrie and a lot of her guests
What's the problem
Is that they talk
Well because they don't keep it in line
Start trying to develop these stories for themselves
Describe their backstory
You start to get these
About like
You're describing is
Is not aliens
What you're describing isn't
Like you didn't
Goal of whatever
Isn't what you want
It's good enough
The trick people
Physics Cliff was my first
Signs like a real wrestler
McDonald's had a farm houses
I need was wanted
And I had to
Recurring nightmares
As a child
But I saw that ghost going in Georgia
Goat
It kind of makes sense to me
Understood
Genuine
Understanding of
Just to know what they were
In Sons of Anarchy
Human being who passed away like we see their bodies floating around
And that's was
Videoeta is parents
Recurring nightmares
About
Consciousness a little bit
Selfie was seeing ghosts
I live in Hawaii for a little bit grown up
And when I lived there I we lived in this house
We came to find out what's hot
For allegedly haunted
The Kasha of Kaimuki
Which is like a
Vengeful Spirit apparently
Lived in this house
We lived in
He's one of those things that we didn't have money
@properties pretty expensive
In Hawaii
For a while cuz no one wanted to move
Cuz local
All this s***
Fiza
These old women that are out every now and again
I think I like I have a memory of
Thinking I saw a ghost
Like I was laying in bed one night
I saw it
In my closet with a
The Flaming Act
Right then I could do the same story that he's doing
I could use that as I can say
I was under the age
Japan
There were things I couldn't understand
Like these women throwing salt at our house good at explaining these thing
Tried to comfort
Me about the idea that these people think our house is haunted or whatever but
They weren't they were the best
Conflict resolution in that in that way you got it in my head like oh I communicate
Real
Vegas X
Didn't integrate the information I was having
Beto's probably playing
Computer game back then that had something
I think I might have at a friend's house
No
Definitely not
Whatever the rational explanation
The circumstances
Like there's a path you can take the stupid
You can take that
Is more real
The path here
And it's unfortunate
Because it is
Like
You know
Is kid that played by Nightmare
It's unfortunate that
He's allowing these fans
In such a serious
I like the idea
House hunting show
On HD
That is just for like
Really discounted houses
Because they were haunted
That would be a really fast
From what I understand I don't know
McKay's but like
From what I understand
After we moved out
Move to Missouri
That the house was again
No one moved in
They just couldn't get anyone to
Look the point is
We all choose our path
Will get back to
I told you move around
And you were suspecting
Or something like that
It's not he's running towards
Germany
Curiosity
Had a girlfriend
I just move there
Josey Jewell
But you still wearing the French service
So did you have a long time there are just you just
I broke my arm at the end
Weeks before the end of my service
Because what happened
And I broke my arm doing
Training and I went back to France
And that's what I meant
3 days later
So
Pretty much what happened tonight get back to Germany and broke my contract when I move to England
So within like 11 months
He moved to Germany for a woman breaks his arm woman
In France that moves to England for
That's not a stable person
That's it that's is really
Like questionable Behavior
I understand moving for like a tiny bow
But like if
If you have nothing tying you down necessarily
You care about it somewhere else
Why not why not try and like start Eliza If it's
If it's all appropriate
Is a little bit much
It's not only that you have no ties
Geographical location you started and you have no ties
You are just
Leaf in the wind we can blown around
I broke my arm
Seems like he's fulfilling all of our stereotypes about French people
The sound slightly more than because of an accident
So are we get back now
Is useful
Paranormal
I guess activity
Heard there was a haunted show
You can talk to ghosts
But he was also having visions back then
When he was younger
And
I think the timeline of these Visions is interesting
Cuz you saw the ghost
Approximately
Play Robin 12 years old
Okay
Priest
Stingrays
Until the age of
And after that
Because I blocked it off button
So the first thing they're at the end is
Yeah there's a voluntary aspect
Barro's Pizza block
Vision
He has a lot of mental fortitude
Next B2
When I got here
It's from 12 to 16
It was terrible and uncontrollable subsided I hear that this might be a hormone
Photo issue
Has ever had interesting emotional
Issues
I think it's very common
You have a pubescent crisis a little bit
Changing hormonal levels
That accompanies that there
It's very simple to look at this and be like
I would say based on that timeline the fact that they magically subsided around 16
Akai here I just
This is
A product of
Miss
Integrated information
These traumatizing nightmares that you had as a child
Evan the hormonal
Shift
So so far
I hear
Believe Israel
Andale
Because now I have to ask
The question
Do ghosts are there aliens
Ostensibly if aliens have treated Earth is a Battleground many aliens have died on Earth
A+ someone on Project
Episodes I don't know
We can start controlling them
He was able to block them off for 10 years but they do come back
Even
Further solidifies in my mind that this is stress related
Because here
Is when they came back
Becky's my wife
The pregnant
For ten years while being married with a block my vision
Because
I2
I respect your wishes
Baseball nut
Being frightened by what was happening this
The sidon
Mac
DC Pride
Do something
Soul by respective Hudson
My Visions off
What's the news
And
When she became pregnant maybe just came back in.
Used to have XP
And it was very disturbing because I was not really used to
After 10 years was
Green Adidas
I was re-reading the employees you know
Had no clue what was going on
So he has this honey business that's been growing and he's going to on the cusp of getting dishonorable mention award tickets
No it's a real business that you like even if it isn't as big as he's
It's still a lot of pressure you still haven't
Are responsible for getting the damn hunting out
You got to go to school.
A lot of work
Gets pregnant which is a
Life-changing experience
The people there's a real blow Hardy thing that I've had a couple friends that kids sale
Everything Changes
Don't think that it's not sincere or real-life fear that is your response
Ability
To have to
Wrestle with
Out of nowhere
Because of the news or whatever of it
Almost always is like
They weren't pregnant
Pivotal shift
It causes a lot of stress in people
So if you have a story where from
From 12 to 16
The time when your hormones are out of whack and
Highly stressful.
You have all these visions
After that they subside
You block them
Once you get married entirely
You know all this time
Then a new highly stressful life change happens
And all of a sudden they come back
I'm seeing a pattern
I don't understand
I know
I'm just saying
He has these vision
Then that coincides
And then after his brain is fully formed right around
11:35
He settles down
He gets married
Doesn't really have that much
And then he has a
The big life change
Reasserting the same hormonal
But he's had before and all of a sudden
Are you going back to having visions
Ulta
Dan
Alien ghost
Goodnight they're following him around
There's a possibility
So
You know
I have
Could be pruned
So as a child
Carrie wants to get into
Whereabouts
And conveniently inconsequential
And only related to
As a child
There's no way we could verify anything
So that's super convenia
Go back to when you were in a 12-hour. Agent and a little later
Okay, said between 12 and 16 you're having visions right
So how were the vision
Characterize at that time
About them
Premonitions
Future events
So would you know something before it happened in the morning
Oh yes
People around here perhaps
Call vibrate
And he became part of my life
I was adamant
To even talk about the infraction hadn't
Resort
Because she doesn't
So
None of us can really be tracked back
Meaningful way you know like
Premonition
Pete was going to playground
Alright whatever
Maybe a hunch
Maybe a hunch Steve has been acting recklessly for a while
Right right ultimate
Inconsequential
So I don't know
He does say
They didn't want to tell his mom about Zoar
Because you don't believe in aliens
Completely rationalist family
And no date
This nonsense
She doesn't
He believed himself
So
I think another
Essential elements
These sorts of things
To really latch on
Especially in childhood
Important you have a source
But you have to have some
I keep my parents have believed in ghosts or something like that
Just wanted to
Because at that time I would have
Relied on this Authority
Figure in my parents
I'm very believe that this is real
Why should I not believe
So I need to find a
Peace
From Sebastian
Martin's life
Concrete enough
Fit me
That there's
Let me tell you there's more than one
Oh boy is Mexico if he talks about his grandma
My Grandma had a vision of the Virgin Mary
So what about
Grandparents
Have a grandparent ever or other
Cher
Decide
Was
She had cancer
It made many places
He was one of the miracle of Lourdes in
She said she'd be why some
The Redskins least on the
Real miracles
Miracle
Driven in a wheelchair
The Grotto
This was back when have one area
Catholic after that
She was protesting
And how old was she
Timer
Popping a 30
Today
Yes
She's very genuine and
I'm still in touch with her but
He had these
Found expensive
And
Again just related to religion
And I wasn't a religious person so
Cannabis card
Has being relevant
In any way
Eastside other stories
Here
The stories about your grandmother or did you run mother tell you
I don't believe that
You can say that he only heard those stories later I don't
If you have sold
The Virgin Mary at The Grotto in the Vatican
Becomes a Catholic out of nowhere before that's going to be a piece of your
Family lore
That's not something there's a good
It's going to be it's going to be something
I mean even even if he had a certified multiple Miracles involving your grandmother
I wouldn't know where they put out those
Because apparently they put him out annually
You would have to just be like hey
H-E-B like your grandmother
I don't do Palau the French
I don't believe it
Huge
I would say
Nationally important
Internationally important
Globally important event that your grandmother's life
And then your mom would be like
Hey don't tell
The kid about that until he's 25
Or whatever there's no way
Family Lawrence
0 miracle
Crazy
Families have
Masala jaising they're on their own path
There's a there's an oral tradition
There's no way that something this important
Wouldn't be
He can say that he didn't know until later but I just
I find that to be
Be Beyond
Credulity
Is one family trait that I have
Throughout
Modesty
None of them want it look she doesn't want to brag
Everybody's going to put it on
Is LinkedIn
That's just over it
Miracle lids
Twice listicle
That's the grandma talk about it
A really bad car accident
In the car
Okay
Experience
Forward
She went through Vista Noland
She swept buddy you know
Table 9
White beans
She told me that
When she
Talk to them
Daddy said he's not your time yet
Be coming back
Your time is not ready yet
And she came back with the heating
Capacity
She never promoted
She always
Westbrook
Never had money from
I give him money myself
Retirement
But she
She never really made a fuss about that
His mom died in a car accident light
It turns out the archangel
Okay and they tell her
Healing powers
Go people with
I would like to know what level and how many like this you roll from a D6 to see how many hit
That she returns to people with their severe burn would like
The timeline on this
Tickets all that clear but
I assume this this song
Part of
Grandma
Couple miracle
Right
But my story by lineage
Really out classic
Going to need to have met Zoar
A bit of
The elements are all their family history of
Sort of grandiose by a normal type stuff received
The timeline of this like
Matching up with highly stressful life
And now he gets to another stressful event
That's towards the end of his
Is useful
Vision
Looks terrible
When I was 16 I had that she had a lot of things happening
I wasn't avoiding school so I basically
Beach hiking with a Bojangles
And I said doing classes
I had
Automatic writing
Just write that
Foreign language
Canadian language
From top to bottom and left right
And I know you would have meant
But it was the one.
Yogi's
Chinese language
Because how to
And I I had
Books dealing with this
Because I travel so much
My dad when you moved away
Throughout everything that I own
Even the oschino the stuff that I had
She's gone
Notebooks the world that I automatically roll but unfortunately my dad's
Rudolph
And that may also have contributed to his
Visions from
5:48 speculate just based on the information that we have
In terms of the story as the one who
Has precluded him from proving his story mom and grandmother about pitched
Heroic elements
Even if these notebooks thrown away
They look at a notebook
Or whatever
He is very much like the sixty-year-old who suddenly
Wearing a
Pinterest you know it's busy
He's clearly his affect
Look up automatically
In person just B Mike
A complete lack of
Next clip
Where he discusses how he learn to astral travel
Something in those offenses a girl that that
And I
Was trying to
Empresa
And I said okay
You know I did meditation
My mother
Cuz she does love reasoning
Adidas
I would like to do a test and
And replace
An object
On your night table
And I never said it before but I could do it
And so
The same night I went to
My bedroom
Lay down in the bed
And instead of a sitting down when do tri-central midday shannan
I was just laying down
Who sing on was
We'll get back to this here in a second
The idea that
You just sort of
Talk again
His mom taught him how to Transcendental Meditation
He's not on
Because that means his mom was into that
Younger and
You know
Without getting into libelous territory
Slander
People believe that
He's kind of a cult
And also there have been something
People have reported that
Canby
Like a kind of dangerous practice
Especially for children that's
Because it is just
Repeating over and over and over again
20 minutes
Eddy Kim take you in Tucson
Hypnotic
Like it is it is something that an unformed brain
Would be dangerous for them
Let It Go soft
What is boarding school
I think there's some dangerous element
But he wants to impress
This girl so we can get
It gets into his meditative state
And astrally travels into her bed
That's what that was
And I became out to my buddy
I was being fooled very fast
Black tunnel
An auto accident I was involved
The night table
Jexi
I just want the three
And I described them as
Necklace
It was a rain
Danica surrounded
And that's sweet
Inter inter inter
Notepad
On the side
VeggieTales no pasta get out of my f****** room
I just came back from a
When I open my eyes I was sweating profusely and I was out of breath
Reschedule
You for real broken throughout
And but
I didn't I was just happy to
I can't wait to go back in the morning and tell the girl that's what I've seen
Soja.
You know she freaked out
House
Looked in her window or some
If that story is even real I don't
Believe that
Proves that he actually traveled
Emmett furthermore necklace and a ring Independence
That's not like
Really high-end predictions for
Teenage girl to have on her nightstand
If it was something
F***** up like some really weird
Window
Nothing
Any of it
Mostly easily could have turned into that
That Medium conman kind of thing
He's telling her small bits of information
And she's giving him
Larger bits of information.
Suggest
Speaking of which
Sebastian
Gets mixed up with someone who might have been doing that to him
And that is a hypnotherapist
This is the most suggestive of human being
Any goes to hypnotherapist
That teaches him
About the
Just go to the meditative
It's not always
Nefarious
Super weird
There are
Therapeutic benefit
One of the big surf
Benefits
Go to dealing with anxiety
You're good with dealing with so
Stress
Which might be part of
What causes
Precipitated
These visions
Now that's tough.
So it doesn't surprise me at all that he starts talking about this selfie
Hypnosis
Started to go to them
The vision stop being upset again
There is also. So assertive
Strange things
Years later you going to this hypnotist
Clinical
Psychologist
You're asking to be Hobbit
Either the Visions removed or or
Trolled the same time you did learn
Meditation
Yes
She taught you how to
Do self hypnosis Scripts
Not a big difference
Between Modesto
I'm really something she didn't know or
Did you feel at work
Yes
I was able to
Have them on.
Which is
Something I messed up doing pressure
And I just said to you
How's the weather cool
Didn't reset from
Anxiety and stress
That's for you to have
Back in 2010
Comfortable
There's so many red flags and
Is describing his
Stuff like that
Responsible for carrying
Whether or not
He believes them because I know that she tries
Pretendplay
You can decide if resonate with you or not
Reinforcing
Like that
You guys got to decide that's or the shed
If she had any like
Interest in the truth
Even if she believes in Aliens
Play programming all day
She had any in
And the truth
She would be like
This story that you're telling me
Is really upsetting
Because you're clearly describing
A timeline through your life of Highly stressful anxious situation
Leading to you having delusions
That you were talking to alien
And what happened
Now
You're talkin to me about going to see this hypnotherapist
Afterwards
Your Stress and Anxiety that you felt about all this
When you're able to integrate the information that your experience
Scuse me Sebastian I have I have
Occam's razor
She should watch
Call this out
Because if she doesn't
It looks like she's supporting it
And that hurts her larger argument about aliens
Space
Because this is a piece of it
To talk about this s***
A lack of seriousness
Of course
Even in the gold
She professes
To be interested
Right now the reason that you
She can't do that
Is just more like
These ghosts
If they find out that they
If they go on her show
She might challenge them right
She they're not going to go on her show you know
Because
If she starts challenging one a****** it's got to be every a****** and none of them can stand up
No not really not really but I do empathize
The situation
Sebastian Martinez
Describe
I don't like how he's deciding to go about his life
Book about being black with friends
That's helpful
But I do empathize them you're not in the same way that you see that
Image of somebody who's like
Clearly working a con now
Was a terrified child having nightmares of a haunted shed
Poor relationship with his dad empathize with responsible
Four people around
M2
Humor this stuff
You know I don't think you should like
If you if I was friends
I don't think
Bi-Rite to be like
Higher f****** idiot you are beautifully laelia abusing about this stuff
Equally abusive
Tell me about
Isn't it cool that you want on spaceship
But that's not okay that's that's just
Situations where
If your Mom and Grandma were
Both f***
Like
Performing miracle
Left and right
You would have just gone to a normal psychiatrist
Instead of
Interesting
Did get some modicum of benefits
Unfair
Discipline
Reset the session
Recovering memory which is one of the problems with these like sort of regret
Gresham therapeutic suggestion
That are easily implantable
It's not always like the therapist trying to
To do that
It said it's a really
To navigate and most
Things responsibly you end up walking away with it with
False memories
That because of the
Regression hypnotherapy
You validate and now single
There's the famous daycare people who
You goes to this
Hypnotherapy
And
He ends up
Figuring out
That it's fixed
He was taken up to spaceship Byhalia
Course and
He's there
He's on the ship
Himself
As a baby
Caesar the 6-month old version of himself
A couple of aliens arguing
With each other
Hypnotherapist tells him
What are they arguing about
I don't know
So she asks him
Ask the aliens
And so we jumped
And we receive
The aliens tell him
We can't touch you
You because you've been tampered
You don't understand what that means
That because I blacked out
Promethazine
I went backwards
A six-month-old baby
And I was going to see
With a glass Dome
He was like a Omega symbols on the seam
Fancy glass with a
Middle
And it was a black liquid inside
Organic
Which was whiskey covering my buddy
And Through the Glass
Gladion so about 7
2 radians we're also about 72
Do not despise
And so when are you
When I saw the play against they were wearing exactly the same blue uniform Missoula when I swim in my living room
Beehive that's upside down triangle on the chest
And the Manitou Beach and you had a helmet
Trident symbol on his forehead
And the new one was next to him and she was as tall as you are
Both
Drake
Right
Currency
Cumulative
It it really started me
And that's what I
Because I knew that that was no longer imagine
Crystal clear
You were that big
So he had the power
Earlier in this episode
Killed when he was 6 months old
These are not specific with what the
Condition
He is recovering memories of being a six-month-old taken up by the Palladium
Who healed his skin condition
Which is
Dubious
Easy there is either aliens
Or was
Medicine
He's only 6 months old
Yeah
Is the issue that
It could
You're seeing depressed is that his mom over the course of his life
Hey told him you were born with this condition know that you would survive
Yugioh
And he has really
Overbuilt
Horrible kind of
You are born with
This condition
Medicine
Took care of it
Lakeview there's a way there's a way that this is also a piece
A family lore being exaggerated misunderstood by a child
So I still don't hear anything
That's all I'm saying
What were the air that the aliens are just arguing like
What are you doing
I think it'll be good for us
It turns out actually
Is a hybrid or something like that
Of course
And he's also part goat
Memories
Experience is all this
Therapy
I asked him is like
Read any stuff about
All this s***
Before
He had these experiences
I meant later in the episode
Because it's not like you says I didn't read any of that but then afterwards I was so interested that I dug in and red
He says I'm not interested in any of that
Nonsense
I only want to talk about what my experience
I based on the fact that he's reference
Greer later in the episode and things like that
Hold on man
You are interested in this
Lying about not being
Interested in order to
Information just comes from me and I'll believe that
Because he can't
I have read all of those books of his information
Lines up
Really closely with those but bacon people should be like
Right
You can't have known about his grandma's certified miracles
Earlier in life
Call into question
Where would you get these sorts of ideas from
It's there
After this
You hanging out
He's jealous
Running a business
Revisiting
Just an invitation
Why don't you come on my spaceship or 5 ft tall and the other alien 7
I'm Not Dead
Something I'm
Literally not interested
Details
I don't give a s***
I don't give a s*** at all
Thompson comes back is okay buddy
Come Joyride
Spaceship
And Sebastian
Scared
To go on the spaceship
F****** a******
So basically went
How is my house
Again
And and we'll come back again the same way they did
What are you nuts come with me
On the space
And I didn't like that
I didn't want to
And I said that
No I'm sorry but I think I stay home
Play Spotify
And I even contacted e-plus therapist and I said I would like to
No be regressed
Maybe welcome the idea of being on the spaceship
Resort if you welcome me
And we see where that where it is
So she could have let me through that
That's not good
License
Real hypnotherapist probably wouldn't
Except a session where someone was like
Alien invited me on MySpace
I'm sorry that sounds really tough
I am going to have to Triple my usual hourly
So it'll be about 300
I did say
Credible ethical hypnotherapist
I don't know I just hear
I hear either this hypnotherapist is made up for like it's just someone real Shady
Real shaky
Okay
So it works
He doesn't still pissed off that he didn't take that trip was or he does though
He ends up making peace with it
Getting up to that does
He finds out what his mission is
When was
Mecca shop
Epsom salt
Open up
He was Rydell
And in the background
And woman one of us
Azure is a bad weather
Let me see them
And what I do
Simpson hot
And when I
3C wasn't that high
Winning Lotto
Just the reason that they care about Heights is it different alien races have like
Different
Characterizing
Free ATMs are taller
Goodwin
There whatever
What
Saudi the man and woman
We're going to help you.
Substitute
Activity
G-wiz Zoo
The wellness
And when we walked up that way
Any
I'll give you his dad
And
Methods
He's already
He's not supposed to be here
Enzo said Noah
Information
Record exactly
They said
That's when
You were better now
Instead
The US opposed
A life
You know basic life on Earth
Emotions
Die
Come back to us
That was it
I said okay
And then he said that but now you'll mission
Has changed
Going back to us
And awaken the Stasi the planet
Okay
But I had no clue what that meant
And that's wasted
Whose sole message that arose from this conversation
Okay
Planet
Dude that's your mission
To become a space
All right and now
You're coming up to me
Guess what
You f***** up
You were going to have an easy life but now you got to go back down there and awake and all them goddamn Stars
You're going to be a honey impresario and then die when you die
Comebacks to your true form
Which is as an alien
And we're going to put you on Coast to Coast AM
I'm guessing
Yes
I hear that it's like
That's that's a mess
Yeah I don't like those
Decision-making process if they are giving out jobs
It's so much of this
It just comes down to
None none of this can ever be
Play Kenny
Allegedly capable of doing
Conveniently
Languages anymore
Because
You know if you had that ability confirmable
You don't know
Mandarin
Right
I could do that when I was younger I can't do it now
Astral travel if that's real it would be so easy to confirm
Can do it
Is not the way you can
Confirm
Right
Maybe not.
Nonsense experience
Hypnotherapy session
You know
The most professionally
So
I hate that like
Now you are the only person who you're the most special person in the world
Picking up to like if we started this whole thing we were taking up to a spaceship
The mission would be like
Run a mildly successful podcast for electing s***
But mildly successful podcast
Hell yeah
Even secretary asks a very important question
How long were you in
Therapy
Like how long did that go on for
Question
Music
How long
Bald eagles
Eddie Muffler
He had other things to do
Jesus you uncover that you as a baby were taken up into a spaceship and healed by Plies
I got brought back up
Awaken the Earth starseeds
I would say nothing else matter
They did also say you don't have other things
Okay cool I'll respect
That's a past tense you are
You are supposed
To be here
You have a mission
Honey doesn't matter anymore
You have to like
To be like
Present himself as a hyper-rational person
Where is like
To do
Sure I had that experience or whatever but
He goes on to be like
Look
Yeah
I talked to Zoran his parents
I talked to the mick told me it was my mission to awaken the starseed
Tell me what that meant
Give me any help
Like
Give you an impossible task will f*** you I'm running honey
No doubt it is a little bit of a nap
It is a little bit like
You're setting the sky up for failure
But at the same time
Believe
Whatever you had
Experience like the idea that there are out there
You are super important ever
I don't believe that the trivial matters of
I just
The small to medium-sized business
Would it be
Like I don't think that would get in the way of like
Everything is changed now know that there's more the universe
Then we think
Pursue this I don't think it would take
For you to be like
Yeah we get back to that mission
Maybe he's leaving off the second part of the mission was actually I need you to awaken the Stars
By running a small to mid-sized
Size starseeds
Is space
Pupus this mission
For a bit
He has a
Some voices
But tell him
How to pursue
Admission
In 2014
I Heard a Voice saying you have to go to Mount Shasta
You have to go
And
I know
What to do with it
My wife
Came back from surgery you should
Back surgery
Call Jojo see smoke in the recovery process
And selfishly I said to her
Sorry but
Hahaha
You're a shity husband
Yeah that's a little that is awful by the way
Never hear a voice that says you got to go
Yeah I'm positive
Mecca
New age
Serta pseudo-spiritual near.
CeraVe
Cult Behavior
Okay so a
Convalescing
We know he has at least one kid
At this very
Perry
Crucial time he's like
I really don't want to be around
Don't you guys I don't think
Is like ever minor
I mean I guess it probably is a version of a buttocks
Probably
Serious
But really works with burn
I'm not sure if you said it only works with Burns that's what you did specify
This fits
The pattern
Was that his wife had this surgery
She needs to heal up you got a kid
That's a highly stressful.
What makes sense
You would also then start experiencing the same
Symptoms that he had before
Controllable on integratable
Versions of the
Is delusion
Minit delusion
Is manifested by a voice saying go to Mount Shasta
I don't believe for a second
He doesn't know what Mount Shasta
Anything about it yeah
I don't think so this new age
Alien
World the voice tells you to go to Mount Shasta
You got to find it
So you Google Mount Shasta
You're not just going to Google Maps Mount Shasta
You're going to look at one of the websites and it's going to be everything you need
Probably but I think you probably knew
Before the
Supposed voice
Knowing about it
Precipitated
Divorce where I would find the answers
To the staff
Carrie gets into it like
Your
You're not a person
You were around when close encounters came out like you were alive when ET came out these sorts of things
Christian movies
Which I think is a
Real
But also a lot of those ideas
About like Mount Shasta
Okay you know like the idea of yeah go to this monolith yeah
This place were aliens
Commune
Before his supposed
Auditory hallucination in 2014
So
Hugo's
Jesus wife
She agrees to let him go
Cheersounds
But he goes to Mount Shasta
Whatever
And there's a lot
Science
The book about Mount Shasta
Area
The local
And this guy found something
Mount Shasta
The Sparks
Curiosity on the part of Sebastian Martin
I was interested in history and I said that all what's the large bag
Give me a book about these Travelodge and
Bluegill season
Local
Hematinic stand
On the mounting on the North side or the South Side of the Mountain
Why you went up there with you
Eight-year-old son is dog
Basically
And you could not really get into it
Pizza is so powerful than
Strange
Market magazine placements
Palm tree
And went back home
The next day when you went back
Zune
The temple was gone
So I thought it was very interesting in
I took myself I need
Contact disorder
So he tries
Define the publisher
Of the book
Call
Calls them
And eat it
Miraculous
Coincidence
Timing
The person
Was staying late
4 hours that day in touch with them
He tells them I want to talk to
To the person who wrote This Book
About Mount Shasta
What can I do and she's like well
You send me an email I'll forward it to him if you wants to contact you he will
So they go through that process
Five minutes later from the author that was like I'm in the area I'll see you tomorrow morning
So you together
So the author is
Is really big
We don't know who this author is you don't see the book
Lot of books about Mount Shasta I have no f****** idea who this dude
Mighty lonely
Might also not be real the next morning
Mount Shasta
This is an M Night Shyamalan twist
Introduce myself
Brisket
Would I
What was
Dokkan battle
I want to see
I actually leave at 6
My dog
And yes it's with a template in the mouth
I never received
Really reading it
I guess I was hitting a vision of him
It wasn't in the book
The whole story wasn't Sebastian
Temple disappeared
Go up there
Can you find your
And there is truth in them thar Hills
You go up there but
Bro
Don't go to
To the place where the lamarion temple was
You don't have no chance
I don't they don't get into specifics
He says go to the other side of the mountain
Is
Look for the big rock
Dude
The f****** mountain is a big rock a******
It's a kind of advice
Thank you found something no matter what
Look for the big rock
Is like
That's a guaranteed
To make it so you don't not find some
Which is
He goes up to the mountain
You find a rock
That's nice
Good
I like the story so far
Now
You probably think
I mean
One mic
That this story ends
With him going
Finding a rock
Interfacing with some lamarion and figuring out what
Going on getting information
Well I kind of think that this story
Should end sooner or later but it
Storiarts to make it look like an a******
Are you are absolutely right this is
The most interesting thing I've ever listened to
Forever is all fascinating
Hypnotic
Sorry
He gets about yesterday find The Rock
This is where I almost fell asleep
It is so crazy I don't know why you telling me
Legitimately
You could have just been like I went to Mount Shasta
I saw a rock that's it
To speculate Maybe
He saw some aliens in the distance
Just before I could touch the Rock
When I go
About safe
Acqua di Gio deafening sound like
Something witty definition
Going down
Playing overhead
I looked around and you know I stopped when that happened
We f*** with Touch The Rock
Hoping a something rotten the rounds
When I touch the Rock
Damn sexy voice says it's me okay
You're dumb Google
Okay
So earlier in the story as trying to find the Rock
He finds a rock in a voice booming deep voice
Not that rock idiot or something like that
Rock
You're good
Sky walked around the Rock
Bathtub sizes
What up
Thalia
Original point where I started
What compose The Rock
And I waited
Nothing
So I
I looked around
Because that's all the way and even from the talking about ourselves
It was
Who sing me becoming more
Heady
And so when I looked on the on one of the Peaks
Onyourhorizon
And the wind was blowing and everything else
Flags
And the world
Instax Mini
And
When I get closer
Average human
And
Looked around cityway anymore beings
Because again
What was Luke goddamn macrophilia
And I'll maybe other things little Kenny from behind
And I put my keys back on
And
The flag salute the robes biscuit were gone
And so I waited and waste time with you
Nothing happens
Had my lunch there late lunch and go back down
To Manchester
Dababy push my lunchbox
As I was packing down
Cetme
And by the way never come back
NFL
Why you so mean
I don't know if the rock touching his any
Historic
It was The Rock
That would have
If it was
Significado, I just watched the Hobbs and Shaw trailer
Yesterday
Fairies
It's going to be great
Superhuman powers
It stinks
Even for like a Project Camelot story that seems like
That is so underwhelming
I want to Mount Shasta I imagine
Show me the touch of this rock I touch the Rock
I may have seen a flag in the distance
Decided it was an alien
And then
Everything everything fits
The patterns of a bartender in the old west
It's probably just a manifestation of his thoughts
Look like this was.
Don't come back here
I don't get anything out of the store
The only reason he can afford this is because
Socialites
I think that's the real letter
He could afford it
Because he didn't have to pay for his wife's
So this episode
We just talked about everything
We got
Twosome lamarion
Pleiades
Wow the reptilians
Keep track of it but I legitimately could
You care less
Oh those are the battle line
Ku-ku-ku-ku Destroyer
Destroyed by
Some sort of natural
Disagrees
She believes
Was destroyed by these evil alien your attic
Regularly
She come into play it's right
Probably
Rock
Yeah way better rock that are boys Sebastian
Sebastian start speculating about how the allegory of the cave
Cave in Plato's work
It was given to him
I'm out
Be a clinical diagnosis for life
Has gone
And then the stories
You actually have of going to experience
Really bored ra0
I'm going to need you I'm going to be to have you back for a couple more apples
Yeah because this story mail promote your book
Next one's a little bit longer but
The new group
Ethereal beings
That
Sebastian has started
To recently
The art group
Yep buddy
So you.
What you call our schedules
Yeah those beings
Just appeared in September of last year
Once again
617 ft high ceiling
Maseca
Sitting in
Always had
I was just
Again
Checking my phone
Post
And I felt
Electrical
Charge
Braids
I knew something to send a message to my mother
And I said how do you communicate with angels
I don't care about
I considered a religious person and when my mother so if you need us you was using
Unlock Android in Android to help patients
Instead of using the
Regular Reggie
Methods
Right right
Ringy-dingy
And so what I saw myself rotting
I wasn't sure and I was insisting on it
I was actually in 60 minutes for
She gets igneo Eaton way to come I will tell you you know I will give you some advice and guidance
Happy birthday and I
Do I really need to know how
Portugal right now
I need to know that sand
No idea why was resting peacefully
Teaching
Accident
11:11
Being speak English
Schedules being sued
Eliza the same time
But dehydrate kissing eyes and have white hair long hair
With white robes
Ageless people at concerts with 100 years old
20 years old
It's been great
But it had become pictures
And Graceland
Barry White
He was the only one with an open book
Was the others observed
And I really
And
My mother was still on the phone by the way sometime
Edsel I was on the sofa and he was right there he was right next to
And Willie open-book in his hair
And she kept looking at me
And we're sexing you know things to do today just didn't hurry up
And I didn't mention a book to her
And I dropped my phone
Place my hands underneath
The book
And I blacked out
Facebook to me
And the
The man that was there was Michael
And yet
What's the name of it
He said now will be sharing with you the
History of space and time
Cool and I was through the cosmos end
That's what anybody told me about Darien saying
They have their own agenda
What you don't see on them
The archangels are
Weary of the
Jesus not only does he have
The gift to see beyond
The veil of death
Is welcomed by the leader
Of the galactic Alliance
Do you know is dealing with
Legit biblical figure
The Archangel Michael is all the knowledge of space and time
Omniscient
Michael Book of Knowledge
Told him the history of space and time
He knows everything
Can astral travel omnipresent
Anytime
Is the omnipotent probably not
Really presenting a picture where he is
Very close to God
Is really troubling Z Archangel Michael came to me and said we got a vacancy haha
Got it out for a bit
We are you Sebastian
Noted ass-whole by your own selling overpriced honey
To take over God Miss for a while
Even scoff all you want to make Heroes out of vulnerable
This was last September so
He's clearly spent a lot with his power in a self-published book
Andy at this website
Drake.
Lightworkers
Together
It's interesting that carry isn't real book back at that she's not mad about that even though she loved
Although
Completely off
Shift
So Carrie starts rambling a little bit
Target.
Should I invest in
Atlantis was destroyed by
Controlled meteor
Which still exists
Underwater military
I'm going on at Japan is
Probably on the side of it
I don't know I don't know idea
She doesn't get back to it but he does throw those Turtles of information out
I was like I don't give a
So we get to the end
I'm here
And this is how they got their energy
And I think that pee
People will find Value here and and certainly
With with your mission
If you
Want to wake up starseeds certainly we want to wake up Stars
And this.
All this because
Well defense industry
Innovation process
Feel the urgency
Jordan supposed to change
Integrating
Wonderball
Alright
Sebastian
Humanity
I want to draw Sharp
Where is the talk about your mission
Starseeds
Everything I Can Tell Sebastian is
The Auntie Jessica
Khashab is the exact reverse
Very clear indications from his past
That he went through some stuff that led him down the path he's on
Visa Vie believing
Visions or whatever these clearly embellishing
He has a family history in the same way Jessica did with her dad
To this world
He has a mom who believes
Heal people with their touch and that you came back from the dead
The grandma who is convinced
But she has Vatican
Certified miracles
Witness the Virgin Mary
So they have very similar
Trajectory
But the difference is
He's never going to get off this Trail
Or at least certainly hasn't yet
Goat saw through what she was doing and saw how it was harming people
Sebastian doesn't seem to be all that concerned
That's kind of a bummer for his grandma
Cuz she's only had two
Miracles
What you got to have three
She is still by the Pixies
He has an ever-expanding
Very grandiose life story
Inca inconsequential localized things that may or may not happen
Recruited by Angel
This is only showing a pattern of escalation
And it doesn't seem like it's going to get off track
He is absolutely hurting people
Shasta
Helping the people around him
Brace on his story
Is blacking out a lot and he starts to see and hear voices
I would suggest
Instead of going to see a hypnotherapist
Meditation
I don't know
We can't
Diagnosed s*** on the podcast or anything like that but there are strong indications
What we see
He has a natural path
There is a explanation
Meats
Criteria
Along the way
This is just a month
In the way that someone like Jessica shop
Down the road
To present like I'm just trying to wake up children
This operation
Roots lightworkers
As much as I get besides then you can also go f*** himself
Is lame
Detox
You're right on that one
Website website
That's right
Put a f****** alien on a passport
Do it because I'll tell you what an alien
Yeah if they are real
The conception
Alex Jones only killed one text
Escalation
We already
Galaxy color with huge fan I love your work