Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Jordan
Been awhile it has been a while
It was pretty good
Austin
Alex Alex
MyTouch and then just like cancel each other out like matter and anti-matter I kind of had a realization when I was down there that like
Cancel run into him somewhere
Like you might be arrested by Steven Seagal
Fun
My parents take me down to the hike-and-bike Trail Apartments
Sneak away like also most of the time that I was there
Was the time that he was on air
Try try try
I should backup
When I arrived my mom had an idea for something that you wanted to go to
Yes okay what you want to do it heard about this
Performance
Called acro-cats
I did I was
I didn't want to know anything about it
Positive reinforcement
Already suspicious suspicious
There's a cat stand
Well we got kind of got to do
If it's bad it's great if it's great on Tuesday night
Knight of acro-cats
Opening night opening night in Austin
I don't want it I don't want to disparage anybody's life's work
Or anything like that
But I would say going to this
Performance first of all
She comes out the embassy comes out
And her
She does not have what I would call performing
Chops
H-E-B cat trainer
Yes a person who spends all her time training cats just
Not have a great
You know that feeling
Host comes out of the comedy show
A lot of children
Couple of like stray adult
Like maybe 20-somethings drinking booze
There was a small part of my brain that thought this is actually going to be framed
Eddie Woodstock
But her show was kind of supposed to be a demonstration of her training
Which involves
The clicker and then positive reinforcement likes give the cats
Chicken or whatever so wasn't just a it wasn't like that
Now
I apologize for
Image is legit
A bunch of cats
Like holding instruments
And doing s***
All together with no interference if you would a Playa. And my off on you
Abandon a minute
Little do you know
Coronavirus
5 minutes hour and a half
Too long
The first I would say our in 10 of it was the cat's coming out individually
From one pedestal to another or like there was a little shopping cart and a cat with
Push it
It was fine
Simple
To do
And most
Most is tough
A lot of the time
Seattle
It was a demonstration that this stuff is very
Yeah probably
Recorder
20%
25% of the time to cats
Didn't do what
Happened how did it go
Nothing could have prepared me for how disappointed
There was a piano and that was the
The closest
Play piano.
20K
A drum set
Two drumsticks
There were set up and if the
I can't press the drumsticks
Then there was a guitar
One of its paws
So bad
Did any
Music
Occur there was no choices
There were noises
Gamblers were
Grounding like spraying
What is automatically play Trumpets
Unbelievably bad
I resented it I am
Murdering myself for not having like 10 million cat puns centered around Charlie Parker and Miles Davis
It's a bird it's got to happen Birdman I can't think of any
Calico Parker
On Wednesday morning
To the airport
That my mom's friend also was there
Procaps
Thought it was funny
Nose opening night in Austin
It really blew my mind
So surprised by how disappointed I could be
That was really what I felt like
I went in with real low expectations you have a great imagination of what Cody bad and
And I was still
Not even an even in my
Head right now knowing what it is
I still kind of imagine that a cat was capable of holding a couple of drumsticks
Getting some cake battle action going
I can see it in my mind
Do you know why cuz you're thinking of like Bill the cat
The Revenant
More than I could ever have imagined about Idaho
And I don't know anything
We are going to be in the present-day you know it's a little bit
Sealegs back
Get back in
Some really interesting going on with Alex right now a little bit of it
Between February 5th
But before we do I got to give a shout out
Two couple of new daughter
You are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Text Emily
Jeremy thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
So Charlie W
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket
Please
So
I don't know if I should lay out my premise ahead of time or let it
I'm not sure so I'm just going to get it
Okay I'm going to play another complex drop
Cat learning how to play the drums for the
I'm going to be
Neil Peart
And there you go without the pain
Bezos world.
It is at the richest man in the world
Nottingham
Oh really
So let's start on the 5th and I will let us develop as it goes
Alex Jones
Heal from that terrible heart attack he had already
Interesting solution
To David nights they're being overworked
And I having a heart attack
Stop it Ryan
Expanding on that
You just really need to take care of yourself cuz I know good and damn well
The three-hour show you prepare for
24-hours here in a couple hours at night
A double
Frankcrum
You just
I feel like this is a cop-out and they're not
Serious about what they're doing
Maledon
But
You should be really close to the edge good place to be already kind of
Mailing it in for work
What's Ranch
Demographic information about
Call
Diagram is old and white
About David nights listenership
But in actuality
He's insulting Islam
Z high-end
Listenership
I'll be a lot of stress
I can't if I can't believe how bad is Austin as it happens I still can't believe how many production
We have honor
One of the reasons but it is happening on with a lot of
Whether it be the other lawsuits
The him getting kicked off
Things you see in like Alexandria
Cortez doing really well in the house people responding quite well
Very effective that scares the s*** out of it
Has Rodger Stones trouble to deal with
Sugar daddy
He has his waning feelings about Trump that he has to
You know dance delicately around especially with the State of the Union being on this evening
Episode
February 5th
So he's got a lot
He has a lot going on
He needs David
He needs us.
Lake Apopka
What are you telling David to play a video or do red meat political stuff
This is his version of that this is Alex's like
Everyone's thrilled to see if you guys can
Just have a jovial conversation
Because what
On top of all of that other stuff
Did Alex's wrestling
There's something else that's going on in his life
Yeah you bet
But before you get to that
Yes but it doesn't these announcers
Talk over his
Like musical interludes
Sometimes you know they like eat fights against corruption
And one of them made a big announcement that I didn't know
Coming to you live from the infowars.com studios in the recap
Alex Jones
At some point
It's no longer
It might have been
Status quo remaining or more democratic
Position
Down the ballot
I guess the last year it's no longer occupied
It is recaptcha
I would like to know
First
What their definition of captured
What the first capture of tech
Does it matter if the Spanish
I tried to find
I turned Antonio so I couldn't make it to that
I did go to the spouse
And I found
Those that were lost at the Alamo the big tribute to Colonel Travis
Man
There's some crazy races statue
It is
Not
There is like an entire 12
To the Confederate dead
It is right in front of the State House
It is talking like it's war of Northern aggression stuff
And then there's another statue over
Memorializing like Jefferson Davis
Hey man
You got to give it up to him
Directions to America
There's a big logo on my mom
Not that stuff is there
It's why I missed out on
So
It's been recaptured Texas is cool now
I'm through talking about on this episode
There's more to this than even clips that I have
And we can discuss that as it goes along but
VIP
If I were to pull all the clips that would be relevant to this episode it would be 80
2 day long.
Here is Alex
Introducing
You can run run run
Getaway
Joe Rogan
Is a Christmas
His blood will fill buckets politically
So Stewart Joe Rogan
He's going to politically slit his throat and have his blood filled bucket
Alright
So I was really hoping he'd gone to the second night of Passover
What's the Cavs
He have angry at Joe Rogan day I know it's kind of disappointing
Theory about what's going on
There's an irony that we're going to be doing an episode hear about how everyone should ignore this
Why tyranny to that but I think it's important you just end record
We're going to have fun on our episode
People like a Joe Rogan
Howard Stern
To the top
Not I'm not going to tell you how to live your life.
Help
Beat by pump it up like it's a paper
Review fight because the only person benefits from that is Alex
And that's why
He's doing
A little bit about Alex and Joe Rogan
And how they got to this
Now we know they've been friends since like 1998 or so they met back in in Austin
Beach other we're crazy
And just like whatever
Joe Rogan was featured in the interview for that
He's been a guest on Alex's show for
Super long time
Circuit Drinking Buddies yeah they like to drink
About 20 years ago
Joe Rogan had Alex on
Episode 911
This podcast
Episode
And Alex got too drunk and acted like a complete
Their relations
It was going well
But since then
Gaston Rogan's podcast
Between the two of them behind the music episode right now
Not really cuz I don't understand everything but I can tell you some of the broad Strokes of how this went fat
Through all of that weird
From about 2 years ago he was on his show till
Rogan has consistently taken the high road bending over backwards to give Alex
The very generous public defender
Even four things that Alex
Didn't deserve
Send at 4
Over the years Rogan is thrown in little critique of Alex's bulshit but it's
Take a presentation of criticism that never really rises above good-natured ribbing
Really fine with it
Where things started to heat up was on episode 1131 of Rogan podcast
Dave Rubin
Is released in June 28th
I'm at episode relationship
He discusses how much he likes Alex but how wrong he is about a lot of things
This conversation was started by discussing Alex
The claims that Anthony Bourdain was killed by Hillary people
And have a sense of that sort of thing
Rogan talks about how Alex is also right about a lot of the stuff about particular leaf
Earlier time stuff that was actually true
The thing that he always brings up his
Is the idea of like
Police infiltrating peaceful protest in order to turn the violent
So we talked about that a lot of credibility even within this art
Discussion of how he's working about a lot of things
But you
Number of the things that he claimed
Are real
And one of those things is the idea that George Soros is a Nazi
Big piece of business
Alex
Call out
Normal stick claim that Soros thinks he's the Messiah and the best time of his life
Alex insist
But Joe knows all this stuff is true
Because Alex knows the key
He's told Joe the
You think Joe is injo is just
Defending George Soros even though he knows that he was a Nazi collaborator cuz out
Alex seems to think it's unfathomable
The Joe just doesn't believe him
Or that he might have looked into it and found out that Alex isn't making s*** up
So
Then
From July 2018
Predicting the second American Civil War with breakout on Independence
On that Fourth of July recorded episode 1140 of his podcast with Joey Diaz
In the episode he laments that Alex has been saying that he's working with the Deep state
Soros apologist
Just because he doesn't agree with Alex about the Nazis
Rogan keeps talking about how much she loves Alex and wishing that he would just calm down
On the second episode Joey Diaz is clearly joking
About being in the CIA
And talking about how he played pranks on Eddie Bravo
Find middle ground
Also
Lely High out of his mind eating
That sounds like Joe but from there after this point when Joe talks about it again on the air
For both of their versions of the story they were in communication private
My gut tells me that Joe is able to talk outside edge
Yeah but I don't know who knows what was actually happening
And I was like yeah you know 2019
Outside
He was introducing Owen Benjamin Leon funny comedian turn fourth our host of Infowars
A sigma
I decided it was time for him to attack
He's getting fed up with a Joe I kept enough George Soros talking points
Without ever specifying what those talking points are without ever demonstrating these alleged
Has claimed
You just launched into a screed of vaguely accusing Rogan of being a puppet of the CIA
Working as a modern-day Timothy Leary
DMT
Mets.
For a perfect libertarian whatever
Illegal
But I think they should be illegal
Infowars
Another important thing to consider is that hates Joe Rogan
I want Benjamin was what you might call an early associate a lot of a lot of the members of the intellectual dark web
But no one really cared when he got kicked off Twitter for harassing David Hogg
Parkland shooting
His
I want the dump f*** article that came out about the the IDW the internet anyway
Kind of lost
He started making videos about how members of the IDW told him that you hate being kicked off Twitter after
Good for their brain
We started doing all this stuff at
Kingdom very publicly Joe Rogan is like that
He considers the ringleader in the glue of all these years
On calling these people out
Because he had an intense need to be the victim of the situation
David foist him into
Infowars personality candidate
Anyting
But I definitely find it at
Interesting to Alex's big turn-on Rogan has happened
Fairly soon after he begins work
Stupid coincidence
Or it could be this dude being really negative influence on Alex had pushed him over the ledge on his
Erstwhile friend
I don't know I'm not sure
But that
It sounded like any other time but Alex is talk s***
It was a little bit more like this
Weird little bit
The normal but not much more
Yoshi pretends to know something circles for a bunch
Never demonstrates
Feels like a big who gives us
An episode 1238
Redban
From February 4th this year
Joe discussed at Alex's in a bad
Play Emily still cares about it but that Alex's lights
He talked about how Alex was lying to him about what he said in the past about Sandy Hook
All the videos
Love Alex saying that it was fake
Was that we just had debate
And I can't I can't abide by that
You talked about how he how Alex believed dumb b******* about Rogan being threatened
And not talking about conspiracies
I have that was all a prank that they played on Eddie Bravo
Joey Diaz told Bravo all this stuff was like
Pull-A-Part
Reporting information
Frank you got that
But through it all
Joe was still talking about how about
Approaching situation from a position of being a friend
It was basically you could stop it up by saying like
You need to stop making things up
But I still love you
Can I be on your show if I saw you I'd give you a hug
Yeah that sort of thing complicated complicated
Because he knows that everybody looks at Alex's like this guy the f****** monster is a liar and all this s***
I've known him for a really long time
He is making stuff up
Physician
All the trouble that Alex
It wouldn't
Be there if you didn't
Little bit like saying
You know what
You would be
You wouldn't be
I've always look I love your good dude
I thought you shouldn't have murdered that guy though
You can't live your life constantly going
Through it being like everything negative about me is fake
Yeah you can't
Tapping into
Being a little bit
I want to say I'm not
F****** the fan
Gullible
But he does have moments of decency to moments of like
Not knocked out falling
Into traps grade on news radio
Wonderful
The 4th they episode with Brian Redban
It's the next day
Alex
Hear about that
He is pissed
Because
Well quite frankly I have a number Theory
Against
IDW dark web
He has Alex
It'd be very easy to be like hey here's a good thing to do
If I were to write this
I would Beyond notes I hate Alec
Textbook
You aren't allowed on social media
You aren't allowed on all of the platform
But you know who is
Joe Rogan
Start a fight with him
Start a fight with him it'll get so much publicity because then people are going to share all of your stuff
All over
Actual fight
You could also appeal to Alex
Ego by being like you could
Like not in a physical fight now absolute
On your on your wall or whatever
You know still like
I think
I get the sense
This is
Like the motivation
Alex probably feels dumb personal betrayal because
It's really hard
To hear
Someone be like
I care about you baby
I know for a fact
You've been lying to me
Because the only response is that really is like
I have I have been lying to you I'm sorry
Let's make it right or
F*** you your clothes
How extensive choose the ladder pad
No
No and I'm so
I think that this is what's going on and what are the further things that
Believe that
What I understand
This B
Howard Stern has been having a Alex
Impersonator come on his show
And they make fun of him
I am so Alex
Started trying attack Howard Stern
And I think it's the same strategy I think it's the same thing but it's got a huge
I attack him to that will give me access to his audience
Maybe if I do it
I can't get new people in otherwise
Here's the important
I know I'm giving
Almost like this
And the episode already
But
Alex's business model relies on there being more inflows and outflows
But he knows that there's going to be
Bebo
You know that there's going to be people that he can seduce into his worldview
It is overly simplistic
Crypto bigoted worldview
Because of
The Allure of the mystery of it messed with the forbidden knowledge
Do you know that he can always get people in the door
If people
Have access to his bank
He also knows
That not everyone staying around
People are going to get disenchanted they're going to start looking into things buddy
At least some portion of them are
So he needs there to be more inflow than out
Flow and everything was fine
From a business model perspective
When he was allowed on every
And now he's not
That's why his numbers are are down is because
The rate of people leaving him has stayed consistent
Writing the rate of people coming in has gone down
Solution today
Find more ways
To get people in
You could do almost
No better
Then Co-op
Joe Rogan and Howard Stern
Especially if you do it simultaneously
So I think that's the strategy that's going on sorry about the little bit of their butt
Pathetic
And very sad situation only thing that makes sense for him to do I mean
Is if I was writing a business plan it's like
Okay so I attack
Joe Rogan and Howard Stern
And I turn a s*** ton of people often
But
Blisters that they have
Just looked into it and it's like this Alex Jones
A billion people
Desperate
Realizes
We can't get access to
Any other way
Big part of it
The reason I want to focus on the Rogan one more than Howard Stern one is
I'm not a big Stern guy and I think there's a lot of difficulties with him
But I don't want to unpack
Rogan is more familiar to our show
Personal
Stop there
Like Alex and Rogan have much more of a personal relationship
I've watched the videos of Rogan talking about him
They come from a place of humanity
They come from a place of him being a friend
But he's talking to a guy doesn't want
Terrible things about
And then took to hear what Alex ends up saying about Rogan
It makes it
Awful like it's a really heart-wrenching kind of
Like I just played
Alex
Right that's part of being a psychopath
Right
You know you got one guy saying hey I like this guy a lot either friend
You know it
When were together I use my friend
Right about certain things I wish you would stop doing that
And then your response
I'm going to hang him up by the legs and
Political
It's the pits
It's not it's not a good reaction
Is very similar reaction to What American Psycho
It makes the most sense as is
Alex speech
We're marching to Valhalla
What kind of mood he's in after he talked about slitting Rogan's throat
Already told you bubbalus volume Enya's of the system a long time ago
God I feel scared
Why are my soul right my heart
Journey
I'm on the path of my ancestors
Why do they not do it it's a loser so
People chosen your lot with the Devil
Take you on
It'll be this contest that defines us
I guess you we are
I start taking the devil on it today we start 11
Menu shivaay Rising
You realize God's in control
Blush got2b
Enemies got to be engaged
Got2b bone
Sword got2b shield
Got to come down that's cool
We'll see heaven
Roof okay
Alright cool
You never like to see guy in this kind of state
That song is a lot better with Alex Jones
Anytime soon
Yeah I just talked to more about I was going to politically split Rogan
Squealing it's up by flag it's better to get the blood out
To that Joe Rogan fix the show
Cuz your rabbit is a freaking hog
Ouch
Ouch I need to drive home
If you listen to the stuff on Rogan show
It's not scabies
It's very soft
It is a friend
Struggling with his emotionally resonant
Yeah
I like this guy if we're together we're friends I would give him a hug
Alex responds to that
In the most in
Human way you just makes fun of the idea that Rogan trying to treat him like a person
Oh I love Joe yesterday
Alex
I still want to be your friend
My friend
I am so scared right now you're so
Popular bald head
Muscles and take all that growth hormone a steroid
Help me I'm weak
I'm sorry
Wow
Threatening
Which is strange
Well the threat is
Like
Alex has to admit that he
Capable of having emotions
Because in this situation that
For him would come off as a threat because
Joe is presenting himself as the
Person taking the high road
The person who cares
Is the person who
In Alex's for at a higher level
It is it is paternal
Joe saying all this stuff is like
Utah
You could say it's you talking to your friend who's lost
But if you're Alex you could hear it as
Prodigal son lost his way
F*** you
You're a piece of s***
You don't like that kind of
There are some parts of
Other,
What do you hear Alex talking about some of this stuff is like
People drinking adrenochrome and stuff like that
The guy I knew
He's going through some s***
Looks like it's yeah
I could see the
Like
Alex could be threatened
By the idea of it
He's in tire
Sort of
Primary brand right now isn't
Someone who actually knows him is pointing out like
Do you have
Shifted entirely
No
And I guess
Could respond to that
Absolutely
Alex makes
Text Joe
I've no idea
Oh oh
Maybe get those Italian Guys in the end in Vegas do something for you job so scared them to
He is making implications
Money does throughout that like the people behind the ustr
Rogan has mob ties
In Vegas
Impossible it's not beyond the available possibility yeah but you're actually makes a lot of sense
I would buy that others like Direct
Are based on
From Twitter
Was on Rogan show
Alex
Was banned from Twitter
Endorsi said I don't know
Offended by that no but I honestly I think
The idea that he wasn't directly involved in that
Oh yeah I would believe that is a possibility
I think it's also possible where he's like I'm of course I don't know why he's banned I'm letting somebody
Twitter right now
Look
All the like if you if he legitimately asked Jack he's like okay
What were the reasons that Alex was bad
And Jack responded with the actual reason
Right next thing that you said like for the smartest thing to say is I don't know
Okay
Trump did that
Stop that.
Trump said that
Prompted that trumpet.
What are your reasons
You do enter a conversation
The correct
Possibly Acura company doesn't know
Operational
I believe that 100% Groupon Eric lefkofsky didn't know s*** about what was going on
In any
I like assertive tendril of the company
See you weren't there on the day he was filming the episode for Undercover Boss
I mean I met him a couple times
But
Casual
I was going over the billionaires list
Yeah I can't
Billionaire son-of-a-b****
My feeling on this
Alex
Understandable
But also on that
Alex claims Rogan disclose
That Dorsey is financially involved with one of his sponsors
Which is Cash app
Rogan says
Disclose that
I don't know I think
I knows it from other Clips I've seen of Rogan talking about
And a reasonable person would assume
That's like from their conversation
That
Dorothy
Twitter is
Like in financially involved with it
It says
As a lot of the stuff Alex's.
Albertsons primary business model for years was having my guests as
Bob Chapman's entire existence of the show was basically predicated on that criticism
Joe might have liver extinct
Joe might have
Splinter in his eye but Alex's
Whatever
Find the proof of the Splinter is in the pike
So the other criticism that Alex has is that Joe's involved in pump and dump schemes
Okay
Maybe
I love it when two people that I don't like
I'm a reveal information where I'm like
Sure
Go for it
I know he's a s*** I agree on all fronts
I know with a reasonable amount of
Very good reason to believe that a number of Joe's gas over the years especially
Really heavily
Probably involved in some pump and dump
I don't know if Joe was involved I don't know if he got any money out of it
Involved in elevating some of these people
Whether it was intentional or not
That criticism is fine
But I also still don't think it married
I really don't like
I think there is a different way to do this
I think that Alex
Is really just trying to lure Rogan into a protracted
Where'd you can get
This is professional wrestler
For sure
This is a job man
Before he gets to Rogan he keeps saying I'm going to get to him
Forgets the other guy
I guess that it's that big stink
Letter
Videos around and stuff like that
Penis
Alex is saying that this dude is saying that Alex
Is threatening to kill the families
Stuff like that
Is about like what do you do with obviously
We bad
Like what
The sort of people who threaten the families
A victim
He's not saying that Alex is one of them
Like
Intentionally misrepresents whatever this
Something bad
People's families right or another like tendril of another correction of this
Whatever
Is this guy
Didn't do it now
Madelaine petsch
Evil in themselves
Viv
I don't think
If I was casting
Joseph
More like Nazi sign
Okay alright
Pathetic
Great Clips
Only vaguely mentioned Alex
Peoples
And second
The first thing that I thought was this guy
He was not a very compelling
So
Eclipse
Garbage
The reasoning that I was
Just enjoy how like Slims
You trying to come down on
For possibly having
Group that
Sponsors hamavet does DMT retreat
Or something like that
What I would call
Prude
That the government
Vault okay
Then we looked at the group's funding Joe Rogan
Single-handedly
We watch the hold
Ayahuasca
Movement with retreats
And the police universities are involved
Which shows you the seven funny
I want to know
How many cities
I want to listen cannot be long
But he's saying that universities are involved
Improve
Substantiate that University
Government
If funding is involved
0 private owner 20 private university
Because
I did find
Ayahuasca
Group in in Chicago
Do universities
I went I couldn't actually partaking
Because I
Pillow
Tiamat Danny's there's one thing everyone knows
I kind of
Faulty assumption that there would be like sleeping bags
Hell no they
Whatever
They're very secretive number one
I don't think her Goodreads
That's not true there is some places
You can go
Letter like a Native American
Places you can
Contain
As part of religious ceremonies
Here are the United States
Number in like South America and Central America
One of Alex's former guests
Who we just tried to brainstorm
I can't remember what his name
Hibachi
Jesus started his own cottage industry
Retreats in
Central America
He didn't have a problem with that guy why does he have a problem now
What are all these criticisms that he's has like there's like
A couple of them that I find
Samaritan
But also
Your reason for bringing this up stock
And the rest of them
Your own stated ideology
What don't you want to maximize freedom
Counter
Libertarianism
Anyway
Alex Logan has government
EPA
Absurd idea
And then he expresses his idea that Rogan participates
But you talked about here.
Call Joe.
Skip it all headed back on it but I said no just translation please please please let me back on
Shootings happen
Stage before
So people right question
Stop going the talking point I said it's really scary
How you follow every talking point
Betty gets even worse
He calls me before the election
Having some pacifism be alright was getting banned
Researching
Floyd Mayweather
Product.
There
Alex's
Complain to someone
Integrity in video games
It is a valid criticism just not coming from Allen exactly I don't know that it's true
Don't care I can't
Stress enough how much I don't care
What these 280 little
Yeah it's only because it is criticism that we've made of Alex
Joe Rogan's doing this like
Shady business. I don't know that he's doing it.
We know that Alex
Orlistat
Alex's in this place
Complaints about Joe
In the same way he did when he was saying that like
He doesn't think that Soros is a Nazi but knows he is because
Obviously
Or they're or they're corrupt
Possibly decent criticisms
Week 1
I think he wants this all out
Conflagration
Between the two the
It benefits him
Is it out here
And then
It's just something like this till 1
Years ago
I should have ignored that
Are Charming.
I want more Joe
I want floor I don't want to be nice
Comprende
I hear so much pain throughout this entire
Fight bang Newsradio reference accidentally
Don't you remember super karate monkey
Weight of War
It's fight for me
How else would it be
At some point
And then the super karate monkey death car will come from my heart
He wants war in the reasons
Estate
Things are in right now is good for
For him
If anything all this is going
To do is make
If you like thinking that Alex
Because if
Rogan's audience
That might
Tickled
Maybe he's somebody to look into he's an equal right and instead is looks like he's
He's pathetic going to lose he's trying to do essentially what
To workout with
Glenn Beck
Right back in 2009
One-sided
You rude
That worked out for Alex
Think about
This
I don't know how to put it any simpler
Another one
Yeah it's just
Start picking fights
With people in order to gain access to Their audience
Claim you're bigger than them
Because I have all the audience members
It's just a principal thing
You know it's just a steam I'm offended by that what you going to do
The only thing I'm going to give Alex credit for
Is
There were so many times you could have got on board with some
Bitcoin scheme
Never
Again I might Furious that that is because he does not understand it because it's not physical
Very possible and fact that he's run buy gold
Cool I want some Bitcoin
You don't get ahold of
I don't understand is blockchain
What's going on
Our laurels
Yeah I do respect that on some level
Because he had a bunch of these
Please Bitcoin
On his show over
People coming in and telling
He could but I agree
Even if it is
Good all them for me that's true
Whatever leave it even if it's a neutral it's a neutral positive or whatever
Alex
Just got this
Has discovered about Rogan
And his position in
In the world
Okay
Everything
I'm going to expose
Because you're there darling I figured it out
You're there baby cakes were there model the future
You're on the internet but no one else has some
Bleuroot everyone
Really hope
I don't think that
Joe's anyone's darling except
Right
Craigslist
Is it like a restrained populist nationalist types
Survey just data about how how many is bad
And you're like a lot of them said I don't know those are the people who listen to
Joe Rizza heavy overlap
You're a little bit earlier but maybe even more to the idea that
Rogan is kind of
I'm back
Then
I gave credence
Like you was right about some stuff every now and again but also
The conduit towards harder right
Through a lot of the the narrative
You got engaged in
Lot of things
Underlying his
It is a ideas
I think there's
Herbicide for that
Diaz's on Fox News
Glenn Beck
Very strange booking
You should all
I don't think
I don't think there's a one-to-one parallel what is the same
Is it there very
That don't appear to be what you're getting involved
Glenn Beck
Was a berry
Important
Piece of radicalization towards hard tea party stuff
And people like Alex Jones
The same
Joe Rogan
Exist
Every sort of tepid bath
You can get into
But the water rises really fast
You don't realize
Always having all these islamophobic assholes
Hey man we're just having to
Great I think there's something
But also
The interesting difference
Is that
Back in the day
Was the sole
Glenn Beck pipeline
Beneficiary
Because people who would get sort of seduced in with Glenn Beck's at 3
When they would watch
Travel towards
Nowadays with Rogan
It doesn't necessarily flow to Alex
It flows to people like Jordan
Peterson vs right
Sobe idea of him attacking joke
The pipeline doesn't
Right
It's interesting I don't know these are a lot of unprocessed thoughts
Alex
Feeling very very jealous that
Like the
View space pictures
Carved out
Almost single-handedly carved out for himself
The world
Has now been superseded by all kinds of dumb
Looks like 9 or Ben Shapiro or
God dammit I paved the way and I'm getting
Like I get it
Yep
He's he's getting taken down by Marlo man that's what's going on here
He's a he was a what's-his-face
He helped
Create
As Foster people who are much more
Slick
Better at the tools of the last generation
That
The nature of life
That's why you got to do positive things
Got a nurture positive folk because they will use those
In positive ways
And we talked so much about it but it's always important
Make an effort to be a ladder down
When I if I go up I'm putting the ladder down for you to
Give me Bono I think a lot of help
He's going to destroy Joe Rogan
The French don't matter to me
That's not a threat to you again I'll never come on your show again
I'm going to destroy you
Get you
Coming
Do you think I am what you think I do
This is like leaving weird voicemails
I'm still your friend
And I care about you
I want war
Hey that's not a threat
Well that's a threat and you do you know how when you know how was somebody's like I love you
You and I care for you and your like I will kill you because that's what I heard you m***********
Those are Fightin words
I honestly feel like
Is this a show
Breakdown
And I don't know if there's much value other than demonstrating
What are you doing is trying to find
NuWave
To get that inflow of people
To replace the people who are leaving
Yeah it is the best way to do it
I don't know
I'm not sure it's a hardest hitting episode will ever have done in our lives
But I think it's
Important
Every now and again
Make a demonstration
She's doing
And why sometimes
It's very enticing
To post a ton of stuff about like
That impulse
Because you're playing into the
The troll that Alex is doing
You are unwittingly being a part of his
PR stunt
That would just
Fall flat
Right
That's that's one of my larger thesis about alot
I am interested
Good to know
Because
Because the
The problem with the performative aspect
Podcasting
You know even if you have Joe Rogan
Audience
He's like
Of that
Like I love you and I care for you and I would still give you a hug
Calculated how much of that is part of the performance conversation
Exactly stand up for a long time
Making things
You plan to say see you next
So I don't know you could if you want
He's trolling Alex with
His decency never like
Gordian knot
You cannot untie interested in
It all makes perfect sense to me
The f****** lunatic of course he's going to react like this lunatic with
Who's clearly stands
It's a benefit from his opportunity motive
Where is with Jo Jo has
No reason to talk about Alex
He does in the sense that a lot of people would be
Find it weird if
People expect him to
At least address the idea
But my thought is like
Snow White
JoJo's actual response like just from a perfect emotional human standpoint to this
Because my suspicion is Joe is going to listen to this and be like
Like I don't know how you could listen to Alex
Go this far
I don't I don't
I don't know if he has either
I'm just saying like
I don't know if you could listen to this and how over the f****** top it is without being like
Dude yeah
If you are not supposed to know the person like a sentence or two words like you know what
I don't was unforgivable and I will never go on a regular show
Holyshit man that wasn't cool
But if you spend an hour and a half I'm going to light his balls on fire with my nunchucks
Dude
Hey dude I get it
Fine but
Reactions
We generally.
And we're not going to do this is definitely not
The ones that are genuine and its next clip
Don't give me anymore pleasantries
Give me your stats
Fabric
Now you understand the ship
Do you understand
Down Hillary
Is this what the shape of water was available at Council Rush
Because God wants Purity God wants things hot and cold not lukewarm
Joe Rogan
Oh that's lame
That's lame
Your heart isn't in it then
No
Wheat
God blessing
Mission before I'm done
At least your destruction
Michelle was only a baby
These fools
Must first be destroyed before
Plant
Awful
It's a kuchen
It doesn't even feel like
Passionate Alex a million hours of Alex in week until for sure when is Harden in
In the weird song titled Alex Watson
This is a PR stunt
The Craft
Do it there is the idea that
Give me your attacks that's not saying I want to fight you that's like
If you attack me I really want that
Yep be good for me
Please I'm just a horrible thing
In a hole
But you cannot
Stop yourself
From responding
That's what's going on
This is a bait
Troll
I'm sorry talks about how effective he is at
Thoughts
Lego
Longs running failure
Shop
Imma run you politically all the rest your people over so let's go to war
No one has ever survived Alex attacking them
I'd like to tell you about two people at least one guy probably technically you didn't survive
I don't want guys did I will fight
This lawsuit or I will die trying
And I'm settled later
Also Alex had to give a public apology
YouTube James horrible she said about him
Like everyone survives Alex's attack
Everyone does
Everyone you know who survives out
They just accepted apology
And don't take him for all he's worth
Brother defamation
Engaged
So no Alex get out of here with his no one survives my attack
The f*** out of here
You know you know what
So far with our knowledge of Humvee Lucaya
He is ever done for the human race is
To the cleaners
It's a matter of empathy
What's a matter of scale
Well you know you know showing Mercy to one person
Non-emergency
You too many
Perhaps
And maybe prioritize the one person who was in the crosshairs over the other
Just I let bygones be morality
And they have in those
If you had a lever would you pull the train to kill one person and save 5 live
Or would you leave it alone
Would you follow through with the lawsuit
With a penitent bigot
Knowing that their apology will be in fat
Tough decision
Guest
Play so I understand greater
Positives could have come out of Alex having to pay millions of dollars or whatever he would have had to pay
Whatever
For all the good
For that
Alex keeps saying the Joe Rogan uses Soros talkingpoi
And like I said he never really explains what
Points are
He does say that
He has like
Inside documents of the talking points but he never produces them he never says what they say
Documents
You mean
By Soros
That
And then they sue me
Amrit jurisdictions whatever I'm not worried about that
Shipmates
Talking points
Is Justice reference
A video that was posted on Media Matters
Yeah now I do the video probably with added it in as much as
Tire show
But it's not edited like splice together in such a way as to be like
Rail
It was totally fake
This is a Soros talk
Because he got it
For Media Matters
Is ludic
That's just
Source
Vicki found
Alex said debate
On Media Matters I found a video that was very clear it's Alex
Literally
Multiple times
Multiple instances
Kids didn't die there
That's not using the thoreau's talking point
Text using
The video that they posted
Is Anythink
Pinpoint
Pretty much
They're not James O'Keefe
Right but that is only exhaust
Joe mentioned that on Media Matters
I found a video of Alex saying
Perfect
It is
What he's done is turned
Any
Point of reality
That he fundamentally disagrees with
Into a
Conspiracy or boros
So so to me it's just him staying surahs talking point is him saying
A reality that I don't disagree
Herdy a reality that disagrees with me
It is almost it's almost like if you if you were if he'd forgotten where the Mississippi River
No it's on the line between these states he be like
Dora's talking
Doesn't mean
Interest
That's from infowars.com or
Daily Caller
Daily
I don't
Not WorldStarHipHop
I do not read it
You know and if the article is good and its source
I'll still take
A f****** article from Daily Caller
If it's
Like if it's a knot
Information
Rite Aid generally most of the time that I have read them
But just because I don't like the source doesn't mean I'm going to throw the baby out with the bathwater and State
One might have a good article whatever
I'm not going to I'm going to come in with a slight prejudice
But you know allow the possibility that this is real
Things like I could do that
I could do that like oh Alex has reference article business big Tucker Carlson
Fun
Because it's
It's stupid
Any ideas
OBD2 matters got some funding from George Soros
Oh it's all Soros narratives
The f*** out of here
Sojourn I got a question for you
What kind of literature we do you know about my boys
The show Alex launches into a course of two clips
A discussion about Moby Dick Moby Dick
I want I think it was read the headline of Moby Dick
Moby Dick
Guy obsessed with rooting for him or wait
I don't think he knows queequeg
I want to say
Before we get into any
I don't know what
I'm not sure but I do know he has not Read Moby Dick
Pressure
You've chosen the wrong side and you're going to be
Destroyed
Matter what happens to me Joe you're done
And the whale
Melba's Joe Rogan
Bill shakes
You should
I sit there
With the number one political show on YouTube
The gel was viciously jealous
Admit it was way bigger than the show
We talked about how I want is showing all this crap
I don't want morals that I didn't earn I don't want to be you
I don't think everything
Is Joe and happy
Metaphor
I guess
Are there any other supporting characters
Meditation
Here's my problem with this I don't even understand why that start
You know I can't understand why the Moby Dick metaphor started
I think what he's thinking is who's hunting who
I think what I think he's thinking he's Captain Ahab and Rogan is the white whale
Yes I agree
I don't get what you just said
If anybody wins
Middle of the movie or the guy one
So you know what
None of them were a good guy
Alex
In that clip I was like I'm very confused by what you're trying to say
I don't understand how the other hand
It was a metaphor for other ship
In his next court Alex tries to take the metaphor in two different
Places
Oh that's not going to be interesting Lee makes it
Worst
More clear that he doesn't know what he's talking about
Well is he
That's true
Alright alright
That's the only part of my
Is Alex going to come correct
Nope
If you're a whale you're fighting a big squid
3 * Benjamin
Noel no sperm
Schlong
One of my tentacles
Retard
Okay
And don't worry I'll show you
Shlomit
Very slowly
Please give you what you want alleyway
Pictures of God
Full
Upload
I wish I was a god about how like is that effect
I'm the squid
What is my great headed
Starts within
Interesting like a joke
12 year old
That's very different
Maybe that maybe
Thought it wasn't
I remember my favorite part of Moby Dick was whenever Captain Ahab
Tragically throwing his Spirit at the well and then goes down and
It turns out that there's just a giant squid that Aiden both he was a real Twilight Zone twist for
Ending
Play disappointing narrative level
Thoughts about
What Alex's motivation is in
Express already
I think
Spr stock
Involved in Owen beds
Being negative in
But then
Next clip gives
A reason
Why he's doing this
That I think is
Simultaneously
True and also Alex
Is staying
A sort of blustery bulge
Yeah
Percent truth
You're my way to get Jack Dorsey
And you're my way to get them all
And so now
It's kinda like
Mistletoe
You can hit those buttons as fast as you want
Just keep coming down
Body launched 1,000 other missiles
St.joe
Pretend Hollywood world
I'm in the
Big boys
Sorry what was stopped pontificating
Metaphoric
Whistlestop is not the 50
2% true
I think Thursday
To Alex thinking attack
Joe will somehow
Be a message
To Jack and maybe get a
On Twitter or something like that
Jack through attacking Rogan something like that
First of all I feel like affected Alex's
It's not really what he's
And then also I just don't think it's a reasonable expectation
Have from attacking
I think
Now white whale
Call the social media is Alex as well
He's going to go down
And
He's never getting back
Neither
And even if he does
It will be at the end of both of the
Friendster is a squid
Printer isn't
Going to be amazing if prinster wound up winning throughout all of us
Somebody just brings it back how
That would be a twist
I don't know if M Night Shyamalan directed Moby-Dick social media
So I even Bravo telling Alex that Rogan was being threatened
Then all that stuff was a Joey Diaz prank
Yeah Alex doesn't realize that
And you attacked me
And say I was dishonest with you and then he goes Owen
I was never threatened Jones what about that
Eddie Bravo
He said that
Why
It doesn't matter Joe
You shouldn't listen to Eddie Bravo Bravo
Sweetheart but he is the dumbest man I've ever heard speak
Very smart and specific ways like a don't take that away from
The infant's brain has a
Capacity
To understand a lot of
Kinesthetic
You and I couldn't talk
Use your body in certain
He's a genius
Very f****** gullible
He's very
Presently certainly has become in the past
I would tell you the very fun person
Be around yet
Ideas
The can't be backed up
Alex is not the sort of receptor
But he's a bad person to talk to Eddie Bravo cuz Eddie talks
It just repeats
I'll take that as a source
Yeah yeah
Joe Rogan
And then when it comes out baby
Out Pizza in my family's been threatened
Bulshit
I don't know I don't know why you think
Turns out is Joe Diaz
EBU
Alex Jones
Or reporting
The Eddie Bravo tells you socially
That calls into question
Everything that
You've ever reported from an anonymous source
Because it could be
Eddie Bravo level it could be anywhere
No disrespect but you're not a high-level Source interesting about him
Island
Episodes
Little annoying
I have no problem with that
I wish I could remember gullibility
Yes he has some interest
He has a complete lack of
He's a complete lack of God
Appear to be like
Yeah wants to believe
It's not that he wants to do anything beyond that it's like Fox Mulder
Which could be Fox Mulder
This
So funny
In the middle of this show or towards the end
And Alex
The break music is playing
Going
Kool herc
Nothing
Launch into an entirely conversation as a heartbreak
Well he talks about darts as a metaphor
I'd like
I'm sorry
Red Lobster off of all of you
I've never felt better in my life
I'm hurting
It like 15 ft Pro triple bull's-eyes
Someone helped found a shot at
You may need to
A great darts of The Darkside you might need this herbal to eat
Man there's nothing like a man expressing.
Deep psychological pain
And then getting cut off by
Yeah of Rogan
You just interrupted
And I wanted to cut a bunch of that stuff
For Alex or for understanding
His mental state like it just was
Boilerplate
He only gets through Maybe
Two sentences
Two or three sentences that Rogan says
You know what Paul Joseph Watson hosting the next hour I got to got to let him host
So
I'm going to get out of here
You know that's
The next day I'm in a week
I know Mike
Well
Last night was
State of the U
So probably going to hear about that
Nope but also
Call Joe Rogan
To it so we jump into the 6th
And listen to this s***
You know I miss Joe Rogan phone call last night
Had my phone off
Traded
I really am so dumb
Disgusted I don't know if I was taking the call and I knew he called
Joe will be Armitage at the bottom of the next hour
No no no no no
No
Used to believe that the real
It's not wild The Ivy at the very idea
Conciliatory going to slit his throat politically
Well it's finished
So I guess we'll take his call five-year-old
The factory
I thought you didn't care about going on his podcast
Seems like you care
Bottom of the shower
Along with traffic
Course
What does that mean
Satire starts with an s
Does that mean
Attire clothing
What is satire begins
I don't I really don't
I don't get the reference
Might be but I don't I don't
I heard that
Yeah I don't know but the Joe Rogan is not coming up
He's going to make fun of Rogan later
Talk about Rogan
But you've made it big enough
If you're listening if you don't like
That will be something that people start putting out
Rogan's going to be coming up on the show
That's such a bummer
Trick videos
That's such a bummer I will tell you this right now
When you type in
Set the nest
Even if you're using quotation marks around it
That sounds about right
Are you looking for satire or
Cooper colloquialisms that don't exist honestly probably a Moby Dick quote
If I had the gas
So Alex
So we all know
Because I've already told you broken
I'm coming
But
If you're listening to this you presented
The premise that Rogan is going to be on later
The show
With a ton of ads
And stuff like that
Because he knows that everybody is sitting there waiting
He's done what is sort of the
Propaganda show version of a thirst trap
Sure there's no cleavage
Or anything like that but it is
Anticipation the idea
That Rogan might be calling
It's like when you're watching The Biggest Little Whorehouse in Texas
Dolly Parton
Navigate to music
Is that Alex does talk a bit about the the
What I would categorize as like blah
He's defending Trump but it's not
The same as a
It's not
The same thing
It's different
Trump five
Virtue of attacking
It's different than like
This guy gets it all
Now the exception is
Was talking about killing baby
As opposed to
You talking about
Preventive care
Abortion
But Women's Healthcare
Alex is thrilled about that
Even
6 months ago
Sing like that would have been the
The entire show
And it was just something you like
Is it was just another
Yeah
There are changes
But it's not really important because
Alex's
Weird on this February 6th
Show in a way that I think is irresponsible
And I think you didn't
Mean to do
He starts
I'm going to be honest with you
He might as well be a Project Camelot episode right now
Slight Rogan stuff and Project Camelot
Listen to this f****** s***
This
You might
You could easily imagine Kerry Cassidy listening to this late
God was real
Call this was real before
Right
I went to a city fully under
Alien control
Like San Francisco or Seattle
Breached
Alien
Whatever's that
That's his one of his producers
Seattle
Answer like Alex going to be like
He saw that
Evil there
And I'm guessing what really happened is
Young Buck some some guy was like
I don't I think that every time we go out at
It's really hostile
And I don't want to be I don't want to I didn't sign up
Ragtime
The case but
Zimmerman
No he is not yet
We would round one corner
And The Smiths
Delete
People were
The corners the next person would finish the sentence
Play Lottery videos
Do you have do you absolutely have a
He hasn't played
It would be amazing if he had
That would be awesome
A conversation with one person over here at the camera pans
Around the corner the other person finishes their sentence of demonic voice
I would I would have
Perfect video to stay to be very very
Yep
This guy's lazy
Didn't even read Moby Dick
I didn't read
That's one
Alex is under alien
Control
Demons whatever you want whatever you want
I don't think that's good enough
Just missing that he is saying it's demons or aliens
Because he's saying that
He makes clear
There's no doubt now
Alien invasion
They worship
Believe that they are
We run into these things they're so low-level they're so stupid they're so hateful
Like zombies is kill people and attack children
Everybody else
Kevin volunteer
Like astronauts
Megadoses of broad
Okay with wires
Weather
Keep it coming baby
I'm eating it out saying
They're the ones that are doing
Insane
That is
Not be talkin
Loose lips
Snakehips
The quote Ishmael this is
Terrible
The idea cuz he always talked vaguely about where he's going
From now we know a lot of that stuff is coming
Stubblebine
General stubblebine Alex could not
Before he was
70 years old
And had been drummed out of the service
In 1984 for bringing psychic
Sheward areas they weren't allowed to be into
And
Years
I don't give a f*** what he's talking about
Stood by the quarks
It should not be somebody that you're like
This guy knows every
So now Alex
You've got this information about the interdimensional invasion of alien demons and stuff
And the first thing you come up with it
Buckets
I'm not
You f***** up by telling me your source
Makes me
Frustrated
That you can't get a metaphor about Moby Dick
But at the same time
You're going to say that there are interdimensional aliens and I thought he was starting out as a metaphor
I thought inter-dimensional nope
Therapy
Wow celebs and the immigrants
I guess it's probably like
What are you in the hierarchy
Disco demon
Well we are in Chicago. We were around.
Big fan of a lower level
Demons
Obviously
The presentation
If it is
We've left
You were a part of
But probably not
He always tries to do this f******
This what I'm saying
You understand how badly this is life
Slater Hill be like
I don't believe it
If you are
If your enemy believe something you don't believe
You don't have to fight them
Because
What
Like if they believe something
No idea aliens give them power
And there isn't a power
You don't have to
Like just use that power it doesn't exist
It's not real
I just want to be really
Clear on this
People who are like
We should
And can provide Healthcare
Spend less money
A ridiculous military
And spend more of that on
And people were like
Maybe the wealthy don't need to have all of the money and we should
Spread it around
Those people are
Demons
Largely
In his next clip
More about some of these generals
Did you talk to
Who have
We're really doing Haley and stuff
Whatever it is
What's going on
I don't they were f****** up Venezuela
I thought gun poster
Oh okay
Operating system
This is not of this world
They're coming in
Can have regulations
The problem
That's really xenophobe
47k
That's okay I'm going to take a stand here
I think that's racist
Against the whole galaxy
I know he's racist towards
Meijer his restraint has rations mantis beings and stuff like
Generals ototo
Meeting in WhatsApp
Call project
Exactly
What's the weather
Is oftentimes makes connection with
The world
It's so much of these
Ding Dongs on Project
That relate to things Alex says
Just overtly great program nonsense that we see
You told me all about these raps
Vacaville
Lincoln cent
With with
Captain Mark Richard
Become friends
Months later
Mark register
Talk to own
Anymore
Videos about help
I'll tell you this right now they would not let up
Let's have a pain in back
He is definitely using a kranda right on his
Sew-ins ex-wife Alex talks about
He's afraid of
He's such a coward
Because
I don't believe this they believe it
You are you are expressing that you
You believe this
He literally just said it's interdimensional
He said it multiple times yes absolutely this is what I believe
He wants to freeze it more like
Demons
Yeah people might
He's accepting
I just think it's so cowardly that
Couching it with
With like
Yeah yeah
Crown
I make weird we're fine making Ark
Claims
It's full of s***
Someone else said it
No it's
Dae what you mean Alex
And what do you mean
You can glean
Text Clues
But there is an interdimensional invasion
That is coming to Earth
Whatever
And there's a tree what is the difference
That's what we're dealing with
A broadcast
Kill yourself kill yourself
They live was about Reagan food
Schizophrenic
San Francisco big Tech literally worship
Compliment your health with another heartbreak sorry about that Alex Butler
I can't get enough of that you almost doesn't know how to do is show anymore
Good that it just gets cut off by
More than
I love it and it almost H2 me a little bit more than even the Advil
Eclipse
Recovery is more funny to have him cut off in the middle of
Brea
The transmission coming
They live
So
He said it's beginning this episode that Rogan is going to be on
Adele
The fact that he's not going
But if you're coming
So it's going to be a surprise
Comstock
Band
Shows up
McAdams
Mike Adams the measles outbreak
Busy guy
Your
A big business to take care of your busy guy
Why did you get in touch with
I'd want to get on today
Why is it so important that you get on
And silly talk some s*** about Joe Rogan
Then Mike says
Consider
It's the way he's talking
Implies that he
Listening
To the beginning of the show
References
Listen to Alex's talk about these alien
The health Ranger Mike Adams
On the cosmic extermination agenda that you have been talkin about I just want to affirm
You are 1%
That the call has gone out to exterminate Humanity
This is why they they love the idea of murdering Christians
Murdering conservatives killing Trump they're all about death and execution
Because the order has come down
From Alien
Wow
People are so gay
White
Jumped
It's just not like
Prove your first concept like like
Approve of the things you're saying I don't know who you are Dan right now either though
But I'm telling you it doesn't matter
How old are you
Pandora
Jesus Culture Riga
Is it sad pathetic
That's true.
Been so successful
Cuz if you hear
Whatever
Alien base
Is not coming on the show
Wright Tire
I'm going to host some of the next hour when I was Interview Joe Rogan
Cats are included in the shower
Let's go ahead
What's the truth
Not satire
Lying
Cemetery Gates
Riverwalk by those
Anyway Alex is going to do this a bit
About Rogue
Without
It's really not know
I really don't think you understand
The point
Requires a
Threat
Thresholds
Concept
Just doing something that's not right
Real
Isn't
Satire
Right
Like what
Sure
You're right.
But I were three of the show
He's been saying that Rogan is going to come on
For a bit of the show
Teasing and
And sort of implying that he's not
But also saying
Rogan's going to be on
What you do that's far or a hoax
I would even accept
If he says we're going to do a bit about Rogan
That's not teasing something inappropriate
He's hoping that some people think that Rogan
Is actually going to be on
In order to boost his ratings cuz he knows that Rogan is
Is a bigger draw
Get
More eyes more ears on the show
Hopefully to listen to
The ads until the payoff comes
But he's not going to be there
And by that point
Which is pink something that maybe Rodi Road maybe he doesn't do this
Project
He entices some of Rogan's listeners with that space talk
Maybe
Maybe he teases them with that carrot that he doesn't usually Django out
Cuz he knows
F****** b******* Neil deGrasse Tyson
What if
That would be a brutal
Brutalx
Is that what's going on
Last night
Call
Vision x i
And phone off
And I got the message this morning
Apologized
If I hurt your feelings didn't have you on but you're in a bad flyson
You're mentally ill
I don't buy that sounds
That seems like the last
Message
From someone who's
Trying
Yep that
That's a friendship breakup right there that's like hey man
I care about you and I love you and I know we're not in Parkway more than Alex deserves
Yeah like
When
This like
Wednesday message
Winston Tower
It was after Alex was on
Political
Apologize
The times that I made
Fun of you with
Yeah
Who's the performer that we're both in bed
He did try and make that
Clear
Like to hear these
Elements
Responding
Like with Josh
Stone
Like fuk
Yeah this is turned into an episode of intervention
Yeah it's it's it it sucks
It sucks
Alex way to tear your life apart around your eyes
Good for you
Things like
This is one of the only people who would have gone to bat
Free first ex-husband for f****** long time
Now what reason you have to do this
Whether it's your desperation
4 rating
Whether it's Owen Benjamin
The bad advice
Your own mental illness
Because he was on
Whatever
This is the worst thing
Possibly do like
This guy cared about
For no reason
You didn't deserve that
You didn't keep up that relationship over the years
And he went to bat
Was dumb to do that
You was wrong
The time be called
Him out about
What you learned about the
How to tell
Criticize
Alex
Because he'd known him
Years and thought he knew the heart of
The man
It turns out
Rogan
Didn't know the artist
No clue
If it's next clip Alex is pissed off
Because Joe Rogan isn't even on his
His goddamn weather
I really don't
Joe Rogan is so far above his level right now is in
Bro
Back when Alex
Like doing document
That Millions
Interviews
Everyone locked up
He was doing Fear Factor makeup
And stuff like that is pretty funny though
Yeah
And I was going to try it
Mix those two eyes
I produce loose change
Counter down had 187 million views on Google
We got to stop that for a second
He produced
Loose change
Final Cut
There were multiple versions of loose change
Before Alex even got involved
I didn't either until months
I always thought because Alex presented is like I was behind
Dylan Avery and Jason bermas was involved
Which is like the fifth version
I did not know that he got a late
Adopter
Of loose change documentary
Wow
187 million views
Donkey testicles on
Billions and billions of these are worth
I don't
Good and sit down
Do I get a tree
Did you work on my radar
When you pulled all this
Tracking radar
Targeting operation
Extreme prejudice
Headquarters
Show Mom
Because you see it's not just that you're on a higher Echelon evil
You're almost there
You are
A good pic
You're cleared to fire Joe
That means your dad my sights
Just about men. The man in me
Be scaring you and those of you need to know
Anderson
I said Joe Rogan is going to be on the show today
You lied you didn't joke
It was a lie
License Owen
Joe Rogan
It's all like
This
That's sad
I'm sad
Weird
Stack
Really
This thing we do
This episode because
Devil versus the acro-cats of Alex
It kind of feels different why
I didn't know I could be this disappointed
F***
I don't know how to tell
There
There is a payoff
To this episode
We can cut
Alex does interview fake jewelry
Right
And
Did this is what I'm talking
Is it him
This payoff is
Astro cats
Claiming that they have a cat band
Because like
Did today
The
Is disposal
She decided on the 5th
That f****** Rogan is
Is dead
I'm going to destroy you
Hasn't brought up
Real substantial in
Documents
Proof of any of the claims that he's making
These like Rogan is going to be
At the top of the next hour
Next hour comes
He's going to be on later
Are we getting out of
Beginning of the fourth hour
So it's the fourth hour
He still on yeah
Okay
Via the host of the 4th hour
To getting what he needs
Nice thought I thought
For sure is going to be
F****** recorded
I thought for sure
Between the fifth
And recorded
Some sort of dumb thing where it's like
Hi I'm Alex. Are you cool
Nah bro
And splice it in
You and your interns
20 minute
You take nothing
This is what he did
And it sucks
License Ellen
He's not and
The Nazis
Drunk
Confirm
Then the secretary want
If you put coins into the snake
Not
That is fake news
Is this bad
I kind of want to exercise
That leads to a
Embarrassing
Bet new donor level
Sneakers
I kind of actually really like that
Events
I don't think he's dead
That is
Children's book level for uninspired Rogan impression
Doesn't sound anything like
I know that I listen
Gotcha
Truffles
I've never listen to Joe Rogan
I find
Most of them
Duncan Trussell
There's a ton of episodes
Of episodes Good Company
He's not a
He falls for what shifted say people with will or able to
Thinking
Because he doesn't have an editorial process to his body
He assumes that everybody has
Goodwill when they're talking
What is Liars
It Sancho
Things
It's just a problem
You're saying thing
He wants to believe that you know
Too much trust
I'm really good friends with Alex for a long time
Do you have a certain lack of guile
That the owner
Or you've overblown what your friendship actually was
Yeah
Like his nose I mean
Their friendship actually
We was
Lav
4 years Gas Austin
How many times do they f*** you fucken take the axle
We talked every time comes through Austin
Fast
Alex never leaves off except for the times he does publicity stunt
Or
Very specific publicity stunt
YouTube Meetup
They're not good
Friend friendship
Space
The time that they've been friend
You've been friends for twenty years so they've been friends for 20 years
It's not like you actually been
Befriend for those 20
Right
Isn't sincere
Possibly
Pretend to understand
We have done
Right do each other behind
It strikes me as
Rogan's
About this
Yep
Expectation is like what their relationship was
Yeah yeah that's exactly right I was being a sneaky snake
Knows the joke and help
Now you should know
Alex Jones
Ism
Cannot be bought
You think I want to be part of your system
When I want to burn you down
Triple-S
Alex Jones
If it is sold out
I shine.
Like you so much I can't believe I'm dirty rags I can't believe
We have specials on gold right now
Every moment
That podcast
You attacked these people and you take it to them all the way maybe I let you be with us
I like yes sir
What kind of Goddard
Okay
Joe
You're all trying to take DMT and get in contact with little floating
Retard demons
From the pit of Hell
I just want you to know Joe that there's a hole
Another dimension
And then on from that and you're just
Not making the cut
You see Joe Rogan walking around
Sure
Maybe he's got platform shoes.
Like elevator
I know you're walking around heaven
Oh my God I thought it was
Spaceship weather's battles
Terrifying
I really think he thinks hired two men
Beans like up
It does seem that way seems like he thinks golf vertical
Dimensional view of higher dimension
If you will
You think you see
Joe Rogan
If he's wearing platform shoes is that good
Also thanks
Seems like a real upgrade
Super Mario
I've already been
That sort of s*** like
Dude
I think so
Whatever
This is creepy
One more clip
When you were talking about
This is all
Give me your money
This is where
Alex
Probably
Feeling that he's going to go out of
And on the end of the six
We get through
Prestige
Reveal
Of likewise
Keeps
S***
On Unbroken
Yeah
These people to come in
And keep watering
Coffers
Because this
Next clip
Is the real
Did he live there
This is reality
Tell you right now
That job
Launch all the new stuff
I'll just tell Rodger in front of God country
Rodger Stone
Eminem
My God going to bless our bank accounts while we can't advertise online
I want to bet on a lizard
Well then you just better yourself in Wizard because Infowars is a standard
In the fight
It seems the symbol a signal
Logo AAA
Needs Lionel's
So raspy voice
4 years old
And a six-shot of me is just like
The responsibilities of like earlier in the morning easier than I ever did
You got
Attack robot
Play the flesh and blood
That is
Completely committed to finding lovely
And the media and system
If you don't put fuel
In the jet tag
Come on come on land on land that money bomb
But I want to drop
Weapons information weapons
My lawyer told me that engaged
Until
The cows come home but I need
We already have great products
Turbo Force through Friday
Wolf
50%
This is Patrick
Roast
Because it's so
And it is a it's a good strategy
Trying to attack Rogan
And make it look like
Hey we're going to have a war with each other
The only thing
Subvert that possibility
Rogan doesn't
Respond I hope that he responds to it the way you were saying
That's crazy
That's
Clearly intercept
No
And that everyone
Sort of.
I've seen so many goddamn posts on Twitter
In Facebook
People messaging me about it
Just like that
I want to tell them all
Roulette
Kool-Aid
I wish I wish there was a better way to say this
Get your instinct
Migrants
Cuz you need to understand how these
People who
Havel will operate
Disney troll operation
John
Large-scale
What is stoic
Interesting
It's so interesting.
Layering war on
Joe Rogan
Alex's listeners
Have been aware
They listen to Alex's show
They hear him go
Start a war
So then they listen to the next episode
Asthma-like how is Joe gunners
And then because the listeners of
Wait this is two episodes of him
Until then they go and listen to Alex's show
Whole f****** goalie and Alex is willing to destroy what is
Probably a meeting list
Joann
In the first episode
I don't like you
Yep
Guilty that I ever like
That's
F******
So he's just going to try and keep needling Joe until Joe response
Video
You're right
It's the ideas
Go bounce back
Put
What
The benefit
Of it is
The bounce back
It comes to
Going to be
Nose
The people will probably go listen
The Rogan show
Anthurium care
Driving traffic
Is them right if the two of them
Hot Feud
Doesn't matter if they both get over
Using breast
Hanover in the process
I'm still f****** over
I might have lost the feud or whatever black get over
Right in the process
Pathetic
But I
Just pray I pray
You don't
But I I would hope
Rogator no batteries
I will say this
The canary in the coal mine
It's
I want to say at the end I don't really know
How much value
This holds I don't know if this was a great episode
But it was
Like really getting back
Jumping back into
To Alex
I thought
Is that this
Was more import
State of the Union
Enso
This is
I have to drive this message
Home very
Don't fall for tricks
Is alteryx
You want to see
Trolling
Communal what
Probably from another
F****** novel
No it's spelled with an i
Scrum
Sue Dickens
Dickensheet
My whole position on this has stopped
Yep that's that's what I would say
We have about strong episodes coming up next week
In the work
Don't have the bird
Of my vacation
I appreciate everyone enjoying
I'm sure
Back to regular knowledge fight
And
I keep wanting to spoil things
Website
Does
If you would go to the
Weevil Wiki
Information
I'm so
Proud of you
Because you've never plugged the wiki before
I recently learned is a contracted idea
Ridiculous
We also have many other websites apparently you can go to fill your hand
Oh yeah there's a third one
It's
Another one
Everyone
We also have
Twitter
What's true
Which is awesome
BookIt all men
Everything was fine
Everyone behaved themselves for the most part
It was nice
Internet Kanab
It's in the end up destroying everything
Guitar group
Make sure that you only sell good people because so far worth
It was good people
1 s******* and we're going to start going
Or also on the iTune
But I'll tell you what you need to remember do you need to remember
I will tell you this
You know what I remember
Is in Lafayette
We've already sent
To hear about the Bezos have
Yeah
I'll tell you
1 dick
That has
Technically probably never killed
I bet he hasn't murdered anybody
Also I bet
And his business the problem
Just the dick
1 dick
Has not killed a guy
One dick who has killed
It wasn't
So you're not understanding how a double entendre
Open Gmail
I'm speaking specifically of the dick
Alright but in the other case I'm speaking of
Vicky
Of the dick representing the man and that dick
Represents a good man
Has probably technically kill the guy metal shows
Alexandra Thurston color