Thanks for holding
Alex
Novelty beverages
Damn
What's the last time you got stuck in
Yesterday driving around with you since I move to
Chicago
Teach me to drive during the store. Where I thought I was going to buy an RV
I realized I needed to get a driver's license
You didn't
Remember how to drive
6th Avenue
Years since I've driven all over the road
No traffic
Time
Yesterday
What happened in Missouri
Reputation
Columbia Missouri City going for the most part
Pretty serious Chicago
Everett every comment I've ever known has driven drunk
It's not a secret
It's almost impossible to get in Chicago
It really that bad
Butter in Columbia
I never drove drunk after right
I got
Not a DUI or whatever but I was so scared in the
Losing control of a car
I was so scared of that
That's from 90
I never
Got in a car driving
Any alcohol
Even one beer
Really yeah
Why is very very
Terrified
I don't know I'm going to traffic
Communication
Sure
Alex Jones
Play Queen
Anyway
Today we got to where we will be back in 2009
Some facts about that I want to discuss them on the other side
They're very
Donuts
Let's give them a shout out
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you coming
If you want
I'm a policy wonk
I'm biking Eric
This one is MCs
Which I can't tell if
Play on Mick
The music video director like Mick ass
I don't think it is MCS thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Finally
You to somebody
Bump it up a little bit
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much Tyler
You can do that
The show we do appreciate it
Redirected website
I believe the Infowars. Wiki directoire
So that's fun
Look
Today what we're doing is we're going back to 2009 and I mentioned
A lot of the name Mister
Kind of
They're not there
Mysterious about 2,000
Oath Keepers angle
We have a little glimmering
And
You know some of those main things
We're really driving Mike
Curiosity
You know aren't that
Spectacular to me anymore but I realize our last episode ended
With coverage of April 13th
2 Days Later is tax day
So we can't
Leave 2009 without getting
Lost
I'm so excited we're going to stick
2009 at least for a little bit
I was like
You don't have to do I'm going to
The Fourteenth and Fifteenth knocked out now we're going to find out what happened
Unfortunately on this episode
I think the most shocking thing I've ever heard.
Without representation
That would have been crazy just from a standpoint that
What like
I can't even begin to talk about
F***** up
The thing that happens on this
What episode is
Like
There are not many times that I'm listening
These episodes
And like my response
Pause the episode and sit there like for a couple of
Minutes
Westbrook
And then listen back to the clip like five times to make sure I heard it correct
So I don't want to oversell this
But we'll get to that
Adrenochrome
The 14th today we'll have to let text ewe
Really threw a wrench into my
My process
I was just complaining about taxes
Any idea if there are more new taxes
And then he discusses away
Squeeze you every States passing new taxes
And they're going to take your property take your home squeeze you swatting you they're going to send the police
It's by the fights back with a second
Yeah Agreed 100% phrasing is so f***** up
Second Amendment
And anybody who shoots
Beckwith gun so you paraphrase something fights back with the second
Beckwith guns
You do not recall the Second Amendment provides
Text Kim
So that's where we start
That's crazy
If you if you
Murder and irsha Gunn
Then they're going to be all in a tizzy murdering terrorists
Restart
Open
With the government is going to send the FBI and the cops to your house
Is going to do as a squid for your 4000
If you kill them
Call the same people cuz it would be necessarily politically-motivated
That would be terrorism
Anyway
Not sure why
I think he's sort of stealing the idea
Getting the temperature of America
Neal Boortz
Neal Boortz is another conservative radio guy
Proponent
Of the
And also
Didn't have Alex Jones
More like a
Give all of the money to the rich
I was listening to Neal Boortz apparently borta starting to cover some
He's like my ex report staying
Alex about like
What is he think about that
Andy brings up the way boards is covering it
Anyway zet turned everything to a liberal issue why is there no left-wing
On the document why is it just right wing
And everything like that you know
And everything here locally in that unnatural and everything they're talkin about all the BT parties like that
One is a whale
Having thing like that why aren't they coming up against this stuff about the irs's up like that
Later the hour
Troubling is true
Wanting more taxes
Thanks Val social welfare yet
That's helping the poor to have big government
Now that's why they basically terrorist
A lot of these documents
Tires because
Question
He's my ex reports about live
Why is it only us
Right-wing people were being pointed out for their extremism
Pretend all government
Is ever concerned about his right-wing
Blind
This perception is created
Reinforced by the fact that people like Alex
Or in his collars case Neal Boortz
Only cover stuff like this when they need to go
Get really defensive about reports
About right-wing extremism
So they can
Just basically prop up their own Narrative of systemic
Depression
It should come as no surprise that the
This version of reality
The propagandist
He's not
Anyway
In April 2001 dr. Carlos Figueroa prepared a report for the US Department of energy and title
Left-wing extremism the current
Threat
This report in many ways
Is pretty similar to
Is Viagra for
A lot of terrorists on the left
For communist
Which may be a cure
I'm not sure but in no way implies that this report is
You are a terrorist if you're coming
Have communist Lena
That doesn't mean that they're saying Communists are terrorists
Anything like that
Very similar to the microphone.
I'm anyways
Exhaust
I wonder why
The report
The threat to the United States government from leftist extremist
Chris considerably in the past decade but it is not just a
It goes on to say that quote
The challenge the law enforcement
Insecurity is not to interfere with the rights of individuals
To express their beliefs
While also providing a means
For the early identification
Extremists were playing criminal action
Which is the underlying point
Of all the quote-unquote
Patriot demonizing document
Did Alex yells about all the time
The same thing
One of the things I found particularly interests
Secular reports out information from a study conducted by
Published in the State University of New York Press
Call terrorism in America
In the studies Smith looked at
378 members of identify
And compare the demographics
For those in right-wing groups
And blessed with
He found that members of right-wing groups were 97% male
Members of right-wing groups
Percent White
Compared to 29% in Blackwing
36% of the members of right-wing groups are over the age of 40 at the post 8
18% over the age of 40 and left-wing
12% of the members of right-wing groups
Compare 250
4%
But the numbers are different enough to be in
Women
Only
24 Terrors for every 76 terrorists
I think there is scrap in ism
You're a terrorist JW
So also in October 2014
Department of Homeland Security
Keep 7220
It's very clear that
You know from the data it prison
Mostly what you find
Is there's a s*** ton
Of left-wing terrorism
I'm in the 70s
And that shifts hard towards right-wing terrorism
From that point on
In the eighties and nineties
Abortion active
The report
Where the number one category of Terror
United States
Comprising six
Percent of a taxon
Percent of 1/9
Throughout that entire time to dhf does make a note the groups like
The animal Liberation Front
Earth Liberation Front were very active
What are the 24 years of the ALS was active at that point
Their attacks have killed no one
And the same is true of the earth liberation
Over that same time. You saw
Involving
Republic
Confront
And the World Church
The Creator
At the same time the numbers of left-wing into
You see these patterns vary
The point is that the government and the researchers in these organizations
Don't ignore left-wing terrorism
They deal with the reality
But there's plenty of left-wing terrorism to discuss
And simultaneously there's even more right-wing terrorism to discuss
If anyone's ignoring anything
Is Alex and his right-wing elk ignoring
They cover all this stuff in order to maintain the illusion that the out-of-control government is targeting conservative
In preparation
Put them in camps
Or some s*** like that
That's all it's all bulshit
There's plenty of reports you can find
About left-wing terrorist about the FBI planting agents with inside
Inside left-wing
Including recently in
How many different place
In Charlottesville
Jensen there in so many different places
Is in the 60s
The main reason that they killed f****** Fred Hampton
Was because there was an informant inside of the Black Panthers
Targeting them
Specifically
And ignoring me
Terrorist groups
Informant
Provocateur
4minute like
Elohim City
You know
And the 90s
I do understand why there would be an informant in the Black Panthers
Know for sure but that's different
The reality of the situation
Today's the day
Best example of BFDI literally
Cleansing agents
Inside the protest
In order to incite
In order to
Credit
You know that as it may we got
Just bogus nonsense coming up here we go
About how
The left is
Free to roam and no one targets them or anything like that
You should kill tax
Collectors
And
Also saying that right-wing terrorist is almost
Are you sure he doesn't he does
Is very cagey about not revealing
Narrative
President Barack Obama
I think first about the first part of it is pretty
The second part is awesome and it's another one of these scandals
But I completely forgot it's level I forgot about this one
She didn't get a rescue dog
The space is right I remember that we we forgot people that about that
Black president strongly in favor of absolutely
To think that when celebrities
Pepsi
Stuff like that
Ism's
To make of the president not getting a shower
In 2009 President Obama adopted America's first
What was the Portuguese water first. You've never had a dog before
Doc's was the first cat
Grateful
Democrat president introduces animals Into the Wild
All things can
The scandals that we all still remembers being a stain on the presidency
Barack Obama
After saying
Absolutely 100%
Only accept a rescue dog
Except that isn't true at all
In a press conference
We have two criteria that have to be reconciled
One is that Malia is allergic so it has to be hypoallergenic
Their number breeds that are hyper hypo allergenic
On the other hand our preference would be to get a shelter dog but obviously a lot of shelter dogs are mutts like me
So we're going to be
Is a pressing issue on the Obama household
So actually
Alex's other
Which is
Going to get a shelter dog or rescue dogs
But the requirements they were working with
By April the narrow down the dog hunt
Dog
Ultimately they didn't find that dog
Bye
One of the littermates of the dog owned by Senator Ted
Exactly
So he bought it for them as a
Lobo the dog is also what's known as
A second chance
Meaning of its first owner had
Witcher something
Carry a little bit of a stigma
Obama never claimed that this made it a rescue dog but guess who did
Caesar f****** Milan did
The Dog Whisperer
He said it was a rescue dog
Even for sale
The chief executive of the Humane Society called Bowie quote
Criticized for their decision
Long story short there's no Scandal here
I hate I hate I hate him I hate him
F*** you
Anybody who talks
Started the goddamn office
Breckenridge
You didn't get a rescue dog
She's not allowed
He's on the up
He's on the up-and-up on pets
So I'm okay with it
God oh my God
Alex
Black is the color of your skin
It doesn't matter if you're 1%
But you're scared
Treat you right
Different conversations
Intentionally blank
Going to want to do what Alice
What's doing it
I just never like to hear anybody
Give like
Racial
And stuff like that cuz, from a good play never come from
Good faith or like
Saying something
It's always exclusionary
That sucks
Stories of a A-10 probably still going on right now actually almost certainly still going on right now
Summary of mixed-race is both
Excluded from the
Skin color
Community
And also
Excluded from
Side of their
Heritage simply
Cuz their skin
Like that is something
Massive
It's all about perception
Right
Gas
He's got a gas and we met this guy in endgame
The Obama Deception
Columns in newspapers been a newspaper work for almost 50 years
Price for American Free Press he is the original guy
Began writing about the Bilderberg Group
Necessarily covered in
Obama Deception stuff alright in the end GameStop
And it's good for a refresher
How about that
Because he works for American
Yeah your name like American free press all those things are
Things about sports
Love man how come you begin something with American
Or is the press
That's great
Hoverboards are awesome
Also
Intentionally trick people
Thinking stuff like what I was just saying
For prosperity
Outlet
Anyone associated with it deserves a fair amount of Suspicion
The American free press was set up by Willis carto noted anti-semite in white supremacist
In 2001 a
Previous publication
The spotlight
Was forced into bank
They were sued by The Institute for historical review
Holocaust denial is Publix
Which was also founded by Willis carto
I'm falling out of the good grace
So he co-founded this organization and by this point in time
He's not doing great
Call The Americans
American free
Press
Minorities into small bits
Ciara
The Institute for historical review successfully sued Willis carto for just
$6
Because he embezzled
Of Gene Addison Ferrell the grandniece of Thomas Edison
Who was herself
A really big anti-semite
Also about Thomas Edison
Not a cool guy tired of guy back in the day and then fired in the next day cuz he found out he was Jewish
Also
News for starting World War
But he's also an anti-semite
And great-niece
WhatsApp
Wasn't
A Hungarian
Newton
So we'll take his his ouster from ihr very well and it one point
Occupation of their headquarters to try and remain
In control
Dollars and then occupy the business that is
Suing you
Perfectly
I'm not actually sure if that occupation was before the lawsuit or after but it doesn't really matter in my eyes
Bankrupted in the continuation of this case from 1996
Diverted funds
Himself
Where you had to declare bankruptcy
And the spotlight ended up having to fold
Because we lost our toes and both of
The grip
He immediately started up American Free Press
And most
The people involved in the spotlight just started working
It's kind of just a Rebrand
You know it
It's good that he knew to stay in his Lane
Except
Also
Glad you check
The most influential American anti-semitic propaganda
The past 50 years
Listen to set up in public
About the spotlight
Repressed as instruments to turn the public sentiment
Badl put that quote mobilizer again
The Jewish population
Didn't have a sports
Medic political Jack rag
With cargo there's no gray area
He did what he did to Swindle money from organizations and to attack the
The Jews who he saw as the biggest threat to the world
He literally said quote
If Peyton himself with all of his superhuman genius and diabolical Ingenuity at his command had tried to create a
Permanent disintegration
Force for the destruction of
He could have done no better than to invent the Jews
Just blunt
That is Harsh
Directions to Alex's intellectual
68 presidential campaign
Running gear and be used for George Wallace
National Youth Alliance
National Alliance was a hotbed of neo-nazis and white supremacist
With many of their leading figures being members of a pseudo secret society called The Francis Parker
Society
The group was named after the sky jockey
In American Nazi who collaborated with the American Bund during World War II
Create a Resurgence of fascism
Particularly after Hitler was defeated literally the Hitler
Yep
In 1960 after being caught
Was falsified passport
This yucky guy
He was visited by you guessed it Willis carto
Who was
Philosophy
He probably wasn't related but yucky killed himself by ingesting cyanide a weekly
For him
Carter recruiting
Interesting Lee Pierce would go on to write the Turner Diaries
Which is
Largely thought of his white supremacist militia Bible
Just took over the National Youth Alliance and rebranded it as National Alliance
Which is one of the most
The virulent white nationalist organization Republic operations during the 90s and early
It's still in existence now
Barely diminished
Pathic
Sucked up in Port
Of the Neo-Nazi white supremacist time
During that
Re-emerge
In the 90s
Sew-in adult races back
Willis carto MD
The George Wallace campaign
F****** come from
Another interesting parallel carto is one of the
People who helped launch the populist party
Best known for
David Duke
President
Where is the populist party was just some of the staff that the more Mainline
Conservatives were at the time
They were notable for their stances about
Repealing the federal income tax
Abolishing the Federal Reserve and cracking down super hard on immigration
All things about all the time
And Alex was like 13-14 when they were coming out as a political entity
Right around with Alex claims he had his Clarity moment reading none dare call it conspiracy
Written by Gary Allan who worked for the Wallace campaign
Right alongside Willis cardo
Oh and also Carter was a huge fan of Ron Paul
And you know what that's Avengers of
Is what we're talking about
They came together there was one great where everybody got their little viewpoint on that
The end of it
It turned into a movie that way
It could be
My point here is that there's a lot of really bad connections that you can see really easily
Both literal connection
People
And
But cheaply here
Is it Willis carto is a flagrant anti-semite Nazi sympathizer white supremacy
Is publication
We're set up
Literally in
Explicitly
To further those worlds
Hey Jim Tucker was the editor of the
Spotlight
Eddie came along to American Free Press
Ricardo declare bankruptcy
Complicit
Do you know what kind of Outlet he was working
Presented as some kind of an expert
Instead of an anti-semite
Guesting on Alex Joe
There is one thing that he really was
The Bilderberg Group
Really like
Curling sport
Really want there to be
There's so many other like only
White
Mostly
His Sports there's so much other stuff I'd really like to get in
But I'm not really sure how much
The patio
Buchanan stuff
The spotlight
Buchanan
And look like
There's some of those connections
One of the problems we don't have
Audio of Alex
Times that those
Be relevant
I almost
Guaranteed
Yeah I have no idea
Soccersuck
And this is the only Charming moment they had just gone back
Commercial break
The Jim Tucker speech
Is a little bit
Labored
Couple weeks ago
That's pretty good
Pretty good now unfortunately
He starts talking about how cigarettes are overpriced
And you might move to Chicago now you might get your first indication
The turkeys in Congress
Cigarettes
Texas pop 62 cents a pack
Jerking food off the table for the starving Nicholas
Carton
Egypt $70 a carton
That came out of his mouth
Cigarette taxes
On behalf of the black youth
I don't want much but that was just
Oh boy
Text Cliff Alex
Jim still there but he's talking about how he hasn't plugged
He wants to plug
And the reason that he's parking is
Is because he knows that there's go
Tons and tons of a good marketing opportunity
I just want to salute
And thank everyone
That has got The Obama Deception I would encourage those of you
To please get it infowars.com secure online video on bookstore
Wants to
Universities and other groups
I love students are going on in
Everywhere Obama goes to speak for getting out thousands of these and the tea party's tokens are trying to call off
Patriots true Patriots
We're going out to these events and and
Party
The full scope of the New World Order
Wards.com
He conceived
It's basically where you seen all along
Dum dum conservatives
Drive to co-op
This Tea Party
The real one show Patriot
Getting me a ton more fan
Give me a ton more
And then we will swing this thing
And for him that like for normal business
Cuz you be like this is a bad B
But in reality for him it's a brilliant business
Because everybody that buying his is going to give it to somebody
Who does not have it
The definition of like
Market saturation
Places
The corners of
Population
People who probably will never
Yourself answer you take a little bit of a bath because everybody
Is
Or whatever watching it on you are saying they're buying it also
You have potential you only
Exactly
That is better than
Tucker's are in the talking about Bilderberg
I mean to his credit bilderbergers like a month
He knows where it is
He does get the place right
It's in Greece
About 14 miles away from me
And the date
Get those right
Super vague about what the
It's going to be about
They're going to celebrate the financial crisis
Does inaccurate
Cuz you know
The best place to celebrate the financial crisis
The place hit hard
Like I don't
Pretend to know where you got the info
From or even if it was publicly known
Whiter than I understand it's possible I don't know
Date
But doesn't that doesn't
Cuz everything else is off
But would you say that don't impress me much by Shania Twain reference
Yeah
We find out something
Very big
Sponsor
Because I've used this project
Nano silver
The smaller the particle
And the oldest antibiotics is a lot of great silver products out there
Rochester Road
Other things like that
Put silver on it
Even though
Michelle
Again
What is silver solution silver is one of the oldest
Natural antibiotics
Super Silver
Supernatural silver.com
So that's it Supernatural silver is the name of the
Homeopathic
Supernatural silver
From everything I can tell this
The first instance of selling silver based product
Which is
Source for colloidal silver
Interesting Lee natural silver is
Actual legit company
At least.
Really be able to prove something is a comp
Write their website list
The PO Box in Huntsville Utah is their address
Leave the date wood
Be filed as a business
With the state of Utah
If
You search the Utah business Reggie
Website
No company called Supernatural silver on file
Even included businesses who
Filings of expire
It would take
The company is incorporated in
And a different state
But if not
If you search the site in the way back
Supernatural silver.com
You can find our terms of service
From like 2010 2011
Operated
Earthcam.com
Call very weird nothing
They're customer-facing
Keep that big of a company
Princeton I found her Twitter and they only have
Follower
Since August
Are they okay their website is
It's just a bunch of
Product like a list of products you can buy that takes you to a check out
It's super minimal
Going this far through it as like well
I don't know I've been able to establish that based on the
Terms of service page from
You can get on the Wayback machine
They are calling themselves Supernatural silver
That's the business name as described there
That isn't
Utah.gov registry
A business
But
There's one place left
Look for info
They claim that Supernatural silver is copyright
They own the copyright
So if that's the case then there's a file
When the government patent
Copyright office
Serena search on that and found at Fountain
And this is where things get a little bit
The copyright is lapsed now
So it's wide open if you have a cell phone
Second
The actual name of the business is silver Panacea LLC
They don't have a doing business as name on sale for Supernatural which is what they're presenting as the business
I'm not sure if that the illegal in Utah as it is in Texas
When we looked into the on Spotify
I don't know about Utah's laws I'm going to leave that one up in the air
However
Because we can now find the business in
Information about
We can find out more about it
Like the fact that so they filed o l l
Paperwork on March 11th 2009
They claim in their copyright application
The first-time business
Was April 9th 2009 a mere five days before the episode that we're listening
To which is not
The business
The business tracking site buzzfile sites an estimate
Silver panaseeda brings in about 7
$3,000 annually
Companies
Pretty accurate
Manta another business in
Information Tracking site
The same annual revenue
If these estimates are accurate that you're the minuscule business that haven't even been operating a week
Somehow being able to afford advertising on the show has been at least competitive at that time
Which seems legitimately impossible
None of this makes sense
Well what you got to understand is that it's really just
Who was the
I should have said person you're right
Because they're advertising
So it's just one woman who
Was
Gift in a bunch of silver
Like a lot of silver
Silver has really have any overhead other than mailing
Could you
Instagram
Suspicious of the sponsorship button
Places to fish
It's entirely possible that the person who started this business
Independently
Sponsorship
Hoping for a big return
Eminem keep my eyes on this one and let you know what comes up if it turns out that it
Really dumb financial investments
I'm ready to accept that possibility seems like a good place to do that
Aldo and the on the other hand
The Church of Jesus Christ
The third book
Does explicitly say that if you are do you know
If you are doing business in a different name you do have
Something is up there I don't know what it is
Interested
And I'm going to keep looking into it see what I can find
But for now
It's either to someone who's like throwing money away
Or houses rates might be
Nothing
You know he might be
That some business literally just started
All that
I mean like if they're making
Jamaican 70s
$3,000
Still in operation
What were the
What would you do
Tweet if you were out of jail Florida had seven.
Buy silver
At this point
Clipset almost
To believe what you hear
Jim Tucker proves that he works for the Willis carto
And what
Clarence Thomas
Call Dorothea
Liberals Barb opposing
Euphemism for
Call Rachel
Alright
Well
Convinced that a ton of time
I'm sure that's a hard r n word
I'm convinced
You fear the r in there
There's no way it was just what he said earlier about the cigarette tax
That came out of his mouth so f****** easy he knows he's on the radio
You just called Clarence Thomas the n word
How crazy is that
I guess
You didn't have five second delay
Didn't have a five-second delay you didn't have anybody on the board going
Dusty
Conveniently dropped
I
I'm not going to play it again but you guys can go back and listen to
Want to if you want to try it
Do yourself Darin words
I miss the forest for the trees
No no I'm going to go with that super races either way
Agrees with you more than anybody else
Even
Thomas
He's still against affirmative action
And that's great that's the most
He's one of the good ones that you could ever hear
You know what I would racist we say that he was articulate
Literally never ask a question in open hearing
Jesus
Right I've never heard that
I've listened to
Hundreds and hundreds of hours of Alex's show
I've never heard of gas soaked
I've never heard anyone say. Call Michelle
Boy
Really threw that one out there
Unbothered
Alex
The casualness with which you use that word we want to thank you for being here you're a great Patriot
Good thank you for your 50 years of service
And finally dropping the n-word on my show because I've been a long time cuz
Lucky
Well I don't know
His book
I'm not going to let them talk without guidance
Alex
Looks up to him
They got to go together the Bilderberg sometime to Bullhorn and chips
Pitbull session
Jim Tucker is clearly a guy likes his booze
He was but he insisted on being interviewed in the bar in endgame
Quite a bit
Together
Knowledge of each other and whatever
But I do know that Jim Tucker thought it was cool to say the n-word on Alex's show
Slowpoke
Alex has done nothing in the time that they've known each other
To make it clear to gym
They don't fly here
That are appropriate
It's a Batman I didn't know what to do with that
Look I'm a racist on my show all the time
I want you to be a racist on my show
All the time
But we can't do that cuz then people would
I know you're 70
But come on
We got to use cold baby what are you
So
Alex
Jim off the show
We got to set up a time
Grease the week
Can do an interview and stuff like that
They doing on a meeting on air
Space
Did you know they changed up from Gregorian calendar because I'm going down
Valle Vista Festus looking motherfukers running around
Yikes
I don't know
I get them off the air
This is why I had to
To make kind of a
Is because it's soon if Jim gets off the air
Alex realizes what's been done
Just said the n-word on
On the show
Pretend
He said a different word
And he's got a spinach
The way he does it
He's not good
You know one of my pet peeves
Is people not knowing what words mean in semantics cuz I know
Robin page count on BBC reporter
Community service same rights as homosexuals Muslims he was arrested
5 years ago
The word homosexual is
Now heterosexual homosexual
Does his assignment
For your sexual preference
That's the same thing with Anglo negro
And I was watching a documentary about the fifties and sixties Civil Rights Movement
When developers called
And they all freak out
So that's the reason I needed to make a point of it
Because
No no I think what Alex is trying to present is that that's the word
The gym set
It is not if you are I looked at so many times
Just to
Make it clear Justified some
Justify to myself but like
Your version of it is totally correct whatever word you use
There was Rachel intent in it is not good
Bye
Because of Alex's
Response to it
Words and semantics
Not the word
He said
Feel bad no matter what
But he did say that Alex
Just trying to get the fence
There are tapes
Oh man 5 second delay Alex a later on
Delay with us
That one f******
Christ
Even if that guy says African American
You're saying the n-word real hard
Yeah it's a homosexual is not a
Bad word
But out of your f****** mouth it's a bad word
So anyway that was really crazy
And like
I did
And writing up on
Do you like American
Free Press
This dude was there
People are
So
Who's calling
And
I don't know how it happened but I've got
I got
Hepatitis C
You got hepatitis
He's like I got him at all the places that
Apartments
What have you I don't know I got it somehow
Should I take my medication
I don't want to hear the answer that question
I'm worried
The government is trying to
Give me things
With my hepatitis
Until Alex starts talking about first doctor I can get medical advice
And he starts talking about
We've gone from one patient 2004
Leprosy
The 7000 in 2005/2006 next year
From where
I mean
Hepatitis everything's off-the-charts
Fast food
That doesn't sound right
Spray Farms
World food
I don't care about that
According to a 2014 report from the centers for
Diagnose
United States
That's it
Not
Talking about things that get brought in
That's over things that number cat
Are you just making s*** up that's not that's not what I think and I think
Trying to save there is that
There were no cases
Then there was one case then there were 7,000 cases and then there were no case
So I think his point that he's trying to make
And then
I don't think
Supposed to raise suspicion
I think it's that
They're bringing it in
Is a third-world and stuff like that
Supposed to
Supposed to Anchor Inn
Leprosy
Or whatever
Global
He was talking about
Like let's say that 7,000 number is accurate for the entire world
That one number is
From the year before
You can be using consist
Numbers
Make a call
The only way
Presenting
Is either
Cheating big-time Oregon
Just making it up
It sounds to me like a
A little bit like Obama's dog isn't a rescue as their Scandal for immigration like instead of there
We're going to rape everyone you know
Or we just might get a little bit of leprosy that's not too bad
Depends on if you're the first
You win some you lose some music
So now we're
We get to the bad part of Alex's
Responsible
I said
Because here
The end
His response
Say something
Super
Just finish up a question
Interferon
Drugs that supposedly treatment for HIV
I was talked to chip in Michigan
Just say that you don't just ask what else
A lot of doctors is not enough doctors
You don't get to start your answer by saying I'm not a doctor I can't
Give medical advice
And then
Answer with
A lot of doctor is a lot of experts a lot of people say medication
Just make you worse
But whatever
But whatever at the end
Particularly
Because it's supposed to
Implied dismissal of his own argument in order to highlight
Take your medication
Yeah that's
Absolutely
Not to take
There there medication
Medical advice
Medical advice is if you take your HIV Medical
You will die
Pepsi but yeah
Could get that naked
They have Maids
Chronic condition
Horrible side effects
Conditions
Also
Horrible sinus
And just trying to make profit
Out of the ideas at like
There's a small /
Percentage of people who will have
Herobrine
Reaction
Therefore no one should
To take those it's so bad
You cannot fight back
Put the Second Amendment right
Straight up
If you read between the lines of what
This is f***** up that's a really interesting really interesting argument I would say for free
Do you know what I'm saying
Literally leads to the death of a person
And that
Purely because they believed what you said that's a really fascinating question
Yeah I know I don't actually know what to do
I don't know what like
What would somebody have to die or would just Grievous bodily
I would say I hope
You know
First of all I'm never the person who asked
Besides those right
I hope that you have a court will everyone expected tomorrow
I mean
If you're like a family member of like let's say this guide stops
Medication
This as an example
Write his family members
Literally
There's a lot of people take your meds are worse for you than your
How your condition
I don't know I don't know if that makes him culpable forgiven
I don't know it dangerous it's super dangerous
You know
Although I don't know
You're making
Is fine but the
Consequences
Threatening somebody shut the words
That are the problem
Yeah it I don't know it's complicated
Anyway
Yeah it's just another call from a guy
This guy
Going to the Orlando Tea Party
Yes
I guess with the tea parties are going on
There's definitely there's going to be a big one here in Orlando tomorrow
Mueller Park
About 6,000 people but we do have
A group of about 20 people a couple of bulls horns or going to go down there tomorrow we have
Crushers
You give out with your Obama Deception in
Call Connor Brothers stuff
Maybe you know this is the first time you're hearing this and you don't know where to go to
You can go to www.meetup.com backslash
Orlando 9/11 truth we do a lot of stuff
Last thing I'll let you go on somebody got to love to do
What are we going to have a special celebrity endorsement tomorrow we got to
VyStar Barack Obama
We're taking to the rally with us
What does speech bubble that says
Administration
Same agenda
One World Government
So that's not too bad
We live in 2019
50 parties
Moving forward from here
So and I'm not saying that
This guy in anyway
Facilitated
Really
Inspirational
Poopy sign
It's just enter
Send it before this
Tax day
Largest
Number of
Tea parties around the country
Was there any sort of
More innocent
That would turn
Super dark pretty quick
I think it's a function of the fact that at this point
I don't think that the Tea Party
At least
Before text
There was a focus that seems mostly on
Being against taxes
It makes sense
This guy would bring it
A big Obama cutout
They just be like
These new world order whatever you like
You know what hanging dolls of Obama
Western
12:00
New admitted
Same agenda
But then we were listening to your show earlier and Bill Tucker
Got to go in that Sprite
Call
They don't have a five-second delay but they do have a call screener it's
This point in time
Come on
You can't pretend you didn't hear it when you rushed him off the phone like that respond
Listen all you dumb dumb
He said different work
Fukkk offf yeah yeah if he had defended it
There would definitely have been more of a
They supposed to him like jumping into being like
People are going to get that for me and terms
Jim
But there would be
Like a bit of
Plausible deniability and what Alex heard
If he hadn't
Rhetoric
Bring up that word
It's not like Alex responded and needed to be like
You didn't respond
He heard f***
Hard r n word
He's like I got I got to save this
So
They either accept
Whatever his version
None of it was or they
Right
And every show
Is this going to be the show
Where we finally get the n-word
Today is
You f****** red-letter day
And that red letter is a hard r
Jesus I don't mean to say this is
The compliment
Rolled with it
Amazingly well like
Negative way
He seemed unfazed absolutely -
AJ
The great to have you on the show plugged
Soon as he got off the phone
Seems like
That isn't something
Could happen
I legitimately can't think of any situation where a friend of mine
Would just suddenly drop that word not be like
Observational only have one more
On this side episode
We're going over here on the 14th
And
If it's an interesting thing that goes on
That for most of the show Alex's
Using the gas
Cities going to have on
Answers guy did he only identifies as
Cantina
And that Economist is
Lionel Messi
Okay might be as much of an account this message but like
Soccer player of all time
Have you seen the
So this dude
Is like having phone troubles
Push back a bit
Six more calls
Boring
It doesn't really matter but a timely Alex gets
Argentinian
Converses
Federer at the US Open
Operative
In Argentina
He doesn't actually get him on the phone and I'm not going
Give him the courtesy of
You playing anything
Because it's just
To talk and whatever
Of course
Spell bougie
He is at these economist's
Discuss the hardships
Economy
However failed to point out that sell Bucci is an ultra-nationalist in part of a group called project
Second Republic
Pendants to Argentina
New Independence
You might ask
I think you already know
The Jews
Balducci and his group believed in a conspiracy known as the Antonia plan
Which plants
Regarding Jewish emigration to South America in the late 19th century
Early 20th century
An exaggerated them
H-E-B in Jewish playing
Take over Argentina and establish a second
Jewish state
The theory of Argentinian Neo-Nazi propaganda for decade
The new style Boutique
Announcement
2014 by the delegation of Argentine Israelite at those
Which shouldn't be surprising
Considering that he
Make a habit of
Being interviewed by Holocaust
Deniers
Like this guy James Fetzer who got interviewed by who once wrote quote
My research on the Holocaust narrative suggests it's not only
But probably
False
YouTube video on his own channel
Entitled
The truth about the protocols of the stages of Zion
Which unsurprisingly was not a debunked
I don't know
All of this
But
It kind of concerns me that anti-semitism
Flourishes in a place where I
May be incorrect
In assuming this
But I feel like there are not a ton of Jews living in Argent
There were a number of
There was
South America was attractive
Number of
Pics of that necessarily but there are there are some
Down there
The Boys from Brazil in South America
Dim sum in sum
Hyper Nash
Situations
And so this guy
Is that that's that
Flavor
He's not an economist who wants to talk about
Alex's
Supposed
The conception of them
Coming in in
Economic takeover and what-have-you
He wants
You do believe
Create another Israel's are you like you can't be
Considered an economist if
Part of the basis of your worldview of
Economy is
First we got to kick out the Jews
That part of the Chicago Austrian
I'm pretty sure it is part of the ostrich
Was Abigail Adams
I think he was more
Just about being a dick
And
I don't know if I would call him a Neo-Nazi
He has a lot of leaning
Some sympathy
He's an absolutely
Somatic
He's brought to the world
So
The idea that I was having
A little bit of credit on the
And that is I don't
Because he has I don't think he has any
Earlier
Argentina
Like I think
During the episode
Teasing it a bunch
I think it's good he didn't remember his name
Yeah
Because he hasn't done any
Research
Mike that he allows someone who
Right to come onto his show and
I think in retrospect Alex would call that a happy
Accident not mistaken Reese
No problem
Probably
But you know what the problem is due there it's the monster
Furtive of how like
You can have somebody who is
Look the protocols of the elders
Zion
Come in and take over Arjun
Make another is real gear
Blah blah blah
You can have that
You can have the editor of Willis carto
Somatic Publications
Come on the show
You can have them all make argument
Consider
Like
That says something
It really does say something
That red flags
The pop up for Alex
Maybe I'm hanging out with bad people
That's not good
The show not good
Where were people
That's a really frustrating
That's really frustrating
It really does seem like you can't go anywhere without somebody eventually being like
The Jews are trying to take over
A lot of places
Soviet Bloc
Currently have
History
South America
There's plenty of country
Have much less
Historical
Tendrils
Like I don't know I would hope Australia
Absolutely.
No not even close
They're so far away
Kind of hoping they missed that one took a knee
That lets me charge it was like
Dude I wish we took a knee on a
I don't know
This is Bernard
Episode
2009 little bit of a shorter episode but
Edwards on this episode
Episode
I would say we jammed packed a lot into a very short. Of time
WhatsApp
Hey do we have a drink
Website
What about a Facebook okay where could you find
Options there
Oh yeah you can do a bunch of different apps do you know what I've been using for my podcast
What's up I like it
Called overcast
I like ensure that
Snowman
Jim Tucker hasn't
Murdered
That's that's
I don't know man I think he probably hasn't
I got a Vibe on him
He just seems like a
The guy who sits at at
Typewriter
Big old glass
Yeah that sounds right
Some Jews
One guy technically
Probably has
Gildedguy
That guy's Alex
Alex