Alex
Alex Jones
All Things Considered
Do you think that
The Dirty South
Or the Midwest was a better place
For hip hop
In the late
All Things Considered
Northern Midwest
Hip Hop
Murphy Lee
When I was growing up in Missouri
Until like 5,000
You might be right
It wasn't until the early
Nelly Murphy Lee
Alright
All the time
Shoutout Justin policy
Your policy
I'm a policy wonk
Text Taylor
You are a policy
Coming out coming in heart coming in hot
At the regular pulse
I'm a policy wonk
Yes we are
Okay when are you guys going to stop f****** around and do the show as well as we could have given the
I would remember
Turtle eyes
Actually kind of scary probably trip
Rattle off exactly how are opening. Surely not the other guy who does
Right right right
But I have no idea what you're saying
Alright
Episode
You came up with an idea
Frankly
It's a weird feeling
I don't know
I don't know we'll see
Take risks
I don't know if you or any of our listeners know this
It's fake news of those things that I think about alot
I have brought something and you need to play the out of
Contacts drop getting cooler
How do you take that to mean he's asking
Did Mars
Spuds MacKenzie
Okay
I just like a house
Mark Moreno
With Pat Robertson do you know who Mark arenas
I mean
Head editor in
Pretty much only writer in the only guy who really runs climates depot.com
Okay he is 18
I think so for sure
This guy is for me different from usual
Cast of
Because this guy
Is a complete sleazeball
Like this point
They're all shooting up for themselves
They're all trying to run their own scam
Right
This dude
Is gun for hire
All the way this guy does not believe a goddamn word
He has found his little niche
He gets shipped tons of money for it and he's sucking
The politically incorrect guide to climate change
And
Genuinely
Should not get an author credit
On the book that he wrote
Because he write this here's a example of his book
Long quote
And that proves
What this guy said long quote
Long quotes
That's it
He's more of a compiler a quote minor of the worst variety
And
Has given an interview with Pat Robertson
Haha haha
Cuz I know for a fact
Look into Pat Robertson side of his interview at all I don't give a f*** about what he
He has to say I hate Mark Moreno
So that is how you into this first clip
Said something
Miami is actually thinking
Subsided
But there's no acceleration in the global sea level
So you cannot
Mankind is always battling
The shores
Sea levels Rising for 10,000
1 + years
The end of the last ice age
Man has always been battling the shore
I don't like the context but I like it
Man is always in bed
Right
Do you think what he said makes any sense
No
I mean sure
Together a sentences yes but I don't I don't know I don't know if it's
Thesis
The man isn't doing anything
Climate change actually connect to each other
Miami is sinking and there's no acceleration of global sea levels
That doesn't make sense
Is it thinking really
Is that what you would call it
No okay
Miami is what you think Miami
Being overwhelmed
You have to go down
It's a problem just off the bat
Could you like
Visual metaphor
Norse Viking stabbing a rock
Hitting a beach with the shore
Sword fight
How do you think man has been battling
Alright so we do believe in Anthem
Is
Content and everything I don't even know
What do you mean man has been battling the
Sure
Damn premiums to say is that
We've been fighting
Rising water
Ferrari Tire
Time on Earth
Articulate I don't know if that's true
Miami is nothing
I will tell you this right now is actually
Utterly destroyed
So the reason is Miami is built almost entirely online
And that's where they get their freshwater
It's called the Biscayne aquifer
This kind of filters water and keeps water fresh
As DC water rises
That kit
Covered by salt water
So salt water is seeping into the drinking
The estimate of
The estimate from the NOAA
Arise about a foot of seawater will
Pretty much and drinking water in
Syncable no that's not
Prior to a NASA in 2018
Everybody thought that the regular rise of
The sea level was going to be linear
Is going to be a steady gradual
In 2018 a
NASA study by Steve marim
Started referencing different satellite data
Cross-referencing it with all kinds of other different measurement techniques exactly how fast
Rising since the 1990s
And I
It is not
Progressing Italy
It is increasing by about 6%
Every single
It's almost exponentially
What is a geometric progression not a linear
I am very very unhappy with everybody because
They're still operating under so much of that like
In 100 years by 2100 it will risen by a foot
You hear that from people with
Weird funders
The 8-year being alarmist for Comfort people
Who has links to the fossil fuels and tobacco lobbying interest a few of those characters
Do we get back to Miami for a second makes it worse if Miami
Ruins
LivWell
Catch Rainwater
A very reputable Source I've heard that in my hand
You can't see a drip on the strip it's a trip
It does not rain in Miami but on the plus side
There's
Yelling about how they loved your last
I'm disappointed that you're not still going
Boy
Okay
And I would say even according to Narrows own quote
That is a conservative estimate that increase of about 6
6% each year
It is risen from what they thought the estimate would be about 2.5 ml per year
Now it's looking like it's going to rise by about
3.4 mm
Puryear
As we continue along
That's conservit
Basically in about 25 years
If the conservative
Sea level will have risen by about half a
Not good
So that means that in less time than at sea level risen by a foot
And Miami Miami will be unlivable
So no more women who are half
Nope
Wilton
They will be able to buy
But everybody lives there
Miami's going to go
Now that we know that my everything
We talked about
Who is trying to
The environmental movement
Solve this problem
Do you know who owns the environmental movement down
George Soros George Soros
But who did he take it from
Soros
Eco-terrorists all over the place
Get people to stop by and gold
Hate hate
Hate the environmental movement
From the right
Mark Moreno has made it clear that the modern environment
Wizard
Good rounds it Civil Rights era
The modern environmental movement having been started by a guy named Aldo
Was
Dope
You know you know those dudes except for all the siblings didn't die
He was that guy who's like 4 years old
So it's time for me to set out on my own in the forest befriend all the animals
He was top of his class in school
Was top of his class in the next School
And then he decided
To go to Yale
Right
Why did you choose Yale
I don't know
Because the year-earlier that started a forestry program
The thing that he was when he was 4 years old discipline of Forestry
And then he got a job
Working for the forest service
He's out there in the middle
Shooting bears
Bears
Shooting mountain lion
Sometimes.
Got to go sometimes I got to go
That's almost man's best friend
That's true
Correctly decided after spending all of his time among predators
Hunting them
He started being like
F****** dudes are actually pretty cool
I like these Predators more than I like these assholes ranchers telling me to kill
So he starts becoming a conservation
Right now driving absolutely
He's going out in the forest
He's got his
Wilkes-Barre over here he's got a spare
Beautiful
And is
Just
Is the guy
Started
In the 1950s and 60s everybody read when he was on the right
Okay no no no
Before
Conservative and liberal people in both parties
Wings
The idea that someone
Surprise
On the left or the right
Al on the right as we understand it now
Why does Moreno guy think that
Where is the disc
There is
From time to time is that Martin Luther King was a Republican
That's all these guys they were on the right
F****** things up
So here we are at the beginning of the fifties and sixties were in the modern environmental movement
Mark Moreno has done his f****** Reeser
Alright
He knows
What the problem
And he knows what the left thinks the solutions
Other
Environmental scares
Things like resource scarcity we're going to
Famine overpopulation
Scared and I show that those scares all have the same Solutions they're proposing today is a different environmental scare
Same solution in the solutions are
Centralized planning
3 distribution
And
Stop threatening International Organization
Alex
Like maybe those Illusions people suggest cuz they work
That is exactly right
They're very effective at dealing with a broad spectrum of problem
It's our secret literally just
Yep you got it I like knowing
Visual
What what differentiates between the modern environmental movement
The archaic
Environmental
Well if you if he wanted to really be
Play the Teddy Roosevelt
Could have created the modern environmental movement
You could make that argument
But again that is
Not hijacking and that's not the modern Environmental
Exactly
Wasn't a party
Kind of situation
It was
Teddy Roosevelt just like killing s***
Animals
He was all about it
Just describing the actual Solutions
To the problem
Yeah that's what he's doing
And he's doing it in this way of life
I'm making it sound like this is a bad thing
Because all of these scares
Were
I don't know since you think they were unfounded
I think that's what he's trying to convey
No
It just didn't
Solve the issues before they killed everybody
Exactly
We used centralized power and Southern
Measures
Pretty much
What
We're done and what they were trying to do
When they came to the Paris agreement
Bulshit toxic waste
Propaganda
You shouldn't bathe in toxic waste in like medical waste
Should be disposed of in a particular way with regulation
Water supply
Dumb
Globalist
That is
Take that
The Paris agreement of course
Is one of these
Sovereignty
Most definitely for sure they want to steal everybody's
Now do you want to know exactly how expensive it is
FedEx
Yeah
International rates that I don't know how about how expensive
Surprise you
Wood that has been now analyzing its most expense
The treaty in world history
A hundred trillion dollars is the estimated cost
Incredulous Robertson
You're going to hear
Yeah
A little bit
How much
Maybe I don't know
I'm probably like just taking all sorts of
Weird things
Play more the cost of the
But
I think you probably know that it feels weird
Rigo model Will Smith lyrics
Go to Yale the moment they open the You Will Smith
I might go there.
What's that what would that be though the modern Wild Wild West movie
Annual
This 100000000000000 number
From
One guy
Please tell me if Mark Moreno
Nope no other scientist no other
Said anywhere near 100 trillion.
He is not waited on the 100-year long cost of the Paris agreement
Going to cost a hundred trillion dollars
Now
What does
The
What he has described in
Moreno's book as the
The game is statistician
Bjorn lomborg
Does he have a Ph.D
Forestry
I don't know
Okay
Vaguely relevant
What you're looking for
Mountain CD or something like that this close
Taken
Amount he was drawing from what country
Review now released only a little bit of his message for coming up with this hundred trillion
Padam padam
Nobody knows what he plugged into the machine his method was this
The amount people are going to spend on it that I think they're going to spend on it
And I called it to
With no numbers
But that's also likes
The United States government is going to cost
100 trillion dollars 2100
Sure sure
It's deceptive
Director of Fitbit
Technology
Water bill pay
Dividend
Exactly
What method was literally that
Yeah I am just counting that no deductions for
And it's like
It's just like saying that the government cost to trillion dollars a year when it's like
Well that money doesn't go away
Right he's not like given to the Paris agreement and they get to keep
Write this piece of paper is Rich's s***
Is actually going to wind up being
Not just less than 100 trillion dollars but it's going to be
Profitable
Exactly
Ideally
Absolutely
My favorite quote from
Bjorn lomborg
It's from 8
So
First up in the early 2000s
He was like
Climate change is real
We got to do something
And then in the mid-2000s
He decided climate change
Is not real
And that was because of a large amount of money
Weird beard how that'll change
Your perspective is going to be a theme
But
Here's my favorite quote from your mom
He did this interview with CBC Radio in 26
He said
I was going to do Alex's Bernie Sanders
Most people die from cold
Not
And so when temperature is increased
We're going to see about 400,000 more
Because of global warming
You know
You hear a lot about those
But you're probably going to see 1.8 million fewer cold
Pizza now
Old people die of heatstroke all the time
But old people freeze to that too and what you don't hear about is that they freeze to death more often
They'll never freeze to death when the world is warm
Is overflowing kind of guy
Cool
School
Colonel vet
That willingness to look at like
Let's freeze to death guys Isn't that cool
Well it's also not true
Generally not because of the element
Because they can't afford their heating bills
The number of stories about stuff like that unfortunately there are a number of homeless people
Fries on the streets and stuff like that
That's not about
Who is -50 year in if you had a place to be inside it wasn't going to be
The biggest eagle in the world
You won't even have to be inside
That's true all right dealer
Jordan
You're a lot of fun
He is
Goes around
Him saying the dumbest
He does not face the 400,000 number on everything
This is 100% something
Pulled from thin air
He didn't he didn't like later on right apiece justifying the 400,000 number
Or the one in the 1.8 million fewer cold deaths
Didn't even
Figure out how many there are. Think that those terms are very defined
Warm and cold death
Let's people burn that are frozen into ice cube
Global warming is good
Easter egg
Here's the best part though
Not only
Paris Accord is fart
Can't afford
Fiscal responsibility
But here's what's even worse it would even do anything
It's commit Nations until do sovereignty and start
Being essentially
Having to bow to a un International Organization
It would have even if you trusted the UN science and Al Gore believe everything you said
It would have no
Impact on temperatures 100 years
It wouldn't even do any
Toya Wright
Fortunately
What this is referencing what is referencing here is a 2015 MIT
And what they do
Was
BMI 10 put together the study of like
Okay let me check
The Paris Accord
Built on every 5 years
East Country submits a new proposal
The new pledge
So the MIT study
If everybody
Just did right now
For forever
They're only be able to drop in degrees Celsius
So currently
Is that all
Exactly
Is your problem
What the MIT study
False
Was that
Everybody
Involved in this
Is planning on not doing
Is everybody is doing what they can for
For The First Five-Year
Bright and then accelerating
Besides getting in the pool
Exact
I mean you're going to have to eventually
Difficult to totally transition every
Bajorans
Got a dip
That does make sense
If all
What that really proves is the opposite of his
What that really proves is that a mighty was putting together a thing that's saying
Guys this is a
Amazing thing that we do this is a promise
Amongst all nations
To f****** try and survive
And what we need to make sure that you're doing with this five-year proposal
Stop rapping
So the MIT put out the study
Goose everybody into doing
Assholes like Mark Moreno are taking those findings
He's not saying
Here's what we need to do instead
Here's what should be
He just saying
She doesn't believe it
It seems like it would be hard to
Based on
If you've read this you're lying
If you haven't read this
Was one of the two
Like a prior is much more likely
He has red
There is one
Expect
That we need to worry about
And it's one day
Larry Nichols has warned us about
Oh yeah this is no more than medieval which crap people believe
Edina can regulate the temperature
Control store meanest they used to believe that
Are SUVs that are cars
Always witch
Alright
I think that's lame
I mean
Look into a lot of the history of witches and stuff like that
Just completely social
Oppression of women
Like women who didn't adhere to the rules of society
Said that they had to
That is true
They are oppressing
SUVs
That's where you kind of get the sense of life
Do you know if he's talking to Pat Robert
And that is like
Coming up with witches and stuff like that it is really like in that wheel houses
You know you're talking to a zealot a religious zealot
He's going to love to hear this
One who does not understand how big a trillion
Absolute
But
Good news is
That
Nobody
After you hear that information
And all the information before
You can tell that nobody cares
It's too expensive to make a difference and it's just witches
Public Health
Essentially from global warming for the 1980s
Phrasing
Performed
There are you an organization
Aldi's
Which is when he use
Starting his b*******
Course clear regarding climate change
Okay what happened in 2000
Nope Paris courses 2015
Okay
A man named
Sure
And a large amount
Right-wing propaganda
With centered on
Tying him together with
Climate change
Everyone
Everyone was becoming more aware of climate change and everyone across both parties was increasing their concern
Mm2007 however
Fears of climate change.
Klein
Among the right
Only
Everyone every other thing has gone completely up
There is a correlation between the propaganda Blitz
That was put together by
No
I don't know
Inside being seen
Grandmother
Through organizations like
Donors Trust
Koch related
Which doesn't have a great name but
It's it's
I've run into that
Let's go through some of the things that they have fun
The donors Trust
Get up to a lot of bad bad business the 2017
Americans for Prosperity
30962331
Sure
The Heritage Foundation
The Discovery Institute the mercatus center veritas
100%
Freedomworks got about 4 million
These guys are in
And we're going to find out a little bit more about
Respond
Places to hide the source of money
Koch related
And then like
Freedomworks
Americans for Prosperity are also Coke length
Tic-tac-toe
Networks around that way
Exactly
They have
Consistently and they've created all of these things
You early to get that propaganda
To avoid this exact
Money comes from
Because it would delegitimize the
Messaging
Trying to put in the world
Exactly
Dirty submarinos argument eventually comes down to just this
Yes
People have
Mainly because the people who give me money cuz guess who
Give him a lot of
Oh yeah
That is a
Exactly what happened
Shifting
The Republic
Opinion
Therefore you shouldn't care
You got it
That's not good I made people not care
I guess it is sort of like a demonstration that people are kind of gullible I don't know what that helps with
What's the climate argument
It really crashes at
But you know what's even crazier than the fact that the Paris agreement
What cost 100 trillion
And nobody even really cares about internalizing I believe it
It's actually back
The world's going to get cooler
What
Many scientists clean Russian scientist
Are predicting a-coming Cooling
Okay
It's just
Is it coming
Isaac
On the other hand
John Leguizamo did a voice
I do remember that
Commercials were just that character chasing the acorn
And we had a district manager
Whatever
AB 40 years ago it still
Dragovic us excited about Ice Age
I'm excited
Animals of talk
People be chasing down a car
Oh yeah
Friendships
Absolutely
Which is the whole point
Oh absolutely
I'm sorry
Bulshit comes from a few different sources
And let me give you an idea of their occupation
Denis Leary
Predicting a coming Ice Age a book
That sounds pretty legit
A meteorologist
That's almost felt something
Doppler Dave out of Columbia Missouri
It might as well be
It's actually a local guy
Neurologist is like one of those local WeatherBug
The most prominent guy who is
Cool boy this is going to be rough
He was the one who claimed that a mini ice age in 2014
Mini ice age
The trailer for The
I mean it was really cold last
But no
I believe this year is 2018 was the fourth hottest year ever
Record timing outside of one of the most mild Winters that I remember experiencing
Chicago
Like in terms of like the bigger picture but
It is
It is something
The issue here is
All of these guys
I completely forgot to tell you this
You know what's crazy
What's that
He gets his money from
Oh yeah
Sodas in a real Trend here
But you know what
You don't need to worry
You don't need to work
Because nothing unusual happened
Is quite literally hundreds of factors that influence the climate
The right now they're trying to analyze what's going on where to buy some estimates we're at hundred year or more so
Sunspot activity
And many people are predicting a significant drop in temperature
Since the height of the last ocean cycle
700 your Lowe's
You shouldn't be worried about
Emily tell you something
Nothing unusual is happening nothing out of the ordinary
Normal for the sunspot activity to be 100
No everything is happening
Nothing unusual is happening whether it's hurricanes tornadoes
Extreme weather is actually at a stable or declining trend on climograph
Text sounds old
Voices old
Hurricanes come out of
Wrong
The severity of
Extreme weather that we
Over the last
I don't know
Oh yeah
As the Earth is warming
In the past
Lexi between 1958
In 2000
The amount of rain
Falling in the heaviest storm
Has risen by nearly 20% in
In the states
That's from 2007-2
20%
20% rise since then
3 times as much as the rise
Between 1958
So in 11 years
The amount of rain
In the heaviest storms has basically
I understand what you have against water
I don't know
A team of more than 300 different
Experts in various Fields relating to
Measuring
Extreme weather
The Northeast just the Northeast
Has seen a 74% increase
Any amount of rain
In snowfall
Everywhere
New York about those like
Terrible
Blizzard
Does Mark Marino site anything
Wait hold on I just remember that that's Avenue freeze-out by Bruce Springsteen
I'm solo
Snowstorm
Are ghosts real
That means it's always been
Much Ado About Nothing everything is
Everything that he is doing now
Is she has written about in his bulshit book
Right
Do you know who he's site
When he said
When he says in the in the book this is true
No
Clarence Clemons
Intellectual version of self-dealing
Literally
His own website for extreme weather Ceiba
Go to the
Oh hell yeah
Intellectual ethical standards
I'm stopping
He's just rambling off things saying them assertively and calling it
Reality
Easy to trick someone
At Robertson
Robertson
Robertson kids
Here's the craziest
Just like Bruce Springsteen
Proved
Of course that it's always been bad
Scientist
No
That it's always been
And you know what else to do.
Because the Tenth Avenue freeze-out
Is it really about the blizzard storm hadn't
I happened to me Clarence Clemons 1.8 million people are
Not going to freeze this year
EBenefits
I'll tell you one of the biggest things
That he has
Absolutely
Ego
Exactly like
Where it is just
He's he's doing so far here's what he's done
This isn't a problem
It's all a lie
Which I'm not saying this
We couldn't do any
People are trying to do about it
Absolutely
Here's what's even worse
They're making this whole thing up
Scientist
Are making it all up
Yep. 902 1380 this was considered the
Climate Optimum word was Optimum
And we had the Renaissance with all this
Crops and Vineyard growing in England
And then
What time they said we have to get rid us92
Disturbia to get rid of them because we didn't have coal plants and SUVs and was inconvenient to explain how something could be as one
Warm or warmer than today
Does decadence
Earlier he said that witches thought they can control the weather
They just erased the past
Medieval warm.
I'm have heard of it
I've heard those words used before
What do you think is specifically like in the medieval warm.
What do you think
Important word
Exactly maybe that's why it was warm because other which activity
Everybody knows
Morris Greenhouse
Yeah imma write a book
Greenhouse which gas
Is because
When you say medieval
You're describing
Not
Just
400 years from
You're describing 400 years
In a certain
Exactly
He is basically saying
See
In Fort for 400 years
It was really warm for white people
That means the climate is wrong
That's the whole thing
Pages
I don't understand
What are these guys think
Scientist get together and we got to remove the
We got to take it away
Which side
Which science that you answered your own question
It seems like
At least
One scientist to be like
Huh you guys have changed this date
The biggest eagle in the world
Global changes or Pages as they call themselves
Support research
Dad understands
The environment not just
You know now we're or the way it's going on but they try and go back as far as possible
So they taking ice core samples tree-ring sample
Holland stalactites
More stuff to see what the overall climate
If the world was
At that time
It's exactly what we would have expected it
There's no medieval warm.
For the Earth
It's just for your
So what he says
In a certain sense he does
Have it right you know scientist
To correct it
Give it contacts
It's the same rising to temperature that we would have expected this
Because humans were doing
Even back then
Anthropogenic global climate change
Was part of the
The deal approved
Consistency to the data
It proves that there isn't some sort of
Hidden like this is part of the natural fluctuation of
It fits in perfectly with
The rest of the day that we see
He from
Previous
Climate tracking
Right right
Is taking this small little piece
Of one small little part of all the research that has been done
And there
Calling it
Proof that global warming
Proof the climate change
That is what they do
The organization
That has really been touting
That medieval warm period they received
530 $2,000 from donors
Erase that
Firmly establish better
I might
Hammer on this
Hammer.
Two very similar
Walk
Cuz it makes it harder for them to do the business that they do
That is
Come into the donors
Absolute
It is one of these things that I
You already know that all of these guys are pretty much paid
The whole time
You kind of guessed.
I went through the citations in his
Facebook
And I tried to find
Anyone
Who did not receive money from donors trust or Americans for Prosperity or all of those things
There were no sources site
That did not
That any source that he had
Climate change was not real or not an issue or
I should not be attacked or that it's actually sunspots or anything like
All of them
Received money from these organization
All people on the same team
Information
For Sarah
Absolute
But no big deal
Something happening
Pissed everybody
Can't think of what it was
I'm guessing it
Cheeky way you're saying that is it says Obama
Okay the recent president who said global warming was the greatest threat facing civilization
And if it's theirs it's a tragedy that he wasn't pushed back on President Obama for saying that
Greatest threat we face
Hays tractor
Also
On a bracket where I'm sitting at
Quite a bit
Was unable to
Really
Meaningful progress
I have one question about
Scott Robertson
Do you think Pat Robertson forgot Obama's name or literally cannot bring himself to stay over
No he can't do it
It's ridiculous
Absolutely f****** insane
And it's all it's so much of this is directly from
People hating Obama
What's the temperature outside
Working with that
Feel like an incubator in
Green Technology
Stop
Leidsa
It didn't help
These folks
Serta Perfect Storm
Like what happened at that time
Was
Mixture
These right-wing synced
Absolutely like piggybacking on people hating Obama
And throwing in the climate-change stuff
That's why it all happened around 2007
The whole reason that all of the
Climate awareness and all of this stuff
DuckTales
With
Everybody hating Obama is because
Concerted effort
To put the two
Together
To make sure that people
Who like black people in Miami people in Florida
They're going to lose their homes there
Vibes
As The Advocate
Ecstasy levels rise
Parts of Florida will no longer be
Yeah and those people are
Oftentimes
Rite-Way
Yeah because it's not compelling
Narrative you might want to say is like
These people just hated Obama
And that's why
Obama was pushing for an agenda
Yep
Uno
So much of the time on our show it's like fear of a black president
Money bottom-line related
Yeah
It's a bummer
Like it really it's like a lot of that stuff
What are the reasons it's good for you to do an episode
Get
A lot of thought I don't get
I don't think that I could credibly have a conversation about it
But the business side of it and
Very simple to understand
And it should give people reason
To be like
Hold the f*** on
Who are you saying these things
Does that in Subway invalidate
The message that you
That's not to say that from the Koch brothers like that
The fun that doesn't mean that every
Wrong
It just means that when you hear someone saying
The funding
As a business interest in the messages they're putting out
Find out if they're locked
Is it should be like
A call to action
You see that connection you got to double-check thing
Absolutely can't take it
Face value
Oh boy
Like like we said so many times this is all normal nothing's unusual
All the time in history
It's no big deal
Climate is in the history of the Earth right now and probably the 10% coldest. In the Earth
Geologic history
Where we can have ice at both poles Like We Do Not So geologically speaking
How old is the Earth
Roughly younger
You know what's crazy even if that was right
100 100
Voicemail
So if you're going to stay in the entirety of the Earth's history
90% of it has been warmer
So you're talking about
5 billion years
Yeah alright
Four Points
Well I had a rough go of it last time
Right now he's talking about 90% of the Earth's history
When it was completely and utterly uninhabited
Then
You're talking about
Him saying oh well we didn't have ice
We had one giant f****** continent
The Earth was absolutely hotter back
Exactly
Is absolutely
In Earth's history
This is the first thing you said that is unequivocally
Let's go through some of the times
Set the climate
EarthSky
We've had a lot of
Live
And we've had a lot of not like
Alright always flourished when there's a balance
Between CO2
Greenhouse gases
There was a ton of methane in the air during the Cretaceous
That wasn't that big of a deal
Because during that time there was also a s*** ton more oxygen
So plant
Grew so much bigger that's why we could support dinosaurs
Being as large as they were
So like flirt
Supporting dinosaurs
Get a job
Central nervous systems that we do a lot of stuff like that were able to thrive
Supposed to
A lot of primate life
What happens when you see rapid climate
Similar to what we're experiencing right now
When you go back through history and you see the history of climate change because the earth's climate has changed a bunch
I thought you were going to
I'm guessing a lot of things die
450 million years ago during the middle Cambrian. A mass extinction occur
Guess what
Due to an increased
Amount of
During the Permian era around 200 years ago
Guess what
God meteor
In the Triassic around 200 million years ago
Guess what
All of them
We're absolutely losing a battle with the
Global temperatures
Rising sea levels and ocean ocean acidification
Yeah man went to the Chicago Museum
Installation about the various
Comes over time
That was something that was clearly
A piece of the
Museum of that if you go through the entire
Get to the end
Hey guess what we're doing right now are humans going to be one of these are the only ones who are
And if he hasn't yet
Weird
Everybody
Pretty much
Like it
Fossil
It is
Awful
Good news
Antarctica growing
So we don't need to worry
That's cuz it plans to support it
Everybody knows that it's growing so much
Guess what
Antarctica
NASA study show this actually growing the ice the land-based glacier ice had been
Expanding and it's contributing to a sea level
Before I respond to that is that true
Growing in land mass
Glaciers are being rebuilt
And the like
Okay walk me through that
The Caesar not lowering
It seems
Not even faked
Not even the studies that are funded by these people to prove
That glow that climate change isn't real
Show that the fees are low
Nothing
He's making that up he's just making that up
Now
Antarctic
Cic
He's growing
There are a lot of explanations for that
But mainly it is surrounded by a polar current
That separates it from the
The rest of the the the oceans are functioning
Hi there is also more snow on
Antarctica
Which if you have a bunch of snow packed on top of ice it's going to keep it colder for longer
So it's not going to fall apart
This argument however is
Because
Since the late
The Antarctic has gained about 7300 square miles
Dearly
Which is
Pretty cool right
I guess
I don't want to answer
The Arctic however
Has lost about 2100 square miles
Florida
It is
F******
Stupid to make that Arc
Not just because the sea levels aren't
But because even if they even if Antarctica was growing enough
The Arctic is losing
10 million Deadlight so much more
Ice per year
Then the Antarctic could ever grow
A lie on both
That wouldn't be a big deal if there was a 12-1 like
Arctic just completely melts off and all of it
Gets all of it
Bok
Pacifica
Grade B
I don't know
He's just lying
I need
It never ceases to amaze me
The way this guy
Because he is a
F******
Squeeze ball
I'm guessing unlikely situation
Rihanna and Eminem
You do not love
I do like the situation between Rihanna
I think they have a strong
Absolutely that's that's a lot of people say relationship
Beds
Astro
Realize
Hawaii everything is music references
Because
This is something that he absolutely knows is not true right it's not based on
He's like the scientists that he imagines erasing history
But with the facts
But you can't know that
He can't
Water levels
Alright
You're not
Lauren
He can't know that
Do not know
Exactly that's called
He can't
No
How much ice the Antarctic
Without also knowing
How much ice Arctic is lose
Right because those can only exist in comparison with each other
Otherwise you're just saying well I guess the Antarctic is getting bigger
Like
Nobody nobody is put together a study about
That without
Pointing out how much ice we're losing
Right cuz it's
It's important
The only people who
Out that the Antarctica
Is growing
Well
Do you know what I'm about to say I have a
Premonition
They're not using
Their own information
What they're doing
Is there taking studies that other people have done
Who are those people
Legitimate site
Antarctic
His growing
Is based off of the same data from scientists who say who have been proving
The internet
Because growing
And the Arctic is
Dying
And they're trying to figure out why there's the
Explanation
But
Ultimately
What these
People are doing is
Fake
Check collect information
Absolutely
You know what this really comes back
What's that comes back cigar
Because algora also featuring him saying that
We need ubiquitous for
Fertility management
Otherwise we need to prevent the number of African countries
Population increase
I'm not sure what he saying
I'm not sure where you staying at
About Al Gore
Is that
Al Gore
Says that in order to fight
To give
Ubiquitous fertility
We need to control the population
Or provide them with birth
Control options
Well if you want to hear the actual
Dubai will control I will get
The real quote from Al Gore
From this
Interview
Take talking about
Depressing the rate of child mortality
Educate educating girls
Empowering women and making fertility management ubiquitously available
So women can choose how many children
And the spacing of
For lying about
I just want to control the population
That's always
You could dig into and you always find it's like
Everything they're talkin
I'm about as providing
The option
The opportunity the availability
People
Is a very tired argument
Oh yeah
These right-wing dick
The bomber
Because it really would be revolutionary 8
Developing countries
The ability to not
The super health
Absolutely
And that's why
People on the right
Aren't interested in that kind of a
Yep
Don't rely on
European Cup
Sprite
This guy
This guy is
Basically saying that
Al Gore
What's to control the population of Africa
Eugenics
Right
And Al Gore is actually saying
I think we should Free People
Yep
Al Gore's involved
I don't know
Everybody
But it goes all the way to the top
Arguing
There's nothing to worry about
This guy is a will
And sadly unfortunate Pope Francis has beds
Blind himself with advisor that have a similar mindset
Doctrine
With his advisors
Is a Jesuit
So all the way to the top
Has Pope Francis said we should worry about clutch
Yeah yeah
How bad this is hurting for the the conservative Folk
And it's all because of climate
Right
All of this stuff
I just I love it whenever anybody throws in the pope like this entire interview
Has
Only like he's just making false b******* and just saying it out loud and then all the sudden he's just like you know
Poke does it to
You know the Pat Robertson Evangelical and as a healthy distrust
Of the paper
And s*** like that
Real skepticism of catalysis
It makes sense that he would try and throw that
Anime
I didn't even consider that of course he's just
That's that's
Bear
Good for him
Krowd
That would do well at
He's
Got Al Gore
Right he's got the Pope
And he's got all these signs
Have you ever heard that 97% of scientist
Does the grief I have heard that that climate change
Forever you are generally heard that
From people on like ham
Who are attacking
From what I understand that number there's nuance
It's not as simple as the 97% number
But
Bat
Tell me what the truth is
That Mark is about to tell us
And Al Gore claim back in the early nineties that they were all scientists agree 7%
In one of the studies
Anonymous we don't know who they are and they claim a 97% consensus
97 scientists
I've always wanted to look into the 97%
Cuz you listen to that even if you are on the left and you are like
Not a climate-change bulshit fat fuk
Are you looking at near 97% you like
I mean I guess it's just a symbol of like look
This is overwhelming
Get me 7% number isn't as important as
The symbol that
To study
Naomi oreskes put together a 2004 study
That produced the first 97%
Hell yeah that mention climate
Of the studies that found a result
And then supplied an opinion
So they went through their information they found this change or this thing
They confirmed or denied this thing
And then supplied an opinion as to why it was
Was going on
97% agree
That anthropogenic
Climate change
Is
Is real
What she did though wish you'd like Nexus search
Not Nexus but you know
Simple
Simple search there of papers looking at
Keywords peer-reviewed papers
She wound up throwing away half of those papers
Because they didn't
Exactly they didn't really matter
Energy disqualified the ones that
Came up with a
I like
We don't know and we're not sure
Useful for
The overview
Exactly exactly
So at the end of the day
She got 97% of those papers
That answer
The driver of
So it's
Not exactly like
That 97% of all science
Jungkook and the people that were working with him
At the time try to repeat that
And they found
Almost exactly the same result
Using different studies using different studies and they went through the what is
The App Store
Like finding a result or anything like that
Just
What did these guys summarize their findings at
97% of them
Wound up being
Anthropogenic climate
This is
The reality of the 97% number
Is closer to
If you were to survey
Climatology
People who only study the climate
Not just climate change but just like hate
All of that stuff
Real number would be
If not 100%
99.9 person
Right
If you study if you go through all non-climate
Everybody who is considered a scientist in doing research that is related
To climate change
You get closer to like 90 to 295
Again
Of all of those studies
The only people that will come out on
Record
The only people that will come out publicly
As advertised their research
No idea
So the 97% claim is
Both
True
I don't know 8 almost
Almost left impact
Because I would rather hear them say
A hundred percent of climatologists the people whose entire life studying the climate
Agree that climate change is happening
Yeah but I bet it isn't even like
Denying
Climate change
Ambivalent
Neutral
Results in their commentary or whatever like
We weren't able to
Define
Any evidence but it
It doesn't disqualify the possibility
In the Naomi
From a 2000
When she was going through
Papers that qualified
Supplied an opinion
Any pinion genuinely was
This is not attributable to answer
Organic climbing
But that doesn't mean
Exactly
Primary
Percent is probably even like
That's an illusion of itself
Exactly
This whole thing is
It's just manufactured in a way that
Disgusting
It really is
Because the argument that you would come back to write is
I say the only scientist to come out on record as saying that it's not interpret any climate
They're all paid by
And then the right-wing would come back and say well
No
You hate business than sovereignty
But they would also say like
Oh yeah well whatever it is like that
The biggest difference
Is that a climatology
Would still be studying the climate
Is climate change wasn't
That's true
That's their job
The climate deniers
Legitimately would not have a job if there was not climate change
The climatologists
Would still study the climate
Yeah there's a parasitic
Exact
Start tonight in climate change might be a little too late in the episode 4
Yeah yeah I realize that now
Imports
Donor fund money but
Significantly proven my point and now I shall deny climate change much like what I got.
What do they use the 97
How to do
I mean
What it what is
Ask yourself that question
I just did
Everybody everybody
They use it
To do something
97% claim with
Who use that to bully people and otherwise
You don't know about
Don't know enough about science you can't count
Bullies there's such bully
I could not find a un scientist who said it was pulled out of
Lord monckton
His book he was cited in Mark marinas book at 3:15
Oh yeah
Crazy old Kook Lord mostyn
It's just
This infuriated because
His
Book
With the line
That's a good start that's a great start right
Climate the politically incorrect
Hatchet-man I am a hat
And to bully people
Unnamed scientist is also probably pandering
Robertson believe it has to do with
Revolution
Nonsense
I think that is also an
Playing the room
A little interested to ask him who he's talking about
You can't find
We might be talking about them probably is
Because he does show up at the UN
But it is not too long ago
An unnamed climate
Generally I find when you don't name something it's because you don't want people to look into it
Persuasive
Speech
You don't use specifics
Because you don't have the
Haha
But I've learned
The last two years oh yeah
That's
It is
It is ridiculous to me
This guy cuz this guy is not just done at Robertson
This guy's been on actual TV
I think I know this guy
I just hate it he's such a used car sales
Yeah it seems like
Glimpses that you provided
Believe that
He's not
Engaging with
Before argument over the place
Yeah and this is almost the full interview
His questions
No cool exactly
Marla sokoloff
And so I'm really cutting out of this interview is like him gone
Like that's that's really what I've got to go
Yeah yeah
There's a few chunks worth like I don't
Me too
Find you you pull your b*******
You know that's not true any
Even while he's staying
Completely not true stuff
The stuff that I cut out with him like
Almost winking to the audience like with a giant Beyond wink sign of life
You and I both know this s*** is
True but we're all here together
Like that
All I wanted to do is grab the stuff that it sounds like he's really trying to sell you on
Like all of the stuff that I've grabbed so far
Really wants you to believe it
Like what do you get from
Assholes
I'm sure the visual that's really all that I'm going to walk away from this way
Not listening at all
I'll probably later
But the real villain
Oh boy real villains of this whole thing
Weather comes from
So we like that
According to Pat Robertson it all comes from the out-of-pocket
What did you mean an out-of-pocket expense is not covered by water
Sunspot activity kick it up a little bit
Just like the scientist
Who snuck in
And removed the 1930s clothes were villain
Those were built
Mahler
Horse
Or even worse
Ganondorf I'm going to tell you there
Biggest crime right now
Or actually Marcus
And as well
It's actually I plan out a quart of activist un scientist people like Michael Oppenheimer
Who took money from Barbra Streisand quarter million dollars
Oh yeah
It goes all the way to the
Not Barbara
Do you know my favorite part of this quote
This quote comes from one place
Barbra Streisand
James inhofe
Set motherfuker
Martial law being threatened
He's an absolute dick who wrote his speeches
Aaron Russo
Whenever he said that Barbra Streisand was behind the core of climate activist
It's Mark Marino Dorado
I thought there's no way that's who it is but it's got to be
Cerina Vincent
I wrote the speech was other guy to deliver and then I decided it
First I heard of this s*** that's a crazy badger
Trick.
Wow
That's pretty cool but I look Alex doesn't have the ability to do something like that
Who played something
So he could beg use it for his own
That's 15 years later
Has said Barbara's right I looked it up for forever
Leaning
Celebrities
She comes up as a Target dollars to literally anyone.
Relationship
Item recovery.
The Destroyer
But we got to talk about the heroes
We got to talk about the heroes like we're on the way single man
Fighting against the system that is designed to destroy them
So we have all these activists
Being paid
5 Barbara Street
Without you
But we have some Heroes million dollars
We're burying the lead on that but that's not that much money in terms of actually going through with
Like a high-level study
Let's go let's fucken places need to operate like actual labs
Isn't down Manson Liquors
Speedway
1331 dollars
Hey that's just stuff you can trace around but not on the bus
It's like covered by
Pre-speech kind of ideas
Pretty much money is speech
Talked a lot about
We have
Talked a lot about how these guys give these money
Giving it to the
Okay
And there are few scientists who are willing to Buck
Really thrilled to hear that
And one of the scientist at Princeton
In the book
He said we're currently in a carbon dioxide
Salmon on Earth
Sounds like Alex
Carbon dioxide
I think actually now that I hear him like through this again like this unnamed Princeton scientist I think it's also
I'm just realizing that Robert
The fuc
Why should I say the name
I looked him up I found him
Monster
The Princeton physicist he's talking about is a Webster
No
Nevermind
William
A actually got a degree in Robert Forster studies old movies
That's always late
Trailer place in the lobby
Rattler
Movie that I thought was good time movie goddamn
Tapper
Okay
By all accounts
A really good physicist
That's cool on credible
No he's a really good physicist
He was also the director of The George C Marshall Institute
You know about
Nope Marshall
It was about two things
Strategic Defense
Add beer pong
Pretty much
But
The Strategic Defense part
Of the George C Marshall in
Was like we got to get away
From dr. William happer
Cuz he's a f****** crazy climate denial months
And they were like we're not
We're not getting s***
Because of you because you are so f****** crazy
So he split the George C Marshall in
And he took over
Fart
And created the CO2 coalition
That
As we go along
Let's see
When did George C Marshall Institute closed down in 2015
It had
It had to
Because it was only taking in $300,000 in donations
And expenses were at about 500
Now
Or actually last year
According to the CO2 coalition
Nonprofit exemption
Application
They will receive a total of 1.5 million dollars
And it only spent about 1.1
In 25
Piper was the target of a sting operation
Is even worse
It was a Greenpeace
Here's the short version
These activists
Posed as your Koch brothers
And they went to him and they said
We're going to need a study
That proves what we wanted
And he said
I can do that for you got it
I do that for you and I like how much do you how much do you
We need to pay you
We got to avoid the look of it
Impropriety
However
If you were to make a donation to the CO2 coalition
Well that's all on the up-and-up
This is
Absolute hammer
All of these people
Read first
And then they do
Write operation
Has been played out over and over and over
So when I say you like
Donors trust is funding
Funding them before the research
Happens and their funding explicit understanding
Study will find the conclusion that is desire
Which is why
This is why you pay up
Frontera you're saying that this thing has happened over and over yet I believe that it's probably like happened a bunch
Times of operation
Over and over and over and over.
How did bread get made
Does it work
That was done in 2015
How do you think
CO2
It's tough to predict cuz the world is so stupid
But you would want to say he's in prison
We live in a dark dark timeline
Probably super rich
2018 Hazard getting close to a million dollars
That
Difference between 2016
So that was to you
Write this year he is grown even more
Almost at Dublin
Exactly
Don't judge my map
Which I
Find very
Interview
I don't think that the laws of nature physics
In chemistry have changed
80 million years ago the earth was a very prosperous place
And there's no reason to think it will suddenly become bad now
Prosperous
Weird word
I mean in terms of like
Conclusion is
Vegas to be meaningless
Still liking more than
Nothing is going to touchmark Moreno's
No it's not
Solid
Very impressive
Oh yeah
Let's see who else
Just a
Just a hammer this point home
Happer
Publicly praised
James O'Keefe
Multiple times
Timothy wouldn't want it
Praise
People who do the things that got him into trouble
James O'Keefe
Operations
We've got
A very strong female
And surprise
Mark Marino
Not stoked
The UN climate
She said
Did Christina forget it
We speak a centralized transformation that will make life on planet Earth very different
That the UN
Climate chief
See anything bad about that
You sing it like it's some sort of really
Evil
I just hear that I feel like
Yeah yeah
I think we do need to fundamentally change the whole bunch of
Oh yeah
Christina segarra
F******
Dope
She has had a badass career
At no point in time has she done
She is one of those characters
More especially the current
Un climate
Patricia Espinoza
And she is also had a cool
One thing that you can go back through with the UN climate change
Is that they have ultimately
I apologize
Your accident attorneys General
They are given
Very little
They have no ability to really affect it
All of them though
Have come to this position through being
F****** amazing at their job
Like these are people who are career diplomats
And career scientist
Who all have
Given us
F*** the whole time
Like for instant with the current
Climate
Climate Chief Patricia
Spinoza
She has been a career Diplomat for Mexico
Basically since she was like 25
She's worked
Non-stop for women around
The world
Everywhere she goes
She has had a positive effect
Patricia Espinoza Credit Paris Accord.
Before she was
The un's climate
She would go through every place that she could
She has an unimpeachable record
F******
Sales pitch to all of these people was incredible enough that people give her
A top honor
In terms of getting the Paris agreement
This guy is saying
Is very bad because she said
Things will make
Life on Earth
Yeah
Different doesn't mean worse
No it does not
Well
Let me tell you some
Guess who this guy hero worship
And it's not just Senator Senator James
Worships that guy
Yeah I would say that's probably right
Once he stopped once.
Inhofe
Hand-speak
He almost immediately
Started climatedepot.com
And that was
Hint
Byerly
Because his connection to inhofe
Let him to his connection to donors
Right
All of that
But networking that's
Oh yeah
And he is
We are bees
Eating alive
You know who else is eaten alive by d.c.
We'll find out
Scott Pruitt
Donald Trump VP
Stood up to the climate-change establishment
Okay
Scott Pruitt
He's eyes A man among men
Is a piece of s***
And realize this interview is that current
This is from 2018
Maybe five years ago or something
This is what fruit was still of course
Live because he's a giant piece of s***
Everybody
If you don't know the evil that's got Pruitt as done
Not just
Not just his like
Scandals in the
Cheating and stealing
Misusing public funds and f****** everybody over
For no reason
Scott Pruitt
Has
Destroy the EPA from the inside
It is only going to get worse
But
If you are at you know everybody already knows the Scandal
So I wanted to look more into Scott Pruitt
And he and I share something
Deeply quotes
Which I love
I love a baseball
Scott Pruitt had a moment
That I liked into Hitler getting denied from Art School
He was asked to try out for the Cincinnati Reds second baseman
And if he had made
We would not have had to deal with Scott Pruitt at all
How to deal with his
Play baseball for Georgetown
And
Teammates
Gave him the nickname
Opossum
Linguistically it's not a bad name but it
It does seem to imply traits that are conducive
Also second bases
Flower shop
There's a lot of plays that happen
Call second base is where you hide the coaches
It's not like
No.
Well you can put somebody
Now that good
But you you bury somebody right field
Only because they're an amazing hitter
Where is the second baseman is the coaches
The second baseman is the kid who
Scrappy
He works real hard he's got all those angles
You don't want to put them on first
No you definitely
First is where you get your
Good morning think about it there
This is been my TED talk about baseball
Baseball is from watching a little bit of it
Game first you got to hit a ball then got to get up at like 9
I like that
Find any of his like that
No apparently
Hit the only home run
No
Also no wait
Pretty good I was wasn't talking too much
I got to try out from Cincinnati
The Reds back then
Baseball player the show
Look if you hit like 300 in college
It doesn't translate to the to the Mesa
Now you got to hit like 450
Out of their butt
Grew up in Broken Arrow Oklahoma
Which is a rich suburb outside of John Travolta
Now it is
Movies in Broken Arrow
I reference was very unconfident
Berenstein Arrow Nicolas Cage in Broken Arrow
After face off so they already switched my data
Easy to make that mistake
The reason that it's Scott
Grew up in Brooklyn
It's because Broken Arrow got its name
Because that is one of the places that
Andrew Jackson
How did Native Americans
During the trail
Broken Arrow was then once again
Stolen from the Native Americans
Buy energy and oil in
In Oakland
Scott Pruitt is doing
Did
Everything possible to continue that leg
Situation where his family was
Was growing up there
You kind of get that sense
And this is the thing
Like of course
Scott Pruitt
Is a member of First Baptist of Broken Arrow
Which is a f****** megachurch
Drake is a dick
F****** monstrous
Give me an example
One of their pastors
Is a atom mask
And he is like the cool Pastor he's got tattoos on his arms
He's the one who's out reaching these like
Look I've been in the ship
17 year old girlfriend
He recently wrote this is a recent
This is like
2 days ago
This is on a blog post
So you know we got all caps
Going on all over the hell yeah
In the all caps that he wanted
Arises out of makes a better God over our lives
Start that over I wasn't distracted by the yelling structural
Arises out of
God truly makes a better God over our lives than we do
Okay I track it.
Adult
Sex outside of marriage
All of the
This is this is what this is about
Sex outside of marriage
Homosexuality
From the doubt
Plant design for physical intimacy is to be between one man and one woman
In the confines of
So they're great
Don't fuc
Yep
Doesn't like I know that that
It's not great we never like to hear it but
Far outside of like
The sort of things you hear in a lot of churches feel like
I just like adding that on there because
You know what Scott Pruitt's about Scott Pruitt
Is that
During his run for a turn
He took a lot of money
Please don't hurt him
Of course
Every
Single f****** one of these people
Is being
Paid
Deliberately
To destroy any and all opposition
But you we don't know that much
When I'm looking at that stuff
You know it's almost 100% of climate
You know if there's a thousand climatologists
One of them is going to take.
You know like of course you're going to make a study that says Nah
But even when you factor in like
Meteorologist who are some of the worst offenders of like
Weather is different
Irabu f******
Calm it down
But
Even even amongst
All of those
Nobody is going on
Do you know what I mean
Like the people who are going out
Talking and making their stuff table
They are pay
The people who are you know when you go through that
Ninety seven percent
Study
Their claims
Climate change is not anthropogenic
Their claims are in those studies
This is not attributed
Anthropogenic
So even those people
Like slightly relevant
Through the actual study
Exactly we might just be looking at a variable
Right
Disprove the answer
Exactly
I know a lot of the information in this episode is
Of course repetitive
I'm sorry I know it with a purpose though
It's not like you're
About differ
People
Throughout the story because driving home the point
All of these people are ill
Where you at where you at
Position of vibes
You can't
That's what these people are
Repeating stuff
Just reinforcing
Argument that people make so often
You think 97% of scientists agree that if we had a heliocentric universe
What about what about the great man theory of science
F****** the entire
When you go back and you look through all of those differ
You'll find that
The reason those one men were those one guy's those those great men
Trends
Is because the trends themselves were
Based on entrenched power
Power control
97% of
Weatherby
Interrupt
Or whatever
And they were doing exactly now if you want to talk about the flowering of the Renaissance
Those were commissioned
Pieces
So much of that was
I'm telling you I want this to be true
You make it trip
You make it be proved
That this is true
And those great men people
We're the ones they were like yourself
That kind of thing
This
Time.
It's gotten away from that
Universal control by powerful
And now a scientific
Consensus
Infinitely more
Then it did
50 years ago then did a hundred years
So when people give you that like
Turn all that s***
That's because Galileo was acting in the spirit
Set the scientific
Consensus
Acting
Yeah
Take me to workout demythologize
Those those
Great
Not strictly speaking
True
The only the only
Almost utterly
Singularly without
Input from without like constant input from other scientists without a concert
Formations obviously General
What he wrote from Kippy in Mathematica that was the
Only time and
Scientific history I can think of where I was like
Did you just did that s*** by him
Self
Yeah
Mypoints
I think pretty clear right
Come to the end of this there's a lot of stuff
You know like the climate Gates
Stop
Misinterpret
Things like that the decline nonsense
Like I expected
Some of that cuz
He's hitting a lot of the normal
Nothing that's absent
I don't think it's the
But
I think you're
Your point is very very well
Playing fast and loose
Did give me that great visual metaphor but
Man has always been battling the shores
Like an accidental
Oh good
At the fruit
But I guess I guess we have
I think we are on Facebook what if you want to
Would you be able to find us
Very foreign
Changing roles
Garbage
Tell you one guy though he is metaphorically
Which would kill a guy
He is not literally done
PetSmart Purina
Technically probably killed a guy though not necessarily with a poison
That's Alex Jones