Alex
Jordan Jordan
Does it feel good to be back in the right side of the chair
Feedback from people taking over and doing an episode
Gave me a whole new respect the hell out of
Being me that I didn't that's for sure
I did not yell at all
Not my style
I'm realizing this now probably a
Wheatley inaccurate version
Of what Bruce Springsteen Tenth Avenue freeze-out.
Bring up the episode about to release it I realized
That's the reason I told about it being about a snowstorm in New York
Because my buddies Missouri we are drinking one night and he told me about how he was in the snow storm
Salvatore's
Now your fingers all the time like everybody has a friend named set
Type of cell
Sitter from New Jersey
Missouri
Rihanna grapes I got her Punk bar called Eastside Tavern in Columbia Missouri
Yeah but I realized
You told me that story is probably
Accurate
Not that one
Owners who signed up and are supporting the show
Ariel
You are now policy
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk relaxed destroyer of worlds
Life-after
Party
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much that was life after party
The parties have ended
Or if it's a life full of after
After parties
Dyslexic
Could beat you know your Evite okay or everybody
Impossible
Likes
Keep someone who donated on a little bit of
So Frank
Thank you so much
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone someone sodomites
These guys do do that good
Click the button
And if you're thinking of you know you're like I want to support Asia
You should instead donate to our show don't I don't know if I want to
General if I want to come down
Present-day episode be going over February 11th
The 13th
Which is Monday through Wednesday of this week
Right which is ultimately unsatisfying cuz your Twitter is abuzz
Trump is going to declare a state of emergency and all that I'm sure Alex has
Tumescent if the news
Will cover all that stuff probably on Mondays episode
We got it we got it will cover the beginning of the week that was
And this week was f*****
World
The beginning of the week and we're going to
Begin on
February alive
On this episode
The show celebrating some good news
I know that I made the prediction that Alex
Does moving away from Trump
And I do still believe that
But I think it's it's
A slow process
Are you still going to validate a lot of trump stuff in order to make it look like the worldview
Resent is more popular
Yeah the victory
Then he's going to talk about it
Is the Trump is
52% approval rating
But
Celebrating a victory for Trump
But it's
It's really more about the idea that
My nationalism by populism is
Popular and we
We can see that by Trump's numbers I'm a driving force
So we're going to see some positive talk about Trump but I don't think it invalidates
The transit
Now unfortunately I think that
The Trump does declare National Emergency
That will get Alex to come right back around at least for another cycle
So I think that'll disrupt whatever process I was seeing happening
But I don't think it's going to be enough for
The long run it's like a divorce
Divorce happens for like a year or two while you're away
Start here
Oversampling of Democrats and stuff like that
Never was just thought it was kind of like
Goofy dumb misunderstanding of how old
Statistics
But the way he describes it in this next clip makes me realize it is a much bigger problem
He does not understand
The truth is explosive the truth is powerful the truth is Unstoppable
When people are willing to stand up and carry it forward
Gallup
Rasmussen
That other polls believe the Democratic Party
Is the dominant party in the US and so far more than 30 years
More Democrats
We have Republicans
Walmart
Why would they do that
Confusion
Jumping off of his confession
Power Wheel power
That's a going on or whatever
+ 6
However Loretta bird has a pretty heavy
Right
It's just Alex
Literally saying that he thinks the pollsters think the Democrats are the party exhaust
We now have the information that we need to address this because before I was willing to like push this aside and
Alex
Is beyond the pale
Makes me think that we made
You need to take
A little bit
Conductor
The pole represent
And often achieve a representative sampling is incredibly difficult
Just because the researchers want to random sampling to take their poll
It's not good enough
Just randomly call 1000 people and see what happens
The characteristics of the people they pulled needs to match the demographic
Information
Of the geographic area that's being pulled
And because of the gearing possibility of the responded to your poll perfectly matching the areas democratic
The results often.
Need to be waiting
Easy example
Older people are more likely to answer their phones
The survey results reflect the answers of
I'm not busy
Acme
So in order to correct for this the researchers will need to give more weight to the answers
People in the groups that are underrepresented in the set of answers
Do they match the demographic
The area generally taken that information from the most read
Expenses
This Probably sounds overly simplified
Like realistically the older you are particularly the more likely it is that you identify as a republic
An older people are over-represented in the Rob respond
Data of most polls
The amount to which this needs to be fixed by waiting inevitably depends on the demographic
Information to pull takers bring in
With the random sampling
So you'll see it right up suppose exactly the extent to which they waited
Credible polling organizations
Conduct reviews on the raw data to process data and everything in between that lead from the rot
To the process
Just how professional statistics
Alex is just
He doesn't understand that's very very basic thing
Said he would understand if
If you didn't drop out.
Junior College
At least like
Send an email to Nate silver
Curious curious really important
Now the interesting thing exactly
Much of this going to play out
Because there's a possibility that even as the generation
That are heavily Democrat now or less
Get older
Past Generations
Doesn't happen
If you look at generational differences
Republicans and
Good like right leaving ideas are taking
If younger
Horsley
Cuz it's like the numbers are
Razee
Bad
Conserve
People start to get older
Or
If pulling
Places find a way to incorporate use
Using cell phone
Or something like that there's a really decent chance
You'll see Democrats
Maurice
Democrat
Morgan Moore responded
Two pools and then you'll see
Conservative
Waiting
Being done
Exposed
I suppose
If I was done trying to
Alex's argument
Better for him
I would say that
Conspiracy
Trump polling
Can absolutely have an influencer
It's on people's behavior
If you see a pole like Frances for so many people during the Trump Hillary campaign you saw those poles
And there is there was a lot more
A lot less urgency there for people who saying
Well it looks like Hillary going to win by 10 so I'm not really going to
He is engaged in
This is I would other words
If you're pulling is not
2 inaccurate
People are just going to write it off I'm media
Those poles even for
Rasmussen which as of right
You still see them within this certain
Margin of
Error that everybody except
So if you want to say the poles can influence
Outcome
That is an argument that
Can be made
If you want to say that they over represent Democrats by 15% every
You just don't understand how
Not know
So now we get to the 52
The New 52
The secret
Schneider
Not at all
But
Trump has 52% number
Spot all the propaganda
Trump
Trump is at 52
Think about that
Done points more for Democrats
Call
I told you he's really at like 65-67
Conservatively
That's
Crazy way to look
Like that
Reflect any
Sort of reality
First of all I have no idea
Because it doesn't appear to exist
In their data from January 21st or 17th
21st
Gallup survey 37% approval rating for the way Trump is handling his job of the president
Which is down from a high of 45%
For the week
Right after inauguration
But also have
Exact same thing as an approval rate
If you look at it by party
88% approval rating among Republicans
Percent approval rating
These numbers actually are part of setting a new record for the most polarized approval rating ever recorded
Simply began in 90
M45
Gallup record
Your president ever
Beating out the previous record by 10.9% and your numbers were
The worst since WWII
Do not necessarily a record button
Pretty good high water marks
Is one of the only
People who at certain points in the presidents
You swinging for truck silly hated
Posted on February 13th
But that doesn't match Alex's 50
2% number corded this episode
Alex is making a Gallop s*** up
2% approval rating on February 11th
That number dropped to 50% on the 12th
And is held there until at
Episode today
43% on February
First
Most people consider this increased to be the result of the State security numbers of jump
Which is pretty common phenomenon in president
2011 Obama was it 46
Preside approval on January 17th
Which jumped
To 52% by the 20
When he delivered that your estate of the you
Union speech
Important things to consider about the polo Jordan
What
Rasmussen releases daily presidential approval rating
Statistics
Appropriate process
If you can solve their methodology call house phone
From 5 to 9
PMR weekend
Exclude the landline who works at night or who likes to party on weeknight
Their process is also an automatic robotic call
So for someone to take their pool that have to receive this call on a landline
It's amazing to me that they manage to find a sample of 500
Responded
Everyday your mind go to that's what your mind goes to
Do you want to roll
That's okay I don't have an elevator
Hello
What's federal government
So heavily but I'm not saying that
I'm just saying that to illustrate to even this pull the Alex pouting is great
Exactly the same
Recent polls
Evan
Aldi's
Open produce
What's 38% of 4
All of it the same
In terms of the polling on a daily basis
But what they do is they combine a bunch of different polls
And then wait them according to the similar process
It's Donald
Random asphalt from other polls
Go over how their methodology works
And then use that to eat
Making a composite
And then put out the
President's approval ratings on a daily basis
If you look at the polling data currently available Trump is -14.8
Approval rating
Which is the worst any president since Harry Truman is being at this point in their presence
With the exception of Reagan
Most people do that as a result of the economy being in the toilet back then and all the Goodwill he had
After John Hinckley jr.
Haven't worn off
I was going to say he had a really good run after somebody tried to kill
Killed he would be remembered amazingly well.
With many circles
So with the 52% approval rating Rasmussen
That's a good
Happy about that
There's nothing
He should probably be bad The Wider picture of his numbers
That positive favorability numbers since February 1st 2017
When he was at 8.01 + equal
Never should have had a positive rate has been office for 12 days
I guess the point is this
Someplace even when they release date
Perceived to be real
It's entirely possible that even after adjusting
Stanford demographic
The Rasmussen poll showed up
2% approval rating
Ultimately I also could possibly an outlier in the data
That are out there
And also could be explained by some obvious real-world events
The State of the Union the ending of the government shutdown number
Variable
But I also
When the bigger picture of everything
You have to make the most of what you have
For now
All they have is 52% of
She got to run with it cuz it makes it look like a majority of Americans
Love
Support for Trump
Adam
FedEx
I'm just so sad
I'm just so sad for the right way
Candle flickers violently destroying everyone around us
Trying desperately to cling to power
They're just
Really
But our argument against the Green New Deal as people are going to steal ice cream
Come on Mark Dice
What are you talk
If you recall the beginning of this week representative ilhan Omar
Head that I got in a bit hot water
We were going to have to talk about Alex's take on that and I really would like the
Republican bulshit horrendous I can't imagine how bad this is going to be
About some of that my feelings about glass
And stuff like that my feelings about
What she probably wrong
Play in terms of presentation
I don't think that you did anything wrong big picture I don't think
She was acting out of anti-Semitism the conversation
We had about that not being the smoothest way
To make a point or whatever
It is important to point out
People
In Congress or these commentators
For the most part we're acting out of
Sword is a craisin
Element
I would I would characterize it not even I think they were doing is
They were defending a pack
And so they behaved in ways
That were disgraceful and towards
Representative Omar
That's what
I don't think that's enough
I think
Recognized that she represent
Credible threat
To the fiction
9 US foreign policy
The people are
Looking for any opportunity
You take her down because of the holes that you can puncture as evidence
That's why they're so afraid after all this Scandal of
Questioning Elliott
About
In El Salvador
I wish
CL Missouri
Incredibly relevant
He's being put in as a special representative for Venezuela not right before being taken
Hanover in the exact same way that we have people who were directly involved
Symbols
You need to
Those are things that are important to come up and most people
Don't do it
For whatever reason weather is
The financial motivations weather cowardice
Not afraid
Of that Brett
Two businesses
Republican
Foreign policy fiction
Muslim Park
That's more important actually accidentally brought up exactly the distinction
I was hoping to make their in my introduction to
Because he lives in this next clip about what
We did and all that stuff
If you listen to this clip its 45-second
Long and you'll see
Have you
Rank Islam
Phobia
Oh by the way of this Muslim woman member of Congress
40 tweeting stuff about Jews having hooked noses and
That is not accurate
Criticism of hurt
And that guy said
These comments are
Tantamount
Ririri
Cartoon
Call
Use misrepresenting.
Specific thing
Jews and their money-grubbing how they run everything and all this stuff
Parentheses B hardcore Somali
Visit Muslim in their country and sell women on slide blocks
What do you think happens when you bring in Islamic country
Baby into a backyard with 14
Pitbulls with with rabies or something
Compatible with the West.
Siri
If Alex believes
There is no
Room for him
If he's defendant
There's no room for him to accept any Islam in the country ever
Compatible with the West
.
That's a big problem because now you have called for the elimination of a religion or
At least the exiling of a religion ever right
Wichita constitutional right under the Second Amendment
There is nothing he loves more than the Constitution
Exactly and that's never read it and cannot understand the f****** work
Ben Franklin
The Constitution
Yeah I remember reading
Thomas Jefferson's Koran
Just had big red x's on every page
And I know John Adams slipped in there and sign
Never change
So I mean this is just
Wearing your shirt as usual
But then
Keep the spirits good to him
And he starts
Deeply irresponsible things that are in no way based in reality
And I'm very excited
You just how wrong he is
After you
Of course
Shut off Stockholm Syndrome
Plural women in office
And now she's talking about
All day
Believable ladies and gentlemen
It is pretty unbelievable
Lee just Alex
Is bigger
What have you
You can't
Define bigotry in a bigoted way
Alex
Dismiss it or say it's okay or anything like that
Arguing about that is going to end up being like
A waste of Opera
Here's a president
Has more women serving in their National Assembly with 28% than the US does in Congress
With 22% even after the strides made in the last midterm elections were made
Any women onesies
Azerbaijan
Before making her the first woman in the world
That's right she beat Madeleine Albright by 4 years was the US
Is first female secretary
But Bangladesh
Bangladesh is the world's most populous muslim-majority country
The prime minister's have all been women since 1996 I can't imagine why
In Egypt
You like Egypt
I heard about that
Departamentos women
Was the first female parliamentarian in the Arab world which he was elected office in 19th
In Indonesian
She served as president from 2001 to 2000
Turkey
Steeler was the elected Prime Minister of Turkey
What are Pakistan
Course how could anybody forget about Benazir Bhutto
Who was elected prime minister twice 1988 to 1990
From 1993 to 1996
Buddha was a member of the Pakistan People's Party socialist Progressive Party and I December 27th 2017
Assassinated by terrorists
Who shot her and then proceeded to detonate a suicide vest full of bearings
Killing at least 23 people
My point here is
Need to find elected female leaders in the Arab world
In terms of that sort of thing
Whether it's at
Or it's just them electing women to high-level positions
Long before we ever did
We have not had a female president
Email president because his is Islam is fundamentally incompatible
Which is why we can only have mail present
It's proven Alex is doing here is a disgraceful disgusting display of islamophobia
And he's trying to erase the historical contribution many others
In order to make his point
He has more in common with the terrorist that killed Benazir Bhutto that he does with any of these women
Many of them have worked to make their countries safer places for women
And make them more Western
Something that takes a level of Courage Alex could only imagine
Also I really really hate his phrasing here
He didn't say that Omar didn't have any consequences
For what Alex
He said
Nothing's been done to
That sort of language is unacceptable
Nothing has been done to her suggest that something needs to be done to her
From someone else that might sound like
Anderson slippers
Alex Jones
That isn't
Credibly violence
The idea that someone needs to
Something to her
Is incredibly soft
Just because I want to make this even worse for Alex maybe because
He uses language like that
I want to bring into this
After he would be presented with this list of elected women in Arab and Muslim countries
No Muslim country would ever elect a Christian to their government
Is over 70% Muslim a Christian woman was elected
The parliament 2005
Boutros boutros-ghali was Egypt's minister of State
App for foreign affairs from 1977 to 1991
Grant
He was a huge dick
And help sell weapons to the hutus in Rwanda
What's a Christian
I don't like it when people bring up Boutros boutros-ghali in any kind of positive light
Bring up the still being okay with his daughter being a lesbian
I get you I get it up
Strictly as a counterexample
Because it's a really really bad exactly
You know that it is a Christian guy who was the minister of State for
Foreign affairs
Good 20
Get doubles 20 years
Or Christian you back
More about religion in general
Palestinian Christian was elected mayor of Ramallah in the West Bank in
A large part of developing the concept of
Food was
ReDiscover post-colonial
Unifying identity
Where's the Christian president of Senegal from 1960
Senegal is a country that is about 96% most
Keith Ellison was the first Muslim Alexa
Did the US Congress
The point here is that by many
Many metric
Much of the Islamic world is far more Progressive
We are
There are 17 countries that require their head of state be Muslim
But many of them other elected post
I don't really like the idea of telling countries how they have to run their
Also once we have a president who's anything
Further away from Christian
Wishi-washi deist leading we can probably talk more about how open and pluralistic we are right
My point is that if you get into the reality of stuff none of it matches
The islamophobic version of history and these countries
Alex wants to perpetuate
Free religious takeover religious back by the United States
Didn't I
I don't know
America is fundamentally incompatible with the world
Like that seems more likely to me that
Although you could possibly love me
Democracy more
Muslim woman who is f******
God dammit
So many of the women that I was able to find your politician
Islamic and Arab world
Like
Majority Muslim country
Many of them had
Incredibly Progressive
Forward
Looking policies
And
Used the idea of westernization
Conversation
That they were seeking
Radically
Were the sort of things that Alex should be in favor of
Because he's into this idea that Islam is in
Compatible with
Good
And that Muslims are essentially barbaric
Horrible
Folk you can't
The forest for
Complaints about representative Omar
And
I haven't really talked too much about Alex's response to the State of the Union Address cuz I think it's kind of boring
You can kind of see
See what he most of his complaints are in this clip
What a monsterous pig
Great sir
Capturing non-muslim areas
Mom has a business
Sorbonne our brain
Detrimental
Today
Nice
That pivot
He committed crimes and Attorneys General
All right New York
State attorney-general picture Trump is broke by the end of the
A plot and that the Russia investigation
Was a cover for
Is it nonsense
I'm tracking down threads that were related to this
Investigation of the Russian interference
In the process you stumble across things are like
That's super illegal it's outside my scope
Take it state court or whatever
That is how things go
That's not that's not a
Facade
Investigation a really important thing that people should
You should be talking more about is
They're all like All Millers going outside of his
Hold on
If you're investigating a crime
And you come across
You come across a lot of crimes
Maybe that's suggestive
The crime is probably there too or even related in some way but discreet
You know that's okay
Bank investigating a bank robbery you find an unrelated murder
Set the person committed maybe in the lead-up to
You might take it to a homicide detective
You're right about the cover-up
Cover up
Omar and
Cortez
Knox
State of the Union
To be released
Port
I have therefore they were against Trump
That's a different different remember different
Okay
So Alex
We're DatPiff
That was that was not good
What shook me even more to Mike or was it any ghost
Commercial break
Eddie comes back from
And he does this
He starts doing another app
On the show but then he realizes that he's not doing a good enough job
Do a second take
But it's all because he saved
WhatsApp
We're going to
Get to this anaplan removed from office
Properly plug
We got going right now
So I'm going to do it
Right now for you
Please gentlemen
He shut out the brain Force plus years ago
Are we going all these top firms all these top research groups this money
Nootropic Ash
Go to all the top publication. All the top study
Look at who the top three or four sellers are
Been looking for product reviews
Then go out and find a top lab Source our products even better and then
Glass
Don't reinvent the wheel just make it better
Yeah
Very popular
Almost 5 stars
But you you get it
Show me images of
I'm just going to
Cuz I had to promise people think I'm directing the show I'm not really
I'm just going to start over right now
Talk about this for the by right now
What I'm doing right now
Operation so busy I don't do this while I'm doing it live on air right now
Thank you very much
That's crazy
We're going to put it in and post
On this life Joe know what he's doing cuz I don't want to stick around for five minutes after the show
Dakota commercial
Like really suck it up for a good minute and a half
Start over
How many does another 2 minutes
Just on that ass commercial but on his
This is too much
This is real bad
It is especially after be like 10 minutes of
Goddamn these Muslims
Wait it's a very strange
It's hard to deal with listening for sure
For sure
And will I keep thinking is like
If you're going to be
Flaming
Awful
Inaccurate
Information right
Right after all of that big guy is
Two tanks
In Saudi Arabia United Arab Emirates has ever done two points Tucker born
But here in America we have the freedom
To do it over again
Yeah
Husband talking about how he's mad
I understand
I empathize
You want to
We're probably going to take him for a little bit of
So in the past month Alex has been saying
You sent out letters
People I need started
People already
Absolutely
Insane got a bunch
This
How dare you actually let people here
We're just going to shut him down
Is YouTube videos using
Stop the white supremacy
That's a slam dunk case
If cost at $90 and she'll win
I've got that out there that are slammed Dodge
I just got to pick a couple of Naman
I just got it
I just got to do it
Sharks in the Letters Out to just to let him know today
Okay
Blustery bulshit
I guess for his journal
Or something like that
I really need to get these letters then that were threatened to sue people who are stars of white supremacy
Letters but they eat another letter and they would put it in and post
Also is anybody get sued for calling out
I got the plan
Please call
Slam dunk case
For Alex at least keep saying slam-dunk I'm like I wish
If it's Alex Alex
If you do list
To wash out
I don't know
Either way
Vanessa question a lot lately and I don't even answer
But
If you want to let people know that you listen to our show but you don't want to say our name
The next time you talk about having slam dunk
Cases
People should call you direct shipment of a court because you got a slam dunk
You say that
I really like that but could you do that one more time
Open account
Operation by me talking more about Rex Chapman from the top
RX7
Good
Good to active
Appreciate that in somebody
At post-career
And faculty at 6 don't
Back in the 90s Chapman highlight-reel idea
George
Dowdy Brown and absolutely
Rex Chapman
Loki
Sick dunker Vince Carter
There's a little bit later
Really good
Very good it is not the same thing in the dunk contest
He got robbed
Not making the finals
What is important is the Alex
It's going to say something
I'm being generous
Do you said something
About
I don't know how to tell you
You this ahead of time really except to say that what I think he's saying
Is he likes the world that unions have
Created
Right
Uses to give
Any respect
To Union for having created those sorts of working condition
Fahrenheit
Express
I'll see if you agree
For an America bitching about how bad it is
Watch outside the US
Option goes
He one of the few places where
You didn't really get all the power than using everybody
The establishment
So I don't think that
I don't think anybody really itchy
Real progress through heaven like let's say
A duel
With a railroad Tycoon
I think he's metaphorically talkin about the hard-fought battles
The 5-day work week
Well let's not let's not forget
Though that those were actually
Very real battles that a lot of people
I mean
Dear we've had our problems
Middle picture correct
Details Rock
Miss sandwich
Yeah we are better because of these
Struggles against
Bright forces
Yes absolutely that's true
But you hate the people who buy filling is Apple
The pie crust
The Giants
Yeah
Just weird to hear stuff
Alex
I mean
He just doesn't know what he's talking about
I love the 40 Hour Work Week
That's great
I love having a full weekend off
That's awesome
I love being paid a livable wage and instead of my children not being at work
I love not being paid
It can only be used at the railroad magnates own store that are actually undervalued and he's
I think he has a real Twisted about what
And how things became too
And a half
Information
That my my family uses to get around
Hating
Important then
Oh my God you do not understand
A generous take ya
You wouldn't even probably be willing to
Gunslinger
Earlier I believe that Alex is drifting away
The perception that trumps victories are his groups Victor
I think the Dynamics
I think that'll change
Next episode
Course
But for now as we're looking for this on the 11th
One of the reasons that I I believe that is the
Is coupon a thousand touch
What is Trump do
2000 Koontz
Why won't he appoint special counsel
Can I connect to Facebook
Get the message
He's watching Fox News at night and they won't talk about it
So he believes that Trump is in so much Danger from this
He's been
From the wilderness
What have you
I love him compared to Hillary Clinton and Michael Moore
Which is basically I'm saying I love Trump compared to people I think are the devil
People I think smell like
Sulphur
So that doesn't mean
Watertown
Sudo globalist
Fox
They won't tell him the truth
Growing frustration
Yeah he might as well say I I mean
Look I love Ted compared to Hillary Clinton
And of course your
This whole like Trump possibly
National Emergency
Pining for and all that stuff
Our recording time we have no idea
All we've heard is all the talking
If he does that I think it'll throw a wrench into the gears and type in terms of Alex
No matter what
I think that there is a tie
Turning away from Trump
The appearance that trumps victories are his victories and all that stuff
I don't foresee situation when Alex ever turn
Entirely on Trump
Until Trump does something
Along the lines of
Actually recognizing the white supremacy problem anime
I don't think he's ever going to do that
But I would be the point
Yeah everything else
He's cared so deeply about
He's turned his back
Things like a Rex 84
Things like
Posse Comitatus
Eccetera conditional
Because drop is doing them in some sort of a white nationalist
Hey minutes next Cliff we have another example of
This one was really f****** hard to hear
This isn't Alex turning his back on another one of his really big
Deeply-held position
In order to support
What he wants Trump to do
I don't know exactly how it is.
Is there a way that Trump could possibly use the continuity of government
Following the Fallen for the
I mean it's getting bad in this week
The cops wouldn't
Accomplish
Global control
Awake
Yes we are going towards
Martial law
War
Where next
Convoluted loaded nonsense
But I would really love to see martial law
I'd love to see Trump.
Continuity-of-government things that I've been screaming about for years being super terrible at
Use those
Just so sad all these Domino's that keeps falling of his like his life's work is entire career
Being thrown away
Is wild it really gives you a cautionary tale about like
What it's like to not have
Unconditional
That principals
Matter
Because what
As intrinsic
And unconditional
Priority
For you
And then when
Just waffle on those priorities
It really calls into question
Senor believability about it
F****** stupid
Stupid
Double edged sword
Like what it seems like now all he really cares about is his side winning
And it seems to be true with all of the right-wing
Like
I would say
Many of them know how shity it is in Congress
So many of them know how shity of president
Trumpets and once he's gone they will all pretend that it never happened and that they were
They were all resisting from the inside I will give you a million dollars inside
Probably accurate that says in 2 years they're all like we were all secretly resistance
I believe that just go back to everything
It's fine I don't know use the memory of this. Of time
Kajol
The point is
Are you
I'm interested to know if this is how it is always been or if there was a
Turned around the propaganda that was built up when
There is no government like it whenever
What's his f*** McConnell said I'd make sure you're a one-term president
It stopped being about
Governing at all
Yeah I think
Keith has always been there
Loyalty to the party
Or whatever
But to the extent
I don't know who I'm bananas
From
I have been able to do I think this is
Very different
Another.
I'm not even talking about Obama because it'd be too easy to point out how I obviously stupid this is
If you just talk, declared a National Emergency to build a wall
Rubble as white people just started lighting themselves on fire in the
Majesty f******
H.w. bush
Emergency
Everyone
Lazy
Problem
Talk about
Thoroughly
If Trump does declare a National Emergency in order to build this wall and stuff like that
Beer that you have to stop immigrant
The emergencies immigrants state of emergency
Point of what Noah's allowed
Right is that
Is that it
What do you think Stephen Miller f****** idea nobody else comes
Ever again I understand
I'm not lightly rhetorically
At what point would you ever
Resend that state of
You can always use it as a
Yonder
What level of immigration
Because it's never going to be
You're never going to get to a point where there's nobody coming
I didn't tell them
Adidas
That is the end of the even idea of America
I agree
Spiritually
The point
The logistics of it
AR
Innocent
Create
Perpetual
State where
Like you are in this emergency
I don't believe that states of emergency work the way that Alex
Like I don't believe that if you create
State of emergency in order to build the wall all the sudden
You're a Duke
Or whatever you call Larry Nichols
You are
He run forever
I don't believe that's necessary
But I do believe that there are certain things
Can do to override
Powers
If it's such a vague
Conceived
State of
I have to like I want to build this wall to keep people out
It's not going to work and I'll get a
People out
So
The conditions that require you to Build That Wall
Are never going to necessarily
Right you haven't you have
An untenable situation
I mean it does introduce the idea of
It's just a big flashing neon sign this is fascism
It's amazing it just says fascism
Well here's the reason why you should also be more
Alex
There's a lot of stuff
I think that he crosses
Align
In this episode
We talk about lines across is quite a bit
I think it's important as you listen to this next clip
Remember that earlier in this episode on February 11th
He's talking about
Resent
According to him
Being over religion is incompatible with America
In all that National Emergency
The erratic
Rank islamophobia
That seems to be one of his picadillos on this episode
I want you to remember that because that was the same episode
It was intense and awful and Target
It was a very targeted
And then he said stuff like this
Towards the later part
If stuff goes into a Civil War photos
You don't go down and damaged trade
Okay
You don't even go out the police you know who the enemy is
Absolutely critical
I want to warm as hell
Another
They're going to get one
Don't shoot
Child
Just understand it's on
Going to wait this out in Kauai
People in those areas that have already made Santa Claus
Everything is going to go down because of the global it's me
Here
Screw this country screw our children over all this crap
Blowback
What do you think's going to happen my friend I appreciate your call
That is so f***** up
That I know that he's
Couching is language so much in the
Starters but we're already planning
Kill all of you
That's crazy ideas
Kill
That's so
Locked up
Which part
Yeah I like
Order to kill globalist
Is idea
You know
Kill the globalists
And of their operatives
Whoever their operatives are off
Because earlier in the episode he even said it's like
People
It was a very
Close to like trans people are globalist operative
Notnot 0121
Definition
He said earlier in the show
Kill the globalist and their menu
If their minions are the people who are the people you demonize
Then
This is when she gets back to go kill those people that are on board with the infowar
And that is not acceptable on anyway
Even if you're saying it with his conditional if she pops off with him that is not okay
Cuz if I've heard him call for murdering
People all the time
I think the thing that blew my mind is that he was talking directly to a person
I just want to talk about
Stuff
And he's like
All I'm saying is you should probably be ready to kill
Womack
Cool music
I returned a lot of things about my life if this is the guy omelet
Your car and Ice down the road you get like really excited
Like there's no way to describe that caller ID
Directions
So now when you hear stuff like that it's really
Cost because on one hand
It's not illegal I guess
Because what you're saying is
We're going to f****** kill you and your people
Or whatever
So there is still like I'm not encouraging violence or whatever
But
It does introduce a really interest
Question Alex never answered
And that is when is Bataan
Yeah what is the point at which
It is now necessary to kill
Unfortunately Alex gets another color
Oh no
This caller
He said some really creepy about being inside globalist and then he asked
Alex
The time is
Which is exactly the issue that is so vague in the way Alex percent
This is Mike.
Listen to what his f****** answer is
I have stood next to Nathan Wolfe came up
Is it dark outside
That's exactly what these bastards
I can't wait to
Deliver them to the bottom of the Davy Jones * 10
We watching
I don't know what to do
Former military police officer
Well I
Goes off
What's the Catalyst going to be
But
Bulimic
We should hold back
When you have a situation where you're saying that there is a
Conditional point at which in order to save America we will need to kill our enemies
If someone calls and talking about the idea that I'm inside people's houses
I know I don't even understand
Eyewitness
And your responses
I think we'll know it when we see it
You are now giving them permission to to find the point when they know it
You'll know when it's time
If you feel like it's time go ahead and kill that global
Very unstable
Subway the longer call I think he's
He's very creepy
I have some rest
But he's far from the most unhinged
I think that's kind of
Bigger problem I would say
His seeming like
Like not to armchair psychologist
Any of this
That guy sounded like he was looking for permission to kill
Yeah
So
Permit 280
I mean that that's what I like
Now it would be one thing if Alex was literally saying
Or whatever
That would be cut and dry fat is
Something they
You that's cry
This is the most cowardly way to do the exact
Message get out yeah but beyond the technically on the right side of the law
You're telling people there is a time
When you see it
It's just sort of being like I want this to happen
But I refused cake
Responsibility
A saying that I wanted to
I don't know I don't I don't think it's illegal but I'm
Right
Pretzel
F***** up yeah that's really f***** up illegal
Somebody go see a therapist
Bad place right now
Gross
Rhetorical question
I would say the question of when
Is a revolution necessary
Lego
United States Revolution
What was that
We got a couple sent text Auntie killed
Nevermind
But you look at you look at the situation that we're in now
I don't know what the point is
I suppose it's whenever democracy completely breaks down
Right I don't know I don't have a definition
Myself
Larger cam
I don't know
It is not a question to
Just given like a
Hey you'll know when
Because especially with
Qanon
Internet world
Evolve to the point it is now
A lot of ideas of what would be a triggering event of something
You don't know who you're talkin
Person has some sort of a belief
The Trump is going to do XYZ is going to be
Some tweet of his as to be like right
You might end up
Show me people show up so many places with guns and Fire
Tremendously dangerous
That's the most generous thing I can
You can say about that
It's so irresponsible
It doesn't
Help Alex at all
I don't help his bottom line
His audience already
This is very stupid
Andrea Lee
When you being sued about Sandy Hook stuff in like
Causing
People so much pain
At the families of the victims
Stop
I can't imagine being
Make a person who
Food court
The possibility
Of recreating that scenario
The inability to learn
From past mistakes
Like he's probably out
That is true
Just
I don't know your Reptilian Brain
Would kick in where it's like
That dog bit me now I'm careful about dogs never
Selfie
Don't do the same thing
Used to do it
We're done with the 11
Episode
Exhaust
I was
F***
I don't want to just do an episode about
Friday show that would be crazy now that was heir to the listeners to the 12th
Thank you very much
13 interesting weird stuff
Inside it it's not a great show
McGinnis shows up
At the end of the episode along with this guy Ali Alexander
And like I couldn't avoid
Does a character he leaves and comes back
His brother-in-law
It's
Hilarious
Great the desperate attempt to get people to share the video and get free Buzz Marketing ride
It's also just bad as comedy there's no
Commitment
There's no why there was no evolution
Hacking
And also the right is really great
I don't know if you know this but the right is really taking over call Joseph Watson
They're really getting
Thrilled to see what they've got
I love
Nick DiPaolo
Whatever
Gavin's on basically because he's suing the splc
That's not going to go well
That's not news
Whatever
Thank you
Pieces of information
This episode
And the first
Is Ally
Narrative lie
But he's telling about a recent murder in New York
And how it relates to abortion
Fishman reportedly
This woman
More than their stomachs
Partial birth abortion
I guess YouTube
The police say sorry
Doesn't matter that the baby was
Nope
It probably goes that thing but I was kind of making
Shut up here
Arabic story
Because there's a conversation
Abortion
New York has become sort of
Focal point of it
I meant unfortunately also this murder happened around
It's creating
A very convoluted conversation in the right wing
I think we need to disentangle Summer
Charged with homicide
You kill an unborn child
That is true
It likely doesn't really have any
Much to do with this
Particular murder case
Some of the language that was taken out of the legal definition of homicide included
Conduct which causes the death of a person or unborn child
With witches
Female has been pregnant for more than
24 weeks
Under circumstances concert
Attitude inverter
The victim of this murder Jennifer Irigoyen
Was 5 months pregnant
So it's unlikely that you was even past the point of
It's far more likely that this
What the situation was involved in her murder is
The prosecutors had an open and shut
The first-degree murder
And the prosecutor probably didn't want to tack on more charges that may or may not stick
Woody's going away for life
Kind of understand
Then why
Messed up in
This gray area
Buckstop right
Corrections
I need to make
To Alex's store
The first is
He didn't
The murder didn't stab Jennifer and stopping
Summit 32
Mostly targeted
He didn't yell quote die baby die
There was a neighbor who heard the attack who said that
The victim scream
About how he was going to
To kill the baby
Match
I think he's just embellishing
Get more emotional to his audience
And make a cognitively twitch
This murder
And abortions
I'm third thing is a big
Reason to change
Existing law in New York
Is because the law
Except criminalizing appropriate Healthcare
If you were a woman there who found under 6 months of pregnancy
Fetus in your room was unviable
Or wouldn't survive after birth
But your health wasn't
Risk it would be murder for the doctor
Remove the unviable
Fetus from your body
Essentially you'd have to go to a different state or live
For 3 months in the state of
Unbelievable emotional devastation
But no one should have to
New York state made abortions legal in 1970
Before Roe versus Wade
What is never update their state statutes
I thought the archaic language remained until very
Literally all the old language did was make it harder on women
Simpson cases like the one houses
About there's still plenty of criminal charges on the books
New language attitude
Clear the only permit
To perform abortions are licensed Healthcare practitioner
So the idea that this guy who is dabbing this woman that's just a late-term abortion is nonsense
It doesn't reply at all
Legitimately
All this is about protecting a woman's right to choose
And many other states are
For pastor York
And terms
Protecting that right
Even considering
This new
Update to the light
It isn't it tragic
Situation where that woman
Boyfriend
Wanted to murder her
Whatever is it
Motivation for that murder is
Was not public by the time
Alex
Let God on errands.
Go to talk about this.
Yes
He probably
Did also want to kill
I don't think that colors anything at all
I don't think that makes Alex's argument make more sense
I don't I think it makes everything
Certainly
But
It's dude
In Envy
And that's that's the thing that's amazing
To me about
The way that the right-wing is
Is always
But all they're really doing is harming women
Like with 24 weeks
What are they really criminalizing
Are they criminalizing doctors
No they're criminalizing women who are f******
Freaked out of their goddamn Minds
Who trained actually
Confirm anywhere because of 24-week laws or whatever it is
And a train selfie
That's what the that's what the law is
It is not a deterrent but it is not something that's going to help anybody
It is only something that is going to
Criminalize the very idea
Deal of being a woman as this debate has been happening
I don't think it is
It's
I mean like in the last month or so
A lot of conversations
In public court is going to overturn Roe v Wade
Who knows
Fairly sane
Because of this New York
Launch
It's triggered some of these
Everybody
Go and read
Some of the
Women
Who needed
Late-term abortions
We're not allowed to have
Those sorts of stories are very publicly available to sub you can find
New Yorker
Huffington Post recently
But if you read those stories
And don't come away with it
From that with a greater understanding of what
The actual issue is
Then you're not paying
There are
It really struck me in one of the articles that I read in the New York
Was the person who wrote the article is talking about
The argument
Legislative
Rules about abortion
Really hinges upon
Like they walk
Oh yeah
Yeah
Well I didn't even think about that
Yeah do you have to make laws is
Predicated on the idea that people is there
Which is the world's you Alex presents
VIP
Murder
Yeah reality every
Single.
Talk to or pee
People who have been in that
Situation
I'm not looking
To kill anybody
There
Looking
For appropriate
I think it's like 1% of all
Yeah
Never light
Decisions
And then when we say this
Somebody like Alex would say what about Coeur
Right
You have more typos
If you weren't in that position
Children Probz
That's not about abortion
As much as it is
I would still get arrested
Cuz of what he was doing
I can't about
I can imagine
7 months pregnant
And getting the news that
Your child was
Going to be stillborn
And then and then having to carry
Pregnancy
Knowing that
You're going to go through two months of
F****** hell
And then years of hell
That is
Unreal
End
Laura really protects
No documents
No ethically operating Doctor Who wouldn't have other reasons at their license
Should probably be under
Review whatever perform
Like late-term
Real late term abortion
When there wasn't a good
Whether it's the fetuses unviable outside of the body or is a risk to the woman
That's
So actually I had a bit of a naive position or just examined
Position of like
Jefferson Pointe there should be laws against abortion
From looking into this a lot of these stories
Looking at doctor's perspective
I've come around
To the point where now by position is
There should be no laws about it all decisions made between doctors
Quite frankly
Position
I100
I remember
Growing up
I remember being
So f****** serious
Hey I mean if you listen to the show you know a group of
If you're new
Welcome to the f****** Thunderdome I don't know what to tell you
And my
Vehemently
Anti-abortion
.
I remember being like 14 or
Knowing somebody who had gotten an abortion
And having them communicate
The entire thought process
And that was
It for me
I was literally like no
Whenever
It's your it's you
I don't even think a baby is he liked it until your conscious I don't even know if you're a real thing
Existence
It's not okay only hurting a person
People could have their basic reality would be handled by oversight
Regulation
The medical industry
Regulations are there could be strengthened
More oversight made
Right to make sure the people are operating
Nafaqo
Follows page
Wishes and they're not active
Ferociously
All of
The things you could hope
Two stalls
Legislatively or punitively
You could handle through approach
And I think it would
Protect
Vulnerable women
Armoire
Than any of this laudable absolutely
So
I don't know there's no there's no end is like
Pointing out hypocrisy now
Stupid
It's stupid they don't give a fuk
But the idea that the
Same group of people who
Want to make it in
Possible for a woman to get an abortion
What'd make it
Impossible not to own a gun
NeverEnding Lansing
NeverEnding landscape
There are even more
Daddy f******
Access
Preventative
Control
What's up
Darden favor of
Like white access to the morning-after pill
Contraception
An honest you don't women you don't want women to participate don't want women
At least then we can talk about that
Instead of all this crap that's their legitimate position
They said that you couldn't bring out over racism to win and they f****** did that
Ugly
I didn't enjoy necessarily
Alex
His take on it
The show on
But
He also
Get to
That's at 1
George Soros
MarketWatch
And it's about the troubles that are fake
They're a bunch of challenges from
Some things like that
Who wrote this op-ed
The challenges
European Union itself faces
How
It probably is going to lead down a very bad Road
Hey maybe there's some ways
They can change
The EU in order to
To preserve
You
Keep these people satisfied
Subway
Not necessarily
The article is basically the people need to wake up
To the idea that
The EU
We'll probably end up breaking up
What will come from that is
The same troubles that the USSR sauce
After
Yeah he wasn't comparing
The EU
The USSR
Imagine that accusation
An example of another large
Group
Ended up breaking up into constituent countries
Right in the EU countries are all still
Fairly Sovereign it right
Unique
He uses the Soviet Union as an example
Talking parrot
You know right
Just do this
That pretty much tell you what's going on because Business Leaders
Sophisticated audience Westshore
George Soros
Illinois
In the euro
Perceptive
Sounds like
He didn't say any of those
Those aren't in the article at all
Now it's
Interesting cuz I was like I read the article doesn't say that
Houses for sale
You think that is
One obvious example is
Maliciously lying
He knows that no one's going to go read the art
That's one possibility
Then he talks about it a little more
I start to think maybe he's only read the
Infowars article about this
George Soros
Who starts talking about
Post
On Infowars
Actually way worse than even that
Let's go to California
Europe
Maybe on the cusp of a nightmare
It's not too late to wake up
Eroded George
Read this passage
Infowars.com it's right to the quotes
Future new world order
The USSR
For my 20 years plus on air
USSR
Alex's throws like a somebody read the headline
Twitter an uproar over Soros
Comparison
So I went to Infowars
That headline
That's not a boil down on Infowars
That's a reposting of a Sputnik article
That is Infowars reposting a Sputnik article critical of George Soros
It's crazy it's crazy
Paul Joseph Watson did a report this is a boil.
A little bit for Christ's sake I don't
But never have any
Clean reporting or anything like that
But I will say
To do with
The USSR and George Soros and it's coming from
I'm going to say good friend going to say it's not bias it's not good
Or however
Not good when I saw it
It's when you put an article in a pot
Potters reloading the article doesn't realize
No I mean a boil down is basically
Just
Taking
Cirrhosis
It is genuine whatever it is that that
Means
And idea enough to know that
A human being should not be allowed to read that
The fun game
Reply but what's really fun about it
What is he does most of it in his evil Soros
Voice it would take us all day
To listen to him paragraph
Because he just said for making through two paragraphs
Here's the clip
Of Alex doing it
Critical error in his ability to read
Which I've always said his
Literacy is
The problem
I'll just tell you what
He thinks that the article says infection inflection
The upcoming elections
Infection point
Affection
It deceives Alex
Island
Miss Whitton touched advocate.
First
Psoriasis name
He's gone off on this infection risk
Yeah this is not going to
In his ear van like
Inflection point is what the ark electricity
Good ristobar
In a second
He's going to do another run
For sure you going to realize
Bankrupt him before we kill him
Upcoming European elections oh George the best
Laid plans of mice and men often do
Stray
Infection
Project project project
So he just does it again misreading of the article
I kind of wish
But also actually if you go to Infowars I don't know what
Bought their using
But I can understand how out
Miss that out
Yeah I'm not getting lost you should f****** know better and it's his website
New Roman
Hey Goodrich
He hasn't read this article that's on Infowars
But naked doesn't know what's going on
He just thinks he finds a word and
Respond it
About that at all
To the 13th
Wednesday
This episode
Nothing
Fun places
But we'll start it goes to
Some places yes
Google start here with I'd like to remind you
The weather
Islamophobic is s***
Personally told his audience to murder is out of me
Yes
Also perpetuated islamophobic ideas that were completely inaccurate Muslim countries now.
On the 11th
A group as an other friend then suggest
His audience that they should prepare for that other group
Ensure that when that other needs to be killed supposed to be killed
And then on the 12th
Soros was supporting a Hitler
Plan well yeah and he doesn't see the
I do agree with your assessment
But I'm more interested in
Like he was
Way off base on the 11
Particularly about the Muslim country
Then on the 12th
He's off on this New York abortion
Crazy far-field is Angela
And then at the same time
Doesn't disclose to his listeners the decision
And Miss Reed's inflection as infection
Hey just does this weird.
Soros
Do everything has been terrible
Like from a professional standpoint commercial back on the 11th
Dogs fight with
Is how he starts to show on the 13
Not particularly focused today and I've got
Broadcast have been particularly piercing
Research reports
Everything because of the times demand it
Individual
That is
Narcissistic bulshit
Especially considering how bad is show is been lately
This is gross stuff like that about me all the time and that's because I'm so down to earth
It's not that I'm
Good at anything
What time is it
Choir memes
Step Up
And release my greatness into the world
If I were living in a less exciting time like perhaps
Good idea podcast
Probably not
It's the times that have made me cry
Sure
I don't know all this is to say that I Galaxy starting out like
Real focused
How to do a great job today
Is going to be amazing
In the show
Turbo Force
Before the show I don't know
I think he's just he's just feeling himself
Not judging
But
Issues
And unfortunately
Like you did
Continuity-of-government stuff
He now invalidates one of the only things
Things that you and I
Mutual
What is it say that we should be legalized marijuana
Procedure General
Inside tonus
Unconstitutional
It stopped
But on the border
Bar
The door
Boats.
It's just
El Chapo
Right there
He's talking about the ideas like season all of El Chapo's
Settling
Convicted Now in America
Probably
Properties
Like the Mexican
I think those are Mexican and we can just kill them
Even muddying the waters
Because in order to
Create this wall
Property property
Like it's not the idea just
The Civil asset forfeiture argument still involves the idea of life
This is going to get into these people's properties
If you want to build
Otherwise why do you own property
That's not the
So the idea that I was bringing up like the Civil asset forfeiture when it's not civil asset forfeiture in terms of
El Chapo's property
Or assets is a preparation
Being fine with the eye
Idea up
People who have property
Having a property
Aiken
In order to
Yes order to
The wall
He's doing this as a preemptive
Waffling
That's a bummer
But
What can you do
Hey the more the more we dig
The more he talked
Amorous
You have to real Prince
White people should own guns
Those are the only
It's the two pieces together.
Chocolate and peanut butter
Next
Women are incapable of
Defending our speech
Women and children down there still got to be men
Real quick I got a pause because he's
Banging out
I know I know and Depeche Mode
Truth is
And it's hilarious to me because Alex twice
It's so clear that you
He's going through
And the lyrics to that song are like
Really right Wiki
The whole song is all about
You're going through some troubles now everything is bad because of your youth
Adopted a Policy of Truth
Yeah
Wants to believe about himself
He's playing at a bunch like
I love the idea
His emotion
Eastbound down roundabout are Trucking
I'm going to steal me a Silver Stallion
You're being persecuted because you told the truth
We're playing our of Elliott Smith
Bereavement flights
Depeche Mode
One of them
How many start the cliff over cuz I want to hear more about
Women and children down there still got to be men
Global experiment
Fusion to Arrested Development
Independence BC she really don't
Species
Week
Weeds
Yeah that's that's pretty crazy
Matrilineal Societies or I'm not going to go
Okay
Well within
Normal
At what point
Does defending the speed
Just turn into murdering other
I mean there's a thin line for Alex
The five percent Nation nation of gods and Earths
You cool and when I was hearing Alex talkin about this this PC
Who can
Protect it
It kind of made me
I heard echoes of it
You know it doesn't stay in the 5% nation release
Play the classical
Understanding
Next put out it was the idea that the black man
Was God and the black woman was
Was there earthquake
And they lived in this sort of like
Symbiotic
The god over the Earth
The Earth supporting
God
Alex is describing a very similar relationship
Between men and women
You take out the Islamic roots and
You know all that stuff
You're talkin about are the ones who protect the species in Brandon
Play the subservient role
Without the man the women or nothing
Right there is the exact same sort of dichotomy there
Have we considered letting women
Instead of like the men
Having a symbiotic relationship with the women
Just letting women have all the control and then keeping men as pets
Has reconsidered the Ghostface Killah
Is actually Alex Jones
That could be true
Now their body type
No
That's a lot of nonsense
Over the course of the last like that are no sense Rodger got arrested
Alex has been really
I would say
With restraint
F*** off
We've heard on the show him being like
Stop I know I'm pissed off everyday
That sort of thing on this the 13th
Alex says
I mean this is Patty
This is Alex. I like it
He is
Joel mad at Rodger Stone
But he can't get really mad
I really think of
Rodger Stone
F******
If we fight
How do you know too much about me
Angel
Knew him a little bit and he knew stuff about you
Never fight with him you would let whatever I don't know parasail
Glide gently down to the jail that is in going to prison
Chocolate metaphor
So it is next with Alex
Go f*** himself
Cypherden
Rogers friend
But he Doles out exclusive yes I'm the Fox News
Shanda Daily Caller
He works here
Take a shower
IPhone chair
It calls for comment on this like 10 minutes ago
Shovel
Rodger stone is filed lawsuit against
What you should say
Before
That's incredible
Picked up yet
District court for the District of Columbia
Found today
Rodger Stones motion
The show-cause order
What's good
Bulldogs
Command Center
Rodger Stone has been charged with h that goes on from there
There's a document writer
Waterstone at work to the Gateway pundit
Rodger
Check my other phone
Maybe hold this other phone
Don't that look like
Where are we
Alex is the best girlfriend through a bad breakup
Pint of ice cream renew Studio
Call Kimmy Gibb exposed to the Gateway pundit I pay a salary works there now
Maybe there's no way he thought on that phone was
You piece of s*** giving work retreat with Delilah from the
The office no she's just don't work friend I get it
Kevin Delilah the exclusive
Cuz you know they have more penetration into non in vain people than I do
That is childish
I love it
You're working with Rodger Stone
The show Alex discusses
Signifiers of races
His life
No
This is part of a conversation
The yard Virginia
Hey
I'm not thrilled that either
Thoughts
About
And then we get back
To his
Ball drop
Entirely
Joe Rogan
If you make dressing up in a KKK outfits
Which I think is the context
That is the capital
So apparently black face and wearing a Klan outfit
Yeah
I don't know if I support
Lime
Necessarily
Very hard I hope everybody got that probably is a Halloween costume
It would be okay
Honda
Fun of the clan with the cost
Yeah
What if you were able to find some way to make a statement out of the
Larger design of the costume all except that contact you would like that person
That would also
Sure
I'm saying
You could stretch Alex
Yeah. Haha
He is absolutely saying that sometimes black face is pretty cool
Inflated throat politically or whatever
Responding it just didn't go great for it
Alyssa nurse
A clip of Rogan
Years ago
Talking about
It's like a 30-second clip I'm not sure
It doesn't matter with contacts
He's talking about going to see the planet
In like a mostly black neighborhood
You go to the theatre and Rogan says I walked into theater and we walked
Which is richest racist on its face
But as Alex keeps trying to
Who is conversation
Rogan is a comedian
Antojitos
You trying to Walk This Way
He's like
I'm not
You said that
Because you're
You're not a racist
I'm in the process
He talks about how Rogan has a couple black children
He's adopted
Which you don't want people to know that it's not public
I don't know if it is or isn't it but it isn't really f***** up right now
In terms of putting Jose business in the street
And not because they're black children or anything like that
His personal life that he tries to keep
Whatever whatever it is like a human
She has adopted or
Whatever the case
She doesn't want that there that is
Right
Keep private
Because
In the same way
Alex
Professor tranky
Keep his children
Private
You have a right
To that as a public figure
Your children aren't
An extension of
Yourself right if Rogan was trying to keep
Information about his kids
And Alex's
Just blowing hard
Service argument that I'm not calling you a racist
Because
The children are black
Bad
Alex
Yeah
Yeah this clip of Rogan being
Being race
Right
He's trying to walk a weird line with
With that to where he's like
If I said stuff like that
Everyone will be mad at you me
But you get away with it
Good laugh
The left would pillory me for this
Because what they do is fine
Clips and bring it to everyone's attention to attack person
Right Edge literally 1121
An example of
But how you get away with
So Alex is going to discuss.
We get into it
I just want to make clear that I don't
Support
This b*******
You know I don't think
I don't think Rogan's right
IFixit Alex is right in his criticism
F****** racist absolutely
The context is there than he's making
Is correct
Alex is the wrong person to make that assessment
Right big much like the people
Complaining about representative
Bar
Being anti-semitic and save tweeted out
Soros memes
Incapable
Making this argument
Without it going
So far off the rail
I can't stress this
Alex has no business
Being involved
Helps no business
And as I'm saying
It goes off the
So hard
So fast
Alexandra
So racist
In trying to
Condemn Joe Rogan
For this 30-second clip
Of Joby
So here's the first clip
Eyewear Alex discusses that clip of Rogan
And then
It's crazy to me how fast this goes bad
Because it didn't have to
Here's how he gets away with stuff like this all the time everyone comes down on
Call me for my speech
Please buy brain
I'm a victim by virtue of this existing and no one yelling about it
Vibrate for whataboutism
Writ large without any like and also here's why it's fine for me to be right
So fat
I've been destroyed and then you sit there
And compare black people to Planet of the Apes
Who are you
Beyond blackface
And I supposedly A-OK
Racist
World champion
I'll stand there.
White people
Where the super Supergirl
You can have the whole left this thing
Bro
Do it
The Westbank
Joe
You can't compare black people to Apes
Also
So you were right
What
What was that
Who is Brave
Speak the word those were
It was a
Rippling
Roebling point
I don't understand
It's to make Rogan look worse
What is it
Yeah
How
I'm not sure if you can look worse
Self look like
Come on
As it was
Cold
Pretty solid tip I got my wires crossed
For some reason the newest one was the Burton one
Did I ever tell you about why would you do that other than to make yourself look like that came out back when I worked at that
Movie theater
On Thursday nights
The projection is to build the movie and then you have to screen it
To make sure that
You built it correctly
You turn into a party
And so all of us would get together
Cedar are managers were over 21
Everybody can rule.
None of us just watching a movie the night before it comes out getting wasted
Remake of Planet of the Apes
I threw most of it we're drinking we are having
A real bad
Is a bad movie
He wasn't the one about us
He was like the whole time at the end when they're like
You coming back
The resolution of the movie
Flying back
And Washington
Rick is just sitting there with his arms crossed
Abe Lincoln
A blanket
Add shot in April
Literally fell to his knees escaped
Burton I've been in full I've been in full movie theaters
Anna movie
Music explosion mostly empty movie theater memory will live with me till the day I die
F****** die
See I'm not sure what Alex is trying
I don't think
He's ventured
How far
Into racist
Territory
Condemning
Dirosa problems
I think he's
Dancing around ideas that he wants to make belt like all of it look
Is there a mutual dependence
Prefer to say
Whatever puts
Simultaneously trying to defend race
Excuse racism
And condemn
At the same time
Right
It gets worse
Even though it is
Conditionally
Because of where we're going to
Go
His next Cliff Alex talks about going to a party where people weren't
This party items
As a plural his thing
I don't think
This sounds like a lot of stories
This
To be like he got invited to a
Legit blackface party
I don't know if that was the
The theme of the party I don't know
Questions
Explain it
I don't like the
Governor Northam
He's just kill babies after they're born that's why
What are the South 2527 30 years ago a Democrat
Yeah
I showed up like 10 years ago
Because I don't want to have some celebration thinking I'm better than somebody
I'm sick of it
He was real yes people though
Racism
I know you're not racing
Itsfunneh
Interracial Joe switcher true like that
Most interracial p*** spot in the South and your older jokes about Lola
I don't like your job
The left wants to protect racism on everything
Yeah
Didn't happen
By the way also he shows up for Halloween
Party World
Yeah that doesn't sound right at all
I don't believe that
They were dressed up like a wrong
That's the only way
Just dressed like James
Malcolm X
Where you hold a card up over your head
Guess who you are and he was like
Problems with this clip of rogue
Whatever but I think of this next cliff
He criticizes
Is the wrong
Talked about it
His pretty much
How do you say your daughter is a night
Hey man it's you up on your sanctimonious hours here bro
Pull somebody's head off
I'll beat the big old black guy
Baby
But you
Pull crap like that
I can't imagine a worse 32nd
Of Annapolis
Yeah
Like very he's like
No black people in they found out who the real life
Inception is like
Three stages deeper in racism
That's the most racist
You can say
Zone understand
Alex
None of this is good
I'm a very goal-oriented
I win
I am also trying to
Yeah you're actionable towards the desired outcome
Is to make Joe
Look like a racist
Honestly
I think another goal that you would
The unwilling
Is
Make Joe feel the pain
That I feel
That would present weakness
I was like
I don't think
I don't think anyone knows how hurt I am
I thought he was my friend that sort of
That sort of thing would be unmasculine
You wouldn't allow him
Trying to show
That
Even though you have said some races
Just things in the past
I know you are not right
And you would not be pilloried
The same way that I am
For saying the racist things that I have braces
If your goal is
To do that
Your goal should also be
Not to be more of a racist than can be conceived of by Joe Rogan
In terms of
The things that Rogan said definitely
Sing in response to
Imply I'm about to have also so much of Alex's
Other things he's said in the past as we've documented
Over and over
Over again
On this podcast
Way more racist than Joe making a joke
That is absolutely racist
About
A black movie theater being playing video
Right
Alex's career as
Highlights
But it is more fun
In the same conversation Alex's beating
Worse than what that clip
Exactly
You know what
Joe you said that stuff
And that's racist stuff
And if
But at the same time whenever I say the n-word to Edwards
All the time
Alex
What makes it worse
I know that you're not racing
I know that you're joking
But I'm going to try and
You as if I believe
Do you were racist
I want you to whatever consequences of being racist even though I know why
Absolutely
Which would people say
And I would love to have that
Conversation
Look like that
What are you doing
Explains into like
Crazy
That was all
Outtakes
Another step
It gets even more racist
But if you thought that was bad
That was terrible how can I get worse
Well because he starts to bring pseudoscience
Guilty
Northern European
No
Average stop
For the highest IQ of any group of people
Put a. On that sentence now and just move on
Please
We don't need bell curve place you've got to stop
That on average white people or Japanese ride up there
Give Garcia
It doesn't mean
They're on that curve
Well for our Russian
Matters
Test isn't that stuff cuz
It's what you're measuring
I want to see this really quick
This is far too complicated of a topic for us to cover in-depth right now
Please everyone
Anyone is making an argument that there are differences and IQ that are attributable
Is doing Soca support white supremacy
Having a quote exchange of dangerous is there any b******* like that
Discredited Theory
An excuse to never have to confront the social cultural and
They've enjoyed
Which are built on the back of the social cultural and economic
Disadvantages
Other populations have been
Subjected to
The primary function of thinking along these
These narratives
Perpetuated is to create the appearance of a scientific sounding way to blame marginalized
Communities for their own marginalization
Pure and simple
Many of these ideas proponents are inspired by Charles Marie's 1994 book
The bell curve
Which Alex even
Find there's one book that everybody should light on fire
Brooke Marie
Completely Miss uses data to arrive
Coke near inescapable conclusion
The differences seem
Between white and black IQ scores as the result
Likes of Sam Harris
Notion of race
Positive differences
And IQ is taken on a new life.
These days when there is no basis in science
Around that
There are racial differences
IQ scores
But the idea of
Positive
The property between
Is a leap that is
Way too far
Deeply f*****
And it's one of the weird things
Allsorts
Savjz
Intellectual dark web worlds
Like you see it with Sam Harris and his acolytes
These people like Dave Rubin
It's coronavirus Diaz around
Stefan molyneux makes
A lot of mileage out of it
But it's not something
Sing that I've really heard Alex talk
Much about
And it's coming in the middle of a discussion of Rogan
And in the same ways it the last time he went
Load it off on Rogan
He did that Project Camelot impression
Where he started doing like
You back
Crazy things are
I think this is another return
This reference to the bell curve and race realism
And this nonsense
I think it's in a
Appeal to the listeners of Rogan show
That are the Sam Harris actor
People who are into
Disable Dia of like
Scientific racism
As opposed to emotional races
That
Did you tell him
Cuz he doesn't know this.
He's an ocean
He's present
In the Rogan
That's f***
Springs
I would much rather you be intellectually honest with yourself
Just say
I don't like people who don't look like me
Then try and pretend that there are
Genetic reasons
F*** off
F*** you for somebody who constantly says
F*** you
It's a coward the Cowardly way to couch
Whatever you want
If you were just like
I am uncomfortable with different
The only reason
Better is that
You with the actual issue
Exactly
Would you hide behind these sorts of
Over intellect
Actualized
You end up having to have conversation
They're pedantic
Nothing
And they rely on
Misusing studies overhears and stuff like that
Never end up getting
Lightworks
You can make progress
Towards what is underlying
Ford
No it's the new way of using the Bible to justify slavery really like the guy
What you just touchdowns
Is that like a lot of
These people in these
These these sort of race IQ science
Computer these days
Public policy doesn't really matter
Exactly gives a s***
Because these
Communities in these populations
Just intrinsically.
It doesn't matter if you give resources
Towards those communities
School and after-school programs
Stuff like that doesn't matter the radar cuz they are intrinsically worse which is a function
White supremacist
Whole point
The whole point you f****** nailed it
H2se
Let's not
Worry about putting
Resources
Into
Inglewood
Swan
It's science thing that
Englewood does
Deserve resources
And so and let's all just go away
No we're good people they deserve rights
Them put that takes it that takes away from those super high IQ White
Kids
Could use those
Right
There's go f*** yourself this very very complicated
Issuance
I think
Things that we've expressed
Tube bender
Invited to any public policy on
School debate
Nobody's nobody's asking me like
Hey Jordan how about you go participate
School in charter schools and all that
So in that last clip
European
I have a higher IQ because of
Being a European
With a higher IQ
That's white people's favorite thing to do is be like they're yellow
Not really
He even matches up with
IQ scores
Ashkenazi Jews
Much higher
But
But be that as it may
The issue
These like this
Because he is a white
He is gifted
With the tire
Japanese people are also in the mix
Up there
But then Alex starts
Alex
Clip about why
From where
Really bad idea people in his
Mcmillions
Have hierarchy
Accused
And it's a problem it's
Problem because what he describes as
The reason
These Europeans have higher IQ
From a evolutionary perspective
Trying to play
Did the Japanese
These people he also thinks
Have iiq and it falls apart
I know you're chomping at the bit I'm sorry
Please
Black people
John
Wife has the highest IQ
Well you better have an IQ
Thousand years in Frozen Wasteland
Africa
Terraria skin
How fast you were
What about long-term strategic thinking
Here and I criticize Joe
Black people dude
We are
Electricity has airplanes in Wipeout
Isn't it funny that they throw at the board
Which fails to that's it
And also
Really terrible like
I don't fully understand exactly
That's trying to
Put forth
So the idea of like you have to get home at a certain time
Fresa.
Therefore intelligence
Uvalde
But
He also is saying that in
In around the equator
You had to have
Cunning
Which is 2 mi a form of
Intelligent
Well I think
Suites in order
To deal with
Bokeelia
Auto kill you
There are a lot more cold.
Spin the wheel
That's yes
I mean that's just
Atlee
It's it's
Deeply
Anthropological
Hunting
Cunning is the
Very race
This way that people miss it
Well
Describe
LeBron James isn't very smart
But
He's really good at basketball because he's
He has a f******
Photogenic memory and can recall individual possessions like a goddamn
F****** Savant it's the word
Particular
It's the code word to describe intelligence
People that you don't want
To ascribe to
T-shirts of arguments of always
Today they are
Used
Recycled
And it's
It's gross
It's incredible growth
Now at the end of that clip
Alex
Yeah I'm not I'm not on board with that specific example
It's hilarious
Is OverWatch
Because none of them are attributable to watch
Awesome it's so awesome
Cuz that would
Terrible
In the middle of the
I think about this a lot
The way she goes out to break
Is always so triumphant
But whatever you saying it was
The middle like you had to do 5 more minutes to go
Most of the time
Did Leanne order rile people
I do all that s***
Breather
Have a shot of whiskey or whatever
So the three things he chooses to talk about the people
Besides for our electricity airplanes and Medicine
Now let's look at those things one-by-one the real history behind them
To start talking s*** to
Electricity research
Electricity may have been developed in harness by largely European scientist
But there also was a theory out there that between * 650
To 150
BCE
People living in
What's now a wreck
Had knowledge of electroplating is evidenced by the archaeological find called the Baghdad battery
People are kind of split on the hypothesis put but there's a lot of controversy about this
People who have
Of what that artifact
Actually used for
And whether or not it was actually Eve
Even the battery
So honestly Europeans may be able to take credit for most of the
Electricity
But that baby Drew
Although there were also cultures who the word for lightning is exactly the same thing as the word
Electric eel
Understanding of the nature of of Alexa
Just some expense but that doesn't
Steps made two harnesses
Also spoiler alert
Baghdad battery
Because of the 16 years of
Pretty much consistent War
Whatever progress could be made
Towards finding other
Evidence to
Reinforce that theory or anything
Nothing like that
Memorex
There will never actually
I think it's very interesting
Possibility
That was a battery
But it's also possible that that hypothesis
Is entirely wrong
It's just the
The finding
Various
Possible
Accepted version of the reality that Alex is operating under is that like for Aviation
Brother's got a crazy idea
And then created the technology Idaho
Unfortunately that is not accurate at all
Legends of people flying go way back but probably don't
Depict reality
For instance like Icarus probably didn't actually have wipes
Galveston
Do all the ship
However.
Concepts involved
In the development of Aviation the roots are not in the West
In China in the fifth century BCE Lou Brock
And Moody
I invented the kite
And immediately after that fact after that development
Interesting application
New technology
Their contemporary contemporary reports
It's done kites were able to lift man into the air
But the first
Man flight
Ever occurred in China in
Using kites
Technology
The idea for many of the elements that would allow the
The creation of the helicopter words
From a bamboo
Vice that was
The underlying technology
Hot air balloons of stimuli understood by the
Back to his far back
Isaac 3rd century
Much of the advances
Invented in
Longest
But never took their there took the logical destructive
Endpoint Technologies
Which I don't know if they could have developed
Maybe they could have
Also possibly maybe they weren't
Do you know
Baby baby. They developed all of the underlying technology
Housing
Yours back
So
No
It's basically just
These
People who grandfather's at 8
Long discovered
Leeks
Principles that were invented by the
Thousand
Sears ago
Medicine is the worst thing for Alex to give Europe
I'm guessing he's just talking about like
Deciding that Hippocrates was white
And I'm assuming that it goes back to
That's what it was
Penicillin
In reality that was Jonas
Yeah in reality that was him looking at
So many you
Middle East
Like I think that I was just
Knows about the Hippocratic Oath
Start
Herbal medicine dates back to like well into the 2,000
BCE
Egyptians
Clearly had Physicians working in the Palaces
Hammurabi's Code which states
1800 BC
Prices
Charge it even explicitly discusses the idea of
Put the surgeons can charge
Sure
Yeah
Many many papyrus
From Egypt from 3000
Is a 800 zaidi person scientist
Allie Evans
Robin altomari
I wrote the world's great names
World's first Encyclopedia of metal
Am 1020
Amara Ben Ali all of my swamp
Performed the world's first successful ice
We could go on and on listen
Stanley non-white non-western influences in the development of Medicine
But it would take all day
We've arrived here where we are today
The entire world has been apart of
Enter selectively erase non-white history
Definition
A product of whites
Supremacist
The larger Point here is that white people or the West
Has been responsible for a ton of great Innovations
Inventions over the
History
Thank them
For it
This is a profoundly f*****-up way to look at the world as if Alex somehow deserve credit
For someone who shares his skin pigment
I'd like to propose a healthier way to look at things
And that is to honor
And celebrate
All cultures
Across the world who has helped lead us to where we are today
Inner Mastery over
Light
Because I think that's a better way to look at things
We've all shared in
This history
Some of the things that the Islam
Sonic World
Help
Create
Stones upon which
The Western world
Could use as staircases
And if we all know if it weren't for anything we wouldn't have control over the
I'm guessing it's a Dragon Ball Z reference
Collaborative effort
There's a collaborative effort
It goes on
Any history
Aldi's
Trucking Brown
Sanko all of us white people for
Airplanes in Madison
It's just it's disrespectful
Instrumental
Meeting the reality that we have now
Like if you just want to pretend
Created the jet
Did it
Out of nowhere
So what you're doing is erasing everything that came before it
You're erasing the
Of largely Dawn White
Plain and simple
There's no way around
Absolutely
History
Dear of invention
Is
So
Furiate Angley
Associated with
Person
It took
Thousands of years and thousands of people working on it
When the Library of Alexandria
It's like
Florida
Knowledge of the world just destroyed
Like we have
DIA
How much was invented prior
Destructive acts by white people
You know how how many times can you think of something where is like
Destroy the history of the world and then they were like yeah but we invented
That
Isn't to say that wifey
People are in
Impulse
People exist
Like it wasn't White
People who looted these Museum in Iraq
13 husband
Other cultures
Other non-white cultures have also done that to other
Like Warring States
And stuff like that.
That's that's what if
Adorable
Destroyed every chance
Profoundly reducto
Look at the world
In such a way as
This person invented
I agree with that
Because there are so few
2 inventions
In the world or even
Breakthrough
Renovation
Attributable to a single poop
It's always
On the shoulders of giants
But others
Even like
When you talk about like the Library of Alexandria
We could have lost their
Put your mind into a place is like
What Festus
What I'm more interested in on some level
The Erasure of
Failures
Because a lot of things
Contributed to
Like our ability to
The fly or ability
Have a coherent Medical
Even electricity
Is people doing failed experiment
That lad
People
Away from the Snapchat or whatever part of
That's where we are
Even to most of legitimate history also set
Often forgotten like
Like he had pictures of people that he thought were in Africa
Didn't have heads but instead had faces on their f******
Orso's
Bulshit
Inspired by
Fanciful ideas
Reality that
The real world
I hear stuff
It really bums me
Because
Because it's also
Completely unintentional
Which is the way Z episodes
Is this
Beginning of the episode
He's erasing the history
Of
Female politicians
In the
Arab and Islamic
Expensive
Disgusting
Because it's presented world
Beware
Muslims are all Savages
Mets
That's disgraceful
Wheatley islamophobic and it's
Counterproductive towards
And then we come to the end of the episode Mustang
Thanks for these things
They brought the world
Are you look at the actual history
Call Vinson
When you deal with it on a more realistic
He's erasing all
These other cultures that he doesn't
Muslim world
Inventing the concept of
You right there's no
I know it
Then you have to thank everybody for s***
You're always going to go back to
Event where do you do that if you do that
All you do is think the Chinese
Irish descent
The Chinese invent
Whiskey sour
Cultures that work
There are still around
Innovative
Really basic
You come down to like
India and China
So
Pivotal
Absolutely especially like mesoamerica
Plumbing
They're places in 300 in Central America that I would rather live in
Then 1584 run
You know for life
If you play that game where you're going to end up with is something that Alex doesn't
Which is that
It isn't
Western
White cultures
Created
The building blocks
The innovation
That the Western Way
He's dead
And I only
Understanding
Help us all
Understand
Doesn't demonize white
People it doesn't take any
Anything away from the Innovations Western
Culture
Only build more robust on
Understanding of how we're all in this
You're right
Inform
This person's idea
Your idea helps
You come up with a better idea later
All of us wouldn't even f****** exist
If all of this other s*** hadn't happened
You're probably right on that
Mathematics
Created by white part of my IQ test
Play f*** you what are you talking about
Alex talks
Leo zagami
For a bunch
Alex
He threw up
F****** liar with an accent
Nut
I'll listen to work
I think I
Can
I've met
Yaks
Find myself
Noni
So he talks about the
S*** that's going on in the
The Vatican
I honestly turned it off killing everybody it off like five
Whatever they're going to come up with
Like whatever
Let's imagine the most Sensational lie Alex
Can come up with
About the pope and the Vatican
With Leo zagami
Maybe
And also I don't give a s***
You know like I don't
I'm not going to
We're already almost
3 hours and
Episode
I was like
It can only be a rehashing
Two of them have already said
Whatever
I don't I don't Point could point but Alex does
Which is the last quote
About how
Is that four out of five
Sergei
Now paint
Is that result from the latest Rascal Rasmussen poll
Because
Because Etienne
The cliff
Stores
Oh no
Anytime you get a very
Very
Intense look
But I didn't work
Pay close attention
Because
This is what is
It is
5 Seconds
Alex
Tells on himself
He just point the finger at him
He thinks he's being
Magnanimous and super accepting
Everybody
It's so f*****
Catholic priests are gay
Homosexuals make coffee
The population
I don't judge anybody
45 years
You are
My children
You know two dudes together like A3
The realisation of what's right and what's wrong is it
Literally the definition of the word he's literally saying that you do together is a 3
On the immoral scale between which is
Incredibly f*****-up
I have aborted my children
When I was a teenager
Which
Like legit
Straight up
Murdered
Humanizes women
By the way which subjects him to all of the punishments that he
Subjects others
Subjected to 27
So he should be if he wants to pull that s***
Then fine go for good let's do it let's do it all across the board
You are doing 20 years hard time now
That's the rule if you're going to pull your.
You think those people should be
God
Forgave him it's all good
It's all good
You are saying other p
Statute of limitations
Look dude that's so crazy to me
Because it's like that this like
It's A7
Yeah which to me is Steve for his conception of abortion should be
Sometimes it seems like
To be at least
Like maybe
It's got to be something to do
Do the devil
Precincts bedevils involved
Right
It's so great if
Which he thinks is murder
Is a 7
Then
To save it
Together
Which by the way is also
Inconsiderate
Custody is about the idea of men on men
You still there
So I also want to apologize I cut that clip a little bit too early
Immediately after this Alex starts
Reading London
Times article
The article's headline says
Infor
Or one in five
Yeah.
Evan never acknowledges that
He said
The exact opposite music
Intro to the same text Leo zagami it's a bunch of bulshit
Episode
I don't know
I find this
Hard to do
Necessary
I'm in this real
Place without
Alex Jones in Fresno
Because
In terms of like I think he probably should be
Thrown off the air
Which is the exact opposite position
First episode of this podcast
I'm there
Yeah because I do think that what we saw on the 11th on Mondays episode
Thought
That we covered
Language
View that is
Recently given permission to his spot
Yeah which is
Kill people
You'll know it when you see it
Better things
Looks like the Supreme Court form definition
I know
That's worth
That's not okay
When people are acting Wednesday
The Time to Kill
It's also. Okay if you're the Supreme Court
No
The question from a caller is Wednesday
The question from a caller who has a military background
That he is in other people's houses
Clear what is Art Basel
Do what he wants to do calling and asking Daddy give me the high side exactly give me the sign-in
Let's go give me a green light
Someone asks you that
Even if you're out
Has to be
Not you'll know it when you see it
Something
It has to be something like
Don't shoot till you see the whites in your eyes
Weird Revolutionary War
It's a reference today
Because they're so close to you that you can't help do it
I hate
And I honestly think there's no reason this has allowed to
Keep going
Like I don't I do think that we're at a point where we're past the
The point where this
Like I don't
Don't know the laws
Exactly where free speech
I really do
I feel spirit
Past this point
Because there's this trivial nonsense like
He's reporting on this Soros
When did
I don't know what to do
That
Very difficult
For me because
Like we have this now Trump
It's going to take
State of emergency
Create
I knew Whirlwind of b*******
And what have you
At the same time
In the
Sandy Hook lawsuit
Alex
It just came out today
The
Judge has decided
But Alex will have
To be deposed for 5 hours session
With the lawyers
And that's going to be
Sweet disaster
So I honestly
In ways that
You have not been subject
When he's
Define people
Is
Cruisin for a Bruisin
Like Huey's Auto
Towards
This could
Actually hurt
Yeah so there's some part of me that
Think we have
Responsibility
Now cover this as it
Because there is a
AAA massive down
Spiral
Wright Realty
I feel that pressure
It suck
Because also at the same time
Absent
Pressure
I think he's behaving in
That it should
This show shouldn't
Exist
The question is not that everybody
Doesn't agree with
Do you know what I mean like
Everybody agrees
Broadleaf probably
That Alex's show
As it is now
You should not exist
The problem with taking
To a quart
Is
You don't know how the cord is
Going to rule
So it makes
More sense to not rule on this
And then have the threat of a
Court action be available
Then have a Court rule on this against you
Because if the court
Listen to If the Supreme Court
Listens to this whole thing
And says actually this is protected
Speech
Then we don't know where the line
We don't know where the one
Because it's like this one world
I would rather live in a world where a broad spectrum of people
Greed set this is bad
Don't take it to the courts and we kind of handle this ourselves
Where is I don't want to live in a world where
We take it to the courts
They say that this is fine
And then we're in Uncharted Territory as to what isn't
Or the flip side
Courts and then a precedent
Crouching
Yeah
Ambiguous
Becomes suspect right just because Alex
Legitimately
As the first I'd rather err on the side of allowing Alex
And also talked about it everyone understand the danger of it
Then legislate
This is this should not happen
It's
It's a strange Place wherein it's important
To have the concept of free speech
Bu enshrine
Walk the same time have the ambiguity of what it is
As a
Fundamental concept
Do you know what I mean
Anyway
You see like
Anti-racism yet
Rogan's Shoes
Anyone else
You can't
Nope you decided to
Fabulous
Back on Monday
Super interested in finding
But we will see
What do its knowledge
We did not end
Brenton Joe and absolutely
Podcast it's going to be coming out
Who's very nice time I appreciate it
Wow
I would say that
So throw you some for b****
But we would do any podcast for any interviews it
Crypto.com
If you guys want us to
Scheduling both
Give us together is
Is difficult but not impossible but not about we can do it
If you would like us to
I have a little conversation
We are more than willing
We appreciate everyone who is that
You want to have a conversation though the best place to have a conversation with both of us
Fun times over there
Overcast
I know
I Apple showing everything so yeah
We're on that we just don't even know about absolutely no one
No one is asked
I would say
Who are the cast of Paris
Spin Alex being a racist representative Omar
You killed anybody
Great person
One who is responsible for
Tons of murders are really responsible for
Lotto
But she hasn't
Probably
Is Alex Jones
Holding
Alex