Alexandra Thurston color
Broken Social
I don't know if I
One of those groups that I'm sure I've heard
You played a couple songs about Dino
But not off the top of my head
I don't know maybe maybe
Shut up we got a clip right there
And I just had written off as like even when I was in college
Iraq b*******
I have no idea what that is
All Canadian
Oh no it was essentially in the Same by all just garbage
Any Canadian band with a rip-off of Rush
Every member of all of those bands has probably been in
Is that why they're called
I recognized but I am
Very prejudiced
Do you like people I
I think like them I never got into Nirvana because the cool
Kids at schools that didn't want to hang out with me all wore Nirvana shirt
Not for me I'll go looking
Pieces my brain
I've not been able to coach out of myself
I famously discovered is a goatee
Text my brother
Pretty cool
Major in college
Thunder-like
There's a lot of good music I miss just because of that weird blind
Open
Talk to you later
Cold
What albums
What's the weather in Sicklerville
The way that I would judge
Describe broke
Is baroque
Post Rock
Does that sound interesting to you
You love horses.
You love her
Alright
Perfect
Thank you so much
Next
Ewok
The ex conspiracy theorist thank you so much
You are now policy
Eczema
If somebody donates on little bit of a
Elevated levels
Thank you so much you are now
Don't get mine until your brilliant someone someone sodomite sent me a bucket of
Request
Postcard
I just got a postcard
I hope I'm not
If this is the correct person to start coming soon
24-0
Have done you can do that
Clicking the button
Show we would appreciate
You have requested a button
But I have finally gotten up off my lazy
Well you should blame the shipping Department
But the different hi.
You need to
You need a break at a shop
Is that you
Oversight from management
But you recently just sent out all day literally
You have one button
So I sent out all of our buttons
Hopefully you'll be coming soon if you are in England
International stamp
Good on something here today that is
Euro time-travel suggestion
Somebody's in that department that was made
Time travel episode
And the
Now that I have reacted what his date was
Do you want me to do
I got everything
Looking backwards
Wanted
Episode
Because
The date that I was looking at
Benjamin Netanyahu
Congress
Weird thoughts on it
I think we were in a position to know what was weird
And what was
For Alex
Oh yeah I wanted to get to it down the road
So
I forgot
Thought I felt but I would constantly be reminded whenever I would think about the time travel episode
Get to that one
I forgot
What date
Requested
So I sent him a message
What date would you like
F***
He said September 1st
I'm not sure what you
So
Not doing that
Because we
Whatever year
So
I ran with that
We got it we got to do what we can to make
Things right so I chose September 1st 2011
Because I feel like that's the time
December 2012
Things get real weird
That's when
Year choice so I chose
I miss this episodes weird man he's already claimed
Brought that up I want to address
The structure of the show
Moving forward
I think I'm done with 2009
Tax day
For today
But it's just nothing
The show is really bad it's really boring
The only thing to take away from it would be
Eclipse
Basically expressing exactly what we've said about him
He believes that Ron Paul in the 9/11 truth movement
Is responsible for the
Tea Party
Hey Glenn Beck in Hillcrest
So we've come to the conclusion that there's not really a whole lot left there
I think we better use of our time
To jump to a new investor
Occupy Wall Street
I think that Ebola timeline
But the one that I want to be elbow timeline
Also the one I want most is
I want to start a hook
And see what Alex
Pitch that
I'm still with the audience pink
If you guys think that's a good idea let me know I would like that to be with our Monday episodes are moving
Emotional
Ignore it
I don't know
Who knows what we might find.
Where did I
Should we eat ice cream I don't know I think that might be the best
Use of our time
We can find a more detailed version
But I understand if a large portion of our
I think that would be
Express
And if so
Maybe the Occupy Wall Street
Who do the next one
Investigation
I'm a little bit Raw on 2009 at the Moana
I don't feel like
There's a lot of answers
Gotcha in April
I think later in 2090 probably
September 1st
A novel context drop
You don't have to take Lexie
Switch them around
Takes a lot of time without stalking
About
Whether or not it's appropriate
Right
It's weird and
Thank you thank Elan it would be what it is
It would be very different
Ops Pro hitting kit
Which the show
That I thought was
The definition
Welcome and thank you so much for joining us it is Thursday
The first day of September 2011
And we're going to be live here for the next 3 hours
Alex Shaffer at the bottom of the
Hours
California
Images of
Police were called
By good see something say something citizen
I was dispatched Remy
So he Alex Shaffer on
Just to give you the details
Set up and was outside
Chase Bank was also paying to get on fire
Someone who walks by was like this is weird
They probably told police they took that guy
And they checked it just wrote
Report about it
It's not
I agree noticing it's weird
I disagree calling the cops
I would say that there's a fair conversation
Should have minded their own business
But also if this guy wasn't
He probably would have gotten
At this point in time it is almost
Negative moral choice to call the cops
Like it is almost it is almost an act of violence to call the cops
That's what I was talking about
The first night that we were there
Nextdoor there was like
Huge
Adrian College party
Until about 3 in the morning
And one of the things I do
It's probably like
It's probably awful
The idea of calling app
Because like what
What you could accidentally
We bring it to somebody
Life-like
Who knows maybe there's someone who's
The country right
Consequences
Yeah it's it's weird to think about now
That is almost attempted murder
Kind of really is
Attempt
Attempted strong but yeah
The point is
A building on fire
Put a regular regular pictures
Daryl guy
He was just like a jobber
Just going in there
No no
Okay okay
Imagining a regular old painter where the the white
Overalls and the white hat
Peter from the 1970s I don't know why that's the painter I'm not
And that is that Ron Paul agrees with him
2012 election
And remember Michele Bachmann
Mitt Romney said that he wasn't taking part in
Atropos only caucus right
Primaries I remember Michele Bachmann statement she put out after
Does she want that primary or that
She was very thrilled very thrilled
So
Disparaging
Michele Bachmann
Ron Paul
Preparing for breakdown of Law and Order
I was able to confirm his views that he gave Robert the Iowa
Was it difficult
Lochmandy bought 90%
Commissioners in perring
I understand
Right
Particularly care about this
To be surprised by Ron
Happening in 2011
If you've already been like Ron Paul comes on your show all the time
You've been supporting him since
2008 election
You shouldn't be like it shouldn't be news that he agrees with you about FEMA camps
Or something I don't really care about that
Michele Bachmann
Inconvenience
Narrative of how things are going
Rock the vote
Oh that no matter what time of factors
F*** it
There's a conspiracy
Yeah that sounds good
What is good to use in campaign
Probably using those former governor of Minnesota money
Could be anything
B Oliver
Inconsequential because almost immediately
Corporal punishment
And when I started hearing him talk that I was going to
Do you goddamn
Better late never lay a hand on a kid
Really I thought for sure my mind never got fit never got there
My fault
He would say why are there though those paddles with the holes in them anymore
Why are we using devices that were specifically invented to hurt children more
I thought
He would be so against the idea that there are public schools
And stuff like that
By virtue of the fact
That they're run by the globalist
Override whatever
I like the idea of violence
Stop with that but no
Didn't blow my mind that's not fair
Took me aback for a second when he starts talking about the
And he seems to be really into the idea of teachers hitting kids
Well in this first clip you sort of expresses that it's better than them getting arrested
But that is
Reliant on a false dichotomy
Or the cops
Sure
That's a problem in Spanish
Caprice and then we
We will
Who want to destroy Law and Order
Yes
Restrict
And if you're going
In a few areas in Illinois and New York where they do not
As aggressive
That's where they have the shootings that's what the teachers are getting attacked that's where your kids are being
That's weather
Instead of
Dale cell
A 17 year olds in the shower
That's there with the school-to-prison pipeline
We should reform
No let the future get hurt you physically
He's the problem of like Emma stolte at a Detention Facility
Whatever
He sees that problem and it's solution is
Looking for computers beat the rest
Which solution is
Systemic reform of
Play previous all this archaic all day
You know to the vet
8 respect
Do teachers are you get get the hit
You if you remember Anna Green Gables she got hit all the time
That's what makes her case
So he
Like
Just the idea of like a teacher giving a couple pops
50 IDI
Throw up
Is a emotional abuse
Used to be
V like
If you don't
Complete the punishment
Uur
That level
And then if you're doing that
Running into
You can't run anymore something like that
It's also a public shaming
Like everyone else is watching
Layers upon layers
Abuse that Alex
Really into
What is being directed towards children which is
Run run until they throw up and that's because they stopped using the stock for public humiliation
You just put a big stock right back next to the basketball court
Right
Everybody get to throw a few painful pop tomatoes
So I kind of thought that that
Was going to be the
Extent of it and being like this
These child detention centers in Suffolk Juvenile Hall
Is bat is a bad place
To go to
Illusion the best reviews to get them
Kind of bad
Going to be it
But I would still an hour about
He starts talking about the problem with liberals
That's the problem
I need to get the kids more
Your shoulder is not watched a liberal
At least he's the Socialists were in front of me
They were totally screwing up
Disease are mentally ill people
Totally wrecked
Uranus is a socialist economic beliefs
Enough to help Steve the means of production
For the speaker
Just talkin about
The baby was like
Little baby
Images
Got out and Alex had to leave the fever
It all
It's crazy
But it's also rely on this idea that liberals don't
Their kids are not for their you stuff like that
Develops this
A little bit more
It talks about how liberals
Can't Raise a Man
Problem
As soon as you start getting autumn
What is going to be absolutely miserable life
Your training is going to be
First of all
I don't know I don't know
This should be in your custody
This is an episode that should be played
Having a dog
Damn liberals
My Challenger
Dog parks
Observing for a month when I come to the dog park
Animals
Turn off my car
So you can't if you're a liberal you can't really raised a dog cuz you allow it to
Weird things out
Groundhog Day
Weird like wearing a
Propeller beanie as weird for dog liberals do as Liberals are more likely to dress up there
Weird Behavior
Old ladies who think Barack Obama is the great Satan also probably put their dogs in tub
Conclusion
To beat your dog
I mean I know that's not what he's saying
I'm using loose lips
Cuz he's not saying abusing that
So bad want to just be talking about is spanking in the home
He's comparing it to
Corporal violence
Punishment
In school
Being okay
It does
A little bit
Into things that are appropriate
Because he's not really cool
Study after study
Has proven that
If you use violence against violent later on in life
It is not they become cool it is that you're just breeding violence over and
Over and over again
Mild
Is appropriate
In certain setting
The life-threatening
Running into traffic
The literature on it
Geologist psychologist degree
In those sorts events
It's okay but once YouTube
Punishment
Once you expand
Is that associated with
Behavior
Yeah
The trouble
The Nuance of that
The result of that
Liberals don't do it enough
The dogs
It's crazy because all of those guys
Who are like
Dude I got
First off
You didn't turn out fine
And second neither did I
Turn out fine excuses
Sentimental
Express
Was trying to justify this
Exact
It's almost always like
Kiddo
Punitive
But not realizing it what year
Expressing
How this
Yeah
Violet
So we
You know you talkin about how liberals can't raise dogs
They're socialists in the movie theater needles are children
Disciplining
Or whatever
Disappoint
He's kind of
Definition of liberal
You talk about Democrat
No
Midnight Club
Define
Is a disappointing definition
Moron idiot
Thomas Jefferson
I'm talking about
They're scared of snakes
Do you know who is the most disappointing liberal of all
You're back
Why do you start with me
Gun
Political definition
Countryside fight
You don't wreck
You don't like people who are ruled
Well Rex was this Countryside and he was
Alex was like well I guess I have a hickey without a liberal
Fanatic
Which is the same problem
Snakes but
Scared of
Shouldn't
ResCare.
Instincts
Understand government
And societies and societies
Definition of liberal groups sounds like you did say that
It's so a liberal is one who is afraid of snakes but not of the government
Good to know
Not sure I agree with that definite I'm not a poli-sci major run
Don't think
Accurately
Depicts
Well I mean
Is polarizing like we're more polarization than ever before
88% of liberals disapprove of the job that Trump is doing
Was so many liberals aren't afraid of no
Sneaky Snake
I don't know
Like you should
Please note please be like specific
Cuz I'm not afraid of a garden snake
Okay
What's 1 of metal
Got to give your card back Unfortunately they just kick me out
I think it's rational to be scared of all snakes
Even though some of them aren't dangerous
Yeah I think it's still probably
I think there's a instinctual like
Human
Yeah Comfort with things that they crawl around on their belly and slither
Welbeck that's like people
Right
Most of us are Indiana Jones so in that we are afraid of
Talking about how teachers
Should be able to
Just go ahead and
Your kids if they want to
The part that I find very
He seems to be
Pining for the
When he is an adult
And
You would never allow his
To be putting that
Eyelash
The football coach
Pops
An NFL football coach
What
To disciplinary action
Stories
We've gone from a manhood Society
Jellyfish
Houston to Liberty re-up on option 2
Beat up his football coach
What's the movie theater story
He's describing is a profoundly fuckedupshit
Would punch a kid tent
First of all time
Is Ja
No one would bat an eyelash at that
Isaac even back then
Beyond
What is acceptable
In the time
When corporal
That was much more regular
Really interesting
When you look at the map of states
It's still allow corporal punishment in schools
Watch Justice League
It's pretty much just the South with a little bit of the Midwest around Missouri and Kentucky
Used in any public schools
So it's still legal
This may be slightly dated info as
I was working off from NPR
It's legitimately
Geographical split
Clearly Define
The more likely estate was to be a part of the Confederacy
The more likely it is that they still allow corporal
Those are things
Contrack
Will Smith
Is that whether it is that what they're the South will rise again and swelling
In 1970s
Supreme Court decided 52 for the corporal punishment
You cruel and unusual punishment
Nor did it tonight the student
In question of due process
In the case Ingram versus right
That case involved a fourteen-year-old 8th grade
Probably leaving Auditorium
At that point
Principal's office restraint
It struck with a paddle at least
20 *
The child suffered
Hematoma
Advised by doctors
Arrest for 11
Some days
Another student at the school to receive the paddling the legend
He was so severe
He was unable to use his arms
For a brief.
Guitar
Nothing
Free f***** up
I mean I guess unusual
Like if you have to use both of those words
Like it is 100-percent cruel
But it is not unusual for this
Have laws prohibiting
Iowa New Jersey
Hitting kids
Privates
The only Tuesday
Out of the 50
That have rules about what private schools
Dude you don't want to regulate private Enterprise you don't want to keep corporations from dumping toxic
Waste into our natural park
And you definitely don't want to eat
Corporation
Interesting Lee a 2016 study in the journal social policy information found by digging into
School districts that allow corporal
Imagine my surprise to read the black students are way more like
Receive corporal
More likely than
Equally troubling their research revealed its 2
With protective disability status
Which similarly more likely
Recipients of corporal punishment in schools
A possible explanation
It didn't involve ViaSat
Further examination
Pure and simple black students male students
Students with disabilities
We're consistently the target of disproportionate punishment
Corporal
There's something is crystal clear
The date of May careers at
Continuous
It is typically
Disproportionate
With some subgroups of children
Understand others
They
Obviously
Like suspensions
Expulsion
Well there's a very large
Suspension
Absolutely
Controlling for other factors
What percentage of
Disproportionately applied those punishment towards black students
Horse and a very similar trend is found
When you look at corporate
For similar in frack
Irregardless of population
Right
Majority-black school majority-white school
It doesn't matter
Across-the-board
Blackstone
AR
Far more likely
In almost every locale
That they studied to be
Feel awful is that is you kind of expect
Because of how bad we think humans are
The revelation of looking at this was the disability
Like that's really f***** up corporal punishment
Consistently used at a higher level
Who are disabled
Really trouble
NOAA
It makes sense to me mainly because I know how much abused
Happens
Old folks home
I don't know why is there a nursing homes with no lights
He says rather than clearly like
I'm frustrated
Who knows how much of
Is based on zat
Just making any kind of
Come up with a good reason other ideas Vine
I don't know if that's the case but like
Stocked up
Just based on the fact there are these
Physical anomaly
You fine in terms
Who is the recipient
These corporal punishment
That's enough that we shouldn't do it ever again
It should be outlawed
It being
Use as a systematic tool against
Set
Male students
Like that
Do that
Unfortunately
That getting hit
Imschools makes you better
So
Never ever fails
Tubi
No matter how many times you hear it but
A black
Child
Seven-years-old
Already
That
You're worse than other people and it's been hit
And this continues
For therein
Tire life
For their entire life in the United
It is a constant
Is it something that is
Like
Much
I was looking at all the stuff I was trying to make sense
Because
I know that Alex hates violence
About it all the time
Like it's one of his
Biggest
Issues
Trend would still be
Detoured
I understand
You want to have a debate about in the home
You know II
I understand
Get Matt
You know
Except severe Scituate
That it may or may not be
But
I do understand where the
Debate
A little bit
Somewhat
Maybe
I don't think there is much of it
Debate about school
Violence
I don't think so
A Alex
Think that there is not only about it
The other side is right
Eating kids at school is very weird to me
Where the f***
Because it has to come from somewhere
Somewhere
The power
And he says this in the neck
Text Cliff
Express is where
It's from
And so under common law
Anyone
Force
And to order that child
Now you can defend yourself
You can't
Defender
You can't just go out and shoot somebody no matter how much you want to
But if somebody breaks into your house you've always wanted to
I mean talk about common-law and we know that that's where a lot of
Is weird sovereign
Yeah yeah
Like off the bat
I'm not sure that I know what he's talking about
Legal guardian
For the students
And it somehow you give up your rights
School that sort of thing
That doesn't sound
It's not
But there is something
Close to
So if I had to guess I would say this is a reference
In loco parentis
But even this is super
In loco parentis in place of parent
Declared himself
Parental over there
Since that way
School for Orphans in Wards of the state
From boarding school
Your brain doesn't have to stretch too far
Fifties in Manchester either your parents or your kids
In loco parentis
Concept doesn't have much
Regularly eroded by
Green Court decision
West Virginia State Board of Education vs. Barnette 419
43 rules
Couldn't be forced to salute the flag
Which means that the students have four
First Amendment
Open the school
So there's a difference
A mezuzah
Oh that's
In cases like Tinker versus Des Moines independent
Community School District in New Jersey versus
PLO
The court found that officials of the schools operate as representatives of the state
And not purely in
Some sort of Parental capacity
So many other protect
Citizens also apply to students
The history of a lot of these.
That's not nearly
That
I misheard you and I heard
Yellow
Follow the electric they wanted to pick you up a little known fact
Take the Long Way Home
Important things to consider is that the roots of a lot of Education
Particularly in this country
High School became more secular nature a lot of weird ideas about Authority changed a little bit
Reflect the changing priority
I've been actual edges
As opposed to school being place where you got moral instruction
You'll notice
Catholic and private school
They still haven't changed that much
Corporal punishment
Is legally
Protect
Much more
So these are the ideas of where the
In loco parentis stuff
The method exist
Now has no business
Is this sort of
Absolutely
Teachers art
Inasmuch as
Authority
Descendants of like
The Catholic
Priest who's over the school spaceguard the virtue
Of all the stupid
It's very different
Babies up considerably in the past hundred years
You still see some things like on a college campus will say it's a dry campus
Where does a zero-tolerance policy
Alcohol even though students their babies
Legal drinking age
These are remnants of this legal principle that was all just kind of decided
To live with
But here's the large anyway with daylight savings time but I guess we're just knocking
Here Jordan is a larger issue
Cannot be supportive of this sort of in loco parentis common-law bulshit
In order to justify
Sitting students
And at the same time be supposed to school
Restrictions on stew
Bringing guns to college
Which campuses
The entire Prince
I enjoy the same rights as they do in the outside world at school
Is that needs to
Extended Gun 2
If he actually
Of course he doesn't
Complete work to try and disrupt the effort
What's the ban firearms
On the UT Austin campus
And he's now hired Kaitlin Bennett as a reporter who's really only famous for carrying
Gunn on the Kent State
Parentis ideas only exist nowadays
Restriction
That exist
Like
Be kicked out of school if you want to
You dated the wrong sort of person
Or whatever
There was a restaurant
University
Go to the restaurant
And that was deemed okay
These students are not allowed
Go to the
This restaurant
No
Private colleges
Okay
Is very weird Iowa New Jersey private colleges
How out in front
Child freedom
I don't know
It's really weird
Has about like you give over your Authority
You give these kids
To the school
I don't know if you understand the ramifications
Asian buffet
But you really believe that then like
Like what where does it end
If they can physically assault the kids
Assault them in other ways
Like what do
Fictional a parental Authority Zen
It's just really weird
Very
Very well
I don't understand where Alex
Middle Ground
I think he just wants kids getting hit
High School
Because I think he thinks it makes them better and tougher or something like that
And I mean
No
Absolutely
He's wrong
But if it comes when I
Is that is
He has to be for
Fishing
Did he ostensibly isn't for
Right so I just don't understand
It's too late in this podcast
Pictures of us doing it
Years now for me to be surprised that there's something
Is inconsistent
Alex
Really makes it seem like he wants
Vacuum
From parents
Teachers
Pastors
Girl Scout leaders
Respect you in any mammal Animal Kingdom
This is already Ross
Ice killer whale
Kill
Can you talk to your kids
That's a good
These seals have school where teachers hit kids
Metaphor is falling apart already
Centralized loco parentis rules for
I mean it's crazy
I don't
I don't know I didn't watch the same
Nature special that he watched
Or whatever
The times when spanking
Is
Like the kid itself is what is life
Sort of exception to that
No spanking
Principal
What I understand
Doesn't have kids
Hi-5
He's describing an animal kingdom
Is the analog to be possibly okay version of spanking a child
But he's trying to
To make that
And people in the schools haitink
Right
For one reason again like I said
Seals don't have an
It's second
The Ava School
It's not a life-threatening situation
It's always
It's always a physical
That you're doing to a
Yeah it's not
Appropriate it's not productive
Nothing along those lines is okay
He's trying to
Muddy The Waters by using an animal
Does it ever cross any of these people's minds
Who are making me to argue
It's about the animal kingdom
It's fine
I bet we're trying to
Like
Like today ever get this like
Well if seals
Steele's don't
Bill
Stop
Like maybe we're trying to
Fuel evolution
Create a better Society
If we weren't exactly like
Steel and Justice something is a natural response
2 something doesn't
A good response
Is a productive response maybe the field
The kid. Making
You know
Totally naturalism
The best thing it could do right because we have higher cognitive function
We could observe that behavior
And then be like
F***** up those animals
Oh yeah
I'm not a Crocodile Dundee
Praying mantis
There you go
Alright
We talked a little bit about
Blind
Baby deer that are almost grown up almost leaving her mother run out but she smell something
She comes out gets in front of a truck
What should I kill the both
Turn around and chicom
That really doesn't sound right
To shoot
We're too busy being afraid of snakes
But she smells
Smell
Of the creature that she knows kills deer
Alex
She smells
Murderer
Murder on a regular basis
To her family
Metaphor
Muddying the Waters of what
Is
For that van because Alex is coming
If your if even if your kid walks out of the traffic
And there's a car coming and you're like I know what to do but I got to get this out of the way if you jumped
But you did save his life
Sure
I hope he lives
You were a deer that might be
But you know what you could do
Just be like hey come back
Certifikid understand
But
It's a mess it's a
Metaphors don't work
Tired
To animal behavior
I got to stress
Details an hour
I can't believe he doesn't our choose different animals to compare
All I can really describe
You want
Because it's
This country
Tutu School
ER now
Castle Law
Idiots
When you put them in that school
I think
If I had to
Gap
I don't think he really believes
This is true
Because it's
Ludacris
Is trying to spread more
Ear of public schools
By being like whenever you put them in there they all think
It's more that you can
Do whatever you want to do
Whenever you
Give over
You've already
Maybe if they're in the school giving up
Guardianship to the school
Somebody had
Pastor recognized
Yeah
It's very,
Now
There are shades of legal guardianship
Hey you're in the classroom
Kid dies on your watch
You are responsible
To that extent
Alex's describe
This is Chris level of
Given transitive
Your rights
Responsibility
Imagines it's like
Mr. Weatherbee wish people would read those terms of service Apple agree
Because if you download music from the iTunes
In those terms in agreement
They can also hate
Come over to Tim Cook
Banana
What he believes
Game of this
It's very weird
Cuz he starts making some
Complaints
That he's afraid of
But at the same time
Your parent if you go to the school
They should be totally fine doing these things
They are not
Terrible transgression
At the school's make
Andy's Auto
Please
Anxi
And and and and and and Bayton switches and she'll games and scams
School District
Dodgeball
And now the teachers aren't allowed to touch him or talk to him
I think this is socialist at the movies
Cedar level
Imagine scenarios
First they came for my dodgeball
For I didn't have an R
Schools
Definitely
Majority of them
From what I've been able to
That don't have dodgeball
As part of their
Curriculum
In
Jim I'm really fine with that
Through a lot
It was the sort of thing where people got hurt whether it was from taking a ball to the Head falling over hitting her head on the ground
Or trying to.
Right
There are other ways to get Recreation this is clearly
Violent J
Well there's always always the kid who is playing the game as a bad actor
Like I'm here
It out
Running
The only things I was able
Go to find where
There are some schools that have band
Running
I don't know if
Rose to that level
Going to
Recent orders
I think Alex is talking here about the
Hangzhou
Is the number schools
Sports games
Without exception all these schools because of
Breaking out between
The Kentucky High School Athletic Association got rid of post
Doesn't count
Temptations
Even in that orders out the association
But we're required to report
Mayor come about
Because of that to say
I do grieve
But it's not like one SKU
You don't say
Decision but I also don't think it's like
Why didn't they act way sooner I kind of assumed it was like
Ariel
Completely voluntary non-binding
Sure
You can
If people
If you have faith
You can have your student
Not fight with
Do it
Don't do it
Yeah
Also I bet those kids who keep getting into fights
Probably
Just pointing that out
In 1994 Ventura County Schools
Post
Free game
To pervert preserve Sports
It wasn't
But
There wouldn't be any different
After the match
They just did it for sportsmanship
Mike talking about the Quest Academy
And England
That could be what he's talking about the possible
Google contact
Early 2011
An attempt to cut down on Bully
That might be what he's talking
Cast and crew
Nothing to do with anything
Further notice
It seems like it's just a vague
Preservation of what
He thinks is the idea of masculinity
I think that's really all it is
Horrible version of masculinity does involve
You get out of line blow your hot child you get out of line the coaches going to punch you 10 times
Great break your jaw
I don't know
And somebody ten times
Sooner or later
That's possible
Now we're done
For now with the
Google fi
Issue
It's the way that Alex
So
It gives
Give me Gibbs
He's a completely random.
If we go back to our talking about I was great for teachers to hit kids you never expect
Did that
And now we get another unexpected
Clock
Except on holidays
Broadcast
30 minutes
Used transmission
Special Report
Bisphenol-a
Information
They are consciously using As a chemical weapon
Panda population
Tonight
Official premiere
Infowars Nightly News
The matter for another day
I'm passing it
He doesn't swipe
Fairplay
Was created
Can epoxy resin
It was
Absolutely
Isn't that
And I'd like to save that for
We actually talked about it
I do
Realize that started in 2011
They had a Nightly News show parent night started in robbed
But I really thought that it was going on
I thought there was a
How could it be
In the evenings Jason
So yeah I guess that was just a unexamined assumptions
Send that I had that in fortnite
Is it still going
Instagram fashion
No.
He kept saying he was going to make it 24 hours
The on-air Talent
He used to back in 2009 almost every episode ends with him
Re promoting happened earlier in the show
Is he
Communications Network attestation
Where they were
Play it in
Who plays
Rebroadcast
Hotel California
Lookouts could do that now
But he knows that
It's not worth it
The resources that he has
Enough to make
Actual different
The rest of the day
Which I guess is
Yeah better for all
We got off on that
Diversion
Teachers hitting kids
The painter Alex
Yeah he comes on
Government
Prediction about selling
Chase Bank on fire
Scene 75
For 25,000
Which is first of all waste by 60%
His prediction was with his
His listeners all like
Lycoming in
Set still crazy
Tell Alex the story of
Altercation
I'm fair to say
Interaction
With the police
I mean I think the
I think that the officers
Ridiculous
I thought it was funny that they line
Beard
Homeland Security
Except probably
Talk to me
Whatever he's on the no-fly list
The police did end up coming to his house shortly thereafter
Even Peyton
It was a formal check-in
Report to someone
People who showed up
Yeah it's weird but we just kind of have to check it out
You know we got to fill out the paperwork that we were here
Find your cool
I don't know why they check back in
That seems like
I don't know maybe they have to according to their guidelines or whatever
I just best practices whatever
Was like
Superbad
Friendly
Play okay that's fine I guess what we got an Xfinity store
Everybody's fine with that
I don't I don't I don't know
I'm not I'm not suit
His plight anime $25,000
Yeah whatever
He went that German did wind up eating him and the painting
Yeah we don't we don't know what happened actually I dunno what happened
He ended up
Getting arrested again
Try to push the boundaries
Totally got himself arrested
I'm not sure I dislike him necessarily he's alright
The only thing is that you showed up on Infowars and was verbally
Supportive of Al
The rest of the stuff seems like
Have a good to see him trying to
Buzz Marketing or something probably
425 Grand
Of course you're going to start s*** from there on out
It's like it's like
Geo detention
Difficult
The show necessarily
I feel like I have
Real
Responders
Okay about how
The Bloomberg
New York exempt
Anniversary
Yeah
I've mixed with about it
We're not going to listen to a lot of
I just have one clip
And that is Alex
That really
Really f****** it
Specifically
Did you get the other guy on the phone
But it'll
Pretty close to
Realtree
Beautiful story
He has these 2911 for
First Responders
Gas discount
You're not invited to the ceremony
This interview because
Because it puts me in a position
On the way
Respect for people
Who put their lives
Terrible
I don't want it
I don't
On the other hand
These guys and Alex
Have a very Twisted take on what's go
The First Responders work
Space
And at the victims family members
I am people who survived
Hire priority
I think that's a weak excuse
But ultimately
Could have been the truth
Zuccotti Park
New York there might not
Have been rude within the
Space that they would have cordoned off
I still think that's probably disrespect
First Responders
You're there
Yeah I never miss an opportunity Bloomberg
But speaking all the interview
The show
Might be
Chivas or two types
Disrupt the event talking about building 7
And that sort of thing
Be fine with it
Individual basis
Because
Even if they are going to
Disrupt I'm not sure I think
Appropriate
I don't know I'm glad I never have to make that right
It is it is
When he was running
The Daily Show
This dude one of the guys who's being interviewed this Joey God we finally get them on the phone
Better
Of course
Responder because he brings up John Stewart
Political
So so it is absolutely like a thing where if you guys had done
F******
At the very least
Cumin decent things
To do which is
Take care of these people who
Arguable Heroes
If you're just taking care of them
Maybe the whole 9/11 was staged thing probably wouldn't get it
Fart with
Yeah exactly
I misspoke a little bit
Because
Unfairly
These to do
911 truth
It probably would disrupt
Is very
Which is to speak out about
The lack of healthcare the disruptive aspect of it
Probably didn't want to
Right
But you understand
Why
He would do
Right
Call to answer
For that absolutely
How much is a wrong person to do
Absolutely
It's so much on
Like that
Piercing narrative
I really don't
Don't have it in me
9/11 First Responders
But they're probably big-picture right about with the small matters
To point out like
I understand why he would do that
Entirely possible that
Just like so many guests we have on Alex there like
Order to get out their message
Like it's entirely possible these dudes were going along with the whole
911 is an inside job here shaking your head
Brought up John Stewart
The other guy
Toddler Ted
He was pretty
Please party on that tip
I'm still fine with them going on Infowars to spread that message
I'm fine with them going on any show to spread the message of like
Hey there
F****** ass over
And we're actually Heroes
Maybe think about that
You know that's why it stopped
Yeah I want to listen
Intuit
Alex
Who's the starting again
You try to promote
He's got a big
With the CEO of Gibson
And they weren't in trouble
And I Alex Corte interview with Co
Throws it
To that interview
Caesar
For tonight
The debut
Open fortnite
American jobs
Broadcast
Red wine basket
No clip
Destroyed
Tiermaker
Joey says that they
The courts told him you should do business in Madagascar
You should move to Madagascar
Better off doing business in Madagascar was illegally imported
From Madagascar from India
Guitars
But they couldn't legally been used
There's a lot called
They were in violation
Using using my gold stuff like that
In Madagascar
None of it is itself illegal to possess
But exported out of Madagascar or India would be
Illegal in the Lacey act makes
Illegal to traffic
Florida
That would be illegal according to
Before in-laws
70 is Flora or fauna
It's covered under the Lacey Act
I mean
He's weird
Literally Gali smuggled out of country
It's not like ebony comes from a f****** I don't know that it's
The ebony was
2011 ebony might have been
The first raid
And then the Rosewood
Both from India and Madagascar where the second
The Madagascar was also the source of the devil
Little confusing
Like where were they getting
There
Spypoint does Renee
The local laws
In the country that they were sourcing it from
And the Lacey act makes it illegal for them
To do that sourcing got you cuz of those countries
Big deal out of this
Jobs in America
Dab going to Madagascar
He's coming on Infowars nightly
They couldn't get the clip together for this
It does exist
Gibson would plead guilty and pay a $300,000 fine in August 2012
So they ended up
Do use the Shaggy defense in a court of law
Provide cover
Maker
Guitar
We're coming towards the end of it
And
The first one
You've discovered
Over the course of the
That Alex has a
Fit of love
The authority
He's a fascist
Well the same time being a libertarian
Which makes
Perfect sense
Turtleson
Not to contradict
Actually most Libertarians are somewhat fashion
Is the gateway to
In this next clip there's a situation going on geopolitical
Moammar Kadafi
Oh I thought this was one that was an international
But
Alex
Uncle
No surrender
Or cowardly scum
There's something respectful about a dictator who will actually fight
Jordan to the history of moammar Kadafi
But let's just remind people this episode
From September 2011
Mere months earlier the telegraph reported thick toffee was firing on civilians
Quotes
Unimaginable
Quote warplanes and helicopters are indiscriminate bombing one area after another
There are many many dead
Our people are dying
It's a policy of scorched-earth
After the situation deteriorated and Kadafi had given an interview wear
Protect him
The International Community was
Really concerned about him
Chemical weapons on his own people
Because he had
Is mustard gas
But he didn't give up when
Do you like 14 tons of mustard
Forgot you know there's something
Sing respectable about
Prince MBS
Because you don't see a lot of royalty willing to kill journalist
Now and just remember that
Underwrite
Getting y
To be like
Cuz
He recognizes what the problems
You really don't
It's almost it's almost like he's he's a dictator murdering
Citizens of his country
The capital punishment
Punishment
I'm just like
You know what you gave up your rights when you decided to live there with that dictator so he has the right to kill you
I think
Somali pirates
Supporting dictators
In foreign countries when he's mister I love
Freedom
It does make sense today
You decided
SMS
God what an
He's pretty dumb idiot
Is
Before the episode
So
How do you say with a grain of salt about how he's going to get
People's calls are called
I got some other news which has been overloaded today
Would would happen
Fever last night of a sore throat
TV show
Almond
I know it's just going soon
All the map for today
Blaming having a
Fever for being all over the map
When I would say
He is one of the most focused I've ever seen
I was about to say so far we have here
Show me all over the map
It's cool that's pretty on point
You want to talk about
The corporal punishment
He did another half hour or so talking
Maybe a little bit more focused on that topic
Did a much shorter interview with
Just wanted to sound bite wanted a little
That sort of thing
Bismarck
Yeah I would say
The first hour were you stalking
Being off topic and all over the place when he is
Nothing but Alex without the flu for Alex with the flu is like early. Orson Welles
Alex without the flu is Orson Welles
In the commercial song
I don't know I just thought that was really weird
Photos of very strange
Restaurants in 5 minutes
You take out the last commercial break or whatever
Like a lack of self-awareness
Like I really don't like a question a lot of coincidences
It seems like you have to admit that some of your conspiracy what's even weirder is the
The thing that he's allowed to be a coincidence episode is something negative
Has befallen him
You got a few
None of the taxes working in the studio when he's trying to launch his show perfect scenario to be like
Sofia Vergara and everyone is disrupting my communication
This is Bell's palsy
The fact that he was able to get to the point
No big deal
The only time that he is
Free of his personal invented
Demon
Is when he gets up
We got to keep that boy
Alex
Keep your
Nothing I want to kill him
Like that but
With that for very long
You need to learn upgrade
Chronic condition
What about
Lyme disease
Yeah that's a chronic condition
Yeah
We settled on it let's get
The only way to keep him on
Fever hallucinations about socialist in movie
I think it works out perfectly
A hundred percent
Stupid Bank
Progressive
Interesting look
I'm not sure
How interested I am in Alex
Around this time frame based on
I like it
I'm a huge fan I don't know how much of it is actually attributable
Book to the fever I think he's in a holding pattern
I don't have a varsity narrative
And that's why I talk about hitting kids
2009 and 2015 investigation
Those are investigations we're trying to find something out
What if we just investigate
How ludicrous he can get on a day-to-day basis
I mean you can just
Random random number generator
Stop I don't have that problem
Well because inevitably
Of sometime that
He does have a varsity
Narrative and now we have a new investigation know I like that I like that
What you have to do is when you're
Creating a generator
Every time you click the button you say no whammies
Okay
No whammies
Respond
Appreciate
To our lives
But also I for my brain
I like much more when
We're in something
That has
Narrative structure
I'm not sure with the conclusion I'm making his butt
It's been fun and we have website
You can also go to fill your hand.
Absolutely
We are is that knowledge underscore
Facebook
Delivery Man overcast
We're not
Brother
We'll see some variety
It is no Arts
A hole in it
Not because of Jim's episode
From now on
I'd love to retain the Monday Wednesday
Friday structure w
But this week
Catch you next time but
Alex
Who painted building
How the guy got killed anybody do know that yeah
Sign
Painter gentleman
Who interviewed
Technically
And a guy
Alex Jones
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color