Alexandra Thurston color
I'm not I'm not sure if I was
I don't know maybe I would be as an adult
Don't think so I didn't have many cool friends
I wasn't that cool
You know like I was trying to buy into it really hard
Gemstone books
Christian bookstore in Columbia Missouri
Devotional morning devotional books and stuff like that
15/16
Hello Google
Because we got a
Very very
Thought-out response to our Lyme disease
We were wrong about that
Swear to God it's the only way I know Avenue is through
Iraq
It's a
Does Look a Lot Like a Rock
We're out of it
Cedar Point
The only reason I even thought that Lyme disease was a thing that happened for a long time
What's because in the documentary the punk singer
Kathleen Hanna
Singer of Bikini Kill
Girl extraordinaire
Main reason that you stop
Performing was
Because she had
Anand
If you know what this actually brings me to the clarification
Clearly you f***** up couple of actual thing
To unclearly please want to clarify
Things that I was saying in no way should have been interpreted as I think it's a good idea to ever hit a kid
I don't I think I made that clear but just in case I did not want to come out for 40 Diddley on that side
I meant secondarily
In the same way that you saw that documentary and that Legend
To believe that chronic lyme disease with a chronic thing and all that
I think I was operating off bad information understanding of
Spanking being appropriate
Situations according to
Like the American Psychological Association
And sorry about that
Fragrancex
Helping you learn
Skyrim you live and you learn and that is
I only know what you tell me about
To do and
I'm excited before we get there we got to give a shout out
Some folks
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Text Lexi
Thank you so much
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of
Really we're thrilled MacArthur Foundation
Donated to the show
Guess what
Guess who's on board now
The Bilderberg Group
Galax would agree with it
Fearnow technocrats
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket of poop
Jar Jar Binks Caribbean
I don't want
Bilderberg Group
You can do that by going to
Appreciate
Absolutely
Or perhaps any of our listeners who would like to donate
I just pretend laundry list of things that we can lie about
The Builder group
Positive
Pretty good chance
Splc
Everybody
Hide under fake names
Tell ya era of knowledge fight
That's putting it way too strong when I'm starting
We are going to be covering
Launch
Did I suggest
I decided as soon as it came out of my mouth that I was going to do it
Irresponsible
This unanimous of a response that's Lionel
In terms of people all being on the same page everybody is very much like
No no no no no
In the aftermath of the shooting spree
Because it's horrifying
With the warp reality that will inevitably cover the event
And uses them to push his narrative
Ultimately I sat with those feelings and decided that this was something that I had
We know that Alex told his audience at Sandy Hook was a fake of that with actors as recently as late 2015
But you been saying stuff like that for a while but we don't know what
For me that is unsatisfied
I know that he's lying about how he covered the tragedy
But I believe that it's in everyone's best interest for us to learn more so we can have a fuller understanding of why Alex
Texas line
To cover up his past action
Right
Today we're embarking on a new investigation to figure out exactly what this coverage of Sandy Hook
There'll be difficult to hear
I promise you that we will do our best
To be respectful
Embarrassed
Consideration
Who eating
Everyone except Alex
In this
You know it's the first time that I can honestly say that Alex
But he is quite literally not a bad enough dude to save the Press
That's true in present-day Alex being sued by the families of the children who died at Sandy Hook on December 14th
He claims that he never said that Sandy Hook was fake money just had debates and looked at both sides of the issue
We know that this is categorically not to ruin demonstrate we demonstrated it plenty of times
So that claim isn't worth our time as an investigation
He's also claimed that after he heard about the shooting that really happened
It only started questioning if it was a false flag
After hearing about quote-unquote anomaly
Like the classic case of Anderson
Cooper's news disappearing people like
Wolfgang halbig
So
At this point we don't really know if that claim is true
So that's one thing we can look in
Right Alex
Beyond that is on specific as this is
I want to have a narrative develop
By the time that he was pretty much
So far under the radar that he could get away with whatever
How did Alex play as Han
Yeah
I have no idea what we're going to find but I was ready to learn to Alex was restrained in his coverage
And misled by India
As I am ready to learn
I think he was the one leading the bandwagon of dumb dumbs down a terrible drug
I don't know we will find out as we go along
We'll see
And I promise that I will approach this with as open a mind as I can
As is alright
I wrote out that introduction
To this just because
Be a little bit
We were then
Necessarily just us talking
What where we're going why I decided to jump into the
Because it could
Get ugly
Really ugly
Well that's one thing that I was considering it
Saw the overwhelming positive
Do it do it was
It's regarding San Diego
Ideal
I deal with tragedy
Through humor entirely
And I am
Would like
Really do not want to be disrespectful in any way
And if this first episode
Navigation is going to just cover December 14th 2012
Does the day of the shooting
And
I'll say this
Exhausted this is
This could have been way worse
The idea of us going over out his response to Sandy Hook
People's heads
Horrifying
I like oh my God
For today
It's pretty soft going so weather
Thinking you're going to be horrified today
Maybe next week from
Slightly lower than neutral position
Yeah yeah
So here we are
We're going to start things off
This is how Alex begin
The show
On December 14th 2012
Hygienic
About you cannot confess
Of December 2012
There is a reported school shooting
Restrictions on gun ownership
Right now it looks like only the gunman is dead
So within seconds
What's a Gunther
Seconds of starting his show
Newtown Connecticut 9:35 a.m.
Lanza shot himself at approximately 9:40
Those are Eastern Time
So would actually be 8:35 to 8:40 a.m. in Alex's time
And it's important he doesn't start until 11 a.m. or noon
Eastern Time
There were over two hours from the end of the shootings
Alex got on a
I know that it was a developing story but there's no reason for him to be so unaware of the situation at this point
The day
If he's presenting it as if he
He has an opinion
Yeah if you want
Cover it at details
That's kind of
Fairly responsible weight
To deal with these.
The idea of leaving the show with it
When you don't really have any information
Is not good
That is not good thing to do
But you saw it exactly right there start
That it's just immediately into gun.
Complain about liberals tweeting about gun reform so quick
G.i. 50
It is
Absolutely expected
But it is
Nevertheless disconcerting that
His first response is not
I'm thinking about the Dead
His first response is that I'm thinking about guns
That's unfair right now
Because at you as you heard they're the information that Alex is operating better information
Bernard has another question
But the information he's operating off of is just the gunman is down
He is not he doesn't know
Did all these kids got killed
He is operating
I don't believe that this is
The first time that the information came out
But at 1:40 Eastern Time
The police table press conference
Detail
But
I think the
I thought you were called reporting was coming out
Maybe should have been aware that this wasn't situation just a gunman
Was down and no other fatalities
At the beginning of the show bear to look at the story
I understand why you
Do a regular show he thinks the story is a kid showed up
Maybe fired shots into the wall or mandatory officer
If only because that's how you presented the store exactly
I'm cool.
News of the day because he doesn't think that this is that big of a deal yet
It's a big deal but for Alex's purposes
It's not as big a deal as
Obviously
Infowars.com
Tucker
American Free Press
A couple months before this
Stuff with that engine Tucker's
I like
To flesh out that story I don't really know any
He was talking about
And I'm not going to look for Jim Tucker's primary reporter
He's going to get to the gym Tucker story about Obama going into turkey what have you
But he also
Start getting kind of
Weird
Beginning of the show
He's very introspective
And starts talking about how he's starting to experience emotion
There are competing forces is the best way to say it there are competing forces in this world
I will say that
A lot of people
And also extremely
Experiencing
Understandings
Emotions
This is strictly
In the context of him like saying that I'm aware of so much
It's not
Services
You say it's almost like
You pick your red-tailed I have no emotion
Yeah I don't know what that I don't know what that means
I'm not sure
That's not new
I feel that a lot
I always
French
Never say that
He he doesn't actually talk with these new emotions are necessarily
But he does talk about how it feel
Feels
Which I find very interesting
This is upsetting
Visitors grandiose talk
Foot
Want to hear
Closest this feeling
Is more more dominating me
The closest I can describe it
Angled
Focused understand
So
Incredibly
Interesting to hear Alex describe how he's feeling in late-2012
Because what he's describing is not heightened level of focus
That legitimately sounds like a medical condition
Now obviously he's just exaggerating to make himself sound like
He's tapped into some kind of cosmic understanding fight for fun
I'm going to pretend he's actually talking to a doctor about you.
If I'm going to play a differential game and diagnose him
Notion in slowly
Similarities
What else is clearly expressing is in the
Condition
Compare it two times
If those situations your body is flooded with adrenaline
Which is part of the fight-or-flight reaction
That you have
Everything is describing perfectly fit
We talkin about adrenaline
It would make sense
That what he's actually talking about it is unable to control production
And release of adrenaline
So if that were the case what symptoms would you expect
One possible cause of elevated adrenaline levels
Is the adrenal gland condition Cushing
Along with excess adrenaline condition
Syndrome then I would expect him to be
Trying to
Troy
Different syndrome
Different symptoms from Johns Hopkins medical schools Cushing syndrome
This sounds like Alex
Upper body
Round face high blood pressure
Reduce libido and sex drive in men
The desire to destroy Alderaan
Increased fat around
Neck constantly talks about huge necklace
This can't be real
That's what are the symptoms of Cushing's syndrome
I'm just doing this
He wants to talk about how is elevated state of red pivot misses
It's either changed status
Clearly
Definitely above his
Reality
It's just as easy to take what he's describing and say that he needs
Go to the f****** doctor
I don't believe any of the things that I just said appropriate
Cushing syndrome
That's all I'm saying you should go get checked out
I'm so anyway
We also know that Alex
And I don't know I don't know I don't think so
Adrenaline levels
Response all the time would be very hard to focus on something
But leave that aside
Construe
Eclipse starts talking about how
Things
And I think if you listen carefully
Get a glimpse of exactly why
He has a bad processor
I booked a public now
And they're like children
Little spoiled arrogantly scared children
Porsche
A book
Before I turn the page
Because I've heard them say it a thousand times
100 different ways
I know exactly what they're going to say
And then I'm going to turn the next page and I know
While he's reading
He's reading something
If it says what he thinks they're going to say then confirm
I know exactly what they're going to take
If it says something different
Probably going to be
What what they mean is what I would think exact
So many times by looking at its primary sources that don't stay with
He pretends they say
That has to be what that process is describing
Yeah that makes sense
Exactly what I expected them to say and then
I used
If I turn the page and it doesn't say what I think
Well I think it says this
I'll save it always from my Xperia
Of something
Like some primary source that he's not missing
Yeah
But I don't think
He was in a book club because I would like if he was just reading like
Ethology
To take me back to like a workshops in College English classes
Chipotle not good
Alex thinks that this is no big deal
Sandy Hook
He hasn't he has no real concern and talking about it
Just wants to talk about emotions
You know we got
Jim Tucker with his news
At this point in the show
Alex finds out the Sandy Hook
Is way worse than
He thinks it was a foiled
Shooting or something
Not knowing a lot of
But by this point
Next
For a fact
Killed at that school
And
Here is in
Dealing with that
It looks like
Shooter is a father
Christmas trees and I like Christmas
Commercial stress
Everybody so stressed out I just feel the bad vibes during the holidays
Dad
Oh my God
Disquiet
CBS news headlines
Is going to physically
You hear their Heaton mediately start
Say what I mean he's not staying it's fake butt
Literally everything he says after learning about the reality of this tragedy
Is to reinforce
Future narrative
He's going to push about it
So
What I set out to do this investigation
Investigation closed
You thought it was a different situation that it was
Now that the reality has come to Bear any realize they're a bunch of
Kids that got shot
And if he still doesn't have any of the real facts
She thinks it was the dad and it was
Once at first then a second later than all my God
Yeah
Him comparing its Columbine because he thinks Columbine was a fake
And then talking about the timing of this Obama second-term he's trying to take the gun exactly
Serve his interests
Pushing the idea that it's
Isn't
Fair
Way to cover the
It is not the act of somebody who is interested in
Hearing both sides
It's someone who's hoping fraying
That the reality ends up matching the story he wants
Citalopram
That wasn't prepared
That was his immediate instinctual reaction
Was to try and find ways to talk about this
That Arkansas
Spirit Oreo
He will not come out and say
But not yet
He was 85% inclined to say that
There were every inclination ever like little thing there is
Ocbf
Things responsibly
Concert with the cops instead of just randomly saying that it was some a******
Unlike
This episode goes on in boron verified
News thing
Come out
Those are the sorts of things as they come out that Alex
Uses to point out
Like they covered this up
Like the idea of
Possibility of a second
Computer
In the future
I'd like
They said that there were two Shooters and then they covered it up
When in reality that was
Reflecting
The fact that there was
Police
Walkie-talkie
Right
Be cautious of the idea that they could be arrested in the woods
Behind unrelated to
The shooter
Recorded
In the fog of
Absolutely
Necessarily
Report this stuff
A couple hours after
It's responsible for Ford Explorer
Probably
So something is coming
And he has for a while in the summer of Rage literally every year since he's been born
Tobacco
I told my wife this morning I said I'm feeling so much dread
I have never felt in my gut and my spirit
They're really going to use this
I'm sure they'll be the usual signs
Very quick
OfferUp it may be staged as
Is possible roads that we're going to be going down
It's quick
It's quick with no information
You just back
This could be station even if it's not it's probably some Prozac head
I know I know
So you cut clips
I just need to
At no point
Even take a second
To be like
I mean even the fake Republican thoughts and prayers to even bother with the b*******
Platitudes of these guys who secretly think the same thing that Alex is picking which is
We better stay thoughts and prayers in order to avoid
Is an interesting question and I wish that I had pulled more clips of stuff like that because
We ended up having
Be here for the next week
Care
For the people who are victims of this
Outside of crocodile tears
Verge of his fake crying voice
But is always talking about how they're going to take the guns is going to cause a civil war
He does talk about all this is so bad
Right
And then there's one point in the episode where he talks about
Thinking about these kids
Like pictures from the school for like a month ago
And the only way he
You can even emotionally connect to it is thinking about
If that's what it takes you to get there
Vine
But there's an
There isn't complete absence of
People who are named Alex on the show
Yeah, there's at least one caller
Who Express like
I can't imagine
People are going through
That's
Fairy live
Another thing
I just wanted I just wanted to confirm so nobody
Thought that it was like
Cutting the clips that make him look like the complete Nutter monster he is and then it was like
It's literally his first response is never
I'm sorry or I hope that this isn't Reno like
Edited in any way except for a starting point right
Reaction was exactly described how most of the show is
I think that immediate reaction tells you all
Need to know right semblances of
Humanity throughout but never anything
That I would
Put in the category of
Human response
There's nothing that is
Recognition of
These are
Elementor
Three students
Murdered in Cold Blood
Yeah
Because he thinks it
Or anything like that
We can't make that determination
Algebra
If one of the his new emotions should really have been empathy
Forgot about the new emotion he one of the emotions he'll never be a watch emphasizing
Jesus checking on some of those old emotions
Yeah it's tough
It's realtor
So after the Parkland shooting last year
These teachers should be armed
Alex was way ahead of the curve on that
After Sandy Hook that was prescription
Into
What should
Orderly evacuation
That
Is exactly what Alex
Would w
His response
Because that is
Is awful
That's something I think
He could be
Defensible about
Because every
Everyone else in the right-wing now in response
Parkland to sing
Very similar things
Yeah I did Alex's take on it was this is a real event I'm worried about the idea that they'll take my guy
Because of it
Not as monstrous as saying it
His actors are there anything like that
So I think that you would want that to be
Unfortunately
Even on this episode it's not
You've already hurt him speculate
You already heard it
Internals of a narrative
But he's going to water
High speed
Grow into
I can't imagine how that one massive blind-spot
Ali video
It's entirely video games ebony is always
An important thing for our Marin
You don't need to keep
God dammit
I think a lot of people
So in this next clip
Alex and started wrestling with the reality of
What's happened
Are you can you can see
I think throughout this is
A part of his brain that recognizes
How horrible
What's happening is
And then another part
Really really wants to say it
Yeah and his next clip
He's dealing with that part of his brain
That believes it was real
But
All he can do with that part of his brother
Brain
Is blame other things
For having caused
Now Shane 27
Connecticut has some pretty strict gun laws
We are just a very sick Society
Charter 5678 breakdown
Eli Lilly studies
He's misrepresenting
Pretty hard
But you heard in there
You got abortion
Prozac
Harsh gun laws in Connecticut
For corporate
Other than reality
In
What was that
42nd
I'm trying to wrestle with
It's pretty
Pretty interesting
You can see manipulation
You can see evasiveness
You can see
To figure out where we going to land on
If you're Alex Jones this is not you want to come into work for
You wish you accidentally called in sick or something like that because
Figuring out where to plant
Something that's always expected
Yeah cuz he's the expert
He's the guy who
Who knows how the globalist to work
And all that stuff
Come on Alex
What is it like
Tomorrow's news today
Play the Nevis Logan Mega red pill
Understanding is above all this stuff right
They expect that from
Studio
And he's blindsided by a bit of news that is
Christ
He's in a position where he needs to stay for
Claim right here already
Him trying to ambivalent
Lee do the fake
Falls Flagstaff
But then also
How to be an unwilling
Is the part of his brain
The runway
Like dealing with
I'm far more willing to give him the benefit
The doubt in this situation
Meaning
Let me let me actually let me try and put this a lot better
Based on his tone of voice
Honda
To talk through the
It seems to me like
He does feel like
Oh no this is a tragedy
This is a real track
And that part is trying to break out because his
To say that it's not real I think there's a Persona has to deny it
But his real human being is trying to break out
This is an issue this
Real I can't listen
Exactly
Human element
Vaxxed
I think I picked up a 2012 I'm giving him the benefit of Doubt and staying that
Actuation
He is 100%
He knows this is real
And he is trying to scramble to find a way
I think that beat
Cuz his response is so much less offensive than we would expect
Because
There is this waffling back in
For that little bit
But you can feed
Clear indications of
He wants to say it's fake
Yeah there is a choice that's going on
Himself
War
To a certain extent
He was covering his ass
You know exactly
Interesting
I wasn't
I wasn't specifically
The idea that like it does sort of
Vindicate choice
Yeah and end intentional line
It's hard to nail down
I think I think
Your argument is strong
I'm not a hundred percent
Just because
No I know that's what I'm giving him the benefit of the doubt that I would not give him later on
Do you know what I mean
Because the benefit of the doubt is
For my job pretend they're nothing framing it is
But it's actually
Alex's
Stop
Mother's Day
Be fake
Seems like really good timing
Alright
Maybe
Maybe you're okay
So that was
He said baby it's real
That's not good
That is not good
That's not a good way to report
Hey this thing happened
But
If we have
These indications
There are parts of the propaganda that we used about other
If some of those things lineup
Elicit
You know and I know
We can't do it right now it's almost
Yeah it absolutely is
Absolutely
Beetles that way pretty strong
His position is
Does development even change throughout the course of
This one day
Of his show
But nothing changes about the idea
If it's real they're going to use it to take our guns if it's fake there
Let's take our gun
No matter what
Hear that Express
Make yourself
Pause music.
Physically
Start a civil war
Before the shooting started
Always honest with you
Feeling of dread
So
Yelling over the begin
Beginning / middle of that clip like he did he really just want one
That is what you get.
They created him to do that
All that is
Is him
Saying it's fake
And also also him saying
Yahoo it is true he does give himself a lot of that
I knew it
In the show Alex Goes to cult
I think
The colors
You here on Alex's show
Cannot be taken in any other way than it
Being the people he has try
Inasmuch as they listen
His show
Like back in the day they would never say like
Hey
Product or whatever but nowadays
Because they have had forcement
I will take
Call if you
To promote my product
Of course
Responsive
Soap
Everyone calls in his show
Are all his fans
Even people who he says I take calls
The disagree with me that usually
About style over substance real actual disagreement
There are a couple times
But
Those people are still reflecting
Now that
Alex
Was it fake
And the reason that is important
Remember that
These are basically Alex's
We're calling it
Is because
Alex
Created this worldview in the post 9/11 World
We're like I know he wasn't
The only person saying it was
Is a false flag
Was one of the loudest mouth
Consistently does call thing
Fake that
The people who call again are ahead of Alex
In terms of the narrative they know that Alex
Alex is it fake just to believe everything like this
You've already said a bunch of times on the show
It's about trying to take our gun
So let's cut through the BS
Yeah
Begin like that last clip
I want to say yesterday
Alex and let's start talking
Doesn't say that it's fake
Good response but
It is you can hear
The yes
Under the skin
Little mouse inside his mouth
Yeah
Are you still following online
And I
Spell possibility
I'm saying that
Shooting star
Amazing figure or the government or Republican
Beer
Excavating
Happen more frequently
Well I know this for
Requires reporting
Large
2 shooters
Reports
When somebody else opens the door when
Programs
Police orders
Regardless
Absolutely
The most important thing has begun defense
You can tell that from the way scary
Responsive that caller is
Without saying yes
Yeah
Vague
He's trying to make it sound
Specific
Perfect condition
Under which we can now save this is fake
Yeah and
You wouldn't do that if that's the direction you wanted to go
Of course
Dumb f***
How can you honestly look at that and be like
It seems like these are happening with more frequency and then be like
Well clearly that's the government ramping up their let's steal your gun
Guess what this is a f****** epidemic
It's still like
Understandable why the call
Would think that
Given Alex's
Yeah
Training
It's hard to say
The course
You know to get your degree you have
I guess
Can't graduate Community College
This is going to be such an interesting
Investigation
Just
Based on the fact
Alone.
Like
Sandy Hook is one of those
Flashpoints in history you can point to where
We didn't do anything about it then
So that means
Like that's real
It's not going it's never going to be addressed
So horrifying
Exactly
You couldn't
Maybe you could maybe the best baby
Well we get hit with more horrifying realities on a daily basis
For writers in the world
To come up with some realistic scenarios that would shock up more
Then the idea of someone coming
Automatic weapon
Killing a bunch of
Children
Yeah but it's
Hard to fathom
Something worse
It was almost like a it was almost a test for America
And we utterly failed
People try not to fail Alex made sure
Didn't graduate Community goddamn
He was just mislaid by these who's playing
Investigation
Directions
Ultimately unnecessary
You just go back to the day we desire for it
Sweet
Recognition
Conscious
He knows it was
Doesn't know how to spell
Yeah so he probably does need those people like Wolfgang halbig to come around
To justify the things that he wants to say exactly
And I take it they're stumped
But
At this point
Can see where it's at
Very clear
Yep
Yeah there's no way that you can
Listen to what he's had to say so far end
Like
You just had debates
This guy would have done anything and everything for
Anyone like even is 99 of his collar said that it was real
And you should worry about
Eddievr
Send nextplus he talks about it
Are you talkin about how it's fake
But not saying
And Compares it to another
I called
And of course you know the Batman
Tampere for psych Warfare
Salary
As part of the program
Aurora Batman shooting will come up
Call space on
I want better served
To cover that on another episode
Because I know it will
On the episode rehab
Take me to
But for now all that's important
Alex
He's comparing it
He thinks the columbines fake
He believed that
Wednesday was directed to do his mailbombing
MKUltra program
False flag blah blah blah
Every single
Comparing
The events to covering
But he believes are fake
And it's not a coincidence
I don't know what a real shooter
I don't know if I've ever heard him cover something
This happened does it suck
I guess actually like
White protesters are hits
Nailed it
When.
Get the taxes by
He thinks that the realest of course
I don't know if I've ever actually heard and I know that
Probably partially because I haven't heard
I believe
Much like there's probably a real use of a source
There's probably an example of a
But he's not comparing Sandy Hook
Any of those
Potential example
He's only comparing what's going on to all
These things he's built up
With his rhetoric
To be triggers
His audience
Is there fake
And he's doing that
For a very specific
Prineville
Surprise
The pop of the narrative
Exactly what we've already said I'm
I love that we already got two
But just that idea of like
Everyone is listening knows where you going
Andi Mack you're going to see you're going to get to the medical mystery
House and Cuddy ever going to make out
Even when it comes
It's kind of disappointing
I wish these guys it had more fun with the shootings they thought were fake like
Look
All of the old
RFK wasn't really killed
Reverb
Brunette. Not that he wasn't really killed
What did Sirhan Sirhan
Okay well I get another one
Yeah so I wish
In this episode
Used talkingshit on the Russians
A lot
Like you in order to reinforce his idea that these false flag attack
He's like the Russians have been caught doing it a bunch
Steven
Clean up the apartment
He brings up as an example of the false
F****** hate him
He now is like I thought it was funny
He uses that as an example of
How dare you get it right
In the wrong service and then just change your mind
F****** ass
Nothing matters
All that matters is
Means to an end end in itself everything is just
Profoundly in a
So it was nextplus Alex
I think we've already seen
Things that I would not
Like to see anyone
Certainly
Times are still not like
There's not indication
He's saying
Things like this
Either but this is where I
Putting his toe a little too far over the
Is also reporting
So when he says that Sandy Hook has The Tell-Tale sign
I think that's a bridge too far
Because
You don't have all the information
You don't have your responsible Place reporting
Even all of them
CBS is reporting that there two shooters
If you report that with the caveat that
You know
Things Are
Not
Solid right now
Or whatever
Can probably walk that line
But when you introduce it by saying this has all the telltale signs
Which is
Implied whatever it is you want them steaks at
Where do you have now
Territory where it's at
You are
Doing too much
To make your audience
False flag hearts
Underneath the floorboards
Every time there's a false flag
Bumble
So in a civil war is coming
God I kind of wish it had and then wait for this moment
There is a Momo
Where Alex
I believe
Scrum
Research and Alex
And knowing how his brain works
I think he almost says
This is f****** b******* this was fake
30 stops
Himself
Very sure
From listening to this a couple times
That he
Really held his tongue
And absolutely
That is restrict on his part
Just want to tell you
Hey there's a lot of stuff coming up in the news
Isaac
I think the most interesting speculation is what is causing him
To restrain himself because it's clearly not the threat of
Beginning this episode he's so far under the radar at this point don't give a s***
Amatory things about tons of people already.
Fear that
What is holding him back and I'm not sure what that is
And I think
The best argument just because we are all pee
Even Alex is a monster
I think it's exactly what
You were talking about earlier
He knows this
Yeah there's a part of him is that
That that
That bit of humanity
If you ever seen a dog fall off a dock
Like a dog videos of dogs falling off docks
Videos of dogs falling off
Health don't park your paws will like
At the dock and there's nothing to grab onto so it'll be like
Like 10 seconds of them trying to stay on the dock and then falling
Hanna-Barbera cartoon where they go over the edge and look down at the edge of the cliff and they're standing there and then they looked at
I think that is Alex clawing at
At the dock
I think it's faster
Do you know that your entire career is predicated on you
You falling off this.
You can't
You kept these children know it is it is very long like
It's it's has to be some
The easiest xiumin EXO
If I take this week
I'm doing something
F******
No you can absolutely see him
Like
Possibly you can see him
Being like my career is predicated and is dependent upon me saying this
This is fake
But at the same time
I genuinely can't get the image out of my head of one of my kids
Being shot in
School
I can't get it out of my head
Give me a day
Give me a day and I'll be able to lie about this but today all I see is that phone call
When I come home that voicemail
Yeah they go for Sunday
That'll be our next episode
Alex's taking calls
Can you get the call for
From a guy in Connecticut
This guy
Is just spouting unfounded Rumours left and right
To do with
The shooting I don't really
And that there were some boxes of
Kids from Sandy Hook
Who were there at the bowling alley
Wow the shooting was taking
Play-Doh that proves it
Art schools
School District
Also I know that
Is it from when I was in high school
I took 0 hour bowling
Because
And I was going to f****** take another
EClass
They had buses that would take us to the bowling alley go to Bullock
Many
Or even could be like
I don't know
Christmas break is coming up holiday break
So maybe there's a we're done with our
Finals
Yeah
There's nothing really necessarily suspicious about the
But you staying at incest
Vicious weigh
And Alex allows him to
Give
All sorts of unverified rumors
On the show and respond to
As if
They means
Here's where Alex
It's gives his worth
Response
Multiple shooters
This is how the people actually got on the property
It's not that he's physically ill
Any of the guy is saying
He's physically ill about
The like
This amounts to the globalist
So earlier in the show us
This shoe
And it's interesting
Kirin are usually
From an ego standpoint
Yeah course
Versions of that
He wants a prayer
But it's not a prayer for the victims
At Sandy Hook
It's sort of a broader prayer
Google I'm calling for the sprayer
He does implies
That the children who were killed at that school
Were the victims of the
The globalist
Prayer
Very
Elicit
Betty's my
Great you might as well say we need to have a prayer and hope that the gun used in the shooting is
Is okay after the end
Christ
It's at
My Lord please
Put it into
So that gun
Can find a better home
What an ass
Totally
You know Alex
He's a good guy
She loves to follow
He's got to wherever
Information
And everything that happened
You can hear that wavering in his voice
Does a
He's gotten telling him that this is
Pretty over
But
Because we have to practice this
Version of
You have to take Alex at exactly
That's still not him saying it was
Right
Hunt has never wronged his audience to accept
His leanings are
So when he says my gut based on all the time
This stop my God is that it stays
To me that's as good
That's him saying
Right guys
This is not real
Without him having
At the very least everybody who listens to him is going to know what that mean
That means
Alex says
Which is this this episode so far has been like
I started out saying that he's 85% leading towards it being a false flag and everything he says
Just goes up
1%
To where that is and we're like
This is 99%
I'm almost ready to say I'm so close
Just talkin about the globalist
And this is probably
The government
It's hard to escape what he's saying there
And also eagle-eyed listeners will remember that when we talked about the Charleston Shoe
His way of
Deflecting from the horror of that
Was to talk about abortion
Yep.
You know that that's his way of
Could possibly
You know what
Got however many years of life they did they wish they could have killed him sooner
Go fuc yourself
I was going to say it's interesting but it's not
Here
Charleston performed with a f****** gun then we can have a conversation
But until then you shut the goddamn f*** off
Deflections the distraction
That's interesting
Noteworthy
The
I would say that you could easily hear the things that Alex is saying
On to whatever is thrown in his face
You know like he's just trying to keep a conversation
Host sharks
Possible
We are in trouble
It's all of it together first reports
I'm not just saying things
The timing
That is leading me to believe that this is part of some sort of a globalist
That's not good
The Tell-Tale sign
Of this being false flag
Rhino the visit
First Telltale
It happened
A gun was involved
Done false flag
You are more specific
These
Tell tale sign
What are the hillside
You're here Alex's
That's not what
What is the signs that you're talkin about
Some years ago maybe when we would catch you see a lot of local police now you're seeing just
I mean
Dominated by fbins
Always the same
Is him saying it's
Without
Confirming to a collar
That this is fake
Yep. Beside you saw the time
What are the telltale signs
Keep talking about
Because
Local
Responding to saying
Let It Go
That's what you said
Connect the dots
Fake
I would say whatever crime this guy is
Imagining
From his younger days
The scale of this crime
It also doesn't match
Breakfast
The amount of resources that we're actually
For assistance from State Police
Obviously would be interested in
The worst school shooting in American history at the time
Yeah so we got that you have to say at the time
None of that means
No except for it means that Alex
He's trying to
That's insane
Yep
So
You heard him say we have some guests
Yeah earlier
He's bumped
Because when the reality of this
He realize like I haven't got to talk about that
He didn't bump one of them
Hundred first Airborne Division for Weather Underground
Larry was a Vietnam vet
But he's most known as the
He infiltrated the weather
An uncovered a plot helmed by Bill Ayers and Bernardine dohrn
Thoughts of America cultural revolution in America
History education
Therapy
In-depth interview from 1980s
Cubans in Russian
Would stick to occupy part of the United States
What's the weather
Counter-revolution
Which of course is supposed
Alex's Patriot weird
I don't
He claims
Members of The Weather Underground told him
Not just going to go along and get on board with what they were doing
Presumably because they were die-hard capitalist
And also would need to
Nothing has ever said about the weather underground or billares has ever been supported by anything other than
There's no evidence of any of the stuff and since he was working as a mole for the FBI
He was never wearing a wire
You never produced anything Auto
Corroborating Witnesses
Come forward
But that has not stopped him from being hero worship by the anti-communist propaganda circles that we cover
They don't depend so much on actual evidence as they do
Appearance of Eva
It was exactly
Kill all who oppose it
Even in modern days
Heather tentacles have been all the halls of Academia in America
In 2016 when Alex Jones finally got to sit down with Bill Ayers
If you recall it.
Go well
Much a creature of whatever whoever runs the justice department
Preacher of the justice department
All the justice department
Military
Education
Interview
The time that Larry Graf wall would have been working for the FBI
Well it was under the Richard Nixon
Attorney general was John and Mitchell
For those of you who don't know what John Mitchell got up to in his career
In the lead-up to the 1968 election representatives of Nixon's campaign sabotage the Paris peace talks
Effectively ended the Vietnam War
They did this specifically to ensure that Nixon won the election
Deal
Menstration cut
LBJ head recordings
Richard Russell Mitchell was deeply involved
Bradley
Johnson allies.
Because Dixon lacked the political baggage
He could give them a better deal too
The actions of John and Mitchell Lee.
Pointless war that could have ended sooner
I need it for
Purely political motives
You think that someone like Larry Graf wall of Vietnam vet would want to work with that kind of
Forgot
Did another call Menorah T leader Everett Dirksen
Explicitly called Nixon's people were doing treason
Twitch Dirksen reply quote
I know
At the time Mitchell was Nixon
Campaign manager
And ran operations
For the campaign
In February 1975 John Mitchell was also found guilty of
Conspiracy obstruction of justice and perjury for his role in planning the Watergate break-in
Throughout his time as Attorney General Mitchell
Left-leaning
Immediately after Nixon won the election
You told a reporter quote this country is going so far to the right you won't
And disrupt civil rights groups and anti-war groups at every
Return
Also he ran the committee for the re-election of the president or is
Which was the fundraising arm of the Nixon 1972 reelection campaign
But really was mostly about money laundering
Creating burglars
Interesting Lee
Rodger Stone also works for creed
Weird
Given the circumstances
Stock
It what Larry grass wall says
Absent any other proof I think bellairs explanation
He's a liar who was paid by a criminal department of justice
Probably the most sensible conclusion here
Alex is just having it
Even though
Newsbroke
Because Larry story helps build Alex's building a budding narrative
Sandy Hook shooting was
Larry story was that in order to
Fit their desires
The Weather Underground was willing to kill 25 million
It's not true
But it goes a long way toward helping a struggling audience come to terms with the idea
Fifties people would also be willing to kill children in order to reach their goal
What I'm saying is that the fact that out
Bob Larry grass wall
Involves other people speak
Volume
About his intent
He has this guy on
Because he knows that there is a
He had it planned anyway that's probably a happy coincidence or whatever because he knows that there's
Something that will help
Speed of a narrative that he's working on
In
Continuing the interview
And I think
Like I said I think that speaks
Yeah
It's never not important to point out that the Weather Underground
Really far out of their way to try not to hurt
Really far out of their way to try not to hurt people as far as terrorist organizations go
They were really going for
0 cash
You with eco-terrorists and Diana
Things go
Generally
Anytime they hurt anybody even
It's a
Profound mistakes
There's planning involved
Just property damage
Yep
Some sort of a symbolic
Most of the terrorism
Very probably the broad brush but
Rules Etc
Terrorist
That exist
That's very different
All that up and wanted to talk about the history of the people that live
Because they don't
Fit whatever
Benign version Alex would like to
His work
And Alex
It shouldn't be
He shouldn't likely regret
Mitchell
What he presents himself to be should be
Super against this guy
Buddies.
Because it suited them
Pinterest
Like I said
Specifically because
Weather Underground narrative
It says that they wanted to kill 25
Which Alex says
Yeah
All that stuff
Is 2
Acclimate
The audience
He would kill children
Right and I
It's soon as I heard
He didn't bump I was like that's what he's doing
I get it
I heard this clip
I was like haha you son of a b****
Larry what's Your Gut on this right now
You son of a b**** that was you do
Fast
You know what do you know it's fascinating
The reason it's so
LBJ probably could have been re-elected
His memoirs
He could have been re-elected
I know Nick's
Like
And was also like when he was calling what they were doing treason
I don't think it should enter the campaign
World
That should not
Do we should not talk about this topic you know
I'm only talking to you about that
What is one of the reasons run is because
Because of his family's history
Of dying
That he would die within 4 years
What are the reasons he didn't run it because
He said that the American people had enough presidents died in office
Year that is doctors predicted is that nuts
President
To rewrite history
The Paris peace talks to begin
That it would
Conclusion we imagine
Right
Is Fantasy of Lights
War ended exactly
Notes from the fact
Right
Difficulty doing that s***
A one of them
Was John Mitchell
Who was the head of the Attorney General
Who
The buck stops with him right
Whatever Larry grass
History
Is almost never like
The right-wing didn't get his ass
You know what I'm saying
Like an American history so often are are like
Here was the moment
You don't like we always do
Murdered the moment that their popularity was at their highest
Somebody murdered
It is it is one of those like
Motherfuking right-wing assholes always say all if we do this we're going to get killed in
Claimed actively talked
Enemies
They get appointed as ambassador to Venezuela
President
Especially
Life
Not make
This
F****** ugly
Right let's find a way to deal with this
Like behind-the-scenes cuz
Let's Roll.
Otherwise we will have two charges against that would be fun
So
Just because
I think
Interesting and I haven't heard an episode
Larry actually shows up
His. Cuz he dies
Huey died by the time
Most of our episodes
Cover like a nut
Panera
Alex talks about interviewing his daughter
And stuff like that
When you ask me
Does Alex
His response when I asked him
Based on your experience
With the weather kill 25
Do you think
In order to get R Gun
The end of
Very long
But at the same time
I can imagine
What it must be like for
Answer keys
Solaria even even me pathological liar Larry Graf wall
Have to say this is
Is f***** up
Expresses more of that cumin
You want to hear
Yeah
So Alex next clip
What's up
So in this next clip Alex
I mean again
Just all insinuation
Comes into a second term
Smells
Just quit
Teething
Just quit f******
Do it just do what you want to do and say it
You have no conscience
Do it or don't
This is an example
Yeah this sort of
With my nipples
So in a text when we were talking about earlier the idea that like there's mist
Recording early
And that that sort of thing happen
Alex is now going to church
The ideas
The people had reported
Various thing
Like there's talk that there might be a second
To the surface
They realize it was that report of the second
They're going back and correcting their story
Alex interpret
Scrubbing the internet
Use that as a correlation
Articles
Health Ranger
From the news
That was going to
Verdad
Is also not suspicious
But
Where there's smoke there's fire
Drill
He's making of like if there was a drill then it's fake
Also there's a bunch of other things that I'll accept it
And I will say this is fake please DeGraw or whatever
French things and established
Sprint
That would be the things that is like
Beyond The Pale
Ironic How concerned he is about the parents of the Vic
I mean like before that we went we need to talk to them before they get harassed
Work at the school
Yeah
Play situations
Implies that he believes that
We're talkin about that clip
The only way that that Clinton
Makes sense
Because he's saying
We need to talk to them before they get threatened
Was there a drill there
The only way you
Is if you
Believe
With no evidence that there
Was a drill there
And
Threatened
In order to cover it up
Tell if there is no evidence
It means that you didn't get there quick enough and everyone's been threatened
And if someone tells you that there was a drills
I do still think
He's on the right side
Legality
Probably
At this point
It's kind of hard to say
Because of what
What are you saying
Plies and you know how is Audie
Yeah
In the 2015
Go back to
Event
It's all actors
Absolute
What do you say
Ambivalent
Ambivalent cowardly
I think it's one of those things where this were an isolated incident
You could
Say
He's protect
But if we were going to if we work more heat anyone else anyone else we were doing
In this if this was court case where he anyone else you'd say
You'd hope so
Kind of blew it on a little bit of that sorry about that
With our contact
Text with all of what we've put together
This one show where he doesn't even explicitly say I feel like we could prove
Beyond A Reasonable Doubt
That he was committing a crime on this show
I think it's
It's a borderline
It's close
I don't know I'm not I don't I think
Spiritually and intent wise
Yeah the intent is there for sure
Butternut Tree the actor
Yeah
But
Let's put all that aside
For a second because
Journal
And tell me what kind of
Any thinks what he's doing is
Is reporting
Like that
It's the one I heard this neck
Clip I was like
No one
Would ever
If they cared
About
No one would
Ever
Put this call to action into the world
If they were interested in reporting
The actual
Fact
Big-ticket takes
Let's play
I don't know someone stole a loaf of bread from Jacob Street
Fine
Whatever happened
They would never do something
This next clip
Grossed me out
News reports
So he's written memo I believe or what
Aaron Dykes one of those guys
His written article enemies
The Second Amendment will exploit
Connecticut
Good shooting
That's the article
So that is already
Leave your comment
That article and I
You wouldn't do that if you wanted real information
Who the f*** is going to leave like a comment on that article that's going to be
If you ever read the Infowars comment
It's insane never do that a lot of spam
Large sunglasses
Question for you
Is Trump doing a great job or is he doing
The greatest job
Trump email
It is not
If you want to get information
On the show
The day of Sandy Hook being like
We got this article with a
Very bias headline
And what we want is
Put on the air like no one
I would do that picture
No one
That is
To the idea that he cares
Sprite
Drama
Yeah I guess
Get people to go to article engagement
You've always wanted to be on my show but you have been able to call yet been able to get through well guess what if you comment
This article
Then I will take that and I will read it
On-air think about how famous you Dan will personally because Alex
Will read out your b******* on air
Painfully siniakova probably accurate
Bentley
Drum up more traffic to your site the only reason
Damn
Goddamn
The great Rite
I never really thought about that I just thought it was like
I want more contact
And I don't care where it comes from
But you probably
This is this is a rare
Circumstance
That's where I'm going
Get a lot of interest
If I can funnel them to my website
Explode well I mean it's like nothing drives up gun sales more than a mass shooting
So there is a
There is a very real
Tangible monetary interest that all of the gun manufacturers have in making sure guns
Got mass shooting
Continue to happen
Yeah it dropped so brutally cynical
Is it that probably what's going
Maybe it is and maybe that
Part of the couch
He's going through
Use wrestling
Where do I live
And now by this point
In the show he's realized
This could
Help
This could really help right
Forget it on the map
Right everyone goes to
To the website
Comet
Maybe we get
1000 ship comment
But one guy run with or whatever
Then that thousand comments
Thousand
Actual hits
Debs
Install more AdSense
I mean it is it is very much like there's no if you recorded everything that the CEO of
Smith & Wesson ever said
There is no way
That he is never said
I'm kind of happy every time a mass shooting happens because their sales go up
He's been like
Mass shootings are great for business
Save that dumb dumb had to do like four hours of radio today
Prediction
About what
Is going to happen
Cuz of this Sandy Hook shooting
This is very interesting
Because
I agree
Grass wall
Alex
If they hype this up
There will be real that shoot up school
Have we seen any examples of him or have all school shootings
But
Even take that aside
The implicit thing that he saying is that this one isn't a real.
Inspired
Which
You just have
How to cut through a little bit of what
Are you saying
Without saying
And realize like this is the
Absolutely
Michelle Alex takes a call
From somebody who
Cousin
Teacher
It's Sandy Hook Elementary
I don't know if that's
No idea faster
Could be
The benefit of doubt
The benefit of the doubt is not given
To an Infowars listener giving a second-hand information
From a cousin
I will never act on the information that's being provided by this guy
Infowars collars who prison-like
Red flags
Back to the school
But unfortunately
Defensive
About the idea that
Like he thinks it
Steak and other people are not thrilled
Oh that's not good
Amateur information
Is going to hell in a handbasket
Alex
I'll try to make it quick Barbershop
I got a text message from my phone about a shooting at elementary school
I live in New York I went to college in Connecticut
Call my my roommate who I went to school with to make sure his daughter was okay
Emily told me that the school was in Newton
You're very
My mom texted me
And she said oh my God that scary School carries my cousin
Call house
I know that we want to
Doubt all of Alex's callers in
Charismatic
Exact
That is not how your brain works when you have a square
First-year pitching
Oh I realize that detailed
How people communicate
His his passes the smell test
I can believe him on the fact and also disbelieve him on the
Interpretation
At the barbershop in this job
And I said I'm not saying that it wasn't but I wouldn't put it past them and they were like
Do they kill innocent children and I said excuse me I said abortion
Taxis in poisoning food and water these people are Satan
So he's reinforcing this caller who may or may not have a cousin who worked
At the school
Yeah who's the false flag
Because of listening
The barbershop
Hold on why would you do that
That should be
Trying to bring this
As opposed to
Reinforcing the
So far the only Heroes
In this story are
Barber shop
You're f****** crazy dude so that's really weird like
Responding to these people who
Dealing with
Like that guy's dealing
Some s***
Like on a personal level
He's got to be strong
Like it cousin was it
Right
He has a connection
What's collagen
Look at that.
And I was like yeah
All reinforcing
The Prelude to staying
And I know
It's such a
And there isn't
Necessarily
A strong payoff
To even when we're going to end this episode
Of him being like
Anything but
He's doing
Is interesting
Because
Because of his personal care
He knows
That it is
Because his cousin
Is it
His concern
His text to all of his family members into his friend
From college are from a very real place of
Did it happen
These kids
Were killed
He's not in the fall he's he's in the false flag but in that
All the kills
All the kids were actually
Murdered
It's not
Crisis actors or anything like that
So it's fascinating for him to call in
When we know that Alex is going to that all of these people work
Right
Because he's getting first-hand
Borderline
From a first-hand stores
That everybody really is dead
Uno
The difficulty of being
Because there are so many
Conspiracy
You could take ya
And maybe that's part of Alex
Is
Where is the line I draw
Or is it
That the globalist
Put the shooter into the school or is it
That he was a real shooter and then they covered it up
Doesn't quite know exactly
Glee what
Yeah
On one level you just want somebody to
Straight up
And
Like deal with the
The fact is there
There's tacos
They're being to shoot
We'll see
If the facts
Yeah
Then there's another version
Alex
Future Self
That is
F****** aggressive
And just I don't
Give a s***
F*** you
If ya go fuc yourself
He's not doing either of those
He's playing the fence
Cuz he needs to buy this
Because exactly what you said
Hour-and-a-half
You knows it's
And there is a
Part of him
Knows he's going
To do what
Yeah
From a very
Exposed
Purely
Practically
Moral
Questioning
Is it
Worse
If he
Knows it's real
And then lies about it
Or is it worse
Doesn't know it
And lies about it
Do you know what I mean
Utilitarians generally
Results
Yeah I would say no
You're doing it makes it worse
Equivalent
Pictures of knowingly doing this or
Mr. Magoo
The end result is the same
But if you
You know what you're doing
You are there is a will Baha'i
We talked about all the time
The idea of
People who are Bad Axe
Position like
That is
Yeah that's enshrined in our legal system
That that winter that libel is
Intent intent it does come in
Legal death
I think
Yeah for sure
I think we've proven that Alex's intent is to lie about
I don't know if we
Proven it but we've seen strong indication
Fair enough
Presidente
I ruin the fun of a lot of these things
Because just like sticks
Hold on
I know that
I know that there's a
But this point I don't
We can't
I think that what we have is
Very
Very strong in
That he wants to lie about this
And his
Vestigial
Oregon
Decency
Humanity
Emotion inside of it says three vertebrae that stick out from his ass
A little bit too far his
It is weird
Tonsil tonsils of morality
20 seconds
I would tell you the truth
For sure
That's the struggle that you have
Struggling a noble
Oh hell no
I didn't expect Define
Like when I look back
Like what I expected
Because I listen to
The Boston bombing
I am here
Right
Is it happen
He's just like
Which is like this is the turning
Because the Boston bombing was after
Exactly this is the point where he had that
Like moral to here are two paths to go down
It's possible that you know
And maybe that's what you don't expect to see
You go back to the actual date things I'm super grateful
Because I did expect
That
Boston bombing
Episode
Yeah
Is this
Wishi-washi and Bev
Whatever
Like you can hear him obviously
But not
Demonizing
Children
This is the David Anakin kills
Like this moment
We're watching this man
He was dark before though
That's true
Yeah
Can all
Yeah I mean there is.
Represent
Alright
What about the
Is that are cheap
Will you ever
I do think it's interesting
Because I
You think there's a demarcation
Like
This is part of
Like I said
Think I think that when
You accept
Lying about Sandy Hook
For opportunist
You definitely put yourself
Send a position where like
You are
You're too far gone
Mike
I think it's possible
Enter a realm of like
I have no soul which makes this doubly fascinating in that this might actually be the one
Instead
Really delineates the Alex of
The past
Who was
Still an a****** but he was also that whimsical
Who is Montresor which is
Irredeemable
And we'll see
I don't know
We'll see I think it's very
I don't know what
I don't know what it is
Cuz it's too simplistic
Shredz
Nascent Humanity
Because I think
We should call ourselves
We are probably giving way too much credit.
Or or what
Right.
That's our interpretation
And of course there's business people search
But we could also be wrong
And be given
Trying to figure out
Where's the money
Where is the money angle he could be just restrain himself because
Look
Market vest
What is the
The best way to
You do it I don't want it
I don't want to stay at if Y is more profitable
And I'm not sure which is yet
Gotta
Surroundings it's possible
This is a human being or operating from Human impulses
It's so much easier for us to empathize with the guy that we talked about on a daily basis
For several years now
If he has that moment
Long pause
Because he experienced
For us to actually
Really
Finally put the nail in the coffin of this is a human without
Human empathy or impulses or anything whatsoever
Because if
Pause
Is
Purely
Prophet Bass
Then this is a non-human
Like this is a
This is a pure
Serial killer
The salesman
Morlock
Show Alex
He's like he's taken
Calls
He's done his business
People about
He has a report
Is a special report
But he
Put together
About the Mayan apocalypse
It's coming up December 2012 versus whenever it's going to go down
The end of the show
He does this
He throws to this
5-minute Special Report
Worst day for it's a follow-up I think that he
So much work into
He's like
There's no goddamn
We're not bumping it
Dickies like
Zoodnews
I'm out of my league
Yeah
You coming out
Get off air
So he just goes to
Dispatcher
21st is not the end of the world
He skips a
In order to play this special report wow
The end of the world but guess what
Vaccines
No it's just a special report was like the Mayan apocalypse shoes bulshit but also
Afraid of all the things
It's one of those weird things.
He's trying to tell you
Be cool.
You know who's afraid of the buying apocalypse
Liberal Liberal
Don't get into
It's that s***
Are tripping out next
It's a super long report
It goes
Across the commercial break
And then in the final minutes of the show
Alex says
To try and like
Bring thing
Home
22 children at Connecticut
That is a inside job
Money
That's what I said I said
Melissa
And daughter like
Esparto
Heaven Help Us
Who knows
Hey if your angle is who knows
Sort of thing
If your ankle is
Nose
Then you can't be speculating that this
Might be
You can't do both of those things
And that's what he's
He's trying to play Both Sides
And the reason he's doing that
We have one last clip
The show
It is just
More
Call
That's literally the end of the show
This didn't happen
That's he's already said
He wants to take your gun
Of course this is
The implicit
Behind that is
Obama
Whoever his minions are
Made this happen in order to give them an excuse to take your
I think like
I mean on 130 substantial level
And for us to do
Cuz at the beginning of this episode
Is it really
Is Alex's
Modern-day perception
Deidre
He thought it was real but then
These other
Forces led him astray bright
Right
Things to do with this episode
Show up at all didn't show up at all
Yeah Alex on his own accord
Is talk
Self
Fake agree
By his own
Instinct on the episode
The day of
I don't think
That this investigation
It's a closed case already
I want to continue
Fantasy
See where it develops
Because I know that his narratives are going to
It works yeah
Forget those quote-unquote anomaly
Quiznos
It'll be
To see how bad
But
The day it happened
He spent all this time
Trying to insinuate
His audience
He has no
Nope one of the reasons that I am
Interested
Is because just like when we started the show
Just like when we did 22
I'm just like when we did 2009
I am all the sudden asking myself all over again
Who the f*** is this guy
What are you doing
Chameleon
2009 Audi
Ridiculous
Strain
Nefarious
Chameleon
That's a new emotion that I've been in that lately just bad
Might be new one to him to I'm interested to see where this goes no f****** idea
How bad is
Is it going to get
I apologize
Really bad it's going to get really bad
I think what we walk away from this first episode with
What is
A very
Very
Clear science
That
From the
First second
You knew this was
Because I didn't know how bad it was
Every impulse
But he had was
Say it
It's fake
And then
Weird parts
Yeah
Overlake
Committing
I think we'll get
As we go forward as
I hope
Cuz otherwise that's going to
Keep me up at night
We'll see
Anyway
Waze website
Hey babe
It that is a place you can
To knowledge right
That's correct
Underscore
Also we are at
Facebook
The goddamn f*** Admiral really upset about that so stupid it looks like a rock
Massive blind spots that I never even can
Sidered looking into like a rock
Legitimately feel the dumbest I've ever felt in my entire life
Accepted
I do I'm wrong I'm an idiot
Forecast for
So much for listening
With another episode
Friday
I'm not sure it might actually be
This might be a barely finish this investigation
Yeah whatever he's doing
The present day
He's already told people like
It's time to kill soon
Yeah it's going to be like
I suppose I suppose the day where he says it's time to kill now
He'll never do that
She knows better at the end at the end of the day
Yeah
Cuz I want to see
But I will say
That
Grass wall
What is a real piece of s***
No he did kill us we have
38 minutes
Bel-Airs was tertiarily involved in this episode because of Larry grathwol
I don't believe The Bel-Airs ever killed anybody
I'll give him the credit
Absolutely
And that's out
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color