Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages
Jordan
What's the longest you had to go without hot water
I don't know
I mean I've been in the woods for a couple days
Like that
But even those times
You know you could go
A ways away and find a shower
But I still think
Maybe I don't know I've never camped in the woods
No
It's like living in a hotel you bring your own
For the summer my parents and I drive across country to visit in California
Paper Hotel
National Park
And stuff like that
KOA
I was just like I wanted a f****** hotel
Because
Today's weather
On the road or sewing
Can tired of these campsites
As we go to a KOA place
He's all excited about
This is
This is great isn't it
There's a little bit of that
Behind some bushes
That is a great mall
Not a
You got really sour about that
Can't play
Angela moose
VI Campground oh that's that's
That's scarier than you think
Everybody likes to think of like Bullwinkle
Real moose
Let me walk that back
Apartment now with
Very inconsistent hot water
I think I kind of been living for two years about the table at least not on demand
Topgolf
The building
We talked about water
Alex Jones
Going to be some fun but before we get to it shut up
And are supporting the shows
Your nail policy walk
Journal apology walk
I'm a partner for Master P
Could have been one of the No Limit soldiers
Nothing much
Famous
Hot dogs
Nathan thinking responsible
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Exactly
Finally
I appreciate it also very much
You are now
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of
I don't want
If you're out there listening music
My book I don't know what a rock or a bark
Attendance
Please do
I was just going to Barrel through December 16th
Hey because the 15th was out what his narrative was going to be
I know
It would be wrong to say anything to definitive
But yourself
Figure out where he was going to land on
Who's all the arrows pointing to Bugs Bunny and nothing helps
Resolve that sort of thing like a day off
We're going to come in
You going to have
His narrative together
I will find out if that's the case
Episode
I opted not to do present-day episode mostly because they don't
I don't care
I just assumed you did a Bernie Sanders impression
Really
Have a whole lot of intellectual curiosity
Or even narrative puncturing curiosity about whatever he's doing now
Like if Rodger actually goes to jail early we might check in
The present but he just does not hold as much interest
Like priority to me
If some of these other things
And we aren't
We are not
Tubi
Whatever's happened
We can't be following in his wake
If we want to do
Do the show we want to do
So where do we go
We will do present-day episodes
Next week this is what I'm so much more
Right now and
Where I spent more of my time
Just all
Cancel
Pipe gave this caveat at the beginning of Wednesday's episodes that that episode wasn't
I don't think you've gotten
Bad
So don't expect
Like we throwing around anything
I don't know what is exact
Something's Atwood
Be traumatic
For someone to hear
But I don't think he gets into any of that Terror
We're safe
In terms of disgust piss is almost going to make the hammer drop even more horrific
We find this episode makes it so much more.
Depressing where it ends up
So
Anyway
Eva's first clip where Alex is starting off
The show I found out that it is Adam Lanza
Who was the
Perpetrator of the shooting
Is viceland a lot of information
Reporting on it
He thinks is the most important
Me away on this
I like that I like that you said that as if
Do you have time traveled and listen to our episode
He didn't show up and stay open
Sunday
Wild horses
I almost hurt him played and if you think of that
Didn't speak much for my mental state broadcast
We are going to be here for 2 hours obviously
I want to drill into
Viciously right now and
Ecology
Throughout history
Disarm the people
So this is what he's more interested
I think the supposedly the means
Tim
I don't know
I think it's still on the cusp
Of being inappropriate monstrous
Got a question we're going to have to keep coming back to is like
Is this monstrous threat
And I think
Because of the initial
Speculative
I think to a certain extent a day a day and a half
2 Days Later
You could still have like we might get more information on this
And it might end up 5
This is wrong also
Reporting
Developing story
Not a
Recover operating
It's not says William Hopper leading a climate change
I know you're not happy about that
Believe so
Yeah
I think that bodes well for
Climate
So
Like I said I think that's
I don't like the idea of
He wants to spend
Most of the rest
Show talking about the psychology of gun
It might it might be the wrong thing to focus on declared a national emergency
Laws passed
Schoolboy
In this next clip though
You hear Alex
It is very comforting
The beginning of the clip
And then wander into very on
But it starts pretty well
But
Okay
Mischief profile
Caucasian
Call Curtis
Autism
British medical journal medical term
So I don't like that characterization of
People
That clip is to me
Leave the path of Alex
Because it starts with
If you believe the official story and I-10
Which is good which doesn't sound accurate though
That is not a good
Reporting
Q indicating that I think
It might be real
But then when he starts giving his reason for why
He's like
Because of vaccines turning a door frame
The beginning point
Right there close to acceptable to end a thought I believe
I think I believe you.
New thought
Yep
And Derek that sort of mentality
Carries On In
Text clip
From a defensible place in
Into a real.
Not vents
Because
Has children and most of us have young children
And when
Incredible
And the reason the reason that it's gone up is because of all these
These people on these sites
Like to see
Offer condolences
Most of the families
Right
Because that doesn't Decay that he does know that
He knows
Tito's
Everybody everybody
He wouldn't behave this way if there wasn't an awareness on some levels at like
Whatever I end up saying eventually
I don't know if you
How much awareness he has it
No matter which end of this road is the beginning of the road is awareness
But this is real
Yeah
That's good
But also way worse eight mix yeah it makes the eventual Infowars harassment
These people
So much more
Dirty
Intentional in and disgusting
Holy s*** these mass shootings
Tireli possible
They are
Increasing
And my children
If that's fine
Fart
You get there
I mean it's not it's it's kind of it's a little bit like that
Right
I agree with you
Dealing with Alex Jones
Yeah
But again it's a huge loss
Indicate
Things later
It's built on a foundation
Absolutely
Right
Do we know exactly
This is that is entirely a years later
This is not excuse
No by any means but it is a sort of recency bias there with him right
Kevin later on cuz he doesn't give a f*** anymore
Because
Like all of us has become
Possibly you know it could be
Preemptive just
Certification for his only wanting to talk about guns
Rightly because that makes him talking about guns and how they want to grab them
And all that stuff a little more palatable because he's at the same time recognizing
The horrible tragedy
So there's
There again
We're speculating
Possible to know exactly
What is going through his mind
These are
These are some of the things you kind of
Might be going through his mind when you deal with someone like that
Inveterate liar
It's like a small
Broken ring in the chin
This guy is a psychopath but for one brief second you can see that missing scale in the underbelly of them
We know that he doesn't
You say it's fake it before that clip
But we have 2:15
I don't believe
Based on our last episode
All these nefarious weirdos
And convinced him
Right
That kind of
It loses a little bit of it
But I still don't know what the path is
There's a real
That he needed those sorts of people to
The cover
Intrinsically wanted to me
Maybe because they're better for traffic to the website
Maybe because they're better
Reinforces they want your guns narrative
Impossible but
I'm excited to see
I bet it's not as soon as we think
You know
We listen to the December
21st 2012 episode 41 of our
Episode
That's true all that much
From what I recall
Christmas
After that
He's got to take
Couple days off Broadway
Christmas
The end of the year I bet he doesn't
That's my prediction for right now
I really don't like him bringing up Sirhan Sirhan like
Robert Kennedy wouldn't be his greatest
Mortal enemy there's ever been because do a lot of that repurposing villains in it
Allies
History
Them however he sees fit the greatest
And murdering the eventual
True president
Example of that
Super egregious that we'll be on our next episode
We'll get to that when we get to it
Wants to make the argument
Course
He's going to
Use resources
Is that I think might be a little biased
There's overtime
Cetera
Your gun
In order to do it that was the first
Serdica knives
In Australia and New Zealand
Brazil
The preservation of
Have you
School shootings are mall shooting
We didn't have semi-auto handguns and rifles
Register
And then
Where somebody uses a bolt-action
That's not how it works
Country
Different histories
Gun laws
And they all have come
Two different places
Yeah if a gun law perspective
Advair
National sovereignty has led them to
1st Amendment
Japan
First Amendment rights are there variable gun laws
I'm just a country
Over simple
Application
These attacks
But the reason he's doing that is because
That is what you'd like
The store you'd like to tell
Throughout the course of history
Xscape theater
Attacks in order to the road gun rights
Gun laws
And he believes that Obama is an aspiring authoritarian Hitler
Then
Follows from those two premises at the conclusion is that Sandy Hook is fake
Yeah
Of course orchestrated by government whether it is real or not it has to
To be orchestrated right in order for the government to take our guns
Either it's bacon
Or it's making everybody it doesn't matter either way
Anywhere near actor
I will say that with
I don't
Very close
Like what he wants to say is
Quickly they marched like him
Who shot up everybody
He was all drugged up they killed him in the school
And then covered it up
What's up like that
That's the version of it that seems like what he wants to tell
The actor stuff
Because even on his
Yeah 100%
This is absolutely him saying that
The government murdered
People
Statesville whole thing like the mood lamp
Ending which we all of course no
Right it is
I think it's
To save it
I don't know I don't know what's worse
Because
Children if you call them crisis actors and it is
This one might be
On the slightly different
Basically
Take it to its parts
What are you implying
People cuz it's not just the government actually
Did the killing of those children
You're imagining some member of course
Pretty awful to put on somebody
The other version
Pretending
Both of them
I don't know where to plant my flag
Worse
Yeah but they're but they're both
Tremendously and
Incredibly disrespectful
Just absolutely psychopath
The only reason I bring that up at all is
Because the tickets in Portage
Recognize
Is there are different breeds
And I think Alex
Traffic
Yeah
I don't think that version
Synthetic staged
Some of that could have actually been the influence
Negative
But he was ready to hear it based on him believing
Did it and I'd setup Adam Lamb so I don't know
Look at you think that 911 is an inside job that's awful
If you think that 911 didn't actually happen in the towers are still there
It's weird
I think
Me the most about this investigation at
The unknown
Miss of it
Great expanse
We're walking in
KOA campsite this is the actual would know
Is that
That nuance
Difference
He actually saying
Lizzy Capri understand that better
Do you understand
The present better
Yes there is something
From that even if it does seem like
A little bit
That's a moral argument that
It doesn't make any sense
At the end of the day there's there's children
The conclusion that
He's tough
His world
I still don't think that lets him off the hook for any
Curiosity
What's an excuse
Still word investigation
Is worse than we thought which was Bill worst still hasn't shown
I don't know
Take the guns they're all doing
Like all this stuff whether or not
They want
How to take gun
Because
Pittsburgh gone on
They want to take guns
Treaty says
Animation for fiction Summit
Church Road
Because civilian ownership a firearm
That's problem
Is that a quote from
Potential source
It's hard to tell exactly
Where that entered
Call phone if you
He's going on about here is the arms trade treaty
Since the process began
Sign
It's been focused
Ton of patriot propaganda
Specifically that it was the world government signaling thereabouts
Everyone gun
The problem is that it doesn't do anything
The arms trade treaty as the name might suggest what about International illegal weapons trap
That's very clearly and specifically what it was
Creating International agreements to put in place instruments to help
Blackmarketarms
Begin to release you should be
Does it kind of gives legal law-abiding gun owners a bad rap
Buttercup
People but it also hurts
It was almost called the no-more Iran-Contra
He also knows a lot of those dude
That could be an issue
It was doing
You says if they're loyal opposition
Like 2012
He is not super into the NRA
Do you like
Right roads
From your keyboard
It's a very boring energy
He has a
They don't actually talk about at all
The Treaty of self is UN arms trade
I go so far out of its way to stress
The individual states are not bound by the treaties alter any of their domestic laws
From page one
Words specifically reaffirm quote
The Sovereign right of any state to regulate and control conventional arms exclusively within its territory
The only goal in constitutional system
The treaty even gives countries a backdoor to leave
I want to be a part of as it says an article 24
Each state party Shaolin exercising its National sovereignty have the right to withdraw from this
They even say that they don't
Have to give a reason to withdraw
And the only qualification is that if a country with drawers
That doesn't mean that they're immune
Consequences for breaking the treaty but only if they broke the treaty before they withdrew
Most toothless thing that you could have more or less
Withdraw from the show you
You've been breaking it and get away with it
The only thing I can think of that Alex
We talkin about here
Other thing
Is the UN report that they released in July
It was held about
Erratic small arms and light weapons
Not surprisingly
It's also didn't say anything about it
Rights to own
We reaffirm quote
The right of self-determination of all people
Taking into account the particular situation
The people's under Colonial or other forms of alien domination or foreign occupation
And recognizing the right of people to take legitimate action
With the charter of the United Nations
To realize their inalienable right of self-determination
This shall not be construed as authorizing any action that would dismember or impair
Integrity or political
Independence Day
Conducted themselves
In compliance with the principle of equal rights and self-determination of all
Wait
If I understand correctly does that mean that if
You are like the Virgin Islands and you decide that you want to be your own country
Illegal weapon sales are fine
No cuz this is this is that report not the treaty itself
Very reasonably could be
Take up arms
American Revolution total selling illegal weapons till like Russia
We got to solve this probably recognized
Of people's to take legitimate action
Realize their inalienable right of self-determination
I mean they're straight-up sing the right of occupied in Colonial Heights
To take up arms against their oppressors
Witches
But I guess if you can
Came to a point where
You could demonstrate or had a good argument that the United Nation in and of itself
Was making it so you had no self-determination or freedom
Jacob armpit
Where is similar to
France recognizing the United States is the country immediately following the Declaration of Independence
You know like the UN will immediately
Cheap knives if you're a colonized
If you're like hate I don't I don't know if
Positive that hasn't been used well or anything like that
Put out in July 2001
That report eventual arms trade treaty
Does discuss the need
Regulation and oversight of weapons
Exporters
You be able to find
Legal weapons traffic
So I bet anything that this is what Alex's
Exaggerating
He was any attempt
To deal with the problems created by the illegal use of gun
And being an attack on his legal ownership
I'm at the position that requires
Create strawman out of every perceived
Attack on Gunn
Which unfortunately undermines whatever he wants his boy
And I also the US signs at but it's never been ratified so we're not really even subject
Ratification would have required two-thirds vote in the Senate
He was dying to 2013
Even though the Democratic
E345 lead over the Republicans that session of Congress McConnell was still the minority leader there's no chance
Alabama was going to be able to sway enough Republicans ratified
God dammit McConnell is going to go down as one of his
History's great villains
He has carved out a real spot for himself has real bad
Civilian ownership of any firearm in the United
The legitimate power Monopoly of the state is not a quote
You want it all
Put out by the NRA and the Heritage Foundation
In order to undermine support for the treaty
None of Alex's information reflects reality nor does it come from
Yeah and even that power Monopoly of the state touch libertarian language
No way a Blog
Would phrase it that way
So in this next clip Alex listen to a bunch 2009
Because we know a lot of those narratives
Is using in 2009
He's using them still
About them as if they're
As opposed to being things we
About
That were dated 2009
Weird
Weird to have Mamas & the Papas behind that
Yeah very weird
Anna Mello
Throw the brake button eating gun for
The Prozac heads
He is gross not good
My exit is just my except all the stuff from 2009
Perceive
The tax on the Patriot community in the
Militias and stuff like that
You put it under a microscope
You look at it and
You see that he's just making that up
And it's this is why
Things
We do or importance
Because now that we have that is a piece of our awareness
And people understand
You can hear that clip
And before
You could have thought
Security at all these people trying to demonize the Patriots
I don't know
We do know real events
Years later absolutely pulling from these Wells of his brain
In order to justify the gun grabber
Paranoia narrative in order to
I don't know what would you call it
Create
Like foliage around having
Talk about Sandy Hook
Specifically
Like in
The like
Wishy-washy
Teasing saying
And stuff like that
It was the day off
No matter what
So I can buy even more time
B just talk about whatever
Talk about
Reality of Adam
Missing the forest for the trees
Yes yeah
Yeah intentionally
Absolutely
That was not a
Goodnight at the end of the clip you heard him say
The video game head
Sure
What is it
I don't know if we I don't know if I know that I was wondering if I can some reporting somewhere
Episode
I don't know how 13 Lightning Returns having is better than
Choose were overpowered but listen
We're having a great time
If he said that he like Eternal Darkness I have to head back to you
In the woods
But it's interesting because
I have heard a lot of
From time to time
Alex just trust video game
Actually we have a listener who is a
He has a
The globalist
Michael
Who message
Me about 1
To hear about Alex's take on
Right
A full episode
It comes
You're not really fully able to satisfy that
I think in the Sandy Hook
We're going to accidentally
He's using to
In the same way that
He's using he's a Prozac head
I want to say that he's more like the bar video games I like
Hunter guide
Super golf or whatever it's called like that thing sexy photo hunt
Talk more about the video game
And how they make
People crazy
They like
It's always just some weird
All movies
He is expressing basically like
Updated version of the
Lights 100%
Tired
Tired arguing
What is usually used by people who wished
To restrict
Free speech
You know people like a Tipper Gore
Who want these
This sort of argument is not something
Ever expect to hear out of someone
Thinks they're a libertarian
Video game guy kill a guy
What the f***
Regular or do you outlaw video games as a v
Mario jump
That's right that's right
Killing the guy like
Straight up
So much Hyrule Warriors
But
They're always called Kaos they're listed as knockouts
I mean
Gray
Take that sort of mentality
It really does
Become like
Neurosurgeon
Slippery slope
Spotlight
It does become a situation where you're like wow
What is it that you're actually
What's the devil
Poltergeist
Well yes
Anything with Gabriel Byrne in it movie
In 2012
They're always watching Poltergeist battery saver
Better yet
Kids love Robert
The other
The other other
Let the idea that means not literally talk about
About the devil like the
What is the
The point where
Your
Like this is no good is that a spy
Censorious position to have
And it is not
Think you expect
I'm someone who is it
Is libertarian
Or whatever
It's not like that alone should be an invalidation of Alex
Pretending he has the principles absolutely
This you wind up getting
The
AR
So if you have
Imperative
Then it's PG-13 you can save
What is that
What does that even mean
Armstrong
Body that does
Terrible
If your parents know what you're going to
You need a shorthand for parent I heard the How to Train Your Dragon
So I'm pretty excited about that
It's called how to train your Deadpool 3
That's
I saw the second
Yeah
I had a lot of thoughts
Especially considering his name is toothless
How to say the Dragon for another day but
Whatever
I was on the gas man
I might not have thought about that bro
Yamato
Alex says
What I would describe as
The most ironic
Given what we know about the
The future
Yeah but like rain on your wedding day but it sounds
Good
2 days after the shooting
But we know too much
So put your mic down.
Piece of
Oops
The Second Amendment
So
I think at the ironies delicious there the idea that he's
Condemning these reporters trying to harass the families
We know that the end result of so many of his actions
And I'm not I'm not saying
People who has
Yeah
Gone to court
Part of their probation has been
Listen to Infowars
It's not some sort of
Wacky idea that we have that a lot of his listeners have this impulse
Harassed
But
Dragonborn out by reality
I think to have but I don't think
It reflects reality
I don't think the reporters were harassing the families trying to get them to say bad things about
They shouldn't take can I agree with Alex
D I use humor to deal with these types of thing
Like fat
Truly is in retrospect
Is utterly reprehensible
Not reprehensible
Reflecting
Or inability to understand what
In front of him
Like the idea that he thinks
These families are
Being harassed by
Journalist work some more actors
We're acting out trying to get the story
Trying to get to do whatever but like
His inability to
Exactly what's going on Isley
Biatch
Sort of Pop immorality
But it's hilarious
Because we know
Yeah and it's not the number one purveyor of making them harassed
And that's not laughing at the tragedy that's laugh
Alex
I guess what you're laughing at is that he knows
Better
You know that heat likes in the same way that clip earlier the replayed where he's giving condolences to the family
Monsters that you know something really bad
Do you know other people
People's actions
Call
Negative reactions for the victim
She is kind of like a
No this is intentionally
Because he
He himself said that it was intentionally awful to
Do the thing that happen
I think you would have is like I had no idea that my action
Would cause this thing that I know is Tara
You should be
Eagle
If you don't know if you don't realize that what
You're saying
Will leave
People to harass these people
You don't realize that
You're playing with fire there yet
Have any Master irresponsible actor that
Should
Just not be allowed
You just shouldn't be alive Sports
America
Miller on Monday Night Football
Hey we already know what he thinks about Kaepernick so we definitely do with him covering
I know that was the wrong thing
Weather
I was trying to pick her up
Tomorrow because I was trying to figure out the slot
To put that we still lost
And my mind wouldn't allow me to go to celebrity gossip
Cuz he would even Peter teal would have to sue them at some point
Yeah
Alex Jones
There's no way
Instead of this
Credible
Powder keg
Operating
Making be the anchor on the local news
Who's like
We have the cutest kitten of the months here today like that would work
Water skiing
We're all excited
Send it to a lifetime of
The worst
Human interest stories
Just inconsequential Americans conspiracy is home videos
The secret service has
To follow him on
Newton like
Go to prison
Kind of hell
Or like
Here the Great
Internship with
The Council on Foreign Relations
Relationship
Or something like that
Wow
To actually read
And discuss
The primary sources that detox
Oh yeah okay
Punishment
Describe but it might be the only it might be a therapy
Make him a paralegal for the splc
I don't think that would do it
I think just assume every
No matter how
EClass
Workshop
You need to have someone discussing with him
And confront him with it in a setting that
We can't leave
Court order
It's fun to think about what
Would be a good punishment
Every morning he wakes up and has to live out that dream of going.
That's what happened
Back in high school on super cool never wanted to f****** goes to high school and is out.
Neck walking in that school
What's bigger your answer your Nook oh
The kids are globalists to these days
Do algebra
I don't know I do
Foundation
End of America
The beginning
Wrongly
Very much I can already tell you wrong
Yeah
Rough and Tumble
It's true
When he says hey lady
Illegal firearms
Ulcer Soul Factory
Because I'm say I don't want it to be
Siri born that way
Gear the Kim
Defining
No
It's just a
Everything's good
Yeah
Yep
America was
That's
This very argument
Has been going on since
The beginning
Gmail
Like
Institutional Congress
There were these gun folks
In those congress's there were so many of them
Socialized medicine and then other people will like
What if we killed everybody like it was it was that
You know like you have so many people like
Centralized Power Within
Going through all this s***
F****** argument
The goddamn beginning
This country is a f****** mess
With differ
Different presentation
I don't know I would say if
The people
Who it wasn't
The majority of people in the colonies
Who wanted to start this Revolutionary War
No
Fine
I got a little bit of higher taxes
Start a revolution that's
Uber travels
I would say
History is boring out there
Really
Well the only reason I resist any of that
Cm
Because like if we were still
Like the United States as it is now but
The United Kingdom right I don't think I'll be better
We can just have the queen on her money and everybody be fine
I think
Quite frankly
If
Like Alex's
Describing the thing
The Revolutionary War
Gun
People having
But it wouldn't be the second
It would be an immense
It would be the first
A baby the structure of government as laid out in the Articles and stuff
Hey the reason
Thought thought
These things that are added in
You back
Inalienable human right
Cut-out design
Hm yelling about how Obama
Cheated
Sure about that
Was a scam as well
That's a music started
Too early I think you miss time that break a little bit
Little bit
A little much
Also things
Was fake
You know like all of it the corporate media
Oh that's
What is the action you're implying
Exactly
Faking
Agreed
Absolutely if you're saying that
Get the old mainstream media
Is Mannie face is not
Is is
Because they know even liberals who
Still believe in the mainstream media are buying guns
Create this situation
Mission in order to
Exactly
Every part of this is like
It is very much a where there's smoke
There's a fake Sandy Hook
Yeah
Pinterest
From this Friday to Sunday
Jump
Is that the cheese
I don't think Alex was even in
Control of it necessarily
I would say just
But maybe what he's doing is there yeah on on Friday and now on Sunday I think we're on much solid or ground
There's a tease
I'm going to understand that I don't trust what's going on
Right right
Here is how he finds
Yeah
He is doing something
I would say
Could be considered calculator
In that
He's not kind of all over the map in this episode
Specifically pointing out
It's almost like he's building a case
Psyche specifically
Finding out the motivations of different groups like the UN
The mainstream media
One of them is conclusion then
To all of
And how much
He's just a result of
He's had to split with
This for a couple days
Chinese War Ready
In the middle of the show
On Friday
First off those are some dope Beats
About people taking your gun
Obviously people having a conversation
Aftermath
We'll figure out where to go from
That much
Embassy in other places
With the Prozac heads.
Has a built-in narrative
About people
Taking psych medication
Making them kill him
Write off like that
He has been my Accra for its third row that they're doing it on
Everybody
Well that DHS report was that other one
We talked about
Yeah Mike is a much better
Interesting
Because
You know the
Implicit vaccine narrative do you throwing out there
Psych meds narrative
There's a
I'm grabbing narrative
And so you have all of the
But
He adds
Because it's a school shooting
And stuff like that
The video game
Right
Get back to it
Collectivist
Prozac
Ridgeland had
So
I mean that I'm more fine with
Video games
Pretty much
At least they aren't absolutes for him
I'm a libertarian
Some wiggle room
There's a virgin that I think should be prohibited
Where is everybody
Adult
It's hard with video
Eurasian has that subculture that you just can't understand
A part of it or around a lot
Alex
Yes
Video games
Because
Right
Not frequent
But it is
2 Days Later
Wasn't talking much about video games
Friday
Now that he's in the age subset
He would associate
With it
Part of
His brain
Video game
It's huge
Yeah
In this next clip
I don't even
The Pond Guy
Years older than me
I don't know my timeline so f***** up
Hi Betty play Gold
Yeah but
First person shooter games
So at the end
No good favorite movies are John
Doodlebops games are problem
Hot water right here
Fire John Wayne
Isn't the coolest ever
Oh no
So what are you talkin about shoot-'em-up games
Created by the Department of Defense
Now this.
Interesting
Alex is kind of right
But he's also kind of wrong
What he's right about is that DOD funding was involved with some of the earliest video game
Like back in the 1950s
A man named William Higginbotham
Who worked at Brooke great man
On some of the early
Computers that they have visitors
Yeah early version
Right by the government
Create
But in 1993 the Marines noticed
The rising popularity
And they wanted to see if there were ways to
New technology
Help supplement
Particularly because
It would be waived
Cheaper than what they
They were working
Great effects
3D environment
Like boxes
Then just developing a software or whatever that is
A simulation
Adjustment
Make it work
But the finished product was never official
It was called Wolfenstein
Who's called
Which is not a great name
Could not be less creative than
Marine blank
It's not the games themselves that have application
A training
And don't explain the reasons
It's the technology that is
Is used to make them
It was the innovation of navigating
The environment
Which shooting games it's the
Team
Recreate Anthony for immediate decision making
It's built into the structure of the game
So those sorts of things are very big innovation
In
Technology
Simulator
Computing simulation
But not
The games themselves are treating you
Right
That's important
Distinction if we have soldiers who are doing the stuff in real life what if we also had them play Counter-Strike
Did that
Well and learn how to look around corners
That's
It's not what they do
If they have the
Has been
Developed by the development of the
These games
Video game
Company
Right
Jahmani on government contracts and stuff like that
What is it game development
The breakthroughs that they make
The training
Things that the Gulf
In the military
Hanyu
Those Technologies
Right is that make sense
Yes like a like One Pilots are in those giant
Yeah this is such an important
What drives the game
And what like
Is behind it
He's not what they're interested in
They're not interested
Open world
They don't want
Train p
Lookout
Enemies
Whatever by playing breath of the Wild
They're interested
The breakthroughs in
Technology that they can
Reply to their own
Like
Like drones and s*** like that like the movie toys not I don't know why I'm doing
Movie Rec
Something like that
Able to
With the simulations that they use for training
Inside the army
Okay don't make
Play Call of Duty 2
Trained right all right
Technology
That are part of the
Creation of those game
In order to use in their own way and order to amplify their own
As technology has gotten so much better
Video game
The
Controls of them has
Developed over
You are essential
Able to
Creates
It is very similar to
The plane that you don't have to fly a plane
Right
Principal Financial
I even Learn to Fly plane
Menards
And that's why everybody in the Marines
Thinks that ebony is an ore and a metal because they play Skyrim all the goddamn time
The point is that is new
An important distinction
About like
The difference between
Pentagon
Video game
As opposed to
How Alex
Presenting
He's presenting it as
They paid all this money
In order
These games to get created
Every shoot-'em-up in them at all
Tile
F****** stupid
Would you look at where the money
Be interested in
Sing
Because I think it's
Evil
I also think
Hope the terms of
If you're going to train people anyway doing it that way
Paying for
So many video games I've gotten
Of technology that there was underlying funding
From the government in order to create
The internet etcetera
I don't know it
More complicated
The Last Starfighter
This is not how it work
There's no intrinsic training that you get for playing first-person shooters
In terms of decision bake
All of those snap decisions
Stuff like that that are created by
Like a purse purse
Person shooter
Exact same thing is like you got a flip that blocks
Yeah part of your brain
You don't experience a descent
Sedation about death video game
Unless you're probably already on that passed
To begin with
For any number of Papa
Facts about the
Video game
It's about the purse
Experience
Right and if you are a libertarian
That should be a big consideration
And for you never once considered killing
The more important aspect of the military in
Video games
Benazepril
And that's our largest intro
These days
Games like Call of Duty all those games
Are essentially
Propaganda
To a certain extent
We're coming out we're like Army propaganda
Pennywise
Another thing about 7
Consider is that the investment that the military
The development of
Technology
A well
Princeton
Stimulation
Therapeutic environment
To help returning soldiers
Ttsd
It's obviously not a perfect treatment
But it showed a lot of promise
Helping soldiers deal with traumatic
Negative
So there is that a payoff
It comes from the investor
So all this is to say that
Stupid
Is dealing with it
Dimension
Supposed
Thinking about like
What were they doing
Why
It is
There's a lot of video game history has
The government
Funding behind
But if you just scratched
Beneath the surface tiny bit
It doesn't
It's not nefarious
It's nefarious
Military Justice
Wants to kill people
Call Sears at Arden
The culture in order
Dum dum serial killers who will go round
That's f****** stupid
That is
That it is on the level of the satanic
Agree
It is
Weird to
I suppose it's not invalid
But it is weird to say that
Violent video games can be a therapeutic
Element for
No I mean for soldiers return
But but it is it is strange for video game technology
Tubi
Therapeutic element
And at the same time
Element that
People used to descend
Sensitise people
Do you know what I mean
But I'm not sure
But I also don't think that the way the
Is it the military
Uses the technology
Simulation
I don't
It's to desensitized
People's Appliance
I think it's just his argument that is is
You know it's kind of
Can boast a double-edged sword
That's not unreasonable to say
But it is hard
To make that argument without
Connection
You don't care
His argument is
I think that this guy
Set up
Finished straws
Have a built-in narrative
I just don't think it's come up anytime that we
We've been covered
Yeah I think this is probably a narrative
Existed
Future
Look like
Department of
The violence doesn't pull out very often
Not often.
I'm so
We hear it now
What is
You taught him how to play
Do you think he would feel differently
Video games
The Alamo
I'm going to I'm going to play out the life of Colonel Travis
And tell him to go f***
Enjoy this pretend lifestyle you wish you were living
Gave him to Valley early enough
I'll take all these conspiracy theories and create my own world and all my God
I will stipulate exactly what
Is going on
What my enemies want to do and then flash forward to a prosperous
Interesting to have him
Expansion of Steve six which includes climate change
Yeah yeah includes climate changes like one of the Elementals
Things that you have to deal with
Not available
I implanted either
My point is that
I think we got a new
Does narratives that
Elusive
Was driven out of
Little hole
Alex
And it's caller says that
That the shootings
Alex
Is responses in
I think that there's a volume
Within
This 30
Let's go to Julio in Illinois
What would drive this
The son whose father was the vice-president and tax director of General
Trick energy Financial Services
Suspicious
I smell something when it's rotten
Dammit
That is the worst f******
In response possible
Because that guy
Expressing things
A big part of the
Right
A response
I don't want to go there
But also
I smell something when it's rotten
Right
That's the thing that he's going to for sure
We just had
Debates on it
Argument is like
I would rather just on the facts and it's like
No you
Of course not
Bexar bummer
That's really break up his entire momentum
Intuit Alex Jones's Whole World falls apart
You see glimmers of what I think
He wishes he had
DMVs episode
Maybe it's a spiritual memory
That caller
We heard both sides
Right even being like I don't want to go there
He knows that the end result of that is the audience will
F****** ignore the I don't want to go there
Fart
In terms of things that we can really nail to the wall
He's not
He's not super out of line
Except for all of the other stuff
Yeah makes sense looking at in Sandy Hook
Stuff
He's very clearly signaled he wants
What's to do in where he's at
But you haven't said the things we
We need yet it is it is like
He is living in a world where he
Can win that lawsuit
He can win the current lawsuit
If he is just this guy in 2012 for the
These two days
He can live
And backup
I didn't say this was fake
I only wanted to have debates
I had my suspicions because I'm who I am
But in the world we live in now
He done f***** up
And even he knows almost certainly
That heat
Alex has version of it is so much like
I have the right to Quest
Babies in incubators and blah blah blah
But he's not
No
He's not talking about like
How they were babies in incubators
To defend himself or why he was
Sandy Hook
Folding
He's not talking about those things but yeah
He knows that he doesn't know
Defend himself
Right
El Super
I know that there is
The part of it that I haven't
Detached
Yeah myself in order to go through all this
Stars
This is this does have
The feel of
Somebody
In the moment
This has the feel of somebody
Pasta Too
Be the guy who says
This probably is
Like he feels like he has a
Ability
To his list
To pretend that this
To imply
He doesn't
Feel like it's not real yet
You know what I mean like this is
This is the this is Alex Jones in a lawsuit
Who can say
Who's lawyer can say
This is an act
This is
This is Alex Jones
The presenter
Who has to do the things
Free show
You wouldn't have to
Find himself a behavioral
Over the last two episodes
Listen to
Of course like I don't think that there's anything in there that legally action
Exactly
We didn't know that he eventually
Does it would be like
Alex is walking a fine line responsible here
But
Kind of right
That's on the side of free speech
You can do whatever you want to do your dick to do it but
You did whatever
I don't yet
That's what I'm saying but it isn't
2%
Eating in court
When we know that the Alex Jones
Is the one from 2015 saying
It's fake episode
Really sharp focus is because
Feedback from the last episode
Talk to
Lawyers
About some stuff
Yeah
They know that
Yeah I meant third everything that were talking about
Is outside of the statue
Even him in 2015
Keep saying it
Listen FedEx
Completely directors
I thought they were kids who died there but
Turns out their work
All that s***
That is still outside
Limitations
For defamation
Yeah
Being students
So there isn't a real /
Productive reason
Bring this to the
Conversation
Yeah
These are these are episodes that are
Find some online
Like I had
Had to dig through the
Like I'm DJ
Trip or something
DJ Cosi
20 albums of last year
It's good but I didn't have to dig
Too far to find
It's available
Due diligence
If they're stewing Alex
Jones about what he said about
They know what the fuc
He said right
At this time
They know it's not
Legally action
It's important for their case
Yeah they would know.
To be aware of it
So I don't
I don't I don't have any
Real interesting
Entirely
Human
Intellectual
Yeah
Just understanding what he was doing
How is Brian work
How
How does a person
Fall into
Exactly
How do you go from Vista
Where it's clear that he wrecked
Nice is 50
People died
Whatever version of
Yeah
Want fire show to be successful in the
Stoked about a day jobs
There is also a
Certain aspect of this
That I find
So relevant to posterity
Like a win-win when the fish people
Take over
25 years
I hope they listen to the show and recognize what propagated
The Deep
Houses rsf
So we won't be able to find out
Great graphic novels
It's very
Foreign territory for us to
Because the
We've done
Taking so long
Yeah
Knowing a whole lot more
Larger context
Text Ryan.
Where is the second
Of looking
December 2012
It's
It's more
So even though
We know Alex
There's so much
That like
We got to get
Percent there yet
We're still doing
Too much speculate
I don't think is wrong
But it's not
It's not where I want to be
Piece of pie
Getting in the pool
You never know what you're diving in
Weave
Committed
We'll find out what the waters like when we
It's it's just that
Dead center in between
Dar 2009 investor
2015 investigate
And yet somehow this
Completely different
I'm get it just like I do
Right is somebody the same built-in defense
Distrusting
Psych meds
Vaccine
Orient ourselves
Yeah
Response
Rusev
Severe circumstance
And just
He is at this
Cuz we haven't heard from
Yeah
So we will learn more
Experience this
I'm glad it's not ugly
Maybe another f****** will find out
Before that
Website
We do have a website
Knowledge feit.com on Twitter
If you are a big
John Wayne's and it's also feel your hand. I think we got to get rid of it
John Wayne
Autocorrect
We are on Facebook
Which was filled with
People and we hope that
Remain a lifetime
Absolutely
Subscribe
Good stuff
About anybody
Selfie
Literal murderer
You know what
A lot of Nazi zombies
In the video game
But
No I know
Technically probably
In the real world
May have killed a guy
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color