Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work
Beverages
What
Hubbard Woods
If you were if you
You had to be a bird
I feel like
Cardinals
I'm from Missouri
The love our baseball
Everybody off
I'm not sure they do I just think
I want to be a Birdseye do the Cardinals
There's another consideration
Lucknow
No further dumb
Encino we've learned a lot about you don't like seeds all that much like flowers
Show me
It's like whatever they eat
Looks great in a fly fly
Teen Wolf t-shirt I don't care
Speed flying is clearly too much of a risk you run into things all the time
Do I live original life
When I used to work at Walgreens
My life here in Chicago I just moved everything was going bad
No stand-up was not going wild the job sucks
I was miserable but I couldn't leave because I needed
One day I'm out on a smoke break
I'm in front of the
The the store
Smoking cigarette in a bird falls out of the sky in front of me dead
It was at that moment I realized I do not want to be with her
Walgreens Sycamore
Call Workout
Was like
It was like someone was writing a story for
Good
I want to be a bird okay alright but I do want to know more about Alex
Shout out
Signed up Anderson
Supporting
The first of all
I'm a policy wonk
Michael
Thank you so much
You're about to walk
I'm a policy wonk
G
I'm a policy wonk I'm sure we've met many a Time convention
Sure
I appreciate it oh so very much
Sherry that you so much
You are now a technocrat
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Someone someone sodomites
I can't
I don't want
Thank you so much Sherry
But you were listening out there
Support their efforts
You can do that by going to our website
Knowledge fight.com
We're doing is we are staying in 2012
Investigation
What happened
When Alex Jones is coverage after Sandy Hook
Investigation
Important for us to find our feet
You know find our base
Stop before we
Have breaks in
Episodes
We're developing
Moore guitar
Brownstone
Currently all are base belong to them
The right
Be doing
You know
For now
It's
I don't know.
I guess it felt like I had appointment to start talkin about
December 17th and 18th
Lest we Wuesthoff we covered the Sunday show on the 6th
Alex was
I found his moral Center it was defending
And now we have
Back to the regular
And you wonder if that's going to change
Fuelvend is Sunday show
And I'll say a lot of it is still too
Just about to send it
I'm not surprised
He's going to spend the next
Being like
But there are some interesting developments
Pieces of her
His rhetoric that enter the conversation
Versation
In the past
Cuz it just gave me an opportunity
And its first clip is actually a great example of that
Alex trying to read
Enforces insinuation
That the government probably did Sandy Hook
Without.
Compared it to all these other things
These are fake whether it's the Aurora shooting right Kaczynski
That sort of stuff
Of History
Operation
Defied
Someone on from the 50s
Is all over Europe
Celebrities and disarm the people
So
He's trying to insinuate with his talk of operation gladio
Nobody ever brings up operation Sajak
Because
It's very red
You never know
Never know
So whenever Alex wants to suggest something some kind of tragedy is fake
To prove that what he saying isn't Ludacris
They have any real defensibility can point to his
Aurora shooting
The time like he's not being crazy
He'll inevitably bring up operation gladio
And with less regularity operation
Both of these clandestine operations that the government was involved into an extent
F***** up pieces of our history
But if you take a closer look at them
You'll see that neither of them really helped reinforce the point that he's trying to make
Namely that the United States government is for
Weekly fine with killing their own civilian
In order to take out
Operation gladio refers to the state behind networks place in countries throughout Europe after
The world war
Creating
It was obviously they were worried about the Warsaw Pact
And having people in place in the country
Countries
Involve to deal with that possibility
Was Dean preferable to having large standing army
Or doing what they were doing
People who were allied with the cause of fighting
Reunions but it was so disorganized they would rely on like
Late night supply drops
And fractured communication
Believe
The people right in secret operation were
The best way to do it
I don't know
This also part of Operation Dumbo Drop
Different
Because I'm not really sure that I can
Say that I'm an expert on the factors that led to these countries choosing that path
Dishonest
That means a lot of claims about operation gladio
Conspiracy circles
Better not
Reflective of
Most fat but based solely on a stump
One of these days
Is that the CIA was involved in
Another is that the stay behind networks in
Countries committed false flag terrorism
In order to achieve their political goal
The basic idea gear
Is it these groups
The threat of the invasion
That never came
So in order to proceed
The agenda that they were created to push
The appearance of that threat needed
Created
Enough these groups
Began fake Terror attacks
To blame their political enemies
Create the perception of Soviet
Infiltration or whatever
Horses are communist
Did in fact
That is what the
Conspiracy World believe
We do not
Know for a fact
No
2004 book by daniele Ganser
I called NATO secret armies operation gladio and terrorism
I'm almost certain that this is where Alex is getting his ideas gladieux from because his version of it and wanted the book
Almost
News about dancers book is it really so much a book that contains documented history
As much as it is a book full of information
Mixed up with unfounded assumptions
Defense studies
Was a researcher on the topic of Norway during the Cold War
And he dug up some information about the actions of stay behind Network
Country
His information is used in a book
And you excited in the bibliography
Olaf found that his primary research as being
Wheatley misrepresented by cancer
The many unfounded allegations
Answer except
Nicest Oracle findings would fill an entire book
Are the reviews of his book followed similar pattern
Hayden Peak and expert who's frequently published in journals regarding intelligence and operations
Took a little bit of a stronger atonement olav
Quote proof is a problem
For dancer
He complained that the outside he was unable to find any official sources to support his charger
The cia's or any Western European government involvement
With gladia
Nevertheless
His book devotes 14 chapters Duty quote secret war in various Western Nation
Amazon his
Dancer fails to document history
Who doesn't know any
There's zero information
He had zero information
0 documented facts
That is really ringing blood out of a stone
Finish this quote
The CIA and MI6
Gladio intuitive
Which is the fundamental assumption
Charged the belief that Alex has
SeaWorld pass
Conspiracy
Siri yeah
It was v18
Could have been
Map
At least the ideas 1000
Especially considering that in 2005 it was revealed that a lot of narrative relies on a historical
30 took to be off that
This is what's known as supplement be to the US Army Field Manual 30-31
Which purports to be a classified section of
The very real field manual 30-31 but is in fact a forgery
Play Soviet distance from
The forged document
Contains exactly what Alex Jones
There may be times when host country government show passivity or indecision in the face of communist or communist Inspired Silver
And react with intelligence test
B transmitted by q-shi
Such situations are
Particularly likely to
He seeks to achieve tactical advantage
Violin
The swelling host country authorities into a state of false security
In such cases US Army intelligence must have the means of launching special operation
Which will convince the host country government
And public opinion of the reality of the necessity
Counteraction
To this and US Army intelligence
Penetrate the Insurgency
With a forming Special A
Radical elements of the Insurgency
When the kind of situation and visit
Envisaged above arises
Actually under US Army intelligence
Controls should be used to launch violent or non-violent
According to the nature of
Basically the protocols of the writers of the field manager
Yeah
Russian propaganda
Right sounds great
Right he should have known it was a forgery when he saw that it was written in crayon though that isn't
Redfin
Exactly everything is right or whatever
It's not
If you exclude this document that serious Scholars informal investigation
Route to be a forgery
Networks that were part of operation gladio actually committed any
Any false flag terrorism
Completely
Lee falls apart
In the interest of fairness
There have been some indications the old weapons caches
Gladiator Style
Networks
And even if that's a far cry from
Proving that the CIA or MI6
Converted these groups into terrorist
There's a hundred other explanation
I don't take that to the
Like a good
Piece of Heaven
From Alex
Operation gladio for me
I'm still bummed about the 14 chapter
Hard time writing that much when I do have
That's
Yeah but if you think
You're like a
Breaking something
The world
Change the world
Imagining
If those
So he's writing like Jack Kerouac
Flooring tomorrow
Gotcha
I'm a Operation Ajax Jordan
Amor real
Correctly
That operation refers to the cia's 19
53 overthrow of Mohammed mossadegh and the reinstallation
Peshawar
Dictatorship over a rock
Something underhanded what you could easily call evil
He doesn't really work to help Alex's point about the
The globalist doing false flags in the United
41 pretty big reason
And that is a motive
Operation Ajax happen because
Was leading a massively Popular Drive
To nationalize the oil at the British company
The anglo-iranian oil,
Which was a threat to a lot of people
The CIA rationalized overthrowing
Oberon
All the oil be in the hands of communist
Termination for sovereign state
Riots were manufactured in the Shop-Vac from Power with the full support of the US government
Because they knew he would be easier
That is a choice that was my
That is kind of how we do to
I know history is more complicated than that brief summation of it but the
Is the Alex is way out of line
Evidence
All of his narratives are built on the backs of people who
Who existed solely to demonize,
He loves the John Birch Society and all the most virulent anti-communist
Weasels you can find
Evil in the namesake
It's not communism
I guess what that's exactly the reasoning the CIA uses
Is propaganda
Justify reinstalling the show-off go up to be a dictator of Iran for
Afterwards
And what guides
Sort of philosophy and worldview is exactly the same thing
That the CIA used to justify their actions
Yeah
That's ironic
It is a little bit it's a little ironic
We move along
You know what just happened
And where he's staying
Amazon December
Crocodile tears
If every disgusting out
So Obama is giving his speech where he cries
Alex
Dead certain
But he was fake crying
Which is also
Deeply ironic
Man
He's milking this for everything it's worth and it's like dude
Yeah yeah
Milking this
Play it gets worse as we go along
Just like hey can we not have kids anymore
Yeah
Idea of getting emotional is not
I don't know I think I take that
Certainly was more authentic that
Absolutely
The first instance of
To major in
Episode
Projecting onto Obama
What he would do in these circumstances
So the first one here is fake cry
You see the Obama crying on television
He's like that
He's like every time I cry it's fake so it must be fake with this guy any any outpouring or expression
Emotion that shows
Non masculinity analysis definition
Performative
I know cuz I do it all the time
Depth
But I think he would
You know you wouldn't
Be saying that if he was
Shooting
Do suspicious but you know what he's not the only one
At least.
In still occupied Texas
Drums are going
What's going on
Cuz you didn't do it
You do if it's a right-wing terrorist all the time and it's all just baked
Why isn't that so much more has happened when there's a Republican president in office
It would encourage
As if it were a real right-wing terrorist impossible Ouroboros
Ozark
No because the globalist are now panic
Because of how powerful and popular Trump is
They're going into overdrive
Of course it is it's all in French
No matter what no matter what happens
Even worse argument because
Cuz it's a bad idea
Don't disagree with that series about
Globalist
Them coming up with utterly silly and stupid plans
But he thinks he's going to take down
Mainly because they're so stupid
It would be hard
No
Which plants
Now so they're doing more right-wing terror attack
It's only going to inspire more right-wing Terror
Because it doesn't seem like in the instances
Anything against the right-wing has actually been.
Dry well
Massive calling all of us
Harrah's or Patriots
Like 2 seconds
It shows a little bit of a
I'm really mad at
These hypothetical imaginary people are bad at their imaginary jobs
Yeah frustrating
He's being blamed
For this because he always
The always personally blame
4 thing
He doesn't understand what's going on in the world
Like that
People are actually saying
Right here
It is incredible
Especially cuz I was referring to an article in foreign policy not foreign affairs
But it seems like he's talking about it doesn't realize those are two
Which does not inspire,
That's not a good time
Beyond that he clearly didn't read this article you just read the headline
The body of the text discusses how a lot of preppers are acting out of rational concerns about be ready for a disaster
Walk them real fast whenever came top or something like that
The article is about early indications that Adam Lanza's mom was a bit of a survivalist prepper
But if Alex could read the article it says
Quote
The extremity of Adam Lanza's crime
Has created a desperate desire for explanation
And dismissive him is a crazy survivalist or the son of a crazy survivalist
Will likely prove irresistible for many people trying to make sense of assets
But the ultimate truth of his motive
Is not likely to be Sosa
Simplistic
Additional information will emerge over the coming days
But we've never know really why Lanza killed his mother and so many innocent
Pictures of children
Understanding the context of his actions May provide
Useful insights that
I could prevent future incidents
But gross oversimplification
Will only stand
The article is literally a voice of caution warning people that labeling Lanza as a prepper and using that to explain
Latest Act is somehow something that will stand in the way of future understand
The tragedy
Literally the opposite of analysis that
Alex could ever actually like
Disregarding the fact that Alex can't
Those sentences would like
Just short-circuited braids like he would wait out and it would just be on the floor and they be like
Pretend he claims to read those are simple
Exactly
It's not it's supportive of his worldview
Because he's reporting on this stuff in the wake of
Giant mass shooting at an elementary school
He can't play fast and loose with this stuff
Really
He is
A couple years later
It's that oversimplifications only stand in the way
Sentence of this article from the other side
If it doesn't even matter what they say
Hear the words when Alex
Reads the word oversupply
Flip acacian
He's like smell that's what I do
Don't tell me not to oversimplify that's the only thing I know how to do
Which might be why I mean it's probably best if you
If he just came out with it and said
I don't care much for articles
I like to just read headlines
He could pull off like his I'm a Gerald Celente style Trends forecaster
All you need is a headlight
Friend right or whatever but
He wouldn't be able to pretend
He's really smart
Exactly
Kind of
He has read over 100 books on World War
I guess
That's okay
That's fine
The title
So we're still
Serta wanting to say
Relating
Two other things
Things are fake
And that sort of thing
And next clip there's another
Lost the trust of the people
So it's all right getting ready to plan and Stage more steaks
Stuff like that
It's not really clear a few things took was one at there will be more
Or is it the other one
Detox about
As a little bit of like
Shrubbery around the
The house
Of our invest
Navigation
It's just more it's more evidence that you just thinks everything
I don't like
I mean
If you are saying
Immediately following
They are planning to Stage warm
It follows that you think that
Mass shooting with
Take that
Yeah
Crazy give them to take that understanding for those works
Benefits
Give you a little bit of the flavors
Get back to talking about gun-grabbing
These gun grabbers
They're going around they want to Grabagun
Don't grab guns
Ask people politely to give
Boy better
Guns don't respond well to
You polite request
I don't respond well
Where are you
At war with them
How many says something else
In the same way is that
Clip a couple one
It's sort of unclear if
Referring to
Hook about
Shootings being
Fake butt
Exactly
It's only reasonable
Assume
That the one that is most recent
She has been talking about is what he's referring to
Right
The system is
Fountain City
Martial law
Video game head
So the simulation
Yeah
Cough
Because I actually forgot that you literally said that kids yeah
That one that one says this is fake
Really
Maryland
What verse what does he mean by that you mean that they created that simulation
Because if they called that simulation before then it would only make sense for them to then have followed
Through with it
Or they're simulating Fallout
From where
No there's no one version of that isn't that
What
The shooting itself
Whether or not the government staged it or not
Yeah
Referring to is the way it's Being Framed by the media
Or something like that
Yeah I could see it being a position
He could defend
It's been no
I have to extend all the possibilities
That's one version of it I could be
How much nuances involved in that
A lot
Aggressive
It might be I'm not going to give him a
Corroborating
Pieces
I'm not willing to accept that as like
A full-throated everything was fake
Communication
What what are the things
Feel like
Needs to be pointed out
Is
Absolutely certain it's real
And I will tell you my reason for that is he is coming up with
More and more super villains in the story and different angles
Attack for them
To be making towards
All right now it says
Alright now it's the government itself
Elements of the government
Every he's trying
To get everybody
Everybody involved in this which one
Is the think you can walk around
He's throwing shade at the wall.
Find out who people are going to react with the most
That's that's very likely possibility
So earlier he was crying
Which I think is a huge project
His part
Isaiah project
Wow
Wow implying that Obama either stage this shooting or is behaving and response
Cast of the shooter the way he has to get more traffic
YouTube Obama
Forever
Is exactly right now
Publicity
Like I don't know it's like starting some sort of fight with some famous podcast
Different events
But are not true or not
In order to get music
Then of course the president would kill
Yeah.
That like
The only way he can really understand other people
Actions reactions
To test if you had to give a speech
Newtown is to fake cry because he needs to
I'll bring the emotions or whatever people have
C2bit mirror humans
You wouldn't use something like this in order to get more publicity at traffic, of his videos
Manipulative or whatever is that and that's the most generous version
Obama kill cats reviews
Which is just f***** up wow
Does brain works
That's okay
Matter
Next clip
He says what his
Who's this guy
Mommy
Parachuting
Television
Program
This is the week
This is this is absolutely week cuz he's suggesting exactly what he
He wants to report
As his ankle
Call which is that
Rite Aid
Yeah we got it I got another angle of attack for these
Different villain globalist to do that for whatever reason
Yeah
Cool
Don't say anything
You don't have to do any of this
Find guns with
This stuff
Wheatley superfluous
Sounds good point just getting himself in trouble because
Because he needs more clicks right
What is going to
I'm more convinced than ever what is going to make unforced errors
So stupid
Is the trash
This is a tragedy
But
We have
We have to keep moving forward as a country I firmly believe
Second Amendment is one of the most
Things
We cannot allow
Our emotions to override our political principles
And while we honor and mourn the loss of life
Extend condolences to
To the families
We also will not bend on our convictions or whatever
There is a can you imagine him
Reading those words couldn't come up
Freestyle de very kind
Dirty reading those words
Hearing his voice
Say those words
Like a divided / 4
You'd still be like
I'm just saying
He could achieve all of the
The political goal without doing any of the stuff that's bad
This is all bad
Gut was telling him all these things
Blue
And that you're okay that's just as God
Unfortunately
Wow he does
Explaining the next
Whoever you trust his feelings
Every time
Houston
Something bad's about to happen
Correction
Something bad
Yeah shot so far
End of 2012. Is a
Condemnation of
It is like we know yeah
A prime example of
Exactly
Horrible Road
So you should not listen
Your gut is unhealthy
That
That is so
School shooting
Yeah
What is Eastlake
F***** up
What he's trying to minimize it to Ally
Innocence of like
Everyone's demonizing mass shootings and stuff like that but more people are killed by deer every year
And it's like hey
I mean if you want to go based on numbers
Fine
But if you want to extend that metaphor even further
What you should do
Like the analog is putting up signs in places where there's lots of cure
That's that's what is a government action
The tries to limit the damage
Of of deer on highways and stuff like that control laws
Country but we can all of Art
Brutal
You know what I'm saying
There aren't
He would be the one if if you was like
Super passionate about think it's a second amendment was about
Like he would be the one thing I like beer or free to roam you can't put up a sign here
He's doing about gun so yes
People do hiplok back t-shirt idea
I don't know
In his conception
Whatever he thinks is coming is worse than the
Yeah
Take the guns and then does going
Civil War
Yeah I know it's way worse than a lot of
Children being murdered
Nothing being done about it and
And so more and more children and murdered
The idea that he wouldn't be allowed to have assault
At the worst
April
It blasts that
Then
He foresees a civil war
Coming because of the gun grabber
So
If you look at if you think about the loss of life that would come from an all-out Civil War
You could say that that might be worse than a school shooting
I don't think it would be a civil war would be like
Tire country
Going like a holy s*** guys you are f***
Crazy and then the 1% of the country that owns
All of our guns
Would be like
I guess we're going out in a blaze of glory
That's their they're all living though Remember the Alamo
I'm saying the scale of that
What are you saying
He's worse than a school shooting not just the extract idea
I'm losing a gun
I know it's an unnecessary defense
I just don't want to be sitting here being like
All he cares about is
You gone eat it is still a
Ludacris for him to eat
Like suggest that it's a likely outcome thing
But it reads what are you talkin about
Isn't
Just that
It isn't just his.
I'll give you that one
No course not
Yeah
But it's where he's headed
Alright
Going to meet him halfway
So getting harder and harder to meet him halfway
Screw
So he's terrified there's a lot of bad stuff going on it's all a mess yourself
Do you think it's time to pray no it hasn't been time to pray
I just commit myself that's all I can say
I think God would be kind of pissed about it
He said he didn't like that s***
I just want my children so much
Obama statement
Democrats
I hate
Kids are killed in foreign countries
As a byproduct of our foreign policy
Yeah
Doesn't help here all that
But
Push
That stuff
It doesn't fly
But it also still could be
Just in the use of the story
In the media app
God
This is just
Little bit
Banana
Of course
I want
Talk to my wife
He just precedes to tell the story he says that he's not going to tell
Teacher
As I walked around the corner and this guy tried to mug me
I had a sick feeling
Becoming
So prophetic dream about that
Person
Infowars
Employees spouse
Wichita
Tent
What happened
Evidenced by the prophetic dream
Is people rappelling into the school and shooting
Amazing I have not seen too many media organization
I've hired so many
Psychics
Yeah yeah yeah
Innovation
Like that's what he's he's established I went to school for
Children
Perhaps the place was a psychic
Statistically
Actually
Gut isn't psychic
Dam break
I found a place in the week after
Assertive
No paranoia paranormal taipa ideas mumbo jumbo
You are you are literally
Not right now
Psychic
Alex talks about how
He is a pow
How awake
He is about
Globalist
Trading
To be so right all the time
Murderous
Unsatisfying
This is what my gut tells me it is
I get that
No I know if you if
If you include the premise my gut is never wrong
I think it is but if you're someone
It's from like a structural perspect
I'm trying to look at this like as if I were an entirely unbiased Observer
Who is like
Bulshit talk about
Is God just throw that out there
I still I still think
Think he's catching his language
And maybe that's the more important
He's catching his language.
Guys this was fake the White House was involved
Silverline
Fill in the gaps in his listeners mind as opposed to overtly making the statement
Burtness is the point I'm far more interested
Or at least I think that's
The conversation
That is pretty crazy lead over
Your
Overcorrecting for your unbiased
Listener
Because even an unbiased listener to listen to buy
This in succession like all of these clips in a row they be like yeah
Was anyone of the clips that you put together
100% proof
But when you got
6 in a row
I am over correct
If only because
I want to get stuff
You cover a conspiracy
Theorist and someone like Alex
It is it is the sort of thing where you
Almost find yourself making leaps of logic
That art appropriate
By virtue of him
Presents
When I'm looking at this
Strict
This means this this means best
Play the fun
Games
You clearly having a lot of fun
Really just got to say that I'm a psychic
No you don't that's fun no I know it is on yourself
I'm sorry
Superpowers
The ability to transform. I want
So earlier you were asking sort of the idea
Flying vet
The government
Any nightlife Clips I think he is
Heavily implying that
My gut
Tells me this
In this next clip from December 17th
He says something that if he believes
And he's reporting this as a thing
That he's it's actual Astoria story
If he believes this to be true
There is no way
That he cannot say
That it
Who's playing
If those are the day
Okay come on
So
Come on
He's saying this in preparation for the
Lake Preparatory stories
Mass shooting happened that they knew was going to happen or whatever it's like
Does that one is tough to get around I'm not sure I can make a good argument for that one
The first instance I think of like
Okay
You are now committing to this road
You're you're bringing in stuff that listeners have told you about
And you're pretending that you can
Confirm
And they are their narratives the only serve
Some sort of a structural Integrity to your idea that it
Intent and action
Encapsulated
How much more obvious
True
Which is like
If you're saying it's so obvious that you're saying that it happened the way your
This is probably the point at which
We can make a reasonable
Statement
That he believes it's
Yes it in some manner or another and it seems
It is that
Ethan Hunt
Went in there instead of Adam Lanza red
It seems like that is where his head is
Is gut
Is the White House or the people in charge and running things in the White House
Involved
Almost there
But this
Is the departure
Absolutely he sang that the government hired the
It will only get worse
Yeah I think because
We know that he never
Steve the light
Intel
And tell much much later
It's a lawsuit
Spiral out of control
He's afraid that they're going to take the gun
Right
He's already made the
The argument he said a couple times
Martial law.
Because of the sand
He doesn't use a lot of specifics
I just can't get
This thought out of my head real quick
We're at a week
After
Sandy Hook
Three days after
0 time for him
Then say that
All the left
The Republicans are just
There to help
Did you
The Patriot
The Democrats were launched
You're really running the ball
Feel right right
Juxtaposition
Sing together
And maybe this is why we
We have heard 8000000 Clips in a row basic
I think it was fake
But with little different language
And you're like
We're going to give you the benefit of the doubt
And it took three days
After 1
The worst mass shooting in America
At the time
For him to say that it's
All Democrats
I feel you on that
I would respond
In 2012
I am responding to a I am in part because we're listening to
Years later
Any Stakes involved in is covering face
But it's certainly not the same as if it was
Happening in real time in front of
These episodes
Podcast in 2012 the day off
Like with alarms
Yeah Alex's suggested this is fake guy right
Much more a big deal
One of the reasons I've given so many benefits of the doubt
Because I know it's going to get
And it'll be so much worse for him
I'm just saying that's that's something that I cannot get out of my head that just like
This is a lesson to learn
Somewhat
I think I think
I think
Appliance
Is on a case-by-case basis
Be careful
But there is if there is a
Overarching
The other side
Don't care as much
Hey Matt
I don't know I don't I don't I don't know how to
Because all the time
If it if you do that across-the-board
Paint with a broad brush
Shove all of your procedure
Enemies
You give yourself carb lunch
Never listen
To anybody
Not
The horrible person
I don't think
So much
Is good
Letting blessing is often very applicable
But if you do reverse Eliza.
That's all I'm saying
Let's let's let's jump back
Okay
Is not done a lot of news
Necessarily
DateHookup
Speculated that
One headline
Sandwiches
Bogus
Right as we discussed
You think
The in response to
Seahawks
He brings up a headline
Arkansas
Already don't care
December 14th
AR-15
Shakira
Uno
We got the newscast
So we already got that
Position between
You the slave
They should have been there should have been a bell that went off where he was like
Parasol Arkansas Darrell goes off in your life
Don't care nobody cares
F****** cares about what the mayor of Paragould
Paragould
Celtigar Paragould people
I don't want them to live in Barcelona
I can understand that but conversely
Take on the situation of Paragould Arkansas
Do you see the story about police dressed up in swat gear Patrol industry
Any instantly reports on it somehow be related to the app
Aftermath
18in reality has
Reporting in the Arkansas times reveals that Todd Stovall the Paragould police chief
Announces plans
Recent SWAT gear patrolling citizens of high-crime areas
In a meeting on December 13th
The day before Sandy Hook happen
And that Clipper just listen to Alex Miss reports the date of the meeting is being December
Because the way he wants to tell the story
Is this happened as a result of the shooter
Globalist
But that story doesn't the meeting happened
Anybody else
Excuses flip
But it is
Stance with this dude
That seems
Very likely
To me to be a straight-up lie
Yeah in order to serve the narrative
The day before
Because then that's the globalist
Martial law
Because there
You know where the globalist want to try it
As they say
So goes the Country
It's a really interesting line because
Yes if
You could say that they
Push this
The day before
Story
Work if
The premise is that this
Police chief's actions are motivated
He can't have both of those
Because
The justification has to be
Sandy Hook
Do rationalize martial law
Today
Siri the police chief
Townhall
And does not get a positive reaction
He doesn't know he doesn't know he doesn't.
Everybody hates it really wants to do this
What did you do
Goes all the way up
That's what he does and then comes back and he's like
Even after I thought it was a good play
But the media never dealt
There was quite a bit Stovall plan
And it's clearly
It's an unnecessary move
Pretty racist way that's the only thing they're definition of high-crime areas and stop-and-frisk
Arkansas can you
Traditionally that
Snapping
Not done well not a progressive Paragould
Coincidence
I'm about it
You know who's leading the charge against oval plan
What else cause martial law it was Rita sklar
The executive director of ACLU Arkansas
Beside the stove
Zero understanding of cost
Matutinal rates
.
ACLU Alex
What's the 10 organization on the ground that was organizing and acting against this guy play
To Clemente martial law in
Paragould
Brothers don't take her with them on tour
There's a little bit of that and they are but then her response to
You could just type out haha
Call you're just twins
Story
Alex
In service
Building up his
Other narrative
You talked a bit more about on the last episode
Which was the idea that he's on Prozac
What causes this
He brings up another headline
And it's always
Is there anything that's going to be
Be dunked on more than any
He says
Anytime is like
Knock it down that one's in my column it is the most dunkable
Is the John Madden
Have a propaganda
This article either any only knows the headline because he's
Google long way to undermine undermine the essential narrative
Break into the article
It's important to remember that he's presented the idea that the global is to trying to get everyone on Prozac
Because it'll make a certain percentage
The population kill themselves or kill others and the globalist use those killings as an excuse to carry a
Nefarious plan
He's not just a concerned citizen who thinks a certain medication
He believes the evil globalist
They're giving it to
I am the public
To f*** them up
Melt in this article you immediately find some red flags
This Daily Mail article
The first is this passage
Could be barred from being prescribed Prozac and other antidepressants
Fears that they may increase the risk of suicide
Using antidepressant increase suicide-related behavior in Children and adolescents
Grab the london-based European medicine
Medicine
The agency did not find any evidence of death caused by the drug
So clearly
The first problem is even the organization
Lobbying to get Prozac Bandit missed that they have zero actual cases where Prozac cause someone
Me to Hartford to wiggle out of
Bicycling reclassified
The bigger problem and the one he can't wiggle out of
Is it that ban was being promoted and pushed by the European medicines
Why is that a problem
Because the EMA was specifically created in 1995
Dammit exclusively to exist as a body within the EU
Their website is Ema. Europa.eu and Wild
Kate
Because they
Eat your body
This is entirely NS
He's literally saying the globalist want to give you Prozac to kill you and at the same time the medical arm of the EU the world
Largest globalist entity is actively and Prozac
In the world of this man
Whims and contradiction
This one is still pretty
Impressive
Everything you saying is upside down
It's well it's banana it's not
No
Right
You can just take the
Medicine
Agency
Right
Even if it's in London
This is also free bread
Literally called the European medicine
Like it's probably part of it
Yep
He either didn't read the article or
Doesn't give a
F***
Now he doesn't give
Well I could also see him not reading because the deadline is the sort of thing that leads
Right so why read the article if it already delivered the perceived slam dunk
Yeah that's true
It's the equivalent of a slam-dunk where you hit the back of
Of the ramp in the ball bounce
All the way to have court but you think that you don't
And so you like Flex
Underground
Sarah Jordan in the All-Star Game clowning on somebody
But
It looks so pretty and
Turns around before you even real talk
Before you before you go to watch it go in
Energy
Misses by a mile and nobody tells him
Everybody just moves on like a Deadman
I might have done that once
Junior High
Good Apollo
Completely
Probably be the best shooter in the history of the sport before
Start
Playing around with those boobs
Whatever and thought I was
Not s***
Is this weird line of life
I think you have a responsibility to do better
Like no matter what no matter what kind of place
We're going to land
Like what version of
Sandy Hook is fake
Your father.
He has a moral obligation
And to do a better job
Evidence
Using
The things
If you just read the story it says the opposite of what he says it is
But he uses the headlines
To reinforce
Whatever terrible Road
He's going down
This is the app
Irresponsible
Someone who
Has something that they want to work towards
As opposed
To find out more about
Clip
Deeply in
And for the first time probably AMV
You know what this is
4 days worth of episodes
After Sandy Hook
This is the first time that I sort of shuttered
A little bit
Actually it's not really about the shooting itself
He's trying to make fun of Obama and his
Response
To the Journey play some of Obama's speech
And the way he's acting
I find
Dodie
Simply represent
I think you'll agree with me
I know there's not
Apparent in America
Who doesn't feel the same
Overwhelming grief
Should I do
Beautiful little kids between the ages of 5 and 10 years old
Graduation
Weddings
Kids are grown
Chemotherapy
The following were also teachers
Women who devoted their lives to helping our children
Hearts are broken today
It's just
Gross
Response
He's just mad that they didn't grow up to pay him taxes
Yeah this is Westboro Baptist
Heckling
Funeral kind of
Yeah it's
This response is very very
F******
Take an hour off
Just take an hour off and let that speech be what it is
And then movie
Don't
That's f******
Yeah
It's pretty bad he also accuses Obama of using neuro-linguistic programming
It's clear from his words he doesn't really understand what that is and I don't care
I think what he thinks is
He's talking well
I think Obama is using neuro-linguistic programming
Implying that he has
Able to
To put people into a trap
Is using magic word
He could never ever
I don't know why you played that
Other than
Into like
I suppose it's a
Preemptive
Defense against empathy
Cuz if you were to have played that speech in its entirety even on his show
There's no way that his listeners are going to
To Heckle the same way
Some of them on Sherwood
There's no way that all of his listeners are psycho
No and if they were too if you listen to that f******
Speech at the very least
You recognize Humanity
Even if you hate everything Obama stands for
Even if you think he's the worst president in history
If you just listen to that entire speech
Uninterrupted you're like
Philia
Build up
Hey
This
This display of
Like a real emotion at a real
Response to
Must be fake
Compared to
Exact or something along those lines
Probably
Cuz it doesn't really matter.
So very similar thing
He's just trying to make the argument
You'll get killed with cars
You know like blame auto manufacturer
Some stuff like that
Sometimes you do
Well when there's when they do it
Get killed with guns
Your blame gun organization
Like that
For that is because those groups like the NRA
They Lobby against
The sort of regulations
The automobile industry is subject
Conversation
Isn't you should blame
For making the thing that's
Used to hurt people
These organization
Actively
Disallow
How to take care of
The problems with
Their products create
I don't really care
Is next clip Alex talks about
Morphle
Thrill thrill Wild
Tehran Iran
Ireland or Switzerland
Why would you want to go to Europe
First Amendment protections no they don't
They don't have a car
Institution with a with the
Bill of Rights at all
Escape the EU
Studio in Europe
I genuinely think he doesn't think Ireland is part of the EU
Island
Nobody
He says that he's Irish
Generally
Switzerland I guess
I get that
Partiality
Historically
And stuff like that
Nazis hiding
Yeah back
Wax tax laws
I guess I don't know
Pieces
Him saying that they're going to release a bioweapon
Does that all the time
Education
All this is just the same stuff
He's now using
The immediacy of this crisis
Vicky has in front
He does that all the time
Not necessarily all the time but it's still in service of this
Being in a meter
Also a method
Not neuro-linguistic
The programming necessarily
By the way
Lexar hacking into
Brick
To make whatever argument you're trying to make
More
Important
More severe
Then it would be heard otherwise
If your I mean every every argument that he's making
Usually comes down to an
I suppose because everything is always
Sure like that kind of thing is always fight or flight
That's the dichotomy
So at this point logical fallacy
I'm sure there is a technical term
Time for that but
At this point
This next clip
And it made me have a realization that I do
Ever had before
Really should have
Should have realized this early
The realization that I had
Is
He's really cute you know like
Revelling
Think part of it is this the sort of spy novel that he's cast himself in but the other part is
Is he he's a nerd
He's a f****** nerd
But without any of the
Yeah he's a civil war re-enactor
But on the radio
That's a good point
Yeah I just
Everything is fine I don't know why
So much of his behavior
You're so dorky
But this for some reason
Especially with
He comes off posturing is so masculine is this jock
Yeah
Would it be cool if I was in a militia
Like you said
I don't know
Goes the other way
Take a little break
Thought about something
At this point in the episode Alex has a guest on who I've never heard on before
And has to be unfortunately very generic name
Matt Williams
He's on to talk to Alex just about how he loves guns
Classes
And
Amanda paranoia paddling about the gun grabbers
Do I have you
Interview
Not really a whole ton
Fireworks going in
In the lead-up to this episode Matt Williams was
And so a lot of the conversation to Jordan and I had
About the interview even though the interview itself quite Bland and on notable dealt with who I thought
He was
And it turns out there
After we had recorded and when I started editing up the episode
I challenged some of my own assumptions
And wanted to make sure that I was correct
About
The
Me thinking that I figured out who this guy was
And after
Giving it another once-over I
I'm not confident that I know who this guy is
So I removed all of this stuff where we talked about him
Which is why I needed to give you all this little
Bumper
He also because in this next clip
He is always going to be talking to Matt Williams
And that is going to say something
But I think it's really great
I didn't want to cut out of the episodes I think it's an import
Peace
Do you know what episode
But I had to
Remove the South where I just can't stand behind it
I guess that's that's that's the situation so anyway back to the episode
Ventura
You had him on and I was very
It was fine
Has no clips
Is
It's a tragedy Alex
Like
Fine as it can be
But at the same time
He is on the side of arm
And stuff like that
But it's not really
Helpful to any of our investigative
I was really into
She came down on Alex's
GE.
They just gave up
Nothing
Arm the teachers
Ideas was
Take people who are
Soldiers in foreign countries
Brick
Give them jobs at the school secretly Commandos
Like Commando
Is a plot
Mirrors at least in terms of
And so he tries to bring this up to
At the end of this this episode
Accidentally
Completely destroyed
The argument that having teachers be armed
Is worth a damn
Whoever wants to be in the school
Miami Southridge Senior High
It was back in the 80s in South Florida so it had his problems all together
Why do you pronounce it Miami because of me Howard hunt
What Alex
Why is e Howard hunt a linguistic reference point
For you
Weird that is weird
Have an officer in the school
Yeah that makes sense we had a substation in our school
Anecdotal evidence that your
Gun loving guest
Is bringing to the table
It doesn't work
So
Alex what I think we should do
I know
Buffalo's
And will jump in
To the 18th and there's much less
To talk about
Is
So much
Defending gun
No real
Nothing really to speak of necessarily Italy
About the like
Is it fake is it not
It's still
His position is still pretty
Most of the stuff in the episode is
Just not into
Nothing at all
He has an interview with Larry Pratt
Who's the guy who runs the
More extreme
NRA group
Gun
Yeah just really help
Wheel of guns in the n-word don't worry about
Sandy Hook
Outside of
We're afraid that people are going
Lights out
That's that
There are a couple things
And the first thing that's in Port
The beginning of this episode
We get a special report
From Mike Adams Health Ranger
Understand why exact
He is on
And he's doing his
Peace
About basically
The idea that
I hate guns don't kill people people kill people
That sort of thing
And what he's doing is he's a video of it is looking at a gun
Trying to make it go off
Without his own action much longer than the cliff
Play but this clip should give you a sense of
Where he's at
Took to actually
Make it shoot
It took a human being
Making decisions
Over that way jerking off right now
The gun didn't kill anything
Now I know what you're thinking maybe
Maybe
Take our
Benelli M4 tactical shotgun
I'm thinking I want to make sure the cameras on your head
Home defense
What's the temperature
The rights really taken over counter
You're so funny
God I wanted to hurt and feel so bad
Blow your own foot off
Mike Adams
Gun doesn't fire by itself
The person has to
To do that part
Example of missing
Point of what people are complaining about when they say the guns kill people
But more importantly it's just wrong
In 2000/2001 sun god with a Remington model 700
How to say accidentally
Because you didn't even touch the
The gun just went off and her son
Was killed
She decided to take legal action and it turned out she wasn't the first person to experience this
Investigation revealed a gun
Sold by Remington designs where the gun could accidentally fire without the trigger being pulled
They alleged that at least 100 injuries
24 deaths were attributable
Guns going off all by themselves without being touched
The very thing that Mike Adams is mach
India ideas
In this field peas
And the Remington cases
Close to the only one
In 2013 I was Iowa Sheriff's deputy Chris Carter suit a gun manufacturer name for Hospital
Africa's pt140 Millennium Pro pistol
Spontaneously discharged after it fell out of his holster
In the suit it was discovered that nine different guns Torres produced
Could potentially fire if they were quote bumped or dropped
Or when the safety is on in the trigger is pulled
That's not good
Carmen
Onion
Kill people
End in regulation
Not received money from the NRA
Consistently voted against the idea that you're able to do gun manufacturers
This problem was estimated at
Potentially affecting approximately 900
56000 guns in
You ask a lot
The idea that you had the safety on you pull the trigger could still shoot
This case was settled in 2016 with Taurus offering to repair or buyback affected gun
But here's where the evil aspect of this comes in
They weren't required to recall the gun
And as such they didn't have to warn people about the danger that those almost 1 billion gun posed to La B
Completely responsible
What what what the f***
And the stories that brought this to light was a family
Who's son who wasn't responsible shooter ended up shooting himself because of this
Malfunction
In a Taurus gun
Curious about the ideas that like
No one sent out any kind of
You should get your Gunn
If you have one of these guns
Nobody
Cod
Real real
Part of the bed
F******
It's so crazy
Part of the problem is that unlike pretty much every other product that's sold on the market there is no governmental body that can recall
Call a broke-ass Gunn
The gun lobby and people like Alex has made sure that never go in
Specifically the NRA had a close relationship with Taurus
Which explains why they presumably a gun safety organization
Didn't warn their members about the danger that these
Defective guns posed
All this is to say that Mike Adams is a
The f****** idiot
Gun manufacturers rely on people like him to muddy the water
And make sure that people think all criticisms of their actions
When often criticisms Aurelius nipple is
Something like
Your product is defective and caused me to kill my own child and you shouldn't be able to sell the product still severely defect
That's not an attack on the Second Amendment at all
This is a conversation
You can't have a conversation about reasonable gun ownership
Responsible gun right
Until you have the same oversight
Pet Supply
Everything else
Applied to God
As evidenced by the Daleks would minimize
24 people were killed by those Remington guns that were defective
Yes yes 24 people were killed
God dammit
Definitively
Crazy
Genuinely f****** crazy
That makes
Evil
Big literally eat
Oh my f******
The NRA didn't even give a f*** if it's
Members got murdered by the
Or their children
Specifically went out of their way
Say f****** knew about it
Know if you think you are a gun owner you think
Protected by the NRA's Lobby
They're actively killing
Orleys not caring as you kill your children or yourself
I don't care about gun safety organization
When issues of gun safety like this
Ignored
That is disqualifying as
Able to call yourself that
If you are a gun safety organization
Then what
Recalling
Defective gun
Because they will kill people
Yeah it's not like
I don't know maybe a detective toast
Could kill somebody
Hey could you could get Electric
Recall
Atlantis design is food not as
Specifically put bullets in living things
Unreal
Because it because it's only there's only two ways to go
What year the NRA you say
We need to have these recall
Because this reflects poorly on gun owner
Directions
Is Lobby so f****** hard you immunized
Every gun manufacturer
This level
To this extent
You can kill you can kill
Go for it
Articles I was reading too.
Specific manufacturer
Company operates
Brazil
Bought a pack
Competitor survey provided like
90% of the guns that were sold
Produced in Brazil
And
The Brazilian government has placed where
Law
Have to buy Brazilian made
Sole supplier
Of the military
Lisa's gone
And nine of their models
We're completely
Defective
Or at least potentially
How to apply completely defense
Future guns they did Market as the unsafe
I did watch a video to the lawyer who is
That case
Defects work
Unloaded gun
Razee
Because it is like
You watch him
Very meticulously turn on the safety
And then pull the trigger as I
This would have fired it does the exact same thing with the AC on
Well I filed my briefs
One of the things that I put very specifically in
The language was
That this has nothing to do with sex
Amendment right
This is very clearly a product
Quality tobacco
We're selling this Pinto
We think it's a great idea we love it
And
We don't even have to tell it
That
Unreal brumbelow
On
Real
Messed up
Wow
Rip his hair out
Become a f****** monk you didn't seem happy
Yeah
That is developed
Not know it's the owner of this Thai restaurant apparently
Since deleted Facebook post
Failed
Give a s*** about
Do died
Inasmuch as I don't care that white children
Something along those lines
Shity
Yeah not good not great not a good response
Pretty bad
Alex despatches Jackson
Politely harass
I will give you the bad news first
What's at the show ends before they get back with any report
So we have no idea how that way we might find out next episode I'm not entirely sure
But
Alex and talking about this Thai restaurant
Make this statement
Any
He's really angry about the racism of
Like I don't care about his wife
Being shot
I meant he says
Zip
Proclamation about
What if I did that about other
When there was a shooting in Chicago
Breakout
20 *
Throughout the 17th
Alex has said
Most of them are just killing each other has minimized
Yep you listening to it I didn't cut those
On my way through
And I didn't have any easy way to go back and find all of them to prove my case
And I was really worried about the idea like
If I minimize these
I would be in so much trouble I'd be off the air in a week
I really want to demonstrate my point
I can't go back and listen
24-hours over again in five
Luckily about 5 minutes later reason
Minimizing and you know what he's
Wow crazy
A restaurant owner
YouTube Haven that way
Here's the problem
I don't like
With the guy who said he doesn't care of white children
I see where he's coming from when Alex does the ship
I'm not siding with that guy
Justify a post
This is this again
The people who are so afraid of white genocide are the people who go out of their way
Way to give her reasons for white genocide being a good idea
Everybody else's f****** like that's crazy that's a terrible idea except for the people who are afraid of anywhere like
What
What you do that
Like f*** you
So
Interviews pointless
I love Don
But
Alex has another guy
Who is a member of conquer
Interesting
Because it always blows my mind
Congress
It's weird I think there's a I think
We often forget that there are 465 members of Congress
Yeah guys in the house there's a lot more of them
I understand that
I mean like house
More
Understandable and that's not
The state
Houses
Interstate
Yeah but
Coming into it with
Present
Then maybe didn't exist
Much in 2012
Where there was
Stigmata showing up on here
No bad
Feedback
Congressperson
On
This is strange
It is a little bit of like
The ability to write Federal legislation means
It seems like
Carolinas
Congress
North Carolina
The best out of North Carolina
Hold on to that thought for a moment
Walter B Jones is a member of the House of Representatives North Carolina
352 February
Actually about 15 days ago
Remember recording
His career in Congress is one that's
Particularly difficult to discussion
Very simple terms
Remember of the North Carolina state house representative
Where you been elected as a Democrat
His father Walter Jones senior member of the US House
419 6th
Walter Junior decided that he wanted to run for his father's open
Running as a Democrat
So we tried again in 1994
This time running as a Republican
Use the strong anti-clinton sentiment as a weapon against us
His opponent Martin caster
With the president
Rode a wave of midterm Republican
Opportunist
He rode that energy table along with
1994 takeover of the house that
Republicans
Run through his career as a politician
Not giving a f*** initially a firm supporter of invading Iraq
He was a member of the Liberty caucus
Some claim to have libertarian values but still co-sponsored legislation
The band online
Jones was the one who in March
Serious
French toast in French
Freedom toasted Freedom fry
5 article in the guardian
The name-change headlines around the world
And it's pettiness
Yep. Not a surprise 2005
Foods that will never happen
Which is the quote I wish I had done that
Taking responsibility away from Utah
I I was a vice
It also should be noted that among the list of his top donors you'll find that he's received
$53,500 from Northrop Grumman
$52,500 from Lockheed Martin
And $48,200 from the NRA
The center for responsive politics list Jones
Does the largest recipient of NRA money among North Carolina
With the total he received including expenditures that they made on his behalf
Coming in at over 56,000
So probably shouldn't surprise anyone that has an a rating from the NRA
And consistently votes against any common-sense regulations about.
In 2007 gun registration in Washington DC and repeal the law that did exist on
On the book
He voted in 2009 to make All State concealed carry permits valid in every other states
Which seems to run counter to
Ideas
Professed to have
But I don't know
Is that really means
To do like with this guy it's just like
If if
Groups have donated
$48,000 or whatever
Is that really all it is
I don't think so
Cuz it seems like it also need to replace the other 50
3000 buttercup
From defense contractors
Is that what it is is it just for republicans
I think it's a lot of that money were to just a
A lot of people's impetus
To behave the way they do
Seems like it
I think
Certainly not all of them but a lot of
Walter Jones
Use the Eddie Eagle gunsafe program
And encouraged
Funding for the program being used in schools
Eagle gunsafe program was developed by and run entirely by the NRA
That is a super slimey move
Disclosing
The news accepted money from and try to funnel government funds to the NRA
An organization that exists almost exclusively
The disallowed apostle
Having a real conversation.
This country whatever else
Can say about how Alex responded to Sandy Hook
These few days we've heard so far
Clearly indicate
His number one priority was to round the wagon
A package do what
With pro-gun propagate
Unreal
F****** real
Is there a
Is there less
Evil
Is there a less evil than he could be doing is there some way we could distract them with
Either something
You helped him over the other side and be like all the wild like sneakers
Take their guns away
Cousins f******
Unreal
This is pretty wild
I don't want to take their guns
Dead but
Assured
I'm at is at the end of the show on December 8th
It's a call from somebody
Lives in
Their kids
They don't go there anymore
But they went to the school
Play this clip
Because this clip is
Firmly demonstrative
Alex
Can't ever
In good conscience
Believe
That the people at that school where at
This clip
Firmly prove
But he has to
I was very involved with the school I ran the Cub Scouts
The third and fourth grade
Sandy Hook Elementary I live like a mile down the street
My wife used to do the tenant Hook Elementary School Clothing line SRI fatality baking all they do stuff for
Christmas and Halloween
Holidays they try to represent having some Gathering or
Parties at the school at night for the
Yeah we're pretty involved we know a lot of it teachers in order
Thank you for what you do before
Forget to do is want to thank you for everything
You do
And I want to thank you for putting up from Victoria Soto
Pittsburgh
She was actually my son
After school
Tutor
Kids were having problems with like math or whatever she
It was a tutor for him for like the last three years he was in Sandy Hook Elementary Phil I had conversation with her
Twice a week
Well she was
To the young girl who did
Seems like a teacher's assistant and she did
When my son was having trouble with math so she would work with the kids after school for an hour hour-and-a-half
You know
Extra
Tutoring
And I'll bring them up to
The skills they needed to
And
Really good girl very smart
And my son loved working with her kanohi he didn't mind being there at all
So he's exasperated
She posted a photo of her Memorial
Infowars.com
For that
Whose kids went to
And don't go there anymore because they're they've aged out
You talkin about
Years in the past
Sandy Hook Elementary School
In order for Alex to Pivot is narrative
Into
Believing that people were Act
Which we do now is
An eventual end
He gets to
He has to them believe that they were actor
Planted in that school free
Years
This guy has experience with these
The people
Lychee died
Victoria Soto die
That's cool
He knows her
I don't I don't I just
It's important to
Nail some of those things
Kingsdown in terms of his
Like how far
It Must Fall
Because that
Vacuum
A human
Response
Vacuum
That is
That
Children's
Absolutely
You know giving a respectful hearing
Bring to this guy who
Again
You know Alex Jones of callers are always going to come with grain is kept
Red flags
A very natural speaking
About his experience
He doesn't strike me
A lot of Alex's bulshit
Where's Duke
Accept whatever he saying
It's so without
Alex
Sis
This is
The reality
The reality of Freddy
Whatever you wants to make on top of that tragedy
In order to defend his gone
And his
Admittedly
F***** up fears about a civil court
Begun
Whatever the case is
Here's what years
The recognition that you see in that
Clip
Is what he
Is that make sense
The Weeknd
He knows that this is real
Was murdered
Uno's
That
That is a
Building block of
His lies
And that makes it so much worse
And that's why
You have to be fair to
That's why you have to be
Fairland cuz it makes
So much worse
The same thing
We go we go over
Is he like
The lies that
People tell about Alex Jones
Often
Spiritually
But they lack certain amounts of Acura
And the new ones on the accuracy
We make it worse
Broad
Alex lied about Sandy Hook
Yes
You see
The waves
You lied about it
Aucd Awareness Day
But he had to have known he's lying about it
It-it's
Just it make
It goes for a opportunist
Yeah
It's just really
Really f****** gross
It's hard.
Confronted with the reality of
Trafficking women
You're at your every time you're just
Blown Away Vape
How
Cruel and
Stupid
Was human beings
Can treat other
Sure you know
And it's the same way with Alex
Send this
Station where you just
You're just looking at that guy
How
Could a human being
Do that
What rationalization
Do you have to go
Every single night
To make it
Okay for you to wake up in
You know
Lego
It's so impossible
Really enter the mind
If somebody who is willing to
Children die
Well I'm willing to but
Making it so more
I think
The only explanation
Is that he has to
To convince himself we have to have convinced
Stem cell
0 train
Get gun
Which will lead to a civil war with the leech
Way more kids
Being killed or whatever in a greater risk to their children
So if you frame it that isn't pasta
Argument
Or something
Stephen Glide
Perspective
That you could talk yourself into
Another problem with that
Scream this will lead to that
It's an extraordinary claim
Requires extraordinary evidence
Yeah
I can't imagine being able to come
Convince yourself
But that was the reality
Without
Reading all the
When you are also somebody who only reads headlines and then reports as if you understand all
And everything about all this stuff
How do you convince yourself that a civil war is coming and that's what I'm fighting
How do you
How do you not
Have like well I'm not sure about
How do you not have
Humility
Or the
Surprising
To just be like
This is what I think
I might I might be way off on the most gross
I think
Hazmat
We're talking about Alex Jones
This
Is what you would expect from
Alex G
We expect to be
Not finally
And this is part of what makes it so difficult now
Is even in 2012
Jones Buick
Minimize the deaths of Chile
You expect Alex Jones to do all of these awful things
Because he's Alex
That was the
Every theoretically reasonable Republican
Was doing.
That Alex Jones
Dissembling to try and protect guns in any
This was not Alex Jones Alex Jones
This was Alex Jones reflecting Maine
Stream Republican thought ahead of the Curve
There
This is not this is not some dude out on the fringes
It's part of why he have to go further
We move along
Is realizing life
I'm not getting the same
Adrenaline shot
That I usually get from being crazy from
Because everybody
They're all crisis actor
For whatever
Got to be something
Christine Isaac
First of all
This isn't
A hundred percent
Navigation to find out when
Four actors
Because I think that is
Common misconception that that's the only negative
About his coverage
We've already seen a lot of
Real negative
An infinite amount of Mega
You see
On the first couple episodes
Him trying to find
Just putting
And then finding it a little bit on Sunday
But the evolution
Mistaken
On Monday
With this
He's being much more over about 6
It was fake and the government did it
He's bringing in is introducing new narratives about reporting days before about gun stuff at the
Priming the pump
Having these paid
Gun people on
In order to
To help the reinforces narrative
I think you're seeing
Pivoting towards like
Hitman
Make a demarcation line
I'm willing
About when like things
The wheels fell off the
There was still a chance
His
Rank speculation
On the day off
Probably could have found it Center
And then on Sunday he's even saying
I kind of think the
The official story is right
That's right
So all the way to
The next day in the day
See how quickly it
But for now it's not good
Disgusting
Alright
Twitterpated
Knowledge underscore
Were there
Describe rape
Review all that one
Before the ballyhoo
So far with ours
Not a lot of people
Is it Walter Jones
Yeah I really was a
North Carolina house
State House member
4 years in dog years
I've got a gut like jump
Can someone ask you not seeing what's going on in North Carolina right now
I don't know about this in North Carolina what are you Regale me with a story
North Carolina
Pearson
That was the first state house election where they all decided that
The only way that the North Carolina State House
Hey Dave everybody agreed to K
So they all got together
Each other
I don't know if I'm miserable
Executive director in Arkansas
Should be
Mirroring martial law
She's never killed anybody
Metallica
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work