Alexandra Thurston color
Work up a little bit about Alex
City Orchestra
Yeah yeah
Over the weekend
New pro wrestling Guerrilla wrestling.
Hell yeah
We were in the balcony
Okay I was just going to be the balcony like speeding in the balcony
IP section
Like all the wrestlers the locker room was up in the balcony it was absurd
Felt
Yes cuz everyone is going nuts for stuff in like
Are you like
The biggest response I had two things would just go
I'm not the guy I'm not the type because
And I wasn't
Falling out of that balcony
Tag team
Little bit of a little bit of a surprise appearance
They showed up
It's big as The Young Turks
Bigger bigger
They showed up and beat the s*** out of
What I'm talking about when we talk about it
They were trying to set up a match for their upcoming
Kicked in the van. Givens of piledrivers
Call metaphor for America right there
Philharmonic you can come up with
That's disappointing
Play was great lot of
People kicking each other in the face
Doing weird flip
Those could not be more diametrically opposed
Do you want to go to the symphony orchestra tonight
Cozy professional wrestling
This dude was like
It was
Really f***** up
Get Madeline
It's really hard to tell if it was fake or not I couldn't really like
I didn't respond like oh haha
Might be incredible
Totally absolutely
That level of awareness
I was told from reputable sources
It was nuts
Good Times
Dino lot about that show
Only know what you tell me about it
Give a shout out to
People have signed up and are supporting the show
She wear nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Marion
Mario
I'm a policy wonk
Sorry about that
Forgot to text later on the apologize
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Next
You are now a policy wonk
Play podcast
Somebody who has donated on a little bit of an hour
Also very much
So bright
Thank you so much you are now it's
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites
I don't want
Thank you very much
Look up button so Sports
Appreciative
Jordans
We are going over I'm sorry
It is another saying yes
Okay
Feelings and suspicions
We're going to start moving a little faster 100%
Intended
To do present-day episode 4
Good bit of Alex's shows
Couple days worth
And I'm not going to cover it
I'm just not
I'm not getting engaged with I'm not defending myself
Do you know who deserves an explanation
One of the reasons that I refused.
Maybe
If you want to play some basketball game
I'm sorry a lot of the episodes that I've been listening to end up like I start listen to him
Later I'll realize you still talking about the same thing
Had a lot of
Covering
Is trying to perpetuate the idea that all hate crimes are
They're fake because
Of the jumpy squat
Dealing with the present
Stop at least
This last week
Especially
Incredibly difficult to figure out an angle on
Because quite frankly
Know what's going on with that story
It's an incredibly confusing story every time there's an update it's like
Sending people text message giving them support or like food in money
Whatever you guys figure this out
Right right I'm torn in between two worlds of a lot of the details
The story
But that doesn't mean they're not true
On the other hand
I have
Zero trust of the Chicago Police Department
So I can't make heads or tails
Used to take a side on it and I
I can't
Deal with Alec
With that
Cuz I was I was wrestling
Figure out a way to likes to do an episode
Room for whatever the actual reporting on this is
Is got to come
So I was like
No I can go over tons of hate crime statistics
Do we have done that in the past.
Why don't I do a breakdown of
The 2017 Department of Justice report about the Chicago Police Department
Found it was unconstitutional on a math level
Those episodes
Frustrated
And like
What whatever
Whatever we can bring to that conversation
Is not now
It will be later when we know what the story is
On it now is irresponsible
And I think that one of the reasons
Wake up like we haven't been aware
Of the story
It would be wrong
It's one of those times where it's like I'm so grateful we don't do a new show because every part of this
Stories you see how shity
The media and everything really is
Everybody involved in this story is doing a job
There's a lot of jumping
To conclusions a lot of
A lot of people
Immediately
Sensationalize
Pong ball of Twitter
Actors bad faith argument
F****** ton
Black people
So I check in with the present Towers
So
Mercury facts
Because there's a
Clarity 280
Right
It makes it much more doable to understand
We're talking here about the 19th
December
Alex was pretty
Much clearer
That he is all about
To find a gun
On top of that
He was
Easing himself
Solidly saying
Daddy believed that the government
He's getting close to saying that victims were actually made
And the government killed them as
So here's where we start off on the 19th
Alex
But he likes to play with his staff member
Fractions
What
That's a headline
People talk
Like articles about
He do without
Before government
It's not important it's not as important as
The game of
I guarantee the government doing it
I'm pretty sure if you were to actually play that game by the rules that you said
You would all be at the very least on a watchlist
Also
It leads me to think that perhaps this
Lacks
Because if the thickest things they can pick up our things with a Google search
They aren't
What's a good boy
I think that speaks to a bad
So I started
The little bit
Furby saying that every government Department
With racist Furbies
I recognized
As I was editing the last episode that like
It really hurt us
Emotionally I think
Release Me
I started
10 minutes
Of inconsequential
Threw that in there now
And that we talked to Jordan
It's more about hitting the ground with a
Little bit of momentum thrown out of a moving car
Instead you're giving us ice cream out of a moving car
Help
Soften it up
We find out
We've speculated that Alex
Cover
In order to make a day should claim
About Sandy
Maybe it is something like that
I think in this next clip Alex's
Has found his cover
But it's not
Some sort of external thing
It's an underling that he's going to
Under the bus
I don't know if he does but he probably should be smart
Eclipse
Christmas tree in Portland
So Alex is
He is not
Like it's my gut you think they did that
Right
The temperature
Who is Alex independently turn the corner please.
All it took was
This Rob dudik
But I said
Producing special report that Alex good point
Who is proof of things don't add up
The conspiracy angle that they decided to take
The idea of the second
Specifically the guy who's seen being arrested in the woods
Read Alex's describe
Number of people in the woods on December 14th
It kind of makes some sense if you look at the area around the school
Too far off
Most of the schools North North to Westside was Woods
As well as the east-southeast
With only one paved driveway leading to the school
Without Road obviously blocked off the woods
Preferable
Be there
Get better coverage than
And they were being allowed to
The police confronted them guns drawn questions
And release them
This isn't the case Alex's picking up
I just bring it up to highlight that there was a lot going on
What Alex is doing here is he's relying on the unreliability of first-hand account
In order to create the narrative that he wants
To deliver
In this case you combining two people into one story and possibly even
It's impossible
It's just alter
See how report
You go too hard too early when you don't have any of the facts
Right
What are the things Alex's probably operating off
Is early reports about Chris band Fredonia
Chris was a parent who's on the way to the school to make the first grade
When he heard popping noise
He's five days away from retirement I'm amazed a little bit didn't get killed in
He tried to get into the school checking to see windows and doors before police approached him
Told him to get on the ground
He was detained briefly but was released and reunited with his daughter who is hiding in a
Another man who was
Detained briefly was described by a first-hand witness
The TV reporters on the scene
And here is the
Earlier
So this may come out of the woods
This man being described by this first-hand
It was being interviewed by police who determined to be an idiot
He saw flashing lights got really curious and decided to check out what was going on
But had nothing to do with the shooting long over by the time he was detained
Suck so hard
Oh my God Parents grieving children
Looking at you literally the worst situation that Curiosity could bring you to
Driving you never expect that's what you're going to walk home we're like trying to peek it
The over on the highway or whatever this was
High School
You could have been there would have been
High school kids walking in the woods looking for a thrown away p*** back one of them
It's crazy.
Which I think is a really good call
Really good call so we don't know who this guy is
He was dressed in camo pants
The story about this guy
Alex is going to the idea of a man of the woods from a different report
But in the chaos of the day and imprecise Reporting the came out of it
Benign
Became incredibly suspicious
The man who supposedly found in the policeman in plain clothes
Who is responding
Into the incident
There's a bit of confusion
Because he wasn't in uniform
He didn't run from the police or get arrested
People were just
Confused because of how it appeared 42 uniform
Cops
To be running with a non
Uniform
Right it made it look like a Chase of them were actually run together
Chase buddy
Ultimately there wasn't any
Disposed
The people in the woods ideas
And starts to Trickle
And this really highlights problems with Alex Jones does
He constructs the narratives out of the suspicions that our only reasonable because of the absence of
Information available
I could have a conversation with him now about the second shooter idea and how it's
December 19th
If he asked me who was that guy
I can only respond with I don't know we'll see
Yeah some guy
Then that's where the propagandist has the ultimate advance
Their willingness to weaponize the unknown
Once all the information is out they can't control the narrative suit their purposes
So when there's a situation like this
It's of the utmost importance that they act
Important
Fast
And that time
One. The concrete is still wet
Thinking car whatever initials they want
Forever
Concreteness event
Information that is solidified will make it impossible for them
Nice metaphor
If this brings into Focus
What I feel about Alex
2 coverage of jussie Smollett right now
You know he's playing with the uncertainty
Of the information
Did you now because of that
When there's more information
She won't have that advantage
No matter what
The story ends up being
Saying
I don't know
Oh man. There's no there's no way to tackle.
God it's so hard because you put yourself into that position
Can of like
Some random ass coincidence
And if the cops did release that guy's name
He might be
Dead by now
He's awake
Easily have been murdered
By one of the
By one of the people parents of the people
Possibilities
Terrible
Just a coincidence makes you
Cheese
I hope I don't
Chris manfredonia his name is only public
Because he ended
Open interviews
I don't know if the police released his
B like
I don't know I think
It's probably
One of the rare super rare but kind of
Not as common as we would like
Police being like
Right on
Target
Yeah
That reminds me so much of the Patrice O'Neal
I never litter because I don't want the chance of
Taasa recede into
Bushes and then there's a dead body and now I'm
Suspect number one
Like that's that's
Exactly.
SPI setting
People up
It is true and I can argue the FBI
Doesn't have a real dicey history in terms of setting people
Kristoff
I find it absolutely hilarious example out and come up with
Is this Christmas tree bomb
The 2010 car bombing playing in Portland
Those take out their Christmas tree light
Ceremony
This wasn't a terrorist unknowingly working with an FBI agent
Under-covered plan the attack
The FBI made sure that the bomb was on capable of detonating
And after Mohamed Osman
Used his
Just set off the inert bomb
He was arrested
Which is kind of b*******
Well well
A lot of it
But a a practice that has been covered and talked about
Is the FBI would find
Potential
Terror Justified
They would essentially teach the terrorists
How to make a bomb and then
Ask him to do the terrorism
And then arrest him after he was caught plenty of examples
Up and this this event actually said often interesting
Debate about whether or not the FBI head
Entrapped modmood
Seeing as
4 months
Came up on their radar
He was on set radar
Because he wrote for a publication called
Jahad recollection
And wasn't contact with
Who's known to the FBI as being
Jahad recollect
I never thought this would happen
Start a day
Entrapment would be a good defense for my mood and set such things
Cover agents
Overly cautious
Justin tried to talk him out of the
Washington
Where is entrapment legal defense has offered Mahmood multiple alternatives
Mass murderer
But he insisted he wanted to play Operation already picked his Target
Yeah I mean that's what I'm looking
Though I don't know how you feel about how embedded within the agents this is not a good example of
Aristotle
Intentions
Committed violent mass casualty event totally clear independent
Prior to the FBI getting involved
They're better examples I could have chosen
I'm for sure but most of the examples he would be able to come up with are minorities or left-leaning
By law enforcement
The story wants
Patel is one of Oppression at the hands of the federal government
Who's label them all the terror
But reality doesn't match up with that
In a 2012 article in Rolling Stone by Rick perlstein
He lays it out really well
The gold
Entrapment
Is 1 a story
Because they're involved on some level the FBI can control how the bus goes down at what point applauded disrupted weather
There's media attention or not
They can essentially use the investigation
To help them tell the story they want the public
To hear to get them to focus where they want them to
The focus
That's why from the sixties until
Present day
These things are almost exclusively used against
Left-leaning groups like occupy
An anti-war movement
With Muslims being a very common
Target in the past twenty years or so
But
It's never the right-wing groups they do this to
Right wing
Roblox are generally found out
Easter
The cape
Something goes wrong on their own or they carry out the plot for
Someone from the group defect
Law enforcement
So many examples
White nationalist white supremacist
Subscription
30 years or so and none of them
Had to do with like
Fpi prodding them
To carry out whatever they were willfully ignored
By law enforcement
Ones that they want to publicize because they don't
Priori
Yeah
Is weird
Garbage
He's garbage
Vibrate
So now we have cover
To jump Whole Hog
This is fake the government
The whole thing is fake
Thanks to robbed you thank you Rob
Reporter
Do
He feels pretty comfortable about
Bees
Smoothly into
Position of
I called
Yeah if you want to play that clip for the is this fake
It's pretty solid
Right I think it's still in the ballpark of like for it unless you were the government
Like anytime he's like we have debates
No you just literally said
I'm starting to think about is like ice
The debate light
But I don't think there's a way he wants to present
I'm starting to suspect
The debate
Weird people
Government killed all these kids
I meant other people say they're all fake
Not it was real
And I will
I bet there were it was a narrative progression of him having Gaston
And people saying
Or whatever
So I don't know
The debates thing is is
Assertive
Funhouse mirror of reality
But still
That to me even Alex saying the government went in and kill those two
Killed all the kids
Disgraceful and disgusting
But it's what you
Do you expect from Alex
And I think it's safe ground
But I don't think it's legally actionable I think it's disgusting
Exploitative
I still don't think alike
I think it's what he
Does
I think that's his brand
You can
Charged with if you just save the government did it
Like the government
Kill
I mean but we don't know about John
Thousands of things that he says that they dead
Narrative never progresses from there
Which we know it does
It'll be like
I'm put off by a monster
Still not like
It still.
We're defining
Fumble
And I find that fascinating
That really interests
Yeah it's it's another situation he doesn't know when to end a paragraph
If you just if you just said it was fake and then put a. At the end of it we'd all hate shown we all move on
But you know the reason
Have to keep
What's going on in the world
Sciatic nerve
And their families
You are a bad person
Tyranny
You are a bad person if you don't
To at least reasonable dog f****** control laws
You're bad person
Yeah
Person that this is the way you behave in the face of the tragedy
You're a bad person. Because of your gun position
I would rewrite that
Is another one of his classic like
You just went
These bad little kids
That's the bad person come out in front of us
Days ago
Irrevocably changed
So many people's lives
You were completely destroyed
And you were like they're dangling these dead kids in front of us
Whoopi s*** Alex
No I'm out of here you're f****** gross
Yeah you're
F****** gross
Already had on
He has Larry Pratt back on gun rights
Forgot. Owners for America
Right
Pnra
Because the night before
Larry went on Piers Morgan show
I don't like being totally
It's one of these things like them fight
Morgan was talking about how like
You should have some sort of gun reform
Larry Pratt is like
Look what you guys took the guns
Crimes through the roof
All that stuff
We're talk about that in a second
Alex is going to make that point
And Larry is going to
3 with him
Need to establish that
F****** stupid
Cranium of the normal
Liberal
Anchor
Violent crime rate
Let's see if it fits inside are yours or
Statistics out of context to argue that the UK made restrictions to gun ownership and then finally defense numbers jumped or bad
If you just look at the raw numbers you can make that
But in order to literally all of the context
And numerous investigations of Publications put out by Parliament
In 1997 the UK pass the Firearms Amendment Act of 1990
Is there regulations in place but registration and whatnot
But this act effectively banned private ownership of
This Act was passed in part as a response
So the dunblane school massacre
Where man enter the school shot 16
In the age of
5 + 6
Shot a teacher and then killed himself
This is referred to as
The UK's first and only school shooting
Possibly because they took action
Address
I'm just going to let you take a shower
Craigslist
Why the Firearms Act was
Provide the necessary context under understand
Is lying about crime rate
Serious person every reason to know what I'm about to tell you
In 1998 Parliament pushed Police Department's crime
There was no real standardization
Apartment issues word identical crime could be
Declassified
Completely differently
Depending on what
Investigated
Completely unreliable in
Of what crime in the UK actually look
So it's a little bit like the difference between
Crime reporting a
Chicago and crime reporting in
Joe arpaio's neck of the woods where
Crime reporting in Chicago would include rape
Joe arpaio's world they're like doesn't even really happen level perhaps
But
Encouraging them
Accounting rules introduced National Crime recordings
Crime stat
Including a 100
18% jump in violent crime alone
Part of this was because departments were now required to include indictable
Impossibly indictable crimes
Statistics
And they also changed
For each crime or victim
As opposed to one crime
For criminal
That is to say violent people
Before it would have just been one
Ride that makes
F****** perfect
April 2008
Most of the way they counter defenses
Would lead to it barge jump
Open statistics
A serious violent crime
They began to include quote gross bodily harm Within
Tent as a serious violent crime
Whereas previously it would not have been
So all the Hooligans finally got
Maybe
This boils down to situations where the assailant intends to do gross bodily harm but fails
To do so
That would not have been considered an instance of gross bodily harm has previously and now was
This change came as the result of
The violence was not.
And to get a better picture of crime as it exists
It would be wise to include attempted violin
And credible threats of violence
Discounting is SiriusXM
This alone led to a massive spike in reports of serious violent crime
With no actual additional crimes being committed
Statisticians of analyze the data and their assessment is largely the
The crime is fairly close to flat or even down
But there's an outward appearance
There's been on the rise since
Because of these changes
Tell crimes are reported
Some s*** all over it
Eczema
Unfortunately 1998 is right after the UK's.
Place for Alex
Take these statistics totally out of context
Represent the guns than
Violent crime went through the roof
Either Alex doesn't know this explain explanatory context
In which case he's an idiot doesn't understand the issues he covers
Or she does know about it and he's intentionally lying about it
Neither are good
And even then like your
It's hard to come down anywhere other than
He's ignorant of all the stuff
Other than the fact
That stuff would disprove what he say
He knows that
What would disprove what are you saying
But he does not bother to
To learn about
Threatening to know exactly
Yeah yeah possibly
It's impossible to know for
For sure
No just faced
Activate
I think you
More stupid and reactionary than
Conniving
Yeah
I think that's probably
Affair
Conniving enemy
I don't know
Puppyfind
That he has been so intense
Send Sandy Hook
About how he knows
The war coming
That's
That he has been
Did not make me
I got to be nice to my wife and kids
Call warm up
To each other
Her husband.
This is a different level of my gut told me they did it
This is reporting at MN
Every now and again bringing his gun into the conversation
Also fun fact Alex got divorced like a year after
Wipe the computers Adam Lanza tried to destroy
Computer is before.
Yeah
Although
I've done it
Deep dive on that
As I recalled
It was a him
Yeah that makes sense
A lot of people
Really we don't really have much to go on
Get back to Piers Morgan
You know
This is great
Cuz this is sort of a
A Prelude
Alex
Morgan show
It does that great publicity
Vista
We're on his own show
Get out of America
Play Foreigner
Neither of you were involved in that.
I mostly kept that in there cuz the excuse me is so weird
Bilderberg trash
Excuse me
Get out of my company's on the show
And that includes me
And Bilderberg trash
Is the worst insult
Problem for the radio station
I think the heat made
You feel that way
We're
That's the type of ship
Do not understand at all
You have a f******
Personal vested interest in the Civil War the Revolutionary War
Hundred years ago paly
Alex
Race memory
Manchester still live within his barely chest you know that 100 times
We bury the hatchet
The Americans because both countries are f****** garbage
How about that
The embodiment of all who have come before
Of course is a
People who did all the revolution organism
King
Miller's surf they were they were parked their Red Coats
No sisters were the Redcoats
Lexington and Concord
That doesn't track
A pictures of a Trax feels good to Alex and that's what matters
Neither of your
Sisters still didn't really care
They were both just working stiff
Or they were all work
Not Alex
Hayward
They were Generals River
Alex's family
Pierce's
This was that
That simple
But you make
Upsetting
About how great
I guess I guess Jaws is real
That's true that's true
Still can go
I think that's where I land on the Jaws
Argument
Fourth
That draws
Did cause a lot of people
Be afraid of sharks
Isn't that weird
Greatest movies
Ever made
Because of it and Alex
A bunch of peaches almost went bankrupt
I just delivered f****** Hawaii a family like who live in California
Close beaches
Can't f****** charge you to go
People who like sharks
He probably meant to say is like
Tourism struggling
Microband last battle against
Norris Dam break
Crazyshit
Here in Mexico
Clip
Raises the alarm
And put the word out
Time for all good men
The aid of the party
Temperature is anything bad happen
Lawless that's pretty bad
Is that
Cancel
Play that
Calling all Calling All Patriots
Redware in authoritarian ism
Hear that hear that as a called
Talk of the revolution
You would obviously hear that is a
It's time to overthrow this f******
Government
Didn't
Terrorist attack on children
Because I want my gun
It's time to roll
You hear that sort of thing in
Especially with the laundry list of supposed crime
Absolutely
What is your right
I have war on the Patriots
Galaxy
You're jumping the gun
There's an extreme
Comedy
As to what he says
Immediately after
Who's that laundry list of things that the government's doing
And then he says
Authoritarianism
So
That's
Why is it that the next thing he says
Everyone loves
New shows
It's not like he's talking about like a place you go
You can buy a gun
Under the radar
TV shows
Yeah
So you can stop
Well you can still find the ratings
TV shows back in 2012
Anythink
Close to what Alex's
He's presenting the idea that gun shows makeup
Half of the time
10 shows on cable
Is a breakdown of the 2012
TV season on network
2 1/2 guns
Young Guns
Big guns futuristic world with Dinosaurs in it
Revolution revolution
TriCity another's dinosaurs cuz I have to go back in the past
It's complicated. Be very excited
It's like a minute number 13
Betty White's prank Show Off Their Rockers
Just missed the top hundred come and get it whenever 101
0 gun program
Vaccina in retrospect that sounds pretty great number 101
So no gun programs on their speak of unless you can something like NCIS
Is a gun show
So if you check in with Nielsen to have the ratings for network and cable program
And the top 10 most-watched programs
The 2012 we're all number 1 through 8 being NFL football
Number 9 was the Summer Olympics open
Ceremony
Who was the Grammys
Their top 10 ratings for regularly
Schedule program for the NFL
Trees for American Idol
With the Stars
NCIS
The Voice
The show Vegas
Save a top-10 programs that were recorded to watch later
Do you know zero Gunn program
Does Mad Men Breaking Bad Justified Fringe
Sons of Anarchy American Horror Story and of course
Suit
Exactly what you would expect
That's what I mean the show
Yeah that's a cross-section of the the the
TV is the opiate
So TV Guide put out a list
The top 25 most watched shows
Both Network
Be called a gun show
Having a celebrity for how stupid it was number 21
Well below Modern Family
And post Charlie Sheen version of Two and a Half Men
I'm not sure that qualifies as something that would scare the globalist
That Duck Dynasty number 21
Incredibly unsatisfying network shows even the ones that had both Network at cable
Inside out
We talkin about cable shows
Done
Thankfully after doing a little more
The most-watched
Cable shows
Interesting the article was posted on December 12th
So this should be fresh and Alex's
Here's the top 10
You tell me if there's anything on this list that you would call the gun culture show
This is a door
The Walking Dead
The closer
Rizzoli & Isles
Major Crimes
Pawn Stars
Rizzoli & Isles everyone loved it
Dallas
Sons of Anarchy
Suits
Jersey Shore
What was I don't remember has a gun show cuz they were always take their shirts off
Make a terrible argument
The Pawn Stars
Might be
They cuz they sometimes have
Guns on it
But it's not
Regular
Gundam Wing
Be considered gun shows now that's just part of the word
I don't know I don't think any of those are Sons of Anarchy violence
Major Crimes I'm sure something
People got shot that's just like a procedural drama
I think I was looking through this list I like I don't know what half of these
These f****** shows are
I don't know what suits is I don't want to know
No I'm fine with it I don't know what major crimes
Specifically I know I
I have no idea what that was
I don't really know what Rizzoli & Isles was I've only heard people make jokes about it
Wait was Rizzoli & Isles the one with Zack from Saved by the Bell and what's his face
NFL bracket
Franklin & Bash
A send a send a blank and blank
Yes trouble
I don't know what it is but I do know what Revolution is
Was very disappointed
Entertainment Weekly article provides breakdowns for all these different
Adult
An adult
1:35
54 and none of them contain any gun
I literally have no idea what Alex is talking about
I can't make sense of it
It does not track
With any of the actual
Beekeeping
Places
Is legally actionable
All of Television to be able to sue him for libel
It's weird I was very
Confuse
We're going to find out more about you looking like
Another guess he's already had
Aftermath of
Sandy Hook
Extreme
Very regularly
It's almost like
You know
I don't know how to describe it
Started
I need have a guest co-host that would be there for a week
No
He used to have like it was a week and your dad like Snoop Dogg was the guest for the week
I do not watch
Any of the late night
I don't either but I remember that because I was like
It feels the same way with this rotating cast of
These gone weird
Like Larry Pratt coming on twice
5 Stewart Road twice in like
3 days
It seems like these we only people get any info
Inputting
That makes sense though because
Especially
Even if he's not doing his own
Naturally he would want to surround
Themselves with the most Psychopathic gun
In order to insulate himself from any kind of
Putting that s*** out in order to make his listeners
Afraid and distract them from the tragedy of the
Situation
Distracted
Keep 817
Keep him on the straight and narrow
It's just a path shaped like a gun
Starts at the top of the hour
As we know the first segment
Is not brought
For the station youth radio station
Minutes
I am so Alex is already
Whatever he says will recap it
That sort of thing
Good radio
Stewart Road
Start stalking
About
The militias are great
He has a quote
From the sound
Father
Declaration right is a going out to break
Solve the mystery
Limited
Wonder what you mean by
Your Birthright
Military grade
Just for immigrants citizens allowed to also
Have that Birthright
That's a question I can't answer
Stop you know I don't know
I know what my gut tells me
Did you catch the founding father that was quoted there
Play pit play the number of times
Steelhead
Google a try and find out who's talking about
Something
Selectively remove that name from founding fathers it's gempa
Cox
List of founding fathers
Temperature
He was just a f****** guy
That's good enough for Alex and Stewart to consider him one of the founders of discovery
Funnily enough
After the country was founded Cox
Declared himself a wig
Which that helped him secure a position as
Commissioner in the Washington administration
Years later he decided wasn't really a Federalists was actually a democratic-republican
Curiously around the same time
Veterans coming from that party
Thomas Jefferson
Was president whose animated purveyor Republic supplies
Great
Opportunistically during the first few years of countries existed
Leveling accusations
He was actually a British spy in a tory
I'm not sure about those accusation
But I do know that it's critics
Would refer to him often and Mr facing both ways
F******
Gateway
As far as things go that's true
As far as mr. worldwide
But not as good
Mr. Steal Your Girl
Is the hero
It was free skating at the time
Also teach Cox
It is widely credited with pushing
For cotton
Main crop grown in the American South
It's worth mentioning that
He was opposed to slavery as he wrote a letter from
Where the slave trade right safe and constitutional
Which state which they do now
Referring to other
But as labor is and is likely to be in America we shall make a progress a little slower but not less certain
Transferring
Much of this business of raising those two
No pills awfully opposed to slavery
Cox's actions in Raleigh
The greatest drivers towards the rationalization of and acceptance of slavery
Free in America
CVS
Quote within 10 years of the cotton
Jen
Use the value of the total United States cropley
From 150,000 dollars to more than 8 million dollar
This success of this plantation crop made it much more difficult for slaves to purchase their freedom or obtain it through the Goodwill of the
From 1790 to 1810 close to 100,000 slaves moved the new cottonland
In the south and west
From each decade
A million in total
Cultivation
Spread slaveholders and tobacco
This crop was no longer profitable made huge profits by selling their slave
This domestic slave trade devastated black fan
American-born slaves
Record for the plantations they had no no
Placed in shackles
Forced March
Hundreds of miles away from there
The enslaved populations in
Cotton producing states.
5%
Per decade in the early 8
Etiquette all be traced back
Exact problem
The tent Cox
Clearly aware of
It is 1808 letter
Namely that
If we do this reasonably it'll take a while
If we had slavery week
We can take over this Market
The labor question
Now that's a fun name to think about
I like your elementary school education or your life
Was Eli Whitney's cotton gin
And they didn't provide that
Asterix next to it
Eli Whitney's cotton gin led to a massive explosion in slavery so horrifying
8/10 coxswain
Peking
Huntington.com
Perhaps
So speaking of yeah
Cox
Kissing rationale for what benefits
Getting into the cotton
Quote the southern militia as it is conceived would acquire the spirit of a core
The state government
Blue cotton cloth
With white or yellow cotton under the clothes
Summer at Autumn
4 piece uniform
It would certainly take a
Thunder
Impressive auspices
Equally important
In the good of the militia
Natural manufactures and it's bright and novel novel cultivation
Those opposed to slavery tench coxe
He's partially directly
Irresponsible
For creating the market where slavery
Loaded and got way way worse
His reasons for that
We could make
You can make a lot of money
I'm at the southern militia could get cool Yuna
Yeah
Sounds
A lot like
Babolat Lancaster Road
Politicians weather like
Look
Climate change
I don't want to move on it though because
I am getting a lot of money and I think we can make a lot of money and if we don't do anything about it
Get this get this like you
Demystify it a little bit like why is
Cox father well because
Use the motherfuker who inadvertently or
Surreptitiously
May flavory
Super terrible
Mister facing both ways
That means that what he's reading about in history
Is
The guys who made slavery words and but I think you just ignores that
Part isn't calculus
Awesome Southern delicious
That's covered in the book that they would be interested in Reading
I've never heard of because we're not reading crazy malicious
Remember the name
Text Cox
W Rosebud
Like what
That sounds so f******
Stupid
God.
Man
Little interesting history
Anyway it is next clip Alex gets back to
The laundry list
She has to be upset
The oppression of gun culture
Walmart
Channel 4 hours
Network
Aha now we have a new Clues alright alright alright about Discovery in history
Channel TV
So we can find what are the shows that working
In 2012
They might be talking about
The three shows I was could be talking about
American Chopper Dirty Jobs
An American
The last one
Clearly what he's talking about
Will the TV show
For this this entire time
Gun shows being so awesome
I should have known it was just some b******* that
I like this reality show that got cancelled
He's the Firefly fan of a gun shows
It'll be easy to assume that the show was canceled because of Sandy Hook
Given the timing of the announcement
Cancellation
According to deadline
It wasn't so much cancelled as it was not
Picked up for a third season
And the reasons given were that the network felt that there wasn't any story left to tell with the characters on the show
And more importantly their ratings
Quote finish down double digits
From season 1
The spider starts strong start
Had a bit of a sophomore slump
No more stories to tell
About what
American Guns
Really just seem like that
Quick story
Like you don't even need Ed Burns for that.
This type of s*** happen
Every time some gun show or some b******* conservative-leaning thing
All the Alex Jones types take a
The cancellation
Auto Network
Decision making
Oregon conservatives in the media
It's so goddamn but I realized
Maybe I should have co-opted that argument if I could have got that disappointing
Futuristic
See if I could have got it a second season
Go to figure it out and write it
The ship
So f****** pathetic
Three shows on
Discovery got
Canceled one of them
Had really high ratings
Probably
Late-season
Write the micros pretty one
More probably probably was because they were putting it up
Open Facebook post
Supporting trickle down economics
Turns out
There's one more show that got cancelled I don't know anymore
Before shows
Nope
Because it was good looking
Definition of pedophile
This is b*******
I didn't know Ted Nugent had a show so already that's a bad spoiler
Google cancel
With that kind of thing happening
As a relates to a show on Discovery
Cancel
According to Discovery news on there called gun
It will be a one-hour special
You know Jordan like something that isn't a recurring show
Babysitter one-off 1 hour thing with Ted Nugent's of Gunn
In the ratings
Newton claimed that he was working on it
People from the networks
Absolutely not true
Interesting Lee in other Ted Nugent Show cancellation news
14 multiple shows on Nugent store
One of them
Idaho
Really according to billboard
Nugent without realizing he espoused
And they quote did not
Tell Witcher of Nugent
Which kind of an open question
So much racist
It's hard to pin. If I was listed all of the racist comedians that I've ever met who still work regularly
Casinos it would be a long conversation
Tacoma Washington
Casino were cancelled ostensibly for similar reason
It 2012
Ted Nugent was kicked off a concert
Fort Knox
Are you scheduled to open for REO Speedwagon and Styx
This is in the lead-up to the 2012 election back in April that year
Cold with recent comments posted on the NRA's official YouTube page
Quote
If Barack Obama becomes the president November again I will either be dead or in jail by this time next year
If you can't go home and get everybody in your life
House of this vile ministration
I don't even know what you're made of
Considering it also previously called Obama a quote
Cuban mongrel
There's a decent chance that just want you to also been canceled for rapist
Impressed that he's going to murder the president
Also just because it's fun
The day before Ted Nugent was kicked off his Fort Knox concert
You come to a plea agreement on charges he was facing free legally killing black bear in Alaska across state line
Keep kill that bear for an episode of his show Spirit of the wild that aired on the Outdoor Channel Wichita
Network network even leaving aside all the stuff about how he clearly likes underage girls stands up
Claiming racism
I'd never kill a polar bear
You might
It turns out
Humanity disrespecting
Things about him
He also doesn't respect nature responsible hunting dwaihy
It's almost like that's all just
The character these people
Ted Nugent
Real piece of s***
He's a real judge
Oh we can talk
For a day is about how f*****-up you was all I needed to know and now there
Also a delicious irony
In July 28th Center in
Virginia
Not deny open carry permit
Unless it's specifically requested by the performer
I said that the request came from Nugent
Quote given the things that have happened at nightclubs like pulse and what happened at Manchester
Nugent security people are taking extra precautions
When the subject of guns came up Nugent's people said oh no no
During the show which was Favre
I'm sold out
Newton used to State patterns. About how great he is
Surprise
He also used the time to specifically insult a man named Andy Park
Parker's daughter and co-worker were murdered at Bridgewater Plaza by disgruntled former coworker
So Parker decides to buy a billboard calling do today
Agree with all those
Sonu and said quote
If I get to political f*** you
Listen to everybody
Including those dumb motherfukers were protesting because they're still grieving
When you lose a loved one we pray for you
Will you lose when you lose a loved one
We pray for him didn't we
How the f*** do you hate the newgen family when we're praying for you
You dumbfucks
I can lift a whole long list
Ted Nugent
Just be ignoring
Motherfuker
Strike a good tone there with the whole
Hey hey
Idiots still grieving the death of his family or whatever it is like that I said a prayer for him
And then worked to make sure that the
The issue is this
Nugent would be
Cuz he's bringing up the idea.
He's associated
With the NRA
Gun regulation
Impossible
Is so funny
At this concert where he's screaming about this guy his team it said no guns
Which makes it always
You're sitting ducks for the gun
Newton claimed that he said
Switch the venue replied quote
We stand by what we said Tuesday night and this is the end of our Ted Nugent story
Football
If you're afraid of the Pulse Nightclub shooting
Is there with guns
Are you actually do
You been gone to your own f****** concert stupid
Yep
I hate that
Yep find something like that that's what really sets me off like that to it to an extent that I usually don't get
But that's
Someone like motherfuking Ted Nugent
One of the worst piece of s*** in the world
Between Hayes
Weird love of underage women
He's violent
Threats toward public officials
Is over racism
His clear inability to live by his own principles
As it relates to
To preservation of wilderness and nature big thing
Aye look guns
Crossbows so much
Is because I respect nature and help
All that stuff Tupac
Now you have an instance like this
Why it's like
I fear for my own safety exactly what you said and still I
Say no guns at the venue where I'm at
Principal
You stupid
Make it so everyone else gets hurt
And then you will how are you
You have to try and insulate yourself
From your own
F****** b*******
People should be ashamed
That is the underlying
Motherfuking
Cowardly nonsense
Cancel
I didn't say that
Oh that is so cool
I'm a big fan of
Simply because of it
Its brevity
Just that
And that is the last we have to say on this
Newton storage
That recalls the what's a if we
If we take your
Conquer you will burn your cities.
The ground and then the reply message
If
Like
Vet vert
Responses
Come on
Cut it out response makes you win the argument regardless
Like that
Fuct
The worst result of our years electricity and this podcast
Long discussion of Alex Jones will really be boiled down to
Buckhead Nugent
Yeah true go
Who is Steph
Listen here
I look forward to the next time he comes up
Because like I don't know I can't imagine what more awful things you can find about him
Well I've never read anything
Goodbye
It's good about it
Right
I've never heard anybody like you're always a great guy
Well-reviewed
Like
I think that double live Gonzo is the best
Portishead live
But that's just me
Buddakan
Imagine Outsiders think about that Fort Knox show
With Nugent REO Speedwagon and Styx can you imagine like REO Speedwagon
Guy from Styx
Acting like that kind of an a****** man
I wish
More bands just
Turn towards
I don't
Wanted plenty more fun if Lindsey Buckingham just went out
How to say it was like
Hey next song is going to be
Another another one of our hits
Let's kill the president all right let's go guys Donald Fagen just loses it in the middle of a peg
Assassination
It's really confusing man I think it's partially
Because he has all the same guest on all the
What time is it I don't know where a lot of our players
You don't like a lot of people that we know from Alex's world where are they
Blaring in his absence
But he's around
He Alex and him are both Big Sandy Hook deniers
Long time
And initially
So like I expect to see him somewhere
All these other dudes
Gerald Celente is nowhere to be found
Peter Schiff isn't around
I don't know who else Paul Craig Roberts
None of these guys
It's weird
It is next
We do
Hear about somebody
Stop raining
As it relates to Sandy Hook
Great investigative journalist
Mr. brainwash
Plastic Rappaport
I'm sure he'll show up pretty soon
Some of that juicy
Rapoport
So
Dirt roads is on because he has a new
New Pledge of Allegiance
Pledge of Allegiance
I don't even like the regular Pledge of Allegiance
F***** up
It's not a pledge of allegiance I kind of miss poke it's more of a pledge of
Independence
Okay it's all just the same
Keeper
We're not going to take gun from people if you try and take our guns that's a Line in the Sand
I'd like what what you just
Reiterating
You say all the time no big deal
So trust me it's not going to be
I do believe that
If we play this out and listen
You'll see what Alex has
Is doing a little bit
He's using Stewart a little bit
Start it off
Welfare
It is because we know what he's talking about
Yuri Doki code
SEPTA that's the welfare welfare
There is that subjects to it
Entirely this is what I think is actually
The most important
Really speak
Stewart
But something that I think is
Hi early Acura
About what him and Alex
For trying to do
Denison people killed
That's the end result of what they're trying to do
Through the actual
For the mealy-mouthed
AR
Always conservative conservative now
These are people who never understood the right to bear arms
The dispensary
No s***
He also even go so far as to say it's
Career change
This is an opportunity
For us to wrap and make sure that
Free of people
That's a hundred percent like what
Is behind what you say
And he's absolutely 100%.
Made this point
Once you get past that point no matter how
Decently a reason
You present yourself
People who stuck around
Even if it is just totaled
Conventional
P line of
Resisting any gun
Legislation at all
Regulation
You're past that
You are radical
Yeah
That's what
Yep kicks
Interesting that you can
I think that's interesting that they like from
Couple days
There's even an awareness that what they're doing is getting
Any moderation
Out of this
Getting it all
As Extreme as we can make it
Get because it has
That sort of thing
Are politicizing
Open attic cover
That are mango
8 radicalized
Exactly something that I think is probably like I think they might be aware of this
But not necessarily
I don't know B
They don't kick out ever
Everybody
It's not like a we get past this point everybody was still on board and is it
Voting against
Our Second Amendment or whatever
Because there's people who were skills
Conservative
And I think it's like
Two same people Marco Rubio still pass the radicalisation point
As
Punching bag
For people like store
Moderate radical so far that we would consider
Adjust a moderate GOP Republican like Mark
Marco Rubio
Is actually now
Windows
So far right
Openly saying kill the president
Like if everybody was exactly what they wanted the world
Governing would be
Like is everybody
Goddamn
Viggo Mortensen
King Addie's
Tea party politicians
It was like if that was all the Republicans
They have no idea
Ruby scandal after scandal
And the ultimate end result
Probably
Well no
Well
Everything else
GOP shell I'm sure he likes it much more now
Music f*** that guy
Souvlaki
He needs those people in order to
Keep the ball moving
Or whatever
Of the world to be like
This is what
With the full recognition of know what you need is a goddamn mix
Who's exactly what you hate
You need to radicalize but you need
Brings up
People who know how to do
The work along with you
And keep them somehow cloistered from
Like
The outright
Association
Deny Xavier hook
Being a Nazi
Because if all of your pee
People who know how to get anything done
Like you
Then it becomes too clear what your party is about
It's an interesting sister
I don't know
This is a lot of the socks that were coming up as I heard
Edx
And it's so important for the moderates like
For the f****** evil conniving pieces of s***
Like Mitch McConnell in Marco Rubio
To have these assholes around in the same way that it's important
Those assholes
Because the moderate guys can paint themselves
F****** radical
Douchebag conserved
Words that you can be
That's what Alex
Being that guy
Being the Steve king of radio
Crush
And I
People who
Otherwise would be like
Racism is bad
Still vote
For racist policies
By saying
Team sports
You know what we can't vote for
Democrat.
No matter what
Burglar
Races personally
But I vote for every possible candidates
Who will promote racist policies
Even if they're not saying the quiet part loud
Because they're not Stephen King
Who is the one who Steve
Who is the one thing
The quiet part
It's f******
Disgusting how well-read
And how shittily people
God
This is why we lose
Do you see that
Jackson play
To be at least
Of that being what they're doing.
But
Alex takes this Independence pledge
Or whatever
Just doing
Which again
A hundred percent
Is just
We're not going to take your
Which is the old key
Initial pledge to be
In addition to that
If you vote to take away our guns
We will vote you out of office
I don't know
Like I guess that's better than your pledge sing will kill you
But Alex
Piggybacks
Is using it to
Get himself
Seems like
Kentucky like national attention
Ghetto
I've made pledges before and I got a lot of none of those
Your blood is great
July
What are you doing store
So when it comes to their radicalization
To know the idea of like
Use this to get rid of
The milk
Try to make sense why you would
In their world
But it is next clip
It becomes very scary
Because dirt road starts talkin about
People he wants
To be on his radicalized
Victory we have
The freedom of speech on the internet
Golden Corral
You might not get a chance about the rainfall in 2016
Focus on the guy with the gun
I don't care if you do or how you do it
Wake him up
If you want to help us
Pass
And I'll tell you why
We have a lot of gas
And that is
Hey
Not for nothing responsible gun owners cool there been in the group there was some really interesting
Coronavirus
Bugatti
If you have a lot of guns
That's something
Tension
Cuz there are a lot of guns
Anyway I think it's possible for a person to
To pay attention
Do that themselves
Like I think
If you recognize I have a lot of guns
You know that's something it's a little bit outside of the norm
Have you keep track of that yourself go to therapy or whatever check in on it
You find who like that's alright it's like guns
Responsible
That is enough
Keep doing that
I think that when you say
We want the people with a gun
And your people like Stewart
You want them for bad
I would say I'd like
People with gun
But not to do anything
Them to do
I want them to calm down
The battle for the hearts and minds of
Hypothetical people with guns
They're like
Get ready
The end is coming
We will need to fight
My Angela
Cool
That may be why we're struggling struggling
Is like wait for the information
Right
Act on reality
That is not as much fun as
It's not as fun to wait
As it must be
Get tons of
Retweets and stuff
Speculating
It's not as fun to hang in the back
They should come out and go
Along with America as it is much more fun safe
Yep make more money
None of the stuff that is the right thing
To do
Situation is the most fun
As the person you're morally obligated
To do those things
Especially
Platform
Because today
Do otherwise is to
To do harm to
People
Set a reminder
A10e
Never fails to report
The reason that this is so difficult
Because we're just big dumb
Right so in his ex-wife
A talking about the ways
We can get these people
What guns
Do our side
Stewart's talking about
Find
Land outside like a barracks
Like and then everybody all the soldiers that are there will be like Infowars billboard or whatever and then there is
Terrifying evil strategy I can
Right
That is terrible
Alex is being attacked
For with dead kids
Garbage
Suggest
Because they've kept
Winning
For such a long time by being
Evelyn
Yeah
They really don't understand what a double-edged sword
Because if your if your angle
Is what we need
Is radicalized military
With right-wing pro-gun propaganda
In order to make sure that if something does go down we have the military on our side
Who will then presumably go to the liberal
Cox home
Whatever it's worth talking about
Like I'm in globalist houses
Don't tell the police
So yeah
We get them on our side
Kill Soros or whatever realize when you make that a norm
Then that is okay
To be used against
Liquid McConnell is like let's get rid of the filibuster for but it at all
Okay
You realize though that later on
That can be done
You're f****** because
As as history has progressed
Progression has half
So no matter how much you want break the system
To f******
That progression
That's really doing is ensuring your own f****** downfall later on
As the pendulum swings
We talked about the last time we talked about the pendulum
If you really slam it as hard as you can maybe it doesn't swing back
But that's not how this f****** work
Like this is a bad idea
Headlights
Ostensibly fighting against
It's not
It it's obvious if you start looking
What is probably the gift
Have having
Time
You know being in 2019
On so many of his long-held positions want
He knew he was safe from whatever tyranny
Encroaching
Right
You start to look back on this stuff
You see how flimsy
Superficial it is
You see how it's not based
It's mostly distraction
Yeah
Rival right selling products necessarily
Are you still selling subscription
Select prison plan
Right
Behind all of it
Of the narrative
The ways it time has shown
That his
Anger
Towards tyranny and authoritarian
Doesn't mean
It makes you start to realize that all of this stuff
Just like
Will you have to make sure they don't do
Exactly
We have to make sure they don't do it and if in the process
We end up doing it
Albee what happened
Greater Freedom cross that line
Either way
Go forward
Or we pull back
We're lunatics
We will never ever ever
Pullback
About how I deal
Donatos
The Flash
He gets pretty into
Fight
Plays out and what he gets to at the end
Is such a damning indictment
Who dies of the purse
Call Lynn
I will never submit to the New World Order
Who you really are
Dictator
Really start living
Here's my problem
If Alex Jones Hood red
Professes to have read
He would have such a better reference
For that kind of an idea then
Be for Vendetta
Come on
V for Vendetta
Grid references you can make
Very easily the idea of ideas being immortal
And the flesh being weak
That sort of thing your ideas live on
To site
Make whatever movie reference
How do you start to realize
Alex have no literary reference
Because he's read all these books
But he has such a like a dearth of knowledge
About these every single time
He brings up a philosophical concept
We're some sort of an idea as opposed to citing a book
Citing a philosopher anything like that he's like
I don't understand
Good books are usually harder to
But he says he's red.
Is my point also harder to say
Like I mean
Not necessarily
Information
I think Alex is to ascertain
He makes complicated subject to very easy to understand
Because he can
He could
Any of these things do that it's like one of the brothers karamazov set
About it if it is just
The thing where it's like
If you knows that his audience
Borderline
You appeal to them on the ground
A good idea
If it's that then I understand but it's almost
Never heard
Accurate
At least cite a book
Heavy reference steady reference
You have
High literature
Joyce quotes
In his back pocket
But
Outtakes
Call Zack
From a guy who's frustrated
I called the like Senators off
I leave a message about
You'll like this
Is b*******
Weirder
Whatever whatever
Listeners would give Congress
Prostrated by that
Alex has a inch
Amazing
Original
Republican
Shout began office and Alex complaining
Complaining about Eid
Doing exactly what
Fealty to somebody lied to your face but at the same time
He was complaining about stuff
I don't know some people went bullhorn to Tucker Carlson's house
Eating
Alex's people at
Something like that
So you could be reasonably like okay well maybe it's a thing about the Quorum in people's private space
Unfortunately Alex
Congressman Talbot
We need to go put private investigators on people
Hargett is harassment
I'm not sure it is follow your tongue
I really should have looked into it the legality
I don't think I'd be comfortable with it
If we could
Really think it would be a bad idea to hire a private investigator on Mitch McConnell
I'm not sure what the
You know I would say don't do it because it is private
You're going to end up finding stuff that has nothing to do with whatever you're curious
Violations
People that is unnecessary
Like whatever problems you have about Mitch McConnell
Should stay in the political Realm
Whatever his cheating on his wife
Tell people why
Why not
Riverview that's wrong if you want to live in that space Coupe
Cool I don't want to live
I would not want to know those.
Because I couldn't
If you can find a
Pi2 just look
2 likes proboat
Connections with
Like that
Then that's more like it
Researcher
Right
It's just that to me
I don't know
On the other hand like you doing is farming outs talking to a
Professional basically
Well yeah but you leave it up to the profession
So
Alex is reading an article
About guns
Alex says
Is a Freudian slip
In this
In this clip
Freudian slip
That he
He said something
Teddy's so f****** accurate
And he doesn't even realize it
This blew my mind
Spanish
You're not wrong
Do you think that means I quit
Enthusiastic
The tyrants
That's why I think he's trying to express
You said that the stone was a complete
Yeah
Wow
Episode Racine a lot of like just sort of standard Alex Jones
That was listened to
Like it's pretty
Display
Which is interesting
Cuz the other days haven't really been as
Regular
That's not see him kind of
Place where
He's comfortable enough now cuz
We can hang our hat on that
Sandy Hook done
Checkmart does Justice Gunn defense narrative
Territory
At the same time
That's litify of the government did this
They did it this is the government doing it
In order
The op to take our guns
That's bad
In the
Beginning of the episode
Alex
The beginning of swords
Alex gets a call from a guy who's like
Did you
Read the article in veterans today
About how
Hook was retro
Tribution on behalf of Israel
For something or other
And Alex
Alex like the good guys
Israel did Sandy Hook
And Alex is like
Look
I don't know who's David General quoted in the article did they name them
This is no good
Like and I was like
Holyshit Alex for another minute or so
Look veterans today has a great name
Integrate URL at like he's jealous of the URL
I have a great night and then he gets into talkin about how they
Like you said he was an a******
In the past
Exactly
This doesn't really work
He probably would have been like
Tell me about it
Has him like
Interesting
Goodnight
Veteran interview like
F*** them
Part of his brain
There has not been a ton
What you would call conspiracy s*** about
Broader
The government did it
There's not a ton of specifics there's that second shooter stop right but that's kind of like
You know that's misreporting that happened early on you don't want to engage with how reporting works
We're not at like a
Towers don't fall like that unless there's
Charged explosives at the right exact points and we can prove that this is how they fell in all that s***
We're not there yet we're just at like
Yeah
And I'm so here at the end of this episode
We find
The clip where everything
Okay
Martial law
What about Putin getting elected
So
Here's where this becomes on 10
This is where this
Days later is taking
The turn
Unpredictable
Much later
The only reason you would bring up
Something like that
Is if you're going to suggest
People
Exactly
Why why
From the guy who knew Victoria Soto
The teacher who died
Picture of her
He's reporting on are talking about this video of the father at leaves names Robbie Parker
Who
Was laughing nervously before
Depressed speech
Yeah we talked about this
It is nervous situation
Is
Ridiculous
To make a claim like
He was laughing before is that interview
That means
Most people don't have to
Press conference
Most people aren't good at Publix
You and I both have years of
Experience
I'm so our response would be very different
Then johnny-come-lately off the street or whatever if we were pulled in front of a camera right
Both sides of his face
Much less discomfort
With speaking in
In front of cameras
I granted if we were talking
About a situation
We have lost loved ones
How the f*** could you even put yourself in that space to imagine what are you suppose right
Normal reaction would be exactly stage preparation
Intrinsic trading and it to bring another very
Yeah like even taking that aside who knows how we would respond to that
Just consider this
Prior
The only reason
You would ever cover this story
Or bring it up with any suspicion
Is if you're intending
To introduce the idea
That his
Kid didn't die
And he is an act
There's no reason
To cast suspicion on the Family
If you believe
Is it people died there
But I need to make this very strong
This doesn't match
With the narrative
But he's been building
For the previous days
Right this doesn't match with anything that Larry Pratt
Road Stuart Road
Weirdo love guns his friend Matt Williams
Earth
None of these people have suggested
In any way
That this stuff is fake
Alex is doing this on his own
He's bringing up this story
Of the idea
That this father
Is laughing
And reading off cue cards
On his own
Is what
5 days
5 days later
He is at least
Speculating
That their actor
Earlier
What is saying
We need to hire private investigators
For these people other than professional harassed
Wow your freelance
Pro bono work
Binoculars you know you'll
You see that his kids still alive bada-bing bada-boom
Closed case
Like why would you want to investigate this
If your suspicions wasn't that they were lying
Yeah and we're fake
Because the only end result if you think it's real
Or presenting
Public facing
Appearance
We get into that mess the whole body
We know that he knows it's
But we keep saying like he thinks
It's fake yeah
Right
He thinks it's fake
Telugu.
Yeah he knows it's real and he has
From Facebook
If you
Think
If you want to present the idea
After think that there's a
It's just so
F****** baffling
Yeah I don't understand why anybody would
Even him
He's ruined
His defensible position
By covering this
We sow the seeds of our own downfall from the very beginning
I guess
I don't know I don't know how
Poetic
Like if I were if your goal is to cast aspersions on literally everything
Sooner or later you're going to get
Get yourself a
In trouble if I were Alex Jones
In this position
Someone brought me this robbed
Cuz he's already in the hopper
Like if it was Rob Rob brings me this video that everyone's
If you bring that to me and I'm Alex Jones and I've already worked for a couple days
To build the
It's all about taking our guns
The globalist
Killed the kids or whatever
And you
Totally everyone died
That's the rock worst
I'll be like
Ha
Let's not talk about that
Okay
I see I see how that would be a natural reaction someone might have to in mental stress
Right
Let's hunt on this one
Cuz we don't need it
Right over and over
I've never felt this way about Alex
But listening to him
Like just a stop
Stop
You can do all you need to do without any of this ice cream
But
It is impossible for him not to
Probably Push Pull
Is that
Even on some level I'm sure he knows that
He doesn't need to do that he's already got his gun
Narrative going on
But
Somebody Icarus somebody eggs
You know somebody's like
Hey
Literally
What about look
Well guess what I'll go even f***
Call me telling me to look into this
Who's the master of looking
It's all fake
Wow
He didn't say anything about it
Camera
Doug right now
I hate that so much
Because it shows
Such an awareness of what the reality is
Within
Creating suspicion
Demonized
Maybe that's just how people react
Distress
Yep
He knows exactly what the true
Truth is
He said the word came up like an actor
Nmds stupid f****** character work
About
Like as if
Whatever reaction he was having
Breath comes
With her I don't know maybe that's
F****** garbage
I didn't expect a
A little bit
I didn't expect to come this far
Crazy
Yeah we had
Articles week
It's not
We thought it would be at least a while before he died
Decided that
We thought there would be some emotional distance
Between when he goes from
This is real and it's affecting me
Maybe the government did it but it still children who died
People who are all actors all of this
Deeply insinuate
Happened on
Friday
Do not be Wednesday
It's nuts
This is
Breezy to me
How did it happen that fast
You know totally it makes perfect sense
How else would we have a gun culture
So entrenched in this f****** country
After all
How is it possible that
She was taken after
Especially considering we know that in the UK
One mass shooting happened
Happen and they went
F***
Hey this got to stop
The only way it makes sense for our culture.
No legislative reaction to this
Is it people like Alex
Can turn that corner
Such a short.
To unify their message of nothing can be f****** done ever
Nothing can be done about that
Because if it took him three weeks
Maybe people would have finally gotten the goddamn picture in 3 weeks
It's all fake
Beginning of this episode
Gandus weapon
And their their advantage over
Decent people is weaponizing
The unknown
Like the idea of
We don't know all the
The fact
You can get all if you're decent person
You can watch that video this father
And not come away with it with any
Confusion or suspicion
Anything like that
But a lot of these other things
But he's already started
Bring up of his own accord
Stuff like that
The weaponizes the idea that
So we don't all
Have the reporting on
We don't have the
And
It just it bums me out
I don't I can't
Prove this but I don't understand how this isn't a financial motive
Like I don't understand someone doing this
Who isn't getting
Paid a lot
Like I don't
I know that I can
Chip back that up
And I don't like to speculate about
But like
There's only two ways
This makes sense
So much fun
What
He's just stalling
I have copies of it
To Keegan
Got us some of those copies and they're terrible
I meant subscriptions to his website
I could see some Revenue
The amount of money that it would
It just
Screams to me
Someone's got to be
Even back then
Someone
To be motivating
I'm actually going to go the complete opposite direction
There is no way
Vete
Reasonable human being
Could get enough money to make this change back
Recognize and I totally understand your bafflement at this
Behavior
At the same time I'm baffled that people kill
People in
Zodiac killer was a think
Not
Reasonable human
A financial interest
This is a f****** serial killer
Of course you understand functioning
Other Avenue
The other area
Sure
Not all of them that painting with a massive broadcast
Yeah there's a high incidence
That in those those sorts of
I just I
I just don't know
Even if your social
Because you don't
What I keep saying
You don't need
It's not
If he's a psychopath
And what he cares about is defending his guns
And stuff like that
The idea that the families are actors
Doesn't help
It doesn't do anything more for him
Then
The government came in and killed these kids
In fact the government
He's probably better for him
Vanity these people are actor
Write the serial killers
Another aspect of that is always wanting to be the smartest person
Public there's a reason like the Zodiac Killer didn't need to send letters
You know
Like that didn't help his cause
Yeah you know the Unabomber didn't mean to send those letters
He could have just bought
The only difference is that this didn't
And
It didn't bring any X
Consequence
So it's not quite like that
The things that got serial killers caught
Yeah
I don't know I'm just saying I don't disagree
Vikas mental state
But I still I still
There's
There's got to be some
Undisclosed
Something
I don't know what it is
It could be financed
Lake from where I'm standing
The operator
It really feels like
There has to be some
Ufinancial motivate
And turning this
Right foot
He also is beholding
A lot of really bad sources
So there are p
People like to see
4chan X
The world
And there could be some like
Really nefarious
Hasn't reared their head
We don't know who who or what is going on
That is motivating
Yeah
I don't know I don't know if it's because unacceptable
Because to me that's
Smacks of a
Certain kind of
Hope which is
A weird way of putting
But one explanation
Yeah
It has to be something more than this guy's just
Serial killer
Because at the very least
I could understand this guy
If it was money
If you because
You and I would never f****** do something like this no matter what the price tag
But we can understand somebody who
We recognize that those people exist
For a price
They'll do that
But the only problem with that is all the time
We've seen Alex showroom
You know it.
Given the awareness of life
Maybe that's just how people respond like expect out of
A stereo
It would be going.
Or
Possibly
I don't know if he's good at this conversation
We're having
Reason why this must
Continue
This investigation
Like it's not
I'm not nearly done
Trying to find context clues
Just because 5 days after f****** saying
He's already
Dumbass unreal
Conspiracy
Being thrown around
Using it on
Insinuate
That the victims
Really victim
So how long is that even take to penetrate
Was that like a pretty quick
Interview
You probably was
Correctly
Conspiracy board
It was a
Current time for
Then it is nowadays
Like
Alex has been playing
Ketchup
Conspiracy world
Impreza
I'm creating fake Zack
His
Alternative
And all that
Was kind of like a big
Much bigger
Deal
Feel like him covering this is
Like him feeling
Pressure from the
Conspiracy world
To cover it
If only because he had other callers were speculating about other
Mercy stop even wiser
Universal
I don't know
I think your assessment of me wanting an explanation
And it probably is impossible
Ever figure out
I think that's fair
Still not going to
I'm not going to stop looking
Alright
I'm just
I'm putting
Button
I love you
Context clues
Possible
Because
Mine
Yeah
I don't know
But
Until we figure it out
It shouldn't take
It really shouldn't
Every other one of our investigations
Six months into a big investigation
Life changing events
Yep and it took
20 seconds for him to speak
Yep
Still say that it's
Real
Workout
I believe the official story
It's so sad
All these folks
5 days
He's already
Speculating
Use the word back.
I can't f*** you
Like if I were to put myself in the
And I know I'll never
But but like the idea of
Even for even for us
Okay
For some reason because of the show somebody kills somebody
Somebody kills him
And they
Do you like an interview with me
My reaction would almost certainly be like a
Weird
Laugh cry
Just like I can't believe this is
This is a silly story book joke
I'm crying
I don't f****** understand
Anything that's going on right now
So if you wanted to call that a can if you wanted to use that video is like a
Proof that nobody in my
Only died you would almost certainly have all kinds of s*** like
There's no way that I could have any control over
My reaction
That's banana
Banana
100 other
Publicized
Event
So you could find where
People are
Awkwardly or uncomfortably goofing off and then get
What's the message whenever the
And so many murder trials have those eyewitness accounts
That are
Oh you know
Later on found to be f*****
Looking stupid weather like well the person wasn't
Affected by
So they probably
You don't
F****** Noah covering the episode where
Alleged
Shooter was a kid who was a victim
En guitarra island people thought didn't respond
That's traumatized
The best way to eat
Anyway I can
Still better than
I have to stress that as much as
Not pleasant
I talk about whatever
I don't want to do
Nope I don't take our audience
It's really want this
To do that either and if they do
Platte River website
We do have a website then
Ritron Twitter
We even have a Facebook group called
We are on
Drive review all those good Etc people still
Yes I would say
The imaginary second
Sandy Hook
Did not kill anybody
I can play
Because they don't exist
Right but there's one guy
Who technically probably have killed a guy that's true
And his name is Alex
Alexandra First Time coloring with huge fan I love your work