Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody walk
Another episode
We're couple dudes you like to sit down have a good time
What's the address
I live
That we drink a lot of wine
Just a reasonable model
Reason
It is a reasonable
And I don't know
Goddamn
But you're quickly
And I appreciate it
If only I were the Eddie Bravo
Dumbly going through this What a Wonderful World
If you are sensitive
Please turn off this podcast
I love your smile
Warnings about
Today we're going to be discussing an episode where Alex Jones is disgraceful
Abuse to children
I don't want to do this episode
Jordan alright well guys thank you very much for listening to the first 5 minutes
Are you really
Arthur episode
We've talked about this
We've texted
Discuss this
I sincerely don't
Like I don't want to do this but I think we have to
Yeah
Clear that if this is
To be your
True Crusade against Ali
Eventually we're going to have to dive
Into the Heart of
Friend in the interest of actually covering if I were I would
I'd be derelict in my duty
And it just so happened that on Friday
March 31st
Alex Jones in an episode that I think is one of the most
Disgraceful things that are
I posit
That this
Is where Alex Jones
His propagandizing
And
Being a bad person
Entirely new level
Somehow I find that hard to believe
I will get into
Tell all I know
All I know is what it is
And I feel like that's more than enough to go to
All of my my reasoning why
The case I will
Establish my premise
I will give a few more warnings
But first what I want to do is play
Out of context
With
What we're going
Oh my God
In the White House
Call me Alex Jones
What is the Texan doing
The President says what is the Texan up to
Nearly at Macado's are in the background
Which store or they refuse to speak
F****** horrible
Emojis for Leanne Macado's
Alex
Just sit there
Watching her
The tiny little piece
It's not nearly as shocked as I would like
Get to be I would like her to be more offended by the things
Unfortunately
Think she's in
Operator
Clarification that I'd like to say is a boilerplate before we do this episode
You wrote it down
I did because I want to make sure
I've got to have
This word for word appropriate
I just want to make sure that I'm clear
Here we go all right
Reading
In no way
Do we seek to minimize the
The seriousness of abuse against children
Nor are we in any way impugning the important work that law enforcement agencies
Please do to fight against
We acknowledge that pedophilia is real
A very serious problem
Any answers about the bigger picture Quest
Regarding
It is ours
Vallarta
I mean me
Did Alex Jones
A documented propagandist in Liar
This is
Dan Alex Jones is a documented propaganda
In this episode his behavior is not above board and his actions absolutely serve
The cause of
Protecting children
My contention Jordan
I'm going to be laying out over the course of this episode
Alright is it Alex Jones
Intentionally put on a p
Piece of stage
Propaganda
Eddie used it audience is understandable discussed
About pedophiles to exploit
I believe
What is motivation
R34
He wanted to say
Ever everyone in the world
A publication
And on the internet and
In Social conversations
Made fun of him for desperately trying to avoid a lawsuit over his coverage of pizza guy
He wanted to sell more of his products
Cuz I think he's going through an economic downturn
Cuz he's broke
Finally he wanted to perpetuate the myth that Donald Trump is
Is working behind the scene
Against the pedophile
He's doing this
Because
Is that mrs. accepted
It follows from that position
That a pedophile Network actually does
Exist
Yeah if it does exist
1st and Donald Trump
Well you'll forgive a whole hell of a lot because somebody is got to stop
Please God damn
Right in that third point
Is
All of our enemies are.
I mean look can't be bogged down in small potatoes
Of trans rights
Isn't coming back
We are fighting literal demons
That's
Negotiate with them
Do anything other than
Kill them no quarter
Yep
It is a war
I don't know if you think
That my Claymore make intention
Is 2
What do you think just hearing that laid out what do you
I think I'm only going to refer to him
Is labeled
Code name of the
You know what I can't allow that
Pretty cool
Not really I think I hate
Quarterback
I would have to do a voice in
Riffing around the DL
Protopic
Are going like
Am I even necessary for this
No I'm horrible stuff
So if you're worried that we're going to be playing
Clips of Alex
Really just like a pig in mud
Rolling around in the
The filthiness that he believes is going on I cut out most of that stuff
Not going to be grass
My contention
Will be borne out over a series of clips
More than enough already
If you feel the need that
You want to make sure that you can bury him in
In his own goddamn self
You can go find him rolling around in that
Really
Jose hard at Muslims
Claiming that they are mostly responsible for sexual violence
Extraneous part three tries to bring in
How abortion
Is part of it too and like celebrating
The killing of children
Is what abortion is about
Are we not
A lot of complete nonsense
To try and streamline mypoints
That I believe this is all theater
And I think
She knew it
From the beginning of the show
To wear the show on
Soyuz
This is pre-written
Yes and it's 44
I think more likely than pre-plan
Hehehe
He had a belief
The things would go the way they do and that's what he was hoping for
Okay cuz he could exploit it
Alright I know we're speaking to vaguely and I apologize
Okay so basically
Victory of Friday's episode
Is that he has a guy on the show name
Craig Szymanski
Alright well I'm already out
He's a former Navy SEAL
Red flags
What is gas
There's not the like
Weird
Horrible
Track that I can find
It seems like he might have his heart in the right place
Okay
She is coming on to promote
A new website
But he has started
And a new initiative
Call Vets for child rescue.org
Sounds like a very positive thing
Going by the name I can assume that at the end of your very next.
I will fully support
This website
Listen
Answer there is yet
How things play out is what this episode is all about
But for now
Sorry but for now let's just get to the first clip
And this one Alex talks about how evil the forces that are against
And then on top of that he gets
Some facts videos
And so it's like eagles coming out of the nest is coming out of the cave
All the answers before these people but
We're dealing with very very very very Wicked people
What's 18
Alleged pedophiles
With the kids in cages
California
28 kids
Nothing about the kid.
Thousands of times over the years
And so this is the real currency the global so I don't know
Watch
People
You can't
You can put all those
Together eseverri can't say that b******* and then
Just throw on
And then Democrats
Fat people
Everybody who doesn't believe in Jesus Muslims everybody everybody who supports
What's the ACLU
You can because he
He believes that all of this is all package
Kidstogether
And that
You know I mean we've been over this a little bit and he does David later the children are the currency of the global
Yeah and what do you mean by that is that they prayed
Child slaves around
And that's the way that they gain favors with each other
Absolutely how do you know what when the value stock market for that like what
Reality Intuit
I want to know what's the what's the Chinese dollar
What's the youngest a child
I really want to know
Didn't read this KTLA article
That is what I think
You shouldn't
Damn
I have read this
And many more
And many many more
And his main theme
About the world as it is is the Trump is rolling up the pedophile
Thousand
Why where did that come
The number I cannot substantiate
Anyway he's given the green light
Is what Alex says
He's told these agent
Being held back by Obama
Cuz he doesn't want to
6th grade 2N
Do you know he was holding the back
Right
Them off the chain and that's why there are so many arrests
Now
This Theory and narrative is incredibly
Full of s***
Explain why
Before I do
I'm not in any way again
Impugning the law enforcement officers who are doing good work
My operating
Stuffy
Alex Jones is talking
Bulshit
Yeah
To make fun of Alex Jones
At reality
So
Let me read my
And wipe myself off anyways
The article starts
Hundreds of people were arrested in
Dozens of sexually exploited children adults
We're rescued across California during a Statewide operation
Trafficking
The Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department
So that starts out with
It does say dozens of sexually exploit
Children
There's no indication of kids in bondage there's no
Discussion of cages
None of that information is there
As best I can tell cuz I Googled it I looked into this as deeply as I could
There is no stories anywhere currently
About kids in cage
There are a couple stories from last few years
Massive
Child abuse stories
Kid being saved from abusive parents
Those are the only stories I can find that involve cages
That's not to say that that's not
Horrifying
But it's not what Alex is talking
It's at the very least
Here's where Alex gets in trouble
The second paragraph
Alright
More than 30 federal state and local law enforcement
And please
Including the Los Angeles Regional Human Trafficking task force
Participated
Third annual
Operation reclaim and rebuild
Enforcement operation according to the Sheriff's
It's the third annual one
So nothing to do with Trump
It's like a marathon
Yes
Flight to Boston
Yeah
And you know why they do it every year
Also because
Barack Obama started it
Oh boy
This is business Apartments
I
Entirely agree good idea
I mean this was because of Obama
In 2010
Former President Barack Obama did
Declared January National slavery
Right
Barack Obama started that
When were these boss
Well
He sold
When were the bus
They were at the end of January
They were the culmination
Of human trafficking a national slavery prevention
They were the ceremonial end-of-the-month that Barack Obama was allegedly
Soft on human trafficking
Created
Well
Also
A little dump
Statistic for Alex Jones
The chew on for a little while
Is b u s human trafficking arrests
Getting an all-time high
In 2016
Under Barack Obama
Well it's because law enforcement
Was coming
Cuz because they do Trump
Let the
Proverbial
The Baha Men
Have finally got there
Gallo
I don't know that much
That's all I remember.
How do I
How do I know
Said something to do with
The national human trafficking Awareness Month
The Barack Obama Started in
We got a couple of reason
That just timing matched up and I'm like
No I read the press release
Explicitly layout but the three-day operation at the end of January
In conjunction with human trafficking Awareness Month
Yeah so that entire narrative about Trump being responsible for all this stuff is really busted
It's made up in order to once again take credit for Obama's action
Because we can't
Great
Sing about Trump for all the Republicans
Pretend
The Trump is responsible for all the good things that they
Couldn't allow
Obama
Look at how the economy
Well we can't
We can't admit that Obama took us from a terrible place to where we are
Look at all the good ship
Obama was a good president
And they really like and respect
Camp in their brains are connected
It's not because of racism
Still around
We got rid of
People were arrested
If it stings
Operation
California
Which of the massive star
Hello
I meant a lot of people
The result
I mean
You would expect to say worst thing in the entire State you like a couple thousand
Yeah
The reality is 28 children
Who were sexually exploited
Were saved
And that's awesome that is the thing I want to make very clear
Is that legally speaking
A child is anyone under age
Yep so Alex's whole thing about this being five-year-olds
In cages and s*** like that
That's not necessarily true
We don't really have that information
It could be just a larger part of
The fact that there's still a lot of women
Hurricane going on
18 year old woman
Right or 17 year-old woman with a sexually exploited child
But I will say that it's very different in the mind
Like what you picture
If it's
Elementary kid
A runaway team
Yeah
Neither were good
But they're very different
There
Now
Oh my God
10 year old your f****** monster
It's it's
I like it's not good but it is lesson
Like
Almost grown
I mean part of that is because
Is the word you have to recognize that there are tragic realities in our world
Goddamn terrible home system
They might run away from home or they might just be homeless
Might get into drugs
That could lead
A sixteen-year-old of their own volition
To end up in prostitution
And get arrested Flash
Save-A-Lot
Percentage
Minority that winds up
Yeah
Alex don't give a f*** about that
It sure would be nice
Unfortunately
Of course
California situation
Pedophile Network literally everything Trump has ever done
Let's not get into that because
This
Statement
From
The sheriff press release
Investigators focused
Enforcement operations wherever
King of human beings
Took place
From confronting the reality of sidewalk prostitution
By conducting Johnston
The challenging is right next to conduct
The challenging the virtual reality of the cyber world
We're tractors believe they can operate anonymously using the internet
The experience of specialty trained
Who posed as an interacted with suspect on social media
I threw that tractors and customers were anxious to exploit
Found their plans foiled
So a lot of this
Prevent
Sure
Yeah there were some
Children
Adults who ended up being
Even adults need help is there in a pimp situation
Maybe we should protect them as well instead of considering them criminals and forcing them to work in an unregulated
Industry
That is a larger point
That I want to make also is that
A great number of these arrests
Prostitution
Yes
There
Some of them
Illegal
More illegal immigrants
Some of it is
Not just because I want to minimize if it
Somebody
To Catch a Predator
Yeah and that's not stuff that you do
And there's a fake victim involved
Yeah so you didn't save anybody
You just got a guy
We're just
But it's not what I want to talk
Who's this case
Really doesn't work
The service Point clip 1
Write a pile of garbage
Create
Beer
In people of something that
Isn't what we're talk
Haley misleading on the packet
He also says that we don't know what's going on with these children legal for you to know
It would be illegal to report on what's going on with these miners
Without their consent
Without them by coming out
I'm talkin about it
Well that's one of the things that is so difficult Elizabeth Smart until she came out
Well if you're if you are a journalist who is trying to expose
You can't
It's against the law to be a part of it for many reasons you can
But also
Alex
Images even stupider because
Is the next paragraph in
The sheriff press release
Meijer in Canton
Personnel from various Department of Children Family Service Agency
What's going on
That's really good family services
Recycled back into the pedophile Network they were places
At the very least
Abolish slavery
Coordinated Emergency Services response
Service organization
We have a little bit of information
Now now you shouldn't give us all the information because those people
Definitely don't
Deserve Alex Jones on this b******* and f******
Once again putting
Victims
Exactly why there is
Misperception that Trump is
Getting all of these pedophile arrest
Going cuz I have no idea
People are publicizing
Mostly
Uno's
Sex workers
And they're claiming that
They're about things that they are
So I found a massive list
That someone had posted
Of all of these bus
What happened since Trump took office
And I went through all of them
And almost none of them are reasonable
Almost none of them are
What Alex is talking about
They aren't pedophile ring
Again
There's a story here from Memphis
A lot of these cases
Law
When is not the hero
I don't know
What do you mean
I mean
Again a lot of
Helping
Not necessarily they're not good I'll make your point for you
This case in Memphis
Memphis operation led by the Tennessee Bureau of Investigation
Thirty-eight men and four women were arrested on prostitution related charges
Hayden's Post for ads on Backpage
For about 17 hours a day for 3 days
People in
And some ass undercover agents posed as a juvenile girl
Eight men responded in page have underage female
To those specifically paid money to have sex
The fourteen-year-old girl
These people are creepy
But there's a fake victim
Involved
So you're not saving anybody
Except
Hypothetical future victims
Which is good it is good but the problem with a lot of things like this is those charges aren't going to stick
Thoroughly
If you look at that this article list
All of the charges
And most of them are patronizing
Esthetician near a church
School
Which is
Not a not a big offense
Anytime there was another charge
They worked the patronizing prostitutes and they were charged with
For instance
This guy
Charged with possession of cocaine heroin and oxycodone
Or this guy charged with
Having marijuana and cocaine
Actual charges are charged with prostitution one
Just turning into one of those like broken windows policing
Where is like you just do whatever bulshit you can to try and get any charges on peep
I will say it's good in the case of things like
It's good but
It's not doing the effective
I'm not sure
I don't think we have the answer
I just have the answers to why Alex Jones
The f****** liar
Are you saying two comedians living in Chicago don't have all the answers
Complicated
Procedure
Southeast
Pose a massive sting
It was around the Superbowl
Happens every year
It's notorious
Every single because people go
Come into the place and then they're all these people are rushed into
Cons of prostitution that goes on around
It's
Are just like they're just going to if they're not put in jail there
I'm just going to go back home
Human trafficking victims
Updating
On its latest operation during press conference Wednesday February 1st
Operation at the end of January week
Human trafficking Awareness Month
Operation violent crime against children
The victims ranged in age from their early twenties to late 40s
So none of these people were killed
Good
If they need help
Good on you to give it to him
I'm not taking that away
But it is not what I want to talk
This is an octopus another article
About
More people
That's all this is
Almost
Temporary Transit
Yeah
So it doesn't actually do anything to address the larger or deeper issue
Richmond Virginia
This isn't exactly the same thing it was another online operator
It's just
I've gone through and look through it and I found almost no evidence that any of these
Legitimately
Possibly
Connected to
What would be a child traffic
Even worse than that post links to all of these stories
No it seems like all of these things are
Really more just to generate
Publicity
Cuz it is
To coincide with
And then
The darker side of it too is that there are probably Quotev
Another
Human trafficking Awareness Month
The thing that you've got to bring in
So I think there's some of that but I mean eight if you are legitimately helping people
I'm not I'm not upset about the motivation
In for it if it is to get
Statistics
I'm very
I'm a little
Some people who don't deserve
Yeah but at the end
I don't know
How do I look
Is Alex
You just made the intro for almost all these photos just going to be Alex
Yeah I want us to shut up about what's going on
Nope no you
What's going on
Thousands of girls
What's happened
Orthodox radical Islam pedophilia
Networks
So I forgot I did actually leave in a little bit of that
You
Questions
Yeah he's doing that
Well I'm just I'm just ask
Question
Why are people be doing things and you're like well
Well they they aren't
Why were they doing
Explanation
No
Do they do it
I would I would like to
Just
Get to the bottom of a couple of
First of all we can
Dismiss the idea that
Love is in the Quran
No it's not
There are a lot of
Children that end up getting married to adult
And that's because
It's an ancient book
There are traditions
Go back
Even in
That have to do with
The time
And
It turns out a lot of history is filled with all dudes
Some of the western civilization has
Admittedly
Cuz you died
Yeah and a lot of these stories that are coming out about
Muslim rape gangs and stuff like that is
I've found no basis in reality
Looked into it baby not as deeply
Is
Suspiciously only on Breitbart and Infowars
At what rate games I am the most
Where Evan concerned about
Sorry
The number one thing that
Is
Is the
Most
Is that
Christianity spread
To the point where
They demonized Gabe
People
Very much
And those rape gangs go around raping lesbian women
In order to
Turn them straight
Yeah
Not
And I'm not even to save that say
Christian
Sanity
That is a perversion of everything that
Humanity should be I agree
I agree
Ghetto cowboy
Do you win
Pedophilia to be a respected Orion
To make sure that if
Man
Comes to your house
Hey I want to take your five-year-old on a date
You can't
But the only evidence that I can find
That
Facts
Is it in 1993 the international lesbian and gay Association of Chief United Nations
Consultative status
Nablus membership
Neil GA Drew heavy criticism
And caused the suspension of the eye gilga
From the you
Oh okay
Explicitly not
International
Association
Back in 1993
Covid-19 94
The ilga Expelled
Continue f****** looked at him
Yeah it look
Yeah
You say that
The UN is trying to pass
Agenda
Under 21
Yeah dilg a still was unable to get their status back
They weren't able to get their consultative status back
United Nations
This is caused a really interesting
Sort of fight
Between
NAMBLA and
There can't be an intern
Human Rights Campaign
Organization
Words to insinuate
The pedophilia is an issue related
The gay and lesbian civil rights
I agree
NAMBLA says
Man-boy love is by definition
The Western homosexual tradition
From Socrates to Wild to get
Many non-western homosexuality
From New Guinea to Persia to Zulu the Japanese
We're for bipedal
Man-boy lovers are part of
The gay movement
History and culture
Most recent like here's
Most recent reference
For what I'm doing is okay
Is Greek
2300 years ago
Yeah maybe maybe you guys are wrong
What the representative goes on to say homosexual to be attracted to adolescent boys
Or just as ludicrous as heterosexual saying it
It's not heterosexual to be attract
The adolescent girls
I don't know bro
Stretch
Right
Man you got to do
Complicated math
Yes this person is of the same sexy retracted
Me and that it
Part of the natural sexuality
I don't think we need to unpack.
And
Nah
This International Association was kicked
Yeah because of because of Nampa
Anybody else
Right and then all the sudden
Like here's the thing
Yeah which is why we should the federal government
That is not
That it is not a
Gay or lesbian or straight
Sexual orientation
What it is
Is you want to f******
Right there's no
There's no I have a gender preference
There's
Tire
I have a kid prep
It seems to be more in Port
Yeah anyway
Why is that
Salon
Pedophilia is okay
This is based on a series of articles
In 2015
He was a guy who came out of the closet
Pedophile
Who wrote These articles
Say art
Supporting pedophiles
So she won't even the most right-wing of people even they are like well hold on this isn't really
This isn't what these crazy right-wingers say
Here here's just a little bit of
His
His article
My name is Todd Nickerson and I'm a pedophile
Does that surprise you
Yeah they're willing to share our stories
For good reason
The children's delay claims
The most reviled status on the planet
1 p.m.
Any chance you have of living a normal life
Yes I'm not the monster you think
I've never touched a child sexually in my life and I never will
Nor do I use c****************
But isn't that the definition of a pedophile
Someone who molest
Children
Not really
Although pedophile and child molester have been used interchangeably in the media
A pedophile is someone who sexually attracted to children
That's it
There's no inherent reason you must act on those desires with real children
Sometimes
Because the powerful taboo Keeps Us
Hiding
Is it possible to know how many non-offending pedophiles are out there
Besides
And too often we suffer in silence
That's why I decided
Speak out
He goes on
To call it
The highest order
And a massive
It is hard to have sympathy
Right
But
I think that I do
I'm in the same way I
This is a false equivalency
But I was really into diaper
Sure like that's gross
It's got to be tough to do that with you
Most play files
Are not practicing
They've never touched
We're getting it we're getting into consent
I appreciate it
This article
Really leave you with necessarily sympathy
And it's not supposed
What it's supposed to
Express is that
There are people
Who didn't make this choice
Being attracted to Children isn't a choice of
These people have made
It's a horrible curse
Facebook when they were younger
Something
Danos
He knows exactly what it comes from
The guy with a brain tumor came in all the sudden he's at
Did the children
Take it out
It's
Is that attraction
Is gone
Children
Emojis
Weird dumb
Monster survive
And I'm the only thing
But is it all
Is it the guys making an argument that
Not everyone acts on these things there's a lot of people who have these feelings who understand
But they can never act on it and it's a horrible person or trying to
To get help with it
Maybe one of the reasons I can't get help
Because if
They come out and say
Pretty much they're going to jail for murder
Yeah and I understand the reaction that people have to them too I get it I get all sides
Crazy but the thing is that this article is this article is interesting and
Thought-provoking more than it is
Looking for
Yeah but we know that Alex Jones doesn't know how to read
He reads this and he's like kind of files okay
And that's not what the article is
So in that one clip
We have three in
Edible live
All-in-one
He's really crushing
So far we have not even gotten
So now we get to
We get to
This man
Greg Solomon Sawyer
Here Comes Alexander.
Tell us about your idea
Currently
I can doing raise all the world
Make Spotify some patriots
That's illegal
Hey we're not going to talk about these
Horrible Vigilantes operating outside of the law with very little oversight
Probably going extrajudicial in
Yeah
We're big fans of lynching
Yeah I mean
That the net really gets to the heart of why a lot of ism
The problem with Alex
Is doing
Operating outside of
Any Authority
And that's really dangerous
Part of the of the law and this is
The most
Addition of
Everybody deserves
Affair.
Defense
That is there
Text the bad guys
It's
To protect us from going
Far-right
If you
Absolutely
Because he said it
He said if I catch somebody
Touching my daughter
I'm going to kill them
Right
That's your
Pizza stinks
And that's one of the things that we see so often from
Electing judges in electing
Attorneys in all that stuff to be prosecutors
Is
We are elect
Them because we want them to
To punish
As hard as they can
And that is the most
Damage
The people that are being
Punished
Don't have it
Will like baby Dory minimums
Susan drug offense
F****** the murderer are pale
Terrific deserving of the death penalty are payout
In f******
What boxes
Years before they were even charged
Yeah that is
That is why we don't
That's why we have those laws there
And
Are also good reasons to not have
Vigilantism
If you're going to get the wrong people
Are you sure
Yeah
Issues
We still mythologize this guy's a hero in there so many times
Oh man I beat up the wrong guy anyways moving on that guy's going to have to shoot out of a tube for the rest of his life
Walter White
Here's a is not a clip
Introducing the song
Intro
I should also add
He said he's going to pause a lot.
Oh no we're going to get interrupted
Enforcement officer
Positive unfortunate time he was saying that in addition to being a Marine
Saw man was also
A federal investigator and I've done some research into his
I read a biography
There was also an interview
On a website
It mentioned no
Law enforcement
His career
How many times have
These guys come on
Turns out
None of what they say is
Okay we have documented evidence wasn't making it up
For five years
Colby from Survivor
The Host
But he was
Gun
Expert or whatever on there
He's a Navy Seal Seal trainer
He's
Listen to app. But Alex's laundry list of other credit
Is not
Anything I can backup he's never been investigator
Well you have now
Federal law enforcement
You have also obviously in the CIA Navy Seals everything you've been in all of it
3000 + reported pedophiles arrested and it goes totally dark
Shows total proof the total control
Sunlight is
The best antiseptic for corruption
I agree and that's why
To Alex Jones claims
Give me a vet in sensationalizing the idea that it's all these people have been arrested or supposed
The pedophiles
That's not the case
Have adult prostitute
The idea that you sensationalizing it with kids
Some cages and all this s*** is just
Again it
It's propaganda
What's the right term for it is exploitation of fear
Sure it is at 2
So he's going to get into why Craig is on the show now in this next
Clip and this brings us to act
Act one was the setup of his premise the Trump
Doing all this stuff
Wiping out pedophile network switch
I think
Based on all the evidence
So according to traditional screenwriting rules
We've introduced the characters in
To get into the
Yeah
So here is
What you doing here
Virtually every
Theron
With this and it's really all about her for our organization
Organization
Walkthrough
It's a pedophile
That fill your head
We're just crazy
Oh maybe it was in that minute-and-a-half long expletive rant that Alex did on our last episode
I don't know what that mean
I don't know either but she was fighting
Is it like a as a like a
Help
Okay what's your point of Jordan
Stop bring that up is that this
Was Friday
March 31st
That night when he was drunk on air
For 2 hours
Was March 30th
This is the next day
And I
Believe
But at this point in the show
Alex is sober
Maybe hungover
But by the end of this
Know how many hours
Houston because of how this radio drama
Does radiodrama ends up
Necessitating
I'm staying around
I think he did his time
And then had to get back on air
That's my theory
Okay sounds very different at the end of this
He sounds like
Last episode
Where where unraveling
Right either way
He did that embarrassing f******
Learn
Oh yeah little learn Rob do
He did that the night before that
Down
Left right
Within 24 hours
Calling Adam Schiff c*********
Screaming he wants to fight him
Losing his s***
Do a duet with the architect
Let's finish out this clip
Keep in mind this is within the same 24 hours
Todoroki
It's by the end of this episode how dry I am
Alex
Recreational feel like I have
The ability to make a positive difference
Since then
Search for child rescue.org
And Just Dance
We got a pedophile Network in control Beckley the NSA
Crazy
He is going to do
So much
And his heart
Search in the right place probably
Respect
You know he's doing what he can with what he has
Jordan Spieth
Into early
Oh God damn
It seems like that might be the case but you're speaking far too early
Is Pedigree a little bit
You know how he learned
That the media is always going to lie that the media is the only
Boyd the mediator
Scare
Basically
Is a puff interview for the most part and then we get to this part
Where Alex predict
So you would say that Alex Jones
Is acting like a narc
Archetypal
I wouldn't put those words your hand
So this next clip is where Alex
Go-kart switch Alex
It talks about how everything you do about pedophilia gets
And that is important
Keep in mind
And the police
Meanwhile
We try to share that on Facebook
So this is important
Because this
Is Alex giving up the game
I believe
I believe that this is Alex
Sort of showing his hand but he knows
What's going to happen in act 3
Spoiler
Also I want to say that are you
Are you, down home country lawyer Matlock b******* right
Cuz I like to take a moment to say that the only thing that I support
On this episode
Is it coming back from break
One of a Time
Alex Jones
Came in from break
Silent Running
Play Mike and the mechanics
That's a banger that's a good song
But
I realized you know that song
No
Is a great song
I'm not I'm not disagreeing with you because I'm assuming that
Your
About to play
I'm going to play a little bit of it just it's fresh in your mind
I think it's important
I swear to God this is
Is actually rella
Okay
Feel like it is but I promise
So after cut through the you like
52nd introduction
Does every 80s movie in one song this is Top Gun this is
Days of Thunder
Basically this is Tom Cruise
But the reason
I love that I love that since
The reason I wanted to play it is I realized
This is the most Alex Jones song in the f****** world
Okay
Take the children and yourself and hide out in the cellar
Now the fighting will close it will be close at hand don't believe what the church and state and everything they tell you
Believe me I'm with
The high command
Whoa
There's a gun and ammunition just inside the doorway
Use it only in emergency
Better you should pray to God
Are you bothering the spirit will guide you and protect from
Mike and the mechanics
Came to life
I know I'm tapped into reality as Alex
I'm saying that I came back from break
To Mike and the mechanics
Silent Running almost as a tip of the Hat
Almost like a I get it I get it I think it's a little clue
For those who like in a really look into it
It's probably just that Alex
I love this song
Swear allegiance to the
The flag whatever I like they offer
Never hinted what you really feel
Teach the children quietly
For some days Sons and Daughters will rise up in
Fight where we stay still
What is happening
Silent Running
Because we need some sort of like
Fun and amusement
So anyways that song is pretty hot I recommended
So we now get to
At this point in the show
You might be wondering
What is going on
He has this
His
He's launching
Yes he is also launching
A fundraiser
Youcaring.com
Okay in order to raise the money for it
And they get into the specifics here
The website is
Cinema World chart of the word
Child rescue.org
For the number 4
Call rescue.org
There's a way to donate for starting a nonprofit organization
At The Gatekeepers
Yeah but we can get all the bureaucratic red tape
Interruption
Donations I know you guys are for real
That poor child rescue.org
He's doing this fundraising
Campaign that they
Youcaring.com
Think
To create a documentary
About this
Riches
Legally problematic
Because
It massively approach
Is defamation
Oh wait
So they're making a documentary web series about specific people did I mess up Network
How would you do that without going after the people
He's talking about going and documenting and going
Buster Network
Well yeah but he doesn't mention it doesn't mention Alex Jones specific level
Pedophile Network
I would not be on the show I didn't
Does go after them
That's not what
Of course not but I know you're right you're right now
Pause Alex Jones
Actually Donuts
Well
Enough
But
No look there are pedophiles
Communities online online
The dark web
You know you want to try and work with that
Goodonya
I'm at work again
Globalist
Is where there's a problem
If you go and you end up trying to
Make a documentary Series where you're going after these people inevitably they are
The crime when you are going after them
And if you're going after them knowing they're not going to
Charged with a
You're probably going to take justice into your own
Do go around
And you document something
You find
Is it someone has committed a crime
Now your evidence is inadmissible in court
Yep so there's no you're doing more harm than good by vigilante
There's a legitimately no upside to this outside of exploiting the fear
Exploiting
That's the only
Real game
Documented all of the evidence that's being cited
This KTLA story
Number of proper Boston
So
I have to believe that they're motivated by profit
Beds
I still can't believe this Navy SEAL guys
If it's possible and I can totally understand why he wouldn't understand all of it
If your Navy SEAL it's not exactly like you're used to worrying about
Search and seizure laws
Yeah like that's not really a thing that you have to be concerned with whatever you're committing those exact crime
You should be you should be concerned if it based on Alex's fake
Curriculum everyone everyone who
Whatever it is
I like what you're doing out
Good on you Alex civil forfeiture
Bobbitt all this stuff is going on all this terrible stuff and then he lies about
I really like
That show your watch
Oh yeah never watching the game
Hey
And you see the proof about Trump on a few issues like this Healthcare thing not being
Obamacare was better than nothing
And I just have every week I'm literally like 100 article
But that also that article on Townhall is where I got some of the references
Is that I discussed earlier
Garbage
What's the local news
Things that are
It's it's
It's infuriating because this isn't funny and it's such a serious issue
It seems to me
Like I hate I hate this
Average intimately hate
Not what I was doing but the weird
Anyway
There's no
In the middle I'm not I'm just I just hope there's no evidence
In any of these articles that their legislators or judges being
Caught up in this
There was one legislator who recently got caught
The seventeen-year-old boy in a hotel room
Party
Look
Scump
The guy in the hotel room
Do you process
It's not good but it isn't as bad as kidnapping children
That is not it's so essential
It's it's
Anyone here
Obviously
Delaney's
If that's the case
That's illegal
Yep the military is not allowed to do operation
Uso oil
Especially not bonforte
Operation separation
And it's scary that the police
Becoming so militarized
Yep goes deeper with Ally
His narrative essay that he's spinning isn't there these
Compound
That are being infiltrated
With military might
In our country
That are housing
Child pornographers
And torture dance
And stuff like that
Military
I met everyone on this
Who is your source is lying
That's why
This isn't going on
Yep there aren't
Military scale battles going on
Because it's not possible
I would say it is possible but
Hopefully we still have some
We still have some
Vivid
The instances of high-profile people who have been
Caught up in
Are numerous
And it's big news
It's all over the place
Also when people are kidnapped
Their stories
People are safe
From kidnapping
Stories about
We see it over and over again I guess I brought up Elizabeth Smart
Tuesday
Girls
That's our in that house with that creepy dude
Yep
There are Dorados
A big media topic cuz they know that people will
Unless
The globalist know
That's the only way for this narrative to make sense
Fortunately
Donation
I'm going to give $10,000 to this
Right
Whatever
I mean it is a lot of money but
You're worth over 10 million dollars
So
$10,000 is
All the months
How this is supposed to work
And like
Why can't we do it through proper channels
It sure seems like
Independent
Circumvent
Also if you try to do it
If you're just a reason we can't do
If you're doing this
Without the
Breast involvement of law enforcement
That's why it's okay
Bristol Police Department
For you exactly what they're saying is being covered up
Yeah
Put Chris Hansen
Big is the
That just b*******
Joe the mainstream media is
Distracting you that's the fake version that they want you to see not the globalist
Cabal organized
The oldest is organized man
See pictures of
You can just create your own reality
And there's never a there's never a bottom
Floor
There's no there's no argument you can
Can make when your
When you're fighting it's like fighting somebody with religion
How do you know how do you know God is real and one of the things in the Bible is just like
When you know you know you know you know you know you know
Great Bible
Alex Wright
I agree it is mild
Schizophrenia
Inability to
To deal with things that are outside of your preconceived notion
It's it's
Form of denial
Living world that you have
Control over of your own choosing
That was the presentation
The fisa
The sort of scenario
Is Ben Diaz
Marine on
Who wants
To crowdfund
Half a quarter million dollars
In order to make a docu-series
Where he out pedophile
Gotcha
Again
Legal issues with that
Whether he's doing this
As law enforcement
Or as entertainment
Either way there are some dubious
Pieces of it
We're just to go back to Catch a Predator a lot of those people flat-out
Prison
No they weren't
TV a lot of them ended up with very minor charges
Maybe even a fine
What liver enzyme
Yeah it was like The Running Man
Sure he wants to do that
God bless him
There's
Chosen Temple
So
He's got to do it with law enforcement
Seems to be against
Two pieces of
Keeping it independent
So your f***
Here's the beginning of
Act 3
Now at this point
We're about to start
Into the end of the show
Leah McAdoo is around
Eventually David
That this point Alex has ended his shift
Essentially
You might notice that sounds like she has a little booze
Whatever
Garage
8/8
Inflection at the end
Is the inflection of the end goes up and gets
Borat
Where's Malik
I also tell
I also kept a clip and because it was the infant
Pennsylvania McAdoo going
Alright
But here's worth X3
Start earnest
Weather
And
We're spreading everywhere
He's talking about the
Along with our great hacking expert I got involved
Michelle Taylor they made the calls
They have the email Rochelle it
They should you violate our terms of service up a guy with a History Channel show 5 Seasons
When we are on channel 5
Again if you legal
To say
Feel like
The credits of the people is like
There's a guy I'll from the History Channel
Are you kidding me a guy from the Discovery Channel we know these are things that are impossible
Hitler's been on
I have
Spell
Giorgio Tsoukalos should be invested
And
Touch this it's over
We don't have $100 Starbucks
Immediately
Gets in
Alright
SimCity need to set up the exact
Situation
Because they are so scared
It's in KTLA
Who are the kids
I'm talking to my kids are on milk boxes
Based on the fact that
He has
3 lies
In there I just assumed the fourth thing he says is a lie
Is that is that wrong of me
I don't know I don't know if these kids are on mailboxes
I don't know
Do it
My point is I don't
I don't know and there's literally no way to legally know who the
The 28th door saved
Los Angeles
There's no way we should be allowed
Speculative and he has no evidence
Is sources have been shown to
Is Alex Jones being told those things
Can probably assume
He's being told those thing
By the voices
Just weirdo collars or Liars
Direct message on Twitter
Really plays the vicar
Yamin is pretty straightforward
Let's see what else he has to say
Violation
Oh you don't think so
Solomon Sawyer
That's not a good time
Semi clean the man
Can you please
I found five instances of him breaking the rules
Countdown Lexa Letterman
Had any
Effort
Justin putting in more work
I would put drumroll
Okay so the first one
Is just from there
Boilerplate
Although you caring has no obligation to screen
Youcaring reserves the right
Screen or edit
Music
Anytime
If for any reason without notice
You are solely responsible for creating backup copies
Bababababa
Already on you can refuse service to anybody
Exactly like most customer service
That alone
I got no legs
No shirt no shoes are illegal no service
Tim called what
Youcaring is a website that provides free online fundraising tool to individuals and nonprofit organizations to raise money for personal
Positive project
Trying to become
Nonprofit
How about Saturday
Yeah okay
Compassionate
Been providing fundraising
And supports a humanitarian causes of the situation
Wink
Demonstrate compassion
Ensure their love for their cause with others
We discourage fundraisers that may cause divisiveness
Disharmony
Within our community and reserve the right to
Prevent remove such
We allow fundraisers in the following categories
Medical expenses
Memorials and funerals
Emergencies and disasters
Adoption
Kids and family
Neighbors and community
Education in school
Sports and team
Pets animals
Volunteer
Service project
Nonprofits
Mission trips and Veteran
We do not allow legal fundraisers for bail bond
Legal defense or criminal litigation
Civil lawsuit
Divorce or cussed
Three issues
And other legal
Do not allow it
Nor do we allow fundraisers involving military conflict and reserve the right to remove any fundraiser that you create that falls into one of these
These areas at anytime with no notice
I mean
The way it's set up
It is kind of illegal
It's definitely it's definitely its
It doesn't fall into the category
No
Recover
For that
If he was an established nonprofit
History
He's not giving this money
No
This is a criminal thing
This money and he's going to
To use it
People down
I feel like at no point in the movie The Dangerous
Okay I'm going to need the crowd
To hunt down people
You agree not to post upload to transmit distribute store create or otherwise published
Any of the following
User content that is unlawful libelous graphic
Indecent lewd
Suggestive harassing
Threatening
Invasive of privacy or publicity right
Abusive
Inflammatory.
Misleading fraudulent or otherwise objectionable
Pretty sure he falls into a number of them
Certainly very suggestive invasive
Definition
Yes
I believe so
Misleading hundred percent
Absolutely yes
Objectionable
This
What Alex Jones
Cuz the law is
Is the law
Now we get down to this next
Dissection on
Indemnification
You agreed to defend and hold harmless youcaring its independent contractor service
And their respective directors employees in Asia
From against any claims suits or claims
Against all damages cost liabilities expensive
Including but not limited to reasonable attorneys fees arising out of related to
Any user content you post or otherwise train
Northridge
Or you
The interactive area
There's no way that they could
Indemnify you carrying
Out of this Witch Hunt
New operation
This is slander City
Lawsuit City
Because actually charged
Actually trying to do a show like this would only work if
The people who are featured on it are already convicted of a crime
Yeah
A release form
Nevermind. Do that
I'm not I'm not
Trying to give legal advice
The last one
The five infractions that I believe I found in the terms of service
User content
Constitute
Encourage or provide instructions for a criminal offense
Or that would otherwise great liability or violate any local State national or international law
Including
Without limitation the regulations of the US Securities Act
Commissioner
This would be very
This this show this fundraiser is very illegal
For those violations
Do they make a big stink out of
Do you know what they did
They wrote that up
After that probably
I got you a once again
Globalist
Now
This is why it's important
That I brought
Attention to the fact that earlier
Alex
Was talking about how this always
Spencer
He predicted
Novice
That's something
Crystal ball
Perhaps
Reading the terms
My argument
But I'm making
Set up at the beginning
Fully layout
Okay is that I believe
That they made this you
Youcaring
Get shot down
Oh okay
Did that
A trap
And that at the end
At the end of the
He's going to read those terms of service
And they're going to tell people that don't have anything to do with that
Even the late tomorrow
Googling necessary to find all of that is their martyrdom is
Complete and all of that is to set up this what happens
All of it is
Is just a justifiable
So you're going to you're going to Colombo the f*** out of
I believe
Just one more thing
They have no idea about violation
Yes
Your acts are a little bit but I like your I like your style
Okay
I believe that all of this is laying the groundwork for them to
To be able to get into the stuff
After they get into
I believe that wholeheartedly
I believe it they did it also to reinforce all the ideas until already presented
About Trump going after pedophile Network
Be at the fact that this guy is fundraiser
The pedophile Network or super powerful even sensor
Fake evidence manufactured
It's propaganda it's stage propaganda
Yeah and the only way that my brain can make sense of it is
That's lucky coincidences or they knew going in yeah
Tough question
Because I I I believe that they have
That level of cutting
Or someone behind us
Cuz Alex's pretty
No Alex doesn't
Alex
Sing.
Direct
That ability there
Being the producer
I mean
Rocky seems like the simple are we calling route
Putting Alex Jones through the wringer for the night before
Just visible that it
No I believe it robbed was a True Believer and
If you not be getting Alex off track
But
Let me see if I can find a way to more
Crystallize my point I'm not sure I have okay
So here is your main point is if I understand
This is
Design
This is all bill
Switch their narrative
Back
To him being the Martyr
Abraham being
The stink off of that
I've been on this ship
I made a mistake but we got
Distracted from the main issue exactly
This is where Alex Jones lies a bunch of
More about what he did
No you're not
Out-and-out lies
In the interest of protecting
Defensive sentence
Like the idea
We're proud of our attraction in the entrance of a
Reality
Alex
Please address the fact that you
Still have not said that the
The shooter in the cat back bossk
Was a white dude
Please address that
Give us
That retraction
You know but you're not going to get a lawsuit for
From a dude and came back
Who's in prison
Yep
Okay
Good breakfast
Emails come out
Aleister Crowley Stone
Rituals
And then there's all these peaches
They say that that's your cheese pizza Shelbourne all that stuff
Check pizza child born
Well that's like internet phone
Yeah you know
That's troll internet
That's what they do in the media awesome 4chan comments they probably constantly
A pizza place
How do you spell Claudia
The flooring is coming
All that is there ever
And
Even then
Story straight but we have
At least that one video of him
It is completely contradictory
A documentation of him lying in a different way than the way he's lying
Right and no one is no one
No one
No one who believes the pizzagate is stupid you're stupid damaging
The cause of protecting children
I can't imagine I know that there's Atlee
At least one dude who does
Cuz There's 7 billion people on this
But
That dude
Isn't it
And it's not it
It's again just this
Miss aligning your critics
Miss aligning of people who are against you
One way is to say
That everyone who were fighting monsters
Keep kids in cages
The other way is
To say that people are arguing pedophilia
Well as an example of a strong man but it wouldn't be
Helpful
So anyway in this next
This next one
This is one of my favorite thing
That is
Alex Jones
I am
This is
Adjust his Showmanship coming out
And then on top of it he started off by insinuating the Civil War is about to break
I can feel it
I'm feeling good
I believe we're crossing
Those kids are crying out to God
Cliche
We don't want to be
It's got to be
And so as a man
You can see how f******
Fake that is
Alex Jones
If you watch the video you can absolutely see how fake that is
It's a fence
The content of it
Makes it all the worse
There's not enough words for how bad I feel about the
This Is Us
Are you getting Wyatt are you getting why I have labeled it a new low
Yeah for him this is absolutely
This is
Words fail me
Motorcycles I don't know I have failed me as well this is unbelievable
But we are doing so
Why do blisters go by
Water filters things you need
Roblox all out there trying to Shutterfly that he's such a best-seller
Yep f*** you
F*** you
CoQ10
Fair enough
I lived in a world where that didn't happen up until
You make me here
It's it's it's one of those things where you put on this show
Visit 3xplay CenturyLink
Because everything is so severe
Yep that's exactly what the game
Support him you need to donate
Twice
Yep
That is
The game that is
100% the game
Navigate to ralix
I think
That
That is that low level
Yep
This whole thing
On f****** believable
No this is
This is
Televangelist level
You know like if your if your
Not paying attention to what's actually going on easy to get caught up in
The sensationalism of the emotion
And if you're someone who is easily
Influence
You know
I think people
Rightfully so are very offended when they hear about children being harmed
I think that using that is one way that you can
Trigger people into not thinking rationally
When you bring those sorts of fat
Alex's doing that
Yeah it's f****** insane
It is next
We get to
The point where Alex
Doubles back
On re-establishing
To make it seem like this
Has been a real turn of events
Right so here's this
Because thousands of bucks every month
No more show scared of this
Nope drunk blurry
And he's trying to reinforce the earlier cuz everytime you bring this
They don't know
I'm not telling you the truth
Millions of people listened to your show every week Alex theoretically
But 1245 using his own numbers
Yeah he's far more popular
Craig Sawyer
The salt man
So they censor this guy but not how it doesn't make any sense
Walking theater
So anyway
David Knight
Has been silently sitting by as co-host
Most of it out
You do have to listen to it for a minute you but
I don't think I made this clear enough
And then they finish their call and Alex Goes
And then
When
What the f***
Don't
Where am I
So whenever the thing
Taken down
They get saw man back on the phone
How to get back on Skype
So there's a break or he's not there and then they bring him back
So I wanted to make sure it was clear
The sort of narrative
So he was on there and then.
He was on 42 announced
The fundraiser
They finish the call
There's a break of like maybe 45 minutes half an hour or so
And it's boring so I got most of that have
And they get him back
During the show
Immediately after announcing this
Yeah
Wow
He probably got
Why they had to have taken because there was a guy
Sing it got up to like $50,000 and
Yeah
But still do it
Is like
Did he actually
Click the buttons on air he shows his receipt on it
I don't know
I'm inclined to be
And they realize
Radar
Yeah it wouldn't get up to the q18 whatever
Well well either that or illegal
As we know it
It's 45 million people are listening to Alex Jones
I'm assuming at least one of the employees
Possible
Yep
David Knight comes in
And
That's the sign of a man ready
For whatever
Well he wants to talk about abortion
Speeding
A sacrifice children to dark God
Baphomet
But
Skips off that
To make this point
I'd like you to not talk
I know I say this too much and I'm sorry
You have never said that too much
Please let the click play always been absolutely correct
Play cuz it's horribly fence
Accepted because we have do not have
Decide that they want to be 12
We can have the teacher you can have a psychiatrist
If I can do that and the kid can make that determination at the early age
California
Yeah
So a couple of interesting things that I would like
But they are very formal
In terms of psychologist
And how they interact with France
The reason is because it is a very serious thing
It is a real thing
Ever use the word
Genderism
In my present
I'm going to feel my hand
Garfield
So it's really
Is because that makes it seem like it's
Some sort of plot
Psychiatrist
Sandy community-at-large swallow
Standards of care
Wpath standards of care
Are the
Generally accepted
Standards
I'm dealing with children represent with gender dysphoria
Mattress
On your own
What are things that interesting is this first paragraph
Important difference between gender dysphoric children and adolescents
That isn't a proportion
Gender dysphoria during a continuance
Rather
Little children
Bailey boys
Who referred to clinics for assessment
The story of Perseus
To 23% of
The children
Boys in these studies were more likely to identify as gay
Transgender
Newer studies including also including girls
27%
Persistence rate
Gender dysphoria into adulthood
In contrast
The Persistence of gender
Dysphoria into adulthood appears to be much higher for adolescents
No formal prospective studies except
However in a follow-up study of the Adolescent
Gender dysphoria
And given puberty suppressing hormones
All continued with the actual sex reassignment
Beginning with simonizing masculinizing hormones
The percentage
Adolescent adolescent
Who had gender dysphoria
No 225
12 to 27 in the most recent
Once you got into adolescent if it persist
They would persist on into adulthood
Wow
Cher
That seems
That's crazy
A 100%
Other Studies have shown that there is a strong
Indication that if it is
Persistent
Into that age
Absolutely
When you're younger around sexually
And the reason that it's important not to treat people like they're weird or
Because
Some people grow out of phases
And for some people it's not even
Who they are
When you have this
12 to 27%
Distance to Dalton from the age of
You can't
You can't be shity to that
April 27th
Psychiatrist
It's your responsibility to
Protect those
12 to 27
Percent while at the same time
Acknowledging
That
As they get older they may
And they may become
Not
Okay with who you are
Where is
84 2
63%
Of the population
Yeah
So you have to as a therapist respect
People who aren't going to age out
And not bully the other people who
It's a very delicate line
F****** hard
And then of course
Is it where everybody knows psychiatrist to
You know how many how many psychiatrists have you cycle
My number
Some socks or grab right buttons in the cancel stuff like this
Clear-cut standards that are that exist
And the idea that schools and doctors are telling them
Years old you should be a boy when you're a girl that's exist
Any response
Undermine
Your trust in
Any of them
Any school
Very possibly
Telling your five-year-old child
You should be a girl
And it's further undermined
Everybody who has
Non-binary or non-traditional sexual gender
And so why would you
And maybe being tricked by doctors
Your f****** kid
Do anything but yell at that
All day everyday
You are the
Singapore
And if you if you run one of those camps
Again you are a criminal
Glossed over in Thailand
I feel terrible that we have
The goddamn pedophilia
People
Who identify as trans
Tune that out right
That's well within character for him
The drunken lieshout that not even
Really
Relate
It's horrible
White noise
But the other thing that he doesn't understand it all as the difference
Between sexual
Number three
Sexual orientation
Which is further offence of sexual
Anything like that
Even
We also know he can't read
Makes it difficult
All the stuff that I presented
Do any of the stuff I know
We did figure that one out
Here's the wraps everything into Trump and then
Really weird way
Really f****** weird
Right now
Red cedar mommy in 2 years and they
Is saying no and all these other people I know
Human Nicki Minaj military operation
Outside of basins in the US
Obama is Muslim
Epic time
If absolutely not based on any reality
Sure that's irrelevant
Niacin
Crying s***
Warthog
One more clip
Again is what it's all about
You saved the worst
We haven't had
This is what this is
I actually now
Dim the same way
That's that's number 36 on the website
I'm not made out of money
But I only investment
100000 is coming now
And pumps
And all their taxes and ran everything
It doesn't matter I'm so committed please donate Austin foursquare.com Friday next to their kind of locks on that
Just please I just want I have a compulsion
I have a compulsion to help children I have a compulsion to fight these people
I just I
That's what I m just
Myself
And and it just it just looks defeat the but if you just support us
Videos get the workout we're going to win
At the end of the day
Money money
I mean
Think
Hey maybe you donate
You know people who
Take care of
Right
Donate
These organizations that are actually on the ground
Who donates one of them
David mentioned make a positive impact
The Ali Forney Center
Surfer homeless
Atq
Youth in New York we're going to do something like that
But I want to
Just play this
In case you missed the end of our last episode
This was Alex
Amir
11 hours
3x play about a propaganda about child abuse
This is what he sounded like
Before but
Learn to experience
Didn't learn through
Education
Or you can learn through
Revelation
Race memory
Erase memory
So there is always more exactly
Common sense
Shelly's common sense
Learning
Elearn
Well you have education
Like you said
Experience
Well it's spiritual Galaxy
And you really learn by screwing up
Screwing up
The best way is to learn
That's why she was quite
The three ways a movie.
Lake
The best way to learn
Slippery
I want I want to play
The night before for 2 hours
He was threatening and standing up like that
Clear parallels and similarities
At that clip to the end
The other club
So in summation
I believe that what we've covered here I apologize
You talk about some of this stuff I really don't like covering
These sort of issues
Necessarily
Because
I worry
That people could think
Our perspective is minimizing
A real world
Is very
That's something I really don't want to do
I don't want
To minimize or take away from
The reality of abusive
Against children
I only want
Two strap
But Alex Jones
Is using it
For his own
This is
Your exploitation
Cheats for money
Well in Portugal work
I would I mean
I'm not I'm not I'm not willing
To give him
There's no all the Trump stuff I'm not willing to do any of the
All of that
Is in service
To getting money
I don't I think anything
I think
Ancillary
Episode
He's done this
How to feel your b*******
Not in not in the long-form narrative that we're seeing now this degree
The only way to
Conclude that the reason that he put
The state are the only conclusion
Draw
Is that
This is all a telephone
Dark World version of
Yes
Jerry Lewis
Jerry lizard has this is the underworld drywell version of
Well I think I'm going to I'm going to amend my statement a tiny bit any of our drought
Do you think I would have been
Is that deposited and I I do believe
The Daleks
Or someone
In-production knew that
This fundraiser would get taken down and be able to use exploitative
The only other possibility I can come up with is that the storyline that they were going to go with
They lost
This fundraiser
And then Alex can be like
So support our show cuz we're supporting
And I would still give them fundraising possibility
And then when the fundraiser is taken down
He much like his criticized
I did not let a crew.
Crisis go to waste
I think it's possible that there is that he's like oh that's make hay while the sun shines
That's possible
I think it's more likely that he knew who could take him down
But this was all a setup from the gym
This Vista
Is one episode
Both
The Great
That
Are stupid verses
Is evil continuum
Evil is the one
That wins all the way on the
Absolutely
Even if my hypothetical other scenario is true that still
So sorry guys but this wasn't
Are typical fun freewheeling type episode
We need to cover
We'll have one it'll be a lot more fun and
I don't have you next time over at knowledge fight.com
Oceans up there for the new stories that I reference
You can subscribe to us on
Tunes
Twitter 100 knowledge underscore
Show up on Horizon 3 starts just a microphone or whatever forever
All right I don't want I don't want I don't want people like this just
Because we have a picture
If you don't like us where we don't have a picture you don't deserve it
God
There's a ton of other stuff you can find on our website to knowledge
Gmail.com please do also
Sending out those wine bottles
Play they are neither steel door delivered
Their side didn't find are growing
My autobiography biography
Why file
Ray's documented the number of his lies and explain why their lies
We're growing
People are sharing this and we're getting more listeners
I I really am surprised and grateful and I'm glad you guys do it like contact
Twitter with people is always really engaged
We like to
We like to be there
That surprised Us in the show us stuff that we wouldn't have otherwise
Thank you very much everybody you're the best
You know what we're also the best at one thing
What's up where a couple
Call a policy
Alexandra Thurston color