Alexandra Thurston color
Greek Novelties even talk about Alex
I should tell you that this is an inch
Interesting
Actual novelty novelty beverage
Novelty beverages
IPA
A bunch of time
Not novel well we've run out of different ipas at the liquor store and they don't have anything other than Bud Light after that
That's not
I can report
Happily
Terrible
Yep this is garbage we're getting sponsor
Riddle of the day
Nice
Kickstart of hydration and watermelon
Oh yeah
Anyway I'm sorry
I was just going to ask you if you've ever lied about how much
Or inflated your self-worth
Usher
I feel ashamed of made like
That's it.
More
You know
You live 30 something years I bet there is a time I did
But I can't think what like maybe back when I get a paper route I might have lied and said it like
In order to have a paper
Something like that
Nothing that's possible I don't know
People know me is this
Straight shooter.
Self worth
But that was
Which is next to nothing about my self-worth but that's called keeping a stiff upper lip
Showing that old British resolve
A man one more bad thing and I'm out of his life
How are you
Right
In order to get more money for
I think that's not called
Yeah
Alex Jones
Yep that's alright that's the dynamic that we have betwixt us
We're going to have some fun and some
Black straight up fun
Just give him some shout-outs to the people who signed up and are supporting the show
That is super slow
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Ewok
Where you got it
BFF
Text Robert suspicious of the most common spelling of Jeff
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next
You are now a policy wonk
Hirelevel
We appreciate it oh so very much
Robert to Roberts today
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
I don't want
Play Gerard Avenue Robert Ave
With these gents do I'd like to support the show and you know make sure that one
Or something
I'm not sure
The button says sports show
Evaluation of monetary
Speaking
Pittance
Yeah
This is cool man we were raised well you know already
It's hard to avoid this sort of in
Information break
What is deemed!
What's going to happen the moment there was a fight
That Rogan Woods
Because the other way with his humanity and be like I'm not going to reward this
Yeah
I have a lot of thoughts and we'll get
On Wednesday Joe Rogan embarrassment parade
Nicely done
Really deeply embarrassing
Like all across-the-board everyone comes out looking bad
Like Rogan looks like he is an enabling f*** head
If you don't come away from it thinking like
Alex Jones is ADP
Believe Disturbed human being
He is really really f***** up
And he is dealing with some intent
Internal emotional
Mental health type issues
I don't know how you're dealing with reality
Like right you can you can be intrigued by his
Conspiracies and Pinky
He's funny and all this stuff you can do that all day long
But if you're paying attention to you listen to the things he's saying
He's describing a deeply
Play Disturbed
Thought pattern
A deeply Disturbed human
It's so f***** up
And Joe is just
F****** help
Please
Yeah because some of the times I think
He thinks that Alex's
Is joking when he
It does not have
And then what
Hi
Are there smoking some tobacco and Studio Alex let me have some of that
Tobacco
As if it's not a f****** video podcast
He's very I don't know how much that I don't know how much
Just trying to be cute I'm not going to
I'm not going to judge
I tried to make some
Like little beginning note
I wanted to talk about before we got into
Just to give
Some of my bra.
What this I think we touched on them already.
Embarrassing
But it's a smart move
Go to because he knows
Both of them know that
It's going to work out well for them
Like
Clix and stuff like that
They both win in the end
The conclusion of the
Joe Rogan Alex Jones
Pissed off
There's a large part of me even covering this is kind of a bad idea
Pointless exercise
But at the same time I don't see how we're in Alex Jones podcast and we somehow get away with
Not covered
You know what I'm saying covering like a modern-day thing which I intended to do for this episode
To do this at the podcast
Feel like this is a modern-day thing
So here you go
Here's Where We Are
It's entirely possible that Alex and Joe's fight was entirely
But if I had to guess from watching this and seeing the way that
The two of them behaved in the
I would say that it was fake from Alex's side and sincere from
I think Joe was scared for a friend who is lashing out at him
In an attempt to get attention
I need dealt with it exactly the wrong way
By caving in and giving him the attention
He was demanding
Alex literally threatened to politically murder Joe on air
The accused
Just having mob connections that were
All of his running
Bitcoin scams
Fun in bed with Jack
Sure the accused
Covering up satanic pedophile ring
Talked about aspects of Jose personal life
He was clearly told to
Keep private
And all of that
Incredibly inappropriate
Abusive Behavior
Was not
Only not
It was rewarded
Go to be really hard to imagine a scenario in the future where Alex does
Throwing a tantrum
Is the right way for him to get exactly what he wants
I don't know
On this episode Alex Begins the show with a glass of straight Tito's vodka in hand
Any get pretty drunk pretty early
Meat meat meat on ice
It's just still straight vodka
Proud of it
The only thing I'm surprised by In This podcast is that Alex was drinking clear liquor
You like weird start with
I'm not I'm not mad at you
Like I understand
To get a buzz
Inch it like that but at the same time
You're going to end up talking about satanic pedophiles and screaming about aliens
Stuff like that
Seriously don't be drunk at new
Well that's why
Start with the clear liquor at right around 45
You can switch to the brown like you got a f******
Handle
Huge bottle of Tito's
He makes pretty good progress
So they proceeded to record for 5 hours
And as you can expect
There was a lot that pretty much impossible for us to cover it all in one episode
Without it becoming as long as our goddamn endgame
That is to say that they're probably points of the show that listeners will think we miss
And to that I say
Fair enough
I tried to prioritize looking at things
Disgusted
Providing new information
Caveat that I don't necessarily believe most of the stuff I was going to say
It's hours and hours of a drunk
Idiot talking
Pretty much
The Infowars two-stroke
Branded but in the same way
And you talked about narratives
Recovered 100 times I don't see a real
Benefit
Can covering it again
The talking about this like why we talked about that
Breathing stuff that he said the last time he was on Rogan show
And some people like like
You talk about that
I promise you
If we didn't talk about it
There's a
5% chance that I missed it
And there's a 90% chance
That I just thought like
Another 5%
Wildcard
Wild Card explanation
Here's what's really important to keep in mind
All this exists only for Alex get publicity that he
He does not have access to any more on his own
Alex has a major problem on his hands
To attract people into his financial web
And Joe is one of the only solution
That he has left his problem
If he reaches a point where you can't manipulate new people into his little Marketplace
Then it's game over
It's just a waiting game to see how long
You can delay the audience
But he has her leaving him
That's all this episode is about
Alex is trying to sell himself to Jose audience
Do an extensive almost incidental to Alex
Except to be a prop
Someone whose mind you can blow
I would put it like this
Alex's be Cutco knife salesman
And Joe is the penny that
Tickets cut-through to demonstrate how good his knives
But yeah that's kind of how I
Fuel when I listen to
Episode
Almost
Like
Joe is trying to deal with it
Human standpoint of like
You're my friend I think you're
We just didn't talk enough and that's why you got mad at me
Trying to reach
A now that I say and Alex's bear to pay lip service to that
Talk about
Your leaders are really going on in the world
Because he wants Jose audio
You willing to tell realize that Alex isn't actually
I don't think you like
Alex was screaming on aired
Not a couple
Weeks ago
On his own show about how my big mistake was I I just
Became your friend
I never liked you I didn't like you
From Joe
The same time when you say s*** like that
I don't know
They don't have
Cuz they don't have as deep a relationship
Edgewood
Deserve that kind of patience and that kind of chance
Right like you
Whenever they talk about any of their
They're like a story that's not good
Every single time they talked about like
Oh remember the good times
It's at one time they ran around and George Bush map
Re-read
That's the only f****** story that they ever bring up of like aren't we great friends
The time wasn't that the brothers I think that's why they became so close
You can never break
I don't disagree
So
Here we go we're going to jump in and of course
One of the big sticking points
It's for Joe not wanting to have Alex back on his show
Headband that he realized
About what he said about Sandy Hook
Alex
Gave Joe the line to like
We just have to pay both
Aunt Jo on his own show and past episodes
Has made the point that
One of the things that I had a problem with
Is that I heard the clip
I went back and I listen to stuff and I saw that Alex was lying to me about the
I'm so
Right at the beginning of the show they
They start
Their fight
A little bit and then get into after this clip
The immediate elephant-in-the-room
That is Alex lied about
Alex Jones
We're live
Go to be here man good to see you
Why are things are happening
You and I
Padua Fresno get a long conversation on the phone
Which led to just a lot of talk to drop today
Cast
We cleared the air on the phone we decide to clear the air Moana podcast
No more relationship
We talked about 90 minutes about how you threatened to murder me on your show and then
Essentially made criminal accusations against me and
Talk about my family in ways that
I made it clear is not for public discussion
You betrayed my confidence on air
I'm sorry
It was Alex
Yeah well is Austin
Right
But being a sad sack
And Rogan being like well maybe my friend really is in pain
Performatively Express
Disease
These emotions that humans
How we got to where we are now that's
Read the first part
You know what his XM was out why not just talked to Alex Jones
You already from the first from the jump
They are not
On the same page
At all until about 2 hours in
And when the when the
Not good
Variable
I'm so here we go this is
Point at which
Rogan brings up Sandy Hook
And a scallop
Makerspace
Clarify
The thing that people are upset about you the things we want to talk about like quick to get it over with or not. Quick
But just get it
Is the Sandy Hooks gas
Yeah
So
Your take on it
First off
Because it's always misrepresented herself
I love Gwinnett
I'm about to lie to you I always expect the next sentence to be
F*** you b**** in The Clique
I'm up
First things first makes me think of Chocolate Starfish
Different reference
Okay okay
Real tragedies
And I believe
Cool
And you believe Sandy Hook app
You are
Video editing timeline
Almost
We already know just from looking at the days after Sandy Hook on our own show that that's
Complete lie
I know how does Joe not know that he's I don't know I'm clear the air and it's
Explain like
What are the things that you know like what
What why is it okay what you're saying
That sort of thing
Just sort of refine his life
Static-X
Lake listeners are people on
The internet or whatever were things that he was
Responding to
Sure I'm willing to buy that
I mean you should have a better editorial policy
In terms
What you report on
Number one
I didn't number to the timeline week later
And then five days later on September 19th
It was fake the day off right
He came to a solid position a couple days after December 19th 2012
He started suggesting that they were actors
You cannot
Make this claim here
This is b*******
And Joel allows it to go on question
Which is a very serious problem just out of
I think I like them are going to work themselves up
Open to like
Possibly a new lawsuit by the time
This is over
Over this
One sentence I really think could be acting
In a bowl like in addition
Like
Getting Alex
To continue to dig his own grave
I don't think so cuz this would be a much shorter episodes
Knock that out the first few minutes
Alex that blows a timeline
Again about that
Hook and we know that from looking back
Just a monster Blaine.
Okay
Well I don't think that's I think the majority of them are angry because the narrative has been that you're sending people to the Sandy Hook
Families hope
Home
Lateral
Yes there is video.
Put together
Do you think it's not real
But now you do think it's real or not
Because your job
You're f****** bad at this
Like
Yeah I just got the police.
And I really hurt people
Responsibility
Go to the
Adult entire episode
The video that is not at all
He's telling a least that the 2015
Yeah absolutely not
He's dodging responsibility while trying to
Again performatively except
Responsibility
That's pathetic not only that but we did here in our days after
Sandy Hook that people
Need to go investigate and hire private
Gators
People to their houses
Well he just said that
Yeah that's a good point he already but you could fall back on the argument of like
IMac
Professional
I'm at the FBI needs to be investigating this
Amateur gumshoes
To get out there and stock peep
I don't know why but I've got this
Joe Rogan
They're not
Cut bait with
I need never learn
Joe Rogan never took my advice when I was his dad
We are all our ancestors
By default that we are all everybody's I don't know
Joe tries to get Alex to understand
There is
Long people particularly
You people going to have
Certain forms of mental illness
You speaking way too broadly
Introducing like schizophrenic love conspiracy theories
It's a little bit to General
Is that there are people
In the world who believe that everything
And that you
Get into
To that system
And Alex piggybacking on that
He was kind of
That way
Before kind of
Before right
There's a problem
Urus pack
He realized he was falling into that trap
And he discusses Atmos nextplus
Stupid
Call Tricia
Everything
Now the important thing about that is Alex only is
He realized
But he was in this pattern of believing everything is fake and that's
Because he became the victim of
Conspiracy theories
Basically
Started treating him the way that they treated
The people that Alex it about
And he then was like oh my God this is awful
Is he dealing with the fact that
He created the
Or encourage these tendencies in
He's just saying it as sort of an abstract people are like that
As opposed to like
My entire modus operandi my entire business model
He's encouraging this behavior in
People and then once it was
Directed it I realized this isn't good
But I didn't change my behaviors but I'm a 10.
Yeah he's he's
Not
Good
Person
Nope he doesn't have a very large vocabulary
I prefer a good Lionel
You know the number of words
That he uses weirdly
Yeah but you knows a lot of five-dollar words that he throws in
I were telling the story of people and white Vans showing up at Rio with guns
My reaction would not be
It was like
Whoa
Unless you're Black Rob
Best Buy
I think you're getting a sense here that Alex's sort of
I like
Lip service to the idea that he did things wrong
Is dodging responsibility
Leave stomach stat
More than that
You seems to be painting the pictures that he's the real victim
In the whole thing what
Of course he only became aware that his behavior
Maybe a mild psychosis because
He became victimized by them
Which is
Drawing attention away from the real victim
Oh his rhetoric and his behavior but this next clip I thought was a little bit beyond the
Happened
Question
Not
Push-up pops
Notion hooked
Fuller house
Houses
Crazy people now
Please stop
This is the money
To do
People weren't still
They were disgusting
The lingering damage of him stay
Consistently in the past
When it matter
That's what people were talking about
And no one was trying to bait him into staying these things they could take s*** out of context
The victim narrative for himself
About this Trump the the actual event
So pathetic
Over and over and over again
I apologize for it and it's over right
Can you can you stop doing me
You don't get to argue that like
Vietnamese were fake
And that gets you off the hook
Because you were reporting them and screaming about how they were real
That is the problem
I understand that you were tricked
Believe me you're preaching to the choir I think you're an idiot
You fall for things all the time
It is not excusing
To be included in his
Yeah yeah
I guess you could I got you know what really what I think he's trying to do is trying to build an argument that takes away in Thai
From his
Because I think a big part of defamation
Comes down to
You intentionally Moline
We both get this little
Is wedge in there of like
I was misled by bad information I came from
Your place
And you don't hate
What it what you going to do
Maybe maybe he's trying to get that legal standard.
Right
Him to do that when
You go back and you look at it that's not that does not accurately
Describe how you
That is not
Okay so actually Joe's an accessory to what I would describe as almost obstruction
Justice
If that's something that exists within a civil case I'm not sure if
Alex if he
He wishes he'd done something
Difference
That's not Alex doing that
But
Something different
Didn't take my shower was as powerful as it was
I'd like to remind everybody that
In 2000
3 years before the Sandy Hooks up Alex was screaming about how his show change the world
F*** you
I believe
Two days after
He's screaming about Jose had to help bring back gun culture and then went out to break scream in Warwick
Listen to the show to find out what
I interviewed a congressman
Big that doesn't match at all and I think it's a very
Pathetic angle to take
Meanwhile ice Scream 4
Years about how I'm the most influential show in the world
We are the leaders and Patriot Radio
Freedom talk
Is
Tonight's another thing
One thing it's super important to consider about Alex's protest that he didn't know how big his show was
Navigate no idea he was hurting people
Is affected in late January 2013
The father of a victim at Sandy Hook
Alex
An email
Letting you been being harassed by conspiracy theorist already at that point so he told Alex quote
Haven't we had our share of pain and suffering
I used to enjoy listening to your shows
Now I feel your type of show
Created these hateful people and they need to be reeled in
You saying that in the reference
To the fact that you used to love listening to
Galaxy was a fan of his show and tell
It ruined his life that is such an unfortunate irony
So he sent Alex an email within like a month or so months after
These consequences
Starting to show up in his life and we're really
Terrible
Reply
What is assistant
No doubt this was a real tragedy
Of course after that response until Alex continue to Peddle the idea.
He posted an article with the headline quote FBI's has no one died at Sandy Hook
Which was an intentional misrepresentation
The murder statistics
I think we had to do with
Like where they were
The murders were classified
Stuff like that
They are
We'll deal with it in more detail when it comes up
In our 2012 coverage in the email
It is a real tragedy parentheses
That the government stage and you are an actor
Different brackets
Is recently as 2015 he was telling collars that
It was all actors
Synthetic no one died there I thought that
Kids died there but after I looked at it I realized
Rizal actor
Those actions came after a parent of a murdered child reached out to him and made him very aware of the damage
All these excuses to the affective like
Full and complete
Wheatley deaf ears
One of the victims who was affected by his behavior
Had made it clear to her
That this is something that is
A problem
You didn't care
I think we have intent
Yeah no totally care at all
He was aware
All this is bulshit
And Joe is allowing him
Unquestioningly
To put this 4th
Bulshit
So
They appoint they start talking about how like
They had a little conversation
Pre-show
And that Alex
Okay
So
This is just kind of funny because it
Indicates how rude Alex
I don't know
Being processed
Because I've experienced
What other people have said
Don't believe it was okay
More excuses more nonsense
I have a lot of
Okay
You're probably even in the beginning of that clip expressed exactly what
Golden
You were letting me get my message out on your show we had callers matters
Before the show
About what I can help
You spread
Plies I can help you get out and leave
You f****** either
The only debate
It's relevant and I don't really have a position on is how much
Joe is aware of the fact that he's being again
Yeah
Unknowing participant
In allowing Alex to
Lie to everybody
More
I don't know that's a debatable open question
Who knows
Joe
O.j.
I think we got a pretty clear picture that
I was just trying to equivocate Dodge responsibility
In some ways
Flying
Even still
About the divided
All that stuff this is just
This is a disgrace people really got to learn how to apologize
That's when there's like a
That's a bad motor works for most people who don't know any better
You know what that
That's real big dump something differently
That takes a big man to say that it does not take a big man
It does not service of
Promoting a further life that would be so infuriating
Regardless of whether or not he's even telling the truth even if he was telling the truth
He is not saying
I am not making excuses for my behavior I'm giving you
Explaining
Response
Possibility for what I've done
I'm fully taking responsibility for what
Been done to the Sandy Hook
There's no ownership
Nope
F****** pathetic
Find out where things
Went wrong
The present troubles
Birth
Bertram
Yeah
Yeah that was part of it
I think that was definitely
Ratchet
Now what
Junior
Okay so nice out at Don Jr is talking
That's cool man
True anymore
Maybe don Jr gave him in
Information
Positive
The point
They're not in can
No that's what I'm referencing
That was switched
I don't like I don't like any of that
It's a long line of incredibly stupid people
Enough
Daisy chain game with Ella
Game of broken telephone
Complaining about the Chinese
At this point he's Google working
Together
That's not a good call
Joe Knows some people at Google
And it's spoken to them
And he's in a hot tub
Dumb f****** stories about running into globalists airports in Hot Springs
China Inn
That they are
And in a way that we would probably
Not be comfortable with
And actually Joe is even like I don't know if I think this is a good idea but here's the exit
Reason for why they're doing
I knew someone who worked at Google I know someone who used to work at Google I should say
Death thought process was
That Google is going to bring Google to China in the center form
They're going to copy Google
This is the real the real worry
Because China copies everything
Intellectual
True but if this is what they're saying
As a business and I'm not saying I agree with this cuz I don't
Get some apple juice new system
Cheetos
Third glass of Tito's
Completely unwilling to hear
From
Yo it's from experience
Here's why they're agreeing
To work with them
Michelle really about
Positions
I don't think that's necessarily a good idea but they're not in order to build a worldwide
My brother arrived
Who you pushing back a tiny bit
Alex is rhetoric but not nearly enough
In effect
Alex is not listening
No Alex when Joe is talking Alex is not listening
You didn't need
To say
I need to get another
But he has to interject here because
It's a whole life
You can say whatever you want but I
I'm drunk
My mind turns off
Because you are a dumb dumb gorilla
You're you're just some kind of thing
You're a thing I am one of the elite damn elevator
Something later is that really almost
About how great
Budget
Of course in the same way that if Alex is on
Chinese
We're going to take it
Also if I was there
They hate taking it on the chin for math
Especially imaginary of Haymaker
But if it Alex is on he's also going to talk about chimeras
I'm fine
Sophie gets into talkin about chimeras and of course
Because this is a show where
There's no time to do research
There's no time to
Respond
Just got behind the board who would like Google something
Alex has the
The presentation of a good argument
Pig human hybrids in in
If you go and just Google the basic information
Pride you're right lying about it but there isn't enough time on the show
To get the new W get the detail of it and so Alex's depositions are deemed to be like
Oh my God
That's
Which is the dangerous thing in one
I'm sure like that
A bike
This is really funny
Alex.
These your Camaros
And then Joe tries to get him
You talkin about
And Alex
His response
So funny
Body armor
Human animal hybrids 30 years ago
Just p***
It's a freaking deal
But you say he's all many dollars even with her real I believe they are
But you see so many different things
It's hard for each store
For years I mean that's just like the Kevin Spacey line from seven
For decades
Narcissistic
Comparison to a literal series
Important
The Joe is trying to explain to Alex
I'm still on a what the f*** were you talkin about
And that's not
Productive way to communicate
That sort of thing
Trying to talk about these things
He doesn't seem to realize that
Is part of Alex's manipulative techniques
That he can't stop on a
Because he needs to be on diori by the time you have heard or else you're going to look into
Be like you're just full of s***
Alex Clare
And also super important
Goats
Spiders making body armor
Baby baby that's so crazy this whole point is it like
He's trying
Little moment
And I don't think that it's
Just a product of his
Intoxication and flipping
He just knows it is a thing
It is a thing she thinks it's a spider
It'd be a fun spot whatever the case would be a massive spider that would also be able to
Like with like
I'm not into that so good later in the episode he talks about how like OSS
CIA was actually British intelligence
What kind of information
Do you have if you don't know these basic things
What do you know about f****** chimeras
If you think spider goats are spiders
Get the f*** out of
That's what I would do
Come on man
The f*** out of here
So I told Auntie by the way it's the office
That's right that's right
I told you earlier when they were talking about Sandy Hook I felt like they might have accidentally work themselves in
New lawsuit
And this clip here is what I was basing this
Conspiracy
About what's going on with him and Sandy
He really shouldn't
That
I'm sorry
I'm a wolf at the door
Family stop running around everywhere
Because the world
I like that a lot like those are the moments that Alex is funny but he's not true
F*** off.
He's just want them to stop saying
I'm really hurting
Also is he trying to say that the media is running a false flag on him
Like they're reported
You get it correctly the media
Is actually the ones
Who are trying to harass the Sandy Hook families
Because they know most pairs
That if they were to say Alex Jones says
Because the
Because people hate the meteor so much
They're going to trust Alex Moore
And then
The media knows this is what's going to happen already off
Then investigate the Sandy Hook I think you're off a little bit
Right right
That they say that Alex says the same
Is fake
And the people hate the media
Therefore they think that that is misreporting
And trying to cover up something
If they're saying that it's wrong for someone
Then it must be
We're going to go to Connecticut
Right in the media is aware that this is what they
I think he's also implying
Yeah, I don't know yet I think that is
Represent
Yeah absolutely
The idea that the media is trying to do this in order to
Precipitate
A large terrorist attack
Connecticut to blame on Alex
This is the definition of
Paranoid narcissism
Just believing everything is about you
It's so it's so sad to see it
Cuz the one thing that he
Could not
Possibly wrap his head around
Is that
The media actually doesn't care about him
Only reporting on things based on what he has done
Right right right
He's gotten so far
Like distinguished
Between what his Straw Men are and what the reality is
My criticisms that are being
Lobbied against him
I don't know if he's able to tell it like
What's real and what's not like what's his Spin and what people are actually saying
And it's interesting
Rosetta
Exist on the same episode where he's saying that like
Years ago I realized that there is a
Mild psychosis were taking everything is fake
Exactly
How you operate
The ability to have an awareness about that and pin it on your past self
Implies
Some awareness that you're still the hold into those pattern
Do you think this is
A situation where were
We're getting Alex
Like without his
Infowars had on
He doesn't he's not wear the hat
I mean I mean like this is more genuine
No
Yeah you still doing a show
Like
And how he's just rambling
Keeps
Feels like I'll go ahead go ahead
Like I said he thinks Joe Alex Jones
Performance right
It's just conversation
And it's not an interview it's just Alex
Rambling about spider goats
How everyone's blaming him for Sandy Hook and I think he's out of Lanza and he's a victim in blah blah blah
Like Jojo
It's not a 28
A good basis for friendship
It's not
Really abusive behavior that has participated
Yeah because I
In the same ways that I want an explanation
A lot of things and Alex's career and a life
He's a lunatic
I think the Joe probably explanation
Why his friend
I think he hopes for an answer other than
Oh he's just a crazy person
Money
So
He's not yelling on a street corner
Because his behavior is very
Very close
To someone who gets locked in a looney bin
Or whatever
You no different than someone in other circumstance
P-51
Orbi home
Yeah like that
Did the last post
And as to which one is with that's the level of impairment Alex is operate
Eating under
These days especially
And I think that Joe wants
Donation for why
Unfortunately
You listen to this episode
If you see
There's nothing I don't think there's anything there
Yeah
I think it's a little bit like
Joe is
Portraying himself as the the person who wants to believe the best in everybody
Yeah it's like
Look I know I ate all of this horror all of this Terror right there
But you're still a human being
And I believe there's good inside you
Like that kind of s*** when in reality
What he does say a bunch of times I am cut out these clips
Because I don't care
But he does say a number X
Another reason the same thing you said on the last
Alex Guarnaschelli
I wanted to show the world the version of you that I love
Right
And it's like I think that's
The version of you that I love is the guy who yells at me for 5 hours
And there's so much on here that just goes
That Joe just left slide
That I've already talked about all these Sandy Hook lies
Joseph letting Alex tell
He lets him without pushback
Give this idea of it
They're trying to plan too large
Terrorist attack in Connecticut and blame it on him
Jordan be like hey that's crazy
Or anything
The Joe seems to want
Is a lion bigger who's clearly mentally Disturbed
And then we laugh at
Which I'm not I'm not thrilled with that
Whatever
Life is what it is
Yeah
Is that Alex
Heroes of the globalist
Well we all do
And he knows that beak
Because of
Primary
Resources
He's talked to the
Leadership
Spiders should be doing
In this next clip Alex brings up a primary source
Completely lies about
Cuz Joe doesn't know what this source
He doesn't push back on
Earth is seeing if I can
To give the propulsion power for this new thing was going to be born
Artificial intelligence
Controlled
Programmers
Google
With the
The Break-Up
I'm so baffled
He's baffled because
Alex
Literally none of that is in Bill Joyce article
You can find it we have a link up to it on our website
Yeah I wrote a big essay about the Bill Joy why the future doesn't need us
You can go read it yourself doesn't say any of that f******
The only thing that's close to that
And Bill Joyce article is when Bill Joy is
Kaczynski
Right among the elite
Or anything like that
He was talking about someone who had a fear of a terrifying future with technology
This is.
Albertsons
Completely lying about the primary source
And because Joe
I mean
Appreciate his instinctive like
Slowdown Frac pump
Read that article
In the time that they have on here
It's just it's just pathetic
But this is all lies
That plan
Either
That the globalist have
Interesting to me
Because either
It needs to have taken more than one conference to come up with that entire plan
The same time
Could have only taken one conference to come up with that
Like they just kept drinking over.
We mailed it
This playing
We're going to follow it to a T
I don't think they were talking about 5G
I think they were I think they knew it
I don't think that's
30 years is how many years ago
20 years ago on years ago
Flip phone
20 years ago they were talking about 1 G
Right
Yeah I guess it's a hypothetical eventual thing
We won't make it
6G though
5G will have already scrambles rdna Dan
Doing the jack off lotion
We would have to have a
We have a locker room environment here at the show I got my daddy's made it already
Eric Sierra
It is next clip they're having a little conversation about Alex's was another one of his talking
Points is like back in the
Please plan that they were discussing
Trying to
Baum's Atmos
Nuke the atmosphere
From like a documentary
Ladies watch
Like that and this makes Alex
Adopt
Can you sit there
I don't have an anytime
I don't have time to go into it as much as you did
That's it right there
I don't know all about that
Nearest you
Are you in your family
It's okay
This is true
So Alex text me when I say
The government has made.
Talkingshit
It's not like
Oh no he's onto our secret
It's it's fun
Joe did not realize that Alex
Was absolutely insulting him
Yeah he's like
Everything you you already do everything I mean a lot of people say you're stupid all the time
I don't know who saying he's stupid all the
Meathead or whatever something
The bigger insult that Alex is making is that you are a coward
You know all the things that I know and because you want your family to be safe
I can't look into it because it doesn't exist
Like how you want me to look into extra
Dimensional aliens make
Contract
With the government go there
Joe's on DMT
Which is what Alex is going to conduit through which the government
Alright appearance
Baboon to his own
Which obviously it is
Just some of this weirdo friends who also should be on chosen God no
Owner of The Joe Rogan embarrassing
Alex
Is it chemicals in the food water
Jim
I don't know how to spell it
It's muscle memory
It's a way of saying I don't know how to spell it.
Reset it
It doesn't work in the inverse
It does to some extent if like what you're saying is
If I write the word I can tell if it looks wrong that's
If that's what he's trying to express 5 but I can only write it a weird way
Nodaway to say also Nick begich if you're curious and don't remember from our show he's the guy who has he faked
Grief from a Sri Lankan
Angels Don't Play this heart
About
The real
Real cool dude
He's also a favorite amongst
The project
So
He's real cool
In this next clip there's another instance
Sense of Alex bring up something that is ostensibly dependable
Google search
I really wish you had written like a like Harry Potter
David like
A whole series of just like
Angels Don't Dance
Numbers of how they're finding you just
As like
You switch it around it's like
This Outfield
Be nice I don't think he has
I think you made enough mileage
Weirdo
Speaking circuit for the rest of his life doesn't have to write another book
Does JK Rowling something if you're a weirdo and you write a book and its influence
Thank you could all that strength by writing another book has information if it can be attacked like that
Who wrote the
I'm a man gorilla whatever was that serve serve
Gorilla mindset wrote another book and everybody's like yours
Fair enough
Control you
Cell phone towers arm at 2
Mind control people
Things if you just do a cursory Google search you can find articles in like scientific
American Inn
And stuff like that
They don't prove Alex's
Discuss to be like
Similar technology
You know you
Useful in different ways and stuff like that
Can bring this up Jamie Google
And then
It's another sleight-of-hand trick that Alex is able to do
I don't want to talk about it
Is begone Intuit Nora show
In the past
That's because
Ectopic
Because
Leads us to where we going
Where we going
So this is a device
By the Gods
That
Has developed
What do you mean who do you think made up
We will
Research
Major General General General
CIA everybody
Before and after
Which obvious reason
Bass
Communicating
Are these intergalactic
2 deals binding
What's the over by the body
This is bulshit
This is Project Camelot
I might be might be also I think museums in Los Angeles
Real f****** close
Like
In terms of
Just going to Los
Breakaway civilization with NASA
Who get the budget of fifty bucks a year
That's all the shadow budget
That includes a lots of money
Like that
It's like it's like Brittany
There's a shadow Parliament
Are the aliens
Fair enough
Major General General General General
Ayahuasca
Conferences
God this is so disappointing
This is your big news
You can't prove any of this
You're just talkingshit and it doesn't
No and it's fun to talk about when your
You're high
And I think that's why Rogan is kind of like not
Probably let him talk
Alex
You are someone
Who tries to make
Real world political
Statements
You are somebody who supports
I don't know
Bolsonaro
In Brazil you're someone who now even though for
Years and years has been
Like
Principal
Opposed to regime-change
You are now supporting what's going on in Venezuela
You cannot
Save the big deal
When you're hunting show that I was listening to this live
There was like 120 thousand people watching it live
Jesus Christ behind
Is
Major General generals during Ayahuasca and make a contract with alien
You're a f******
A******
You're a joke
This is this is pathetic I don't like that I feel like he was f****** with
That's a little bit with the
General
General General
Hughes is vamping I think a little bit
Transfer who he's talking to
Bring up the
Real 40.2 later he says
B double bind was
3-star General
Point Break
Never done DMT
Elizabeth
That's very dumb
Yep. Dmc4 obviously
I don't know
I don't know why they would mess
If you don't do it for obvious reasons
The only thing I can think of it's an obvious reason
Is it illegal
Well
Yeah but there's ways you can still do it like you know
Stuff like that there are loopholes and stuff
You could do it
Without the Legos of I think it's just anything
Drugs are bad
Or something like that
The only obvious reason
Or he thinks it's intrinsically evil to do those drugs
Interdimensional beings
Because he's not afraid of anything
But I don't know
The point is
He's never done for obvious reasons
But
Basically.
What does Michael alien an alien landed right now in our parking lot in a little gray
Big black ice
On psychedelic trip
I just don't think he's ready for it
Oxygen
Brains
Sleep apnea
Oxygen
First Memories Forever
I want to see child
Are going to shot I've seen ever
Everything
God dammit
I I have
Mild hallucinations every night so
Know that aliens are real It's seems unlikely to that he's had this his whole life
You know like if what he's
Describing is like his super out of shape missing
Massive neck
Causes
Sleep apnea
But that's more of a recent development
His wife
It does seem that what like
I don't know
I don't care to litigate that
Really I just bring that up as like
Alex trying to sort of big dick
Prior Lake
You've done DMT and Ayahuasca a couple times
I do it every night buddy I know more I've seen everything
This is
I got bad news for you I'm above your turf
What a dick
What a f****** dick
You pretty pretty bad
You think that's cool
Guess what
F***
It's 91 of the story it's one of the license
Is everything
Yeah
Gross
Right
In the episode
Beginning to the first instance of Alex talking about childhood memory
There are a number of them that some of them are pretty close to
We've heard before
And those things
Are flushed out a little bit more cuz he's wasted
I meant some of them are completely new development
That leads me to one of my new conclusion
Did Alex Jones Is Dead David Jones
Might be a complete lunatic
Right though
Touchdown him in the Sun
But like you know he he was clearly into the John Birch Society
And he had some weird influences the past down to Alex
But some of these stories that
Hotels
AR
It's hard to say with the line is
Between like Alex's dad possibly crazy
Or
Alex
Wheatley Miss remembers things from his youth
And is allowing his dad to
Baby cats
As a lunatic
Backstory remove the probably from technically probably
Bleach kill a guy
Maybe we'll get that that'll be at the end of this episode
So
It is first one Alex was 7 years old
And he heard his dad talking about his
Free practice
But Molly was more there than meets
The 200 boy
Dishonor
Okay why
Probably
20 years ago
Before anybody else is talking about The Clockwork elves
Precise
Not the CIA
Walmart
I don't know what that means
Never been part of any other stuff
DARPA research projects
That I don't know all the details about
Because they want
Program in Maryland and underground basin
I want you out of this
Bored
Okay
So a couple things I find really important in there one is that he calls his parents by their first name
As opposed to like highlighting hair relation
To each other
Which is weird
I meant
Like I don't understand why his dad
Movie like I can't talk about this National Security project
But that's what you're not supposed to talk about
About this
That's how Alex talks
That's how Alex reveals information
The prefaces things like I am I can't get into these I'm not supposed to talk about this
Give this more as an expression
Alex Jones
From his childhood
Then
Actually actually a memory
Of his dad explaining
What was going on with these two cyborgs
Either that or DDS David was
I think that if if Alexandra
Whole time
Is brought a horrible
But I think I did
I think that even if he wasn't f****** with him there's
Clear indications that he's allowed Alex to
I believe these things
Without correct
Or maybe he just doesn't give a s*** you know it wasn't working on f****** cyborg
When you were a kid that's ridiculous
And Alex is like
I just hear you
Confessing quite frankly
But you made two cyborgs CIA has a rule about
Well
Let go for it but I mean like going under in in that kind of thing like getting any kind of laugh
I'm positive that there's some sort of like
NDA
Yeah it sucks because of
If you're unconscious or I'm in Twilight or whatever something
That you
Shouldn't exactly that sort of thing
But with DDS David which is the new way that I'm going to say it
Hey man
I could definitely see a situation where
If you had to go under anesthesia or something like that for 3 minutes
They would only allow a dentist
Or Doctor Who had been vetted
Manhattan mdan
In-Place yapping like that or I could see it being a thing where you can own
Only get local anesthetic
Or topical anesthetic Novocaine
Best of YouTube
Revealing comforter is too high
Or
Impossibility
Wow that's a fourth possibility
Discount Tire
Syrupy like you can go in but you're always being monitor
Like someone is there
In order to make sure you don't say
I like to imagine that at Tache has a
So I don't know whatever is cases I don't believe Alex
His story is
Your old memories
Wingstop
Is not on the up-and-up
Or at least
What does version of hip
Because Alex showed him endgame
When he was making it
His dad endgame response
This is all bulshit
Is that
Quite different
My dad never told me about all this stuff
Boulder chill
20 year old daughter she's like 14 hour
They should have like an hour to watch
That's not true
It's all true
I was in junior high school recruiting of the program there
Everybody
Government
Special
Smartest in Texas
This is stuff we talked about before David globalist work
But
I didn't harm enough people
Villain before these kids the plan or not
Reject the offer
Or whatever
It's a completely ludicrous childish idea
Of how some sort of operation would work
He's talking about Ender's Game
Yeah that's what it is
Yeah probably
I trust you
But this is a child's understanding or something and child hero-worship their dad
I don't even believe
Leave the
Statewide test
Exists to decide who the smartest kid in Texas
I found this out
Get that out but I mean
You need some DMT and figured it out
Blood
Bring it up
He doesn't have much SB Raptors
Are you angling for Carrie
Absolutely
So
Alex brings up
Abortion
And
Cowboy
They have a little conversation about how there are
People who are trying
Babies alive
Just Elder Oregon
Post-birth
Right Center in Virginia
Was talking about when
In Black
Nope
But we do find out why that happened
Racist black Facebook
Now what about that
I really think it was right might have initially been but the reason story came forward is because
Will get to work
But
Blackface
Actually what we call it now
We'll get to that in a second
But in this next
Alex talks about how abortion is
Just about stealing babies
Is Oregon
I have some thoughts
I'm confused
Well I didn't see that I am very
Very concerned with late-term abortion
Poster how much money
Wait a minute lyrics
Oregon
The fifty grand for a fetus
But your 500,000
His whole argument about chimera
Is there trying to
Create organ harvesting
Type things
Chimera
Kind of defeats the purpose of chimeras
These are kind of the same thing
I don't understand why you need both
Rates are going down of course
Wow you got to eat for not having enough kids
I know I know Jim Cramer for mad money is big massive is always Diversified portfolio
That's true I guess my complaint
They control a lot more oil so we're trying to find our own sources
Energy
Women control all the babies
We can't be having that we got to make sure that their stuff was that.
So creating spider
It makes perfect sense
Make sense entire argument hinges
Around the idea that the governor of Virginia was on a radio show was asked about
A measure that
Was being
Scuffed
That would
Put No Limit really on when abortion
Could be
Done
I don't like between the between the appropriate care of a physician
And a woman
There should not be
Appropriate
Of course you know you need to have doctors
You know what they're doing interacting
Responsibly
Unfortunately
But
I don't like
40 something year old men talking about abortion
. no like I don't like it
I kind of don't even don't even like when we talked about it other than to be like
Hey
Go for it if you want it
Because Alex and Jo at 4 start it would be
Consider is that Ralph Northam
Get on this radio show
Something
The effect of actor
Keep the
The baby
Comfortable
And resuscitated if that's what the
He wasn't precise enough in his language and he was speaking really poorly but what he was talking about he's a non-viable
Stillborn
Bye
Being by labor a non-viable child or child with a birth defect like
Examples
You can find all over the place like a child
The brain
Or something like that
Abortion
Not talking
About euthanasia already
Like that talk about a very very rare situation
Where in
Looking up baby is
Born
Completely on
Yeah
If the parent does water resuscitated and try
Keep it alive yeah then why would they not do that right in the meantime keeping the baby comfort
Super Bowl 2
The greatest extent you can
Isn't
Necessarily some sort of a weird nefarious
They're making
Are complete
Movie bad argument out of
Intentionally misunderstanding with the guys
And I got no skin in the game
How could you not have empathy
24vac
Situation where
It's a baby is alive
You know you don't most rather it was stillborn
Because the babies alive and they're trying
To keep it alive for something slowly die
Ladies come out
And she got
Did not have a late-term abortion
Because it was very difficult for her
To get one in the
Yeah
And she had this child
I am
She
Did she had got a later
Proportion
Because the child ended up
So many
Medical complications
Spend so much money trying
Keep it alive it still died anyway
Of being born
And there wasn't
Like
It's still in utero that that was going to
To be the case yeah
But you couldn't travel across state line
Get the abortion pill
Brutal and that's exactly the sort of situation
This governor was talking
To feed Hugh
Anti-abortion
And a position
How come you're out
Take position
I want to watch a parent
B torture
And then have them watched
Cuz he doesn't care
Talk about in the crassest
Possible
It's because everybody on the right
Really understand
Maintaining this abortion
Is essential to them ever winning an election
Go vote
A big part of how they hinge the evangelicals without that block block this Within
The right-wing
Coalition
Exactly
The single-issue floaters
In terms of abortion
The right-wing in the GOP alive right and so you have to
If you give even an inch
It's going to be whittled away
Yeah guns and abortion
Go to the biggest
Little Owl
The GOP
Conservative
Built their f****** party into giving all of their money away
Yo G
That don't fit with like let's say the evangelicals
God I hate everything
So anyway
Alex is wrong about this makes a meal out of talking about it
That's gross
And then he plays the video
He has been played as boj me.
And yeah
Do you know Governor Northam does day
You keep the baby comfortable
And he does have a bit of a Southern accent so Alex
To be like that didn't I do a good impression
Because they have that like that
That
And they don't have
Explanatory context or anything like that there's no time for that on the show
I told you the governor said Vicky babies alive
Therefore my conjecture that they
Keep them alive
For two weeks the Harvester Oregon
He's also true
And Joe doesn't have a foot to stand on because
Got his mind blown by this clip of Governor Northam
Really goddamn that's how this works what happened literally
All I can think of while if you're if you're putting clip
My next thought is like
Tell me how this makes sense
Because this is this is
Because you're sitting next to duplicitous
I know
So Alex needs a little bit more support for his argument other than this
Completely misrepresented
Clip of the governor
Okay
What kind of would it be like a is it like a stealth cleaning van
Thought
Check project
Manipulative
Edited videos about
Planned Parenthood
This is the Center for Medical progress videos that came out in 2015
Completely
The dirt like manipulative Lee additive that got these guys in a bit of hot water about Italy
Videotaping
These people without consent
A misrepresenting what
Full tapes
Show right
So I was just bored
Happens
So
When you actually do that
You get into legal trouble
Droop and ilex
So
Yeah we'll get back to this topic of Alex's
About abortion a little bit later because he has a bit of a blow up
And start screaming in a probably fake way but also see
Kind of real
Terrifyingly angry where 14
You're a revelation
Mercedes
Incredible
But
There's so many levels
Like just like
Just
Like if you take even the having sex with
With this
Older woman
At the top of the equation
Being in the household
Experiencing something like that
Look at that he's just friends with this girl and he's over in the dads like
I f***** my daughter go to join our satanic cult
That would be deeply traumatizing
Incorporated
You think the sex with her was awesome
V
Oh yeah at least
It's
You are not capable of processing
Sexual inter
Intercourse and the intimacy that comes along with it when your 13
A seventeen-year-old girl
Having sex with a 13 year old boy is abuse
Is profoundly f***** up I don't care if Alex looks like he was 16 at the time
Or anything like that that is not good
Very thetis
Very bad now when I was 15 I was dating
Somebody older than me she was 17 she was a senior at the
And it was very much like
Sleep together
Because that was a whole mess
You know like it that was one of those things were both of us were like
Warren High School list
Just be
Cool
I think that's good
I also want to say I'm sorry I didn't mean to
Cut you off
Expressing I don't think
He tried to get it
Get inducted into a satanic cult
I think that's probably just his weird fantasizing
Memory
That's probably a function of him being
Really f***** up
But can you imagine going anywhere
And having somebody's father who you're
Fishing with say I sleep with her too that doesn't end in like
Best Joker
No
Okay cool I'm going to run as far as I do
So I don't care
Alexander like the idea to satanic cult
Tried to get him involved in
Part of the
He said that he was a hardcore Satanist on a past episode
With it
Cuz this isn't trying to get recruited into a satanic group
Now a little bit later he says
In order to get into
Groups you have to kill your dog
What
Yeah
Yeah you don't say that
It's implied
He's presenting it as like I would never do that I never did that
If not necessarily his dog maybe was just a dog with rabies
He said he had to stop at the
Lakeview little
The little parts
You killed dog in order to get into a satanic cult that is a possible
Believe most
Cruelty
Is one of those Signature Signs of Assyria
Real killer
I believe you was cruel to animals but I don't believe
The window dressing over
The story
The satanic cult that Dad was f******
King's Daughter
Alex
I believe maybe he had inappropriate sexual relations
As a younger man
Trauma involved in that and not processing it in any real way
No
Here is something that Alex says
That
Is really one of the reasons why Joe should think twice about having him on his show
And also if you're going to let him be on the show
Push back on things like
Because joke.
This is so f***** up
Works there
And they're tough and
Cool
And just a little bit
Cuz they're powerful
Why is that
Chinese
Like that
Mongols Seattle Marvel
I'll give you think about Japan Japan has a long history of being a noble Warrior culture with a samurai
All the martial arts of compliment
Oh boy
I said presented without comment because I refuse to even engage
Alex
Deeply fuk up
Crazy crazy things
This is something
Want to ask because I do feel like it's in Port
Joe is coming off like the shittiest piece of s***
That
Could be
In your clips
Confirm that this is the tenor of the interview
And not like
Cuz you clips about Alec
Yeah have his highlight-reel
A little bit further
Variable
The changes every
But I will say this
I don't want to say look he's a thing
Fully understood that Alex was lying to him about the even
First 20 minutes or so of like
F***** up
Does Alex comes in with a head of steam
And he's just ranting while Joe tries to respond
Slowing down
Going to be whatever I want it
Right-leaning Intuit
Instead of being like Alex what are you saying Native Americans are easy to mine
Control
Prove your promise
Or anything like that he's just like
Well do you think there's a cultural explanation for why
Asian militaries like military turd
Vision goes the way that it does in China
Because I think he's a little bit realizes
He's playing handball with the curtains
Play an actual game or have a real time
Alex is going to get the points you want across
Emily soon is Joe response not like Alex will take
Conversation
In a new direction that he can
In control
Do a certain extent it is still a show
So he can either have a
Or he can have a fight and then it's over after an hour
Is Merrick
I think what's going on to is
Is that like
Yeah it's just sort of like a Don't Rock the Boat
Kind of thing
8 a recognition of like
What would we going to do
What's
What's the what's the game that
Going to play but
Question more specifically
You're saying but Joe's coming off like a pilot
I think there's an argument you could make that that's a fair assessment
But I also think there's an argument
Could make of him being a showman in the situation
Moderate
Whatever is
Being sad is bestie
You can and then just doing a terrible job
I don't think it's
Penchant
But I also think he doesn't recognize
Yeah I think he gets caught up in trying to make sense of Alex's
Words
Rhetoric
And he misses
He misses point a
Because Alex is already on
Right right right
It's one of the intrinsic problems why you should never have Alex on your show
He's going to say things
You're just incapable of
Responding to
And then it's broadcast
Unchallenged unquestioned
On your show right
And more people after-the-fact record of like either
You don't challenge him and he says a ton of b*******
And you gave him a platform
Challenge him
And he gets in a fight with you and then he gets
Even more publicity gets really weird like that Patrick bet-david
Yeah that's it
It's like a
The only way to win
Like that's the situation there's more game
I agree
So you talk about these genetic
Mind control ability
Levels of various races
Isn't good
The type of racism that you're like this is bad racism but also
I mean nobody else is throwing that racism around I think so people are I think there are
Pacific point
Pretty specific
Offshoot of a lot of
This sort of race realism the
Racism
Yeah those those sort
I think there is some of that
Which is naturally transitions into
I talked about him
About how like
The Japanese and the white so this must be televised
I don't care about that we don't need to listen to that but it leads
Is preposterous
For sure yeah
Is this
There's test that you can run terms of math
Psychic
My skill is a swamp music
That's not why they
That's how I
I don't think anyone would give a s***
The song morph acknowledge and all of that
That's so stupid
Complains about
People making accusations
Oceans about him
The real world
Deeply ironic
Stephen Colbert
Well that's unfortunate
And then people yelled at you
Houston died our actors as it got harassed and got death threats
I don't give a fuk
If someone yelled at you could someone made a joke about you
In a late night show
I mean sure
I don't like any kind of harassment falling on people I think that's
I would support that
I'm sure that Stephen Colbert didn't say that Alex
The clan member
I'm sure there was a joke that he was making that compared to the two or something like that
Welcome back to you
Listen
The guys that Alex was a clan member but
I take no pleasure in reporting this to you Alex Jones at the clan member
Interview with Bradley Cooper
Knock knock
What Alex did to the Sandy Hook
Any kind of
It's a hymn to be like I'm a victim of this negative attention
Does people melt Molina me
Take a pick a number ass-whole
Way more guilty of that than anybody else so I'm going to revoke that victim card from
Go fuc yourself
Alex talks about how he knows a guy
In the UFC
Who you want
He will not die
He's about to name that guy
He's not
But then things turned bad because
Because the network
That is strange
Demand
Okay
Monster
This is incredible
Set alarm for this new big lucrative shall what they said
You're going to come out to downtown Alex Jones on the show
On the show
Well they need that from you
Yeah but why would they need that from him
But that gives you even more tension
They're Duluth
Ponderosa
Going to give you a few specifically denounced Alex Jones
The cooking show
Okay
I believe you
I believe you but I'm saying it just seemed so crazy
To denounce you on the television show I'm not saying it's impossible
That's what everybody
You're a rarity
This is the moment where Joe is like hey dude I am actually in
Show Business
Done all of that I've been given not how it goes
And how everybody has to denounce your else
It is the mark of the beast is saying that Alex Jones
Close to where JoJo lives USB related
8 he's trying to
Appeal to Jodi like they're people you entering
Could be you next
At the end of the few
No he's pandering
The only people whose Independence and does their own thing
Reneging on all of the things that he said about Joan the last month or so
You said that you
Complete shell all this stuff
Easy protective recognizing exactly
What's going on
In both that story and not recognizing the same thing is going on on his show
Wait
If that guidance is that only give you more attention
And you liked it
Are you get it understand
That he's giving Alex more attention but I think he thinks
More harmless than he is because he doesn't recognize those things that Alex says that are
Completely not based in reality that our soup
Super dangerous
And racist
Native American
To mind control
He doesn't recognize that it being is toxic
Cancerous
Whatever
He's obsessed with being the guy who I'll talk to whoever looking at Tyson on the other day like not the other day but little bit
Is really gone up Stars
Joe's obsessed with that
Don't care right-wing left-wing it's important
Interesting
First Alex came for the Native Americans
Then he went for the Asians
And I said nothing
But he came at me about UFC
And I'm going to shut
Right I'm going to push back pretty hard
Like the two of them had a bit of a fight
I think it's an open question how much
Of that was up.
On Alex's part
The intensity with which he
You followed through with it
And like I said the level
Streets
And stuff like that betrayed
Confidences
If that's what Alex was intended
If he was trying to bait him into a war
Or something like that
That makes sense
But the end result of that wouldn't be to get on his show
You know some sort of
Yeah but
Whatever the case is Alex
Explain for this next cliff
What he felt the breaking point
With Joe was
When he realized this guy
Too far gone
I got to take him on
Where
When I saw you was Breaking Point
Do shelters full of crap George Soros
Was a victim of the Nazis and Holocaust
I go the story that I watch the interview
And I don't know what he did I don't know I don't know him
I don't know I've no very little about him
Remember from the story was that he was saying
The one the Nazis occupied
He was with his I believe it was his uncle
Is Godfather and took him around as a Christian and pretended he was a Christian where they were stealing from these Jews
Hollywood
Take the end
He just thought it was normal because you was 13 years old but was talking about it
It did he was shielded by the
Disperse
What
Well then it's over I would be willing
Wow I mean to be fair he does go on to say
Eddie doesn't
But it is more reasonable
I'm irrational because he's talking like I watch that interview
You can't pull the like
Sleight of hand
That you normally do I know what you're talkin
And about your version of it isn't true
Start with that qualification
I don't believe that interpretation
He says
It's worse for Alex after he explains why he doesn't take that into a
Joe Rogan
Goodies to eat to settle that was just taking proper
Now they work
This is b******* already been taken away
The Godfather was part of cleanup
Cruise that would go around to the houses of people who
It's not Alex and presenting it as
They showed up. And then yeah
Supposed to
Catalog the property
Nazis were going
Yeah this is b*******
If Alex knew anything
If you would know that
He's trying to presented as
They were the
I don't know what the Silver Surfer that came around us via The Herald
Of the Nazis
Rare is coming to me
Circus World
I don't know
I mean
It was more
George Soros
Cuz I don't know much about it
Feed the real Absolute Auto on Shepherd
No it's f****** not
It's open to interpretation you have Justin validated your entire arm
If you are just saying that this is how I look at it
Then you are
You can't make the claims that
But you do
Especially when you presented as fact
A million times
Nazi collaborator it's not
From his words
I get the sense that he was a Nazi collaborator
Collaborator
He's reporting it
The fact that he's on Rogan show
And Rogan
Smallest amount of pushback on this guy
That's not what I said no so that interview doesn't say what you're saying
It's a matter of interpretation
Because he knows that he
He pushes harder
Or like if Joe pushes harder or is Alex's
No absolutely
How do you know that and it's like no answer
Well that's why our that's why our interview cuz Joe hadn't watched
That was such a
Move on Alex's part of just like
I lie about all the time
There's another interview
It does contain all of the information then even I don't even know that I always
What I want to make this point
It's moving the goalposts entirely
When you realize that you're f****** argument doesn't staying everytime
Every f****** time
And because he's able to
Because Joanne
NPR interview
And because
Have the f****** time
Do this stuff looking into this.
He ends up having to
Stipulate Alex's conjecture
Or whatever he has to at least allow it to be like I don't know
Right
Say I don't know and then Alex
He has to see the point to him to some extent
And Alex
Interpretation
That's enough
Thing for Alex
Text effect
Because he would never say that on his own show
Going to be like it's open to interpretation
That's pathetic
More about Soros and
A claim about him
That he's never made
Before
And is
Cockamamie bulshit he's actually a dog
George Soros
George
Tried to crash the pound
The pound
So the pound stuff is fine we'll talk about that a little bit
The stone
Governments all the time
Which is just
Him trying to
Help democratizing forces in
Soviet Bloc countries
Roots Cafe
Add Nas
But he's never I've never I'm not going to say he's never said it
Because I don't know but I've never heard him say the George Soros
Rams the breakup of the Soviet Union
And I'm here to say that if he did he should be Alex's
Hero
Alex hates the buckets
They are guys of the antique
Communist propaganda
Hero worship
Rose quarterback
In Alex's World shoot
It's crazy
What a f******
That's a great question
That is not
Who's like
That Reagan speech by Tear Down the Walls
Talking about
It's nonsense
Diculous so like I said
We're going to get to this this question
About breaking
I think we talked about it a little bit
Before but there's a little bit of clarification
Location that might be useful
And this is really funny
Because this is one of the only
I think it might be the only incident
Where Jamie look something up
Did Alex is talking about
Rogan reads it on air
Wow he's doing it to just read
Get a derailleur
Against
George Soros
If highest level ditch day
He is the manager or was the manager are you shooting again
But how do you know if you remember research
Marshall Dyer
Did George Soros break the bank of England little bigger please
In Britain black Wednesday September 16th
Break it
But they force the British government from the European exchange rate mechanism joining the ERM card
Grown-up please
Although stood apart from the European currencies the British pound blah blah blah compounding the underlying problems inherent in the pounds include
I'm not seeing this where's the park with George Soros Douglas
I'm just trying to find it
Interest rates to teens
Shorting the currency
British government gave in with Drew traderma
Although was a Biddle
Bitter pill to swallow the pound came back stronger because the excess interest in high inflation
Searles pocketed
Dollars on the deal
And cemented his reputation as the premier currency Speculator in the world
If your currency speculators know what you do though I don't know what
George Soros
So you just moves on today
But that are important
She was didn't crash the pound
At all
You profited off it
Because he was shorting the pound
And the reason he was shorting the pound is because of that
European exchange rate
Mechanism when the pound got into a deer resistant
Get intuitive
Begin with but when they did
Huge mistake in terms of tying it to
The German mark
BRB amount
The exchange rate
Nailed it
Was something that was unsustainable
Yeah and it had to stay within a certain range above or below
That exchange rate
And because of the inflation rate
And the interest rates in the United Kingdom at the time
It was just impossible for them
Keep that up
He wasn't the only one
Just the one that made the biggest Bet On It were able to recognize the signs
The place for anyone to see
That they were about to
To have to default on
That was going to cause the p
To go down
And if you were able to
See what was coming
Did You Bet On It
You would make a lot of money
Doris looked was like that's a bad idea and then bet a s*** ton of money that it was a bad idea
He had some concerns about if it will made him end up making
The big bet that ended up winning him a billion dollars
In all of this
Billion dollars off
Regulate speculations that articles to come back much
Stronger because of the
The crashed it was terrible
In the immediate but it was
Better in the long run
But the issue is
Was acting on
A report that
If you get heard up from
The head of the German Central Bank
You'd given an interview
And he was talking about how some
Even if
Some
Currencies would have to be
Devalued
Essentially because of
What was going on
The prevailing
Standard of the
Strawberry
And so the idea
The president of
German Central Bank was coming out of those things
Throws is like
If we're going to move we gotta move to
Today we're going to bed
Life
So much more signs here
So he
And his his boys
Made a massive bat
Paid off you
Yeah that's what it is
Break the bank
The back did it to themselves
He had nothing to do with getting into
Erm
He had nothing
Things to do with the rate that they ended up nailing the
The pound to as it relates to
There's nothing
Thing that he's responsible for in this other than
Yeah capitalist speculation
The perfect job
There's a lot more little detail
But he's just blaming Soros
4 thing
They
He has enough
Explain it in the morgue
Detailed and complicated way but it does seem like the basic story is
The British government did a bad thing
Stupid yeah yeah
Entirely stupid
The time it's
Maybe foolish and short-sighted
But it was in response to financial troubles that
Pound was in
When they decided it wasn't
The decision that was taken lightly
State resisted getting involved
For a long time
Right
I'm being in the ER and the exchange
What's something that would help stabilize the economy
So they chose to do that
We're foolish
In terms of the rate
Songs like
Got it
Bet all the money
Are they made a billion dollars
Pretty
In retrospect
I imagined Soros
Absolutely on the Vanguard
So many other people were like
This is a great idea and we're going to work it out
Because the ways East
Speculatory
You're borrowing a ton of money
To make the bat right
You know and if if
You're wrong in the pound goes up
You have just now borrowed a ton of money and lost everything
You have to pay that money back
Relatively speaking of
Is probably a good probably wasn't
It probably wasn't that scary
Because
It's one of those things where even if the pound does go up
It is definitely not going to go up
By as much as the pound eventually went down
You know I'm saying Shirley 20 million dollars
At the risk of making a billion-dollar
You're playing is variables and right
Felt like if something
Epsom salt
World
The British economy
British
Replacing all of that was able to
Like they were able to
Make it work
Erm
Yeah I'm and it went up
He would have stood to lose
So much more that are not very high
But if it went bad
You wouldn't be George Soros possibility did exist
This goes to history of reflux
The idea that you have to
Be flexible within Market
We have to see what's going on and act accordingly
This giant Bethany
An act of his
Reflexivity
Principles
In practice
Because the idea was weak
At like 10 million dollars
Or whatever
And that's one way to do it
But reflexivity would tell you
This is an opportunity where you can make a billion
Right why not do that Ocean's 11
You're going to lose
To the house but if you make a big bet by the window is only open it
But now
So whatever
I do believe that there is
Ethical conversations
You can have about that but they're not with Alex's
He has nothing you have no f****** idea what he's talkin
About you just wants to
To demonize this guy be
And supports liberal democracy
Forces
In countries that he wishes were still part of the sofa
Union I guess
Or in America
Yeah I told you when it is that you think he has it's a bad idea
I told you this a rogue variable
Annual correctly guess what it is
Eddie Bravo Bravo because I can't
Schedule to do an episode after Alex
Have you showed up early
Embarrassed because
Aleve somebody dumber than him
He needs to have an elevated status
Over somebody
He can't have that with Joe
And also Joe realize this isn't going all that well if I get in here will at least have a third wheel
It's everyone's problem
Might be a part of why the episode
5 hours long
Because they just decided
Keep calling but here is Eddie's in
Introduction
To the episode Alex gets
Oh my God any problems here
Jesus Christ
Great
So he
Alex is wearing a
Part of it was to troll
Either flat-earth guide
It's complicated
So I think he was trying to f*** with Eddie
By wearing the shirt
And Eddy
You son of a good workout
T-shirt
No no please don't
Skillet
This which is why I don't want to do it tell me
So this goes on for a while
Is a sad display of a drunk a*******
So
Eddie shows up story about being like
I guess maybe he worked at the
Strip club
It's irrelevant
It was a flat strip club
The guy who ran the place was like
If this little lady
You can choke me out then I'll give her
Are the keys to my car
And it's young guy small woman who Eddie had taught how to do a chokehold
The guy out
He passed out hit his head on the ground as soon as
Brownie
He was Furious
Got to give her those keys
That's fine story
Sick mask what is the same time in the realm of Joe Rogan show
It's a fine story told well
Suspense
Fair
So whatever
Amanda Alex tells this story
I think he's trying to build on
And be like art
Deeply Disturbed
I don't think I've ever been choked completely out
Super hot chick
Tied up
Have sex with you
Is it true story
And she's super hot
Relationship like 30 year old boyfriend
Show me the parking lot
Oh my God
Yeah oh my God
So that's the guy probably
Nicola killed
No no no no
Dude
Hey Jason
Community in France
People in particular probably
Maybe from abuse
Who he was sexually active with who forced him into cross-dressing
At a young age
Requirement to have sex
With her if the story is true at all
Tails are weird
There is
No problem with that among two consensual adults yes yes
Nono twelve-year-old experimenting with makeup or any of that stuff is Noble
Big deal that's another piece of this another piece of that she is also a victim
Girls f****** a twelve-year-old and a thirty-year-old sign
She's got range
Difficult
No but I mean you're describing here not you but if you really take all the packaging off
F***** in the choked out
Kind of stopped
How does a
You're describing Alex Jones as a 1213
Danger old child
Being in a
Super chaotic and
Like to the point where Justin
Existing in that space like I said
Story told
Just
Existing in a space
Where you're at
With a seventeen-year-old girl who is being abused by a thirty-year-old boyfriend
In the context of a quote-unquote relationship
That is enough
Really have a lasting impression
That's terrifying to a child
That
Control
And in blackest debility
Lack of any kind of
Real
What you need in your formative years
It's great
Took to come to Ethel
Adulthood
Is absinthe
He's saying that this is a girl whose parent
We're never home
So she was f******
30 Euro
And then she acted out on me as well
Like There's No Parental soup
Supervision around
There's profound abuse happen
It's just like
Thank you take everything
You take everything out of in your life
Like what you're left with is like
This should be a story for therapy not laughed on Rome Show
A combination of a lot of
Like f*****-up things like
But the worst part is
Is the way that this story is being told as if
Putting makeup on
Is
First off geisha
Yourself
This story is being told like
Like how
Whenever a
Adult male teacher
Has sex with one of his students everybody like this
F***** up right but whatever I had sex with one of her students were like
Given that
And you're like no no it doesn't
Bissell
F***** up
It's people's brain
Yeah
To some extent
Alex has the right
To tell the story however he wants to
Cuz it is expiry
You know what I'm saying
I don't think that you know
We need to
I don't know it's such a weird line like because what he's doing is normalizing all of these
Which is bad
But at the same time if that like
I don't believe this is a
But if
In the context of
His lifelong therapy
He's come to peace with these experiences that he has
About it and be like in this crazy
I don't think that's bad
Are response
Rogan and Bravo
To both be like
Hahaha this is funny
Like there's no way that anybody could tell me that story and I wouldn't be like
That's
You need to deal with that
You need to
Deal with that in a
Much better way than telling me the story like it's a joke
Cuz that's f***** up
SMS
Wow irresponsible friends or
Accomplices
Yeah
Enabler
For sure
Everything that happened on the show
And I staszak
Like in the same way like when you buy an album when you're a kid
And your favorite song on it is the single
Yeah it's just not a good album
Why did anybody
Express
Whatever is that sort of thing
You get the album like f*** this
That's kind of how I feel about this this is the single and I think this is one of the clips that
Probably going to be
Gift around and go big
And what it is
Is Eddie Bravo
Trolling Alex
Really hard
And it's hilarious
Level
The studio
Italics
Freaks out
Do you really think
People out there campaigning for late-term abortions
To give a little bit of context
The reason that idea scrolling him like this
Is because Alex does that about Eddie's flatters belief
Actually believes
Is there's a flat or like that stuff
Just to f*** with him
And Alex is losing
Okay
Play Maddie
Plainview we went into a long
Conversation
First off
If you allow yourself to get f***** with by Eddie Bravo
It's not even human.
There's a delightful on some levels
In much the same way when I was
Stop the guy in the crowd like I don't know if that
Same way listening to this I don't know if Alex is Anguirus
Performative yeah if you watch it you see his face he does look
Not like he's playing
Yeah a little bit
All of his outburst
Emotional
Like this doesn't
That's not you
I don't really care
Clearly f****** with him
30-second Alex I was f****** with you
Daily fix
It's bad that Alex got f***** with by Eddie Bravo
That's pretty sad the worst part though is Eddie Bravo going
Of course I believe that
You didn't even have to do that for
You could have just said you were f******
More about this about
The house
The governor Virginia's Brothers t-shirt
Just of course I believe you
Organ harvesting doctor
That's just
Yeah
But
This is
What happened
And how he was on
Blackmail
Organ harvesting
Kkkk
Oregon
That's a good
Conspiracy
I'm so happy
So you shouldn't tell just married
Has created
Completely different environment
Even if like
Sure him f****** with Alex
Cause this emotional Outburst what have you
But
They threw out the rest of it
It becomes much more palatable feel like everyone has
A position that they can work with Eddie Bravo is there
The steaks are gone but you don't have to talk about this
Sandy Hook have a shutdown Showdown
Also I would say that Alex another reason besides the fact
You're forced to f*** sheep and give guys jobs
No reason you didn't join a fraternity
If you went to a junior college if I dropped out
But that's just my take on it you know
So
Eddie is there
Alex wants to
Impress him
I am Joe
Start talking about
Course
It's some point Alex talks about the Piazza
Really long thing that he goes on about how you used to have like a bunch of box
Garage
And even know what was in them and then one of his family is going through and they found like a Nazi
Metal he bought at a garage sale or something like that and they're like oh my God
That's a family issue
Family member if your family member found a Nazi metal you're not able to have that conversation
That's on you
That's on you and your family
I don't think that you have any Nazi metal makes you a Nazi
I understand people who have like historical
Interest in that sort of
Possibility of that
Into World War
Antiques their relics
Holding those things
As long as you own
American sings also
Or you know the Allied Powers I guess
As long as you have a spectrum
Of these antiques
And not just
Please.
Very normal describing is
More like
How he has no idea what humor is
Like there's no way they
Cuz if you
Because if you did find that
Not to meddle you wouldn't think that he was in
What you were saying
Probably because he's running joke
Would definitely be something that you start throwing in there where you like
Oh yeah because I met
But that's just how people respond
It's whatever but
Besides
Dirt
Oh
Your secrets
What are the dishes
Who's telling you the stuff
Beyond classified Eddie
Do I mean
You work for a dinner of indoor air conditioning
What about dinner
Housing Authority
There's a huge Park
But the point is is that
Hitler was on the cover of Time Magazine
That did that
Stop like they've been very clear about their Man of the Year. Reflected leaving Port them
Unfortunate
Hitler was on the cover of time
Does not mean that they were like
There's a conversation to be had about how the
Like the buns and
Stuff like that there were tons of America
Nazis
Lot of business
Centrist
In favor of
Now you can go back and read a lot of probe killing all the Jews
Greens are really shity
That's what
Comes up with
Because he doesn't want to talk about his grandfather
He wants to introduce the idea that his grandfather gave
Secret information was a German living in Dallas
He also killed
I don't remember when
Nope
I don't want to get
I don't want to
Eddie
F***** me on
When I was going to tell some
Straight up a male Authority
Grandfather
But
Alex regroup
Who is grandfather
And I don't know if this is what he intended to say
But this is where the story goes
Xbox.com
Because he worked for this guy that was a refrigeration air conditioning
Recycle your dad all the car dealerships in Dallas
And what did they tell you
Your grandfather is little
Braun
What
Army Warner von Braun
I get it now
Is f****** brigan fire if there's a hero once again
Distantly
That's good timing on 80th part like
That's actually being funny
Now I get why you
Jesus a new Wernher von Braun
Great
I guess
I don't know if that's
Truewerk
Courtside
If we allow it to be the truth
It makes this next clip
This is eclipse
I'll let that slide
You say something like
I got question
Uber mention
Oh shut okay
Dude if you want to be clear about this
Alex is up here on Rogan show straight up saying that his family was recognized
As part of the master race
I don't think I need to take any more time out anyone today to explain why that's f***** up
Because uberman she's like it doesn't that's a Nietzsche
What after he'd pass
About the timeline
But his sister was involved
The term because she was
Nazi sympathizer
Clean off the idea that refers to the area
Which
You are reinforcing your belief
In
Whilst telling
The story your family is exact
Which is like
You mean they were not
Cuz it sounds like
It does really sound like that
Alex
Grandfather's
Were those Metals you had a box
Your grandfather's War medallions
F****** know but you don't
You if you are somebody who's like
I f****** hate Nazis they're terrible
You don't get drunk on a
They only talk to other people in the club the master race
Nothing
It's what I heard him say We are family is
Uber mention I was like
Oh God
You know who doesn't say that
The family
G with a very small
No it says
Venn diagrams
The wrong way to look at it
What's the tiniest sliver that is just Alex
Their families were also Uber mention
It's fun to be part of the master race
Cuz you really don't have to deal with reality
Sure
In his next life we get another glimpse so earlier I was talking about when he was seven or so and he heard his dad talking to
About making to cyborg
And that's cool
Apparently
So we hear about his grandfather
Don't know if it's
We're not entirely sure
Okay he doesn't say the last name so I'm not sure like
I would assume his mom
Father's last name
Ruby Hammond
Cuz her name is Carol his dad father's last name would be Bowie
No no
Jones
Which is David Bowie's real name
He overhears his grandfather talking about some
Stopped when he was a child
And now he related
Scrabble
So I mean be how tangentially
He's jumping around from topic
Atopic
No stop
There isn't a real point to it doesn't really have any
The only think the point to the story's just revealed that his grandfather was a Nazi
And so now he has to rewrite that to make it sound like his grandfather wasn't
He also talks about
His grandfather worked for
Extorted by the Nazis
Like something like that
He tells a really long story
It's very convoluted about like
The grandfather
Is this guy that you work for had to send tons of money to the Nazis share
Something along those lines kind of like informing
What Vic
Like what conversation Alex is trying to
But because it doesn't
Make a lot of sense
Was that like
The Nazis extorted
Like I don't know if that's the secret of Hitler
I don't know if
The beginning of this conversation
Information about Hitler
It turns out that he
Blackmailed and HV AC guy
8 HP AC HVAC
Yeah
Not a bad strategy
Make a little.
Certainly is well within their repertoire
Time.
Indoor air conditioning was
Outdoor air conditioner
Sure that's what about what about
That's
There's a distinction
But is not a worthwhile to fix it guys
Guys crazy
So earlier we heard Alex say that NASA was the real devil
You bought
They were the shadow
Shadow equals real
The real
Do that
I really don't think we do
IFixit Knuckles is there anyway
How it is next clip Alex doubles down on that and then explain
How that came
Because Rogan is
Government government
It was British run
They said we've got all this on the drawing board
What's the German
Never really used to be a cult
Thank Patty
Because we now bring in foreign governments there's like government
Germany's government as well
That will be
EU is a plan put together by the German Breakaway
Secret program contacted aliens
They were the ones who came up with the
He just described the globalist plan then he attributed to the billionaire conference
There's only had that conference to talk about it be
Because they were aware and we're getting information
From these Germans or maybe not germs
Tours in contact with a
Right
I would assume so it does make sense
Germans are aliens
And they're getting pissed
Nation from them
Is that like what we have here is out
Presented
A dichotomy of to Breakaway
That's one is the British
And one is the
The German and they're at war with each other to some extent
No but that's
The German secret space program or whatever
He's protecting Americans
He's also presenting
Bebe
British Breakaway government as being involved in our government as well
If the two were at War be in congruous 4A
To have both
Existing within the
The same body
But he doesn't really
Sweat the small stuff
Here is the other things that I think
Everybody's
And I would say even out
King George
Immortal
Okay and the scenes
Of the British got
Everything else is a f******
Clock
Sleight of hand
Still alive you're serious
Alex is missing ever
One is missing and your theory is
Thing is citation
Missy underlying proof other than I heard a weirdo
That's not good
But that is not good
Microsoft Encarta
Another problem is
It's one is the British one is the German
The Germans influence
Are NASA through the Operation Paperclip
And all the Nazis coming over in
Right
It also makes it
Difficult for me to
Integrate all of these ID
Okay
You don't need to do all that
What we're in contact with
Are you getting this from you stating until confident
Literature literature
Historical books about mainstream
Surreal definition
Problem
Go to statements
Cuz they were in contact with the aliens
IL million
Okay
I'll prove it to you but I need a rebooking
In order to do in front of Joe
Duval of Micah
Conjecture about
But I will send you those
We're going ahead of time
Got to be great
Those books are not going to say the
This is never going to happen
Although
That probably that bezel problem
Why would you mail
Also if you have those books
Got the little tabs
You should know what books
You would think
Especially when they are
Pieces of
What you think is the big truth of the
The world technology
And all that stuff
Where are you getting this from
If you can only say
The literature
You don't know what you're talkin about
You don't want to give that citation
Because you know that if
You do
Someone to look at it be like
This is a nonsense book this is a Project Camelot book
Of the idea
Fat
German
Came to
Eisenhower
And we'll like
Guess what
All our technology
That
A good meat
That's a good meeting that's a good day
Very boring man
Bit of a teetotaler
Has a meeting with some German
Aliens are real
The guy with the brown bag dude
Brown Bag me up
The part of the Project Camelot like a alien
Narrative
In some
I don't know how
Pervasive it is
It's fairly common
Treaty with aliens in order to allow them
Kidnap people for scientific purposes
But it's also based on people actually believe
Artful retelling of that
Where is incorporating the Nazis come
And being a part of that
And maybe that's a part of people's
Paranormal
Argument
As well I don't know
Catfish guide
I don't know I read Hellboy years ago I thought it was
So Alex
Gets into a bit of a Jag
Which we know
Yeah yeah yeah
The oldest misrepresentation of Carol Quigley's work there's no source of
It's about like
These
The globalist
As it were or the inside
Whichever
Terminology the Rider 2
They controlled all sides of
The conflict
Manipulated Hitler into doing what he did in order to
Blah blee bloo
The saying that Sandy Hook was fake
In this next clip Alex is talking about his beliefs
All that Hitler setups
His biggest piece of evidence
Answer his biggest argument
Is that b******* story that we've talked about a bunch of times
Rudolf Hess
About him flying in with a
Peace treaty ride parachuting into England
Scotland
But
Do you know all this nonsense
About his fly
Alex talks about this
And then I
I realized
Summit
Major problem
We've never pointed out
With Alex's Theory
And I'll tell you what I'm doing
Rudolf Hess was the
The guy Hitler
Just 1941
Corsicana
Who was a Nazi in German
The French do down beachy French 75
Here's the
Nothing we've talked a lot about the problems of Alex's fake story about Rudolph house
The peace treaty that would have ended World War
Set off all that check
His name was Rudy
Kind of rude
To call him rude
Rudy
Nice rehash that here but I do want to point out that
Glaring hole
Alex says that Rudolph has had a treaty for
Peace that representative deal between the Germans and Edward
The problem with this is that
Has flight for Scott
Happened on May 10th 90
And why is that a problem
Well because Edward the 8th abdicated the throne on December 11th 1936
P-39
Three years after you'd step down as
So he never would have actually been in a position to negotiate a peace
This narrative
Complete trashed it only works if you have no idea
I like the basic facts
About when things happen
No grasp on no in your heart
You cannot step down
Once a king always
No
Yep no cuz you wanted to marry a divorce divorce not done
It was absolute
Yeah abdicated the throne for that
Couple years later WWII
Two broke out he was in no position to charge
He wasn't even in
England for most of that time right because he was kind of
A scandalous figure
Yeah and that whole narrative like
And in all that stuff
The royal families of most of Europe at that have been f****** each other for
Forever
We're related to each other as their royalty was related to him
Because royalty has such a
Delineate
Countries borders
So you have like Old Kingdom
Stuff like that that existed
It's all you have intermarriages of
The kingdom of
What part of Germany
Holy Roman Empire
Yeah you have all that stuff
That makes it incredibly complicated
Misrepresent
There's there's
It's fertile ground
For lying about stuff
But the reality.
Don't match up I just think it's hilarious but Alex
Rudolph
Past would have had
Peace treaty signed by Edward the 8th
That would mean
Between
Existed
Before World War II
Even started
If your five-year-old
Peace treaty that
Predated the outbreak
WWII
Which makes no sense furthermore the chicken was not in control
Right
Talkingshit on Chamberlain he does talk some Chill Chamber
Hey that's fine
But
Because this next month is Farm
Get that motherfuking thought so loose
Fake
I need to hear about aliens
Don't take pill that cigar but I don't smoke marijuana
Nobody is ever
Swisher Sweets
Just f******
And you're doing the whole like
Shittily swearing at
Cuz you're really bad at it
You might as well say you're getting
Nonsense doesn't serve any real purpose I just
I don't know
And you're in La probably without your family because you're going
Fly back the next day or whatever
Where would I look at it
It's probably just bad here
Janoski Nike
This is fake vodka
No one would believe
Yeah
It's not saving
Face or any
Big box just water
Dump it
Is a stupid f******
Grow up
Joe wants to know
When did
The connection
Between aliens
Did Nazis
Now you might think that
You might think that's a question that Alex can answer you be wrong
He just decides to start rambling about other thing
Tell me how the connection between aliens and the Nazis took place when did all the start
At the beginning
It's people
A genetically available
To interface Native Americans incredibly diverse Universe with all these dimensions
Where's consciousnesses
Has no energy ever destroyed all continues on
Hive organism
Race memories
But not ingest some compressed
Epigenetic system
Electrochemical
Lower dimensions
They're holding their breath really like my family
Give us more XP
The idea that ghosts
And they're holding you all the time right there loving us
I don't either I also don't like most of my family
Like not to say that I don't like my family or anything like that
Don't like my family
Die from serious question
You go past them
I don't know any of those
People I've never met them I would like them to leave me the f*** alone
I don't care for this idea of us being organism of
Likelihood Vincennes in
Victories of our
Our path
Free Willy
Completely Nautica
Rugged individualism
How is individual Eva isn't even possible if you were a hive organism
Of everyone in the past
Also
Brother
Write to me my brother come from the exact same genetic life right
So you want pictures are they
No no okay I want to go in
Divorce situation where they have to choose or your fingertips
But you know what I'm saying
Or does all of you all of your ancestors
Depending on how many children
And then after like five generations
Split 100
Different places
This makes no sense
It's ludicrous. Since Metallica
Romanticize
And pretended that he
You proved as the idea
Proof
Find it or whatever it is
It's right
You think it's something Beyond
Right
Crazy
But here's the bigger point is that we know this from listen
Goes back to like
Religious ideas
Expressing
Some sort of a Trippy
Far-out kind of ibf
The piece of his religious zealot
Joe is allowing him to
Express these sorts of things
That really
There are fundamental
Pieces of what makes him
A religious radical
Christian Fundamentalist
Weirdo
And it's just one question.
And what else has even think
He just thinks it's
He thinks they're high and they're talking about space
He doesn't realize that
Alex is like
And that's why God is
Controlling the world and but also there's
Shadow governments but it's all under God
He does kind of get
Get to that in a little bit
If we get another glimpse of what Alex's
His dad has told him
About the past
Anakin
And if so
Dubious
My dad didn't tell me this
Dentist
Chili sauce
Southside we had virtual reality goggles
And we are eating wrong
Something else happened and I'm not at Liberty to get into it but I was shown
3 years ago
What University of Washington was doing under Bill Gates
Images of a nice
What were they doing
What are used to date that they don't know what they're being given this year
So you think it's some sort of
Alien intervention types
Your heart off 45 minutes
They pump oxygen in your blood
In the meeting
You're in the meetings with freaking aliens
But there's no power shutting your heart off it makes you have that psychedelic experience biking blood in your oxygen keep you alive
Okay
So you can stay longer
Understatement of the century I don't know officer
Like Bill Gates run Washington University
He donated a bunch of money there because his dad wasn't alone for there any grew up in Washington
Yes there is an association of Bill Gates in the University wash
45-minute for next week on how
In order to save it
They house
Killer
Jesus
I'm no doctor I'm not a scientist
I'm like if you
You did stop someone's heart and you were able to
Blood flow to their brain
You could keep them dead for
Like 5 minutes
It's very possible because
The difficulty is when your heart stops
It stops pumping blood and therefore there is an oxygen that ends up going to your brain right brain doesn't
Have oxygen
A certain amount of time
It becomes
Damaged
To the point where you
I believe that there is a
Theoretical theoretical possibility
But it seems
Incredibly
A way that you have them go into meeting.
I don't know
I think that there's a lot more he needs
Prove if
Medically hypothetically father
Right
That's what I'm saying also
Like even though
More like
You're describing those
I died for 2 minutes on the table and I saw heaven
Vision
Things where it's like
No your your ranges
Hallucinate or anything like that
Does deserve like a shout-out
Outdoor whatever
When he talks about his own
Experiences
Communicated
With something
But that's not to say that it wasn't
Within my head there's no reason to assume
And out
Even says I'll never be able to know
Either way right what's the point
Your own subconscious
So like
Yeah
Like
Your best bet is
Schrodinger's cat
Kind of
Jumping into the multi
Swear it's like
You have a you keep shooting you have one bullet and you keep shooting
You keep shooting
And at a certain point
You're actually realizing that you've jumped into the Multiverse
The only person that you could ever prove that to
Subway
We can
Subconscious mind does exist
We haven't proven
Extra-dimensional
National bae
Do exist
These entities that I'm talking to when I'm hallucinating
Are either a part of my own subconscious
Or their demons from another dimension trying to talk to me
Considering one of those things I'm confident is real
The other I don't know
I think it's probably rational to err on the side of
I don't know
But if I had to choose an explanation I would go with it's in your head
No wonder you believe
You didn't
Alex talks about the
Of the Bill Gates
45 minutes ago to be just aliens
It turns out
You technology
When you're in there
Joe asks for example
Knock knock
And it's like the things that you tell him they come out and they tell scientist it works
Like we're going to shed
They didn't
How would you microwave
Yeah we're not you do with microwave anything
Anything absolutely
Some technology premise that
Kill people for saying specific Technologies
Gave them the technology flying for any kind of
World government to draw
F****** stupid
So now we get another childhood memory of Alex
Cuz where he overheard some
But I don't believe is
True
But
Turns out
Does lady
Come over to his house
This is is this all about f******
No this is
This one's just overhearing another
Stories are Gruffs yeah
Gross it's just
This Walk This Way with come over
She talked about
Yeah we called the Psychedelic research
Population
Breezy certain plans in India
San Francisco
Addicted
Google are YouTuber
No squeezing drawing
They won't tell me specifically
Girl you sexist pig
For the wind one more time
YouTube is just alphabet
It's just the same company
YouTube sets 2014
He doesn't deal with these things realistically
If he did
Movie Yelling about Susan all the time because he got kicked off YouTube
Jack
Yeah there's like
For companies who own all Media or whatever it is like everybody has their own Subs
Who's the CEO of YouTube
Yeah like in that indicates to me a lack of
Interest or lack of knowledge about
And hey Eddie
The woman
He does know that a lot of money off YouTube
CEO of YouTube
Pretty safe to say he's in the top 1% of YouTube channel
He's probably matter
Before
Unlikely he hasn't
Where were you better
Because he's one of their biggest
But you have somebody else
Text Samantha
Imagine Dragons
Not our podcast I don't think this has been a good
Did Rogan and Alex
So made me real bummed out when Alex
Alien
It back somehow that's disappointing
I figured
Get some Tito's
Disappointed
I have lost
Respect
Alex
The first time he was a Highwayman
So they talked a bit more about aliens
And it's most
Lee in concert
Sequential bulshit
That is so vague as to be meaningless
The Great
An hour Grace well
If not the greys
What is it our Grace
What do you mean by our grade project
Okay alright
Do you think grades are like a like a robot
I think I might've heard that theory
Did the ideas
Leaving
Biological Android
I mean
Cool
Display Flyers that we talked about all the time
It's really disappointed he's way better than him because
How's Joey
About stuff helps the pill go down
Yeah
Because she's she has an agenda
I need to know that Alex is going to get drunk
Start yelling about how aliens give us all the technical
Cuz now that they're past the rapprochement getting relationship
New lies or my refined lies clear the beginning of this
And now I'm going to make an angle for your listeners
Because
Spirits of God
But no
I don't DMT every night because my thick neck exit and I know everything I'm a psychic I know about
The German
And the Nazis
Meeting with aliens
Continues to build back when he was at Washington University
The killing people
5 minutes
Ibf
At all
He does talk about it later
Okay what he says
But he has to reiterate it
But
Because he reiterates
He accidentally said something
That most people probably don't know what he saying
We do
Me neither
You think I give you this information sometime before the filter like for sure
And just because
He was famous
So you think there are
Especially
I'm sure there's people setting everybody up
SoJO Spa because I never realized it was 2012
Supercomputers Vic
Answer somebody from MIT
Clearly misspeak
You said two weeks ago
Weeks after a
But
You-know-who
Alex
Book says in the CIA
You know
You know who else believe the Sandy Hook was fake and told Alex to say it
Stevie punches you know who else has a degree in international relations from MIT
He's talking about Steve pieczenik a hundred percent 100 probably doesn't want to bring that up though because Eddie Bravo
Yeah
God dammit
He's a phantom
Alex
Direct
Right
Elastic cause ripples
He doesn't want to have it
But he's pretty clearly
Bolstering
Steve CIA credentials
Stuff like that
Probably mixing up multiple
But the
He's clearly talking about
Is
A picture of match up with Xavier Verizon
Is this another situation where we're finding a
Bore excuse that it's not his fault
It's not as f*** off
Specific example of the excuses he was making
Earlier this house
Do you think that's possible that your sources give you missing
If
You
Did your sources
Sometimes give you misinformation
Don't operate on the information
People give you
Any of that information
Figure out
Clean information sources
Heaven's use those
Instead of his record lying to you because their own agenda
Rogan credits 48
Titanic
I've been followed around by a all by lights
That
Spoke
Volume brevity
Well place
Wouldn't work without the I'm not in the CIA
Mediator
Such a good it's clear he's been doing stand-up for decade
Alex's sort of press to the wall here by by the
At the party
You give
How do you know this stuff
You so,
Confident about the ideas
And here is where we get back to General Albert
Dirt
Stubblebine
Literally been trying to find out what's going on
I'm not the one saying there's all these aliens
The entire government
And all these Advanced groups that's what I've given up on space
You're all about interdimensional
Okay
About what
There's not just one group of lately
Rappers what's the different groups
Christmas song
You know about General stubblebine right
No don't
General
Clandestine operations for your scammer flight 15 years
Shovel for whatever
Also private discussions and this is like 67 years ago
50 years ago
This is the guy that ran the whole show
Yeah
That's a joke about Washington
So this indicates
I hate this so much Penny does the dabancheng
On the Shelf like when he's talking about that invest
The pedia article about Soros and the pound
Cirrhosis history
Walkthrough walls and teleported
Or whatever
You can just say whatever information you confide
You do whatever you can find
Is a whitewash of the reality that I've been able to find now I refuse to tell you
Where I found that information I won't give you any citations on it I'll say it's mainstream literature
Documents
All that stuff but I won't tell you anything
The Anythink
You think it's real
The f****** whitewash
And that mentality
He is exactly what helps was talking about the beginning of the show as being
I got it right now
All the articles
Okay well the article doesn't say what you want
The whitewash
F*** you
It has much to do with anything
But it's
Like
Talk to Rabbit
I like to celebrate that I like
Like a pure kind of like
A true esoteric
What do you say the ocean with the Tri-River is the triage
It seems to
Tubidy
These moments
Where he's getting
Deeply poetic and there's no agenda
The two it necessarily just something weird
Consciousness in the universe is inter-dimensional space craft
Beyond that
Those are common
My research
A consciousness
Location
Okay
System of
Survival ofthe fittest
Gotshell
What okay
Hop
What
That's not a comics
Stop this podcast is a good way to end this motherfuker
Is it's gone long already passed the
The 3-hour mark that they usually Rogan shows usually go
Would like both him
We just got the Consciousness is a comet in evils of the tail
Call the guy that's late house party I got a lot I don't know
F****** baseball game extended nothing let's move on there four ways to work what kind of
Someone's expressing that you like
Not much more than enough
You are gone
Research I find comet
That was the fish f******
That was actually an
From Al
I could have been
Back when he was 30
Fish joke about
This is just
I mean
I enjoy it on one level and I enjoyed
Incredulousness
About it like
Sure man
That's a lot of words
Hey yeah so we're out of beer we got three left
Beer drinking ability
You know it's really time to go when I was 12 okay
Comment in the back part of it is evil
Jesus's get behind
Show me Satan blah blah blah
I'm about how he's a psycho
He's already talked about heavy as BMT dream
Every night
Everything everything
If I want to stay
The dismayed
Sodalite
Because
He's talked on his own show about the idea that he saw himself getting mugged in a
What do you leave with is this
This made me laugh so
Let me tell you what my
Okay
Talk about 12
12 presents
What
To say that is arrogance I won't say that
Have had Dreams by whole life
It come true
And the weirdest thing like a lady drops
Pickles at the store
I'm there
It was more intense it happen
Was it exactly how you draw
I would also be
F***
Because a dream about a woman dropping a jar of pickles
If there was some sort of like Celestial intelligence there was granting Alex his
Prophetic vision
You could stop it or not doesn't matter it's inconsequential they don't care to
Charged with Pickles.
To drop someone's going to have to
Clean it up I guess it'll be a mile
Inconvenience for an employee
So low stakes this psychic ability
Is
It turns out
Very bad
Not it
Or try
This lady is going to drop
You f****** pickle
What are the universal
God is a cucumber
Possible
Pickles because God despises
The pickle no no no you want it
Alex
Because
Pickling
The Cucumber becomes it's
Much like a caterpillar
Into a larva
A butterfly
Stager whatever
You put those cucumbers
In pickling juice
Become so much better not realized
Cucumbers are Audrey Hepburn
Got cucumbers are races
Pickles
Cucumbers
Pickles our nation is to
That's the that's the only
This conversation makes as much sense as anything Alex is so that's a bad sign
Prophetic dream
And he said something
Think about a dream he had
Was a much younger man
At this is this this
To me was
Real f*****-up
It is a little bit of a longer clip but it be
Because I wanted to illustrate how Alex is
Like the wage is not together
Is
Traveling
. you'll see what I mean as soon as
I would have this dream
Cuz God knows everything is a super intelligent
Omnipresent
We're trying to find out where we came from
God is like a virtual reality simulation as well
I want to jump in here really quick and say that I think that
Recently he
He read Scott out of
The book God
The guy who created Dilbert
Hypothetical thought experiment
Call God's debris
Many many years ago
Please try to be like I'm not just a Dilbert guy
He wrote this book it was basically the argument
The God knows everything
Except what universe
Without him would be
Receipts searches
For this wisdom
It's a lot of things that I was
Describing in this
3 when he was 3 years old his dream
He had from the perspective of God is
Kind of similar it's not
When I was 3 years old I
Had a dream for three straight years
Gilbert would be a hit
Came true
1 parallel
With Scott Adams
Close enough that any know that
You've Got a Friend
Who's been on the show botched
It's close enough that I think that maybe he's being a
Bye
Every program every operation
But the earliest memories The Edge of Insanity
And that's not a thing
You can say
It was a message
Skyward
I would have to go into that
Trying to figure out what was going on in Everett
And like knowing what's going to happen before it happens and then questioning it and then it never been wrong
Crazy stuff man like
I just so much stuff where it becomes like
You just reach that point where
You don't even know what's real anymore because it's so crazy
Can you see like
You talk about it
That's what freaked him out
What about to do with the speech
Trump speech
Sometimes
Your brain works
He's changing
Making Connections work
Connections don't exist
He's talking about one thing and realizing
He's in over his head
And not making sense so we can
Something else like
I say things on the president repeat them in the CIA is freaked out by it
Yeah
Childish
Affect
Like
As much of a goof
Gullible weirdo
Do you still on the level enough to be like I don't
You're talkin about
What is that
This subject you were talking about you started by talking about dreams you had from
God's eyes
Or whatever when you were three and now we're talkin
I'm about you and the president
Mirroring each other in the CIA
You aren't making sense if I were ever to be
Gifted with the opportunity to see the edge of infinity
I would come back
With a bit more of a higher mindset then
Become a talk show host and claimed at Sandy Hook
And aggressively never read
But then expanded to the point where I
Bulshit
Some sort of a yacht
Star baby doesn't want to become a positive influence
Of people like 8
Leave these Petty differences behind
Or even then or what Alex impulsively
It doesn't mean anything literal edge of infinity
Friar version
Nihilistic
Yeah he thinks that he's the guy who's telling people all this stuff doesn't matter
When in reality all he does is
Aggressively over-inflate
To reinforce status quo whether it be racial
Gender-based
Leaving like that
The definition
Of
Of make
Looking things
Regressive
The presentation is I'm above the right left paradigm
Whatever
It's nonsense
Anyway
It should make this is also this next clip
Want to play this
Kind of half
If you're going over this episode
This is the other thing that everyone's going to put into
Gifts
And I understand why but I thought
Problem
What's not funny
Rap music
Alex
Exhaling aggressively
Cuz you realized like
Going to make a point
With that but I just
Everything is done
Yeah I find that disgusting even in terms of Alex
Whatever you trying to say about himself
Or whatever
F*** off you think that's.
He's being like self-effacing in
Humble
And what he's really big is
Dismissive
And disgusting
We get to the tobacco
I can I can say for sure
If you watch if you hadn't smoked
Penny tobacco
Before then
Regular marijuana
I ain't got no blunt
Is God is always
In the beginning of the show
He was misled
He was all of this s***
And then later on in the show he says his guts never wrong
Going to drop pickles
Or something like that
Oh this vilamit scientist guy named Steve
Miss leave you at
Completely destroy right whatever you were doing
You don't have any of
The important
Instinct
Whatever he has like he thinks like my guts never wrong
On the table is God is always wrong
Beatles
Is
Heathen taken to a cow
These other things were
Cinctive light him
Deeply
People astray
Right
And that's
To me like
It's like he's describing
The worst
X-Men power you
You could have like
I look
I'm a mutant
I have these
Psychic powers
But they're all cucumber base
That is my gift
And then Professor X's
Cool
Weave
So
Come on down
I mean
Nobility Foothill
Be more like ad
No like
You're not useful fighting Magneto right unless
True words can you make
A Marvel hit us up
I just saw that trailer for dark Phoenix
Peruse the magnetic
Put
Gene Dragon do against the magnetic pickle guy
F****** nothing
So at this point Alex guitar
And you type pretty
Conversation
They had off air
Addition
Bulshit
Whatever he was telling Joe
Before they started is b*******
The ways percent
Also both
Tell me what
You were actually you even before all this happen
You were planning your exit strategy
Are you get weary of the
Fredo fight
Long adventurous lifestyle power like 60
That isn't
Sure
He had to have
Thinking about cash
Hangout
For sure
But I also don't believe that it was
Before the
Looking
There wasn't there wasn't part of him that was like
Eager for The Fray he was all in
It what happened is after the election
We realized I've committed
And also I have nobody who can take over the operation that I can get a piece of retired
Selfie
Negative situation
But it does Judaism
Mythology
Beneficial to
To make it look like he wanted to quit before all this started
Of course
Victimization
Globalist
Really kicked into overdrive
And that's what he
I was already
Like I wasn't sure about Trump or whatever
Elephant attack me so much makes me have a battle at 5 never give up
And an insult
They kept me in the game I was playing
They kept me in the game attacking me lying about me
Now I do a lot of stuff
So
He always
F*** off
You got reinvigorated by
Christmas present supremacist
Guy was ahead of chance
The Wynn
But now the consequence
The chickens have come home
You don't like it
Because people are like
Hey dick
We put up with this for a long time
And now it's unsustainable
Now you're a problem
We should go
Should have dealt with you but you were too
Just a goofy soccer who was lying about everything
In a
Find what
Systemic
Piece of a
Upholding a system
That is
Killing people
So the report recently about the
Yep set up at the border
He's a part of Defending
Do the part of Defending bolsonaro in Brazil
Defending now
The regime change in Venezuela
He's a part of rationalizing trump doing this
Dumbass
Publicity stunt b******* in North
Korea the only helps
Like he's a part of Defending these
Dangerous
And I understand like
The foreign policy tonight
Wasn't
4 or anything like that
Worse now
Yeah I'm not going to go to American foreign power am I
Ciara
American f****** Revolution
As American foreign policy
Yeah the difference
Today is
Or at least the appearance of a
I think of that does has
A marked difference
And how you're presenting
Yeah
That is
Is deeply chaotic
It allows a lot of Bad actors
Advantage of
I think
Huge part of
Mainstreaming even before the election in the lead-up to
Mainstreaming in normalizing a lot of those eyes
He has that now
Have grown Beyond him
Like they're now on Tucker every
Before
Well in the way that they had.
Hide
Exactly believed all this s*** but they had it's not part of public this
I'll help make that apart of public
Hell yeah
So
I don't know I mean if you don't like you want to duck the consequence
Satisfying
Not fine
No I mean I understand it.
You can't
In the same way you can't jump the consequences of what you said about Sandy Hook
I don't care if you're staying
You did
You did that
You had millions of listeners
You knew what kind of info
Who doesn't matter
Whatever you want to do now doesn't matter
The damage is done
So when he's
He's talking about all this b******* like I wanted to quit I don't have a heart attack
50 50
That's just his mythology
That's rationalizing where he is now
Pretending all of these attacks that are coming against him
I just came out of nowhere
The strawman version
I hate
All these people
The way that I
Becoming an that made
Endometriosis
You don't talk that much about Trump
But he does
Not as strong as
Trump shows that Isis
Is a dirty a******
But it's not
For off in some way
I hate Donald Trump
Because I got behind Hillary was bad
And then he became my
Because
Your trunk
In a fight like this with so dumb.
Place like
Personal perspective than I appreciate that
But he's not here. I don't know how many people actually think that he's your identity
I do
I do you know
Complaining about
The end result of his
He's complaining
People perceive in him as like Donald Trump as my identity
14 years all he did
Was get on his show in
Everything possible to muddy the water in defend indefensible things that Trump was doing
Nationalism
Like all that s***
The idea that he's like
He made his
F****** bad if you
That is what's going on with my identity
Then why you behave the way you
You did
Problem
Your behavior
Is what led to this
If you hadn't said that everyone at Sandy Hook
Where actor
And you haven't called that pain
You hadn't done that
No one would say you did
That is absurd
No one would do that
I wouldn't do that
I treat Alex
The most fairly than anybody ever.
It's disconcerting for someone who has much as I do
And studies in
Next time buddy
I am
Overly Fair
And I would never characterize him
Is acting the way
Is part of his identity
If he he
Mated apart
I would never say that Trump is his identity just said if he had
Branded himself that way intentional I was going to say
So for 3 years
Non-stop I talked about how great was and how close I am all the time
I would die for her
And now people think that I'm just the Trump guy
People think I like
Props
Dude that's your career
He discovered the prop active
Electric
To the main
Headlining
Yeah Alex
Have
A career that was based on other things
But it certainly turbocharged your career
Did you ran with
Intentional
That was your
Gimmick you accepted
And you now have to accept
That you did that
To deny that is
For money
Right and you didn't believe a f***
King word
To do cuz it would
Give a little bit more Credence to these like
I don't want this
To be me I just
Accepted this
Because of crass
Consideration
Exactly
Yeah it's the only way what he's presenting worth that get the f*** out of here
With your like
I don't want I don't want people to think that that's my ident
Because of
Gofucker
Exactly
So
East High
Okay
But the fact that quick
Does kind of give me some
Yeah maybe you don't get high but he doesn't get high
If you're getting that quick you probably won't talk to me
And paranoid
I totally
I probably
Ingested marijuana
Edible
Three times in the last
Or something like that
Loved it when I was much younger but
And what have you put like
I understand that the idea
Because like I don't smoke
And it's be fair if I were in
Situation
Comprable to Alex being in a stew
Studio with Eddie Bravo and Rogan
Of course
If the stakes were tires without stealing with right now
Probably wouldn't smoke
I get doesn't seem like a good idea to f****** your heads face while at the same time being sued by Sandy Hook
Victor
I think he thinks he's navigated the territory successfully
And now we're going to the
The fun part of the trip
I'm not coming down on him
I think it's a dumb idea
I wouldn't do it just because
I would rather this
Disappeared
Real weird
It's like how some people react like getting Doug with high or whatever it is where it's black
Take down
Yeah
But like I said hi
And he should be
Responded
Campaign
Cool
But I'm just
So can I have a little bit more of a personality
He's a in them
Give me more weed
It fucken tired
Because I think
Killing the park
I want more weed
Example of
And your
Complete enabling
Personality
Again
If Joe Rogan
I think I would be f****** fascinating
Yeah get it really f***** up because they
Crazyshit
But to be fair
The craziest s*** that he said
Was when he was
Early parts of drunk
Just
Just dropped glasses of Tito's in he's talking about Native
Perkins being easy
The mind control
F***** up things like his grandfather being Uber mention
And stuff like that before any of the weed comes in
Yeah
Your
You're on grounds that you're comfortable being on you drink a bit it's super weird
Artio
In that
What that what he said earlier we've just kind of moved on from we have to and then and then you're like
You brought it up again like wait
It really did save Native Americans were susceptible to Minecon
Control
That's at the end of the ship you don't like
Get out of here
Huh
Just wife isn't good
As an exercise
You know it's just not a good thing to
To do
Disorder show
Right
F****** positive
If we paid as much attention to
Two other episodes of Rogan
Pinchot as we do with what
More than enough
Yuna
Alex puskita more tobacco
Super
So that's popped a little more tobacco.
Shout out to
Joe McAdams
Headspace
He starts talking about races
And most of it is super unimportant
He's just saying that he isn't
And it's stupid
Videos
This is a big
Let's wrap this up
I don't know what it is
Oh you're a racist
Say your car someone is they are
Restaurants
Text & Beyond bike rack
Or because there is one
Mexican for 3 hours
A hundred percent believe in the tower real of Mexicans
I do too
Mexican food
Do you want that long pause there
That was because Alex was like
What are you talkin about you doesn't realize it's Bravo's
Next to a Mexican for 3 hours
You said wait
I don't think the pause is Alex feeling like I can't believe I sent next
Claritin
Justin being like I don't
What you're saying
I don't get
Processing
He's f****** soda
Drunken High
Billy
I'm not playing a ton of clips
From the end of this episode
Because it is so
Disaster
It's just them
2nd episode
And the natural rhythm
Are over
I meant Alex being like
The prop in order to start a conversation
Like it's trash
It's awful
There is something
Ends up being discussed
That I think is very important
Use somebody pile drive to you
What happened
How old are you
Wow
So was it a friend
And his cousin or something
You know Got Me Down
Here's a victim of racial attacks
I'm not like Jeffrey
Jussie Smollett
You literally said that you wrote the Mexican I got my leg broken being outside
Personality
Do you have any significant change
Sometimes juries
Especially
It seems like
Real
Do we got to get to the route
Brain damage
There's no doubt
So I guess we can
Take that as a
Curiosity
Put check mark
And we definitely get rid of the probably there
The person that Alex is talking about who had medical copy
Translator that died
Possible
Yeah
Alright
But the other thing there is
The distance to be
F****** crystal clear
Joe is being like that's good timing
When Alex is his response
Your personality changes like
Who's all good for
I don't think that was a joke
I think it was Alex
Responding
Like in a dismissive
Kind of way
What he's asking me
Is
Threatening question
In some way
Because if I recognize the fact that
I got pile-driven on conch
Concrete when I was
How did the personality change
Cuz that is a very
Common
Right with severe brain
Trauma
Alex's I think
Dismissive
Answer the Joe is
Is a joke
It's not a joke
I want tell you this
The pile drivers actually moved
It's banned by the WWE here we go
If it's not performed the odds of it killing or paralyzing someone are really high
SummerSlam 1997 Owen Hart delivered a botched Piledriver to Stone Cold
Steve Austin
And broke his neck
In the middle of the match
Thankfully he was able to get surgery and
Recover from that
Guaranteed
Stone Cold career be cut
Way short
Most doctors who generally aren't thrilled to be asked to comment on this sort of thing
Agree that the pile driver
If it's delivered in a real-world scenario would almost
Definitely break a person's neck
And would very likely immediately
We kill them
The direct downward force would cause your spinal column to
So the odds are of
You not
Very least ending up paralyzed
Are very very
What Alex is describing
When is a situation
It doesn't
Match with like the idea that you stood up
I don't know if this is true
It seems like it's not true or at least The Narrative of it seems not
Like combining two story
World
It is almost certainly
Exaggerating
Even if it even if the sequence of events that he's too
Describing happen
It wasn't that he got
Full on
Piledriver
Write more like
He got
Thrown or whatever it is and he's been
Describing it as a pie
In order to kind of mental image
What he survived and end
In a superhuman way right
To the ground
Oh absolutely
To be like
I think that any
Anybody who talks about real fight in the real world
I think you have a responsibility
Piledriver comes up
Don't do that to people
Yeah
No his his argument would be
Don't do that to people because they might stand up and then punch you in the f****** throat that's Alex's exactly
Jesus
Preposition Earth proposition
And they're like you got pile-driven and
Man punches guy in
Whatever you interview accepted
Let's let's imagine let's stipulate
Experience
Is an imp
Like that is
Cuz this guy is the state wrestling champion
He's a muscle
We guy there's a lot of weight to it
So when you pile Drive someone part of the compression
Part of it
Is there weight coming along with your Waits falling down
And knocking your head into the ground
Covid-19
What is it it's someone
Who would be able to deliver that with
A ton of em
Right
State rest
When Champion not a professional wrestler
Would deliver a Piledriver have a good point
Kind
Who's wrestling move
You know
You in a Full Nelson
He wouldn't be like I saw this I saw the Undertaker do this like
F*** off
It is weird
It's true that what you have to come
Alex that is
Crazy
That is
That is a trauma
People don't go through
Yeah
This
Every bit of information we have about Alex
The childhood
From
I'm basically every stories ever told about his childhood
From so many serial
I've experienced nothing but non-stop prom
Until I was killing people
But for him it's like
There's literally nothing that you can describe his childhood as
Other than
A Non-Stop
Combination of
Statutory rape
Goddamn mind control games by his dad
And then now physical
F*** emotionally threatening situations
Whether it be
Believing
Document to ascertain
I called
On
Look No Boundaries that
Situations
But he finds himself
I don't think I necessarily believe any of
What's the details
Of course not
No but if you take him at what
If you believe him
This is a really really
The portrait that he's painting of his younger
He's
Exactly the rest
Refer someone
Who needs
Yeah it's not somebody who's
Funny
It's not somebody who has
You can last at Houk
See he is around
And if you don't believe
Leave him
Kind of weird
Because I was lying
Image that their childhood was the sort of thing
That would require
Decades of therapy
In order to get you to be able to integrate this
Healthy life
Yeah
It's kind of like
I don't know what you're getting out of ragging it embellishment
These stories that are.
We f***** up
I don't know I just wanted I just want to be clear that I don't believe this stuff
Just because he's saying I'm not getting
Trick by like some sort of
You know a goof
If you do believe it
This is very serious
That's what I'm saying
I don't believe the details of what he's
But I do believe
In the overall trauma
Of what he's
Yeah
Yeah go to some
Senior in high school house in a Mercedes
And get injected into a satanic cult by killing knock
I don't think that that's not true
But I do think
Something
Happened
Wherein he got really traumatized at a very young age
In a way that is a far lower States version of that
Person at likes
Some sort of a church that
It was a little bit weird and they wanted him to
Youth group or something like that and he's
Is that story whatever emotions he felt
Threatened
In that
In that moment when they like you should be a part of our group but they give a lot to offer whatever
That that's entirely possible
I don't know I think we drift into you like
The possibility of
Irresponsibly psychoanalyze
I know you're saying is appropriate
But if we get more specific
Feeling very hard
That does describe trauma
The details
Who f****** know whatever happened
This guy was traumatized
Whatever his details are are secondary to the fact that he is describing
A very real trauma that he experienced
Regardless of a group
You know or tearing in a biography of
Deeply troubling stuff
I don't know why
You want that to be
His backstory
It's not true
Yeah
Better now
Because life is just
For boring I mean I guess he could be from a from a standpoint
Could be
Trying to elicit
You know like
Look at look at how f*****-up my childhood was
But then I don't understand
A patent office bragging
Aggressive
It's just macula
Posturing
And a lot of it
Like at its core like a lot of those stories
Even the ones by like
Does prabhas f****** the seven
13 Gibraltar
The macho posturing
It's a high-school kid reflux
The teacher and everybody gives
Hi-5 and you're like no that's
But Depot
We f***** up bright
Answer this next clip
Aregularguy
I would like a bunch of people
It's like
Darth Vader
Fight
I was a kid
That's gross
That is
2 problems
The first thing
You said the first time I bash someone's head to the concrete which applies there was nothing
Oh yeah not just
That one time I did
Evan second because I got higher than
Inhale
I got
I got it
Villanova drug Xperia
Off closet
Pain to somebody
Concrete
I felt
I felt like I got you an elevated state by causing
Movies playing
That is
David David Wong
Wrote a book
Call.
Futuristic violence
T suits
I really love that book
And the main villain in that book
Is just the essential Ave
Avatar
Toxic mask
Masculinity
And his
Huge deal is just
By this
Violent
Bulshit
Masculinity ideology that I have
I feel the juice
I feel the edge
Adrenaline
Greater than any feeling in the world and I'm
I'm destroying the week in order for the the true Superstar
Society to be built entirely around the adrenal
And eats like crap
Yeah it's just
F******
Disgusting
It is
Just
The point is they're going through all the like he's
He's being described in his actions are
Such that
It cannot be more obvious
That pictures
Masculinity
I don't know what to do with those sorts of things like
Get really tough
Because like
I mean I don't know
There's a world that
Exist
Who's making all the
The concrete he talks about it a lot and talk about it
So like
If possible he's making that up
If he isn't
He's describing
Taking great pleasure from do
Which I f***
He's making it up
He's making it up in service of saying that he got great pleasure from it
Which I also hate
Because that's also part of his brain
Then he's imagining what it would be like to be on the concrete
And thinking I probably
Getting really high doing
There's no way around that the Dozen
Describe someone who is
Deeply Disturbed
Yeah
Even if it's in self-defense
Like I understand
Punching somebody
Is there, yet
Or whatever
I'm not going to I'm not going to I hate violence in all its forms
But I'm not going to the
Say like self-defense is bad
Or anything like that well if you're Christian
There's that whole turn the other cheek
Right
Look
I don't
There's any Circle
That's where you're banging
That is justifiable
I don't believe
And then
Imagining or haven't
Response
Did you get high and enjoy it
Is just your monster
Absolutely disgusting
Real or not you are a real or not monster
Yeah bro
I-88
Enough
Years into this where
It does kind of seem as though
Our least I feel like I have a certain
Can handle on
When Alex is
Making something of whole cloth
Write and when
He is exaggerating something they did
Yeah exactly
There is something
Too many of these stories
Trauma
Did
Happened I don't know the details
It's not it's not the same as what he's making
He's like my
My grandpa was German
Yeah if he was completely made up there would be either the
I don't want to get into it
And I'll leave it as like a
Hyper detailed like
To the concrete I remember because he was wearing a nose
T-shirts and blue jeans shorts
Send you know there would be those hyper-specific
Take details
They kind of tell you you're just f***
And making this s***
He's done that on some occasions
Some of his violent stories
He's on his own show
He's not doing it
Here on this Epic
Stick is really
Important
He's telling he's really f*****
Top stories
Kind of owner
The idea that there f*****-up
After
Like two clips prior I believe
He said
I'm brain damaged
There's no doubt about it
Yeah
When the kid dropped you on your head
What effect did it have on you physically
It was by the field house
Cuz it's cousin attack man I beam up
Wesley Chapel
When I got up
He couldn't understand why
Energetic
Equivalence
You don't understand being the hammer
Anime
What happened after that
I mean I lost
I love you slam I have the ground
The concrete crack
She was like only as bottagra
Know that story
Did you go to the hospital
They didn't check your head
Do you telling me that pile trap
Episode 11 in the gym
Reading my check to see if you have a severe concussion or anything
I mean I don't know
That's f*****
I don't believe the concrete
Broke
His head was split open any of that stuff
Because the force that
It would be required for
Either of those things
What happened
Would probably
From that
Maneuver
Now that it's just
It's just hero story invalid
Yeah
But he's
Presenting
Freeware
He didn't have
Hospital they didn't check
Checking for a concussion
He just went to jail they stowed him up and then let him go
If that is
Reality
This is
Huge turd
Yeah even if the key is broken
Even in the eighties
Which is around when this would be happening
Even then
You would still at
Go to the hospital if you were bleeding
Profusely
And required
Stitches
So the story being that he went
Straight to jail
I'd suggest otherwise
Kind of a kind of suggests that he's making up a little bit of this whole it
Entirely
I mean baby who knows
Pull-A-Part's
There's a lot of this here
Nonsense
Earlier
We heard him talk about this
Going around with when he
Who choked him out
The first time you got
But turns out
Used to choke each other out
The fun quite a bit
I did that
I've heard this from a lot of people
This is not part of my childhood
But I've heard it
The number of times
This clip
Is so f*****
Cuz he's talking about it
Scrying
Talking about
The memory
Of being choked out by his friend lost
Didn't you say that when your friends are choke you out you that was his long dreams
I have three lights
What time I
They choke me out also
Horse
Evan White
Thousands of years ago
Lifetime lights
Am I growing food
It was like
Just a moment
Kids everything
Kids
And get starving
People attacking us do you think all that information from your ancestors somehow or another encoded somewhere in the car
That's
So f***** up
Here is what I will say
So this wasn't a thing like when I was working at God can
And it was
God can
So
I was there for a full month
Or whatever and
That was living in the
Little cabin bulshit
It's with other people around by
Some of whom brought this whole thing up
Hangouts
And I remembered
I remember doing it and
One time I do remember this feeling
Like
I woke up and I felt like I had lived in
An entire differ
Like I remember there being a different thing or whatever it was
Not going to cry about it before like
Weather
Specific alucinacion
You have
Waking up
From being choked out with like a euphoric state
Yeah I heard that
People who are into like
Like
Play Within sexuality there is
To get choked out
Pleasurable
Experience
Controlled environment
And I'm not going to judge that I am going to Judge Alex
Political commentator
Coming on Joe Rogan
In the show
R5
Or so of the show
Pretending
Esoteric spiritual truth
To him and his body is choking
Route
And then
His children starving to death and living as a farmer
Yeah
It's insane like
Yeah I don't
I understand you not wanting Rock
Response
You really think that
People are
You know like your aunt
There's so many points when you should hit
The eject but
Yeah I love this like
I'm across the table with a lunatic
Right I thought we had a friendship
He said he was going to politically
Hang me up like a
The pig and slit my throat
Right and I don't know how you could do that
JoJo rabbit
Politically
We made we made peace with
This long conversation on the phone that we
We had
He pretended to apologize for Sandy Hook
I didn't realize you was lying to me
Through most of that
Who's had a very weird
Conversation that is going to bunch of places
Now he's high
He's telling me about all this
Brain trauma that he f****** had from when he was younger
Yeah
Choke him out
You loved it
Edit connected him with his ancestors
I wish
There was an opportunity
For him to
Actually have
I wouldn't say backbone
That's not
Because Joe is
You know he has back
If he wanted to
Could have
Push back against our
Exact
Curly Howard
Right like it's not that easy
Coward
He doesn't have the wherewithal
Even if the present
Automotive
And he should
Because what Alex is describing
If wife
Unchecked
Appears to
Normal
For Heroic
4 funny
Any of those
Three possibilities
You walk away
What Alex is describing is
Deeply
Play f*****-up so
Situation
And
You don't have to call it bad
But you don't have to allow it to
Representatives normal heroic
Or
Yeah this is not except
Nope
Solar eclipse day are just Alex
Super high
Drunk
Trying to talk politics
It's a little bit
Oh no
And he said he wanted
But
He also want
There's 100
Thousand people watching
Weis
And he wants to keep it going
Which is why
We've gotten to the point we've gotten too already right
But these next
After the headliner goes up the hose
Tries to do another 10.
That was
That's not
No
Alex is holding
Very polite
Almost to their detriment
Looking
I know that Joe could have done better
And actually I'll get to that
But before we get to
That Alex
F****** dumb
Things
About politic
Or at least his political
The first one is about the LG
Trans people in
All right he shouldn't be
I know and this position
Disgusting
And probably one of the worst thing
You could have
Other than ounces
That is all trans
People are pedophile
Which
That's the worst
This
But where
On the way
Westside this is
The Japanese
Taxpayers will pay for it
You sit there and do it
So there's two problems
Who's that one is that he just too
These teams
I'm sure they're more that I want to highlight
What is the east
I think the trans women or the only
People who exist
Because he only talks about these issues in
In terms of I chopped dick off
Yeah because that's the only way.
Yeah you know like cuz I understand
That's f*****
That is that is exclusionary and it erasing the entire
Men
Or people
Oliver the gender Spectrum
Exactly what he believed
Is what's being talked about
Second
Very repulsive
The idea that
Trans people
Need to get surgery in order to
Prove it
That they believe what you know like
Whatever
Hey if you don't get surgery you don't mean it
Like that kind of thing is it
Exactly what Alex
Is
Describing
Is position
If you're not willing to chop your dick off then
You don't me
And I don't
I'm very sorry
Of people setting
Whatever say
Of of
Proving you're right
You
You are there
Great I'm libertarian
Auto Care
I'm not judge
At the same time
Autocorrect
Oh you couldn't
You got no
Then you're already wrong
Including the second clause
Which is you need to
You get surgery for me to validate your
Identity
It's f****** awful
I'm a libertarian
Don't think I'm a pressing
And then say
The only way I will acknowledge you is if you
You do what I
What is my bench press
It is like I believe the Japanese model
Muse model
Who is
Sure
Cuz I don't care I don't like
I'm a libertarian
I believe
So cool
Your bigotry cure bigotry
Trying through an Express I'm not a big
I don't care you're smarter than everybody
Yeah Q
It would
Prefer
I would genuinely
Prefer it if
If you just said
Trans people are gross there when I don't
They're weird I'm threatened by them because I love masculine or whatever
Voluntarily relinquishing
Masculinity as if that's even
F****** thing
My worldview is dependent on this
Buy a system
This bifurcated system
And there's a Power Balance that is intrinsically within it
It anything that's
You're ruining it for me
And it's the only way my brain works
And I
Some men are actually identified as well
Women in surgery in order to identify as women
Totally valid thing and it's something that everybody should respect
Didn't care about that muddies the goddamn water
Hoodoo
F*** you
If you because of
Just said it was gross
Then we can have a conversation
But if you hide behind it is though
He is the reason that he jumps from A to B to C.
Yeah
It's the same story
Do you have to
You have to just
Make an audit
In order for you
The red flag
Around
I did so sick of it
He were to just come out and say what do you mean
You're saying
Which is the
I think this is gross
It threatens my worldview I'm scared of this
I don't know what to do with it
Then you could
Coolest talk
He's the Matador who hasn't
Trained or what
He's a Sitting Duck
He knows that that
Is bad
Use the red key
Right ever whatever
Dumb narrative
It's the thing that all of these people do when they're talking about
The lgbtq
Cute
It is always this
Idea of
If I were to say my real is
Which is bad
I'm grossed out
Not understand
Then the conversation because
Why
Why do you feel that
That's a no because then they have to wrestle with
It's not that they're having a problem
They're not having a
I am
Because of my problem
And making their lives
Deal with the
Feel this way
It all falls apart
Because I think on a on some emotional level
They recognized
That what they would have
Dilworth
With that wife
Entrenched power
Those are unwilling to unpack
Right because I have a privilege that is
Unpacking that suitcase or whatever is
Unwilling or unable
Able to do
It does
Make good sense
Syndaver open
If you can find some store
The way to
That is never the cobra
Yas track from
Yeah
The Y
Find out why
They're distracting
I'm having to talk about
With other thing
External because if they admit the Y
They would have to
Too bad
Fronts the reality
Or that have to
Given that they have to accept that it's actually their problem
F****** tied.
Does alien ship
He's talking about and then finally
Presstube
Stubblebine
The unpacking of the
Yeah
Don't want to
Because now you lay your cards on the table
That's why
Yeah
Talk.
Do it come on
Come on guy I know I know
In high school
There was a kid who
Was
Just very gradually all he did
He started
Signing his
Name on paper
As
And
That was the way she
Came out
And most people didn't even notice it
Most teachers didn't even
But it was such
Such a powerful thing
For her to have just
Done that
In a way that is
Not
Just amazing
I would never if if
I would never have had
That's incredible welcome so much horrible things
The possibilities of the bullying
And whatever people
Control of her identity in a way that is
Is more powerful than
I could hope
To do
I like itching
Incredible
So he can go f*** himself
Whatever
Not whatever I didn't mean that to be
But in this next clip Alex now brings it
Re-stuff
What you've already heard
He loves Korean food
There
I think is one of the
Practice
Black people
Cuz that was really expensive
Concierge
What the hell is one was like
They were like oh my God he's
I feel like I should give you context
But also allow you to live in that gross space
But that was brain works
Expressing
Have you started that clip by saying I don't go off of
Money
And then the end result of it is
Spell by-product
Which isn't it awesome that I show some
Sort of compassion
Towards a black
Then all of a sudden black people buy products from me
Weird
So what are you talkin about is that woman who drove her car into a barricade at the White House
And she was shot
Hey the f*****-up
Situation
Wouldn't have happened if
German car
Barricade
I don't know all the details that's
Situation
I do think it's
That I could bring that up as like a
Evidence
He cares about black people
Yeah face on all the other stuff we know about her
And what
Let's let's bring the one black woman
Great
You did it
You've solved
Racist
Pile of
F****** garbage
How
Goddamn dare you say
We all knew it
That the reason was
Purely
Money motive
But
God dammit
The end on this
So there's another good
Five
Weather just like
Who needs
Click click
Enjoy
Press stop record
The his five-hour episode 20 or the actual
Mtume
When Alex is saying like
Crazy eyes
I just
Maytag
Conspiracy of
Person who is
The victim to self
Black people
Bought my shoes
No living black person has ever experienced as much racism as
Is Alex is it
Experienced from
He also said that
Is the new Martin Luther
Yeah
So
We come to the end of it and like I
Don't
First of all Queer four-and-a-half hours in
Episode
Hey everyone who is
Complained about our short episodes
Go suck a lemon
Second
I didn't that was
It was a little
But I do
I know I know you do
Because I
Are we always go to
Too short
Anyway
My point is I didn't want to do
Episode
Cuz we had a lot of fun with
Various
Yeah but I do. I don't
This was
And I don't think
More attention should
To be drawn to it
And I do
Recognize the
Sort of
Hypocrisy of it
To a certain extent
We're doing an episode about it while saying
No one should
To pay attention to
Well I mean the very is the Hardline for us to walk the very concept of our show is
We cover Alex
Jones
Which
By necessity means
We have to bring it
Alex Jones
So when Alex Jones does a
Stunts in order to get attention
Weed
I have a certain responsibility.
Cover it while at the same time
Recognize that we are
In a way participating
Again the very thing that he
Desire
Initio of
You shouldn't cover it
.
Edgemoor you should cover
For him
Inappropriate
Is what you mean
As opposed to
Do what he wants
Do I
Cover
Cinebowl
Questions about this
Episode is only because of that pro wrestling
Vagueness of like
I don't f****** know what he's lying
Hang about here
Yeah you know how much of this
Is blustery bulshit
So there is there is a part where we're taking
There's a little bit of faith
On our end
Should we care that he's talking about
Basically being statue
Raped by a bee
Abusive women
Repeatedly
Should we care about that I mean
But
Is it a lie
Is it a machismo
Right
We deal with him by whatever
You do the best you can
I like Alex with Steve pieczenik we do not trust
Blindly
Our source
True
Amen
The bigger issue is
The conversation about Alex
This is kind of moot
To some extent
Because we know him
From his
His Works Ferg
This is just Alex
Really f***** up on a show that
Uno's
It's way more traction than
And he's trying to
To appeal to Joe's audio
All these alien Dumbo
Did aliens and meeting
My dad
Did
Cyborgs and all that s***
All that stuff
You get
I'm
Pointed in Rogan
To a very soon
Serious degree
I understand why
He did what he did
Be present
It is coming
From like a human
I love you you're my friend
Yeah I want to
Give you a fair reading
And I recognize that
You only lashed out at maybe
Because we weren't in
Communication
If you felt like you were on
Outside
And I was
Rejecting you
I think that's a dishonest
Of what Alice
I think that
I think
On one level
Way to accept
Embracing
King of Alex's
Wichita Falls under that heading of
Enable
Like Alex lashed out
In a wave
If not playing
Like I don't think
Planet together
Alex plan.
It was art
Official
Sure but did Jose response to
If not playing
Is the worst
You could do
In these circumstances
It is allowing a
Behave the way he
Lead up to this
With the stunt aspect
Bummer to hang you up like a
Stuck pigs
Throat politically all this s*** yeah like all that nonsense
He allows him to behave that way
No
Alex
Exactly
Which is
Yeasty rolls
5 hours
With Jose audio
And Joe's Auto
Will think
This is one of the most a
Episodes ever
Cease having access to
Space aliens
Alex get back any of their father is a
Used in with Wernher von Braun
You get back any of this stuff up it's not talks about normally
At least not anymore
More vague
Vague language Papa
With the
This is him
Posturing
Joe is allowed him
Essentially
To come in
In Rec shop
He is just allowed
Maybe like
Aren't you interested
Not all of them like B
Enough of them
It'll probably give
The blood infusion that he needs
With the
Is inability
Get new people
Call Ann
He's taken
Dumb people
Listen to Rogan
Know about alley
And fed them
Is marketing
He's giving them
Fusion that he needs
Things going
For a little bit
And that I think is it
Pathetic Act
Grogan weather is intense
Pure or not
You got played he got played
Firepro exactly this is boiling down to to reality
Rogan
Nose
That
Alex was playing him
Rogan
To accept it but yet
You probably knew
Either he knows
Allowed it because he
Also
That it was a thing
That people would come to his show
So either with cross on his part as well
Or
Rogan
F****** place
Like there's no other option
To look at this
Either
I steer towards
The ladder operate
JoJo behaved on the
Like I said
Play where you talkin about how like
This is the Alex I know in love
Right I want
Able to see this version of Alex
It's fun we're laughing we're having right time
That sort of thing
There is dispersion you're describing is a manipulative piece of s***
I think that he doesn't recognize
So many
Give the things that he
Funny about Alex
Are the
Tools that Alex
I wish you realize
I'm doing like
Yes all that stuff
Is a tool that
To manipulate
You talkin about
At the same time
Rogan
Years that is
Disc
That's it that's funny
I don't I
Is that track with all people Gaston dad
I know
The letter as well
And it does seem like Joe is coming from a good place
Position
And he doesn't realize that Alex
Is not actually a spy
And he should have listened to me when I was Joe's dad
And told him that people who lie to him to his face
Hernandez friend
If only
And also Eddie Bravo
Is dumbest yet
Still probably 60 I agree 100%
Longer with just Jo and Alex
He probably looks better
Oh yeah
Getting him in there is a rogue variable
Really
Exist
Close to listenable
Anyway
I hate this
But I hate I hate
This
Think Joe
Wrong
Regardless of his intentions
Could be great
Could be coming
Play Swan
Whatever
I don't care
This is garbage
Amateurish
He's allowed
Just say all sorts of things
Indifferent
Ansible on his show
And he has no idea why there
And that's the
The problem that's the problem
Sick people we have this fun time having these conversations
That's cool
Your infested with
Manipulator
You have
People within the
Agenda
You aren't having a conversation
That's the problem
They're having a conversation
With your listeners
And your watch
Exactly
You haven't conversation with Duncan
Trussell Ari shaffir
Joey Diaz
Tom Segura
These people
You guys just
Spitballing ideas
Maybe you guys say some stuff
Pretty f*****-up
You're that is what you want the show to
Reduce it to be
Being like
Vaccine standard
Held with
People like Alex
People like Jordan
Peterson bio eunapolis
These people coming on Dave Rubin
Candice
These kinds of
People who are
People have an agenda
They aren't there to
Time
And f*** around and then whatever conversation happened
There there
To push something
And they
Exploit
Your position
Of like
And that is it like
Here's a
If you're listening
Go ahead and text
If
Somebody's somebody should be your friend
And I will tell you
Hard yes hard
Very simple
Alex
Shouldn't be your friend
Depart now the problem is
His principal or whatever he thinks
The show is
But it's a good idea
Yeah he has
People playing
Who are subverting
Format
In order to push something
Then he doesn't want to be
Associated
He becomes a soul
The extent to which is a willing participant
Or
A victim of it
I don't care I have no idea how much
That is okay
Either way proof of the pudding is in the
And the response
And the end effect
Is that
Negative message
Skip perpetuated
And go unchallenged
And that is what we
Thomas episode
So I would like to end
Joe Rogan
And Alex
Joe
Come on man
Alex
Hope you die bro like this
Hope you don't have a heart attack by 55
Find
Hope you have a heart attack
Well there's still time
Anyway
Weaver
We also have a Twitter
We are on Facebook
We're on iTunes we're on overcast we're on Dog the Bounty Hunter next week is that
Well then we're not review
Tetra tell your friends I don't know
This might be a terrible
The plugs and
No it's kind of bonus
I get
There will be some
Some criticism of
Hey Eugene cover when Alex said this
Or whatever
Okay
We could not cover covers the entire episode
Without doing 10 hours
Yeah I was going to say we covered the stuff that matters over all the clips
In an hour
Would you say
And we did about
Four and a half hours
Bulk
Of the actual show
An hour
Worth of
Actual audio from the
If you think
Uncover something
You think is important
Ask yourself
Is it something we've covered on our show a bunch
That's a good question
If it's if it
It's not ask yourself a second
Does it matter
If you're new to the show
Start from the
And that good luck
And take two years to listen to it because if you've Mainline it there is some
Some trouble
Don't do that
We love you I would say
That
Eddie Bravo
Is a choke outs
But I don't think you
He's killed anybody
I think we would have known if Eddie Bravo
I think it would be in the
Authorities would
Describe the almost
A guy in this episode
Great detail
And that's not what I'm
Because he is also
Technically
Probably actually killed somebody
Holding
Alexandra First Time coloring with huge fan of your work