Alexandra Thurston color
Hey everybody
Naked in public
Streaking
Something that you probably do while drunk enough time.
Remember it
That's not what we talked about
The last week
Bob Breck
Long episode about Alex
Do we need a break we need to reset
Excited
We've been in the world of Project Camelot
So that is what we going over today
I like to give a shout out
Do a couple of people
Who signed up
And are supporting the show
You are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Megaman next not Louis Malle policy walk
Alex
Thank you and I will probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
We appreciate it oh so very much
So Caleb you are now a technocrat
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Palatka
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Legacybox
Sports bar website
I want to see real quick Rogan episode Iowa's
I was editing
Took forever
Got into a little bit of an argument with someone trying to f*** with me and
Twitter
I got really excited about it in the right headspace to be like
The actual interaction and then like
I started to see you like
Why haven't I
Hookahs.
With social media and stuff like that I just don't really care about it all weekend early post whenever
Off all social media
The future
Like what people
Completely
Happens to me every now and again I got really excited about the possibilities
I'm going to be on this posting all the time I started following some listeners who was suggesting that I
But I've never go to be posting stuff not caring about Twitter at all but
Windows are where I thought like I'm following I'm going to build this account
It went so fast
Yeah remember you are G
Ram
That is a Liquors look like
Interact
Yeah
Social media presence visual brand Ali
F*** you this soon as I wake up
What were you think
The reason I got off Twitter was because it was
Wow you're really funny
Let me follow you on Twitter on Facebook and on Instagram
I don't really
Do that he's like as like weird
I think I've ever wanted to do
I just deleted everything that night yeah so anyway that's to say
That's just expect that I'm jumping in and actually going to
Probably
Probably not he's got this project
This is an episode where Carrie sits down with a gentleman by the name of
Jer subok
Alright
He's a bit of a yeah I don't know how to phrase this
He believes
That he has decoded a universal language behind all language
Okay
And that the aliens are f****** with us through our line
That's kind of his big promise
I think that's the plot of snow crash
I think it's the plot of a number of things
Pierre subok
Man that's a great man
Eclipse
Consultant
For Ridley Scott
I can find a citation on that other than
His own website was written with his input
Has been involved with
On my radar is
I believe
I don't give a s***
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy
Project Camelot and very happy
Today
I have a fascinating guess
His name is
The Box
And I we are going to be talking about
Holographic
And the secret
Hidden alien code in language
Very exciting
There is a secret alien I like it find out
How would it even work
I would say that it's mostly involving snakes and words that have to do with snakes
I wasn't the whole thing and I don't know I think you just doesn't understand
Bring up repeatedly
Big question
Can he speak
We in language
Like
Because of
Speak of f****** a lot
He doesn't like Carrie get many words and you being very rude
Peter jumps
Into the proceedings
And he's going to lift off
Strike you it sounded like they're relevant to linguistics
I studied theology at a level
I Got a Name
Theology a level
So real quick just because we're in the United States grew up in England
I still think he's French space-based
A thing which
Might be a bias on my part
I'm going to leave it alone
A-level education is done in high school
It's a part of college prep course work somewhere
Equivalent to but not the same thing is
By AP classes
The G-Class in 80 level
It sounds like
I'm happy about that I'm sure his mom like that on the break card but
High school so I can tell you very certainly
Pieris
Your only contact like really with formal education in theology which isn't even linguistics
I got some
Opportunity informally to go to office today theology
By teaching you a professor on this professor was looking for them
Basic basically with the right credentials
So which are you
So I would
Phone number of years
Apologize
I got an agent and I kind of exhibited within London at st. Martin's
It didn't really turn out
Chihuahuas fight difficult to up next living as a pulse right on sister
People
To make a living
Now basically video advance of the computerized
Twenty years ago it was extremely difficult
So then I did a teacher training costs and I talked or not
And I did this for about 8 years
Increasingly became interested in occult symbolism
So I decided
Take my job and focus full-time on
So you wanted to do that
This makes no sense
To be a really interesting
Figure out who are the people behind the presentation
And he's just like trying to figure out like what the words and he
His bio Eva
Where flummoxing
He's presenting himself as like
Expert in
Secretive
6 would make sense why you try and make everything
Assertive
You responded to what does it mean
To be informally
If I understand history correctly he was asked
Informally to come to Oxford because one of his
Former teachers you a professor professor and they were like
We need somebody with the right
Credentials
In Oxford
And those credentials I assume
Being
A friend of a former teacher that the professor
Scholar on Ancient language
He has a degree in Fine Arts Pacifica
He claims he's starting to Urology in formal offer to study at Oxford
No sides
Turn it down
It really doesn't look like Pierre
Actually studied any of this.
Informal
Which is a huge problem because ancient languages are infinitely
Complexity
Often disagree with them
The finer points but etymology
If you read his bio
He claims that he turned down his offer to go to aux
Statues
Degree in painting in art history
At the University of Wales
Interesting late the University of Wales isn't really the University of we understand it it's a system of universe be spray
Read through Wales
Biggest schools in the system are adverse with Bangor
Example not the University of Wales
It may just be an example of him putting it really weirdly
I find it a little bit
Degree in painting in art history so even if he's telling the truth it really doesn't matter
He does have a degree in pesos
Whales because he's talking to Carrie cast
So he did not graduate from
Possibly I mean the way I look at it like you could say the University of Missouri
What you do your references University of missouri-columbia
University
But there is a university system like there's a um Rolla there's other like satellite
Yeah if you graduated from University of Missouri at Rolla you probably say you got a degree from
I'm have you right
Maybe I don't know it's not like it's not like many people would say I graduated from the University of my
Miami Ohio
University of Miami Ohio
Music like that
Are specific to a certain thing you're studying
Okay satellite campuses will have like a really good act program
Different places I went
The school I got that
Degree from that school
I don't care to spend a whole lot of time on this but I just thought it
Because that's
Not expensive
For learning
His credentials cuz that sounds like a really
So I can see him
I really think that's probably like preschool education
Dude
You're so close
Between 2002 and 2014
Better able
It's not
Someplace where he could have learned two languages or got credentials and
Linguistics
It's more an indication that he was probably on a track
Becoming
What you described in that clip in the early 2000s
Workout
The further reinforces idea he claims to have been a member of the ins
Which is a specific level of their organization
Annapolis diploma related
The teaching and specific formal tea
Teaching
In order for Pierre to a bit member his educational path
After his art degree
Would likely have had to have been in
Is it further bolstered by the claim
That he holds a postgraduate
Application in further and higher education
Education which can
If you're not paying attention sound like
I have a postgraduate degree
In some form of higher education
A degree in education
So he is
He was on a teaching path and then decided
I don't want to do this I want to f****** talk about aliens
I can read words
Whatever
Eddie presents himself now
Pierre is a leader in the
The field of biology
Which is described as quote
The study of Angelica vessels through religion and mythology
I'll go ahead and admit that you're the leader in that field considering he made the word up and I'm the only person besides
Whenever they're read
Skype
Also in 2010 pierce the back with a guest on the overtly Nazi leaning and white nationalist show Red Ice Radio
Unfortunately their shows are behind a paywall
Listen to it but the description of the episode includes this
We discuss Zionism
The connection to Mars ritual sacrifice or the origin of the idea of a holocaust
That doesn't make me feel great
If you're going out of Nazi sympathetic show to discuss quote of the idea of a holocaust
I'm pretty comfortable assuming you don't think it was a real thing
Questions about it cuz I might
There's no way to create a fake account
Yeah so this guy seems like he doesn't have any credentials
You be saying things
But he does about linked
Little bit
May or may not have been a fine
Green painting
An art history wanted to be a teacher his portrait painting business wasn't lucrative cuz the internet wasn't around
You know what is lucrative
Talking about weird s***
Great career path
Bebe
It's not honorable somewhat Noble profession
Maybe maybe you should
Still working my way
So this is what I found myself actually
Becoming interest
In this episode
Because before this
Kind of seems like
You've got a a weird but
Fairly common path of
Is is like
She's not going well
I'm going to Pivot into this weirdness
Yeah because
They know that there's large communities of people who are very suggestible
Fairly gullible
A bad with the word known as he's pretty good at making bad points
This is where I became
Interested because
Pierre in the next clip reveals what
2Pac
From being an art teacher
Into
Being this guy
He doesn't save this is what got him off track
If you pay close attention
Stoptech
You'll see that is exactly what is another book
Interesting office. That I found very fascinating which inspired me to research and children
The subjects
Aliens and then how we will Jam Define 189h last so
That there was the academic Robert temp
Send email the Sirius Mystery
This was a baby
Waste Management
The ancient amen hypotheses
Sertraline
Aliens
Facebook really awesome being bastard
My book studies Ancient Aliens in Hainan this is another book but until
Taking shots
Wow
I like it I like it
No
No is that about how SiriusXM
Mystery is a book published by Robert temple in 90
The book argues that a tribe called the dogon in the African nation of Mali
Extraterrestrials from the Sirius star system to up till present day
These. Talk to jougan about culture and art
And all other cultures from which all these cultures spread
Without Alien Force
Set the jougan we're talking
Star people
Was that was just to visit them
Surprised to learn that the jougan people were aware
Of the furious's
Compendium Stars which they shouldn't have known about since
Are white doors and are essentially invisible
So they wouldn't be able to tell if those Stars about them which people in other cultures know about
Conviction took note about
The fact that they did because they were relatively uncommon
Like they were isolated
This was not information to Robert Temple
To buy visiting the jougan
He learned about this star wisdom that they had from reading a book called The Pale Fox by Marcel Gruelle
And Germann
A pair of French anthropologist ethnography
Who studied the dogon
Groupon hotels in Amazing Stories
The dogon
Who told him if he's invisible stars in the Sirius system which they called
Tolo
It's a great story and really if you look at the world at the time it's super unlikely that they picked up isn't
Information from past visitation from other cultures cuz like you were at they were fairly uncontacted
And the people who had come did not appear
Do I have the
The information that they were relay
To these French
I kind of don't
Because that suggests there is an Eddy
Kind of oral tradition
From
Prior to any number of
It is
I don't know I don't know how I actually you that I'm not going to destroy this
No I didn't know existed
Unfortunately 1991 Anthropologist Walter Van Beek
Ultimately
They were offered a Coke
He found that a whole lot of the things that greeland detailing
He wrote this about the Sirius ID
Tolo interpreted as real as their name for Sirius
They disagree about it with each other as to which star is Matt
For some it's an invisible star that should rise
To announce these to do or the fast
Okay
For another is Venus
Guto lautz
All of them agree however that they were told about the star from Brielle
Well I think I think that there's actually an interesting wrinkle
Do this I think we're going to get to a deer.
Okay I'm not entirely clear about that
Stop the mail down
You want that so
Walked away from the main camp
Had to pee
Started singing the classic
Sirius song
Maybe stories complete
French Dudes didn't do this out of any actual
Evil intention
It's most likely that they asked
I misinterpreted our answers
Because they're reporting on the study wasn't overly sensationalized initially got very little attention
When it was published back in the 90
T30
Either way it's
Complete nonsense
But that
GameStop Robert Temple
Using it is the central
Surface Book
Arguing that the serious aliens were the route of human civilization
And his book has been a big
Piece of alien Cannon Everson
Gotcha
Gotcha noted that Roberts working on the Sirius Mystery in night
Is that Mentor was a man named Arthur Young who actually invented the Bell Helicopter
But was so disgusted by the
Nuclear weapons after World War
He completely dedicated
Themselves to be real weird paranormal stuff
I like it
He seems alright in a lot of his stuff is
Is around where I don't know if I like it
For that but
You like f******
She Too Young establish the foundation
For the study of consciousness
He would meet young enterprising Robert Temple
We'll go on to become a secretary
For the organization level
Super into the idea of the
The Council of nine
These paranormal conspiracy world when you hear about someone channeling alien information
The Council of nine is very often mentioned as 9 powerful alien beings
From serious and often have some sort of like
Creator deity
The motions
Right in 1952 the young was one of nine people who attempted to make
First contact with the council at a gathering organized by Andrea
Who Rich was a bit of a paranormal hype man
His most notable for introducing the world to URI Geller
Climbing The Gallery at which point
Quinones Hoover
Also Keller could apparently teleport rise stuff is true
A lot of the stuff that
Approval Richwood. Come out and say about gallery
Like that he had come up with while he was at the time
Lavagirl
I'm like that
You can buy anything if it comes from the Council of nine
Not just like
Do these aliens it was the Melchizedek order
B2 at 13 years after the Gathering young would tell a twenty-year-old Robert Temple about the French Anthropologie
Its findings with the dogon people
It almost certainly added a little bit of his own to it
People who study the supporting documents and the book temple ended up writing
How weak it is on evidence
30 must have been writing it to please his boss R3
Who was a bit obsessed
With the aliens
Some serious helicopter
Pricing
Hit my boss loves buck
This article about the dogon having contact with aliens
Increase
Temple by brown-nosing his way into a helicopter
Wound up creating entire f****** mythology behind alone
Erik von detten
I don't know exactly how the timeline works but
It's not like controller
But it's not like he's single early responsible for a lot of this stuff he's just a p
He's a big tender
Make make that might make it
A little bit of a surprise to learn that on the cover of the Sirius Mystery
There's a promotional blurb
From Isaac asimov's that reads quote
I couldn't find any mistakes in this book
Has like a piece of literature
I know that asthma doesn't have the best track record at least not
It turns out later clarified what was going on here
He sent me the manuscript which I found unreadable
He asked me point-blank if I could point out any errors in it and partly out of politeness partly to get rid of him and partly
Because I have very little of the book
True
I said I could not put out any certainly did not have permission to use that statement is part of the form
I'll just have to be careful hereafter
Perfect Saturday
Perfect story but it also speaks to Robert temples manipulative
Business like hitting that blurry
His work false credibility well done well done
What is a good Griff
The Robert Temple Road is shooting misleading book to suck up to his boss
Misinterpreted
7 Frenchmen
And that is what Pierre's the Box B is a major influence in his life
And that he said
The book made a good argh
This guy is
Super dumb
Yeah
Wow isn't that great a great story also I really like
I really like as above
Clarification
How dare he use this quote it's more like
My bad on this one guys
That's a delight
And now we get into like other in
Does the pr sabaq hat
And one of them obviously is David Icke
Is the
The paterfamilias of a lot of
Thesaurus
Omnipresent
David Icke
I also
Around
Probably around 2
It's contact with David ice work
NFL
Is research how absolutely I'm fascinating
I was a little babe
Dissatisfied with
She got a loss of this which sense is circumstantial evidence
Circumstantial evidence
Primary source
His dad was fuckingawesome I love anybody
F*** off
You know I I thought he was really at the Forefront you know his book about lizard people running everything
Unparalleled
Bakeries
Already I did firmly establish to someone who might be a good
Formal education
But it is next I didn't want to
Include all of the
Times you just rattles off words
Nail Wednesday
Instances that he talks about Greek stuff that I actually know something yeah we can talk about the
Include this is just sort of
Acrostic
Action of what
It's like listening
Him talk about his work
Cuz this
It's it's filled with pennies
Knock knock
Okay
Is just like listen
I just ate it makes me
Uncomfort
Symbolism Cindy true
There is a universal grandma
So for example
Different on numerous languages
Are you outside are the Mesa contumacious liverwurst or what
So you at work
Many different languages
Give you a few examples of the word play
In English
Wood
Versal of the word
La choza Pollo Loco
Gospel was the Roman god
The game within the Japanese
Coming to God
Hello, is a wolf
Virginia Arabic
Is Scott
Iowa
Will be out again so I guess though I'm not entirely sure
A little bit down the road
I can explain exactly why he's
Very wrong
Episode first of all I love that Robert Temple stuff
Highways
Not take the
Talk about stuff like that
But then I started to listen to
Just rattle off
These words and make connections between
Larger point that isn't fair that doesn't make any
Did it really reminded me of when I was
Fairly young I
Check myself
Cuz I was really depressed
And I was
I was going through this
And I checked myself out of it
Because the people there
Refuse to let me
And the roommate that I had in the room I was in
He would always be
Carrie rounded
Dictionary
And yelling at me
About various words
Profound
Be related to
To each other
But this is a preoccupation that Stumpy
People have
Rooted in
Mental illness
Right life of connections that don't exist
You don't realize it's hidden
Intentionally
And they put red at front of it which is why I
Need to happen on Wednesday
It's obvious Dan it's that level
Behind the time that I'm
Referring to
There's a little bit of a hostility behind
Pierre stock
Talking about if only because he won't let Carrie talk
It is the idea of like
Usurping
Ruler aliens
Dominating the planet
There is an anger that he has towards them
In his like
I've cut through their code
Let me freak you
No
But they're also got
Mention that I don't even have a clip of
Is there a dog
I'm up I like that
Human beings best friend
Yeah exactly
How are you I like
When they just throw in something that you're familiar with and they're like yeah that's also an alien
Yeah I know but that's what they all say everything
Anyting
Strfkr
Obviously there is Delia
Alright what about
Figure dogs
Absolutely
Small dog teacup dogs
Serebii
It's just nonsense
And maybe it's just me
Because I had that
But I did get really
Creeped out by listening to him just prattle off words
Later where I will explain why he's wrong about them and then explain on a larger sense
What he's doing
With linguistics
If you studied linguistics
He would know is that
But it just
Just is
It just feels like someone
Is a little bit
A little bit off
Little bit little trouble
I don't know if they're real
I'm going to go with coincidence
But in this next clip
Larger mythology
Mystic part of it out of it
Lot of the larger mythology
Come down to
Misunderstanding
Specific
And
Next clip
Pierre
What that thing is
Which was the creation of the original
Serafino Electric
The other is the Caribbean
Protohuman rice
Relationship The Rock hello and the High Spirits
So this is essentially the answer
No the unsurpassed was have corrupted by the Denny's
Danielle
Is really another word for a genetic engineer the engineer
Chase Bank
What's the song
You just basically co-opting Nas
Stick ideas
Consulted on Prometheus
Bulshit like that in the ology in high school's version of
Throwing
The anthroposophy the demiurge
The idea of
Stuff like that the first
Creation
Being that Realm
Ours is the secondary creation is created by the demiurge
Like that's that's a lot that that's a lot of stuff that's very complicated
That is very freaky
He's World an example of
Douglas Adams
People whenever they
Okay I'm going to take something you had this thing that you really probably don't know but
Same thing that you know
No no no and then it goes into
And then that is also this and this and this and then and then
Where is the
And so the whole thing that I'm saying is absolutely nothing but it's stuff that you already know that makes me sound smart because I'm
Differently
You know enough of it to know that it's
Uno
Greek word for man
The Greek letter for
That is not correct
8th District results
Okay
Explained
DPAC
That's a humans have taken
So really when we talkin about the adamic really talkin about Marsha
Interesting and shrugging coffee
Now obviously Mi 45 Destroyer
My understanding of this Sunday
Is that the seed of man was taken to the Moon
Systemic signifier of the money
Which is an egg
Second creation
So yes there was war in heaven established
There was a war in heaven
Mars destroy the Moon the Moon has evidence
By the The Pearl
Normal
I'm not sure why you had to outpost on the moon for a little while not sure what the point of that was
The Earth
You don't need to refuel on the moon or even I don't like
That's that's absurd if you make a trip to stop over there
Crazy so if you are going from Mars to be
To Columbia Missouri
And you stopped off ingested
On the way
Alright Jefferson City
Cool people from Missouri College Jeff City where everybody is in there
It's like maybe they left for Mars whenever bars was closer to the Moon then
Jefferson City is in its orbit
How about this one on there
How do we even know the moon was orbiting Earth at the time that this occurred
The Moon is real
What does the moon itself
I don't know
Project Camelot actually really great question
I'm sure he would accept that booking to start a change.org
To be the best way to do
Really asked whether the Moon is really imagine how much you would Gala Kari Jobe you the best
Just to use
Broad spectrum of knowing language
She's already talked a little bit about Greek
He's talked about
Hebrew
Did he think he can speak please
I want you to put a pin in that cuz Carrie asked him that later
It's not supposed to be a got your question but it ends up being blocked
And you of course need to say yes to this question
And then maybe speak
Little bit of one of those languages
If you just said
Yep I do know these languages
Cool let's move on
It's a problem that like if
Like I know this from my study of
Baseline understanding of ancient Greece
What are the things that I was very impressed with is
If you don't understand
The nuances of
Pacific language you're talking about
You don't understand the particular word
Because sometimes things mean
Completely different things
Depending on the context of the Sun
Depending on
Acquaintance of the noun
Think 10 min different think of the word f***
I don't know the context of the word f*** you don't know what the word Funk mean
Sterling
Totally there are those things
Idiomatic
Isn't that exist
You don't study the actual language
Your talkingshit
And that's what he's doing a lot of butt
S*** about Hebrew
Scary
Where your way came from the tetragrammaton
The word of God
Comes from directions in
Aramaic they would be like
Yeah that's the right way but it is
This is
We blow her show on
The same ideas and counted as well
Because the magic word
Yahweh
Hold on one second
Sorry
I'm sorry I was saying that
Emoji of yet Yahweh question the word
You think it's so funny to me that carry get the
Explain the word play involved in the name
God I love it
I every time every time her show is revealed in terms of like
Yeah
So good
Sayings that the tetragrammaton is a play in some ways on I am I was
Like that that's what is the idea behind
I think you don't prove anything I think you proved it
Okay how do you prove it all
If you were an all-knowing all existing all-powerful God
Your your presentation
To the
The people who are subject
Obviously
Would be in Powerpoint
Certainly
Then you would just stress
I am
I am I was I will be
That sort of thing
I don't I don't see any
Nefarious word
Replacing here I think I see
A very basic think I think
As I understand it and I don't know the store
But I don't
That's even like a nun
Conventional thought
Like I don't think
Oh isn't this week
Colors are cool
Pitstop minor
Ancient Greek
You don't get all the learning
You would have gotten at least a little bit of Hebrew
I doubt it
Because the Council of nine
Apostrophe
Yeah well that's
It certainly has taught college courses
On Biblical Hebrew
We learn more about
Linguistic play
I know that he hasn't established visit
Talking about is little bit
Play like cognates
And then like twisted around
Inverse dog
You bet like that's a whole thing
Supposedly
Dear that he is aware of
A universal language
Behind
Cities founded
Yeah
There is a lot of that going on
2 hours until
Long idle
Really understand what
He thinks
I don't know what Carrie is trying to get to other than
There's a lot of words that sound similar to Spartacus
It's tragic
Telescope
We learn about the word worship
Okay
Wows
That's not it
Distance
Interesting
Cattle mutilation is going back thousands of years old
Coupling what's happening within the natural world
Collection
Kenosha
The Angels is very important
So if just the brakes for a second
What are you talkin about is
UFOs
Upside down
I was thinking
He wins
The moment he said that he was like check this out
Exsanguinated
I just want to make sure that we're all on the same page
The word worship from
Angelica Schuyler
Disgusting
Angelic Silas with the boa
Worship
Because that's very
I'm not sure what that means war or w
Nor
Reference to a vessel
Flying Saucer
Yeah but I'm just waiting
It's nonsense
And ship
From the old English
Mike Skype
Which is a reference to a state
So it's a state of being Worthy
Is worship worthy of
Praise
Backpack
Has nothing to do with
Ships
That comes from a can
Completely different etymological
That sounds like something that you would learn if you were studying
Pretty simple really simple stuff but nope it's alien spacecraft
But we don't need to worry about the war part
I'm just upset right now
War war war war war
We did it yeah
V
I think that's the bigger issue here
Troublesome is low
Innocent cliff
Pierre discusses criticism
Democracy
Antenna
Stop plus his answer is not very good
U.s. mail around Hopewell
Next question that most people ask when I talk about
Wendy's worth
Save this generally is your scholar is opening in your academic
Community
Cuz this is b*******
Most of the time you're not coming from a great place to be if people are constantly ask if you're making
What's up
Of course he's real
Britain because the most polite way for you to say
You're full of s*** in Brittany
Are you sure you're not mad
Making
You sure I am giving you one chance
To say
You made this
I made this all up I'm going to tell you you're full of s***
Well if it's in a lot of different
That's a process
That's question
You're just going back to your bad Avenue
I need to talk about how you came
It's dicey
So
Number things that he says that at that same thing like God back
Gorgeous dog other languages words
Either a
Deity figure it out
To the name of a dog
Or something like that
And not worth talking about
Frankly put this next one
Absolutely
So I know a little bit about
You suggesting
Crazy
Lunacy
Remember
Call Integrity
So
And it's going back to veneration
Creekwood office surfing
Office worker this is why the office worker
What is the symbol of
Oh my God
Thrilled
It's pretty
Oh man
Cookie said something
It's very similar to Soros there and then
Office in Greek
Or opus
It's not related at all
Our word office comes from the Latin word Christian
Which
Pierre might want it
Into the word
A serpent
It's very
But they're very different words that
Roots that come from different places
It sounds the same but that's it
It's wonderful for you to
Have real
Knowledge
About etymology and how this guy is
Full of s***
But
At the same time I feel like anybody was even a cursory
Ability to critically think about this
Would listen to what he saying go
That is
Dum dum dum
Brc-2 Beach
Write Greek word
For serpent
Most common
That's the second most common
The word office from
Yes
If that is
McKay's
For office
Not that
Because that's what they're trying to communicate
So the plan is I understand his plan
For the Council of nine or whatever it is that we're talking about here
Correctly
What he said
Across
Timeline
Through different languages
In order to influence
By using this underlie
Secret language that connects all of them
Together
Manipulating ability
Did not extend
Before the Greek language
I just want to f*** with those people what they want
How what what's the word for office in Greek sound a lot like
Graph paper
What do people use in offices all the time
Directly similar to etymology Roots there I believe
Graphite
Graphite pencil for writing
Escape that can talk
Calculator
Graffiti
Conspiracy
Spectacularly really think the guy with the telescope
F****** sewed
Buy accents
European accent
She's like
Because if you imagine
Like
Southern twang
That
You know why we think what we think about the south right
Cuz it people like
But the guy is funny
Yes
But Pierre does
About what the Mayan
We're up to
As we all know wondering what the Mayans were up to in all of this
Believe that the end of the world
Skorts
Rare
Pretty clearly that wasn't good on him for that
Bye
Currently the scoreboard 199999
To what
But
Pierre has
Maybe about the Mayans
We're actually up to
When they were writing
Miss calendars and stuff
Possibilities trying to change the timeline
Possibility.
Mankind
Call Nelly
Clearly
Is correct
Essentially what we're doing this while living in the past
Some of these coaches are trying to do
Was trying to almost
Address
Well the timeline would be intensified the Next Generation the next calculation
Would be an explanation possible while they met another culture.
Attract
That
Was
Astonishingly stupid it's wild that was
Truly almost almost respectable in the level of idiocy involved
It's almost like
Even somebody who is stupid enough to believe that would be smart enough
Never to say it out
Well it's
Because someone who would have these ideas kicking around of their heads would be able to articulate
I can't prove it
Here's an outlandish thing that I believe in and it's definitely true
I read that weird restraint that he's showing that also I kind of
There's a part of me that resents
I really kind of
Captured
Like
Former WWE writers
WWE
Give me your wildest bulshit
Bernie Mac
Man that's
Stupid
Not as stupid as
Talking about Greek words
And he blows that blows it real bad
Cuz they knew that a crisis was happening eventually and
Or whatever
And they knew that back then they're trying to avert
Just trying to avert
Or something like that
I thought you meant I thought he was thinking that the reason that
We didn't
Knew we were going to die in
And so they sacrificed a s*** ton of people in order to change
Is the timeline
Because in 2012 we would have had a complete disaster annihilator
What is an agonizing come up with
Might be what you saying
Ballpark
Yeah a lot of underappreciated
Screwing up again
Greek
Basilisk is a second person
Basilisk off
A type of cake
So this isn't a long string of various cultures have
Words
For like royalty
We're just going through working gone through everything
I don't know or any of that stuff
I'm sure it's as bad as this
If this is example that I do know some
So the issue here is a misunderstanding how language works
There's a mythological being which dates back to at least the timer
Pliny the Elder kaldi basilisk
And plenty the Elder was right on everybody knows him now
100% Acura
Visit large rooster snake hybrid they can kill you by looking at you
The issue is that it was named the Basilisk because of the Greek word for
King beanbath Oleo
The idea that this thing is
King of the snakes
Sewing Greek it was called Bacitracin basilisco
Which is just a slight tweaking of the word to mean little King
Yeah that's all that is
It is proof of some kind of linguistic word placing
Hide the reality the world or at least
Bars Pierre comes along and crack the code
It's just a mythological creature being given a name
The story
Wanted to
Convey about the Beast
Mainly it's royalty
This would be legit as stupid as me making the argument that kings are notoriously all drunk
Because there's that cream ale out there called Little King
And why would the word be the same if it weren't for hitting reality about King
Aliens aliens
The name Bassett like basilisk
Comes from basileios come
Comes from
So like
Right
Is just putting the cart before the horse reimagining
How
Linguistic Evolution happens
And how things are named
Incredibly stupid
This is Baseline
Right now the French phrase Le Petit more
Is actually coming from because every time you came
Used to die
That's just trick
This french guy
You might be
So this entire interview in the basis for a frozen scholarship boil down to two
Phenomenon
The study of language
If you ever be much more aware of
He actually studied languages
These are what's known as false cognates and false
Friends
There are tons of examples
Words in different
Is it sound similar in
Even have similar meaning
Butterbeer
Because they comfort
Distinct etymological basis
This is what's called a false
Cognate
What are the most
Common and famous examples of
Is the word dog
Being the same in English
And in the Aboriginal
Languages
Despite there being no relation
The two cultures that would
Explain this, now.
We have to consider is that ever
Language contain
Thousands and thousands of
Possible the two cultures
Come up with the same name for
Vocabularies you're looking at
Eastbound
In some cases
Yeah
What's important here is that
These things are understood
Blue study linguistics
Because they consider the etymology of
The words and how these languages are formed
And where the
Influences
It's not some
Mysterious
And completely lost
And a false friend is Alex Jones Joe Rogan
Their words in languages that
Look like there
Connected it sounds very similar but mean
Thanks
These are what's known as false friend
And they're often the result of lying
We're just borrowing words
Assured Source language
Then tweaking the meaning over
The time
Call Pearson deck.
Pretend that just because of word
Great sound similar to word in Japanese
They must be related
As proof that the reptilians are playing
Tricks on us with words
Almost
Absolutely simplistic way to look at
Linguistics what about Dan the Native American group that
Spoke Japanese
What what
Group or whatever it is
Found that their language was
Strikingly
Similar to Jeff
Bright
Clearly mean
Haley
Contacted them and aliens
So we can assume that all
Chinese people are aliens
Getting into it I don't know what the explanation
Is or even if
If you're not making
It's up but you're not
There are plenty
Mayan
Is there a hundred different explanation
Cultural transmission
Happens
And it all comes back to the
Trade route
That happened to know it early
Early Times
All that sort of stuff
Could be that explains the whole lot of
Look I'm not an expert in the
I like languages
Stuff like that night
I have a
The water
In terms of knowing what I know about
But be
Because I do know that
I have had
To study some of this
Stop
That doesn't mean that I know what the same roots of things are anything like that
Buddy doesn't for my ability
I need to know how you
So that part is where I get a problem with him
Because these things are so
Easily
Like the Basilisk vasileos kind of
The prefix on the word for a kiss up and down both of blood
This is like
It's embarrassing
On a number of levels
Pierre
He's presenting fun
Siri
Namely that the reptilians
Behind everything
Pictures of language for
Course
And that's fine
I understand he's got a
New portrait
For the rest of his life
That whatever
Does indicate a realtor
Understand Linguistics enough to understand
This guy does
Not know what you talkin
In about
He presented his academic
Credentials
I have nothing to do
The subject
He's talking about
Complicate
That he has
I guess
Read an article
Is inspiration for all of it is a book
Yeah you are you correctly stuffed it up
It's one of those things where you are
Capable of
Tricking people who are not going to look at
The idea of getting super super high and saying look at all these words
S*** that does make a lot of sense
But if you're somebody who's like okay cool
That sounds like a
Interesting information
I'm going to take one more step and then
Inoculated himself from the second
Stop by
Earlier like
People come up to me and they say Pierre
You just make us up
He sort of shielding himself
From Carrie ask that question
Because he's
He's already a strawman caracat he's already brought it up and addressed it and salt it
To why this is sort of relevant
To our world
Like Alex Jones
The interview
About how long
Might have
Call language
Conspiracy
He wants to
Get into what she wants to talk
The Moon
She also wanted to also bring up
Maritime law
We're basic
Rule by maritime law Jordan Maxwell talks about satellite
Fibonacci
Steak
State is a mirror image of the ships which is
Of course
And stuff like that it's kind of
It's a metaphor
But they're also like
You have to consider again
Part in worship
Are
Current route
Just because they are the same
Same word
Anna written
The same doesn't mean that they come from
The same etymological Root Beer Crazy
He's obsessed with
Ship beef
Because he doesn't
Understand
Changing path that word
The reason that we are under maritime law is because and you can take this from the etymological
And time
Which means that we are married to our concept of time
You can mean
Happy
So we are happily married to
Set the timer.
Yeah
No we can't do that
Alien
I promise
I promise you I'm not ending this episode no way to make him look
Like
Kabul or anything like that
I've done is cut out
Rambling
Paragraphs of word
Ultimately
When I started listening
Who's this I was like
We have to do an episode
Because I love the robber
Yeah I want to talk about that
And then as it went along I like this Izzy
Desert
Eclipse
Because he's doing
Long paragraph
That he's just
Delivering
Need to talk.
This is
Tragic
And then you get to
The end
And where at
40 restarts
Mike maritime
It's unfamiliar
And I was like oh okay
Well we can we can
We can deal with that
I'm not making
He's an absolute moron
Duskull
Address
That he is
Is using
Language which he is
This is
Conspiracy
Byhalia
You're asking me if he addresses it what does that mean
Bring it in
Either
Female garment
You want me to
To put on a dress
Is that what you're asking me for
Then
Because the very words I speak betray how important the aliens are
Reptilians wanted when wearing dresses
Confirmed
Of any validity
Is it he then says
And I am working on a language that is under influence
One World Language bring up the fact that he
Is now working on a language that is unencumbered by alien influence
You can go f***
Well he did bring up at one point
Like
Is a twin
Call Weldon nevermind
Like telepathic
Good interact when they were younger course
And we all know from studies the twins telepathic
Really connect and then also have their online
Is there gobbledigook today
Everybody else
There is that in
But
I don't know if he like actually
Advances that as
Are we okay with twins
I don't know I don't think so
I don't think it's okay
So that I'm racist
There can only be one damn
Highlander version of fertilization
He's
Pierre's
Is
You like calling out word
Play
Past culture
Clearly
Because the serpent
And in this case that mean
Sort of the demonic
They love it there like
They're like those friends you have a go hang out with and it's just
Honda Accord like Non-Stop
I like that serious aliens
What aliens and run
I'm a big fan
I like it too but it does
A little frustrated
Oh no I already hate this guy and I wish I'd never talked
He's against the wordplay of the ride the surf
So you don't have to
What holds
I love just
Might be one of my favorites
Jose like
Man has always been battling the shores
Human languages
About this encryption
Which is a high degree of artificiality
The artifact is this
Idea of a universal grammar is
Prove with olive
These disparate words and
Four languages
That sound similar or appear similar to
Artifact
Artifact that is
The proof of the
Alien transmission of
Bababababababa culture
Linguistics all of that stuff which is like
Make that clear cuz he hadn't brought up
The artifact
Is juice
Leprosy
If you wouldn't come
All the woods
About the same
Because the language is working
Okay very very well said well
F******
Dance
Robert Whitehorse
Suggested like
We are really
Undercutting
Like rare really
Yeah that's
Seems like a cumbersome plan
Cuz it has to be
Been going
Chinese
As a language
And the morphological roots of the Chinese language
Thicker learn Chinese
In that time
These aliens could be do you know multilingual
Be that complicated.
Why do you imagine that it's difficult for them
Why not just introduce Babelfish
We have right now
Well this is
This is snoke explained it's never been made into a movie
Giving away the Tower of Babel
With the Tower of Babel
What happened was man freed himself from the dominance of the the nam-shub
The people who can speak
Things into
Tubi
Hypnotize all Humana
The Tower of Babel coming down and everybody not being able to see the camera on
The whole thing falls apart and that is
Protecting ourselves from from
And
She is an example of somebody who is trying to hypnotize you
Buy just really quick
Awkward
That he uses to surround dog equals God
And then he called it a day
I get man
There wasn't any point
Gravel Springs episode that I do
I don't understand how somebody could listen to him say one paragraph and not be like
I got it we're going to move on
Well and it becomes especially bad after the
This next clip where Carrie asked
And that we talked
Better
You actually speak these other languages I mean
Etymology
But I'm interested
Helicopter symbolism
So again when I'm I'm following an idea through an unthinking roll
That's not how it is
You can't be like
You can't have no awareness or understanding of these languages
Just look forwards
I get that
What is
Out of it
You're just
Looking on a very surface-level
Make an argument out of
No he might as well have just said
That you got a bunch of dictionaries
From all different languages
Any just
Closes eyes turn the page
Spin around and presses down on he's like okay this one says
Canterbury
It's like that's what he's described
Let me Care Bears
Came up with
Express
I don't know his tales are full of s*** to
It's the same
Is exactly what he's doing
It's just a embarrassing
Like
If you're presenting yourself
Does an expert you have to stop
You ever had
Yeah
Carrie cast
And you go on
Do you know these lines
You're not going to be asked
Prove it if you
She said yes
If you say no
Another language
Like
All you have to do is not say stuff like that
And then you could maybe sound like you know your schedule yet
But
I don't know maybe he's not used to having
People call them out
Also what's his
What is baseball
4 proof
Bounce
That's a good Baseline
My bad
So he says
So here I go into the English dictionary and I look in Latin
There it is
Oh there's this word in Chinese there it is
How many languages is
Required for him to prove that connection
Yeah right so how can you even
Consider describing a universal underlying language
When you only have a few examples from a couple languages
Knowing that there have been thousands upon thousands
Right
Doozy
To find like
Even prove it to be
Is totally up
King
Giving basilisk
Being
Mr. hybrid
Character
From mythology
He would then need to
Prove in other languages
Is there is a bad Leo
Connection
Being being
Cross trans
Through all of them
Instead of
Culturally
Ambiguous things
That are similar enough
Gabru from that
Specific
Is that whoever
Initially created
Mythological being
Impart that it was kingly
With that
Can't really prove that king equal snake
Right doesn't work
The only way his b******* would even be
Like
Considered
The only way that would be
Considered as if by some
Ridiculous
Diculous coincidence
Literally every human language
Dog memes.
Well there's only two
Do we know of one is that average
Right
Puzzle
Sweet mystery for linguists
Not really long time
But if it was like oh in Chinese the word dog the sound dog
Transfers to
Dog
English dog is Dog
And in Swahili.
I would just be like so much of a coincidence that you
You could not help but think maybe there's something by agreed that would be a Cause.
Take a step back
I still do
Approve anything
Because a lot of those cultures
Might have
Etymological roots of
Whatever dog is based on
That
Could be being
Played with
Between like cross-cultural
Like I know my my we've loaded everybody called the dog.
Play it still
Prove his argument that alien
Created language
Oh listen to you continue
Instead of like
Psych
Not kick him out of the office
Every language
Even an American and
French and different sign languages
Everybody knows
That that
That you are sitting on right there
Is an office
Everybody says everybody
Snake that's because of demons and aliens
Casual are they working against
The serpent is that everybody's ever really taken down and argue
You meant by saying
What about
Startups what is the sign of the serpent office in Greek
Like what if
Then Buck
System startup
Who are evil
Internet themselves
That allow you
Dress casually
They are there were two
Did the serpent sister
Right
How did you deal with that
Well we've been having the great Noti Wars for a long time
And that is not including people
But not as a major
Your player so you got Google
Right
Add a note
I don't know what you want to do that and imagine everyone their worst eyes cry
Google where's Dartmouth banking operations Binaca
It's those extra four letters that's what
That's why
Bakery
He doesn't know he's lying
That's one
I want
There's an inch
Justin problem
Without you even for people like
Who
Like I think I think there is
Intrinsic
Egyptian
Hieroglyphics
Are always a sore
About what
Imparted here
The perfect
Translation
Rise of a lot of hieroglyphics
Really understand
The idioms
It becomes much more difficult
I will say this
Does not study
Sometimes it takes a fresh pair of
I agree with I agree with me one
Primus
He's making
That is
Well now I think
He probably would say that but it's not part of his argument
I don't think there's a
Understanding
Any academic
Of the hieroglyphic
Language
From
I think that's probably I don't know I have
100-percent
I think that's the
Where he goes from there
Is not good
Very good
Probably going to disappoint a lot of y'all
I think we
Willa dealing with
Also a relationship
You have to understand.
Do not want this information disseminated
So there are if you like example
Heartless
Brookwood
Priest-class
Are there villain
From Context Clues
Okay I mean I never went out circulation in the priesthood know how to read
They just don't make sense
Agree completely
That
Ino just
We just want to say that I have noticed
Stop
If you study the glyphs
Listen
Explanation
They try to tell you what one thing
Looks like
It almost never looks like what they say it looks like and yet it does look like something
Castle
Concealment
The two things that are that
Just talkin over Cary
Very rude
Let's play this out
I'll be karaoke
You be someone at
That one
I well I was going to say that it
Actually looks
A little bit like my arms are crossed
Sakhmet
Who is
Eyebrows
Okay
Now there is a lot of room for interpretation
There are many different things that can go on it
100%
I do believe that we understand it enough to point to the fact that
This is been seen on many different worse
Chip sites for the godson
And so we can kind of draw from all of these conclusions that
They were most likely referencing this
I can see your frustration
Space
Ship
Alright
We're going to have to get you out of this McDonald I am a map
I imagine happens like I go around
I go to these tours
Hieroglyphs
People who are on the
Tours in the expert
They don't like what I see in it
That's fine. Two different conversations they're trying to lie to you
You about it
And then also I do
Just did I just say
Regard
Dismissing of Scholars
But because the people that he's claiming or lying about
Dedicated
F****** life
This research
This is another really important
Done what
A debauch
Is done
I love these
People are project
Is short circuit take a shortcut around
Like legitimate
Rigorous study right
Because people in academics
Things you study I don't know linguistic
Study evolution of
They study cross-cultural
Language
Did the way there
Uncultured then it's
Borrowed
Like
The form of
Actually
What he's done
Created the
Without
Any of the critters
Come to the academic
Because if you are you saying that his
If you are someone who is
In the f****** academic world
You were baking
Arguments
You would never it
Would never fly
All the academic world is is about
Being like
Let's let's look at what you're saying
And if you are right
Hooray
But if you're not
Perreo Sola
Because then we can refine our ideas
From there
Team from
And hope week
Figure out a way
That also help
Future Honest
And because he's not willing to
Engage in that process
Nephew lives entirely outside
Of the academic world but
Still pretend
The part of it
And all that does is
It's a cheat
Alex
I said Alex
Because in Ennis
They start
Talking about some really
Galaxy
Okay
And some of these things
Or exactly what
Heard Alex
On Rogan's pod
Also
Getting.
So there's a military structure
The reptilians again having a militant a hierarchy
Call structure
And they are where you get you know the Army gets
It's orders.
Absolutely centralized intelligence
Where we have there is Carrie a
Express exactly what Alex
Was talking about for a very long time on Rogan podcast
These alien
Literally speak to you are given the military and intelligence order
Stuff like that
That is the big truth that Alex wanted to
The drop
His you take all the military the general generals
Vmg and then they go into meetings
All that s***
That's what's being expressed by carry a stomach here
Like
What would
Look at that stuff coming out of Alex's mouth it's not interesting
It's exactly what.
Youth fox say
The point I want to make
Is that like
He's not treated like these
Bucking chute
You should be seen as a
You have
Yeah you're being like
Maybe he's talk
About some secret document I haven't read
He hasn't
Talkin about the same s*** that's on Project Camelot
Justice unfounded
It's really disappointing that everything is
F****** related to it
Like episode episodes about the Sandy Hook investigation and then the very next thing we do
Something modern
With
Tim and Joe Rogan
We talked about Sandy Hook let's do a project Camelot episode that'll be fun and unrelated
Everything and then bam it's right
Some of that is the sort of just the foundation of why this show exist
When we started this and the reason the Project Camelot is part of our sphere is because Thursday Loki
Connection between
Like it's not like
It's not like that
It doesn't always come up
Really important
It is the same
I'm sort of
That's why I named the show they're all con men
Or something like that you know
Play the longer Twitter handle that's for sure
It is
People are playing with
Masks
Maybe you're different prison
Yeah that is
Manipulating gullible people
Into heaven political
Who's that are f***** up and are really bad
It is up to earlier to talking about their like we're under maritime law that's trying to
Encourage people
Be Sovereign citizen
Ubisoft
That's what hard right is he
You know that
Boil
In Greek is actually basilisco so
Now that's hot
It's a coil office world
That's a good product
Where's salad office oil it's going to really do I don't know what do you need in the office
Through the day
That was one
40 /
About like
What Alex is bringing him
The world map
Much like a
Pierre I can't prove any of this
Partially in in
30 recognizes that
These sorts of ideas are really attractive
He might be able to pay
Yeah yeah
Even Project Camelot
Nurse who are
Into the
So the idea is it like
He's mirroring
Here.
Edit bases
Probably
Just alyx trying
His audience
Portfolio
The same time
Do you still Express
This next clip
Does a little bit worse
Because
Scary mirroring Alex
And not very.
So we're also talking about
Money
As being a form of
Imprisoned by this financial
Indebtedness and then
Yeah and then this is how they rule is through
The indebtedness that one is supposed to
Feel and behave as if
And then their control over money as the Rothschilds
Of course the red shield
You are hiding that the the higher levels of the Anunnaki
Illuminati
Their services to hide the others right
He does agree
It's just a
Federal Reserve
With
Like a little bit better
Dressing on
That's the same
Years ago about the idea of the Ross
Child's Run the World
Wingstop near me
Hidden Powers behind
She's just powers are there
Well
I do remember this
I do remember that both Ron Paul and Bernie Sanders
Steamed up to audit
The aliens
Correct
The Federal Reserve was created
Really find the most
Repulsive
It's all bulshit
There is an idea
Is the system
That that
United States
Credibly
Abusive system
Business interest
Used to
Make you in
Incapable of escaping their grass
2/3 mix.
You know Alexa
They do not
Some sort of Anna farias globalist
Alien plot
It's
The extension of
You can't get away with it
And you're an amoral
Company why wouldn't you trapped
Why wouldn't you
It makes the most sense financially
Note so many of these people whatever they want whenever they describe all of these problems
And then
Ghetto you come up to them with historical basis
You know whenever people describe is making us all slaves you know like all of this stuff
And the solutions that are
They're like
Finale was not enough racism and it sounds like socialism so I'm going to go with us it's probably a lie
The s*** why would she
Come into the studio and be like listen I have just uncovered a new plot
The reptilians have started payday loans
Or something like that
Why not
Cuz then you could use your services for good
They charge
Don't f******
Who's whatever narratives your ear bandying about Notre Dame demonize the Rothschilds is it that f****** matters notion
Their family's wealth
Been diffused over generation
Right now
For some sort of positive thing like that
Target your f****** audien
Prisons and we need to get rid of it
Why not why not
If you care why not
Well because
I don't know I think it's because
They're trying to attract and they know they're trying to
Like that's hard
When whenever I whenever we talk about self-awareness
The farthest
Even if you're saying that they are are on the stupid evil Spectrum
You know where they're more on the stupid side
They're smart enough to know who is going to buy their b*******
It's right winger
Ugly stupid
It's that whatever
Whatever language they want
It whatever they want their points to
Ardmore track
People on
Absolutely
I mean it
Some of the day would never
But he was like I was a tribe of the
The political divide
I'm talk about it
Got all that s***
No
You know damn well
Is attractive
AR
Aggressively
Like skeptical pasta
Reasonability
Hallmark
For sure
So
Work
Look I know that your guy loves
Novel
I don't do superhero,
I can't do them
But have you ever in your life
Are younger man I've never done superhero
Swamp Thing on the superhero powers
Tragic representation of the damage that we are doing
To the environment
I understand
Superhero
I don't think so he has powers
Powers don't make you talk to the guardian
Dad
So many people could be Spider-Man
It's not about Spider-Man
It's about the choice to be a hero.
Okay so now
Like Marvel stuff
Are you just saying if they aren't superheroes
Gyros
Thrust behind
Engage with the mythology of it I don't read the
Ethology
Because we're about to we are going to get in
Superheroes in
I remember the Greek for Ironman
Is actually
Iron
Experiments
Nampa Idaho
So Jordan
Here Comes
We're getting into comic books
Be ready I don't know
Think about this
I think this is really fast
G
Nope
Terry is bringing in stuff
This is very familiar
Alex Jones
Phones world
Then trying to
To bridge the gap
World
Like
Really insane
When I heard this place I got really trouble
You'll see
But what I want to ask you how
To do with the role of five
Which is the internet
Follow the information and as well as
In connection with technology
Do you even see has a lot of radiation and that this is somehow
Supposed to be detrimental to at the same time
It's quite possible that this radiation
That mutant if you follow the X-Men story and this is
Space Program knowledge.
If you want to
Basically a human for special powers in human
Get them to expand into that their brain that they use excetera
What you need to do is
Houston with radiation or doused the mother with radiation
Yeah this is what they are doing now planet Earth and
People are in a panic over this
People are in a panic
Acknowledge
LG but there
Their concern seems slightly
Difference
Inasmuch as carries cancer
And the ex
More like a bonus
You watch any of those movies
You know that
Pretty terribly
Right
Magneto
Or whatever.
He did a people just
Accepted Newton
Allegory
Just like Jessica
Completely destructive villain
Yeah like that guy who was a toad or whatever
Free creative
I get I get it
Do you know
Do you know why
Do you know why all of those arguments
Easily
Bulshit
Incredibly stupid
Just on their face
The X-Men is a Sikh
Secret space program plan
Of course
No that's that's utterly stupid
But part of the reason that it is such a stupid idea is because
Those comics
Started
Around the timeline when we understood
Radiation
Right so
If something's going to bring up a little bit later
We're radiation to be capable of creating powers
It would have happened
70 f****** years ago
In the early 60s late 50s comic books
Restarting
To be created it became a MacGuffin
Became like a storytelling
Actually forget
In order to tell these stories
If you really want to get into that it's about people who are different
Not being accepted by
Humanity as a whole
Dumb people responding
Poorly to that in some people
Trying to
GeoVista
Of the Xbox
But you can tell 100
Print stories
And they
Well I mean when you look at the I don't remember
Did the first of the second X-Men
It was
Higher
Coming out allegory there
This is the gay experience of coming out there is one line that I thought
Justified literally the entire X-Men series
Whenever somebody comes out to their mother as a no
Axeman and she goes
Have you tried not being and you're like that is the f******
Kingline
I don't know necessarily
If it was intended to
Any specific
Group that is other
Early exit
About
Groups that are marginalized
Needing to
To find each other to help each other
Exist in the world where people don't
Understand
Program kind of thing
Gracie's mute
That's what they were
Dikets that implies to me
That's something that she's hiding her mind for a while
Fit like
Not even just 5G
Before g-technology
Is it the flood women with
Do they give super baby
Do you know how you can
Tentatively
Is because
With radiation
Whenever radiation was this new cool
Something they used to put it in goddamn toothpaste
Heathwood glow
You then lost all your teeth
Another good
Lost Sawyer
What is a general stubblebine
Create superpowers
People that failed miserably
Military test where they would set off
It would set off a nuclear bomb
And they would have if I know what you're going to say
Bunch of soldiers got to
Superpowers
Training exercise where they walked
Through the
Debris that was left over
Whether or not they were visible and what
We could set up a nuclear bomb
And then we could use that
Is a cloaking Tech
And those guys
Did not
Superpowers bulshit
That is how that
Bulshit is operating under a I don't
No 70 rolled
Do you understand
What radiator
Exactly
That's
Nut hold on hold on
Percent of people who get exposed to
They're all in bunkers having their secret abilities test
Sounds
I would say
In terms of
Approve
Whatever
Is like a side
If you want to tell me
They all say I rejected
First
If you told me that 99.9% of people
Exposed
Two tons and tons
Horrible debilitating
Right now
Or whatever
Get super powers in the government
In the lab
I'm going to tell you I can't disprove that
I don't think
The true right
My gut says no
And I'll wait until there's any evidence
You say it is
The bad represented
Because what you said
Text clip
Made me laugh
So f******
This is
To Marvel
About Marvel
That is actually news from 1962 about nope
I know you wish I wish this is news from night
I do remember the TV service
Incredible Hulk
Gamma radiation
I have recently also found that the
Spider-Man with also bit by a radioactive spider
This is very cute because this is where they are going
She's f****** with me
She is f****** with all of us that is bulshit there's no way
She is f****** with us
She has recently found out that the Spider-Man
Know that what she has recently found out
She just waited all of
She just
I was watching it I was watching the video I jump
I don't think it was it's crazy
I just found out Spider-Man
Was bit by a radioactive spider
Essential plot point
I don't know.
20 movies have come out okay
Here is here's what about that
You talk about that now
Specifically this is recent
This came out like a week ago
Do you know what else came out
No
I haven't seen it but the trailer made me
It's f****** fantastic movie also
Stayed apart of
Nicolas Cage calculator that movie
So carry his found out that the Spider-Man has been bit by a radioactive spider
I can't stress how crazy that is
No she had
No
Cuz when I heard that clip I was like all right
I get it if he's talking about how the The Hulk
The Incredible Hulk
Even come also from the roof rake no version
Possible another TV
TV series orphan movie
The conversation
These Brave brought that into
It's okay coming in
Also
Radioactive spider
Ivy like
You're just adding
Conversation
When she said greatly Disturbed
Word Vila conversation there's no way I will buy that
Not even
At the very least she's a human being in 2019 she knows about the f******
Spider-Man
Now you need to see the movies just like
Spider-Man with Tobey Maguire 1
In the trailers
Definitely had him
Fire spider
Percent
I remember that very clearly
The first one came out in
2001 movie theater backyard
And there were trailers for it that had the
Twin Towers
They got recalled because the enemy helicopters
We acquired all of
No no no
That that's it came out on 9/11
Recall all of them because
So many red wing song
It's been I don't know let me look at my clock
8 years
They first like a big Spider-Man movie came out Amazing Spider-Man cartoon
Friendly neighborhood Spider-Man
Friendly neighborhood spider
He was
She was f******
This is Tupac's recently found out
It is unacceptable
No matter what the argument is it's unacceptable
Ausable
That is impossible
It's crazy
That is 104
This is not the first
Conspiracy douchebag
To talk about Marvel character
And radiator
Conferences
So many of these paranormal bulshit
Schooner or later
In her path
20-year career of being a conspiracy theorist
Somebody must have been at a panel at have been like
Mutants are creative it's just like in spider
And I think there's one
Possibilities
Just working with us so well don't carry
It hinges on Reese
Let's laugh at this or whatever
But I do remember the TV service
Incredible Hulk
Level of gamma radiation
I have recently also found that the
Spider-Man with also bit by a radioactive spider
This is very cute because this is where they are going
She is so deadpan it's hard to tell
Not a bit
Also Phil Hartman levels right now
Also didn't
Radiation
Because of something
He doesn't become the Hulk because of the radio
That's the root of it
He's Bruce Banner David Banner depending on
Yeah
I like the idea that she
Like I said
Well
Well plate
Second is Snow dead
Orthodontics
I think it is probably
Speculating
Is the into the spider-verse
And it's a more diverse
Version vampires
People end up
That have been attacking much more from the right
In the same way that went Ghostbusters Ghostbusters came out
Everyone on the right was to protect and they're like f*** this I hate this noise
And so the ideas like into the spider-verse
Being a movie
They came out with a black
Spider-Man other Spider-Woman Spider-Man
Right
Spider-Pig Peter Porker
Spider-Man
Dia of
That identity
Spider-Man
Just there was so much right wing
He's online
That you became aware of it
Is also the Multiverse theory in
Into the spider-verse so that maybe one of the read
Jason said it penetrated into her Bowl
How many maybe but I think I think the bigotry is a much more like
Right
Why is it now stuck in your craw
It's been
Almost sent Spider-Man came out
Like
It's been a long f****** time
I don't know
I think
Superman
Is an alien
It's not even from here
You know what I did
The globalist
Did you hear what I just recently
This
Goblin King
Whole Foods
Banana
Is the Green Goblin
I'm not sure if I'm going to go with Aquaman
You know what's crazy
What's up watch the Aquaman movie the most recent
Weather
Really negative
There's this massive undersea War about whatever it is
Is right and Jason Momoa Aquaman
Can communicate with all of the animals or whatever
But it's not presented as communication so much as it is mine control
So what Jason Momoa does is create an army of
Slave
Nobody ever talks about that
Well I don't disagree
Cars
Oh yeah
Spiraled out of
These guys are still go to driving cars
. but I lost the thread don't know how to do this
Coming out I can't wait for it
83 Howell
Which are the complete inability to die regardless
To have that Wolverine
Regenerative main character Shield to Avery
Anyway that's a
Is better than
Spider-Man
You haven't seen into the spider-verse actually really really great
Passengers is better than all other franchises
Of all time
Anyway I'll talk about that because it's the craziest
B******* in the world
It's nonsense
So we come to the end of this episode Jordan and what we have is
In front of us a tableau of like just someone
Doesn't understand linguistics
Linguistic
Which is fun
I think that Robert
And I always enjoyed
That's what
We got to talk about that
Did the
Influence of the Alex
Whether it's
Sovereign state
Rothschild Bank
Whether it's
The ideas of life
What's 5G
Being dangerous
Yeah
Play kits
These worlds are similar
The way they're not similar
Alex
Concerned about 5G
As trying to give
Cancer
Serious concern has recently found out about Spider-Man
Which is nuts
It's nuts
I love it
That's why we talked about this I don't like that Alex has a literal reasonable
Position
In terms of radiation causing cancer
Is it based in
It is
Bananas exaggerate
But the idea of radiation causing cancer
Make sense
It's fair
Yeah where at
Radiation creating the X-Men
Not fair
The idea that you don't know this I can't get over that
Good job good on you
Goodonya
Tabaxi Eddie Bravo this episode
Reality-based
I'm so I'm glad we
Weird for us to do this on a Monday
But that's what it is
Is
We needed a breath
We all little bit of a
We all need
Another episode
You with
Geppetto
Debra wants to go check out a believe there's actual
On Facebook I'm not good at I'm not good at promotional
Free promotion
Nothing like that but
You can find it Cosmic Geppetto's good time I really enjoyed talking to
Amanda I mean
If you listen to this podcast pretty regularly I don't think
We talked about all that much
That's new
So check it out
Good
Beyond
For my plugs if you would like to see me do stand-up
Just start going to a lot of stand-up shows and then maybe sometime you'll see
But we have website knowledge fight.com
Find all kinds of
Showing
Indeed
Do we have a Twitter account
Underscore
You can find that
Reviews
Pierre has murdered the English language
I will say that a hall light
Rock Devastation of on linguistics
As a form
But he's never murdered
Buddy I appreciate
Because there's one guy
He killed the guy
Maybe probably
But for now
One guy has probably technically murdered a guy
Alexandra Thurston color