Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody
Jordan
Got any hot sauce
People I believe that I've found by hot sauce pepper
I could be wrong about this selection of hot sauces
From
Beginnings
Can see the Hydra Hail Hydra
Marvel Universe
I believe the other song
I thought was a scorpion
Pepper
Trinidad scorpion sauce
And it was great
Just the right level of heat a little bit scary really easy
Not easy but enjoyable
Rideout okay
There's a fruitiness to it
So I believe once I move into apartment
Start my pepper Garden the first
Things
Stream
Scorpion
About it
Peppers
Like very gentle
It's always got to be something aggressive
7 poisonous
Venomous
You know
For the fruit
You plant know not to cuz it hurts
We're the only animal dumb enough to be like
Taste good
If you'll watch
Absolutely focus on
I don't know if there any that are named after cuddly animals
Peppers
And I just
There's a pepper that just straight-up look like a
Okay Peter Pepper
Existed
How did that happen
Multicolored
That would be great
Okay I'll work on that I'll cross-pollinate
That might be a little bit outside of my
The migraine some abilities that we will try
But I do know a lot about
You shall learn
Continue are looking into what Alex
Sandy Hook and how his
Reporting
Has taken
Has been molded
A shout out to
People who have
Text Jimbo thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Everybody likes next
Your nail polish
ARG
I liked
Nick
Are you sure it's not night it could be Nike
You could be mispronouncing all of these literally Quran. I believe that
Jambo I might be way off
I apologize
Next
Appreciated
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Appreciate
Keith
You're now technically
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket of poop
I don't want
Jesus Christ
We appreciate please do about a month behind
Shoutouts
Just because there are a lot of people out there were very generous
And I'm sorry
I don't want to do a half-hour of
Policy wonk
And I don't want people with one sound effect absolutely
Individual mamao that we can do it at episode while still giving everybody their place
A little bit of a delay but
December 20th
2012 21st
Right
The world
It's mostly Alex David Icke about how the world isn't ending
Reptilian overlords
Very convoluted
Was that day about the by apocalypse
So he doesn't talk too much about Sandy
But there were couple clips
That were from that episode
That I pulled just as a reminder
So we don't
Skip entirely over
Crisis actors who predict
Did the end of the world or maybe they were
You're going to that from
In this first clip we find out where Alex's editorial position
Is here on the
The beginning of December
System being a winner
Just like
Meriden
Peter denied Jesus
I'm not sure exactly
Gotcha we have Alex
Coming out very
Clearly early on that
Official story
A story is affable so
You know you don't like to hear this the day after
Where we last left
Starting to
Suggest
That the father
Who was interviewed
Is Greek people needed to investigate
On the 20th
Maybe like the stories
Affable
Easter bunny tail
It's not good
I'm not excited about that
But he does spend most of the time at the beginning
The show just talk about the establishment
Symptoms you got to watch out for Global
Hard as he has been already
To just gone defense
Gone defense
I'm going
Ways that Alex portended his own descent into stupidity
He did say that the way that you win is by deceiving and the only way that they
You can do that
Is if you are willfully willfully ignorant so it does kind of suggest about him
You give you gets pretty
Call
Which I'm not sure why you
Needed that it's kind of fun,
For him to actually want to and fulfill his
Promise
To get to call
Call
This caller is talking about how bad
In the day please
Used to act
Currently to make
Because I kind of relates to
To Alex's
Is that
You'll see
When I would be walking down the street in my own neighborhood I would often be stopped as a as a Young Man
Evolve now
Serious urges actually seizing people and things like that
So just colors describing something from his childhood he doesn't sound like a young man
Pretending
He's trying to do that to suggest
The globalist
To bring in Marshall
Feasible
New York
The coming martial law
But as he does so frequently what he's doing is presenting a warped version
Reality
Completely erase
Contacts
From the conversation
In this case what I was talking about is the stop-and-frisk policy
Operated under
Particularly troubling except from the early 2000s
The policy was an outgrowth of the broken window
Dishes
In which larger more serious crimes
Naturally spray
Following that logic the police prioritize stop in Petty crimes like public urination public transit fare evasion in the like
Environment where more serious crime
Didn't go great
That's the public
In reality it was just a way to Shakedown and terrorized my
In 2010 a police officer named Adrian Schoolcraft
Recorded tapes
Police roll call meeting
First District
Of the bedford-stuyvesant
Area
They clearly show the
The commanding officers explicitly telling their officers
Trouble
Reports filed
Schoolcraft was detained for sweet held in a mental hospital for 6 days
Retaliation
Ultimately
To pay $7,000 for his own
Speak in 2011
680 5724 people were stopped
Come Frist
Of these people 80%
Completely innocent of
A number that is super consist
Yearly data analyzed by the New York civil liberties
And here's
Between 2000 to 2013
In full effect
Stop was never lower than
Interesting Lee in all those years you want to look at them at any of them
Frisked who happened to be white was never hired
12%
Which is considering that New York City is approximately
At least 44%
5% of the people stopped
In 2080 5% 2080
7% with this
Without socks
Please Shake people down in New York and doesn't bring
The conversation
He's lying by omission
He's doing such expressive white supremacist
Disposition
He's totally New York
The stop-and-frisk was specifically
Used as a weapon against minority communities is
The definition of be right for the wrong reasons
Tim Roth
Yeah but it still boils
Complaint which is
The underlying complaint is
Like that's really what they're bitching about
Essentially
I thought about that
I really did because I thought about how that could
Fit into
Anime
Cephalic
Yeah but if those things
You talk about other targeting minority communities
Because that would help make that
He just wants that
Piece of it completely left cuz it opens a door his
He sort of argument
Which is
Dhp
Horizon Destroyer
Right stuff like that
Right and your quotas being failed
That's crazy make money
Jordan make money
They destroyed the reputation of policing in America
Good workout about
The picture of police being out of line
It's an important distinction that needs to come up every now and again on this show that just because he's
About something
You could be entirely wrong
You said he's taking these collars
And
Get the call and wants
And this guy has
An interesting piece
Of the story that he wants to report
And Alex allows
Do so which
Sandy the supposed Sandy Hook shooter Adam Lanza was found only two handguns not a Bushmaster assault
Rifle
What does rate
There's an article
As part of a promotion
New York
Absolutely Alex
It's all right out there on the opening up enough publicity and enough of it can be
Giving out to the public, maybe I can turn things for awhile
That is super easily is that a win we've talked about this before and I apologize
Name or his job but one of the
Go to work in likes that design and graphic
At work on
The Dark Knight
Is from
Kansas City on a map
As I remember from the last time I looked into
It's very very
And all the other stuff is
Misreporting the idea that they sent out
BeIN sent orders to attack
He did say that they control of their City
What look that's the least important thing I think I want to talk about
Dark Knight Rises
Apology
I'm getting my Tim Burton's All In
It's for
Exactly all getting mixed up
Okay I think
Is really just
It's very stupid
And it's just indicative of how
He's trying to bring in as much
Narrative
And that's just heard of it
The muddy the water
Seymour
With hearsay and bulshit
Do you know what's even crazier send out physical maps
Actually sent out
The single
From the Yeah Yeah Yeahs
Maps
Do you know when that came out
Don't know
Play that on Rock Band 2
More important I want to talk about is that this call is repeating
Incomplete
Information that he picked up somewhere
And Alex is doubling down on its a great disbelief
His listeners about what happened
You're talking about
Adam Lanza
They didn't even have a
If you read the police report on the shooting at
All the shooters person with loaded semi-automatic Sig Sauer p
269 mm pistol
Additional
Located near the shooter was partially loaded Glock 20 10 mm semi-automatic
It appeared to be jam
However the next line explains that quotes a Bushmaster Master model XM
6 rifles located
Away from the shooter
The rifle shoulder strap
Was attached to the front but disconnect
Get to the part of the
The disconnected rear portion was the result of a
Field nut
It's unknown if the nuts failed when the rifle
Or as the result of being dropped
Referring to the floor
So using that weapon is evidenced by all sorts of other friends again
Possibly because the strap
It's unclear
Exactly why
There's also people who suggested that added Jam
That's not entirely
They were able to
Do I
The people who are investigate
Able to fire
Yeah it doesn't appear that it was critical
But for one reason or another you ended up throwing
And favoring
It could just be a crazy thing in the moment of like I'm sick of all of this
Mass killing I wanted
Seether
Four wife that gun
Was found a little further away from him
Then the two
This guy is pretending
But there wasn't
Bushmaster rifle there at
Lanza also had a ton of ammo on him
A person including one shotgun shell
Even though you didn't have a shock
There are other shotgun shells found around
It dropped but it still raises the question
Why the ammo
Was there a
I have a shotgun
If you just read a little bit further in the police report quote
Recovered from the car wasn't its match the 12
12-gauge shotgun
24 rounds of ammunition
That would make sense then
He just left the shop.
Couldn't carry it I don't know
And that was there for when you get back
To the car yeah it is possible never know exactly the answer
He's dead
Yeah
Completely different rifle
Kill his mother but that gun was found
Organs found in her house
That she loves
Channellock
Too many guns
I'm not comfortable making a hard.
Determination on what is
It's a lot of gun
Bad idea that this caller is suggesting
Alex is irresponsible
Explain
You part of what's being
You presented as
This story is a fairy tale
Right that's
It allows for
The muddying of the waters
It's b*******
It's how Alex build
Real-time
Some of this is a collars
Perhaps
Or has difficulty taking a lot of calls
There's a part of me that wonders if
As if there could be some sort of like
Where are they now VH
Who call in
Like is this guy still denying Sandy Hook
Like I want to know more about this idiot
And what it is
He's doing with his life
Yeah
I bet he is
There's not a like
Agree
Percentage of
To buy intalex
People probably can
Figure things out
It's not
Hey but I bet it's not
I would say it's like a
A large percentage
Percentage lease
Every year whatever and they're just like
I'm done with the
A certain percentage go even further in become white nationalist
Malicious
And then everybody else just kind of
Staying in the
The fluctuating middle in the dryer cycle
That's possible
I don't know
Speculation with no information whatsoever
For sure
So if Alex gets back to the
Or something
What is wild
Is the school district in Michigan
Week left of classes
Because there were fears of school shooting
Because there were rumors being spread that there was going to
Apocalypse
These kids are too distracted
We're just going on break early.
Afraid that there's going to be a mass shooting there were threats
And everybody is wild
Because the article that I read about afraid
School shooting because
The they looked into
These rumors
Nothing
The reason
Being ineffective
The kids are too distracted occupied with
These ideas
You know just because
You find a rumors
The kids aren't going to emotion
Beetle
The fear of the anxiety
Spreads like wildfire
Cervical disc
Was like you guys are going on holiday break anyway
Is the same as closing
End of the world
Terry
I don't want to die okay cool we're going to go on break a little bit
So
In this next clip Alex
Get really defensive that everybody
This morning
4 years
Hair
I think a lot of people don't know
Your position
I think that's the issue I don't know how anyone supposed to know what you told people off air
Except
Around this time
That it's b*******
Totally reasonable I wonder if
You present one time where I kind of want the world
Retroactively retroactively to have ended in 2012
Just for him to be wrong it's not the one.
Still get to watch him
Burning flames
I guess fortunately it didn't go that way
If we would have
I saw that
How to keep steak
It's super Bazaar
Because like
Generally speaking
But I listen to these episode
For about an hour call
I might be like next time
Multiple calls
What is
You know fairly early in the show
I was bizarre
When you get this call from some
Suggest
Glad
Morgan
Call station
Stance
And I was hoping you'd heard of her
She should be good to have on your show
So I love the idea that
I sure do but if you would spell regretted his voice
It's not regret its frustration with his phone system
Like its
His collars
Because they often don't know that
He's gone to them
If you listen to it as much as I do
That frustration is there
That little conversation with somebody can you hear me can you hear me
Alex Heights
3 seconds
The owner of the gun case indoor shooting range in Hot Springs Arkansas
Does an official instructor license
The NRA
Interesting Lee it
Plastic fitting
See you guys in 2014 sheep and all Muslims from her shooting range
Okay thanks more than enough loss of life on my home soil at the hands of Muslim
To substantiate my position
Can and will follow the directors and their Quran
And kill here at home
He's a narc
All places
Never in my wildest
The First Amendment did not include protections for Muslims and defended her action play sound right
Interpreted as being very scary
Two Muslims walked
Dubai rains last week with allah-o-akbar ringtones and message alert tone brother smartphones
Facebook little English have proof of US citizenship
Shoot gun
They were constantly glancing towards
The cameras in the rain
Looking at each other in speaking in their own language
She went on to say that
Nothing here
I've no way of discerning which Muslims will or will not kill in the name of their religion in the commands there
I choose to err on the side of
Caution
Unfortunately
To be flipped around Subaru
Members of violent white nationalist groups of the government are on the mall white man it's almost like she's
Not advocating for that
Necessarily
To what she's putting for
She's very Stu
Yeah this is how this s*** always goes
It's the same thing we talked about in terms of Ted Nugent
Gonzaga score
These people pretend to have a principled absolute moral stand.
The right to own a gun
Is the most important part of being free
Restrict anyone's access
Misticanza
All guns
Entomology
As soon as they feel threatened
Electrolyzer
Restricting the very right
Yeah to believe is sex
These people are all liars
Well if she staying
The First Amendment doesn't cover
Muslims
Yeah fine
If that's if that's you're saying then get the f*** out we don't need you
Everett
She's also saying that the Second Amendment doesn't
Because they're not allowed in
Gun store
So they aren't legally allowed to
Carry guns
She's essentially saying that Muslims
Morgan ran for the governorship of Arkansas in their 2018 election
Set up any legal raffle
$50 to her campaign with her signature engraved on it
When legal question started popping up she refunded everyone's money but it Bears mentioned because he thought that was a good idea
Running in just a Republican
Primary
Disposition
Was pretty on point
She brought it was $200,000
Much of which came from political
Play Sharon address
Call Business Services Arkansas
Commerce and action
The maximum amount allowed to her
But also
People
A group called conduit for action
Convert fraction as a hard right political action committee
Which is super against Governor Hutchinson
Person that you would be running
Because though he's a Republican
He's not as Hardline as they want their governor to
They publish articles on their website like this one from
Just about a week ago
Governor's tax plan to Fort Constitution
About Hutchinson
Proposed increase
That sounds like something that the founding fathers were real
During the election Republic multiple articles promoting Morgan's campaign
Disclose
Clone political action
We just shady as hell but not illegal in Arkansas
It is a problem
On the other hand
Alex would have loved her if she owned a pool supply store in Austin
Said he never would have had the same young girls
I understand all the information I was able to find most of these are clones
PA
From conduit
It really has to be
No okay there we go
Alright I know there's been some discussion about it
Because it is a really f****** weird to allow
Maximum don't matter
Republican primary
Which is super f***** up as the Arkansas times pointed out during the campaign
Power was about winning the vote
Call Morgan
Republican primary for governor bike
Compiling the most votes
But she's already won the race by driving Governor Hutchinson
Declaration
Open position to
The farthest right reaches
The political Spectrum
By being in the race you required Hutchins
Come out from the shadows and Pandora
The further right parts of being in the race
Dante's rhetoric towards the LGB
Community in about women's rights
Became far more toxic than it had been in
The campaign cycle
And this Jordan
Is how the Overton window shift
She's a perfect
Example of
Yeah
Jesus
Dick
Sheetz
I don't know if she doesn't come on eventually
Political action committees necessarily even wanted
Effect right
Woodforest Hutchinson
To change some of the
The position store
The harder right
Funneling money
In order to push him to the right
That's how this works
Yeah there's no way they would actually want her to win because obviously it's her first day in office
It would be like the Constitution
What would be what are you doing
Yeah
She would not have a very successful term as Governor
I thinks you might get herself into
Bit of trouble
Even hard right folk or not
So
Alex just ordered Treads water for
He has a guy
My friend
I don't know
Derek Fisher
Formerly of the lake
Not Barrack
Me and my dad went to the Lakers
Preseason game
Years and years back
Is he a good guy
I don't remember I don't think anyone is mean to me
A check wasn't even
No I was there we got in early cuz it's not
Through like a back door
Forget autograph
Yeah yeah
Sounds like Kobe Bryant
It was there I got his autograph and
Eddie Jones
Yeah
Derek Fisher walked out
I think it was Sean Rooks walked up
Midland power forward
I did not I wasn't interested in
So that I'm getting these autographed news people I look over and check
Free throw
He's warming up shoot
Horrific Lee every time
I never imagined
Just a little boy
On a basketball court
Jessie Shack
His bodyguard
He's like no
It gives me up
Littlefield
I mean obviously I pay his salary and everything
He's the boss babe
What you going to do
Point is Derek Fisher
I think of other people who are on the Lakers around that time
Andrew Bogut is a big pizza Gator so he could have been
It's true. It's not it's about
Bar
But he's a good guy
Interview because he is
Liberty
Bob Marley
He's been a longtime member of the NRA board so Alex being like they've gotten more extreme underhand makes literally no sense
He was a member of the board's almost the entire time Alex has been mad at them and calling
Control 12
Wow you sitting down with Baba
It's just meaningless if they have gotten more but it has nothing
Things to do with
Anything that
You know he's just been there
Being a bit of a right-wing
Years from 1995 to
For bills who sponsored became
What was that name of the post office another one was about the number of night
296 Atlanta
Commemorative coin should be
Another was about how Alabama Florida and Georgia
Share surface water rights
To the Chattahoochee River
The 4th
Bojack
Wichita
Play one woman by the federal government from requiring States
Spouses
People inside
Alright
Wow he's a piece of s***
Unrecognized whatever States
Thanks Bill
I have to concede that a lot of Congress members on both sides of the aisle have
Levels
There's this horrible in terms of productivity
Majapahit
For that
I don't think it speaks
Super highly
4/5
Is fat and all you Come Away With Me
Some coins
The name post office in a bill that deeply undermines
The group
Right I don't think that's great
You know
I mean
The argument against that
When you really get down based on
Democrat
And how garbage they are
Is not going to have like
She probably won't even have four bills passed in the next 8 years
Because they're so shity but she's already done far more than any of the other Hunters
Call myself out for that
Don't really on the surface get a whole lot done
I'm saying she's got for bills
Years
And
I do want better for activity
Time I recognize that it's an endemic system
It's beside the point
More to the point
Perhaps more relevant to our conversation in office 48000 5
Hundred dollars from Lockheed Martin
$3
The NRA 39500 $50 from clock
Representing
Three of his five large
Campaign
Contributors recent Tire
In addition to that is political action
100 1970
$3
From gun-rights group
Also be a board of
Member of the National Rifle Association
He's not someone who's
Even close to being unbiased on the subs
Jacob Gunn
As just another example of Alex
Pakman show with shells
For the gun Lobby's come-out is fasted
Aggressive
Possible
Against the very idea of reggae
Latorre reform as it were
NES
He's just
Complete friend everybody's a gun show
Yeah nobody else
Except
Other than
Ventura that you could call not a
She'll for gun entry
It's crazy
It's not a 100%
Agreement among the system is what it is
Of course you can buy politicians because you already have a s*** ton of money
You've already bought enough politician
For them to make it okay for you to buy
Politicians
Supreme Court Justices
We'll make it okay for you to buy politic
America
Can people is old don't have a 100%
Ratings on everybody should be allowed to buy
Like if you pulled a Merica they would be like
Well 40% says it's like that doesn't make sense at all
Yeah it seems
It seems like no matter how you phrase it
Look at it
There's a better way to do
I think our politicians is a great idea
Whenever you could do
Just use a lot of money
To change the political system
To benefit
She was involved
That lobbyists Bruce plan to give bar in a 38 caliber pistol
Widener says that he remove the magazine
From the gun but didn't clear the chamber
We were handling it safely
Accepted it was
Certainly inspires confidence
Especially considering that according to Bruce's LinkedIn page
The conditioned air Association of Georgia that has extra weird
Subway
Almost shot
The reception because I'm disappointed
Disappointed you're looking at the wrong issue
It's true it's not that like the bullet missed
It's him it's also could have hit anybody else
No I get it
People who
I know I know
Fatbardha initiate
So it's not so embarrassing
Then he was the one receiving the
Figure is giving an ant
Keep going to a guy who's
Is a board member of the NRA gun guy
You should do your due diligence
Make sure there's not a
Real embarrassing things about a podcast
Undermine a lot of these arguments
But that's that's
Talk about
Whenever I whenever it's like
10 guns or whatever
It is not
That you
Can't have all those guns
And it's that
Every gun
Multiplies the ability for YouTube
F****** minorly
Just increases the percentage of chance that something is going to
To f****** guns you handle
The more likely it just as a statistical you know
Datapoint
Like I believe people should be able to have guns
Responsibly
And all that stuff
But what we're talking about
Even two possibilities
People who handle guns
Responsible
In FA Cup
I am
I am unable to hear Bob bar without feeling like you're leaving off the
Like I always hear Bob bar in a mic when are you going to finish the word
It's a Bob Barker
When are you going to say Bob Barker
Also Bob bar was the guy who led the charge
Who was the first person
In Congress
Call on
He's an hour
He's
Mostly about
Look like it's a real thing
Which is
I guess
It's important
As much as Alex
Are not influencing him
Except for
Like to send
From any
A source on the show
There's nobody who's coming in
Poisoning is mine
Twitter whatever
You should know
These people are nuts I don't know the. Is on the street
Alex Telles
The real issue
First person shooter games
Soldiers wooden
Kill people that's why they invented video games
Right
I beg to differ I will actually defend
Strangely enough this is something that I did read up on a lot of stuff
Ammoland
And it is
Very very unlikely for a soldier
Do to actually
Play try and kill
Like so many of the bullets that they found have been p
People literally like intentionally trying to miss
But at the same time nobody wants
To kill anybody
So there is a very high like
What times after the
Free throw percentage level of trying to kill people
But if you're talking about you're not talking about it
In terms of like
Amtrak
People are still on the air
People are still on the side of maybe we shouldn't kill people
They're working video games around the world war
Next
Wants to tell Bob about
It's pretty scary
Bento's on Archer
Dot-com
Chinese government
Because you bring up so many good points a lot of people don't
Google
That's not a great response to
I think you can probably guess just from
Listening to Alec
You might be sensation
Attack
A respectable former House member
Operation
I did post an op-ed titled innocent blood demands no delay for us guns
But it stopped just short of saying
Something like
Hey Obama everybody gun
You can find the article online and if you do you'll see what it really is
Mostly about how is awful and heartbreaking
These mass shootings are in America the reason it is electoral politics
The author specifically points out that Columbine happened in an election here we
Probably a big reason why no one was
Willington
Due to possible political G
They point out that
Because Obama doesn't have
Have to face another election
Rare position
Where there isn't a concern for
Really just escaping
In fact
The up at further points out.
Years even the Democrats
Ostensibly
Like the political will
Influencing funding
Provided
Honest by the NRA
Specifically pointing out
When the NRA gave three
3.2 million dollars
The candidates
98% of which
Republicans
Interesting Lee in that election the largest pickle recipe
Another money
Who's California's Democratic representative
It's real strange
The blue dog Democrat
And after he lost his
2012 he tried to Stage a comeback by running as a Republican
2015 Switchback being Democrats running
Otherwise known as a f****** a******
Haha
So he was part of that
Percent of money from the NRA
Motor 2.0 this piece
It is about that.
Do anyting
You can tell that from lines like quote
Control the United States
However this time the public feels somewhat tired and
Helpless every time a tragedy appeals for gun regulation
Disappointingly always fail
Goddamnit there's a resignation in the tech
Profoundly felt the tragic
Was
Do people who are able to
I feel things all around the world
Define call to action
But it's kind of meat
Taking in the full context
The rest of the Arctic
Actions speak louder than words
If Obama wants
To take practical measures to
Control
He has to make a preparation
For a protracted war and considerable political cost
This is to say that lipstick Services meaningful is meaningless
And ultimately of Obama wants to make
Make a real difference
The gun fetish
Country
Are going to let him do anything
All in all of the article is
A really big really is what we all felt like the the next day
Yeah that's fair I mean just anybody with empathy emotions is a lot of people
Really where
We're not doing anything even after this
Then it's never going to be done
I don't know what to do
Other than
Myself from
From care
Well I guess this
This is just business as usual so I don't have to
Feel anymore
It's recalled
The New York Times wrote a piece about this article
Nonprofits around the same time
There was a man who
Children
These attacks happen no matter what weapons
People have
None of the children in China died
So
Cuz even if someone comes in with a knife
Estep 22 kids
The f****** terrifying awful thing
At the very least a little
Further line by thing
You just broke the story
Paul Joseph Watson posted in the op-ed on it
Icom on December 20th
The day of this episode
Breitbart.com
So Alex
Their propaganda
Pretending
The first one on the scene
And pjw
Even a paragraph citing the Breitbart story and blanket
Of course cover the Breitbart article
News
Interesting L one store
What does give Alex credit for breaking
The story
The Communist Party
Communist Party of China
Is that the US should disarm
According to Chinese
The recent school massacre gave all
Gave all to understand that one should not wait any longer
The country's leaders believe that the brutality
Connecticut
Support for arms reduction
Infowars.com
That's from December 21st article Improv
I'm not really sure what that means or even if it means
I don't know Source on this story
Mozart
I'm not sure that
I just want Alex's got this story he lets Bob go
Get out of here Bob
He just trusts your own
It's a different guy
Okay
And that really starts
The feel-good get them in there
He took calls earlier in the show so we can just breathe
They are now
They kill everybody
The most brutal
Yeah yeah
Later on later on
Still he did still bubbling under the sea
And then he gets
This
He talks about
Chinese newscaster
Where is covering
Tiananmen Square
I think it sounds like him
In the present
Square news
Square
Satisfaction
Oh my God
And it's just incredible
But it's in chai
I don't know I don't know I don't know if he's ever got it it's a mystery
Very similar to him
Taco Bell
Yeah
You know I was thinking
While he was
While he was talking about that
I was thinking about how that the New Yorker story that came out about how Fox News
Is the mouthpiece in the propaganda arm of the traffic by Erasure
Yeah I'm like I imagine myself being Alex reading that story and being like
This is the problem
I was supposed
Give me the state media
Fox News took my game
Took my game and went pro with it
He had I mean not
See that coming
Even in the early
Of course
I mean
I don't I don't know
That's what he wants
But you wouldn't want to be
B Fox News
He wants to be the propaganda arm of the trumpet
Stricter rules
But that's what I'm saying
Even then he must be so angry
To realize the extent of
Yeah because
That's that's it like one of his big selling point
Being the state-run media is like
See nobody nobody can regulate my s***
I don't give a
Ffcc I don't care stupid
Bright
You guys could have picked me and they would never even though they would write a New Yorker story
Yeah like I give a s*** you know
Although on the other hand Fox News doesn't give a s*** either
There is that there's more people on the record
Around Fox Valley
You got to get rid of mice
You got to give it up to the Somali play
So in the next clip Alex
To say something
If it's all real
Nope
People say
Exposing me
What's your plans
System here has prize in the world
The Patriot
The Americans
Greatest Prize
And they're willing to Nuka City
In order to
Make Alex look bad
Be arrested
I don't see how that's not trying to scare people
No
The anime
Is willing to kill Millions upon millions of people Scorch the Earth around them
Possibly cause lasting radioactive damage
To the entire world
In order to arrest
Right that's not that scary little narcissism
Anybody who expresses feelings of
Lawson
Certainly
Buildings at
Why would you care about these 20 people
Million
Because they're going to Nuke the city
Upside down
December twenty
Alex
Understood in the
Text of all the other things
All this points
Like in recent days
Keep seeing this video of Robbie Parker
Suspicious
Actors
Like an actor up there this needs
To be investigate
Smells too high
People need to invest
The globalist
Plaintiff
Lucas.
Takeout are patriots The Greatest Prize
In the known world
It doesn't make
Everybody's face
Radio
Okay
So
Really weird to hear that level of
Scaremongering
Over what sound
Seems like the track from a Jane Fonda workout video
I do know what you mean
Yeah it's strange
Glutes
It's disconcerting
Certainly
The idea of like if you love your family better get really Act
Local access
You got to get in people
Whose faces you got it you got it
Infront everybody tubes
That's probably just an expression of
If you guys
Do these they
It's only going to feed people to me
Exactly
Because you'll be like
Maybe
Be your idea
Reference reference guide
Be a large portion
Audience
I'm here
What are you saying
Context of all
You need to get aggressive
If you love your family you got to get really active
Occupying government
August
Interested investigate
As he has already said people need to do
The getting really active part there is
It's just frustrating
Contact drop from
Play earlier
Battaglia
You are
So we get to the 21st
Pickled cucumber debate
Got to pick up in Alex's world
We got a reference
So
We're to the 21st the end of the world
David icon
It's mostly just talking about
How
You know there are evil forces in
In the world
Course the world knocking
That is most
Conversation
About
Sandy Hook
Now we see
These ideas that Alex is already
The Batman
Jane Fonda workouts
That doesn't come in play specifically
He's probably in the background song
So Alex
Have this conversation
Awful
Well I just think it with heading to Alex to a point in the New Year in 2013
When somebody sings going to come together
Good point election to win
We have space
Clifford talking about
Obvious agenda
Poochon down the rose
If people
Absolutely
NAU
Hi-Tech
Top-of-the-range luxury capital
And the rest of the people
Actually an object
Interesting
Enum
Sandy Hook
Dark knight rising movie when abilities
Recorders from
The manipulation of
The human subconscious mind which then becomes
The conscious Minds perception of reality
I don't care about that Batman nonsense
Do people not know how f****** stupid that is
Anybody listen to David I cannot go
Dumbest f******
I get the music British accent and that can confuse a lot of people
Lips a lot through his nose and
Dumbfucks
It is true that
Who's the author of The Hunger
Did live in Sandy Hook Village
Also Caitlyn Jenner formerly live there too
Is that meaningful
The actor Anthony Edwards used to live there
So what
The author of The Lost weekend live there
Does this add to the conspiracy
Jenna von Oy who plays sticks
What the high school in San Diego
We're Spix's hat
Part of the globalist
Actually that is I don't know I would really valid I would believe that
Anybody anybody
From the show Blossom
Town of Newtown
That list expand
Quite a bit and now includes Charles
Joanna
Joey Styles the former ECW announcer
And Elia Kazan
One of the best directors in film history
Play we forgot.
People who are from places
So-called
F*** you better better to like work on it
You can't that's a shortcut
To do
First
Not investigating
And second saying that they are not coincidences
That's proving my dumb argument
And the plot of The Hunger Games
We have nothing to do
Due West
The shooting
Not so number one battle royale when she was high in protein
Really have to do with
The directions
Yes
Great economic
Different
The classes
That is true
The social stratification
Aspect of the movie
But
The movie is about a cat
Contact
Yeah we still haven't gotten to nor is there any indication that that is diverse
That's true
So here is the last clip from
Where are they
You can look at Sandy Hook
It's about
An excuse to take guns away because of the same reason that they stopped
Johnson ammunition
Another one next
To to create emotional trauma
Collectively in the population
You're talkin about psychic vampires with David Icke
Ridiculous
Staged
On his
They're doing it to create emotional trauma on a worldwide basis
All in on the little bit harder it is
Yeah Alex's
It's not good
Have these ideas
Presented on your show on challenge
If they're not ideas that
You don't want
Your audience
It's just a b
I still don't think
We've we've reached the
The point where he
He's fully committed to
This was fake argument or anything
But we're past the end of the world
And we've seen the continuation of the
Wall-to-wall gun show Gap
And the breaking of that pattern
With one of the
The craziest people who exist in the world
This drama
And all this stuff
Swarthy
Nada
Confident
But Alex is going to find gooseberry
At all
That last one there
Alex
Concerned this is going to
To create copycat
School shooter
Nothing in terms of regulating gun laws
You are you can be pretty confident that was going to
And then you can just say that I called this these are all because of
Yeah the last one
Is all just copycatting off the last one pretty sure that you
Have some culpability
In those f******
I'm not willing to go that far
Is not
Certainly not
But I'm not sure of
What
He's guilty
Sounds
Sounds like
Nervous book
Do you like easy
F*** you
You're a f******
He is
He's not he doesn't even believe the dump
Listen to
He might
I kind of regret earlier episode of this show I might have said he
He has some
Just respond
Like the vague self-help stuff
That is incorporated within all the other day
Message
Defense
They could get anywhere
Goop for a cake
Self-help
I think I probably
Yasso
Wasn't hard enough on David Icke
But
So I don't know I don't know what the end of this
What
What will you
Receive
Progression
I think we're still seeing a bit of a holding pattern
Is part
I think you're starting to feed the audience catch up to him
Salacious
More calls you're seeing that influence
Come into the program
And then the idea
December
21st 2012 showing
Have David icon
But because of the timing of it
David Icke is also introducing a lot of really bad idea
Sam evolution
We'll see where it goes
Well the fact that brings up
The feedback loop
As being like Alex
Bringing up the feedback loop as being some
Part of this whole
Yet not realizing that
He's in that feedback loop with all of his gas
With all of his collars
Of him saying s*** and they're all just mirror
She is in this
Constant like
Hanby
No in
Information
That
Is that I
Will interact
That is not supporting my
Yeah
He doesn't realize
Part of the loop in the same way
He's a part of politics
He is a part of the thing that
Yeah it is much as like
Basically just
Virginia Morgan
Of
Like you
Like I'm above the right left
Perpetuate
Is 2
Try to work
The Bush People further right
Right
YouTube Ozzy
Left-right paradigm
This feedback loop
It's going on
When he is pushing it
Super far towards
The Sandy Hook was fake
Mentality
Oh yeah so
Yeah that's a good point
He doesn't realize it
Hopefully
Hopefully will be
Further
Event
Progress
But until then
We are ozone's we are
We are
We're great
Dolphin do
High-pitched voices
Really really phone am in phone in those plugs
Yeah I'm looking over this and I'm not seeing anybody I like
No I there's a there is a murderer's row murderers on the show
Hoboy
Leaving David Icke is ever actually
Killed
I don't know
Crazy enough
But he might have
Anybody
Totally
Think that's accurate
In the clear
Bad
Bob Barker
Yeah I guarantee you that of all the people we have talked about in this show only Bob Barker
That guy
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work