Alex
Forget a grave what are you talkin about getting pumped up Elementary School
Okay I'll give you a
Ariane memorable can remember that I didn't deserve it all
Michele Weaver
I dropped out my senior year of ice
But I also skip
Like
Two-thirds of my junior year
Halo mask
In that time of course
Expelled
I showed up and took a couple of the finals I took my French fry
Final
You got like a 98% on the final I'm just going to give you credit for the class
Cuz I was one of the only classes I actually
Did show up
Cool
I could handle that depressing
High school was a
Broadcast
Now I'm producing the show
I don't know
Could
I was just channeling my inner Pierre
Monumental episode to go over that will cover the days
March 5th and 6th
Just Tuesday and Thursday of
This week
Rays baseball score
Of the very infowar
And there's a lot of things we can speculate about what it means
Wyatt what's going on
Is that
Quite a ways down the road
But before we get to today's episode I'd like to give a shout out
Two couple of new people signed up
Inner sporting show
Call Matt
Thank you very much
I'm a policy wonk
Nicole
It's not
I'm a policy wonk
Level
Appreciate it very much
So clit
You and I
I'm a policy wonk
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
To support the show
Little bit lower
Then it is normally but
Full episodes across-the-board
5 Hour episode by the week
Save knowledge fight HD
Will
Dealing with Chicago real estate
And trying to find a new apartment real hassle
Into my life
Appreciate
So Jordan today
Episode
Is it crazy
It's a lot of
Lunatic nonsense
And here is an out-of-context drop
Today Show
But here's how well we start things off on March 5th
March 5th 2000
I'm your host Alex Jones
Herein
And political coverage pants
Here in our new state-of-the-art studio and got through my stereo share now
What are you about to drop
Al-shahristani blockage but we are moving forward thanks for your prayers and your support
Studio
I've been working on for a really long time
I don't know
24-hour
The style.
Football
Network
Well you got like what 3 hours of David Knight
3 hours at 4 hours
Maybe it's two of David Knight
How far of Alex in 28 hours total
I mean Weldon 20 hours is a big jump
20%
You know what even better
Just put your toes in the water there
See if you got somebody who can step up
I mean I believe you have a new studio
About that be almost ready for a really long time
But I believe they finally finished I've Studio
Going to go to 20 hours a day
I think that's just a brass for a long time
But the fact
Westlake
Beginning off of all of these platforms ever
Rolling back
Talk very openly talking about how
Getting kicked off of like Spotify and iTunes really hurt him
Fidgets
Through mediums like that and when you just rub that information
They don't think about it's like all I can remember to listen to the nobody goes to the second page of Google
Right word at
You're more likely to listen to it
And when that subscription isn't there
Messerli going to go to the web
How much money has
Who have lost
From all of that going away
It's it's huge
Studio
Strikes me as blustery nonsense
Clear indication that he has some sort of benefactor
Dark money or an angel investor
I found a bucket of gold
You might just find right
That sort of thing strikes me as that
Being a possibility
But that's not the most important
Don't doubt that at all
The most important
The intro to this episode
I should tell you
The most important thing
Is it Alex
Is wearing a cowboy hat
Dog cowboy hat
And
Set reminder
And about
Can you put a cowboy hat on
And shortened put a cowboy hat on
We know from listening 2000-2010
Alex is mr. Watson Brothers I believe
No longer occupied Texas
Visiting Austin
Having to hang out with Alex
Was a lot of possibility
Number one we could be speculative
Almost
Never leaves the United
Yeah we almost never comes too often I think in the time that I've been listening
Maybe
Twice before I've seen him,
Emagine Lakeville
More
So he's gone
Edward still Alex Mike
Call
Or there's a very simple explanation that Paul was it
Come hang out with Alex
Pay face service
Paul Joseph Watson
No he was like Laura Loomer and all them just hanging around which the argument that he was coming for that
Yeah you talked about how I pack as much cock
Like the sort of thing that would get him out of the United
I'm playing but there's a lot of possibilities
Could mean something
Or could just be
You coming to TPAC
I'm leaning towards that doesn't mean
Well we will have to see
Sonia
So
Pornography
Would you believe
Cuz that was Tuesday night
Stop no it's not about that Alex bolsonaro the video that he tweeted later
So Alex is a big story
The UK that he wants
Talk about that have to do with them
Have some thoughts about that
But I was about to say
Is stupid
Infowars.com as well
Blocks all p***
Free p***
Go to infowars.com
And everywhere
The national move in the UK
Call freeporm is really
Systems
This is the plan
I told Sam to couple years ago
Talking about it
Old is just old
You pay the government
And then they put software on your computer that watches what you do and you give them your ID or passport
Dumps like a truck
The publicly you're going to opt into a dossier
Search.
You turn on the television
A shot works
How did you got another partner in the bedroom with you it's called the British government
It's coming here this is the model
Is that a three-way or how many people are in Parliament
Very few of whom you would want to be in bed for the novelty
He's a bit chunky for my tape
The UK isn't
Blazing age verification system
By proof by providing your license or passport in order to access free p*** sites
P******
Has the cookies in their browser will retain that verification and not require it
To be put in every time they click on a new p*** site
Nobody
I'm not going to that
There isn't a software that you put on your computer
Part of this
Although I think it's a little bit of a clunky sister
Like if you have a shared computer your kids could still easily slip through verify
Your browser there other ways that it's pretty obvious
Ways these get around this but that's not really the big issue
The big concern I would imagine would be privacy
If you give the government a passport
I decode they can obviously track all the poor you look at
Scary
Luckily
The government thought about that and offered another one
Get an age ID
From an article in the Sun
As well as registering with hid
Exit p******** using High Street shops
Shops will offer a special ID card
Known as Porta
Airport email address
There's an anonymity
Target
One of us 1000 shops
In the UK
Built-in
The program to provide a layer privacy
Well still ideally working towards make
It harder for kids to find
I don't think it's worth while I think you're fighting an uphill battle
Insanely easy
Define p***
Hey if you want to
Like back in the day when it was much harder when they were just
Stuff that you can wander into the forest
Yeah it was easier to restrict access to
If you still want to make it a rule that they stuff
Is prohibited to people under 18
Need to come up with a new novel system
To to be able to do that
Because functionally it's not a rule
When I was 16 and they have that little ru18 yes or no
Is going to your sting operation my name's not there
You just click on something
It's just them covering their
And not them actually stopping
It's the
I get it I get
I get it but I also
It's probably ineffective but the arguments
A creating a dossier of B
People's habits and stuff
They have
Parson
The system that are in place
Specifically to assuage that
Concern
I suppose the only thing that I would say my only take on this
Which is look whatever you guys do whatever you feel is right
From reading all of human
History will find
You will not defeat p*** no matter how much you fight against how much you struggle
Drive
Towards sexuality section
Expression
No matter how much
To try and repressive
Whatever for
Spike's what are the books that the church band
Got around in Europe during the you know
1418 there whatever it
Is there was a massive
Bring up p*** distribution
Just end it was just like
Weird illuminated text
It was so huge that
Stuff like a
Literally the Bible with people weren't even allowed to because that was restricted was also being sent along
With tits
You know like all of that underground distribution
Periods to route
Street history
His always also been like you're describing is a piece of
The Vanguard of speech has been on
Metaphor
To fight
Too hard
On menu
Front
Especially the times for the Trident terms of government becomes like this
Confusing. I know it when I see it like that
I will tell you that a video of somebody peeing on somebody in carnival while they jerk off
That's probably why would say that
I don't know if Alex is that the UK isn't
Just trying to stop
Kids
Would that lead you to believe
Because he knows more about
Okay
Government of the UK or the US government
Asinine
Aggressive promotion of homosexuality
Muslims
I just
Lgbtq
Sexualizing
Officially adopted
Nokia bolsonaro is
It's all for a while
Let's let that out.
The story that Alex is talking about school in Salt Lake or salt leave Birmingham
The UK
We're students are being taught about lgbtq
The goal of curbing homophobia early in their lives
This application program was being taught by a man named Andrew
Who interested
Out of all the teachers in the world
Who is on a surprise
Best teacher in the world
There were over 10,000 dominis from 179 countries for this honor and he's
Best teachers in the world
Program called No outsider
Unfortunately he ended up getting
From Muslim and Christian parents who felt that his program was sexual
Just kind of indication could have used the program like moffett's back
Outback license Drive
He was quoted in the guardian
We've got to find a way to engage.
Yes at the moment we're having challenges in my own school but not running
What alternative is there
So
You have this situation where there were a bunch of parents
You complained about this program that was
Promote tolerance and I will go on record as saying that
Should I understand their position and they should also go f*** themselves
Christian Perez
Complained
Muslim parents
Because it wasn't a largely
Muslim
Part of it is kind of
Superfluous
To it just being religious.
I'm sure the study I'm sure the people writing the article definitely had their own little bit of
It was Muslims
There's a little bit of that there
The school ended up kowtowing to the
The pressure
Curriculum
So I mean
A tickets I think
Terrible
The problem solved
I mean that program is kicked out of school
So
Piece of s*** right
Operating
Schools programs
But because these Muslim people made a big stink about it
They were allowed to get out of the
Pro
Yeah like the parents
Muslim
To say
Teach your daughter and your son
About
But
Radical Islam
We're going to put a dress on
This is how the whole left the system works total
None of that is true
And I was curious about this idea is putting forth about the idea that just recently
Muslim grooming gangs
I got arrested
Pedophile
The child abusers who have been arrested
By groups of child
1 stories
Woman being arrested
Epoch times ran a story about 33 man being arrested for sexually abusing children between
2002 1000 in West Yorkshire
Who's the only big stories he can really find
From recent times about England
And groups engagement
Neither of these stories include any indication or even insinuation is to
The race or religion
Persuasion of those
Piece of the equation
Right-wing manipulation
Of a serious issue
For political gain
There's a vast majority of grooming Behavior Asian individual
The demographic category in the United Kingdom that involves people have Middle Eastern
Report put out by the think-tank quilliam
Show the 84% of grooming gang offenders are quote of Pakistani origin with Muslim
This is accepted as gospel by people in these uniformed dekuyper nationalist
Looks like Tommy
Anna Moses
Usher
However people reviewed the report has found some serious problem
The largest is replies under is not a legal designation that exist
The behavior that it describes Faith child sexual exploitation
To be counted as any number of offences
Is the Pentagon
Investigatory
Yeah so it goes to like what was actually
Are you conspiring to
Two prostitutes
Somebody
Alright
According to the guardian Nazir afzal is the crown prosecutor Services formerly Don child
Prosecutor
Most responsible for bringing down grooming gang
The media he observes pounced on cases involving Asian
But often ignores those involved in white
Surprise
They go on to point out that an offender's ethnicity
His alternate only recorded when they're non-white
Which makes more complicated
58 cases of grooming gang arrest
Between 2005 and 27
The problematically
The child exploitation and online protection Centre found 57
Child sexual exploitation arrest
Squilliam
The group regressive left media did it
Completely Savage takedown of the study
Which cuts through all the problems
Definition
Sources methodology analysis
And everything else about the report
Including links to stories of over 100 White perpetrators
That match quilliams data requirements work
Completely ignored by the report
A list
Less than half a day yeah that sounds
They just completely ignored all this
So if you are a f****** propaganda
Ellicottville and a lecturer in security and crime science in an expert on child sexual exploitation
The fuc
Phone
He's going to make fun of names no I'm just saying that that's that's like a weird nowadays determinism kind of thing where your name
Game of Thrones
Put out this report out of a desire for funding and if that's the case
$20,000 from Sam Harris over $1000000 in a grant for the John Templeton Foundation
Interesting Lee appear reviewed study in association today
Sounds that the Templeton Foundation
Was part of the network of Foundations
The quotes supplied fun
To the five organizations involved in actively mobilizing tea party activist
Templeton even finance a group
Called Let Freedom Ring
Which is deeply involved in
Tea party activity and Templeton Junior the head of the foundation was listed in
2011 Mother Jones
As being among the donors allowed it
Add a Koch Industries seminar as haven't given over $1000000 to cocoline causes
Nothing else that would be enough to know he was in
Evil Pizza
By meeting with his Dad who started the whole Foundation
The junior is
Yeah be more active in a lot of this stuff
This is the Overton window
Billionaires Finance organizations
Extremists like Tommy Robinson
So they can work to distract the public from working to actual
We sold the world's biggest problem
Namely that there are billionaires
But I think was probably the most important part about all this
Is the victims voices
That are lost in the shuffle
They're basically just being used as props by these bigoted to run their Auntie diversity scam
And that is a treasure
The independent random piece in March 2018 written by woman who survived
Kidnapped and abused
Rotherham
Grooming gang
And I think her perspective is one that Alex
Mainland Europe
Conflict surrounding immigrants and refugees has been fueled by stories of women being raped by migrant
People have been calling calling for violent action against war on Islam
As someone who's experienced licensed I can tell you what's
None of this is likely to make a difference
Did the behaviors of groomers
Like terrorists they firmly believe that their crimes at the crimes that carry out are justified by their religion
If anything
Probably make groomers stronger in their conviction
And drive ordinary young Muslim man towards fundamentalism grooming gangs
And terrorism
Of course my main perpetrator quoted scriptures from the Quran
However almost identical scriptures
About the stoning to death of Virgin so don't scream when they're right
Can also be found in the Bible
The problem is
The text itself it's how it's fundamentally
In fact
Spy terrible
Human Injustice
People from Africa violence towards lgbtq
All the major world religions including Hinduism and Buddhism
I've also at some point but sometimes human rights abuses against children
Why does my
Terrific religiously sanctioned sexual violence
Torture so I definitely need to be aware of religious extremism
Potentially harmful
So that we can protect people from it
But for Tommy Robinson and his followers to focus on
Anti religion
Based on a cruel misinterpretation of some scriptures by some people
Is unhelpful to say Valley
Many of his religious theories and
Conjecture or not I can relate to
In my real life
.
So
Is this idea about grooming gang
Is generally used as propaganda against
Muslim
Based on this
Origin
Dubiously written
Report by the quilliam faked
Have experienced this
Have a different
Perspective on it
Then people who
Like Tommy Robinson are trying to create a career
Out of fighting against
Using
People like the Survivor as a shield from criticism
Try to stop the theoretical
Epidemic
Caused by Muslims
Do you just really want to hate me
Fury
And you know is the thing that makes it even more obvious
The whole reason behind the
Lgbtq
LG
Goddamnit I cannot
The point the point being
He is saying like
This program
Lgbtq community
It's clearly teaching them oral sex
Which is like no you're obviously obviously signaling that you're real problems going to hold off on that Converse
And possibly fix that peoples
Identities are intrinsically sex
Yeah cuz it's the only way that Alex
I understand that
Take a note
Marla blow somebody
Regular ice cube f****** Maxim magazine
I think what he's doing is gross
I think that when you look
Realities
Talking about it becomes more clear how gross it is yeah and when you read the stories
People who are in fall
It's very tragic
Real issue
But you're never going to solve the issue if
You focus on just like
Is all Muslims doing it was Crackdown on Muslim
And stuff like that
There are groups
Child exploitation
You just have to deal with that
Reality
And then work on
On how you feel
Like it is not a religion it's not the
Fuller going to find a way to preserve
Anytime
Into something that can be used as a bludgeon towards people that don't like
Literature classes
Workshop
Adjust from like reading a book
Like you read I don't know why I keep bringing up a Hundred Years of Solitude on the show
Workshop settings
Even that you sit down
The books
You bring something
Different to it
And you can interpret
The even novels
Profoundly differently than somebody else
There's only one book that I think everybody interpret
It's the same way
And that's A Separate Peace
Have you ever read
It's a book
That everybody pretty much interprets as being terrible
Okay
Bed bug
The same thing you said about gorilla mindset
So it is actually really good
You read it your likes you but then later on
Bonjour Rogan
Other snake attacks coming very soon Josh's bag
Don't worry
One of them is not him coming on torsion
Play sneak attacks us
I think I still have control over hitting the
Boop button
Is very finely I told you to hold your tongue on that idea
You're putting forth about you
Interpreting
View school programs
Being sexual
As because this next clip where he gets
Real gross
It's Muslims they're upset
What about
Sadomasochism
Heard about sex changes in children have you heard about
Fisting
The kids are like what
Cabool pedophilic assault
Social engineers
Can you imagine that
Can you imagine
Anybody being like a child
What do you think about fisting
I don't know how to add you so f***** up fake version of
Text evil globalist to be like
Live countdown what are nine
I just
It's weird it's very weird
Like I really
Like listen to that get bummed out by sexual preference
Like the the word sexual being in there
As opposed to a is not divorced from
F****** s*** is f****** for him
Misconstrued by even
Bright
Disentangle in his mind
Do you have that anyone would
People about
Like gay people
Existing
Like them having conversation we're like
It's fun.
What
What do you imagine
It can be fun to suck dick
But not all the time
Indoctrination
PowerPoint presentation
Yeah
It's not it's not
It would be like my guy almost Nara I think he's got some link
At whatever next clip Alex gets super
As we discussed earlier
Diaz
He's putting forth
About that
Complained about the Muslims can get out of this
Gagan doctrination or whatever
Deseret Industries
Complained about this
He's now decided that Muslims are real cool
This is one of okay support of the weirdest
And I don't think he's going to be able to keep this up
But it does tell you where his truest bigotries lie
I'm going to say it right now on air
I take my hat off
Ahmad Muslim Community
Because they're the only group consistently protesting and saying no
The children as young as 3 years old
The boys are girls
Pedophile
Colt runs in UK
So I salute
Muslims in the UK
Her being better people than the average British citizen
Better than the police above the government that's what about that
That is weird
That is really weird
Sufficiently homophobic
Jeff creating false versions of
The UK Muslim Community
Yeah
You went from like
A week ago being like Muslims throw acid in people's faces and they're the only ones who kill people to be like
Heathrow Kings of Build-A-Bear Cisco
It's so f****** terrifying to continue listen to this cuz this is present-day Alex
Like you want to live in 29 in 2019 and thanks was this week
Done with your b*******
And it's like nope
Still there
If they'll f****** there all the times always
I promise you there's no like greater context
Activist that makes it make sense
Parents complained about this
Tolerance program this school and now he's decided
Muslims
Play
Beautiful
Islamophobic rant
You did that birthing couple years back about going to suggest kicking all those ones out of the car
Country
What the f*** is this what are you doing
It's nonsensical
Well you got to give it up to the Somali pirates
You got to give it up to him
Like I said you was talking about the grooming gang stuff
Earlier this address
And
He said something in this next clip
I have to say it maybe
Stop at 12 year olds
Why
What what what
Confidently say they've stopped at 12 year old
Nothing
There could even be a headline
I don't see any reason why
I don't get what he's doing
What kind of lunatic would be like well
We got to figure out the age of these child grooming gangs quit so
Headlines
Grooming gangs usually stop at 12 there's super into exploitation and kidnapping
When people fight
We have limit can't do it
Well that's good
This is crazy
This is nonsense Nana's and I don't understand
Really what the point is
Is his anger at Muslims
Conditional
His discomfort and
Very serious problems
The gay community
Lgbtq community
Is not Paramount
Yes I think that is what we can take
Solidly
Positive
Within days he will start yelling about
Undoubtedly
Brief moment where it almost seems like he realized
Is that Christian extremist
Like himself
Have far more in common with
With Muslim extremist possible with anybody else
Hey man
You want to do lunch and I want to kill people too but at least looking both
I'm up and make Society super press
Possibility
Just trying to troll for like media attention
Somebody picks
Isn't this voter yet
Yeah something like that
Joseph Watson
More boring than just a good that happened
Alex has another big breaking story
Have to do with
Like to talk about
Trump derangement
Syndrome
And that is
Trump does
Is no good
Snowflakes
If we've seen anything since the mid
It's that there's a far larger
Proportion of media figures
Especially
That have
Syndrome
I think one of the main reasons
You can really eat their what
In the sense that like she engages on social media and dunks on people
Pretty regularly better than they are firewifi like propaganda
Duncan Robinson
A big scoop about
And I have a scoop about that scoop
It's not a scoop
That I really don't want to just put it out there not giving attention
You will
And
Everybody's really excited right now.
Yeah you know me
The Creature from the methamphetamine with gun
Everyone is just so excited that she
She didn't steal a million
I went in this morning when I saw it in the SEC record
Federal Election Commission records
Of course her and her business manager pocketed Millions
Totally legal
The first thing I would point out is that
Well first of all
Has not been
I read I read some of the story and immediately it was
I'd like I read the headline that I read a little bit more and I was like oh guys you are really trying ever
Read They're throwing everything
We especially the con artist variety on the right
Find SEC data about the funding of AOC campaign
Considering their hard records
Little more than two billion dollars NetSpend
Approximately
Smile again for the campaign
The amount even raised by political 1590
$2
Also I have no idea what records from the Securities Exchange
I don't know what that has to do with it
No
Amazing amount of b******* right there looked at stock record
Sure
Really strong indication that he's making stuff up records
About her campaign fund
Alright buddy
So
This is all just part of a right-wing smear
Finance
I don't pretend to know everything and if the in the next few months there any indications
Brazen
That's what they'll be a problem and I'll take I'll take that when that comes when there's any proof
It doesn't appear that they did
From the information available
So the issue at hand
Is that psychiatry
Brand new Congress and one called Justice Democrat
Campaign LLC
What is the temperature
Public about this was
Create a system where would be possible
They don't have to spend all their time fun drive
Fundraising
To run for office
The Pac-12 send some of the money to the LLC
Which would provide the services
Candidates
Worry about the elements of running for office that often keeps qualified candidates for me
Inconsiderate
This is a new fundraising bottles
But their lawyers have added what they do and aboveboard
Found that to be accurate whenever they came up with the idea
Utterly and completely public about hey this is our news
We're letting you know way up front
Verse same day we started and we told you
Chakrabarti appeared on The Rachel Maddow Show to discuss fundraising strategy on May 18th 2016
Exactly
Grimm the DC bureau chief
The intercept
Looked into it back
In 2018 and found their practices were all above board
On some
We will chat
At least you're now Justice Democrats
I've had a post up on their website explain how the process works
Discussing the legal standard
And highlighting how the money is
And why the system needs to be set up like that in order to
They're very transparent about that
What happened to the Alex. Sensational article in the Washington time
And didn't realize that it was
Was just a smear based on something
Explain two year ago
This is sloppy s***
But it demonstrates how are you today
Derail her abilities Beyond
Especially the oversight committee people not want someone like her
Get her you can't take her down
Take her down she's not
The Democratic Party
People who
Are long-time career politicians are dangerous
Is as well exactly
Do you have a part of the reason that the Centrist Democrats are aligning so hard with Republican
Yeah at least appear to be inclined
Their capacity is
Vegan
Position
Screw things up for a lot of people who posted for a very long time
And as much as Alex likes to pretend
But he's above the rigmarole on the bric-a-brac
He's very beholding to a lot of those things
Because he
Define some salt as opposed to it
Yeah it what is mainstream
What does he do
How did he stay in opposition to the thing
That is what Maine
Extreme culture turns into
Completely
Morrison
The people who he complains about you you hate the status quo
And that's your status quo
420 brand is against
X yeah
If exchanged
That's hard
Do that
So Alex
It turns out also this is this is pretty good
Does pretty good information
He missed a production meeting
Before this may
March 5th episode
I don't think
Define dubious about.
The way he describes his
Is processed in this next clip
Is so amazing
Someone tried to
Describe it this way
Tries to take their advice and described it as virtue
That kind of thing
What makes them
Good
You'll see what I
And I just didn't get here for production meeting this morning show
Want to move face to tomorrow if we don't have that
It was the same story yesterday on
Animal producing now live on air
This is totally transparent television
Wonder why
The same talking points every show from
It's just corporate guys right up here
And then they put it out
And that's what they do over and over again so that's why it's so boring
Reply it's so stale
You know it's not spontaneous that's why
The first time
Because people are
Hungry
For reality
I love reality
Those other places prepare due-diligence
Warriors before
Yeah sure Alex multiple times
Google X
It's important Alex
But he gives Rogan
First appearance
Was the biggest of all time
That is true compared to his first one
But neither of them are even half of the downloads on YouTube
I don't either I don't care I don't even I don't even want a I don't even want to mention that pettiness
Because his pettiness is insane and it's once again
An example of him
Clearly telegraphing that he
Used
A man who thinks he's his friend and he is not
Call myself because he does bring up
Elon Musk episode did better than his first episode but now this new episode
Alex is about 9 million
Downloads
Of the new episode
Elon Musk
2 / 20
I know I know I know I know I know
I'm preparing this episode but
Comparison to the amount of research
John to prepare the
A prepare research
I did 30 minutes research on that stack
I get hours of research on this.
Previously in the currently
I don't know that mean
But also if you like and you only do I like
200 pages of articles
All of the claims that are presented in it
Find out who are the people
30 minutes
Go f*** yourself Alex
I ran out of time so I only had 30 minutes to prepare updates
Because they've never looked
So it's
Yeah
Added a bunch of research on this.
And so I'm here
I'm just telling you that
Dolittle
I completely forgot to
That was his audience or people
30 minutes
Who is who plays HR his father why doesn't Alex make eye contact with me
Busy doing research
He's just trying to make make things right on it
Things that little love
Diza is talking to the producers now video
You're rambling this is nonsense go to a video adrenochrome
Bright
Me nude what are you talkin about
The only way that it's not
Oh my God
I got to get my house in order
Got to do 30 minutes of research on my stack
Play this on Rogan show.
To Brogan wouldn't let him
Because
Dickie head
Like the beginning of the video is a clip from Fear and Loathing
Where they talk about
30-second skip past it
And he's really proud
A liter of quarter of children
Back to the bloodline looking
You want to know why that's bulshit
And then take another step further past that realize that Hunter S Thompson wasn't writing realshit
Another step back
From people who have done it
Really ineffective
Thompson was real journalism
Gary Hart being an addict
280.
Existed
And weaved into
Of the hyper
The realistic version of
Fear loathing
Makes complete sense
Dogs
But if you want to just watch for your love
I've seen it a few times and that 20
17 minute 20 years
Been a long time
Don't miss it
Me too I do like
He does really get a chance to shine he doesn't make any sense
That's everyone's in snatched
There's a poster that looks like a poster for snatch
Has Benicio del Toro part of my memory
That time that I worked at the movie
It's something
He was in
The post
Very close
Was he one of the
Original High Skies was wearing the
I'm going to
Going to be the worst moment of my life
Dance on your face
Traffic
Know that
Frankie four fingers
Myself
Got a check
Next movie after
Could have swore that he wasn't instead
God dammit
Wolfman
That was not a great one
She could have swore he wasn't immediately remembered after I said if Eddie was
I'm so sorry
Does gasliter gaslighting in action you made me think that there were
Another poster that I was thinking
Next clip
Bring up the names
Obviously
Means the face gold which is horrible
Sign of things to come at Faith Goldie's in the mix we're all in trouble. No one's doing great yeah
Pack and breastfeeding
She comes on the show we're not going to listen
Too much of her
But I will say that
You go back and you listen
To her
Appearance
Is she speaking in a lot of code
Real
Yeah yeah yeah
It would it would end up as being like let's listen to 20 minutes of her her interview
I didn't think it was worth it
I feel like we can take that as read
Did she has sort of
Neo-Nazi
Leaning
We talked about that a ton before
I think it's more interesting
That this is how Alex
Decides
Start their conversation
Little bit inappropriate
I wanted to get you on because
You're doing what's really
Really
Faith
You are going after
The Shootist
Lee's Chicken
Republican
Establishment or really just Democrat
Twitter right now in the show Mountain View
But you don't class two beautiful women together for smart women
No. Right now
So he's like
Married
F****** gross that's inappropriate
Unbecoming
Of someone who tries to
To pretend he's Hesperia
That episode we talked about with Katie Hopkins
It's like that stuff
It doesn't even seem to indicate the
So I'm not going to Alex's Behavior
Inappropriate
8 is 1 of those things on the right-wing they're like
These Republican
Beautiful
I love
It's it's crazy and then you get a little something
Daddy is again the idea of how you shift over
Look at it like it's so important what you're doing and that's going against the Republicans that aren't hard enough
Crazy as we want
National
We need
The people who were sort of milquetoast on the fence
To be forced
Take the position that they don't walked in order to save their bases
You are doing that and you
You're hot if people like it that you're doing it just like Jan Morgan
Very exciting for him
So
Isn't that cool if Alex talks about her time at CPAC
I'm not sure that she comes in on this cliff
Too much
Complaining
This is wild
Express in the same breath
That he doesn't have a problem with people being
Gay but also that there's too many gay people in the GOP
Which is hard that's a fine line to walk especially since that line doesn't exist in your just a
Homophobe isn't good at
He's not a good typewriter
Is him trying
Swell
Jake Lloyd
Democrat
What about your pillow
Homosexuality issue
The Republican Party
What's this song
I don't understand what he's trying to present because if you just take him at his word
Too many gays live in there
Right blackmailing with the idea that they're in a relationship
How is everyone
Bite the pillow
So you guys come and be on our side on
I thought it was crazy cuz that democracy was a sexually transmitted disease
Express is homosexual blackmailed by intimate partners with Athens
Committed relationship
Monogamous
Facebook it's complicated
Oud seed
Cricket
Please try to express his nuts on its face
And then it's even more nuts but he's trying to
You say that like
Outlook
If you say you don't have a problem with
Like people being
Lgbtq
But that you also say we have a gay problem in the GOP I really feel
Listing the same space
I actually do have a wave
Can have that conversation
But
It's not the way out
How can we have that conversation
Well if we accept that there are a lot of gay p
People closeted in the GOP
Maintaining cover of being or having a beaver part of the LGB
Community
They have to
Make compromises
Subway dzar
LGB
It's that
They wouldn't
Be accepted
Were they
Live publicly
In the political sphere
So the issue isn't
There's a gay problem that problem
Yeah
Also gave lesbian
Is Alex is talking about that then his position on this
Totally different
It would be
We need to all be more accepting
People of different
It's sexual proclivities
As opposed to
To being like
Too many of these f***
GOP
The f******
Seems text Democrats and get blackmailed
F****** weird
That is such a weird thing
Okay
So our problem isn't that they're gay
Our problem is that gay
Can be blackmailed by
Partners
Because if they were out
We would not accept them in the GOP
Contingent
Exactly
Hallucinating a larger problem
But you're still at that
Entire interview
And there are tons
Of like
Zales
He's talking about
The problem
Call them the globalist
Finish prattles off like a joke
Relations of
Existence is there also
Code words
In order to
One World Government
The protocols
Typo
Tough interview n
And I think space like
I think this makes it clear distorted
What you saying
We all have to do our part because
They try to take
Chuchua Grassroots
A truly Grassroots Revolution
Which means to return
The old order there's absolutely nothing
That's right in the old order is the New Order of Renaissance
Nice 2500 years
These demon and lizard
Those really consider what you got you got the demon
Which is something that Alex
Andy's classic
Related
Blizzard
That's f****** faver-dykes characterization
The characters who he pretends out real in the protocols
Pictures of f****** believe there's lizard
To be like
We all know what we're talkin about the gap
Would be something that I would even be willing to entertain is if she tried to coat it be like
Lizards
Break
Like if she if she bucks back
Defensive
To learn from
Faith criticism
Different conversations
Jordan in the next
Rodger Stone
Isabel
Wednesday
He does have a
Securing on Monday
I would say I think
Bb8
Percent chance U
I'm going to be so mad if he doesn't go to prison
I'm not to be mad I'll be surprised
It'll be like a
Oh my God so I told you already that Rodger can't be on the wall
Alex is kind of pissed off about that
Talk about it
Shroyer
You sent me a text message
Especially the end of this morning
The Goblin
He said that too
Sad and
So I can send
Private conversation
People on
Flexi-Rod group
Is the
Rodger getting a gaggle
Control Rogers narrative
Like entirely absolutely
He just texted me said I love you man
I love you
He's going into fight the Goblin
Or whatever
He can now shape this exactly how he wants
This is a win
He doesn't have to deal with Rodger trying to beg for donations on his show which was a huge sticker
Hey now
Yep Rogers become the person that he can go to and say all they didn't allow me to have a pencil in there so I'm
Just going to tell you what he said what is a pencil
Control of Rogers narrative
Anymore
I guarantee
Rajaton f****** text him I love you I'm going to defeat the Goblin
They're going to murder me and it's because you betrayed me
Text me that he loved me the other day Alex you're not fighting hard enough for me I'm going to get Travis Irvine to come up there and kick your ass
I hope you go down with me
Rodger texted me that you love me the other
You son of a b**** was on there and tell everyone that Randy credico a g
Like I've been trying to get
Get on get on it
Jack Rogers
F*** that must be a real weird relationship
Complete control over it
Confront and that is awesome power.
So navigate to the point where Paul Joseph Watson shows up
Forbath
Call Noel
I hope I hope he gets hit by a truck
I'm talking about how
Real
Real week
But this next
Illustrate
Perfectly their
You get technocracy connection
Completely
Basically
People have access
To everything
This is the army
And I say level connections everything
Represent the idea that like if you're a good globalist
With the system and stuff like that thing
Like his blackheads
Embarrassed
The only reason that I think I clipped
I'm telling you something
That's how
Look at me
We're not lying this
Time you are to default
Conversation
And you will sometimes
That
Look at me
But here's what I'm about to say
A number of times
I love it I love that dynamic
Because it's it's first of all abusive
Been there for f****** ever so you know
He knows what he's
So much money
Like if you consider the salaries
Time for like a course
How much is Paul making
Yeah it's it's sickening the very least enough to afford a flight to Austin
Take money for what does
And for remarks of Lights Austin
Pretty expensive even from Chicago
Malone from
Old
Yes
So
He's talkin
Censorship and how
Conservatism
Under attack
Where do I find
I find perfectly boring and I don't want to talk about because I just don't care
Most of the time it relies on
Twitter or or whatever Antichrist
Trackdown
A million different
Threads
Help
Right I just
It's not
Even if
Even if every
Is true I'm still not convinced that I care
Yeah I don't
I'm going to leave that all aside
Because Alex said some really f***** up things
Studio
Appalled
Is totally fine with
The first one isn't all that sucks up but it is a little
Backpack
And I watch Tammy Allison or or New Wave hookers
New apartment
CeCe he's not poor guy also he was caught with p*** open I know I was going to say go f***
Kind of matches with Alex's psychology Arrested Development
Where the younger you would pretend
Call
The real thing
F*** off
Kind of
Mcmeme the story
The idea that
Revealed on air
And all that stuff
It's Debbie Does Dallas
So in this point we get back to
Did AOC narrative
Alex
Is going on
With Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Dinesh D'Souza
I'm Batman
Number 2 documentary
And they're really upset about him going in the 2016 election
Thousand dollars
They said it wasn't listed properly on Federal Form
You're welcome
I got the article right here we can show TV viewers
The shoes
Cortez
Years ago
Millions of dollars
He's trying to conflate the idea of these like justice Democrats Ryan.
Champagne
So there's a few problems
And their similarity
The first thing is
That's the fur
Problem what Dinesh D'Souza explicitly a felony
What AOC did was
Completely legal it was the brand new Congress and Justice Democrats
Also they were worried about Dinesh D'Souza in the 2016 elections so they did
They put him in prison
That's absurd
Since he was charged on May of 2014
Also District 2016 election before any of the primaries really egg
They had psychic powers
Play the guilty
Because he knew that he would have played play the victim card in the court of public
But he could only play the role of
Court
Right
Minimize whatever sentence
These are completely different scenarios
Is right
This is a demonstration of how his brain work
Connecting are not related at all
Conundrum
The Republican is not Republican
5 faces with Trump
Trump has committed campaign violations
Trump has broken the emoluments clause
Trump has committed all kinds of crimes that are well and very obvious
So4
They have to try and create a what about
So like this okay
You're more right than you even
No because
LLC registered by
It was registered
Delaware
Pretty regular thing
Yeah
Corelife
In Subway's
Insult
Even better serve
Alex Newell
He was talking about
Vet like
Hey
You know
Michael Cohen established an LLC in Delaware specifically
Except even more
Make
Cohen couple
Look you know but it's like you avoid that
He's already established
What's the narrative where it's all cullinan
They're all just bad at like Ira I read so many things
Oh did you guys know
Feds
Aoc's campaign advisor
Millionaire
Guys
If you're pathetic
Actually went to production
And I was in
Be doing a much better job
That's what I would say
Yep
So we got to stop giving advice
This next clip
I only included because Alex does Bernie Sanders
Because I'm Petty
So let's get through it
Talk about
The hypocrisy because
Tommy's in socialist never owned a factory
Just steal money Paul like like
White people
IDrive hundred-thousand-dollar vehicles
Bernie Sanders has written at least
I was going to say also that's from Of Mice and Men
But it's pretty close to his burning
Paul Joseph Watson finally
You haven't heard
He's there he's blooming in
The wings cuz I don't want to ever hear his voice
Not over Skype
I'll tell you that
Not over the phone
But intersex
He thinks he has a god
About to Alexandria Ocasio
Cortez radar
Good if
Because on its face
This is a bad wreck
Reputation
But let's another break-in Scandal by AOC
Which is a complete
Fight new story
She's tweeted the Jerry Falwell basically wanted to kill a Muslim
This is President Trump's fall Orange
This common
From folwell did not
Cloud
Alright Paul
Tall
You are missing the forest for the trees
Also they said the Trump said the n-word over and over at CPAC with that's not true he said it at my place
A couple of weeks ago same level of like that I'll like it like it was in a c-pack
Okay I understand and Jerry Falwell Jr
That it was
Good shoot
Right if more people had come
Concealed carry
You could stop those Muslims before they
Did blank
And then he fumbled over his words by him as he was speaking
Because what he was trying to say obvious
Terrorist
Whatever
Right came out of his mouth
Because those words exist in the same part of his brain
Criticisms that are being made about
If more people had concealed carry guns they could
Until Muslim
Before they douche
Exactly that is a part of
What is autopilot
Sure that we put a good picture
Because we can't have any anti-Semitic
Kill all Muslims
Straub and Paul Joseph Watson
Create
Not what anybody is saying that you
What did say
F***** up
So
I mean
To take her face because it was
How she said it was
How do we lose its beak
Cuz they don't care
Because they don't f****** care has
About money and Society
That's a good point
Yeah
Because
Rarely
Has Paul Joseph Watson Institute
They've been working together for a decade
Do your bodies
He calls all the time is that all I need
Get this article up
Right just write articles
Alright big headache
Depend
Relationship
Yeah
Studio and they spend like I said a lot of time talking about
Were victims immediate Center
But
I think
They come
Wasted
The rest of the time
But they have
Half an hour
On an issue
No one cares
They're wrong
About
Jordan is going to be grossed
Who's going to run for the Democrats
Michelle Obama's not going to run because she needs a physic
Tustumena washes
Nobody even if you left the old upholstery serious
She has the face of a man chest shoulders
It looks like she's got a a summer sausage enter fan
It's like Obama was raised by a train transsexuals obsessed with it
That Michelle Obama is Michael
She's got but we worked out yesterday
Lubbock
And somebody
But I mean the fact that she's got
It's not a bad thing
It's just that what weird psyop
For the elites are they so obsessed with me
First
That's crazy
Conversation
Brothers four
Maybe 15-20 minutes
But Michelle Obama being a man
It's it's real f*****-up
Mobile right there
You ever thought
It's not a good thought
You're very angry
I'm just going to sit here and
Figure out how to put this into words
Is aphasia
Very generous
Putting what I'm thinking
I would I would go as Primal scream
Wendy Marcus.
I'm actually very
II
Just been pathetic
Can't
Except
Because this
Outside of
Regular
This is something that's outside
Not not for everybody
I mean for this
Subsection of humanity called
Badfinger
Yet will I mean this
F***** up
When I hear stuff like this I just
You have gotten so into
Trolli
Memelord sort of
World of
Of the internet
The departs of Reddit
But you have lost
Control of what
You're even saying
Because in the past
Waffle between like
Legit accusations
That they're lying about
Michelle Obama
Being
Yeah
We were just joking around when people Preston
I'm about it
I don't like
That he's now
Sort of Rhian
Invigorating
This in 29
But I also recognize that he's probably trying
Covering
Like that's the disorder
Defensive game that we have to play all the time now
Because when he talks about these sneak attacks like going on Rogan
The speaker tags are also him talking
I'm about stuff like this cuz he's hoping people will cover him to give him more attention
He leaves
Hewitt on his left his own device
Wilderness
Who is going to run out of supplies
Ready
Quit
At this point
But if he keeps playing games like this
Keeps trying to do
Do things
Essentially troll people into keeping his name in the headlines
You gets a little bit of
You get some supplies
He get some water
He get some
Really f***** up
People who believe whatever
Dumb s***
Cute rolling to Media ways to donate
Or whatever you're like that
The game
That's a possibility
Other possibilities
He just doesn't give a s***
7 fun with his buddy
Either way
So abhorrent
And so pointless
And they think it's
Funny and it's not like I'm just as I am
There's nothing even
Orderly rapist
Cuz it's really racist
Serena is so good because she's actually a myth
Things were never replied to like Sharapova
I guess she wasn't that great
A better figure than tennis player
Against strong
Women of color
Their stature
It's so hard to unpack because it is an attack
But even
Call
Attack is on
Because
People
Don't stake.
Word cheat
It would be
A horrible
Nothing but in that world it is
It's f***** up
I don't think either of us are triggered
In the problem
You were breaking up
Disappointing is a massive under
Massive understatement bring up is also a problem
Conversation about
There is a part of it that you're trying
Gheefunny
There's no joke
But the other thing is
Alex
I'm not joking
This is like
This is true
This is
Fruit
If the joke is that he
He keeps saying
He believes
No joke
Where's a joke
How many how many different ways are the globalist ways can you describe this
First off
Anyting
That invalidates literally anything you have to say about anything
If you ever talk about anything that the President says or does
Criticism that the president
You have been validated and you are worth
Is so much
Similar to
So many conversations we've had where it's like
Let's engage with the right and how they think
There's nothing to engage with
You gone
He is not to be involved
.
A lot of thoughts
I will Octonauts as well
Niihau
Not about this being
Nefarious
Occupied with the ID
Idea that Michelle Obama
Play
Whether I'm right or wrong
I mean Michelle Obama
Anna
When she comes out it's like
Everybody's
Problem
Water hose
He's real interested
No I understand
I meant gross show
Weird talk about
Corn
Teaching kids to 5th and school and what have you
And then towards the end of it for like 20 minutes
This big Swingin water hose like it's gross like
From just a level is like doing a radio
Show show I would say
This is gross
Disgusting
Any other radio shows like
But there was watching a video of Trump's press conference at
Nothing between his legs
I think
He is actually a Ken doll
I don't think he has a penis
I think it was removed
Nazi
Father
And I hope everybody knows that my prompt
Chicago
Comedian Adam Burke
Micropenis
And that
Hit this to me you're such a
Distillation
Of
How Alex
Deals with
Yes people criticizing
He thinks that they're f******
Accordingly
My problem is the more they mess with me the more I work inside the week
Did I just expect you to give up
Going to go anywhere
Nothing's going to happen
Like like you like you
Do I dream about
That's not good that's not good
Sympathetic
Like these apps
Concrete ideas
Reporting
You f***** up on this
Do you work
Putting people in danger
You have caused
Harassment
Tons of people
That sort of
Big because of your action
Because of the lack of
Well I mean earlier you said you missed this production meeting
Just do your editorial s*** on Arabic
Cause of that sort of sloppy
You have caused me
Massimo
In people's lives
Will look
They're f***
That's fine
F****** with
And I went people f*** with
I want to strangle
Wrangling
We're done
Wednesday
It starts
And Alex Hayes
Big announce
Just a few minutes ago before we went live
Emergency call from Tommy Robinson
Leftist
Documents
Desperately trying to set him up and send him back to prison
Brought down
Nationwide
Tens of thousands of children free
I thought yesterday on the show
You were saying that the Muslims are the only ones
You are great
Does bettas and Tire
Career
Demonized
Muslims
Is a living hero
I'm not sure Moses
Not sure really how to work that like Moses
Tell you about what this is about
On the evening of March 4th Tommy Robinson showed up at the house of a British journalist by the name of Mike.
I saw this unfolding on Twitter about how scary the experience for him
Police reports that
At least one article in the guardian
And Tommy Robinson Zone
Live stream
Study put out
Micah doing some reporting on Tommy Robinson
Habit of showing up at his critics
In the clear attempt to intimidate them into silence
In addition to
Dachshund
Without ever
Because he's
Live streaming
My kitten's trying to get the ball rolling on a class action lawsuit against Robinson
Clearance
Betting definition
So naturally Tommy showed up at Mike's house around 10:15 p.m.
Bang on the door and insisting that he want to just talk
Just wanted to talk
My climate there was banging on multiple doors and windows
What you took as a sign that it wasn't
Just Tommy there
As this was happening he began getting tons of messages on social media
Different account
Tommy
All stuff Mike
Is posted screenshot
Mike called the police
And told him to leave
What you did
Only to return back on bike store again around 5 a.m.
My call the police again and filed
Tommy Robinson is doing damage
Neutral
Because
It's an absolutely clear cases what he did was illegal
And out Mike isn't afraid of
David please audio and video.
He probably wouldn't have to give the police anything so it's Tommy's livestream had all the evidence
Necessary
Including Tommy Robinson giving out my
Full address
And threatening to expose him and calling him a paddle
In order to save face as all these monstrous assholes
Tommy is now playing the victim
Houston saunas
He went over to this guy's house
Threatening
Because it was in response to
To him receiving a
Informant
Against him that was
What you think's is exposing its
He didn't allege that Mike
Head
Things to do with letter being delivered
I don't know why you think so
Him showing up at this guy's house
Twice in a night
Is an appropriate self-defense
Absurd
Your honor I do not stalk that man I just showed up at his house multiple times in the middle of the night
Without his consent and screamed at him and knocked on his door
Other than
And I gave out his address to everyone listening in my life
Forever ever violent stupid
What this all boils down to is that Robinson's fifteen-year-olds Syrian child
Edit School in Huntersville
Because he can't accept any in
Victims of something
You made videos claiming with a child in those
Girls at the school previous.
The videos
Something that he was in all likelihood just making up explicitly said was false
Mike stockberry was part of a group
That was raising funds to
Play pay the legal car
Just
Slander Against Child
And he was
Fuct
What do monsters do when they're back
What corner they attack
Or in this case
Show up
Mike
Received tons of messages on social media
From Robinson
They're on their way to his house
People on Circle
Even in Europe
European far-right Circle
And
Mike posted
The video of coming home to find a note
Azdor
It says we'll be back
But of course Alex doesn't give a f***
He doesn't care that Tommy slandered an innocent fifteen-year-old child who was the victim
Bullying
It started all of this
He doesn't care that Tommy absolutely harassed Mike's duckberry in a criminal and actionable way
And Michael
Terrorized
Because of it
No
The story that Alec
How to tell
It's how everyone
Poor Tommy Robinson
Deal with
These people who are
Is surrounding it. I will say
The only version of is that I
F****** come close to
Cuz Alex
Please a video
Of
Confronting people outside his house who he says are MI5
They have recording equipment in the back
Back of the car whatever
It's very
It's nonsensical
8 is not evidence of any
But
If they are
They are there because what
He did to this guy
Because
He
The other night
Went over to this guy's house
The police came
Talked him into leaving
And then 56 hours later
Showed back up
This guy
When all he done
Is respond to the fact that Tommy
Slander.
Who was the victim of bullying
It was like
Let
Crowdfund
The legal defense
Required for this person
Just do him
Be able to
It's monstrously
Pathetic
And Alex
Is
First aid in Tommy is
It's faster
8 idiots
Wide variety of
Acceptable punished
That don't actually
You fit the reality of the
Is that
Tommy Robbins
Has done more damage to the world
Steve yaxley-lennon Orem
Whichever
Has done more damage to the world than anyone murderer
But if you murder somebody you're going to spend your life in
Probable murder
You are the instigator for so much
Violence and horror
And yet
Your you're
Amethyst
To the stuff that I wanted
Bring into the conversation
Grooming gang stuff earlier
When we talked about how all of this
This bike Williams
Reports reports
They put out was
Deeply flawed and
Didn't take him to work out
That fit their own diagnostic
Because they were white
Tommy Robinson to someone who
His Maiden entire career
Out of
About
Muslim
Our leading these
Rape
And he's the only person who's willing to stand up against it
Give Tommy
Hover
For the Islam
Phobic
Bigoted
Xenophobic
Yeah it exists in
This whole
Continue
So Alex is got this message
From Tommy that's not good
Critical
But you can't khatami on the phone
Cuz he's the
So
We get to Alex
Telugu story
Arrested for Christian cross
Across the street
Germany Sweden others have been ordering churches near Old processor
Wonderful thing
Alex is talking about
From this story
Posted on
Euronews
35g
Greeks that charges of public property
Anorexic Construction
The cycle
On the Cliffs of apia in Viet
Lesbos is capital
Is on the grounds of the island
Archaeological law
They weren't in trouble because it was a cross
Xenophobic
Because of where they built it
The exact article talks about how a simple cross was erected
But it wasn't on protect
So no one got arrested
How to
Profound way sloppy
Because it was on archaeological ground like protected
It was because the ghosts
The bring that up in the article but
Thrust of the article is like
Let's believe that that's
Bulshit
Wow nonsense
His article includes
The fly
Interesting Lee the same Rocky cliff
Is where a quote
Cultural coexistence
Tore down another
Because it was
Offensive to migrants
Their source for that story is a hyperlink
Another Infowars story
The only source for that second for stories and articles
Greek City Times
It doesn't say that a quote
Cultural coexistence
Tore down the cross
That is completely made up by Ben Warren
The writer of this Infowars already
That article
In the
Greek city time
As well as the recent one in the Euro News
Only reports that a group called cook coexistence
Communication in the education
He complained about the cross and request
Is there a month
Later it was destroyed by Vandals
There's no indication
Head
Add vandals are the same
That's okay
Chores
In their editorial
That's as the level of like this is Barbra Streisand donates $100,000
Is coming out of Senator inhofe mouth and then Ten Years Later being like
I don't need a reference that Barbra Streisand down there today was you though
You're linking to your own f****** artist all the time
That's pathetic
What did the original story was written by Paul Joseph Watson
Concrete cross
To the Greek City Times
Witchduck
Say that
Coexist
Enough through like
Take to switch won't do
Person who wrote the
Infowars
Just make the
Existence group
Toward
Explicitly
And there is nothing in any
Resources
Anyway back that up really
The premise of
Varsho but I like these
Concrete
That are just like this is bad
Reporting on a
Indisputable
I'm take all of you
That is literally just job
I don't even care what direction this is torture
If it was a project reporting something you don't have the right to
Episode we talked to
You accuse me
Paul Joseph Watson
I'm showing up
In Austin
Absurd
It's crazy
Yeah
To excuse it
Feisty
All of the
People posting that Paul Joe spots
Studio
A group on Facebook
Let's knock it weird about that
Like he was showing up there too
Now it's time to get weird when I listen to the March 6th
Next Episode by figure it out I know exactly
Why he was
And
This is the end of Infowars
Pushed you
I guess 89 years ago to start your own Twitter to start your own YouTube to get out on air
And I have encouraged you just because the way the world works
Go out and do more and enacted
I know we tried to do some TV stuff in England
NFL through trying to herd cats
Your own site your own operation we're very excited about that any successful operation
You also spawned
Your only hope is they will grow up to be just as strong and successful as you've
He had to make himself at the Abbey
He's done
That
Individual
Holy s*** well I think it's a smart move on Paul's Parts because Alex is already said
Start your own thing
You didn't need him for years
Paul Joseph Watson is he
Basically
To soft launch
His own goodbye
Amazing
Was
I think
Probably an excuse to come to
Studio
And then also
Probably
Tie up some loose ends
Yeah
Are you says on this episode
Like it's in need
I'm done with it down with Infowars
He's doing the whole thing he's saying goodbye but is God
Latest
For this guy
Ziploc
Are you recognized
See the writing on the wall
Huh
It's bad
His
Friend
Oldies old
People
There's no real engagement
People who are younger do like me
It's because of History
And he's do that service
To do this
Hurrah together one last time
That kind of goodbye
And he's going back to f****** London
And he is going to stay there
Empire
Let's see who we get
Available
Is a lot of people within 40 probably also look at the trucks yet
Completely poach the entire operation so f******
Looting funder
Yeah the people who pay Alex's didn't have an ego too big
I think that this is like
I know that
Hey I may be
Speak to
Sometimes
This is
Alex
John this really is it
This is like
Illusion Paul Joseph Watson
Is
Stoke
Crucially
Devastating
F****** moment
I don't see how he exists
Because
Paul Joseph Watson was really the only thing that
A demographic that wasn't
Adagio
People who are still mad about OKC
I don't know
Brain survive
Leaving the one
Without the one person
Who kind of connect
Under 50
Yeah I really don't understand
I might be wrong my projects
But it's
I don't know who she is so the answer is probably not
Kent State
Who now works
F*** off
Butterfly kits
Can I hear this
That the fact
The first date
Why did you waste that time
With your guy
Knowing that the next day on are you were going to announce
He's going solo
He is done
And they keep you in the spring weather like
We'll still collaborate
I don't I don't I don't like the idea of
Them
Claiming that Michelle has
Has a dick being there
Like the end of Ocean's 11 moment where they're all standing around
The f****** fountain
No not thinking that they're going to get back together now we're going to part ways
I don't like that
What Alex need
To do to try and not deal with the reality that Paul
And that he had
Pushed Paul out
He said
Repeatedly on here
We can't afford to pay the salary I might have to lay him off
If you're Paul Joseph Watson what are you going to do
Fight for yourself create your own sake
Haven't eaten for years
So do your own f****** thing
Is that real
Royale
It's going to be a disaster
I don't know what is
Man
Heavy
Fitness
Rock the foundations of War I don't know
You thought I was talking s*** when I started this episode
Redwood Rock the foundation of the many times before
This time I was
This is
This is huge
Holyshit
Cuz nobody
He has on staff
Is even close to his popular or as good
A propaganda is Paul
Like
These people
Schlub
He's got
Imagine how pissed off he is
Is this the color of money are we watching Paul Newman and Tom Cruise break up
Is that what's happening right now in the near future
No I don't think so I think all is going
To become the new
This eccentric
Propaganda Outlet
Probably
I think he's going to say is out
Say what you want but
The Hardline right-wing lunatics that Alex
Quartz rose quartz
Steven Universe
Follow-up British pop
Is there's not going to
I don't think they will
I don't know this is going to be
So fast
A sorcerer
Who wouldn't
Still fuk around with
No course
In America is going to listen to
I really don't believe that
I know it is
I understand
His presentation
And exit weird
Frenetic
Constant Cuts in the
Yes
Music
Did eviction
Create something
Successful
I think is foolish
I just don't
See how this is the
I don't see how Alex doesn't turn this into a into a professional wrestling
I don't think
Can I think
He has created his own
Better
To some extent
This feels like the beginning of
The end
Like
Completely
Perspective
Losing Paul Joseph Watson
And this really to me
Sounds like someone
All the persecution
I get to know listeners
Can I get to know people like Tommy
Robinson
Turn off the best Father's the best activist
I need to know the people that don't back down to censorship
I get to know the
Troyer's and I get to know you
About
Some stupid Hollywood Manor
Brad Pitt set
Zumiez
Yeah
Hey look
Look everything is been really tough in
People are really mad at me but it's all been worth it because I've got to
Meet you
Alex doesn't think
He runs away from them that's crazy
I know the best journalist
Laura Loomer
Like that
It's old so insincere
What's behind it
The feeling of it
Is
I'm done
And maybe it's because
I think
Here if I had to guess
That's not even like I am going to fight for Jeopardy even through stage 4 pancreatic cancer
That setback
The ability to make that joke
Is so cool
Yeah
He came in like a
If you haven't seen the video go watch
But Alex Trebek
I don't want anybody else
I believe in
The connection that we
I don't want to hide
I am dealing
I'm going to fight
And then he makes the joke
I have to
Cuz I have three years left so good
Amazing so good
Yep
Everything you wanted Trebek to ever be like
You said you thought you knew I thought you knew him from the game show
But you know there's always that distance
This personal video you're like
You are you are what I've always believed you
Jesus
The humor of it is just
So
Yeah this is the
Cuz Alex isn't dealing with anything other than his own consequence
USA in America we don't deserve Trebek's
We deserve Alex Jones
Deserve
Fracture back
With life of qualm
Have an accent
Because
Outlets
Good for
The reality is like
Crucial mistake
I mean obviously
4 years ago talking to
Rodger Stone
There's a big mistake
I think every human being has ever talked to Rodger Stone later on found out it's just a mistake
Enabled
In ways that Alcon
Rodger way to
Control over
Editorial process
Operation
But I think Alex f*****-up
He included Paul
In the people I could lose
It was talking about like we're losing money
You guys to donate
I'm going to lay off Rodger and Paul
Like that sort of thing
Is the only excuse
Maldive
He's been waiting for free
Years
To be like I don't need
Your dumbass
To be attached to me
I'm not banned from
Twitter I'm not from social media
Ivan
Like I'm just wild you've given me an excuse to start my own operation
Right
And that
Paul Joseph Watson
Hertz Alex
In a way that
No-bake
No censorship
Africa
Because it takes away the only
Competent player in his Opera
There are other people who
Do like
I don't know
I don't know why he reporting
Do like two star match
Or whatever
You know whatever
Millie Weaver
Distract people
Paul Joseph Watson was the only guy who
Who's coming
It's like
I understand
Craft I understand
Buganda there I'm helping you you and I work in a symbiotic
F***
I think would you hear stuff like that would you talkin about like
It's so great I mean how much I love
Like that's what I hear when
Allah Allah
Worth it because
That one show was really great
Because I did this I got to be
I have to
Of course I'm not saying he's not it is
Successful
The festival circuit
Everyone has a story of meeting it
What's the story you get
Like
It's been years
But it was worth
Wire Z
I believe he wants to quit I agree
I agree with you on like 99% of what you're saying
All I'm saying is that there will be
Last Ride
And that is going to be the fight against his protege
This is f****** smarter than that
This is the whole situation he's going to get taken down
He is
G-Eazy
Craft
I also think that he is incapable of avoiding his
Bass
In which are too attached attacks
That is a
So even now while we're talking about him allowing
Go
In three months he doesn't
He doesn't have a f****** memory
He doesn't have the capability
He went from
Massacre
Talking to him
The difference is that Alex knows what's up
He knows what's up
Like in Inverness
Circumstance
It was Quicken
It moves faster
F***** up
Alex knows exactly what's going on
And it's something he's probably been trying to
Avert for a very long time
We just Paul wants to
He now can't
Troll that Paul
Kent
I understand where you're
Coming from opposition
Signed is the day's walk
Psychic
He's always
Preservation
MyON
Composition
But
If Paul
In his
Media operation
He starts
Still putting the same
Toxic s***
That Paul has been forever while he were
Is Moritz
Like
She probably will.
Of course
I think that Alex will
Recognize
Guys that is
That's an extension of
Isn't that awesome
That it's doing
Well
He gets mad
People like Joe
Because Jose just a friend of
The Joe Rogan Experience
Isn't offshoot of
Podcast
But whatever Paul does
Alex will be able to
Claim ownership of
If only in his own mind
So I don't think
He wants to fight that
As long as it's
Enough
And Alex
I think
I would do
But I think the hill
Be able to
Maybe settle
These lawsuits
And whatever it.
Efinancial
Still walking
A couple
Dozens a million
Liquidate whatever
Dumb s***
Live
Wife and Kids
Right
And then Paul Joseph
Safire
I agree with where you're coming from
I guess I just disagree in that I think Alex is a pathological lunatic
To the point where I think if
Rick
Started an Infowars
Dot-com more honor roll Alex would try and destroy him
Like there's a certain amount of that out of like
I want you to succeed but I don't want you to succeed as much as
Cuz I do
I mean there'll always probably be
Petty jealousy
There's no doubt about
We recognize
Is he's not good at
What he does
Also it's like he's not according to himself
She's dying
You know whatever is physical
Stop is
Like he's struggling
He's not as
Good at his job
And Paul Joseph Watson is a good
20 years
Like that guy carries a mantle of the
Call Joseph Watson is like 21
Paul Joseph Watson is like five years younger than
He's probably
How old is Alex Alex
One he's probably
30 ft
About 30
Paul Joseph Watson is younger than me
Yeah from hell no
No chance
Early 30s
S55
He has
Express
He is a spring chicken
Compared to Alec
And so
I just
If you are someone
One who works from
Even if you're a
Brazen propagate
There's two
1 is
How do I make
Maximize my profit
I think Alex Mack
Maximizes things by getting out
I'm still getting a
The cut in somewhat
Like trying to bully
Advertisers who make go to
Paul through
Getting a cut
Whatever
Forgot
Or even if Paul Joseph
Communication Network
And Alex will be
To get a finder's fee for that
Event if
Ideological
Then Alex
Give up
Let Paul take
You have already
Mentor
As best you can
He will fly with
Yeah
There is no downside to
To quitting
And letting Paul
Do it right
Ego
I agree with every reason that you have saved
I agree with everything that you have said
I would I would even
I would even say if we were to talk
To Alex
Victor's
Both of our advice to him
I don't think
He is
Capable of
Uptake
Makes me think
You think so
So anyway
Then we'll see what happens
I'm not sure
But we'll see
Until we fight
Do we have a redo
It's a place where you couldn't find Alex Jones like social media sites like Twitter
Facebook
What do we have a group
We got
We are on
I think that
Where we need to be at
Just say
Benicio del Toro also probably hasn't killed me by
We can't prove it but Alex
He probably has
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color