Holding
Alex
Is unavailable today
I felt
Emergency episode because
Super excited to have her on the show
From
I wasn't fast enough when you said I'm Dan I was going to I was going to shout in my best Jordan impression
But I can't do a very good Jordan depression
GoFundMe
Reporting
Yeah conflict reporting have worked in like a rack and in Ukraine and I'd like to have also covered a lot of protests
Including a lot of the street fighting between fascists Nanny fascism Portland so I'd like to do more of that and I'm putting together a
Audiobook
All of the intellectual origins of all the people who have like invented right-wing terrorist as it exists like
Coast Guard
Interesting
The things our listeners are into
Dimension that up top
Alex Jones one hell of a stochastic terrorist he's he's one of the best
Robert
We're going to be going over
And I understand that
I really like the food in Austin
With with his with his choices
What a badass
Restaurant
I just wasn't Austin to beginning of February I ain't nothing
Everywhere
Why would you eat anything good barbecue if you're in Austin Texas
Aldi's story boy restaurants in Austin
And I need to fill you in on this
Aware of it
He came to Austin
Was he's leaving in
Yeah
Alex's show on Wednesday
And he about to start his own operation
Very sad about that
I literally jumped impounded my desk with excitement when you said that
I'm not a fan of Paul Joseph Watson
And I am a fan of him having less money
Well I think I have a bunch of thoughts getting all of Alex's assertive support
Being able to run an operation at all
Play Frank
He doesn't write
Other people
Lutheran Paul
Just devastate
Alex
Started being the general consensus was
Caldo
Kind of shocking to me that that's happened
I might have to let Paul go
I can do my own
Brought it upon himself
I'm super curious to know who's
Call it was for Paul to leave
If it was Alex's that he wants to quit
Fan I'm not entirely sure if that is
Possibility
Yeah
Is him saying
And I want you to
Continue
Or something
How could you have Alex Jones say or intimated anything like that to you and not have your soldiers shrivel up inside
Being a being a real
Lifetime
Resistance
You in town on Tuesday and Wednesday
Alex
Complaining about Twitter a whole bunch
That they were going Beyond
With Owen Shroyer
Ama
Because Alex
Is so f***** up
He is
Profound lederach
At 4 in the
First. Just want to say
Super excited for this and I honored that you you brought me in to hear this
This beautiful things that we're about the experience together
Do it last night
And then as I was going over at cutting the clips
This morning I realized
Set a remor f***** up and I even remember it being last night and last night I was like
I'm so excited
I need to qualify and that is
That I'm Paul announcer
DePaul is leaving on Wednesday
But they know it
There's an awareness that this is sort of like
We can't publicly say drought you're leaving
But we all know it
So that is in the room at this unspoken
Probably was part of why Alex is drinking so hard
But there's another element
He was talking about
Look like
Just covering his bicep I don't know
Either way if you got surgery
He might be mixing booze with painkillers
First time that I'm on Alex's side because
Mix incredibly well together and there are no side effects
I'm no doctor
Alex's behavior on this episode
Here is an out-of-context drop from today's show
Liberal
I just want to say
I can smell
Bourbon
Watching
From days ago your phone across the sky but across the country to 2 mi
My my desk are whiskey
I'm not going to play you most
Beginning
Because there's a large portion of it before Alex
Paul
Probably spending
1520 minutes
Just complaining about Twitter
And talking about how it was awesome and
I'm broken and I'm not interested in that that's not a conversation
I'm not particularly Charmed by
So
Will jump in here
This is
Forever
This is where they go
This is Twitter
Description of
What he's doing
He will be bleeding out live
More or less
There's an irony
Marvelous
Alex
Is speaking a little bit too loosely
Auntie accidentally reveals
About
I'm not.
Sooners good Trump
This is the time
There's no better time than now cuz this is measurably
That is
If true
I want to know what they said as much as I never want to be in a room with Donald Trump jr.
Yeah yeah for sure if you could somehow bugs at lunch or whatever
Don Jr is Mike cernovich
The people involved in the
I give the most Credence to the idea
Yeah he let Alex
Usher
Unsettling
That there's nothing good they could be talking about
I wish I had a funny joke
As a as Jordan but I assure you I am I am shivering
And
Contacts
I think maybe they flew him in and they were talking about how Trump needs to
Make an executive order that'll Force
Or something like that
The Free Speech executive order or whatever
It's one of those like a mark of with how Wild Things have gotten that like if that's a thing that happens if this year
President of the United States
Which is an executive order forcing Alex Jones back onto Twitter
I wouldn't be
Real bad
Push
Reality
Is literally the opposite of free speech
Cuz he's had the freedom to decide who can use their
Nightclub
View of the
Specific
Complaints that he has bats at Twitter in Jack
Appearance that to Jack Dorsey had
And it seems to be that
Alex's mom
Rogan show
To be friends
With Jack
And that Jack
Is like
Being a dik
Even though
Well I mean who wouldn't want to be friends with Alex Jones a man who accused his good friend Joe Rogan of being
Part of
Horrible conspiracy and probably
Pedophile
Great friend Alex Jones
My friends call me Sneaky Snake
Promise to destroy me for my many crimes that that's the real Mark of a
Is promising to destroy you for your many crimes
Pick you up from the airport
My best friend's birthday just last year I hit a bag of heroin in his house and I called the police
You're a good friend
Alex discussing
Kind of rejection
Where is a weird head space
I see your eyes getting really why
Okay so
Damn you're the expert here
I've heard Alex Jones drunk a number of times
Not as many as you but a number
And that is the drunkest I've heard him sound
I'm curious as to where he lands on your scale
I'm glad you asked
Goat
Cocktail hour
This is like a happy hour getting off lunch truck
Relatively
They would go to commercials
Visibly more f***** up
He's just taking shots
You know he likes you like
Taste of liquor
I don't know much about Paul Joseph Watson personally but I've drunk with a number of British journalists and the drunk is nice
FR all I missed
Standing Rock because the British guy was working with an I got so drunk that we overslept their flight by five and a half hours
So I have to imagine that the presence of a British person here is exacerbating this in Norman
Well I mean
Be there
This episode
Miserable
But I do agree with you the presence of more drunk
But it specifically
To run his business
That's definitely a piece of it but
This is Joe
It's what I told you earlier it's a little bit sad
Egypt
Someone Shoulda stopped
Quite frankly
Anybody who cares
Would have stopped at yeah that's that's the Alex Jones
Tagline who cares should have stopped this
Disgraceful
These two dudes
20 minutes
Twitter all that stuff
Remembers that they're supposed to be doing
A business everyday
Phone call
This is real is not censored
Aw
Did remember that they're supposed to be
I mean I would I've never denied that about it
But Alex remembers their supposed to be
Promoted
Great
Paul Joseph Watson
And talk about how
You get to talk to Paul
Call
Emperor
You are questions okay
No dry political stuff
What Donald.
Level
All children
Fertilizing fields
Cricket
Pollinating spreading the seed
Call m.d.
In the throne
Coronavirus
God
Meet me Anderson Hall God
And it's all God
So he is the goblin Emperor but he sits on the throne of the Neanderthal God now I'm really curious like like
How does this
What's the separation of powers between whoever sits on the anitol throne and the Goblin Emperor whose scene
Is probably at campi constitutional
Textual analysis
It's implied that the throne
The occupier of that head
Far gone past
I don't know if that metaphor works
But
I took
He saying
Paul Joseph Watson
Has successfully carried out a genocide against the tall
Is that is it first of all
Complement
I think that's probably
I mean
I don't know how you guys do it in the big city. Chicago
Not a lot of goblins
I'm not I'm not inherently biased against Goblin
I put you down as a goblin
Gobble gobble intolerant I would say
Is the Alex
Is the
Throne
Bearer
Or or
And it
The goblin emperor
Part of what he's trying to express
Is it
Is it conceivable that
Alex Jones
Has honest
Sympathy and care for Paul Joseph Watson
And knows that his organization is going down in flames and 1/2 be okay in the
Concede
Okay
You know me I'm going to try to find the the best in somebody
That's a possibility that I
Imagine if
His primary care
I don't think
Somehow make Paul and charged when it does go down to get stuck holding the bag
I would be surprised
Yeah the thing that I've always
Hated about Paul is how
As may sound ridiculous but he's very smart
Is Eazy-E dead why he's the one f****** Twitter for one reason like he's
So much better at writing the line of
Doing a lot of dangerous propagandizing but not getting shitcan in
Yeah
Crafting intelligence whatever whatever it is
It goes back
Lucky
Model
Because Paul is grown up
Is younger man around a lot more
The technology
Yeah
Alex Jones was always really in is
Was that his best when he was just like
Ranting about kooky
Crazy stuff and Paul is an actual like
Fascist
Propagandist drumming up
Racial hatred
Trading underground VHS
Not a media organization 1:45 in the morning like
I just watched a documentary about the stretch and bobbito show
Underground hip-hop College radio show
From the 80s early 90s
Like freestyling on their show
Fix truck
A bunch of Hot 97
Instead of
Be at the college
Hey sort of didn't have the same
Ability
Next
With folks
Yeah you should be a crazy person that we run into when we're exhausted and
Driving long distances or just got home from a graveyard shift
That's
Android UHF or whatever it was when he was on Austin Public Broadcasting whatever that way
Would like back in the late 90s
Comforting almost
If you don't
The feeling that I get it
When I'm watching
Drunk baby
Where is he
It's that when I listen to him
You have this is a guy who is
Nuts but okay
What's do for a living
Yeah
And now it's the guy who
Should never have stopped ranting about the aliens
Promising Lake
I want to get the stuff when I was fun
Yeah
Saleem's make a little cameo
Alex
Operate mostly do that because
Next Club
History of calling himself Neanderthal so here is that
Let's talk about neanderthal
Fishing right now
Tell me about the Galaxy
You tell me about it
You completely forget to put this is the other conversations are having a completely moves
There is so much condescension and Paul Joseph Watson voice
It's weird to feel angry on behalf of Alex Jones but how dare you
Call
He made you
I feel I feel exactly the same
Mugli dismissive like this
Yep
It's really shady Behavior
For people who
Leaving coworkers
Ofrenda coworker
Anybody
It's one of those things like
You can tell there's no one who truly cares about him as a person like
Took him into
His friends and family got him help
Like he was
Institution because even as like you know
Famous and whatnot as he is he's got people who honestly care about his health and well-being
There's no one like that for Alex Jones
I think I think he probably that boat is sales
In many ways
Best Prosecco
Probably
Oh boy I'm worried about those kids
They'll be all right I mean is alright
If your potato salad
Tons of money
Good education
And stuff like that
I don't know I do feel bad for them
Alex realizes once I realized
Here's the problem
We did the show
WeChat
Talk to people that have been censured
Here tonight
Say what
They achieve these goals
Bwg really see that like
Everyone has this when you're drunk and you get that you have that point where you get more ambitious
Run tomorrow in the woods
Exercise
Already in the middle of
Yeah
That's rough
They get back
Yeah I guess to get right to it and it's productive
You are incorrect Alex complaints about leprechaun
Easter bunnies are walrus
We talked about
Leprechaun
Did you see some leprechaun
The point is that those of us
Personification
I love that Drogba
Desperately wish
There's an alternate universe somewhere where Alex Jones has never talked to a president
And spend everyday detailing the leprechaun conspiracy I wish we lived in that
It is what it is a better present a better hypothetical present
Think about this
Alex's talked to multiple president
If you
Cuz I know that he got arrested or at least escorted out
Add a route
Yeah
Back when he was governor
So
He had some sort of a K'nex
Should with him
Lobster bush
Trump
Sure he's never talked to Obama
No
I bet
Yeah yelling though
I mean I wiretapped the first or the second President Bush but I didn't talk to him
Yeah I could especially back in the text
Different
Pretty out there in
Not
Because he talks about leprechauns also I don't know if leprechauns
Additional
Not what I would have gone through
Number one
Pot of gold
Lucky charm
Alex again realizes they are not doing it
You're going to
Cuz that we're late
These people be mine
Hellboy
What you want to do
Amanda
Spectacles
There's so much behind that you're in command
Patrick bet-david interview them and toxic
He lost his voice and Alex
That's horrible
Like if that same like
There's some real Emotion by that
That was a real thing
Wow
Jerks if we don't promise
Are good people
Therefore
You're in command now
You are the goblin Emperor you are in
In charge
Petsense
Question
Where is made very strong indications that he is not as interested in Trump as he used to be
Literally saying
Trump
Having a good time
Charleston
AJ's establishment type person
What's Alicia be abandoned
I'm happy about that seven persecuted for supporting Trump
I got
Cr1 updated properties of them
They just run me off Trump.
Trump
Maybe trying a shrub
And so it doesn't matter
Instead
Particular phone call
Wow no one even liked did they not at all address that
What did Paul Powell said something that like
Not happy with that
So the idea that
As he's walking out the door
He cares at all
He knows that Alex is f***** up this whole time
He's either laughing condescending
Or just like
Checked out
You are.
You take over
That sort of vibe
But
That is
Interesting
Turn on Trump
It specifically what is the idea that he's not been able to get back on Twitter
Like he's mad that Trump isn't putting that executive order out
That will allow him to have a social media presence
So that is what
So you sure it's that I mean you heard that you sure that and not him talking more about likes
Is it is it really just Twitter and not
I'm pissed the truck didn't
Jail the globalist mad about that for two years
Trump's actions are also like
Example
Because if
Trump a patriot leader
Describing him
All of the issues that Alex has
Globalist
The need to get me back on Twitter
It's none of that stuff
Invalidation of crazy president
Thinking that these are real problem
I mean it's a nice to hear him say that cuz I feel like maybe he's I hope he's speaking for
Other people that 2020
Is it a f****** disaster
I do like hearing Trump made me turn on Trump like that
Give me a little bit of Happy
Something you never expect to hear
You kind of expect that people are on the path that's are on
The possibility of sincerely like I'm done with it
I think he'll jump to it something worse
Then Trump
Yeah but
New Jersey with one f****** thing at a time right
So you heard at the end of that last clip
That's a call
Getting down to it
Make a call
Here is the first Quest
Buckaroo Banzai
F***** in hillbilly stuff that I don't know about
Facebook
Hi state
Question
Were you in a bonsai
MD angriest I have ever been
Buckaroo Banzai is a cultural treasure
It's
Have you ever wanted to see Jeff Goldblum
Dressed as a cowboy
Fighting evil alongside
Rock musician / neurosurgeon slab rocket engineer /
Race car driver
You had me
I was already sold
Grateful
Call Joseph Watson
I can't think of a West hillbilly movie
Conspiracy stuff in there if you ever read like the illuminatus trilogy or any Robert Anton Wilson fiction
It's like a movie that's very much in that sort of vein
Yeah yes
I really like honestly think Alex would have enjoyed it
So you get another question
The goblin emperor
And he has Paul Joseph Watson
Question
Megan
Wow that was honest
Okay then
Pull out
And that is the issue of address of Chrome
Drinking children blood
Which of course is somatic
Rich people
He thinks Elites are really doing
Presses that in
What you think about
Mainlining adrenochrome
Alessi establishments obsessed with the children's
I don't know what to say what time
Ordered
He's a good guy really come on
Bill Gates
Jason windows
How you penetrate
Should I question
Good good instant analysis Portland
How many
How many breaks
Has he taken at this point yeah
Earlier where we are on the drunk tail
This is the kind of this is the level
Leaping into this
Like so f***** up
Yeah
Heartbreakingly drug
Yeah if I saw my friend like this at a bar
Cab
It's absurd
Oh I wouldn't leave anyone alone who sounded like that cuz they just think that he doesn't sound like
Wasted a hat like he sounds wasted in broken
Yep
That is
Heartbreaker
If you cared about someone you would worry about self-harm
Famous Tate videos
It's it's pretty bad
Where Alex tries to get some
He tries to
Exploring
I haven't long gaps in his sentences
But he tries to
And just talk about like ancient esoteric ideas
And I will tell you
It does not work
It was a lot of Lifetime show
That I made that decision
Alcohol teacher
And now there we are
God is on our side
And all these enemies are attacking us
Already sold out
I'm glad you're here in Texas
I'm glad that I was chared
Weather radar
My rollover dad
Make sure whenever they see my big big Valley
You know that was somebody
Jennifer Justice
That's where we stand right now
A lot of people that lot of stuff before us
Sure we got this far
The people don't appreciate
Wow
Ship
But
Long positive
But no
That's deeply
Upcider
Yeah sorry recognize how much
Yeah
A little Philly
I mean I get pissed at the Ancient Aliens guys to when he
Takes credit for the pyramids away from the Egyptians but that's not the way to express that
Muscle memory
Like yeah
Used to talk about these things about the many lifetimes and stuff like that
Giselle
Stumbling into traffic
And he got hit by a boost truck
Yeah I think he hit the booze truck
So what are the pieces of Alex's
Mythology is that
The globalist
He's on buyout of
Xpressbet
Think they offered me everything
The entire world
Anthony gets asked about this
What do you expect
To be quite frankly
When the little green leprechaun
Showed up with a pot of gold
Instead Alex just come over to the dark side
How did you resist
Wow
Intoxication or if he's like feeling really f***** up about the idea that like
He's decades-long fraud
That the Elites in the global
Adidas
Wow
Except
Is
Taking literally
The question that I asked
Leprechaun
Right right you might be so drunk
Abstractly
That is
So you're either too drunk to think abstractly or too drunk to lie
One of the two
The idea of him being offered a ton of money comes up
Is a couple minutes later
And Alex
Answer
How much was it
How many steps in a mile
Stepan Rangers
Harborview
Volcanion
Play Z-Ro
Hours of dinosaurs
Okay chicslook Freedom do you guys have to send
Hard-hitting question
Do they have to turn down baby constantly
No problem
Facebook
Christian conservative girlfriend
How do I suppress
So I guess
Millions of dollars
Differences
There are there are large didn't they have been three different offers
So some sort
He's so consistent
Is Owen
They're both being pretty mean to Alex I think he knows
Alex isn't going to remember this
I think that's part of it
And Alex never watches the content
To do that with all the
Turn on air
Roger's going to prison
Jeroan
It's never going to happen
Owen Shroyer
Choice between my cat
And I was bleeding out and needed a tourniquet applied
I think I'd try for the cat first you know it's not likely that they'll be able to pull it off
The cat put its possible
If possible
You don't have a fever
No no
No
Nor do I trust him to apply tourniquets
I thought this was no longer responsible
Play stupid s***
Owen Shroyer
Paul Joseph Watson
And everyone at Infowars
I take child endangerment it kind of sounds like that right now
Might be a crime
And this next quick was just like
You are so f****** awful
I'll buy you beer
Divides when you say something
Put it out in the universe
You know
All I know is
Associate
Really
Yeah in response to a question
And be like we have to take care of you
Like you are in right now
Insane
It's a profound abuse
She loses the ability to speak in complete sentences and
The course of that like 20 seconds
Do I go to bed
I don't know why on air
It's heartbreaking that the man who is
So drunk I doubt he can stand
Hits
That point of realization before either of his Sober Sober colleagues do
Really
Embarrassment for everybody like
Stop with embarrassing
Oxycotton stupid
This is next level
But
He also picks up the self-awareness
The people are laughing
And the Paul Joseph
Owen Shroyer are laughing at him
And he tries to express it in this next clip
Yeah that's days like I
SharePoint
Right now
Horseradish
That's
That's very that's very sad
Yeah most of those weren't even words
Nope
Starts with bomber Pilots
Everyone's laughing
Everyone is lying
I didn't even really here like up until everyone's laughing none of that wasn't eligible to me
I mean bomber Pilots are important
I got that
I appreciate you
Computing the ennobled bomber pilot
Oh man a good bomber pilot
Things to do
Vomit people
Is one of them
I think Alex is trying to use it as a metaphor but being really unsuccessful
Over over global of territory
Let's just
I would
Windy windy
In a year or two
I would love to
To see someone just completely re-edit Top Gun
Replace Tom Cruise with current-day Alex Jones
That would be be able to capture intoxication
Then leave
3 years yeah
Okay alright
It's going to destroy democracy will get to see Alex Jones and Top Gun and
Gone with the Wind
The Democrat
Small price to pay
Paul Joseph Watson
Alex getting into the emotional part
I'm a beast
A lot of the time I know he's fake crying when he talks about like loving this country and stuff like that
Sure I think that this is real crying
I want to see
It's about is even more f***** up
By Twitter's lawyer
Congratulate your children away
Procedure wig
I didn't do anything
Rich woman
Vagina whatever
Is Alex
Vagina
So
Insulting her like that
The kids away
Which is really f***** up
That was just
Really sad
That was just a man who's lost or is in the process of losing everything and realizes it breaking down
Down in front of his friends and then realizing he does not have friends
Poking at my
If you know Alex at all you know what state
That's not going down
Crying about it
Bucked up these people
Awful people
I feel bad for Alex Jones
Yeah I know it's one of those really weird feelings
I hate
I hate him so much in this tiny snapshot at 8
Because for all of the many things that he is Alex is clearly not
And
Narcissist
He's definitely a narcissist we know that and he might have borderline personality disorder but like
I don't think
A real
Psychopath
Cry about his kids like that
That's a person who
Really cares about something
Alternative explanation
He's a sociopath who's really drunk
In that circumstance
I don't know
That seems like real crying to me but he does like Alex Jones has been doing this for 27 years
A thousand times
Which makes it harder to look at
People think exactly
Said they're like I hate that I feel sorry for how I
It's the reality of this
How many sets important especially for like
Your show is essentially
Analyzing this guy and what he's doing and trying to explain it because he has he's not unimportant he has a real
Impact on the world and it had one but he
Like his whole brand of what he does is so completely devoid of empathy which is why he's able to do such terrible
S*** like you did to the Sandy Hook families because
Like
Cut that out of his work almost entirely you get these little Snippets of it feel like when he's crying out but also like
During that
We first heard about Sandy Hook
Like
There were those little moments for you can tell like oh he might feel terrible about what he's about to do or at least
He's conflicted
He does it
Like
F****** for that but like
They're like those moments where you can like see him cross a Rubicon in his own head
Damn there's a choice involved with
Depressing whatever feeling you have
Whatever like
You have empathy
But you ignore it in order to do the job
Or whatever the mission
And if you do don't look at him that way
Missing context
I guess there is a point
Feeling bad for him every now and again
Yeah you got it
He doesn't cry for long if I were them I would say over
This is it we are done
My boss is
Having a meltdown
I pissed at the cameraman
Pornography like no no no no
No
Whoever's the producer like where
Where is Alex's dad
His award
Where are these
About it
Yeah
Scrying
Question
I guess in his
Why do they hate you so much though Alice what is it about you that they date
Music
Did he say I've got music or I like that music
Reflective
Bumper Music
Like that
With that
Yeah yeah
Yeah because even resist the a softball underhand pitch
People hate you
That question a thousand times
Pretty sweet
Earlier Owens
Alex
They're still on the air
They're on the radio
And so he knows that these stations
Playing the show
The country
Do not allow
Because towards the end of this house is so drunk
He just can't stop swearing
Alright
He lost control of his own abilities
Probably earlier
A little bit earlier the show
Complaining
Is a dick
Alex is bad that Jon Ronson a couple weeks ago Alex
Snake and it's trying to set him up for something like that
I'm not sure
Talking about
But
Towards the end of this
Jon Ronson
And I will let you decide whether or not this is a real Jon Ronson call
And we're talk about John earlier and Alex
I don't know what the screeners
Are fighting about now
Hello Alice
How are you friend
I'm judge
My friend a little busy man
So lonely
Are you lonely
Sounds effect Jon Ronson
Yeah who goes through like three accidents in three sentences
Is that a good point to bring up the idea to Boston
6 conservatives are getting better at comedy
Scaring scaring
Getting so funny
Conservatives are stained
Here
What the joke is
I take it to the Jon Ronson have an effeminate voice
Yeah he's he sounds a little like a lady
That's
Solid
Solid setup complete jokes
They didn't develop the theme at all either like
I know you can't rely on Alex to do set up work here
The two of them should have been able to ask a question to the comedy from the collar
He's there he's playing a character
Or anything like that
The elephant in the room is that you're not you're not really
Or something
Nothing
Emmett's next clip
We get to see the psychodrama that's been building of there we can't talk about
How Paul is leaving
Kind of comes to a head
Where Alex
This
Paul needs to
Specific
Better addictive of like taking over
He's operation
It-it's
It's almost like he's trying tonight him
Or something like that
It's bizarre
We don't want the leadership Paul
Zyrtec-D leadership
Radical Muslims
Perverts
Penniman
Leadership
Flareon
You have to take me to ship
Or someone else will say I
Italian
Take it
You don't know what else.
That's so important
For Alex
Wow
He really seems to care about this
Yeah
Performing
Yet about having someone to carry on his legacy I think I think there's a part of it is that
Work for will go to Dust in the Wind
If someone else does
Keep the fire
Probably
Is Paul Joseph Watson is the person who takes
I might be able to still make some money off that
Being in between responses
Something
He would have influence over Paul like he be able to appear on Paul's show
And stuff like that
His personal
Even if
410A
There's some of that in
This makes me wonder
What we don't know about Infowars as Financial or legal situation cuz I
It seems like something
Calamitous is imminent
Or even could be Alex's help
Disclose for radios
John being an elder
Yeah but like 65 when you considered all the drinking
From
Childhood fights
Stuff like that
If you stop working with something I certainly would want
Continue doing this
But
Suspicion
Part of it
And it's not necessarily the lawsuits.
Because I'm not sure if
But the stuff allowed
Discovery
Is Suffolk his financial records advertising
I think like that
Probably
Concerned about that
Information becoming public
Oh yeah
Destroy his entire thing
Connection process
It invalidates the entirety of his career
Like he's been someone who is paid by
A special interest or something like that
He's not the man in the woods
Screaming
Stop profit
He is just another shell
I wonder if he's got money from the NRA
I don't think back in the day
Maybe
More recent
Yeah yeah cuz he used to be Auntie NRA controlled opposition and stuff but
Gun owners for America or preservation of firearm
Really big into as Gunn
Groups back in the day if possible I don't know
Specific Siri we have is like
I don't like not from Minecraft's been funding his operation for the Last 5 Years
Episode
He has a break and he's a
And
Before him on the show of being like
Volume over you must be the leader
The Muslims are perverts takeover
The show
This war
March 5th 2019
And
From today's broadcast
Not for a long time
Wow
It's almost
I don't even know people to understand them
I think we can
He's right
Jokes about fruit
I feel
Too gross to make fun of him for most of this funny to make fun of but
Phoenix
Difference of these people that he's worked with for
Cancel lifetime
That's
At least Owen just came into the fold like a couple years ago
Alex's known Paul Joseph Watson since he was like that like covid-19 or something like that together
Early Infowars days
Family
Brother Houston
There was a real connection there that should exist that appears not to
The bomber
Yeah it's hard for me
Contacts drop
Thumbs up
Call Michelle
There
This will be talked about for a long time
Is it car crash
Except
Anything you're walking away from this with
I mean did he do we see him
Walk away from the table
No I don't believe so go to break and then
Capable of walking
Five pm
It's not like a late night episode
I don't know cuz I listen to the episode
For now reasonably normal
I think it's got going
The fourth our host took over on his show
Start slamming until start
Hour and a half two hours
That's plenty of time
Is inspiration for this amount of drinking was because
What did really come from a place of where he emotionally wasn't sure how to handle
Paul's departure and so he was like
Just started drinking like is that
Does the timing of MS
That sort of stuff
Pasta
It it seems important
Timer
Either that or some other bad news
Definitely emotion
Out of him than I'm used to thing that's like not just Alex Jones Telegraph rage but is like
Human
We'll meet at matters came out with a story about the vet
Story about that the Sandy Hook victims families
Recently to this
And realize that information
2 tons
I don't know I think
Alex is aware that you
Piss without Paul
When he knows he has to announce the next day that Paul is starting his own operation
Hey Paul says it's within a couple weeks like it's a media
He's going to start his own thing immediately
I think Alex the part of the awareness that he hasn't I'm announcing
The effective end of me being able to do what I do
He overcame
It made him so essential as an employee
You need to hire
He put all his eggs in one small racist British man
Classic
And that tiny and Englishmen
Certainly.
I think they're strong indications that Alex
At least emotionally on his way out of
How much of that is
I'm excited to see
Robert
It's on iTunes Spotify where you were blue pods are casted you can find behind the bastards
Me at I write okay on Twitter and War on a
Everyone go fund me and you can podcast
Superman
Highlight
I am grateful for that and for bringing me on I'm not
Comedy stuff as usual man Jordan
I was listening to you guys in the car on my way to drive to The Hollywood Reporter podcast today and when I
I love your show and then and then happy to
To be your your Owen Shroyer today
I think you treated me much better than 0 and 3
Guyger support
Complement
Owen Shroyer probably hasn't killed anybody
Yeah I'm sure you're probably hasn't and I I don't say Paul never leaves his house so I don't
Pause kill anybody
Leaving now it's down the path that might lead to his own destruction
You could say their accomplices to an eventual murder
Pet spot
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color