Alexandra Thurston color
Two years ago I moved into this apartment actually we've done this entire podcast in this
Interesting
As of like just a short while before
Like a couple of months
We started this podcast
We've not Rick we've not done this show outside
That's fair to live
Is it not always been
Call me up at six months
The new knowledge site
Headquarters
Is
Chicago real estate is
Pain in the ass
It sucks
Anywhere suck
You have Apartments
They all know
Did they hold all the cards
They are in in
Tire control
And
They do not
Like I remember moving into my old place
I like
Maybe six years ago
And I got a super great deal
Like they were going out of their way
And then over that time span
Raising the rent and raising the rent
Cost of living
Whatever
Did you know that you can
Say no to that
I didn't know that Joel just the other day
I was complaining about how
Is there a Zurich
You know he could just say like
I'm not going to pay that much how about we say twenty bucks
Extra
It's perfect
Crazy
Keep you in
Look what the f***
Right I was never do that to eventually it got kind of silly
But I see there for another year because I was like
I just don't want to have to
Fight series of fights a Non-Stop
Pretty rocks
I couldn't
I lost my job
And I had no income
And I couldn't break my lease
So I just started finding people on Craigslist
And there were a bunch of weirdos
Weird but there was this one dude
He was super cool
This is important to the
The story
He was black.
Okay
And I was like f*** yeah you're the guy to Subway
And he's sending his
Requesting all that stuff
And they were like
Your credit
Which in Chicago real estate is code for
Your bike
Significantly
So what I did
Gave me his pay stub
Edit was
Who's all right okay
And so I was just
You pay me right now
Which is against the law
Dangerous
Somebody came around to my apartment from the real estate
Company and they
And he was like
A while now
They were like that's not okay
Email the guys like no you could have supplied I'm just I just stay in here
Mirror
I'm watching the
Anything
There's a thousand possibilities
He got a cosigner and they're like whatever
I guess at that point what are you going to do
You know you already got someone
Squatter's rights
Level of conversation right
Fruition
So
Take a moment
And are making this all possible
I'm a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk Europe next
Ankh
Is there a
Sara Smile
Mike
Possibly
MB
I'm finally doing it on a little bit of an elevated
Do Kevin from
You're now a globalist
A mom and tell her your brother
Someone someone sodomites
Thank you so much from Poughkeepsie
Gypsy Kevin if you're up
Kevin of Poughkeepsie
Preferred I
I waited
Honorific title
If you decide
Refrigerator it would be delightful and extremely helpful
Frustrating
You just go you see apartments that look like
I've been out of the loop it's been a long time since I've been a part
Hunting
Yeah
I'm really starting to gain a day
Appreciation
The people who take pic
Pictures of apartments
Because they make them look amazing
Cuz you just do CDs
Apartments they look amazing
Pictures and other profiles online
Stuff like that
Call you go down and check it out
Is dogshit
It's crazy yeah
I've just I've had so many
Dead ends of run
I have I have some
And I think things
Going to workout with
Back to normal pretty
Yeah but for now
We missed Monday and this is going to be a little bit of a weird episode also in addition
That some of that I got to talk about this
Life as we know it is only compounded by what's going on
Speak with
An episode we talked about Paul Joseph Watson leaving
Merry Christ Robert Evans
Came in and did that bonus episode of Me about
Fantastic
But he tried to do Oreos have
Breakdown
Because he knew that the neck
De Paul was announcing that
He was leaving
He was in a
My working
In theory is that
Wheatley emotional state having a breakdown
He was also drunk
Motivated by
Reality
DePaul
That's a high-stress situation
The only thing that could have made that better is if
When was like
Great job they do that Alex knows that he has to be in studio on Wednesday
Because balls make that announcement
And then Alex is gone
David Knight hosted on Thursday
I hosted on Friday
Hosted on Sunday Monday
I really wanted to
Continue the story
Because the pieces
That we saw there at the end
End of last week
Right
This is big
For sure am I I was getting very self-conscious
Maybe I misinterpreted
Pieces
Right
And then when I
Look in the night
Try and find new stuff
The cover from the present
I see apps
Alex Alex is gone
He's missing in action on his own show
Scheduled vacation
Immediately after he has a freak out during an SB anything session and Paul announces he's sleeping
He's on a galleon doing it
Ethan saying I don't I don't accept the explanation
But he's on a vacation
And honestly I was starting to take the
But he might be dead
I don't like
Like I started
Tuesday I started watching Owen
Cover
He look like he was going to cry
Ocean
Severely looking like you
But his eyes were red
There was a reddish yeah
He was distracted looking all over the studio as if
Something was going to break in at anytime
We saw that Alex was a broken was a shell of a man
After all that
He had a
Interview with Steven Crowder
Run louder with Crowder
That came out I really can't believe that
It was prior to the AMA
He was not nearly as f***** up
There's no
Rio Linda
No signs of
I didn't know how any of that was possible I didn't
The real
Deeply
Goodbye
But Alex called in his own show
Start a website
Still alive
I don't know if we would ever know if he wasn't
But if it's really
Confusing and
And heavy
Trying to wrestle with
The present day
And I've been trying to
Reconsidering
Looking at
From different angles practice
Figure out like
Alex isn't.
Vacation what is he
You doing right
Like could he have gone to rehab
Probably not
I see that is working against his recovery make you like
Not have any contact with the outside world rightly 7-Day especially your own propaganda radio show.
The part of your addiction
I think that's unlikely in my mind I thought that was a possibility
I also thought it was a possibility that
You finally getting
Surgery for his big stick
Mac
That's probably unlikely
Cuz he just got surgery
And I don't know how okay
Two surgeries in
Surgery
Essentially put
I probably wouldn't be able to record or or even really
Get left for
What three months
Maybe also I think is that were the case then they would be upfront and say that that's
That's what happened
Announcement
Surgery
Saving surgery
No
I don't know what's going on
Very well possibly could
Just be legal s***
He's been so preoccupied with all the
These lawsuits
Possible
Maybe it's gotten to a point where the lawsuit
That is lawyers
I'm not to host
If you saw him on that you would absolutely advise him
Right
Mira hot mic
You can call into your show for like 2 minutes
Extreme about the globalist
But that's it any price to liability
I don't know I ate a weird situation for me to be in that I
But none of the possibilities look good
The only
Pictures of
Because
The only person who
Could have filled in
Should take a long leave
Absent
Is the same person who just left
Strongly
Paul is not good without at
His is his bench players are are not court-ordered gone
Rodger
They're not Clippers
Heart attack
Supposed to
Music
Is playing right now
Hear it
The man who can
Oh
Save the music I thought you were going to go Lionel
Lionel stew into qanon I don't think Alex and I had arrived super tight at this point
You know the present day I spent a lot of time that I have had available
Trying to
Trying to put together a present-day episode
Do you want to talk about how
The truth wins in the end
I don't want to do that
Still not worth it
You want to hear that I don't have to listen to a lot of it already
The great beer though
Mispronounced at
The one who is Super Bowl
I know I know
Who is boring
I just don't know what
He does have a beard
Okay
In addition to that
It's almost like
Everything
Coming up
With no Rosa
No trying to find a new apartment
Right I keep going to these goddamn places look what the places that I went to
I swear to God the landlord was taking me up to see the apartment I walked he's like it's not great is it
What he said was a great sales
I think there's a big story in here but it's really inaccessible.
There's debt that's
Re-up
To the Past
Tried to find
Extend
We can always do that
Alex
Is in a
F****** awful holding pattern
The end
Guns guns guns we get to
We're going to go a little bit over the
From December 23rd to
December
31st
Today okay
Morgan Spanish the year 12
Pretty quick fashion
Because there's not a lot
December 21st
Huron Allison programming absolutely
Desert
Ideas of the desert of interesting things
It's all gunship
It's all
They're coming to take
You're gone
So get ready to have a civil war
Cuz they're going to start
Underlying message
Well it's like
You're gone
And a certain number of you are going to kill them
Lisa come to take your gun
So that's why they're doing the gun grab to begin with two
It take to shooting cops which will start a civil war
It's almost all he talks about
Repeatedly
Over and over and over and over again
Dave's hours
There's nothing
The drives own
Sorry
I'm just saying that that man that's the first plane by the globalist
That makes
It's a it's a
Multi-stage lamp
Has a lot of bullet points let's put it that way
Relies on
An accurate assessment
Of what the other side will do if we
We do this
Because it's a boy
It's a globalist plan written by Alex
More accurate than the one he just tries to write
You know it's like a male screenwriter writing bad female character
For the global of course terrible job
Thinking of what the cabal would do but agree weirdos with guns
Really tied up tight
Start on the 23rd
And this is another
Piece of
What Alex
Spend
Much of his time
For the next week
Of the show on
Topix
White House petition
Several thousand
So Alex Piers Morgan
Sonofabitch
You have no teeth
I'm going to sit this one out however the chips
Fault let them as they may I don't care about this at all it's always interesting because Alex's
Obsessed
Evicted
Newspapers
And then
You spend so much time on this because drudge reposted
Alex's
Piers Morgan
Everyone else starts picking it up because it's on Drudge
But Alex about how no one credits
Infowars
And
Call the messages
Yeah how many which country would you most like a morgue
I don't know man in America
You got to deport him from a better country
To get deported from
Right
He's got dual citizenship in order to answer your question you requiring me to
To choose a new home for Piers Morgan alright
Tanzania
I don't know
From there they have marsupials
Snap
Absolutely
A couple days after this Alex
Realizes how much press and how much Buzz Marketing
You've gotten out of starting a
Dot-org
Morgan
Charges filed against
Feinstein
Yeah
I don't have a backer on this one I think I'm good I think I'm going to let this it's really fascinating
He's
He's trying to get these three
Treason charges
Feinstein
Whatever you right now I'm not a fan
Alex keeps insisting
He's going to do like
A big expose on her
Does
Murdered her ex-husband
Is all right. That's not number one in what I would go with could be worse
Right right
I feel like
If you murdered her ex
It's a sad display of like
She does insider-trading but then doesn't really go
Get specific
Insinuating that she helped
There's another serial killer in that help serial killer
I don't know
Fun
I think that he's just
ReDiscover change.org
And their potential to be
Used as
Like the end of 2012
Chock-a-block
With him doing that
Just a bunch of change
Change.org possession
Frazee
23rd
The Feinstein one is
Talk about it cuz
The same thing.
It would be ironic
Barack Obama's
Change.org
Idea of
If you get 100,000 people
I will respond to
Regardless
If one of those was
Alex Jones would like to
To kick out.
That would be
Yeah
Respond to it I don't know I don't know we're going to see how this plays out
Obama saying
Alex doesn't talk about that for a
Okay that's right
To dress it there's no way out
So we'll know
Shortly what ends up happening
I'm put seven the 23rd
24th 25th
I am so when he comes back
It's just all guns all the time
Just sucking
Gun gun gun gun gun to come take the gun
Be very afraid
Normal Alex Jones Show
It is 18
Business as usual
Yeah you could be 2012 could
P2009 it really doesn't matter
Surrounded
Other than
He's really afraid
About them taking the gun
There's an intensity to it
Yeah
Really
So if you played a context for me I wouldn't be able to guess
It'll be like
This could be Mal this could be 10 years
Probably not
Yeah but yeah you could be almost it could be many many different times
Career
Adolescent
Cuz it's like
Directions to world is having a conversation about
Like how important
That
Was
Not like there's very little about that
Which is
Again why were
Looking back at this time
Just need his coverage of it
It's all just
Like if Sandy Hook is a
He's talking about CMD
Which is the
Perceived gun grab
And then the Civil War that would be triggered because of the potential gun threat
Global is not talkin about the actual event
And I think some of it is because it is
Incredibly
Painful
To be honest
There's a certain part of me that
That is
Relieved by that
Because while doing the show like
When he did talk about it
So f***
Harmful
Yeah it's a bummer
FedEx
Like even now while you're playing those clips
And we deal with the date
We know how close this is
And you can you can listen
To this end forget
You can forget that happened
While ago
Because we don't live in that we know exactly
Right
Right I'm having to go into a holiday season with that
Weighing over their hearts to lose it
Holiday after the worst
Sting
Yeah so like
Is it real
Cultural moment
It's happening
And it's barely not at all
Somewhat comforting because it would
It would be awful Sandy Hook investigation
Where every show was just the worst
S*** that he's ever
Like a greatest hits
Sandy Hook
It would be
Devastate
I think we are
But it's also kind of Interest
Because Alex
Black guy in present day
I talked about it and then I moved on to other stuff yeah
Kind of accurate no he's not terribly wrong there
On the 19th
Suggest that the father was an actor
He's already
Suggestive very heavily
That he believes that the government did this
Killed all the kids
Use data plan
December 27th episode
We get the first time that Alex makes a really full throated declaration
About what
About Sandy Hook
Most
Coverage of
In the episode
What are the rare moment
City comes up
Bushmaster
That's a bet
Harshest or at least the most concrete statement that this is a false flag
Right you still not committing and anyway to the actors idea
Student brought up
He's not getting
Crazy with
Course of these days
His collars don't seem to
Super interested
Becoming Civil War the globalist
The kickoff
Good job
Corral in Conroe
Versation in that direction
Is really interesting
I think the worst
Thing about America
In that case
Is when he says
Do you really think somebody would just steal grab a Bushmaster and start killing firefighters
Someone who tried to kill his mom with a hammer where Maybe
Yes
Unequivocally yes
I do think
That could be a headline
Tomorrow
I'm surprised you right.
I don't know if it would have surprised you
Too much you
I mean you would believe that it happened
Yeah for sure
Perhaps
We've already had enough mass shootings in 2012
Respond
Fish
Dumb dumb
In all of the time
The day of
All of Alex's
Have been
Gun propaganda
They have all the people who have either Financial
People who
Work for gun
Manufacturers people like Larry Pratt has been on
Twice from gunownersofamerica
The group that the more extreme NRA
Stewart Roads from The Oath Keepers has been on twice
Like all of these people who are just
Gun people
Heptagon
But none of them have had weird ideas about that
Right
People who have either Express
Condolences
This is really sad or try to deflect
Into guntalk really is true
Yep isn't
Little bit like
Every single person agrees
The worst thing that we could
Could do is
Dress this
Correct
Because that breaks
The part so many of our narrative
Still info
So they they still have that
To protect
Is that Alex likes
Bring these ideas
Yeah you know and so far we've seen no evidence
Racine only
Alex letting his own mind
And responding to maybe a bloggy Sawyer's
Something like that
To get him to the visit
That's not
Caruncle
Research right that leads them to that so his attempts to
Dependent on other people
All these other people Poison by mind
Falls on Deck
Not just that
He's other
Instigators are is
Truecaller
So there
Re-enforcing they're creating that
Calera
He says something crazy
Is he in there like
Yeah I know I heard it was this
With no
You didn't hear anything
People running away from the callers are going to call in and
Repeat that back to Alex at reinforced
The talking point when they
Absolute
So we finally on this 27
27th 2012 episode
We finally get a guest is bringing Alex
Doug Hagmann
Aussie Northeast intelligence
Right
He sucks
I told you this before
And I'll say it again
All you need to know
About Doug Hagmann
Is that
Currently
In 2019
One of the regular guest on his broadcast
His coach Dave dobbyn
All you need to know about him
Rug Manhattan
From now on I have
More to say about him
Another day
Do I do a deep dive on
Oh that's
It does with these guys a lot of
I'm looking at you Alan Walker
The plural
So Doug heckmann comes on and he pretends
Department of Homeland Security Source
Sure who's telling
And
By the way Alex
At least 14
It's a really
Solidify
Ugly puppy pads
My source would not go to that level however he did that there was
It looks like tomatoes research at you will find things
Better not right with it
Your Source sucks
Even if even if you was trying to lead you in a
Real direction that
Witchy weather
The dumb
What's the
Station there's no parts of it might have been looped in
Really
Yeah
I would assume that there is a Homeland Security aspect
I think I could be a compelling argument
Especially in the early points of it when you're not sure the nature of the attack
Ride
Green children
One of the issues
It's gotten Us in so much trouble
In terms of
These sorts of things
Is
Beginner Department
Inability to
Communicate with you
From
DHHS even if they're not active
If we involved like
If there is a paths
Right ears on it
First of all
Communicated
With our
Examples exist Beyond even 9/11
How to reach other
I would like to think it was I think like the salary negotiations on Friends
Like if they were only then Gunther could have got it
What are the great
Great Injustice has of art I've never intentionally
We watched an episode of Friends
Not much there
Very much of note that Doug Hagmann is
Dispersed person
To enter Alex's world
Rockman hack
Rock band
He is the first person to enter Alex's world with us
Supposedly realsource
Who's telling him
Sandy Hook does that up baby
So he
Is patient zero
The publicly facing
Part of Infowars the radio show with someone who is
Leaving out
Cuz nobody nobody is pretended to have any
Not yet
And this is our first
Doug Hagmann
We go to the 20
And much like
The present day in 2019
Alex Jones
Butt implant
Mike Adams is hosting the first two-and-a-half hours of
The show because Alex is
Alex's behind-the-scenes working hard on special
Investigative research
He's not it leads him to his declaration
Reveal once Alex does get on there and it's f****** disappointing is
But it's not as disappointing as look
He is fat
We will
Exchange
OST
Dianne Feinstein
Can't quite at the meter
Mike Adams starts the show
Is a guy who runs
Glock Outlet
These they're filling in
I really don't think you can be a health Ranger and a huge gun guy right like that
Michaels
Contains multitude
Fair
Crab Coronavirus
That broadcast
Across-the-board
But that's totally
I get it
Pattern of olives
Understand the author of
Okay
Kelly O'Mara
The author of psyched out isn't she know she's not the Doctor Who's no longer allowed
Author who wrote the books
Colon
How psychiatrist mental illness
Oh I thought it was more about like how
Okay I brought together while somebody's
Newsela
She's not a psychologist or psychiatrist
Political science from the University of Maryland
I will give her that her bio repeated verbatim on tons of website
Flames
Congressional staffer for for different members of Congress
But nowhere do they ever say who they are
But I'm guessing that they were whoever these four craziest people in Congress were at any given time
I have no idea
His speech writer
Coming back 20 years later
Barbra
Sure
Insight ran from 1985 to 2008 but with the magazine is probably best remembered for is being
The first ones to report
Completely fabricated
Story that Barack Obama
At least 4 years
Islamic madrasa in Indonesia
Clinton campaign
Provide them with that story leave us alone
We didn't say that
Not that one
Believability
Someone from the Clinton campaign
Did give them that story that does not let inside off the hook for notch
Absolutely
22 involved
Use the conservative
Media as a weapon
Good like
What now
It's 2019
So we're all good
12 years of the Clinton
Campaign staffers being
I mean I don't know I'm not saying that they did obviously
I'm just saying that
If it if someone were to give me evidence that they did I wouldn't say that
Put that out
Campaign
Bandits
The world of right-wing propaganda
I know that for sure I've heard Alex at least allude to it
Fairly recent
If memory serves
Correctly
Something real
Whatever the reality about their story have it their sourcing
Important
The holes are the inside has no rats
Also Insight magazine is owned by Reverend Sun Myung Moon the head of the Moon occult
The Washington Times
Really yeah
That makes a Larvitar with the Washington Times and insight
Cornerstones of Reverend Sun Myung
Infiltration into right-wing media
So it gets more.
Kelly just right for inside
She's also a contributor for the citizens Commission on human rights
With a name like that we know we're dealing with a straight-up organization
All those words are really good
Center for American progress
Commission commission implies collaboration
Right
Organization of the people
Not the fact
I think it also implicitly as a right-wing
New source
Excludes people
The cchr was founded by the Church of Scientology in 1969
It seems to exist
Front group for the church to whitewash their extremist Auntie psychology messages
A search of deceased ehrs website turns up
33 pages of Articles written by Kelly O'Mara
Perhaps most importantly articles written by her for cchr dating back to
2 / 4
December 2012 when this episode is from
Did she was working for a straight-up Scientology funded anti-psychiatry propaganda organization
Original name was the CCC
L.ron Hubbard
I believe that's what it was
ABC order
New York
I like that
Throwing the baby out with the bathwater and I tried
People regardless of their affiliation
But even I have to
You can see that I think
Disqualifying
Critic of the psychiatric
To work for the Church of Scientology
Yeah you lose
That's not good you lose.
Different standards
Is that the discount
Text Magic
As a legitimate
Escape the Fate
Got to keep them forever
Yeah I thought that was great
Oh it's one of those things
Jessica
Do you have somebody who's now bring it cuz they talk about the psych stuff
You know they talk about how these are suicide pills
Don't really have any guests on who can back that up
Is it claims and assertions that Alex's make
Claim these red studies
Finally they get somebody on alike
What's up with her
What's up with you
People on
Where it's like
They're not
Climate
Doctors
Where's they're not
Anybody with an a
Expertise in there
Fairfield
There's somebody with a degree in Paw
Political
That's more like
You have a degree in law
For whatever it's worth.
Positive
Necessarily
Patrice
Pretty passionate
Like she's written articles about this stuff
4 years
It is possible that she's on
If you don't have someone who's
Makeup expert in the fee
Field went to school for it and opportunist
Right
I don't think that she's an opportunist
How many
I can't find hard evidence that she is a Scientology
Gotcha do I will say
The cchr for years
Heavily implied
EBay suspected
Scientology pays well-to-do propaganda for the
Either
I think there's two possibility
Either she is a Scientologist
And then she has a religious
The psychiatry
Is evil possible
She's not a Scientologist
Accentuate
For at least
Yeah yeah
He's fit like
She has to know
It's the Church of Scientology
It's behind this organization
I would say I mean I mean everybody
To have butter
On the bread
I hear you land the metaphor
Bread is buttered
Who cares where butter in the cross sign
Just butter the crust
Look if you wanted to take a crust buttering job
She could have her own blog
Fulex
Yep
Weird but also stoic
Like
Much talk about Sandy Hook
I mean Mike Adams says that
He believed like
He's perpetuating the this was only handgun
In the school dress Master is because
He is operating off bad reporting
He plays a name
ABC clip where they has bad earlier
Information that the rifle was in the car as opposed to once
The information
In the car at the rifle was
Nbcnews
He's saying that the rifle wasn't in
The school
The car never only handguns
The school so I'm giving Mike Adams
A good bit of leeway
At this point
Put hue
Reporting
On misreported
Yes so are you right
You're right
I think the credit is
Well I mean there's so many times
Do the stuff and they never show their homework or anything like that
Like argument that goes a bad Direct
Yeah it does end up in there be multiple shooters
Like that because
You only have two hands
No it's not but
The misreporting of MBC
Cnews they did say right
For sure
That I am report
When people bring up
Bushmaster
A gun
I'm not just
Crocodiles
It is a very
I wish I had
This whole episode.
The real Crocodile Dundee
Be about 40 f****** time
No it's because Alex has narrative about the real crocodile. About
Tried to come take his guns and he shot some cops and then
And they killed him
But he repeatedly as an example of this is what
Grabbers work
It's ship
Sowega
To the 30th
And again
Rock not a lot that interesting to our investigation
Is this
On the Rogan show
Recently
Alex came back on Joe Rogan
Podcast I remember
Recruiter back when he was a kid
And he f*****
Haha I believe that was the thrust of his story
Braids girl was
Being abused by her
Edna and Alex
Right
7 years ago
We finally found it.
Hi
Do you think it's possible this is one of the times he did crack
I could
He has talked about being out like on a beach doing crack
With attractive girls
Stuff like that
Smoke smoke some
Music cracker map
It's entirely possible these are the same story
Cuz it's 8:00 girls at a bonfire outdoorsy kind of thing
Progress
Differences
Between Alex's
2019 version of the story and this 2012
There's no relationships that he
Has become aware of his daughter for sure the walk home from
Love the idea
Like this mental image is so funny to me
The idea people inviting Alex to parties
It every time you shows
I'm 13 but I look 16 and I like to party
I'm at fistfights I drink beer
I like to go to parties
Good like the Craigslist
Missed connections where the guy is a cannibal
Hey I'm looking for somebody to eat
And then you show up
We're just hanging out
Bulshit
Bulshit more like an entire
Like group prank
Luther like
We are going to
F*** with this kid
Esps behavioral issues
Did you get it
Just
Put on a wig and invited to a party cuz party
He's going to recognize you
Put on a wig
Wear black
Whatever
And then barbering we're all saying this is going to be disappointed people are
What is going to propel our documentary 2
I think it's going to be hard cuz
Exist
I feel like that interview
How that is going to be
Yeah
When you invited Alex to your parties where you f****** with him about being a Satanist
Might be saying
Well you're doing a great job
He's hanging out with John to Grandpa
I do know that he is
I think the end is exactly why
Retained
Personal story because he believes it gives him this like
Authenticity that other radio other radio host his
Have never experienced that have never been brushed up against
I know what the real reality
Is it supposed to their man
Manufactured bulshit
Reality
Swap meet
The parties
Tired of it
Walk home
Regular parties
I would assume so
I mean
F****** do what thou wilt
That's the extent of the house rules
At the same time
If your 13
I'm not even the most
You should probably not have 13 year olds at all right
60 minutes
Clip left
The 31st
I think
To give a demonstration
Alex's hair
He's been really Doom and Gloom for like this entire week
Just Dance
News I believe
Antagonize someone
And his audience
Do something
I think that there's a day like this year
Trying to
Somebody to
Cause
That's a big one
Yeah I don't know it's
Feels like
It feels like
He is
It really
But I don't know how much of it
Conscious
Like I wouldn't accuse
Of intentionally trying
To get someone to call the shooter
But it is
It is a big
Logical extension
If that is the truth
But that's going to kick off a civil war
Why wait
For that to happen
Yeah or whatever
It is easy for one of his listeners
To hear that
And then the other piece that is important to me
Is that
If
Someone
Do that
Where to like go shoot up something
Inspired by this
It would help out
Because then
His arguments that there's going to be
Copycat
Doug Hagmann saying there's going to be more
Rug Hagman
Has the same
Intense
So you're Alex
Consciously or unconsciously
I lean more towards unconscious but right
So he's kind of
Instigate
Whereas
Is rugby
Seems to be aware of his
Narrative
Do you think he's insta
I don't know I don't know I don't have enough time with him
But I really not enough
Even second-guesses
Intentions
And I don't question of intention is so important
Because if he's intentionally trying to rile up his audience
In such a way
That they will go attack somebody
Really really sucks
If he's accidentally doing it it's still super f***** up super
It's not like
Legally actionable
It it's not
Yeah technically
Drug rug
There's going to be another
Malik singer
Be copycat
Right
If Alex's rhetoric does inspire some
Go out
Shooting
That validates the rhetoric
You've been putting out there's going to be more
Inspired by the right that's
And then further
Inevitably the person who did it to have
Tightly
So much
But he's been putting
Now that still doesn't
Make it
But the elements are all there of
There is no real downside for him
If he doesn't care right
Right what's the temperature
Every month
For this to occur
Like I can't imagine putting myself in a place
Swear
The best circumstances
Stanford
Lake pictures
Like at the end of the day
When a mass shooting
Their sales go up even talk about that house
Contacts
I'd like isn't it great that more Americans have guns
When are the same
Maybe a couple more
People getting guns but mostly people getting bored
See what I would be a reflection percent 1% of gun owners
75%
Something along those lines in the ballpark
Yeah
Regressing
There
Where is it a totally open about that phenomenon and almost celebratory
Yeah
We've made a s*** ton of money
Exactly
And it yet
Which is heartbreaking on its own
But still none of it
None of it
Intentionality
Because I ate
Easy to hear the things I'm saying
And get the idea that I make
Accusation
Play right now
Everything Alex is doing his super dangerous
Even if he's not playing with these people at Hooker actors
Buddies jumped in
Civil War is imminent or going to take
You're gone that's her to stop
Is that Justice
The circumstantial evidence
What is
Overwhelming
I'm even the queen Bono argument doesn't really
It doesn't help me
Solidified
How much is just like an
You know what I'm saying
No matter what
Because if he makes these arguments and one of the listeners
Does that then
Things could play out the way I described
Or if nobody doesn't
Great
Because there aren't more shooting
And stuff like that
Can then be like
We stopped it
If I wasn't the Watchman on the wall scream my lungs out about
They
My behavior
The things that I was making you afraid of right you're welcome
It's kind of in
Incredible
How
Good position
He is in
As as
He's doing such
Monster
Or at least defensible position
He's behind a wall of
Deniability about stuff
More importantly
His
Profile is so much
Lower
Do you know
Cuz he's trying to get that.
Dance clothes
2012 I'm mad at Nancy Pelosi
Publicity stunts right well for him and then also
He's going
Inevitably
Run afoul of
Good taste
These RV Sandy Hook
He's going he's going to make those Legend
Yeah
At this point
Because
W
Witches
Which is of course
Something that like reinforces
Decisions up until
Words like
I am in a position where
Probably
Things that are somewhat legally action
Right
Nobody
Like people are paying attention
But not enough people to
To cause me
You know
So
He's a huge
So much in 2000
He is so
In 20
Dumb s***
With no fear of reprisal
No fear of reprisal
Cumber doesn't
Seem right cuz I don't know if he could ever be unencumbered
Tubi
Hornet track
For sure
Like
Harnessing
Severe paranoia gun narrative stuff
But that's
Entire career
So
He's been going on and on about how like they're coming for the guns going to be civil war all that stuff
It's on the 31st
New Year's Eve
Here we go this is when he celebrates the birth of Christ
Week 4
Be forgotten
Never brought to mind
All the cares of laughs
Euro behind us
Better future absolutely
A wise man
Auld Lang Syne
Quality for most people
Resolution
I want to lose some weight
Want to get back to
Being active
Diet
Alex is the exact opposite of what he has hollow
On New Year's Eve
100%
2 Peter
Garage
Political
Ladies and gentlemen
New Year we're all going to have our throats
Year America dies the Bill of Rights
Is gone dead
Throats and carotid
And jugular I'm not going to lie to you
Bummer
My New Year's message
For about 4 years running has always been
Goodbye to a shity
Year
Send hello to a
Even back
No I think he's a bummer
Just gloomy is it is it still
There's still a moving on aspect of
Goodbye
There is a difference to that where this is
I know this is all, we're all dead we're all dead this year
To be like haha
I think he just kind of got really excited about being right about that
Happy 2013.
It is over
We're getting our throats slit
Hezel Honda
Percent
Willy-nilly prediction
He is really feeling that
At this point
How's your throat
Okay well then I guess he was wrong
Squidward Howard Patriots throat
Racist
Supremacist
Better than ever
2012 in Alex Jones timeline
Hey can I apologized
This is a little bit of a shorter episode but no.
Friday
Hopefully this place that I'm going to check out tomorrow will be
Be good
And I'll be able to get
And if that's the case
Ryder truck
So getting the miac report removed
Appreciate your patience
And also I will keep you up-to-date
Honest Alex Jones backup
We got we got hot sauce watch
And we got Alex Plus
There's a lot I got a block
Giant
For the record Dan is still make
Taking the juggling Mojo
He is making the Dismount to the end of the
Triple threat
While you're juggling
Do we have a Twitter account
Pizza Hut
Me and there's one last thing like we're podcast
Is it always that way
So I would say
These people
That we talked about today
Kelly O'Mara
I mean she's been a shell
Certainly giving bad advice probably lead people to not take medication when they probably should
To be medicated
It's an accessory accessory to murder
Bright but not not with her bare hands
So she's in the clear
Probably have done just that
The young man
Alexandra Thurston color