Alexandra Thurston color
What was the last time you were illegally fired by
I feel like every time I've been fired
It's been called for
I don't know
Millionaires
At the carwash
No no
Play w g grinder
Play Sitting on the Play Store
The franchisor
W.g. grinders 1920s
Place with
They were one of the early places
Quiznos Style
Hey hey
My boss their posture
I've been fired from
So many places
Direct
Newest son-of-a-b**** are you serious
Tuesday damn
Tuesday
Scott
Kluthe
Who is the boyfriend of one of the Real Housewives of New York
I didn't know as we started this that you were going to be named
Oh hell yeah
It's not necessarily represent
Knowledge fight LLC
Violation of
Let's switch it turns out
A reason that I can't tell all the right
People
And I can tell you that labor relation
Incredibly helpful and
After I filled all the affidavit and all of that stuff
And everything was signed away and I'll good to go
I was like I just want to make sure I'm a comedian I'm a public figure I talk about stuff them
This is fine to talk about writing he's like yeah
Specific
But let me tell you some
It wouldn't be a bad idea to
To tell people about the National Labor Relations
And what it is we do for work
Hers all across this nation
Which was written by Aaron Sorkin
National Labor Relations
Bored
No it's perfect world I would be in the middle of trying to
Get fired if enter a very complicated
Tyler J.
Spirit
Keep our spirit is there a lot of people out there who are signing up to support
Appreciate it very much
Do some people have signed up to
To Westport.
First
You are now a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Giordano policy walk
Thank you
You are now a policy
I'm a policy wonk wonk
Badass
What's the first
I'm not sure
Good morning
Caleb
You so much
You are now
Someone sodomites
Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much Caleb
I'd like to sports show what these guys do I like
Motosport
Please do it be helpful so I'd like to start out this episode today
Language is a little
Sensational in the last episode
I know that I called myself out for like these are stupid
But it's still not the kind of conversation
Star show
Especially because
Little more time is going on in the mystery solved of where has Alex been
Austin American living in art
Happier time for him
So I knew that Alex had recent
Learned or the world has been reported
If you was going to have to sit
For a deposition
In Houston
But none of the stories that I had
Had any kind of specifics of
Timeline
However I found an article in the Austin american-statesman
For last week
That was talking about Thursday
He had a court appearance
That
The judge decided the
But he had to sit for
For a deposition
This Thursday
So on the 14th of March
He had to sit for a deposition
I'm still not sure why that means he was gone for a week
But that has to have some
Maybe he had to go to
Connecticut to give the deposition
I'm not entirely sure
That explains his absence
If the
Lawsuit is brought in a specific
You
Do you have to go to that state to give the deposition or you could you just rude
To go extinct
I don't know I don't know how it works but I do know that
Pending in Texas
I don't know there's so much
Non-transparency
In terms of like how this
Call Casey
It was missed by our
Or speculation
Bring up the possibility to
The legal cases
We're getting real
We just thought that it could be
Be worse
After listening to
It was it was
Everybody
Betty Wright
It's it is what it is
Explains pretty much all
Case is getting real
He's in a bad place
I'm thinking back on Thursday
The 14th he was back
Studio doing part of his show
So everything is somewhat back to normal
We'd not have time before recording
To cover music
Half an hour or so of it
Is pretty boring
So
Not enough present-day stuff to go into so we're going back
To no longer 2012
2013 January 1st second
What's the temperature
Amanda
Episode
Text crazy
Like
What are the really frustrating things about studying Alex Jones and take
Bring him in his own linear path
Is that he never gives you what you think
You're going to get
We expected
Good bit of Sandy Hook.
I don't know where
Videos of the cat
Yeah it's the middle of December
To have a fair amount of coverage
The false flag
Suggest that people or actors
Certifit
Fear that the globalists are taking their guns
Which will lead to a civil war holding pattern
Until the end of 2012
Laughing about how people thought
That he thought it was the end of the world on December 21st people
This is a crisis level emergency
The gun grabbing is going to happen
It's it's
It's not so you expect that
After the holidays
Not really focusing on anything
Can you just kind of Costa
Draeger's
New Year rolls around
Then you start to get that new field for a month and then it all goes away and comes back to ship
Really feeling it on
The first
You can hear them this first
Official
I will
He doesn't
Define distal
I hope
Looks like
Soul searching
I'm going to put out more information
That does not suggest there's a lot of depth
To that song no no it doesn't the most informative years
Equivalent of like
Just saying I'm going to
Eat healthy this year
At the end of you like I think I did
Reviews.
Plastic
Zagg pronouncements of of the new year
He doesn't make another documentary
Cuz the last one that I ever put out
Stretch
Was that
With with 1,000
Joel skousen
Did not know about that it's just a really long interview
You can bug out
Long to just talk to Joel skousen
It's so long
It it's longer
Zen documentary
But I watched
Not good
I don't think it was a good idea
Salt Lake
2 hours really got to go hard
To be shittier at your jobs
The project Berry
I wasn't really thinking about covering it for the
This episode
Things to do at
Glass about
Like legitimately the documentary
Is Jacob Wohl
And Laura Loomer
Just sitting around or standing outside door
That's some compelling footage right there
Terrible
Did they use real probably more visually stimulating then
Strategic relocation
Alex's
What were his places
What if we looked into it and there was it like
I don't know where to hide my gun I guarantee there would be some useful information
It doesn't pay me to admit that
Even these like crazy survivalist
Do have some pieces of good information like I know how to get water
You bet
Everyone should know that
So
It's just
It's a matter of scale
So
The most informed
But if you're ever
I'm going to do this
I'm going to crush it
The rest of the show is dogshit
Of course
It is a no-man's-land I listen to it I can find
Nothing worth discovered
It's a lot of like looks like
Kind of stuff she has mr. and mrs. America get ready
Your guns
And in order to justify that he plays a like
Years and years old clip
I'm talking about in the past
If she was able to get a bill through that would have taken everyone's done she would have done that
But you can't
She couldn't do it then was implying in any way she still wants to do that
Legislation
So he's using that to make the argument that
Dianne Feinstein is a
Mr and Mrs America
Something that Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie movie
That's where they fell in
Lowe's
And that the doctor
From House
Was that was
Movie
Jennifer is trash there's nothing going on there
Walkthrough your thought process
On the 2nd
January 2nd
And Alex
Man of 10 seconds
Can't remember what year it is information
Alright dude on his desk
Real facts
It's already
Eddie's Betty says it every day so it's
You can take a little while
It's already the 3rd day of March 2000
Any does not explain it all why he
He's saying that the Year is already longer
But I wanted answered
Ciara
Picture this year
I did one bad show that's about it
What was
Professor Snape
Dumbledore
Rick was still around in 2012
Fine as long as rickman's around it was good times you know what else was around
That was still around
Larry summers in 1990
Whoa
So
Get rid of people
Like that but they're a couple problems
Larry Summers
Media has a link to it which the research process was just to make sure there was something on Wikipedia
Forget that there's a second
So I couldn't
The second problem is that if you read the Wikipedia entry about this memo the second paragraph on the page
You just get down to the second paragraph
You find an explanation that one Larry Summers
Didn't write the memo
The guy who did text the memo with meant to be satirical
It means to prompt interrupt departmental debate
M3
The verse of the memo that was Week Tonight
Was doctored specifically to remove contacts to make it
Seem like those proposals that were being made or serious
So somebody added a modest proposal to make it look like they really wanted to eat more less
New Yorker the author of the memo
2 Summers
Is it
Walt Walt
I strongly recommended that
He say I had written it and then you just signed it
Larry said no that wasn't just dial
Whatever you signed he would take
Responsibility for
He took the flag
In 2001 Pritchett spoke to the Harvard magazine
Specifically light out what it happened
Basically the summation of his explanation
Somerset requested that he read over the world bank's global economic prospects
Report which was largely about trade liberalization
He was tasked with writing a memo to Somers NY
Which ended up being 7
Long
What are the points Pritchard said GPS was the World Bank
I meant that free trade would naturally
And specifically like automatically
Lead to environmental benefits in developing Khan
Quote he questioned the data supporting that claim
Criticism Road isn't ironic
Conventional economic term
Dumping pollutants on pork trees would be welfare enhancement
For the world as a whole the bank audit endorse policy
Right
They're up there after Pritchard says
Someone with access to the memo doctor Ditka
Combined to The Heading In the sentences on pollution
Toxic waste
Shorn of their context than the intended irony
This one page form appears to be a policy proposal
The version of the Galaxy's red is
The doctored one page
Which version not the version that is the actual memo
All he knows is that there's a Wikipedia article about it
And that's good enough for
He has no idea he's read the propaganda version
Of this
D2
As opposed to the real version
That sounds about right did they find out who dr. the memo or did that guy get away with
Go to bed
I'm not entirely sure if they ever rebuild
Whodunnit
The trace it is b*******
Congratulations on starting 2013
Very informal
Cuz I didn't know about
Information
Most of the first
Wasn't talking about Dianne Feinstein
And I'm continuing these.
Are you gone
Trend
Where
If Alex has been doing
Some soul-searching
It's in a weird Direction and it's about his own celebrity
Because it next clip
Alex talks about Howard
He's never tried to be a movie
And then tell the story about auditioning to be a
Point of order Tommy Plata is linklaters if it's a
Different project
Experience
Other movies
Radio talk show host surprise
Dick
Auditions for movies
Already
Alex
You would never
One of these Casting Studios
Alex
Porto Opera
I mean
What's the answer
Because if the answer is no
Is the answer is yes
Alex was a super attractive
I've seen his broadcast
From 9/11
But you know it's from 2,000
I don't know if you took like a real downward slope in a year's time
What you look like an average
Maybe late thirties do even though he wasn't late that's what he look like
Sauquoit average
Flex boat it's the old
Inflection that took him down the path we're on right now
Sex worker
He was rejected from entry
Prince into that world after
Turn
Ben Tommy pallotta
Where he played
Greatest
Crazy man with Boulevard in the Pirates of the Caribbean foreign remix
Sure
Even matches
Is being crazy guy with bullhorn in a link later
The growing up
Is pretty cool on some level
Even if it is because linklater liked him and gave him the part
It's still an achievement
Subways
I don't want to take that away from
But okay
I want to know
What would have been around 2,000 what Titanic Good morning Vietnam
A little bit before
As the book goes
Asian role in talk radio
What other movies
What's the AUD Network
Yeah I guess
Radio movie
So it is
Conversation about Lake
He went there he was trying to audition
Free movies
Something like that
He starts talking about
Disgusting mrs. Hollywood
And how evil it is
And it gets caught up in it and starts lamenting
The women who have been chewed up and spit out by the system
It's on this one huh
Farm girl from Kansas
You don't have to get back to that energy
You're just perfect
Perfect proportions
California
She oughta be a movie star
She was so pretty she was so smart
That's just what she should do
A lighter shade of the Black Dahlia
Thousands of times
50 years of Los Angeles salon
Mother
Wholesome
Mrs America
I think Alex has been listening to Too Much poison and maybe hasn't been listening to Mama's Fallen Angel
Cowboys
I mean
Fisher
Businesses
Exploitative
Clearly
Describe
Connotations
You know perfect complexion that's America has a perfect
Fix complexion. Like if only she hadn't of done that she would
And found a man
New version this could have gone whatever
For that but he's trying to compare that to America end
America is a
Mafia
To America
And Hollywood is apart of
There's more
Anthony start
Ramblin a whole bunch settle down we could have
Canada
Well I mean
The queen
Are we staying in the Americas want a relationship
Brushes
Traditional that Mrs America Russia would never allow that
Not at all
Number for does Fall Apart
A little bit
Alex is trying to make that
Talking about
How there are like
I don't even really know how he gets into it starts telling stories about how
When he was a kid
Outside of Dallas
The town in order to buy beer
Okay
I'm not really honestly sure how that relates
To the largest
The conversation
To do with like
Mafias make
These areas of town bad
And like the police is with the mafia
Yeah
I don't think
He gets that far
Complaining about it in some ways to say like
There were terrible things going on there but I could go buy beer there
More time talking about how he
Got beer there connect now
It's not like he is trying to say
See I can go anywhere
Because I am not a terrible situation
These neighborhoods work that they didn't card people for alcohol
Without realizing what he's talking about
It gets worse as the clip goes on where you talked about going to buy beer
Indeed
Put 100
Is like New York
Of the stuff that goes on out there
I don't really
The problem that I have is he's not really
He's not really deal
Ewing weather
Steven
But he's painting
Are you just got done talking about how Hollywood choose up Annex
Louisville
These impressionable young
Impoverished communities we could buy beer to take it back to the rich place
To lure cheerleaders through his house
So I don't understand exactly where the disconnect is there
But he's a f****** dick in the story right
I am going to go to this neighborhood
Right and they've been specifically put down there
Let's sell this kid liquor
I'm going to take that liquor
Backup to my rich f*** neighborhood
And I'm going to try sexually assault women
I mean
He's describing is like
Youthful Shanaynay
22 Atherton
Although he's talking about it with like a very naughty
You know they are out of someone who is like
Maybe in college reminiscing about high school years
Is pushing 40
And have a family
I remember when I was 15 and we used to do that
When I was younger it so I bought
I could get
Cards
Drunk
Play
Manipulate time back and forth
Alex goes back to that metaphor that he was
Who's making about America
Turned out by Hollywood
And ends up as a
The prostitutes
Heroin overdoses
If you thought that first telling of that allegory was gross
Strap it in
Way grocery
More or less the same stories
Sites to tell
But go harder
Beautiful
Pieology fence
You shouldn't have to announce why right now over
And cigarette Burns and cuts all over it
Overdosing
There's always
She's 6 months into it
Mom
Little kids
La Carreta
Don't you ever try to leave me again
Arc dad dad on a dirty match
And Brazil
This is
Did that
That
That was his grandma that's her that's her letter Alexa
Just getting into telling the story
An excitement of the
Gross misdemeanor
It's dumb
That's a gross person
Wrong with having that Dark Fantasy a lot of great writers
There is something wrong with the way he tells it
Yeah everybody
Literary achieve
Scare
That's it
He's using it to reinforce like his idea of what
His perceived enemies are doing to the
The United States
So I mean it's manipulation pure and simple
Manipulation by
Gross button
Yeah really f****** gross
Even the writers for Dragnet would be like
Pull it back
Come on
This is a weird
This is a weird place that
Episode
Departure from
These days
Stopping
Real weird
Just kind of make you scared about gun grab
Much more like
This is a weird Alex Day
This is strange
Forget the talking about these
These shootings that are happen
How do you compare
Other killers
From the past other serial killers
He comes to the conclusion
The combines all of them
The dog walker
New York
Worshiper worshippers are our problem
Our problem is devil worshiper
Going.
He's grasping at straws and terms
Figure out exactly what
The Narrative is about
He's already
Volkswagen government
All that stuff
But
He's still
Unclear how to land on
How did the
Explain Lanza
Because there's documentation of him existing before
Information that's available that he can't just make disappear
We have to still contextualized
As of the beginning
Is
Like he's already laid the foundation of the psych meds
And video games
Like that
To Hollywood
Hollywood is just
General
It is
Satan
The problem
That's not something
Oh yeah
And it was almost like to hear on
No I don't even like to go Brett all the time
I was just letting you know
Barack Obama
Do some of this comment
Because at the end
He says something
That was the present time
Is that real
Taken
Scana minutes
Considering he will seriously
Flipping test
Because actually a fair point but
Very poorly said and the other point
The idea that
Barack Obama can get away with these things
He's black
We racist
Viewpoints
To have
But
Or at least I think he's
Trying
Is the idea that probably a lot of middle-of-the-road democrat
Didn't do a good job of
Obama's
To the fire and demanding more out of
He was delivering
The function of
It is
Ethnicity at all
I think it's a funk
Function of dumpy monster
It is it is such a thing that you pointing out
We in that
The right would say
She's doing all this stuff as a way to criticize
You guys love
Liberals love it when he does that
The ones who didn't wear like
Democrats
Well you're not being loyal
Everybody who
Who doesn't want that to happen
And the people who say we do are the ones
Like that's essentially like
Worldview
Loyalty
Yeah I think
Okay thanks to Anna
NetSpend
I think that you just had you had a situation
People aren't good at being their own
Watch Dogs
I think you see that to some extent with either party whenever they're in power they don't do a good job of
Calling out the
Of the person who's on their team
Present
I think that's a natural phenomenon
There are forces
Within each side that dude
Try to do
But they're usually on the outskirts
They're not usually
Closest
To the actual levers
The power
Coming from the other side
He's always in bad faith because we're going to do that once our guy is in
Was not right or whatever
Calling alien Omar
So
Is something
Really opened area of exploration
Episode
That I'm
Getting a little bit in
On this episode
Opens up
Of understanding Alex
In a different way
I think that's
Because if you're not paying attention
This guest
Bucking bull
This person would be not even a blip on your radar
But
You look into him a little bit
You scratch the surface
He becomes
He becomes an introduction into some really f***** up world
That Alex is connected
2 in waist
That we might not have
Realized
Here is
Captain Mark Richards
Congressional whistleblower
Okay I don't know I don't know if I want to know which
Where this is going
Soap operas just one more in a long line about Stephen Iran-Contra
Fair
They almost got that would have changed the course of the universe
Russell every comic as that story
I really don't I bet you do know no gay guy I've ever done ever done would have changed
Career let alone what they have it done
Bridgewood opened up for no I've never been close
Proves the rule play from heavy metal
Thousand of those
But a story about
Where part is that a number of them aren't making things up entirely
Even if they're embellishing a little bit to make a hero story for themselves right there not
Like making it up out of whole cloth Like Larry Nichols can lie about the extent he was involved
But he was definitely make
Can collect calls on behalf of the contras absolutely
He was lying about the truth about the
You could have been like if he was in
Yeah
Company in Atlanta in the late
In 1985 a guy named Gary Bast came into his operation and offered to buy the company
To stay on running
Gradually became
Testifying
Is people who worked with Gary batt
Play Robin Williams what is this
Investigators looking into the Iran-Contra
Scandal they interviewed their offices
And deep that his evidence was not worth pursuing Iran-Contra businesses
People
Substantial
Neither he nor Gary bass got in any trouble about Iran-Contra it conveniently Bob claims that all the records
The government has by the company
Have been classified as top secret
Shopko
We have
It we need to get to the
In the world to establish a villain
Gary Beck
Because you can repurpose them later when you need them
Like having a hand in the Oklahoma City bomber
Slater
We'll get to that
Iran-Contra special prosecutor Lawrence
Decided
They decided to head out to the woods in Montana
For now all you need to know is it since 2014
Planet is heading our way and how they leave their building
His career path I'm not going to like this website include the section of photographic evidence from
A various playing
It includes a picture of gold bars with the caption quote
Fort Knox
The rest of the pictures are
Okay that's good
It's just a bunch of picture of bars of gold
Could be
F****** stock photos
The rest of the pictures are clearly photoshopped Shottas
Are you suggesting the picture of a real life wormhole
But it's just the moon with spiral drunk
Coming out of it
Okay
Video game
It's at least decently done
So that's this guy's career but that's not nearly all he's
Next clip
We get to hear a little bit from Bob
He gives his own fire
Alex
Miscellaneous random
For myself for this morning program
Exactly what you been saying
One of the primary people
Creating
So
His buyout that he wants Alex to know
Is that he personally
Was the parts of starting the militia Patriot movement
Name of this episode
Close it is to the actual
Don't forget you in Montana you have to start a militia just
To survive out there
It's kind of part of the team
It was an early member and leader within the militia of Montana
One of the first militia groups to form in the aftermath of the coast
Thereformation response to the Ruby Ridge standoff
The actual guy
Attend the meeting in Estes Park Colorado that would go on to be known as the Rocky Mountains
Conference where the modern militia movement was born
160 self-described Christian man who were all very white
Not to discuss their discomfort about how the Federal
It was behaving
Particularly as it related to
The central figure of Ruby Ridge
For this point a lot of things that we've experienced as being deeply interconnect
Like white supremacist groups
Certex protester
Christian identity
We're just vaguely but intensely anti-government group
We're not generally working
Together
Extremist existed in those categories previously
There are often unwilling to collaborate
This 1992
In Colorado with an attempt
Just saw that robbed
Good
Uno
No I don't want that
The meeting was organised by extremist preacher Pete Peters
Is Ministry largely centered on his argument that homosexuals should be put to death
As he laid out in a booklet
I'm sorry was white
Rock rocks
Yeah representatives of the Klan Christian identity of the Posse Comitatus
A literal Murderers Row
This was a meeting that is literally something out of a comic book
A gathering of villains who don't really even like each other against their common enemy the federal government
We need to take
Alright we're going to take your
27 years later we can see was
Probably pretty
From Stephen of right-wing extremism in modern American
Close to the Rocky Mountain Rendezvous for the idea of armed civilian militia
Twerk
Armed civilian militias would be mostly white middle-class
Individuals who are not necessarily racist
Either anxious about the economy and their future
As it turns out some excuses for bigotry
Never stop being affected
Anxiety
You see here from these groups like the area Nations and
The clan
Christian heating up
Get better recruitment they realize that they have to Brand as being about economic anxiety as a
Close to the actual racist
S*** that they were actually
So
That is to say is
History
Everybody around here
We know
How we feel about vinod
Of all kind
And a lot of the white
But we can't
We can do it
Well it would hurt.
Clan members and Logan would you rather successful
Would you rather
Was a strategy forming brainstorm
Plant
And how the situation the Patriots found themselves
Malady of evil moment where it's like Holiday Inn
Conference Wireless
Sales
Jeezy All of the ideas.
I'm on any of Alex's shows
From any point
Very close to Alex's
New York
Meeting with Louis
Representative
You may recall that beat was the guy who came up with
Concept or popularized
The concept of the leaderless resistance
Which Alex talked about being apart of
In the mid-90s
We have the force
We have the capacity we have the world and we will not
Call the one
Special Ops
Where are the ones galvanizing organization
Where are the ones
Counter
You
Trader you globalization and you Governor bush
From your CIA running Harriman brother
Royal family
We got your numbers and we're galvanized
And we are moving forward and you be fully aware
You're going to pay
Direct Car sponsors humor
11 years prior to the 1992
Disbanded
Emergency room
What year was training
Reclaim this country for white
What they were about a little bit
Rocky Mountain rendezvous
Larry Pratt
Head of gun owners for America
Someone who Alex had on the show as a guest
In the week after Sandy Hook
Strongest proponent of the strategy moving forward being the formation of quote
Unorganized militia
Which followed beam leaderless resistance ideology
That's making them almost impossible to
Larry Pratt was one of 106
People who were at this Rocky Mountain rendezvous
We're all of you
The representatives
From the clan
Aryan Nations other neo-Nazi
Group Christian identity
Text protester extremist
All together to strategize
Along with Louis beam
It's insane
This is a real very serious problem
Really
Bums me out because
If that was the plot of a warrior style Road movie
A small group of a white nationalist
Call gang right that go to this meeting
They realize what's going on almost
Immediately
Everybody likes
The doors
Through each different gang the Klan is all wearing white Hood
The Aryan Brotherhood or whatever it is they wear
What do they wear
And then you got
A sign that says the three people voted on the Fed
The Holiday Inn Express
I can't find it
We list of that hundred sixty but I bet there's some other names
Oh yeah
Sure
Becker
The rendezvous
You don't start the militia of Montana
But almost certainly exist
Previously
Occasionally take up arms and storm Courthouse
95 most of the militia of Montana's work was on the
The information Warfare side of
They were less paramilitary in nature and more of a mail-order militia
They were clearing house
4 militia groups to get videos on how to start your own militia
The author of the report
About about that
Backlash from people like
Which isn't a coincidence
You know what that reminds
So much of Isis
Perspective a little bit
Defending
These Patriot militia types
When you realize like
A lot of
He's actually
Involved with
Rzp
Who were the ones
Who started this
9 starting pitcher was Chaka block with racist
Anti-semite
And very dangerous
So
I think Alex might be in
At least at this point
His career
Earlier
Yeah that's who is ahead of that
Mercenary group
Blackwater Erik Prince
That sounds like
Something that he masturbate
Like bij if he wasn't at that meeting
Like every night.
Dream-come-true rarefied air
Considered himself actually I found
Father
Sodalicious
Situation where they at
Inside of things
But make no mistake
The materials are distributed included a ton of white supremacist publication
Work by Holocaust deniers
And plentiful articles referring to Judaism
Movie quote synagogue of Satan
It was a committed member of Aryan Nation
Before starting to downplay that part of his life most likely as part of the message
Rocky Mountain rendezvous
In order to win people over to our side
We have to pretend we're not racing
Turn of events
For 2006
His brother kicked him out because he had cheated on his wife
Which life started to organization called the Coalition for men's rights
Which is basically a support group for men who had restraining orders against them for abusing their wives
He was kicked out of the group for cheating on his own one his own
Immoral
The leadership of the Maury show
No do I get from the pronoun
We started this
Attract
Of where the hustle goes
Price you guys are awful
Shortwave radio in early
Boards on the internet
Let them know about the noble get their oppressive federal government
T95 article in the guardian
In speech after speech Basu dire warnings of
The coming threat
5 days before purchasing a gun
The 1994 ban on limited number of assault weapon
The leaders urged Their audience to read the writing on the wall
People control
According to the militia it's all part of a wider and undeniable trend
The government is now at war with the people
Weatherby excessive
Do taxes
Expanding regulation or plant national identity card
Washington is constructing the apparatus of
Alex Jones May as well
Those beaches
That is his
World Series 1 million
Derail the militia
Community in no small part because he wasn't a body made of exactly what the
But as soon as he actually
And blaming everyone else
Intoxicants
Blaming the Japanese
As retaliation
Another terrorist attack the casting of the subway
Conspiracy theory was
Beebe so
He was forced out of his own group
He was he was kicked out of the Michigan militia
Because he was
Forever Pets
Real dumb
Somewhat but it also was indicative of the level of identity crisis
This world
The world
The real face of
When was about it been revealed
Although the attendees of Rocky Mountain rendezvous
So hard to conceal it
And that's recruitment went on the decline
But of course
The ones who did come around after that play
Radical than the recruits have been previously thought that McVay was
That these guys were betraying their eyes
Ideals
And the ones that suck around the ones were like yeah McVeigh was absolutely right on
So of course we're not going
Or they're the ones
Internalized
It's all fake
This is the point where I get I'm getting a little bit
Maybe I'm drawing connect
That
Might be a little bit
I'm not entirely sure
This is a woefully simplistic and CliffsNotes version of the story when you look at the Players he look at the motivations you look at
Connections
I find it hard not to come away with one very strong
Conclusion
In the early nineties the militia is Montana in the Michigan militia exist
Symbiotics state
Radicalized
Immediately shortwave radio what-have-you
The Michigan game
Alex Jones is clearly at least a spiritual extension of the militia of Montana
Has he has a medium out
It spreads the narratives propaganda
Towards that paramilitary group that will give them the training
That they need
To become
Dangerous
So who's the Michigan militia
In this equation
The guy who started the toy shop
But the question is a little bit more complicated
Then just saying
Or whatever
Do the Rocky Mount Rendezvous happened in 1990
82 is before the election
The militias did not officially begin their organization until mid 1990
3in Turley 1994 election of Bill Clinton
The first Democratic president
If you take Carter out of the equation Clinton was the first Democratic president since LBJ
And the Civil Rights Act
The rise of malicious
We fight against
Further expansion
Human rights
Non-whites
As it was about anything else
But they were too hard
And they were too fast
And they overplay their hand
Exact whether or not it's about to do that
They
What
After the bombing of the Murrah building
Militia Act
It hurt their ability to do much more than Purdue
News propaganda
The Montana militia Alex Pepsi a burning
Until the time was
In 2008 Barack Obama was elected in the same way that the militias organized
Met up to plan their strategies
Estes Park back in 1992
Literally 2009-13
Far-right weirdos plan to Summit on Jekyll Island
Georgia
To plan their next moves
In their struggle against
A democratic been elected
The time was right
Deformed
I don't think there's a coincidence
I really don't
Because I think the way you have with these groups as when there's a republican in office
They know that whatever they care about isn't going to be infringed upon
Window discourse becomes so much closer to what they're into
Why not just engaged
Did the Civil process
Right or at least back
Bush was in office
Why not try and run for office or why not try and deal with this through legislation
Has President we don't have it
Sympathetic
So we're going to have to use
Right
Jekyll Island meeting was organized by Alex Jones is Bob Schultz of the we are we the people Foundation
It was gorgonize by another of Alex's get Edwin Sierra
Another person who was there with Eric cutting
Representative of the oak
The group in which Alex finally found
The Michigan militia
To his militia of Montana
The Jekyll Island meeting involved to radicalize town hall
That were being held around
Perfect opportunity for recruitment
Something to Alex and his oathkeeper buddies to Rhodes of opened
The meeting also involved learning
From the lessons of the past
Timothy McVeigh screw things up for the militias for a long time
The force them into a position where they had to
Construct elaborate
The Pretenders attack wasn't
Exactly what they wanted
Does it happen
But the problem is they also provided
With an
Did benefit
Because they spent years insisted the OKC bombing was
Conspiracy
They've created a built-in.
Sprint
Future events
It could be that could derail their move
When one of their members would inevitably take
Antigovernment message seriously
They had a built-in
To say that it's
The globalist trying to make us look
I think that's where we find ourselves
In 2012
Have some of this
Explains a good bit of Alex's
Operation
And how
In French
And a lot of this militia history
I'm seeing himself as a part of
Yeah but I also think
You such a
That like obviously
He doesn't explain every
No I don't know
But he's pulling these negative
But I think that this is
Is a huge one
And I think
I think on some level it goes back to
The beginning of his
Is it possible that these organs
Innovations
That works
We theorize in and all that stuff
About
Some kind of dark
Is it possible that
These organizations are the ones that
Al profit
It seems unlikely I think probably
Maybe provided a support
Network early on
Those communities
Another voice
Of their side
Material support
But like Alex only got on the air
A lot of
The Montana
Both lost a lot of their
Oh I mean like as time has gone on
No Keepers start coming in together like
This is it this is starting
To be a group
Tribunal throw around money
Where they started
Let's get involved about
The first time
April
I hate like
Talk about
A blogspot
Keepers he didn't even have like a normal website
URL
I don't know
This is the
The part of it that I think is
For Alex
The part that I like
I think whatever nefarious in
Influence there could be
I don't think it is anything
I think this is
This is closest to where Alex Hart
Really like
Yeah in some way
Feliway the layers upon layers of onions
He's like the guy who
Wants to
Dress up
Play actors Soldier
And 100%
Is
Surrounded by fascist surrounded by biggest
Nauseated
People
And does he
Damnedest
To make sure that
Pretend that they're not those things in order to keep
I don't know there's a lot more gear
And I think we're only just
Now starting
Into Summer
Glimpses
Of Alex's militia leaning
And one of the reason
For that is I think it's probably a
Of his show in the era that we don't have
Archives
Yeah like I think if we went back
I mean we have
Just a small glimpse
Of stuff from the 90s and Clint is him thoroughly saying we are the ones with the leaderless resistance
In the mid-90s
Soleil
Did did
That I have
My working
Is a lot of episodes
We can't find
Would probably be
Very deeply
Stoked
In malicious.
Fleet like a lot of those gas
From that world
We're probably stick
Pictures of your show back then
And now it's not so much
He's grown
Evolved
And now we have in the wake of
Sandy Hook
Do you have
I mean not that it wasn't
Do you have Larry Pratt
On twice
In the week after Sandy Hook
What was at the f****** Rocky
Rendezvous
In the same week
Stewart Road
Twice
The Oath Keepers guy who is
Whether you like it or not
Essentially an equivalent to the Michigan weather
Because if you really look at it let me what do you have you have a bunch of people
From The Oath Keepers who
Baby it's not with your
Malaysian is about but there's a
I can come up off the top of my head with the least five people try to plan terrorist attacks
I think I had to
Both at least
Their parallels that are very important
They're real
Do you have these guests three rhymes
Sprite do you have these guests
Gun
Supporting weirdos
But there's more to it
And then now we have on January 2nd as Alex
Cuz pivoted away
From it being about Sandy Hook
And now it's about.
Exactly
Ideas that these militias were
We're putting out
In the 90s
You know this idea that the government's coming to take your guns and there's going to be a civil war
This is very much what
The militias were saying it after ruby red
So of course what is he do he has one of the
The f****** man guide
From the Montana militia
Doesn't bring up that he was one of the leaders of the militia of Montana
That was a whistleblower
When none of that
But what is
Is in the aftermath of Oklahoma City
Bob Fletcher
This guy who has Alex has on his show
You know what his comment was
There's a tenth planet
Nibiru
Get ready for more bombs
Okay
Cuckoo cuckoo
So I think
Discards a little
And maybe I'm making a mountain out of a molehill
And I
Might be a hill Mountain
Situation
If you look at this I don't see any way to escape
The fact that
The influences of Alex are all
Present
In
The early parts
Of the militia movement in the early 90s
That was
Inescapably big
The things in the messages that they had white washed and put out into the world
Are very
Consistently repeated analysis world
And then guest
Who are
From that work like that literal meaning
And then from the things
It grew out of that meeting
All there
And if
It it
Hates a leaderless resistance
Alex
Cuz you can't 100% time to each other but
We need those tapes
We need to find those old episodes
I think there's a
Treasure Trove like things he doesn't want people
Do I bet
Especially the time he told the story about the first time I did p***
Viagra
I'll call myself out a tiny bit
Analysis
Because I think it is kind of overly
Simplistic to be like
Demolition of Montana in Michigan
Operated as like one wasn't
Information on Military
Because there were other militias around 2
I just look at it
If you have
If you want a successful operation
You need to have those
Two things bsep
From each other
Yet working
Together of the people who are being trained
In
Military tactic
Putting out
Tropicana
You need to be on the same
Page but you cannot be related
You can't be the same thing
Because
Let's say one of these guys goes and shoots up something
Then
You jeopardize your propaganda
Outlet
Do you know
I'm separated
And I think
Yeah I agree
There are very very clear parallels right yet
History doesn't repeat it rhymes
Like this
This
Explosion of
White nationalist
Militias and
Murderers and all that s***
It
It wouldn't be as
Often
I don't think
I could be wrong but it would
We wouldn't see as much
Violence
If there weren't
Some sort of
Concerted ideology
That ties all of these
And we wouldn't be and we would be able to do more if they had actual
Physical connection
Organizations
That were doing
I don't know let's play
In his.
Benny's garage
You know when that happened
Like
Right
What an essential piece of
How things key
Keep moving forward is Alex
It's on Aaron says
Did this is a false flag and the government report comes out
That's a real threat
It's not really a big threat to Alex
In his operation or anything like that
Is a big threat to them
To not be
Connected to them
Lead
Some sort of charge
To get that
Redacted
So which is why
Even though there's
Consequences for
That's troubling
Not great
A little bit later the episodes
Calls
Alex gets a call from a guy
Who
How many
If I hear
This guy I think
Jesus
I don't know how much
Literally
But he's scary
And he confronts Alex about
I was that girl from Cairo near police
Call Alex
Privilege
Yes I just wanted to let you know that I've been speaking with you for over to listening to your program for over 2 years now
And nobody has ever called in
Tell you what I'm going to tell you right now
There are secret sleep sleeper cells
All over the country
That are ready and willing
Take charge of the situation
And I'm not talkin about kicking people's doors in
Alright
Let's be
Clear
If you talkin about
That he
His buddies were involved in
Yeah
But I'm not talking about kicking doors in
Organizing Macy's style parade
That's already but also notice
The people that I hang out with
Call ex-military
I spent 20 years in the Navy
And I know that I
The only thing that bothers me sir about you
Is that you were never in the military
So you never swore an oath to the car
And I have my doubts about you being a DOD plant
And I want you right now to your worldwide audience
Tell everybody
That you are
Real
Because you offer
You talk a lot but you don't really offer any solution
And I'm an action person
About Solutions
Earlier
Now you're calling in
The Constitution.
Who is that Alex is like you're just calling
More than two
At least
Callers Play Hold On
I have set
Instead things that Alex like right right
Questioning this guy in anyway because he
No
This is how you play with him
And everything goes fine
You get out of pocket and he will actually
Respond to whatever you're saying
Like a normal human being
Which is
I don't know who the f*** you are
Stop process though
If he were a DOD plant
I believe he would have had to swear an oath to
To work for the defense department
I'm pretty sure that no matter which side that guys landed on
He would have had to swear
The only way
Susan isn't he's fine
That's it
I'm not sure exact
Where is the
All the time
Usually when he's coming
So a little bit of a wrench
And now expenses Wheels quite a bit
One of those callers have called him out
And he forgot to hit the
Person on Earth
It didn't
Interpersonally
He doesn't
Let's just move on
I'm totally fine
You can't hurt my feelings Ivan
What Solutions have I
Also going on where
Alex's responses like okay good I'm bad
Pallet
Like
It wasn't even
It was a conditional
Sword of judgment
You didn't serve the army
Defend the Constitution
Hey man
I love you I support you all you need
To do is
Swear an oath right now
And we're all on your team
Is reluctance
To do things like that people can
Confront like I watched the whole thing
That they want a lot
Saying that you didn't marry her brother
Right
That's a
These were trying to set some sort of a trap that like
Or not they're going to make a big deal out of whatever you do
That's not what this guy was doing
If Alex has said I understand I haven't served in the armed forces I wish I would have
Have done everything might like to uphold
Dude
If he doesn't
Text now
Say where you wanted to hit
Maybe
But
Salute you were on your side or something like that
They're not going to be bummed out to
Figure Alex velluto
The Constitution
It's not a trap
If there's no trap here but Alex is so defensive and weird
That because this guy is
Critiquing the possibility
That he isn't
He wrote that he presents himself
He's got to respond
Thank you f***** up
I think it's
The guy question Alex's manhood
And Alex's
Like the way
Text military we all swore notes sleeper cells
And that's where Alex is like
F*** you you think you're great
Maybe
There may be some masculine
Piece 280 I think it's more about love
Douching
There might be
Much like Lennie in the B
That metaphors pretty appropriate
I think maybe there's a subconscious liver that's about that
Masculinity
But I think it's
Do more like
Loyalty
Country and how dare anyone
Impune
Whatever answer Alex
Swearing an oath to the Constitution
He's done that a thousand times
That's true in the phone
Tell me that you love the constitutionalist
FaceTime me bro
Hello
So
Things that make people like that last call
Who is in a terrorist cell
Activated
Great-uncle
What
Is it
No other people
Around
Not to split hairs
From knowing a lot of the criticism
About Alex
And Eve
Communities online is message boards
One of the issues
Only talked about having family
And stuff like that
Constantly talks about family being in CIA and s*** like that
Vaguely referencing
Paranoid
Real militia types
Like
The people who are
The descendants of the Michigan militia
They are
Suspicious of people like who have familial ties
The intelligent organization
That vase t as part of the enemy part of was trying to
Infiltrate
They are like I have a great uncle cousin who
Covert Ops
And I don't
If the CIA told him to go deal drugs
And kill people in Chicago
Dead
Right
Bright there's no way you're walking away from
Disruptive inverter a bunch
Two people
Just sign you don't want to sign
P***
That's what that's what's being expressed by that caller ID
Only a little bit later in the show
Alex manifest exactly why
The hardest core
Folk don't
I wouldn't
If you were operating in a splinter cell or you imagine
Do you spell there's a problem
Mexico plays the last one from this episode
Alex
Nation.com
They are trying to move on
We can back them off again that's how I look
If we get the word out
We can
When this ago
That's not what they did in
They didn't get the word out
What Bob Fletcher was involved
You could make a decent argument that the militia of Montana was less
Violently oriented
And that's probably why Alex would have Bob Fletcher on
As opposed to
Someone from the Michigan
Or something like that
I could understand his
More
More comfort
With someone who wears uniform as opposed to
But make no mistake about it all of it grew out of
The Rocky Mountain Rendezvous that was
Lousy with Nazis
Ariens White supremacists
And people who
Wanted to blow up like so
When Alex says we need to do is what Bob did in the past
Not
Cool
I was struggling to find a way
What was it like at the globalist
Bob Fletcher is super uncool
Super
Confronted him
Absolution
Absolution is do what Bob did.
Didn't the 90s
Going to end up with
Do we eat
He's going to end up with a national Guardsmen caught with a s*** ton of f****** guns ready to start killing.
Guy from
You're going to end up with all of this stuff
Showing up
Bunch of globalist
The mail
So I just be like
I want to call myself out of tiny
And I think there is so much more
About this this
And I think it'll be probably impossible for us
Bully
The militia movement alexson
The consequences thereof and the parallels between
2009 and 9
B3
It would be something that would be doctorate-level
Lord of the Rings trilogy level of information
Right
But I think some of these things are important to introduce to the conversation
It was that episode about Bill Cooper
Without
You're fully diving in
Introducing
N2r
OurWorld
We're able to
Right
Part of the Arizona
Yeah we take a toad dip because it's what Alex Broughton
Conversation
He has Bob Fletcher on
I don't like
I don't immediately think
Like oh
I know
This guy who is second banana in the militia of Montana
I don't have that encyclopedic
Knowledge
Alex says that he's involved in the Iran-Contra
I started the militia movement
Yeah yeah yeah
You start to fight
These parallel start to be
Clear
You start to think
You start to learn
A little bit more
I already knew about a bit about that
Montana militia
Oh wait
That was started by
Do Estes Park Summit
Who else was there
It's not weird
There's so much
There's just so much
What did he have Bob Fletcher
He specifically have Bob Fletcher
Well that's what I'm saying it suggests to me that Alex
Purposefully gave him the intro of somebody who is involved with Iran Contra
As opposed to giving the man's full credit
Right by which include
It would be super
Suspicious
Himself was probably like
Don't give me your actual intro
He talks over and when he's like I started
Yep
Don't tell anybody
Because generally he would want to be associated with
Which
There's a discomfort with where he stands
Not like in the hierarchy
In terms of where the narrative
In the beginning
Like I don't know if you want
People to realize
That like a lot of
These people that he's talking to
Are who they are
Are there such
Extreme
After this
She starts talking about Nibiru
Fletcher
Fletcher really just started
Strange
Dreams turn for the guy to start the
Modern militia movement and leads
Into the depths of
How many people at this point
A few
It's you then just be like
You know what
I got to reach the top of my profession
I think I'm going to start talking about
10th planet
You're kind of a con person
You just like me
There's nothing left in this well
Let's try
Yeah
Mike cernovich
Pick-up artist
He's dropping off at
Same thing with Mark Dice
Being a memory scam salesman
Pick-up artist who wrote a book about it
Either Satanist everywhere racket
Wrote a book under the suit
The one popular online
Self is Mark Dice
And started going out Alex's show then try to do,
Blankets
It's all like these people are all over the play
There's no disk
Anchor
I'd like to relate to that on some level
I did stand up for a long time
Stop
Like I understand pivoting
Because nothing is soprano
All of your
That's why
I think that's
Psychopathic mine Psychopathic narcissistic mine view of like
Why the f*** I just do this
Get out bright
From time to time with these guys were they like
Yeah I'm just going to write a book about being a pickup artist now with
No
Research note
Nothing no history
I'm not f****** work at all
I'm just going to say a bunch of dumb s*** Big Break
I'm the smartest human being on the
Like that's something you wish you could
Yeah
Solid
Militia of Montana
Was like
You know they were a mail-order kind of operation where they were selling
These DVDs in it
Information
National things
Right
You can make the Alex's spiritually
In terms of trying to monetize
The militia world
Yeah there's like a scam
That didn't
Exist as strongly
If some of those other more militaristic
Right like how the clan was an MLS
Like that whole thing
Is full of thoughts
If any of this pops up going down the road
Here in the beginning of January
How Alex Price
Navigate to
Really treasure
Where is Waterloo
Anaya
Early 20s
Have to do when you're in treacherous water
You got to give it up to the Somali pirate job through it
So I don't know we'll see
But also
Need to find
Episode
I know they're out there
I'll just put the call out
Does anybody have any idea
How to get your hands on
Real old episodes
If that is I swear to God if the last Blockbuster standing
Has all those tapes
We're Road trippin right now
Public Access
And
I think there's got to be copies somewhere but we don't have access
They don't have access
CIA
Who work there probably has copies
I need them
Do you have them let me know
But until another episode this is little bit
I was really hoping nice
Restore our rabbit
It was a bad week
Express
Life stress
But your situation
Has pivoted into a
More stress
Cool but different
And I'm gathering
Really really sit down
Good 5-hour
It just
Arc legs back
Our ability to Traverse treacherous Waters is coming to close
Set an alarm for the ride along
Next week absolutely
That's correct
Crazy
Incubus everybody
Listen
Patreon
But for now
I guess if we look
This not have any winners
I disagree I think there's one
Is Little Richard
The guy who wrote the Larry's a taken out of
Fair enough
Butchered I'm certain his never killed anybody cuz I one guy techno
Probably
Is a gentleman by the name
Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work