Alex
Just a tiny
Arizona
Most people would describe an unhealthy amount
Stream beverage
Yeah
Maybe I don't know your back but it's all signs are pointing
On Saturday
Apartment places
Are closed over the
Weekend but the final like application
Everything went in on Friday
So I'm expecting all your back on Monday
But I have a lot less stress
On that front perfect I appreciate you asking and I'm sure the listener is a very
Interested
On your news front
We can't talk about it
Wanting to know how that story
In your your situation
But
We can't talk about it
Until there's some resin
What's up
Maybe we probably shouldn't
Smarter not to I think so
I'm moving into your new space
Choose what brings you Joy
Videos
Okay
Maybe remove a box
For my room Ono
You've just taken away your own free will
And I'd like to take a moment
Before we get going
Do I get a shout-out
So first
You know I'm bad with names
If I'm just going phonetically it's merging
I can't I don't think that's right I'm sure I mispronouncing it probably Miriam
Honestly I don't know I apologize in advance
Your policy walk
Thank you so much
Dot-dot-dot underscore
I'm a policy wonk
Eeyore dragons thank you so much you are now policy walk
All
Robot
We appreciate it very much
Sojourn
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
Set me a bucket of poop
These guys
Website
Appreciate
Before we get to it there is one more fun thing
We shall do
And that is given
Very special thank you
Who
Novelty beverages to enjoy on this episode
Espresso premium of Premium properties
Going to like it I don't know why
That's delicious
Incredible
That is 2 letters no.
Call Blaine
For an address to send
And unfortunately I'm not at the point where I'm willing
Give out alright
Because yeah I think we're in a position where it's at
But Ian has our address from before when
Play 20 eyes on the show Becker
Yeah and so up everyone I really appreciate the offers of like pieces of Art and stuff like that
And after I move
Inside of a place
Because I really do appreciate it and I think
It's that really cool impulse I don't want
Respect
People's generosity or anything
Today
We are going over the
The day
What is March 15th
Before our time
United States
Previous night
Christchurch
49 people are dead
The results of the
Fired on
People
A couple bosque's
Gauging their Friday prayers
I don't want to get too much
To that story specifically because as a
Is the case
There are developing
Elements of
We know the basics
Certainly
In terms of
Got you know
Did he have accomplished
All the other
I don't think every record this year on Saturday
I don't feel like
We have
Reporting reporting has not been not going to make any claims
Enough to talk
About what's going on
But we don't know enough
To pretend that we're experts
Absolutely not
Alex
T.i.
Well we're in an interesting situation because I know
Rush Limbaugh has already claimed
False flag
Right
With a little bit we're on a
I'm not sure if
He is a committed
Holy
To that line
Assume that we're in a situation where Alex is going to be
Oh God no
He might be getting sued more goddamn
Legally actionable
Probably
2 scale
It's worse than whatever Rush Limbaugh said
Couldn't you have learned
Nope cuz pathological
Alex starts to show on what I would describe as a rocky footing
This is not good
The show start
The music plays for about a minute a whole minute and Alex comes running into
Restart when it's normal
Comes in
Real power
Whatever
2000 plus years ago
Okay
Launch new movements or revolutions
Butchering Sharon body
Okay see you little bit
I mean I don't think he's being very subtle
F****** rock
Do you start
He's trying to imply that the globalist like to launch these false flags on March 15th
I guess yeah
From the beginning who knows
One of the main problems with pretty much
We have enough recorded history enough a really wild s*** that's happened could absolutely
Conspiracy out of just about any date
I imagine the fake terrorist attack happening on May 23rd a random random number generator
And now I will pretend to be alexcraft
The speculation about this terrorist attack
On May 23rd
Globus love to attack Crescent about May 23rd because it's
Mirror
The only one who can defeat the Muslims
Why do you think creating a false flag Pizza in Northern Ireland
Started with the first few world
34 on the real life Bonnie and Clyde by the globalist police
A they were free for all those strong armed robberies and murders
Well this is all good fun
But the way I imagined it going is that I come up with a random date
Pretend that there'd been a terrorist attack on that day
Unfortunately I don't think that game is even possible to
Play
On May 23rd 2014 Elliot Rodger killed six people in a murder spree their Isla Vista California motivated by
Feelings of rejection
By women he found attractive
You go on to become a meme in a bit of a hero to the online world
I promise you I didn't cheat like a date
And just work backwards from this
I chose a random date to make a joke
Out of this
Inevitably you fine
You know
Terrorist attack that is real on
We should probably think about that
It's a it was a grim.
Also important point the Manson family murders in 1969 happened on the night of August 8th
And nights
And it literally nothing to do with you guys
Alec has no idea what he's talking about just connect
Completely unrelated things together
He doesn't care about doing good job you didn't care about having any information
All he cares about is justify and white terrorism
Private Muslim victims
Attack any empathy
Human decency
He's a complete monster
Anytime in space
30 seconds of starting a
Yeah you got out strong
Restrained reporting make sure that we have all the facts
And then he literally says we don't want to be sued
Let's not do it
Let's knock
He says that to everybody in the office
No you don't do any of that stuff
You were you're pointing out the first-of-its-kind
This is a false flag
And all that s***
Jesus
Sedative
But okay that's good is a false flag
Investigate
Shooting
More than 20 years ago
Semi-auto and then
Single-shot shotguns and rifles
Special licenses
That doesn't sound right newzealand
You take everyone's gone
And it's important to investigate all the angles of this current issue
Is really rough position to be
To be honest like it's really not good if it's as if this is where he's coming from
There's a bad starting position
There were the gun laws in New Zealand are incredibly Lacks
That's one problem that we're going to get to
My first point in a bad bad start here
Is that nothing Alex has done or does about a mass shooting or even a complete
Could rightly be called investigator
All he does is obscure things
Anything other than blindly embarrassingly covering of white terrorism
Disgusting
Secondly they didn't want to rightly pointed out
Making s*** up about gun laws
Which will see a demonstration of later in this episode
The legal actions he's talking about happened in 1990
Me too
Altitude was really a greater registration requirements for gun owners
Among the changes were adding
Requiring that license holders reapply after 10 years
Making it so only licensed gun owners
The amendment also created a new category of gun from a legal standpoint
That was a military-style semi-automatic
At all
Making that up
Yeah that sounds right
Thirdly and most importantly
This wasn't the result of a stage 2
This is a response to be very real arawana Massacre
That took place on November 13th and 14th night
It all started when local a****** David Greg with his neighbor allegedly about the guy's dog being too loud
By arguing gray went over to the guy's house and shot him multiple times with semi-automatic rifle
The neighbors 2 daughters were in the house along with the daughter of the neighbors girlfriend
Gray found one of the girls named Chiquita age 9
And shot her in the chest
She would survive but the other two young girls who he found later
I'm shot died on the spot
Griffin set the house on fire
The girlfriend's daughter was in the house was shot at
Approach the situation
The help
People who stopped their cars to try and help
With what they thought was just a burning house we're fired on
He killed more kids will happen just be out on the street
One of them was out looking for his lost dog
This all led to a standoff with which ended with him being shot by the police the next day after he charged out of the house
Magellan
F****** kill me you bastards
You didn't actually die immediately
Turn off successfully killing him
He will get his wish though and he died from his wounds
Before arriving
Hospital
When was all said and done grade killed 13 people for 11 years old or younger
One of them was a police sergeant
This wasn't a false flag this wasn't a staged event
This was the destruction of many many people's lives
At the hands of one man with a bunch of
And just because they should so stupid is a globalist
Did like somehow plan this arm Awana Massacre just to grab everyone's gone
Why the fuk didn't they do the second part of the plan
Why are they so competent about the part of this with a pull off elaborate Act of terrorism in order to steal people's gone
But they can't f****** finish Step 2
It's impressively shity
Did Alex to be working today
Deprive people of their grief
Inability to heal in the present
While still having time to be complete
Inhuman monster
People who lost their loved ones
29 years ago
He is so bad
This is so bad
This episode
He sucks
At your Plex faith not
I believe I'm really frustrated with this guy today I'll be honest with you
I don't know I might end up a little bit on the nose
Brutal
That's f****** brutal
I don't know about
Right lying about a guy who for no reason other than he was mad at his neighbor
Ended up killing
Four children and nine other people
Over a two-day Massacre
It's f***** up
He's allowed to lie about
No one thinks that was a false flag
Except Alex
Swag
Didn't happen
You just making that part up
Sorry I'm a bit
I'm trying to I mean I'm still trying to put together my
My feelings on
Everything that's going on right now and I'm
I'm trying to avoid
The the biggest trap
But like
To sensitize
Like I'm decent
Like I just
I don't even know how to process this is a
The tragedy
That much anymore
Become
So commonplace
And I don't know how to process rape
Because it's
Become
So wrote
It's almost like he's not even
He's not even performing
He's just reading a script from the last
White terrorist attack
Which was probably yesterday
I honestly think there are some differences
The end
I
I know what you mean
And it's really it's really hard to fight back
Against that
Complacency
Normalizing
Horror
That is such a part of Modern Life
You bought
You have to fight
Absolutely
But I am I'm not
As a prescriptive thing
Like we have to
Force ourselves
You feel
Anu
If you don't
You you minimize
The reality of what's going on in the world
That makes things easier
For people like Alex
Play their game
Alex Britt start to talk
About the manifesto
This guy
Right there's some issues this
Then we'll talk about some of that
On the other side of the
Clip but
Here is how Alex decide
To start covering
That
Newswars.com
Praises coming
Call short
Socialism
Find Candace Owen
By praising them
So
There's something really weird going on with his terrorist Manifesto
Doesn't pick up on for almost the entirety of the
The show while he's talking about it
Towards the end Harrison Smith comes in
And he's trying to warn Alex that there's a lot of Fortune 8chan type
Trolling stop
In the text of it
Emory's be careful about like
What things actually need water inside
Alex has no
That stuff
And just keep barreling forward with the
Position
I think even shut off.
In the middle I don't know exactly
Harrison's in the middle of a sentence
Oh boy
I'm not entirely sure
Be straightforward argument
Being nice
But other parts
The corners of the internet that we don't live in
Like trapped
People to report on which media coverage of
Robert Evans Road
Explain this better than I can
But I recommend that everyone
Very well.
I do want to point out that this is an impressively unfair acts for Alex
Claim it this Manifesto is pro China and socialism
Because it says positive things about them
I've been in the same breath claim that is anti Candace Owens and Pewdiepie because it says positive
Things about them
This is very literally doublespeak
What else is doing
For two conflicting
Sausage with audiences head at the same time
And it's an abusive Act
If positive things being said about someone in a terrorist Manifesto
Either mean that
He's very into those things
Who was the Beast demonizing them by association
Then the only truth that remains
Is that only Alex's judgment can be trusted
Anyone attempting to cover reality would never behave like
It's the exclusive action of a propaganda
And given the
Constanta
It's an activist
Cruelty towards
I read over most of the manifesto of what I come away from it is this isn't even close to us
The power with what I expect out of a man
It's not like a brother
Manifest content
But wasn't
You're almost to a fault
He's very clear about what he was doing and how others could do what he did to
Included excerpts from his diary
Jarringly up
This Manifesto is clearly someone who has inspired in a big way by brevik
But is also someone who's lived on online World 8:02
And that online Manor
Communicating
From time to time
And those insincere Trolli aspects of the manifesto make it
Very difficult to assess tone
Even the parts
Entirely sincere and literal
That said if Alex wants to cherry-pick lines but
Ecofascism and liking
China that sword Cuts both directions
For example the Coast Guard terrorist
Liberalist globalist ideology
Especially White
Which is basically a guiding principle
Editorial
Infowars editorial Department
Such a thing even exists
The title of the current terrorist Manifesto was the great replacement
Which is a reference to the white genocide almost all of Alex's reporting
All the time nationalist South
All the times he's gal'd about the dangers
Is a variable birthrates a demographic
The cliff Alex's deep
Deeply invested in the Great
Replacement narrative that is the title of this guy's Manifesto
I'm not saying anything other than the games
You playing isn't
It goes both directions
I think it's absolutely had blood on his hands
This attack anyway because of anything I read Manifesto
Discounted most of that document
Is being unreliable narration
Alex has blood on his hands
Constant irresponsible excessive and disgusting demonization of Islam that he carries out in the way
Perpetuates the idea
That there is no moderate
Alex's blood on his hands
For the way that he incessantly called immigrants and Muslims Invaders
Alex's blood on his hands for normalizing
Existential fear it is dumb listen
The information ecosystem that he's a part of its not okay
And attacks like this are the natural fruit of that ecosystem
Alex has blood on his hands
And we focus on him
Cuz the show is about him but he's far from the only one
Ignore the dump manifest overtaking cautiously with a grain of salt because ultimately it doesn't matter
Doing everything in their power to insist that Muslims are incompatible with freedom
And white people
Everyone from Sam Harris
Ben Shapiro
Tucker and Bill Maher
From every dumb f*** with a struggling YouTube goddamn present
I think Islam hates us
There's something there that is a tremendous hatred there
We can't allow people coming into this country we have this hatred of the United States
And the people who are not Muslim
When you ask yourself what happened here the answer is really simple
Just get another person who took right
If you believe the words
Zippy's monster say
I think it's only a matter of time until there's too many of them to stop them from dominating white people
Killing Muslims is one of the
Predictable outcome
And there's literally no chance I would ever believe
50 islamophobic media chorus doesn't understand that fully
This attack was a natural endpoint of that rhetoric
It's been allowed to
Metastasize
It's eggs are not going to get better until that is a
Very seriously
Frankly
Very honest
Very
People need to understand
The parts of this
They are complicit
I take it you're a humble
Fearless moral inventory
Centauri
I don't think
That a lot of people
Specifically the people I just named
To do that
And therefore they will continue to
Part of the
The process that feeds
And that is nothing to do
I don't give a s***
Do with the world we live in
There's a little
Denim
My mother
I'm in a mood
People people come to me for yelling but today you're all about it
I'm I'm good
Got a lot of
So
Alex isn't doing good today now I doubt it
I started going through this episode I have
Of note about like
Points that he's making
Anime
I'll go f*** yourself Alex
MMA
3 hours later I realized
3 minutes
Episode
That's not good
Call bad
Anita's
Is unfair
The idea
What are you trying to do with
He's pro-china but
Because you praise both of them
Play abusive
That made me want to lose my mind I don't know how you can
Because what he's trying to say there is he's trying to say that
The manifesto
Right wing
Figures right because the only
Is if you was also attacking right-wing fig
Right so in the manifesto raises all of this stuff because
Love
And he has to say that
He's praising right-wingers
As part of the plot
Otherwise so he's going to be like exactly
Meanwhile everybody
I took any time
Like really look at it
Understand
Contacts
The came out in
You get aftermath
Yes talks about the being radicalized by Candace Owens but it's
Clearly a joke
Yeah like everyone who was a
The joke
Trying to make some
The defensive propagandist
Or the overzealous over
Eager presumably
People on the left who want to attack him
Like whatever it is is exactly
An instance of the
The thing that is in that Manifesto as
And it played out exactly how it probably was supposed to
Yeah pretty much so there are these sorts of things where I
I don't care to engage with most of the
The text
Lest we
Possibly fall into
Trap like that
I would rather look at the larger contacts
And the parts of
Absolutely
Arson
I really don't care about manifestos except as a
Learning tool
To anyone matters
Is that you
This is what you want exactly
The real
Text means nothing
Because we know why you did it
Because of what you did
I don't give a s*** about the Unabomber Manifesto
The only thing is
What do we need
To do to keep people like you from
What is the environment later understanding
The text
What's wrong
You don't get any credibility
Then a f****** self-published Amazon author just because you
You kill people
Reading Anders Breivik
Manifesto in 2011 probably wouldn't have been
Deeply affected
As it was when I read it for a podcast
6 months ago
And the reason wasn't because of what he
He was saying it was because we now live in a world where you feel
How's that manifest exactly clearly motivated
The manifesto that came out 78 years ago
You probably be very
Pesto from present day
Deeply affecting
Because I would see
The Shockwave
Specifically by him
You can very clearly see
That he was inspired by a
A project
You're only provide
Fighting more space for the people who are not going to listen to you say
Look at how bad this is
Says they're going to read it inside
Who gives a s*** about what he has to say
I don't think it's
I don't think it's the right thing to do
Is appropriate
Assume that
Gospel
That's one of the things I don't try
Absolutely
Trip over their own tickets
The documentarian 20 years from now combing through the through the manifesto and
Doing a whole like
Post-mortem on life in general through this manifest
I don't want anybody talking about it right now cuz
It's just pointless
But not a ton
Because I don't
Uses something
Ann Arbor contacts
Profound from
The manifestor
About who he thinks
I don't know all the
In the shooting video
Internet
That's a boy
Coming up the TV
What the f*** are you doing
He's a weird leftist
Ecofash
His words
Exactly
Mosteiros described himself as an Eco fascist
Call Joseph quotes
Manifesto
Make you laugh
I mean he's a fascist
Texiko however you want to take
Presumably
Admirers
Because they are because they're currently
Well no not just that
They're currently holding
Muslims in
Concentration
They're doing this concurrently
With this guy hundreds of thousands of people disappear
Right right
Piece of his support of China or
I think it's probably more from the context clues up
Right
It's boards
Just the idea.
Country for Chinese people
As opposed to
Open Annex
Alex wants
It says like
Yeah course the globalist love China this guy loves giant liberal
Do you like to eat
Costa
You know what some f****** people on the far right also really like
Fries
The moment he's like
Weird leftist
You can just say what you want
That means
In the same way if I say
Nationalist terrorist
Coronavirus
My instincts say okay
But that's the wrong answer
Take left and right out of this
This is a
Network
This is a concerted effort
People
Who are white
I think you can't take that lesson right out of
Because they're closed
Honky definition
Now that's sort of thing because I think you get caught up in too much of the minutiae
And people are able to
You crafty Dodges in order to get around
The guy in the manifesto
Hates conservative
Biggest conservatism
Corporatist
Because of other reasons
You talk about
Box
It's a mess and this is one of the
The issues that like
It's impossible to mail anything down
Who knows how much
So it's best
Engaged
Watch outside
Just
Alex
Is trying to prepare
That's about all we can do
If we can't nail down any larger conclusion
About his word
One thing
Frustrates me so much
I don't understand
What they would think if it works
To go the other way
Do you know what I mean
Not exactly like
How many terrorist event
Have we had this f******
Already this year
Right
What if we had the same cluster of
I don't know any difference
What day event how many before they would start saying wait let's
Start limiting guns
Let themselves die over and over again they would just want a war right
I don't know
I'm not entirely sure but
Application of
Attack
That
Done
Themselves
Conversation
They create the world
Idea
Grayslake
Them
Complicit in helping absolutely
Text there we go
But when it's a Muslim
Shooting people
Akbar
Frustration
Control Islam
Practitioner
Hernandez being reported
They call it a good Revolution
Clip is really revealing
We've always known that Alex thinks that Islam is all one does something bad
Expect a conversation
Be about how Islam is
He's always disappointed that's not enough
People having a conversation
That's what he's describing is my big frustration
You never understand
The people who are saying
This wasn't
The people like you
We told you almost ones are evil
He doesn't understand
Have to defend
The entirety of Islam
If propagandist an anti-islam forces
Trying to attack
It's the Fox News
When it comes to White
Be able to see the difference between criticism of white supremacy
Nyt
That's troubling
It's almost like the default position for white people it's just never
Expressed almost does feel like that's a late belief that he has fit colors
He relates to this stuff
Also a recent study published in Justice quarterly found that attacks carried out by Muslim
Receive on average 357% more media coverage
Then those committed by other group
The study found quote out of 136 Terror attacks in the United States
Muslim committed on average 12.5% of the attacks get received
More than half
Of the news cap
White terrorist conversely received
Proportionately little mediator
Because of this disproportional coverage many people are duped into thickness
The far greater threat to them
When in reality this is far from the
People like Alex Jones serve to make that Gap in perception
Versus reality
And ideally they want to make it so wide that it's impossible for that Gap ever to be bridged
Leaving you with no other answer than to take matters into your own hands
It's really hard to look at the reporting that Alex is doing
Today
In the circumstances that the world is
Anak think
But he's trying to
It really is
The way he's behaving
When the reality is so very clear
Absolutely
Your move there though is
What he saying
Is
I don't think it's okay
Have a white supremacist
Terrorist attack
But what about other terrorists
Seaweed
So we shouldn't do anything about the white supremacist
And only focus on the ones in Egypt or whatever
The whataboutism there
Is just too
A posture in action toward the
Inciting event
Don't deal with white supremacist
Call El white man white man white man
What are we thinking about drugs
What about this
Don't worry about it
Never deal with the problem at hand
Well
Guess what
What about everything and every further action is going to be that problem and it
It's never going to be white
Supremacist
Terror
Has Alex
Like going to church
If your argument about why people should be upset about a shooting in a mosque
Is that Isis attacked churches
You are playing from behind
Your argument is terrible
And here's a big reason why
Eustis is a terrorist group
And they're treated like one
Our country is literally at war with them
So if you want to justify a white nationalist shooting up a mosque
The only real way
Avoid sounding like a fuking idiot
Is a white nationalist
Constitutive legitimate terrorism problem
Except
Be treated this.
Otherwise
So f****** stupid conversation you're trying to have
Also I said find a church in the Philippines
In January this year
20 people
But it didn't happen on Easter
Last Easter ISIS attack of Church of Pakistan
And for people workout
These attacks are awful but it's just a blip in the news
Mainstream media Outlets covered both of us
Interesting Lee a search of Infowars archives actually fails to turn up stories but either of those attacks
But a simple Google search brings up stories
From The New York Times about both
So really I'm not sure what point Alex is trying to illustrate out here other than he's a f****** idiot needs a job
Define irony for everybody in
Did you cover it
Wars is faulty
Whatever what the f*** ever
I'm certain that those attacks were like mentioned in some like
Larger article about something else like in paragraph 20 or whatever
Nothing
It's all bulshit
You babe
Like we were just sort of talking about
Making fun of the idea of a little bit ago
The idea here is to
Deal with the fact
This is white supremacist white nationalist
Has been a problem for a while and it's rearing its head Missouri
Shocking
The awful way
Again
Texas
To describe it as terrorism
And that's what I think because
Does open up that idea that we
In the same way we treat other terrorist organization
Trying to disrupt their
Communication
Filtrate
How to figure out how they operate
I'm figuring out ways
To neutralize social media platform
All that stuff
He doesn't want
That conversation to start
So he
He calls them
That's bees
This was a crazy guy
You said that Miss next clip
Migos down
A road that I'm
So fucken glad
This guy was a crazy person
Muslim groups decrying Islamic Terror attacks on Christians and others
F*** you
Truck attack in Nice France in 2016
Released a statement such ugly crimes are corrupt of the Earth
And follow in the footsteps of Satan
Cursed out in this life after
After that attack the Arab League chief
And called it an act of terrorism
Do United Arab Emirates foreign minister Sheikh Abdullah bin Zayed Al nahyan
I'm not yet said
Terrorist
Crime makes it imperative for all to work decisively and without hesitation
The counterterrorism
All its form
And manifestations
Clubs in Orlando
That was at a gay club there's no way Muslims would speak out against that
According to Alex
Najee toward from the Council of american-islamic relations said quote we condemn it in the strongest possible terms
It violates our principles of American
I have a word for Isis and their supporters you did not speak for us you do not represent us you were an aberration
Afghan president Ashraf ghani
The quote I unequivocally condemn the horrific attack on Orlando Florida
Nothing can justify killing of
Bangladeshi prime minister Sheikh Hassan
Who's one of the female Muslims in elected office that Alex pretends don't exist
I condemn this dastardly Act
To tear in the strongest pop
Apple term and reiterate my government's zero-tolerance policy again
Any form
Terrorism and violence
London mayor Sadiq Khan said quote this heinous and cowardly act impact on LGB
Key people in Orlando
Is an attack on our freedoms and values We Stand shoulder to shoulder with the people of Orlando
Hey what about that
There's no way Muslims looking down that right
They should all be for it because it was that you know about the drama mohabbat know that
Muslim Cadet that attack
The Council on american-islamic relations
Statements quotes
We strongly condemn this brutal and cowardly attack and reiterate our repudiation of any such a salt on freedom of speech
Even speech that mocks faith
And religious figures
The proper response to such attacks on the freedoms we hold dear is not to vilify any faith
But instead to marginalize extremists of all backgrounds
Who seek to stifle freedom
Extra created wine social
The Arab League Chief Nabil al-arabi
Terrorist attack on Charlie have those newspaper in Paris
I could literally do this all day
Impart consider doing exactly
Just going through every major terrorist attacks committed by Muslims
A listing of condemnation after condemnation
Influential Muslim
Islamic organizations around the world
But ultimately
I realize there wasn't much point
The perception exists that Muslims are speaking
The contrary is going to change his mind
Has been closed off by Propaganda
However their two important points
Need to be Broad
The first is that it's a little insulting that so many people seem to insist on making Muslims apologize for and denounce things
Nothing to do
That seems very
The more abusive aspect is that Muslim
Are speaking up about this job
The people like Alex aren't listening
Muslim leaders could denounce
Violence all day long
What is the only place Alex gets any of his information from is the Drudge Report good luck ever learn about the larger Muslim War
Ifucking wrote that at the very top whenever
He said
Where are the Muslim voice is it
What you're going to say is oh well they're just saying that because they have to
These people do exist
You're always going to say where are the Muslim boys
It's an insane level of gaslighting to complain all day that you're being blamed for the actions
Another white guy at the same time to call Muslims condemn the actions of another Muslim
I literally cannot imagine a less
Responsible way to carry oneself
As a broadcaster
Particularly on a day like this
Well
I mean
If you're just doing it in your day-to-day life you're piece of s*** you don't have tons of people listening
That's the part of this petition
Insane he's reinforcing this idea like a lot of his listeners probably like yeah you know what I haven't heard any Muslim
Speak out about that cuz they're not listening either
It's not it's not a healthy ecosystem
It's a place where
Wounds Fester
Wounds and in deception
Inspector
You get you get into informational gangrene
Along the line where you guys think something terrible happened to you
And that is just
Countenance
It is just
Puss covered wound white supremacy is the pus covered wound of America
The Beast of metaphor
Disgusting
Next clip
Someone still have a little church
Love you too
One word stead condemnation
L
Because
Everything outside
And the Muslims
Okay so there aren't any normal Modern Love
Muslim
Christians in Iraq
In 2014 Miata mean madani
The secretary-general for the organization of Islamic cooperation
Released a statement saying
Under the threat of execution of Christians in Iraq
He called it a crime that cannot be tolerated
Gourmets the head of the religious Affairs directorate the highest religious Authority in Turkey
Sad quotes
The statement made against Christians is truly awful
Islamic scholars needs
The focus on this because an inability to
Harold's the collapse of civilization
After the 2017 bombing of churches in Egypt by ISIS
Director of the Islamic Network
As Christians around the world
Observe Palm Sunday Last earlier this month
Powerful Bomb Blast struck pack
Christian churches
If you chipped in an assault Claim by the Islamic State
The timing and brutality of the attacks
Particularly shocking
Violated
Christian houses of worship and holy holy day as well
Islamic networks group in the San Francisco Interfaith Council joined Muslim people of all faiths
And leaders across the world not only asleep
Reaffirmed a long relationship
Commonality
Christian
Again this list goes on and on and on
He's not listening
If you did you would
Lose
Righteousness
30 uses to Market in defense
Bigotry
He's a scared pathetic man
Also
If you want to get really sad about a website
Go check out Muslims condemn.com
Where you can find a running collection
Things prominent Muslim took
Website
Condemn
Do you know what's not on the list
List of things that white people as a whole don't have to f****** apologize for it doesn't seem like
Going on TV apologizing for
You said it wasn't great
Great
Imany called Mexican spiders
About the f******
The f****** president of the United States condemnation of white Terror
It's not even close to be concept that the condemnations of Islamic Terror
From the people that are full throat
He can't even do that
He can't even do that and most of the condemnations of these attacks don't even
Do the thing that Alex
Pretending
Condemnation
Hiding behind like this isn't Islam
Yeah.
Go the sword thing is not acceptable
So
Look I'm done now I'm done with that game let's get on to this next
Warehouse comedy
Christian
He called himself an Eco fascist that thinks
The right question
Show you and I and all of us can blank
That's why
That's the big takeaway they want you to have well
Takeaway here is they're covering up
And you don't ever hear
Muslim group math killing
Whoops I'm not done with that game
Remember the terror attack in Paris back in November 2015 the one that involves suicide bombers and hostages at the bataclan theater
It eventually ended up in 130
Eagles of Death Metal concert
Be careful on american-islamic relations
Released a statement quote
Despicable attacks on civilians
We condemn these horrific crimes in the strongest term
Indonesia condemns the violence
What's the temp place in Paris
Sheikh Ahmed al-tayeb the grand Imam of off
I was Harvard University
Center for Sunni Muslim scholarships we condemn this odious attack
The time has come for the whole world to unite in order to face this monster
According to ABC News the world responded to the Paris attack
Quote by India
Muslim gathered Monday to protest the violence
And we stand with
Parrot
Protesters also trampled on an effigy of a member of ice
Even though people like Alex consistently refused
Heroes of the Muslims the world were trying really hard to
MSNBC
From right after that to terrorist attack in Paris
Mission of eight leading national and local American Muslim groups held a press conference at washing
DC to condemn the Carnage
The Paris attack was on a vet Friday
The next day Muslim groups held a press conference
And still Alex pretend there isn't any moderate voices in
Just pathetic
And now I probably actually I'm done
I'm done
I told you
Do you know when you look into the sort of thing you can
Can find so many confirmations
Strong and meeting
Fall end
I come from a real place
I why you look into that sort of thing
You can also find tons of article
From people in communities were like
I don't know why everybody
Keep asking us to do things when we are in no one's list
Right
Extra painful level for a lot of people in
In these organizations that are about Islamic America
Relationship
Like the idea of it like we're doing exactly what you're claiming we aren't
And it's not good enough for you
It's really paint
Victim-blaming
To gross
The other thing is
When you on the date you find those strenuous than strident condemnations of those attacks
You can also find
That same day an article written by one of these guys
Where are the Islamic voices
3:20
Episode
Avenida same breath saying
Why are these
These people politicizing this is in order to take
Politicizing
Assertive
Side
Where is he thinks that everyone else is
It's just a stupid game then
He's playing
Because he only really just outlined the globalist want to put these labeled conservative
They want to put these labels on there
So they're larger community
Conservative has to accept blame for what happened
I haven't heard anybody talking about him
Kris Jenner
Projector
Obviously saying though is when he puts
Islamic
Terrorist
Labels onto anybody
He's obviously say
That he wants
The entire group
To be labeled and accountable for the ax
Actions of one person
You think that their equivalent words terrorist
So he's he's even putting out the Playbook Vicky uses
As well as a way to
He's woefully Tramp
It's bad
Any other day
Two things could probably
We could cover it and it wouldn't
They know given the circumstances it's just
I'm sick of
It's going to be an episode where I'm just like I'm not playing around
You dumbass hole
I hate you
You suck what you're doing is dangerous
Let's stop
Let's stop the pretense
And getting worse
But this is
But if not it's it's
A previously reached career-low
He scored 45 points in a game before but that's a career-high you know what I mean is the literal opposite of a triple-double
Club 1010 turnover
He's trying to play a full game with no static
Are all turnovers
I'm so in the next Club Alex
Like descends into
What I would describe as just like
I think this is really
Gross
Florida
Watch this one side
Start watch again
The first time you
F*****
Are you f******
I don't understand why anybody would watch that
I understand
People have
From a forensic
Perspective
Stuff like that
Researchers things like that I kind of understand from that aspect
I'm not even close
I would never consider even to like make our analysis more robot or whatever
Audio
Play blurred vision of it
Is
Abusive
That is something that is inappropriate
I really can't put that strongly enough
The kind of show that
He does
Playing something like that
Devastatingly inappropriate
And I would even say the same thing like
I don't think
I don't know what they have I certainly hope they haven't
But if Lexie
Fairly similar
Criticisms of them
Just stop and think about why
Sensationalize make people
Soufeel
Because he
What's 2
Like there's no there's no
Positive
No news
He wants to watch it
Like that really is that really has to be it
This is some sort of torture
Just just playing actual gun violence
What would people even his listeners what are they
It's going to make them think this was a globalist
There's no reason
Especially for blurry
That's all he wants to see
They just want to see his literal fantasy come true
But that's something
Who is audience
Quite well right
Is fetish this is a fetish
I'm not that far but it's
We find Alex using a
Previous narrative
Built
As a waiter
Enforce his
Anti-itch
Islam mentality
Hey because we do the show the
We already talked about this
Narrative
Will you be able to tell why this
Lesbos
Add
Mexico summer name
The island of women
Isla Mujeres
But
Incompatible
And we wonder why
He has a long
The other long there because I think he realized
Sounding like I support what this guy did
Islam
What's that
The killer was justified because
I'm nodding slowly yes that is what he saying
He said quite literally
Because Islam
It is
Quotes
Heavy scare quotes
It was
Architectural protected list
Yeah
Or anything like that
Alex
Of how incompatible because you left
Are letting these people into our country
Then what do you expect coming up hours
Oh boy I'm really sounded like I like this guy that's why there was a long line
He called himself because
This comes into a bigger conversation
Alex is struggling
With how closely
What if
The world
View that he puts into
I think that's an important thing
Clearly Abbott
Texans
Turn on some level
He realizes
I do want this guy did he showed up
And that isn't dangerous f***** up line
Time to walk if you get it
Compass 2G
You want
Next
Discusses how do you have them
Sarcastic
If some of this is jokes
Controlling and stuff like that
Dedicated
To marxists communists
He calls them anti-white
Murder
So I don't know how much the
The guy actually sounds like
He's just going to lay doesn't matter it's just like when we're talking about Muslims decrying
It doesn't matter it doesn't matter what the Manifest says he's going to say what
Paddock shot up the Las Vegas
Alex
Getting stuff like that whatever your enemy is that
Things Declassified
Yes sources in the DHS and blah blah blah blah
Knowing
So Alex Costa calls
Tries
Take calls from
Specifically Newsela
Australia
And
The only gets a few callers
Sleepy boxes idea
People who know
He goes to brings up the idea that the
The shooter
A terrorist was
To climate change
Eventbrite
Earlier
He doesn't think the climate
Sophomore slump
No that's how he describes
And so like that
Does mention
Manifesto
And so this caller has a dumb question
However
Climate protest going on
Current vehicle
If you want
That's a good question
Not
No
College breaking up because then we really understand what
You think that there was a climate change
Protest
A student walkout some stuff like they cared about
And climate
News coverage
That would have been going to the protest
So the guy's point is that he didn't really care that much about climate change
According to the range
Broadcast is supposed to have access to
The question that this caller is asking is already
Again I don't know how much of this guy's Manifesto to read is sincere
But Alex is already tried to use the manifesto as a source
So it's part of what's being covered
In the manifesto the terrorist
Makes totally clear
Was entirely about killing minority
Who have to higher birth rates
He believes the climate change is a problem but it's one that would automatically be solved if all the quote Invaders as he
He calls them were killed because they're the ones who were reproducing too much which he seems to think is the totality of the
I believe Alex just said that
Argument that he makes all the f****** time
Thank you sayings
We are also
Reproducing
If the guy is being serious
Manifesto
Climate change
Or he doesn't really know anything about the actual science
Behind it
Most likely this is
Probably a sarcastic answer in the manifesto
Or equally likely a belief
Incorporated into
Worldview
As a way to make it look like a picture of Muslim wasn't based on pure visceral fear and insecurity was actually rude
Burdensome for 10 tomorrow concern for the planet
Just like some people
Pretend racial science
Can black people have lower IQs
Either way Alexandra crawler have zero idea what they're even
Pretending to talk about
Is the show is just an exercise
Futility
It's nonsense
Complete nonsense
Alex finally gets the manifesto
Looking at the cover
I'm cover as a design on it says
Does the great replacement
And then has a bunch of pictures
Issues
Alex
And Noda
The ones that are
Convenient for Alex to talk about
He pretends are a joke
The things that are convenient for him
He uses
Of the great replacement
Workers rights
Protection of Heritage and culture that's a sucker but again
Addiction free community
See what he's doing there this is nonsense
This is the end result of him trying to
Horse those cans
Collecting ideas
All that matters is his analysis
Having not looked at this before
Looks at the cover of it
Cheat codes it
In a way that means nothing
It's a meaningless exercise in symbology
It's like he's got
It seems like he's a child in the doctor's office in like a pediatric
And you got the three-year-old there who's putting squares through the the square hole
And circle through the circle horror
And he's looking at that kid
Just like all right so this is a square and that goes through the circle
Now they tell you that it doesn't go through the circle whole but that's because they don't believe it
Because it's the same size but it doesn't have the edges
V2
Trying to protect the culture of the
So it wasn't a real terrorist
Yeah
He only opened strongly insinuating that the globalist
Cichlids
I'm just saying that as a whole throughout the entirety of every year the global stage of terror attack
On March 15th
Kind of makes it a little more over naturally suggest
Not a real thing
As journalists and reporters
This thing is a trap
Exactly
What he says he wants to do
Terrific
Is there an available close to Shooters radicalization
Great deal
Black
Better word
Posting
Those last three
Do you know what he's reading
Somebody else's analysis of the
Robert his post on telling cat got reprinted
Imitate
His primary article
Alex Jones
We're just read
The first person to be on both hours
Amazing
I wish there was some sort of an air horn we could fire off for that
Real
Contribute
Reading the bios for his guests from your Wiki
Anything
It brought like a little bit of a
But I was accidentally quoting Robert
Nextcloud we get to that caller who explains done
Wheatley opposite
It's a very strict meeting I had to go through a 2-hour interview
How to renew my gun license in Ansonville the family then what's that but you need to help those and down
It's very strict
A person with a license can buy a semi-automatic
Alex Azar
Narrative that first of all there was that attacked
20 years ago where they then got rid of all
Also the idea that outlawed semi-automatic
What about right now is that
The thing that he just describes a license
The person not the gun
Like one of the things that the guy was like holyshit
The Gun 2
Need to register everywhere
I'm not sure exactly I don't like that
I don't know enough
Possibility
He had was
Like there is a possibility
I don't know
Recording this on Saturday
Or Monday before this comes out maybe we will look
Naive or unaware
Hey guys wearing tonight
So I'm Alex has
Comes on sometimes
Girl
She comes on for the woman named Syrian girl
Partisan girl
Okay but is from Syria
Everything I understand
He's kind of Bashar al-assad apology
Like
Chemical weapons attack
Volkswagen
Back to her
Reporting
Infowars
Is
Reason
Appearance
I don't want
She is just saying like hey
Seems like f****** around
Be careful about it
Goes right
There's almost no contest
To even accept the idea
Disabled
Literal concrete
I'm so whatever is difficult because the manifesto is written
What amounts to an entirely different language
That people that because we can understand the words we think the words mean thing
And they just redefined words so they don't
Anyting
Who is not interesting
Especially because Alex
Get another gas
Who
Matt Bracken
He showed up a number of times
Run the website called enemies foreign and domestic
Nick.com
He has some history in
The service is
Also has written about
Starbucks
C4c the race war
Is worldview about what's coming
I think we've actually
Gotten fairly in
Is s***
Love gun
And is
I would say
More extreme than Alex and he brings to the preceding
He's got a sword
Oh God no
Dog
He says the guy sounds like a Serbian to him
The Cyrillic writing on the on the weapons even using old church Cyrillic
This is Extreme
Wow
Wow please please tell me that he's in actual islamists please that's what I want to hear please give me that
Pretend I didn't say exactly
Videos of CIA
Who is
I'm at
When they come back from break
Manifest
He's doing a hypothetical
What's the question
European heritage
She's Australia
And the answer that he provides never specific
He says that he is Austria
You just point out that Australia is an offshoot of Europe
Like of the penal colony all that stuff yeah
Based on this bracket
Arises that he might be Serbian
The problem is that another in another Point spells things out more clearly
I was born in Australia to working-class lower-income family
My parents are Scotch-Irish
English stock
This is shity work on Brackenridge Park
Is self-contradictory
He's his speculation or whatever he
He's reading into the manifesto by something that is literally in it
He's doing a really bad job and if
I don't know
Just a second or Serbian writing on the Gundam
Colluding in
Bugging
The fact that two like the lot of
People in the right wing
Are inspired or
Inspiration from
That doesn't mean that you Serbia
Anders Breivik was very inspired by the same
Yeah
None of it
Irresponsible
To the table
Irresponsible about being a f****** monster
Boutonniere
Further irresponsible because
Adjusting
That maybe he's a crypto
Do you know that different kind of his llamas
F*** off
So here's my bracket
One-upping himself
What stupidity
To be effective than infowar you use the ammunition that's on the table
And the ammunition on the table is to call this the Facebook Massacre
Penis right on Mark Zuckerberg Mark Zuckerberg
He's the guy that made the tool
That instigated
Promoted it if not for Facebook live streaming
He might have done something else or Nothing at All
Murder there we go.
So f*** off you're an idiot.
Totally
If your oil if you're if you're willing to allow that
Avocado
What you're saying
Cause this
You are a strong connection is better
You have completely ruined whatever foot you're trying to stand on
Is that argument could be twisted that way
They never do
Against
Very much against that
I don't understand why he hates Facebook
Like that ft
He's taking the line that's like
If you do that sort of thing
It's not Facebook's fault
Fitbit's person live streams
Facebook where they do they make it so no one can lights to
And then people can't get their messages out
I see what you're doing but that's only because you're being confronted by
I think it's because he's being confronted by
The fact that he was kicked off Facebook isn't it isn't allowed to do Facebook live in
He knows the pain he's literally like it's almost like if you shutdown
On my face
If you shut down Facebook live there's no chance I'll be able to eventually
Exact
But for now I can still
So you might be asking yourself
What's going on with Rodger Stone in the middle of this episode
Nice person
Not enough
Rogers
Obviously enjoy men
She won't even talk to me
Featherstonhaugh
Rogers gone
She's gone.
An amicable parting
To be fair his operation
Launch
So that that could just be the interim. Specially while Alex is so
Preoccupied
Lawsuit
He starts complaining about how Jerome corsi suing
Little bit later
Max Wright
Matt Bracken
Cuz that guy is
It is analysis of this attack is
If you
And I thought that was as bad as it
Could get
How could it possibly get worse while Alex wants to make this a three-way dance
Stewart Road
Warning about false flag
But he got caught
Stroud's what's your first approximated
What's a video video online
I think this guy was a
Believer
Apparently
He wanted to start a race war
The same it's going to be used to attempt to
Disarm
And also to censor us
So I'm actually being like this guy is
Cuz you don't expect to hear that
Stewart Rhodes
Why does not surprise me later use the term us
What he said
Pronoun
Alex
This guy is a True Believer white supremacy
And regardless of whether or not he was mine controlled
It's going to be used to demonize us
White supremacist
White supremacist and I'll allow you
You two have that right
Biggest grape
. possible or whatever the biggest
Benefit of the doubt and assume
If only because that doesn't make enough batter
That is all
The care about is this idea of like
It's going to
Argon
Being gone and
Later
Society
Like a released a statement condemning White
Keepers releases statement
White nationalist
Some people have no
Committing the same fallacy
Alex
Muslims
Just because we didn't hear
Their condemnation of it doesn't mean it doesn't exist
Like he's crazy
Well he also said of course this was going to happen because of Muslim so I didn't really bring the store next one
Even in his condemnation of white nationalist terrorism it's really in condemnation of Islamic terrorists
They're not even that it's an insinuation that all things are because of Islamic
Sort of caught himself
Sort of agreeing with
Motivate
This terrorist Act
Rhodes falls into the same trap that no one set for him
Innocent
When I was worried about her concern about masturbation
We can't
Hold on I don't agree with the way this guy did it
Yeah
You saw a very real problem we can't
Yeah I mean that's close to
Like
Non condemnation
That's really close to her right at guys in it
Society
It's like running a very serious risk of like
Well
What you do is
You are
Encouraging
You crossed the line of what is appropriate
He had a meeting with the HR of white supremacist than they were like hold on
You need to give a speech to the all the white supremacist then you have to say
Listen we all agree with this guy but we don't like what he
Did we think what he should have done
Is just been really really racist
And make sure that all of our policies were racist
Estes Park
What are you f******
Doing
Concern
All
Totally
Cool method
Because their fears
The method
Interconnect
Absolutely
I'm going to lay out my thoughts about
The end of the episode
But you cannot believe
The things
That this guy believe
And then Alex Jones
And Nazi where Italy
Do that
It is impossible
To escape
The natural
End result
Of this rhetoric
And we'll get to that his his
The only way to read what he said is
He was talking to the victims at the mosque
Said what was going to happen you moved here
Bright
You built that what did you think was going to have
That's what he said
What was it
That's exactly
Alex realizes maybe she's getting a little too hot
I'm so he's got to tell a very not true story
This is up there with the Nazi hat on Halloween
Okay this is up there with the globalist to the hot tub haha
Yes
This is up there in the pantheon of not true Alex story
Details that are
Oh I was it I was in a hotel Mexico
Hotel
I was watching
Jeb
So is Muslim
Hijabs
Friend
About what
So the
Wrong response
To Muslims is saying
Be my friend
Guess that I mean
The story didn't happen
Happened but it is kind of try
Yeah they all hate you should never
Muslims that are Resort
Mexico
They hate your beautiful supply shop in Austin
They hate you
Depends if you committed against them
Leanne killing
Even
Justifying murdering Muslim
I need some ways because you deserve
You get
This entire show so far has been him trying to say
Him
It reinforcing the things that are behind
What is terrorizing Muslims around the world
Like no matter what event
First attack outage
If you just looked at this show and the rhetoric of
He's putting forth
It is what leads
People to attack mode
There is no way around that
Nothing
So already hurt Alex
Kind of accidentally
Start talking about how we
Agrees with
What the terrorists
Yeah I've already heard
Roads are exactly the same
And now it's Matt bracken's turn
To basically agree
I've been reading the manifesto and
You know there's a there's a lot of what
The shooter says that is on point
And some of it isn't about the decadence of the West. We've been discussing the
Are the eleven-year-old drag queen in
This is a society that's intended
You're on his side a******
All three of you motherfukers are justifying
Equivocate
And making okay
What was done to these 49 people
And countless others who survived
And the victims family members and their loved one
Traumatized because
That is all
They're getting on air in blaming their perceived enemies
And then at the same time in the same breath
I mean it makes a lot of great points
This isn't someone at a cocktail party
Years later telling you about how the Unabomber had good point
This is the day after father situation is still broiling
Bobby situation
Crisis it's a life-or-death
Situation for tons of people
He
Said parentheses
I mean who hasn't thought about doing this before
If you look I read his Manifesto he's made a lot of great points
I'm just saying I thought about doing what he did
If you mix a lot of grateful
It's hard not to hear some of it
So in the next with Alex makes
F****** bold pronounce
The entire Manifesto on air
Heart attack
Thrice
I love you like selected little blurb that is in Turnbull.
Come at me bro
Laugh at him
You are Icarus flying too close to the Sun
With your bold pronouncements of reading
It's ridiculous I would love to
Ariel
You're hooked on Whiskey not Sonic literally impossible for him to read entire page
So he doesn't
Get into the
He starts talking about how these Mass Shooters aren't Brave
Islamic
Whatever
Warriors
Islam
Not good
But before we go
F****** awful it is
That stuff over
Policy of
Fruit
Yes never again is what you swore the time before is underneath like that
Awesome
Just like underneath
His
Horribly
Casting
Lake desire for a actual
I guess
And then this condemnation
Audit Muslims
Attack women and children
Here's a shortlist of white terrorists in the United States who targeted women and children
Which is not
Surprising at all because they're terrorists
Timothy McVeigh intentionally chose a federal building with the daycare center in it because he believed he was getting revenge for Ruby Ridge
Randy Weaver son was killed by the police
He wasn't opposed
Dylann roof killed Six Women in his church shooting two of them were older than 70 years old
He wasn't a Muslim
Robert Gregory Bowers the terrorists who killed 11 people at the
The Tree of Life synagogue killed three women
None younger than 75
One of them was 97 years old he wasn't a Muslim
Patrick Kelly the Devin Patrick Kelley the terrorist behind
Springs mass shooting back in 2017
Kill 10 women and children and one unborn child
He wasn't the most
Elliot Rodger of the 2014 Isla Vista Shooting
Dudes
He felt didn't deserve the women who had chosen to them over him
He killed two women but definitely was trying to kill one more
He wasn't a Muslim
This list could go on and on just like my Muslim condemnation
Terrorism
Alex is
Like making definition
Of Islam
Buy a definition of terrorist
And refusing to accept that it is not a one-to-one parallel
He is demonizing an entire community
By making
This is
The dangerous red
That existed
In the world that is unfounded
Not based on any
And only leads
And putting people's lives at
Let's let's
What you talk about him
How many times how many times does
The government said he loved so much run by Trump
How many times
Women and children specific
Do you think Christianity is anti-abortion
They're so against really want women and children
Let's talk about him I don't give a s*** about terrorist about people
People
Christianity really loves
Women and
Alex supports the children locked up
Women and children
Concentration camp
Stan bright
Grateful
Love women f******
Alex makes a Target out of that child
Survivor and now he's working his way up to making a Target
I mean the entire Community of Christ Church to some extent in New Zealand
If you were a Muslim and you were to listen
I don't know how you would
Like with this sort of rhetoric being put forth
By someone who has a large audience
And knowing that whatever is being said on the radio show.
Comparison
What's being said
Off-air
Places of the internet I don't understand how you could not feel
Completely threatened
If you were like
I don't know for 12 year olds
Just wants to live their license
All that stuff I don't know
I don't know how you couldn't feel like you were a Target
What
What b*******
Is obvious
Is that with these things
Is it used to be
You would have to go to 40
Two Fine people
Essentially praising this guy
For doing what he did
The day off
Exactly
They used to take awhile
The GOP and Fox News and Alex Jones all used to have two grand Stanford
Yes we do decry this and then a week later they could go back to the Muslims
Because everybody kind of forgot
Now they do it the next day they don't know they don't even wait
Until the end of the event
To say that Muslims fault
Can you really grow shortcut
Anyways
Which Wich
Stomach
Does it mean to be a
There needs to be
Some sort of holding people accountable
For what they put into the world
Leads to
Right
So it is next clip Alex
Text
Surprise
Associa Hawaii
Carlos The Jackal in something others
Sure you got the right off the bat you got to oppress women
When you can get you married who you bye
The wife at the girl has nothing to say but who's she married
And if she doesn't do what you like her to do
You can hit her americollect
What's wrong
Male get rid of all this idea of Islam goes straight to Christianity in America and you will get away with
SMS
You can f****** Lobby
People who killed
Billion
47 months
You cannot
You can Lobby in be associated with
With jeffry Epps
Literally
And still not have any consequence
You can literally be Jeffrey Epstein and have very limited consequences for your pickaxe
I mean this is all this is but I hate him
Alex
Pretty much says that the attack on Christchurch was a false flag
And then you're going to love what happens right after that
I've been saying
Invasion going on
The attacks on mosques and I said they're coming
Here
Weather
Really do it
Sure
Prices
Please don't forget I keep forgetting
Nice
He's just adjusting this was
Without any
Do you know where
It somehow almost
It's almost comforting for him to call it a cost as opposed to blaming Muslims themselves
For making it happen
American Auto Sale in Faribault us need to have a false-flag I guess
Interesting
This is entirely Islam's.
Which state
Whatever
Yeah I mean
Certainly this is the first time
In our two years with
Regal
So
In terms of
If he's blaming Islam or if he's
Volkswagen
Whatever the case may be
Behind it
And that is the Alex's
Is really the victim
This attack
You know that I know you know that I know so in this next clip Alex I know and I don't want to
Keyboards and I don't want to know anymore
Commiserate
As white people
Are the real victims
Of the Christchurch
That you don't use the paralyzer on me imma be pissed
Flash my vape pen works
Manhattan bottles
I'm good but
What it is what it is
Down in New Zealand
See if not a capitalist American
You know what
They're coming for it that's an attack on US America directly
Do super smart
Girls
Gross
Next level
In terms of
That's just
If you take
Do you know Tony radical man
He'll have a great business
But if you take an Egyptian man
Turn him Muslim
Well then he's going to start acting like an animal
This is dehumanizing
Yeah I mean this is
Next Level over
In terms of what he's putting in
To the world like there's no excuse
If you're if you're putting stuff out
Cannot be broadcast in the lead-up to
World War
Yeah what you're doing is you're saying that all
Muslims share quality that is
And inhumanity
Yep
And that is never accepted
They're animals
And that is that is not okay
Circumstances
Particularly
After
Water
Of people because
They were Muslim
Happening in the world
This is
Insane
This is really insane like me
F****** prayers
We're not even there
We went from a massacre happening to out-and-out defending wire Massacre
Should happen
And
Ascribing blame
Do the victims
Insinuating
Because of
They are capable of
This is just
F******
I just I just don't know whether it was
10 years ago when people
Said this without saying it
Do you think so
Cuz this is not a crime show that yet
Variable
Perspective
If you're looking at how you would love the world
Secretly believe these
But aren't allowed to save them
Freely in public
It's not that much better you wish that everybody understood each other
And cared about each other on it
Obviously
Right
But it is in the real world
IFixit
You would rather
People
Right
Destroy entire
Community
Hates that
It's a ad like I suppose the only thing is what stage of dealing with
Cancer are we at
Because
Where is Extreme right
Search for Oliver goddamn
Collagist
They're just trying to demonize these wonderful cells
Yeah
They grow faster and you can't kill him
That sounds good
See that's up on some level this metaphor.
Because there were warning signs in
Dupree metastasizing
FaZe
And the people who were
We're the ones who got those signs
And retractor
Stuff like that
And what's interesting about that
You look back at Alex
Wasn't
Hedonism
Like what he's
Become Now isn't
Is that
All of this stuff is that world change
Yeah the militia Patriot
Jaheim some way
Predominantly
I'm anti
And it's
It's troubling because all of the other stuff
Before informed
DHHS
Bia taking
White
Seriously has aided
In the world
You did
Previous
Even believe in these things
Is a part of
What would the present reality
Traps them in this current ideologies because if they were to accept
I changed now they would have they would have to accept that they were
Wrong
To change that
Yeah
Let's break
Heavy stuff
Because Alex
He starts getting really
If you ever need a
Assertive glimpse
At his narcissist
How it works
This next clip is Xzibit
We're going on behind the scenes around here
Power structure has figured out that
He's not going to work the people are against it
Hit the people that run
Salons compartmentalize
Avengers
Scramble to figure out what
We have reached here
And I'll just leave it at that
Different level
Government military
Literally
I'll just how about we don't model everything up after time to shine
Let's start
Do you understand what he's saying
Cuz I'll spell it out for you
Do you think he had globalist
To the table to be like
Should be on our team
Now things have gone so bad for the globalist
Did he have globalist that are coming up to him in there like
He is now the oracle
They could tell the globalist out of right the ship
He is acting like he is now
No because he's getting a consultant
He's not working
But the approach that they're having his different apps
They're like this dark side
Don't you love Satan
Don't You Love
Not anymore
Alex
We don't know how to take
Is a pathetic level of narcissism like just
I would love
To talk to someone who listens to Alex
What's the show Hoopa
Give that
Yeah like I would love to
Figure out what it would take for
YouTube
Yeah
Phrase it I asked
The hike-and-bike trail
That is crazy.
Lifelong enemies
It's no good we better call in Alex for a consult
It's nice to take that little moment
To enjoy Alex's
Is narcissism
Because now we get to the point where Alex
Like just generally
Don't do that even if you are a mainstay
News source
Probably not in anyone's best interest
To read this guy's
If you're Alex it's certainly going
A productive exercise
If you're a researcher
With full understanding of
The contacts
And you're trying to put this in a larger
I like
A larger world that explains.
This event but so many and how it ties all that together and you're going to put this together over this over that
Like a year
Read the hell out of that Manifesto
If a murderer
If a mass
Murder happened yesterday
Delray
Let it go. Now
I mean like really though
No matter who you are no matter what the
What time frame is
Be careful
Because you might be
Helping
What the terrorists wanted
Yeah I know I mean
Like
That we've already talked over and over again about some
Trolli
Clearly jokes
Sarcastic
Attempt
8 people into X wires
If you don't know what you're doing
And you just read the
You run the very serious risk
Terrorist
In the end goal that they
To write it's a game that you shouldn't play unless you are very certain you know what you're doing
One of the reasons why anytime that we talked about any
Anything from
The manifesto on this episode
I tried to
Clear
I have no idea
Serious about this
The only use Bing
As like
Well let's what Alex's say
I don't know where
Does not what he has to say
Right
Alex
But he also clearly has
Red
And is just
Getting these texts
From his
And ask
He starts to
Respond
Is in his normal by
That's very interesting
Something to see how that happen
And what
Because of that
I think you know what's
I chose firearms for the fact that it would have a social discourse
United States situation the world
You should just got it feel like you had a home as a man to show you were successful
Analogous
Just talkin about
And also
You clearly talk
Using people like Alex
Use all of these guns
Because I know that people are going to have a conversation about
The last is going to move gun regulation
People like
Some sort of 8
Further conflict
I don't know if that's actually
But that is what
Alex
Not realizing
The side
That the right
Plays
In the manifestos conception of the back
That will come from this attack
Next clip
I think
He starts
To get
Maybe a little bit jealous
What about the shooting and more about have better aim
It's more about the ideas
Fractions
Set up pressure left-wing the United States
Speak
Abolish
Liberty
Wright's by The Leftovers ultramatic station
She's all written
What's going on there there's a sense of Alex being like I already know
Which is not something you wanted
Here be to a terrorist
Sincere or not like whatever is writing you don't want to be like
I've been saying that forever man
Later when I
Keepsake
Moringa terrorist Manifesto
I would want that I would want that
But you understand his insecurities and pettiness require
This is
Is my s*** right
I didn't get it from him he got it for me and his biggest problem with the mass shooting is
Is plagiarism
Something like this on here when you're out
Probably a bad idea
Anybody
Exactly what
Alex
You listen to
Pull up
Do you know you're heading into a tailspin man
He kills people you think he came up with it no
You just see Harrison Smith put his head down and walk out the door like that I tried.
Oh well
Galaxy
Expressing that he's mad that he
Get a shout-out
Honestly believe that was going to happen
I mean
Quickly save that
Like that but it's sort of the sense that I get
Behind his word
Is it
From there
What the f***
Worse than him not wanting a
He's talking about like all these ideas
Guys putting
Like I rebooted 1776
Where is the real leaders
And I never was going to act like
Forever
My reading is
He is saying
This guy's attack was unnecessary
Because we've already started the process by which we're going to get rid of and solve all the problems
Manifest
It's already been triggered the the movement to get rid of all Muslims that's already started
Ivan bear
I've been telling people to
To do what you what you told them to do
For such a long time we've already got the ball rolling
What are you doing
You don't even bring anything to this table
But a better reading of it is possibly
Like
Speaking as Alex
I am afraid
People are going to look at him
Figure in some sort of a pushback
Against invading Muslim hordes
When they may be wild
An immediate response
To first of all the aftermath like the day after
A terrorist
Like this
Like
You are so
Beyond
Bucked up
Expresses are entirely expresses jealousy of him
Is attained by the dirt
If I'd killed
I think there's a
I think there's a little bit but that's not that's
Alex
Look into the like the actual
You kind of
People are going to give credit
For a movement that I started
If the
The push-and-pull
Between the
The surface world
Of all this stuff like Alex
Tucker
Really disgusting
Islam
Display on the rig
All of whom are hilarious
They do all this stuff on the
Publicly
And then there are
People like this guy who shot up these
Who are doing the the other part
Which is The Logical extension of exact
Most people
Like the Ben Shapiro show
The world
Whenever these terrorist attacks happen
Clearly an offshoot of what they put into the world
Rhetoric
Like holyshit
I'm not involved how dare you say I am
Write analysis like for this
That's where Alex lives
And I think it's
The Peace of the militia.
That he kind
Resents the fact
The part of the info
He recognizes on some level he wants to be part of that Michigan militia baby there on the front lines
Uno's
Reclaim more like
The person who put the
Anti-immigrant
Rhetoric into if you go shoot
Is
Be the guy
Who
Sounds the alarm it is always antivirus
Which informs color honor last episode
I'm in the Splinter Cell
I wish I could be there
You don't think I do anything because I don't kill people man what makes your s*** possible
Iridescent
He's not getting the facilitator
He doesn't like being
John Stockton
Absolutely
He knows his place and he understands
Cosmology
Subconscious or conscious
Do you understand
The structure and
Because it's
The place that doesn't
If a place that takes the most
Because there
And it's the place that doesn't
Real crazy
Susie Astic
Doesn't want to be the shield he wants to be the sword
Is there something to
This guy
Are you
His responses along the lines of
Given the resurgence
And that's what
Has policymaker absolute
Here's Alex's
Attempt
And response
Where are you a supporter of Donald Trump supporter as a symbol of
Which is not for Trump
A free market Americana
Unify
Okay
Full on false flag
Professors wrote this manifest
Requires that
They were strong
And research
All of their possible ratings
In order to
Perfectly
Create a facsimile of what a right-wing person would say
Professors nefarious
Manifesto did research
Found out what
I don't believe that that's
Hard to believe
No matter either way
Travelodge
Only because they know what that they would
What you know
I'm talking about something
Okay
If these leftist professors wrote that
It necessarily requires
That they also had a hand in the actual shooting
Or they were at least aware of how the shoot 20 minutes after
The shooting happened being larray
Brett
Create
Zach
Right they didn't
What it would require is an Unsinkable
Ability
Control coincidence
From the beginning
End of the world
So in this next clip Alex talks about Howard
Manifesto
He talks about how
Candace Owens radical
Now
All the reporting that I've seen
Outside
Directions to recording every article that I
Like this is clearly a joke
Alex
In this next clip
Clearly recognizes
That it is a
But he refuses to accept that
As a part of his narrative
You listen very closely
Read about that closely
You will see
But he knows it was a
Yes
Agnus help push me further and further into the
Violence
Trolling
So I
Extreme Action she calls for too much
Even provide text
Is a total satanic inversion of reality
Devil note
Recognizes the reality of
No it's it's
Devilry
Patrolling it
Self
Also
Proof
Fat
He's right
I got
Candace Owens
Radicalized
Because he's
Influence by state
I think it's super unlikely someone's writing something
Weather
Marshalls
Anders Breivik
Dylann roof
Denise Schwartz people
Anime say that there
MainSource
Radicalization
You can't take that serious
Like it did just ended
Nonsense
And frolics to record
Recognize that it is
F****** around on some level and then refused to accept what that implies
Is just
Matt Bracken
Kind of
March
Manifesto
Closest
With us
You're a golfer from
Yes
Welsh
Oops, time
Oh no that's you shouldn't you shouldn't murders
Manifesto
Out loud and say
That's what I
Nope that is s***
The time on this episode
Because he has someone else
Flower
Weaver is coming off it so I turned off the episode
Google
Whatever rainbow snatch
No not
So Alex closes at his analysis with
With this
Strong were very generous
Close out his support for a white nationalist terrorist
I was going to say his b*******
Similar
Tumblr
Ways to characterize this
At the end
This Friday episode
Globalism wrote Lodge
Amore the globalist
Catofashions
God help
We don't know there are other people I don't know
Synthetic
Again with the caveat that there's possible in sincerity in the
Needs to be comped
It says the writer is definitely explicitly
Do use of the Fourteen Points
In the document
He also uses
The 14 words
And he uses that word nationalist
Contacts
I'm not a direct member of any organization or group is all I've donated to many nationalist groups
Interacted
With many more
In response to his own question quote were you or are you in National St replies quote
Yes predominately in Death Note
Later he says quote I am an ethno-national
She's pretty over
The only information
This possibly
A dubious Manifesto
But if you goes on it
The guide the very literally
He's National
Do you know what I think I think the reason that I don't care what he has
To say
The
The manifesto
I think the main reason
Is the same reason I don't care
You know somebody
Some
GOP senator says that they're not a racist
Care what you say because everything you do
Specifically
Targeted Lee effects minority
Define racist
Whether or not
You are self-reporting as a race
Definition of
I don't
But this guy has to say I don't care about anything that guy
Because he went to a mosque
And he murdered
And that explains itself
Done
Don't know why he killed people
You're saying
Reinforce
I also don't care
Bring up stuff from it
Because Alex is bringing up stuff from
And I'm responding
You're doing good
And maybe there's a
Engaged
Find hearing it if someone
The only reason I felt
To bring anything
I think
Calling out
Uno's
This is sincere or not
But if Alex is going to
Play that
I know it behooves me
No
I will not be swayed or influence or
Consider any argument
That involve something within that manifest
I don't give a s*** about
You can tell me what is Manifesto said so cool with that
But if you say because his Manifesto said this
You should
That's why I tried to make it very clear to in my
About this
Absolutely
Yeah
Here we go all right
It's all too clear to see what's happening here
On this episode
To the end of it
And he knows that he has to fight back
To get the idea that this really was a xenophobic Muslim terrorist
Because of course
But there's a part of me that suspect he doesn't
Even understand
The scope of what he
He's dealing with
Every touchdown of the last episode of major element of the undoing of the militia Patriot community
Was Timothy McVeigh
The ugly face of what was being preached on shortwave radio and on hidden message
Or just put on full display
If people had to deal with what was in front of them
When shown in the full light of day became inclimate incredibly clear to everyone
Radicalizing crazy
And it was an inevitable conclusion that eventually someone was going to follow through with their life they kill tons of people
If you truly believe that a global Italy
Group
Are planning on bringing an oppressive worldwide involves Universal pressure
Forever
It stands to reason
That you might consider option
Other than I don't know starting an absurdly dumb radio show and then eventually selling
Is your plan of action
A certain amount of people who truly believe that message
Some terrorists
And they're going to believe that they're Justified to do so
Hey Timothy McVeigh for Speed
To see what was really going on
That they didn't have to
Previous
Christchurch
Has the potential to
To be the same sort of watershed moment
For what the militia Patriot
Has become
They still love their guns
Danielle about the new world order but the primary preoccupation of
People in that community
Is a hatred of an education towards Muslim
Everyone kind of knows that most
People are going about their daily lives and they don't have to know about white genocide narrative
They're pushed in these
Or the idea of a demographic
Quit in the
A terrorist act like this makes
Some have to look at it
In a way that Timothy McVeigh forced normal people to learn about the New World Order
The idea that replaced
Siri
The idea of the replacing
Theory is one that ultimately by definition
Must lead to violence and murder
There's just no other way around
If your problem is that and I'm just making up these number
Muslims in America have twice
The birth rate of
And you're scared that eventually that will lead
Them having the numbers required to take over the country
You have an unsolvable problem
Well you have a horrendous horrendous biggity besides
People based on one attribute
But you also have an unsolvable problem
Relative birth rates become except
Can it be 121
Can you only accept 2.7
521 birth rate between non-whites and white
How are you going to enforce that sort of plan
Before you can touch on the logistics of what these people are complaining about and pushing for your already at the point of racial quotas
When a person isn't as valid blinded by hate
Constantly reinforced by manipulative propaganda
Is exposed to these sorts of ideas
The Logical endpoint
Of this thinking
Comes clear
The first suggestion that probably be made
Beautiful sweet Deport all people who don't fit
Conception
What you want
The population to be
Many of those people
Airforce deportation would necessarily economically crippled
If not
Put them in legitimate Danger
Dependent
And then you have to consider the fact that at least some of those people that you want to deport wouldn't agree to go along with it
Possibly many
Well I guess you'd have to put them in
And before you know it we're already at the first stages of another Holocaust
And we're not even talking about the point where
What kills
Justin logista
Physical aspects of
What this world
View implies
Leave YouTube
First steps
Of the Hulk
Absolutely
Without exception
There's no way around
Thought about this a great deal
If you are obsessed
With demographic
Idea
Any sort of variable birth rate idea
The Next Step
Conversation
That you have to have
Basically this
At what point is it okay
Right
If your problem is Muslim breeding
Or something like that
What level of Muslim
Having kids are you okay
Where is the line
Well
I mean I suppose the only difference
White nationalist Nazis
Now
Attempt
To claim from
Nothing
Not the nothing
Is that
They don't want to create the Holocaust
They want to look
Hey look if we were running Germany in the 1930s
We would have just moved all the Jews to Israel we wouldn't kill them Israel's Forge
Arabia's for Muslims
America's for white folk
We want you to have a whole let's not deal with the fact
Totally fine with Germans Living in America
FedEx
I know they would do something like that allowed to carry
Through to its next
Implicit
Behind
Absolutely
They will understand I hope
Phil understands that a live
Little better at this is not some kind of liberals just call everything to disagree with
This is a very batural extension where the logic of demographic anxiety
And what are the reasons
Is because the idea of following through with its ideology
If you can think about it for a short amount of time
You start to realize how f****** stupid
The ideas of trying to put this in action
Any other way
So if you are someone who believes in these idea probably start thinking about it like
Are then going to go out of their way to create
A humane
Ethnostate
As it trickles down into
Ends up
Because that is always end up
Easiest
The cheapest
But it is also what logically consistent with this world
Like
I don't mean to say that it makes
I just booked
Extension in the next step
Next Step
It is not
Absurd
If you agree with the first premise
To get to the king
That murder is okay
For these
Exact
Even if you say you agree with the premise but then you say well but we would never let it
You're full of s***
You would
Well and you couldn't control it even if you wanted to
In the same way that I'm sure a lot of
People who are making good money also
The militia stop
In the 90s were like actually bombing Federal Building
You can't do it
You can't control this Beast
That you put out into the world
Because there were people who will hear you
Take you seriously and think
Well
I'm going to be a hero by doing
In a way that no one else will
People who
Agitate toward
Things that
Need to be dealt with
As accessories
I don't know how you do that
I'm not entirely sure what policy exactly need
So we need to start having that conversation
And I'm just sick of
So
I said my peace
Haven't got the
Sorry to yell at you
No no what what you're going to apologize to me
Auto Parts
I think I think what's amazing
This Epic
Is
How
Many candidates we have for the people
Who have not killed the guy
And I'm going to go with
Literally every Muslim organization that you said
Terrorism
We have 100 Muslim organizations
You're f****** kill the guy Dan
We probably had
Is the guy who
Alexandra Thurston color