Alexandra Thurston color
A little bit about
Jordan
What is your favorite
My favorite what do you mean
Do you know
Like a little trinket
Souvenir stores in bought one and had
The rest of your life you know
I got you the little nope nope
Or something like that nope
Oh yeah I mean the closest thing to that is when I was in Austin
We went to just
Some sort of a vintage shopping
Ran into a guy who
Fixes old radios
I got sold like a really old radio that looks fuckingawesome
I want you to have some sort of like
He got married wedding party
And he made a little those Funko doll outside of all of the people who were in The
Cherish
Really cool
Have you ever been in those stores
It's never appealed to me
Okay
I don't know I mean I guess probably cuz they spent so much time growing up in Hawaii
And there's so many like touristy things
Obviously tourism
Huge part of the
The industry
Local economy
And so it always appears
Stupid
These are the f****** people who are
Just coming into enjoying our beach
Bratz lyrics
Confrontational but I think we're good
The cute seem to not believe that I'm not
No I don't think I do we're flying to your parents house I bet I could find some
Maybe actually know I've been in your parents house I don't I don't even know if they have it
Hello Kylie.
I was just there not too long ago and I didn't recognize much of anything
There
You don't know much better
The old past
We're back
2012 take a look
January 23rd
How Alex responded
The aftermath
Sandy Hook
Before we get Today Show
Like take a little moment
Out of our time
North Florida Gun Show
So first underscore Rio
I'm a policy wonk thank you very much
Princess something and words
Just old
No
I thought it might be knowing
But then I realized that the last name is also
No thanks but thanks
Spell thain
No thanks
Both Worlds
Anyway
No thanks
Somebody
It also very much
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket of poop
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much. Thank you very much
For sure we would appreciate
Little
Dangerous
Out of whack
Things you don't expect the pop-up become
We're here
Fort Worth
Post-sandy hook business
Appropriate
Probably scream
At their phone
If we didn't
Bring up the fact that This American Life
Just did there
A piece
Two segments
And a lot of people have asked
You gave it a listen
We're your first day
Oh Alex is lying people who remember him they didn't like
Yeah
Yeah I think I think
I think so I think I was probably
Some of the most essential pieces of the coverage I think you've covered
Up first-half about Sandy Hook
In terms of hearing to use struggle
Perspective
That hold the whole situation
Have you started narratives that are brought in
The world the actual
First-person damn
Well I mean you kind of
Maybe not intentionally
Somewhat subconscious
Justly go out of your way not to
Because
You know
Like hypothetically
So monster
To then have it brought
The real world and it's
Stark truth
Is kind of heartbreaking
Listening to
Truly
How can somebody
Do this right unaware of the effect
Did they have
Horrible things
Yeah that's kind of in the realm of
We've talked about this
These things kind
You know
In terms of the information base of our podcast
No that's not
New
At the end
Where is Alex's origin story
Really
F***** up
Oh yeah
Journalism that we couldn't do
The idea of going in finding
These people that Alex
Yeah the idea of like
Alex has one story
Five other people have
Hundred percent
My favorite guy was the the guy who
Who found out that
Entrup love each other uses like
I don't know if I want to
The guy who is Alex beat the s*** out of
Almost killed
Yeah I mean exist stories that
The people from his school Tell match up pretty well with some of the
Hero Stories that Alex has
Just without the Alex
Picton Park
To justify
Impeding
Fleetmaster
Also the idea of him running around the school
Matches up almost entirely with Alex
I got lured into
Even a lot of that stuff
Isn't really new to our
During the people who lie
Threatened
When he was younger and stuff like that
The thing that rang the most true was when
Woman Within
Talking about Holly
Describing
All the way
Would threaten her with
And it was like
Cast I have you ever heard his about what the globalist
Will do to you they'll take you down and right
When she said that I was like you didn't like listen to his show to know that that's a big
Part of his performance still his
True from those people
From Justice
We've been able to get a
From looking at him
It was
Awful it was awful
It just makes you realize that there's no point where you're going to come up with VP
Right
Hey you got me
There's never going to end your job
Ronson
Who did a very good job on the PC
He's like
And let me tell you that I am not going to stay.
If I was good at it
But
While he was talking to Alex
I told him the story of how Alex is a huge Apple Alex turns around
I've never been an hour
For your own
Brightright
Alex has always known that Jon Ronson ism
Media figure like he came into his life as a reporter right along with him
Covering him for a peace always
Be nice to him
Eunos
Platform to be like Alex
Beat the s*** out of paper
I was never in his best interest to be addicted
Of course not
Haven't I always
Ben strategic about our relationship
Also Alex
We all know the truth
I thought it was
Insight
You know tough but if it's
Same time
You know
Proof that there is no positive outcome
Who is
Nomad for a while
Demonstrative
On NPR
Reaffirming of our like
Our instincts are too bad
I think after 2 years of listening to the got a pretty good idea of what
How much transition
Away from talking about
At all
All just gun paranoia they're coming to get your guns
Going to start a civil war
Baby boo
Uno's
Maybe you know but first we ever out of context drop
Propaganda
Redial
What could you be clearer about immediately
It's propaganda
See now you're not being clear about terms
He'll explain it later but
Fink
That's actually what it mean
So we're going to listen to
To enter into
Obsession
On this episode
I think someone is recently
Explains that gaslighting is
Nothing
Idea
He talks about it
For almost the entire show
Name for what I do it's very weird
But I was listening through this
The show The Middle
Keep talking about gaslighting
So I pulled the clips
Specifically just to illustrate like
Alex is aware of what gaslighting
But as this goes on it just
God it's so bad
Because I have the definitions in the history of gaslighting
Call charm
Just one time.
Define gaslighting
You walk in
And because of the
I got another example telling people that you never said that
The constantly telling people while there's evidence
Extreme version of gaslighting
But you carried out and perpetuated on the This American Life episode
Is the next clip him being like better example
Play clips from my show yesterday my catalog
Basically just explains it like that
It says that it's a trick that the globalist
Because of TV never being dumb or whatever
It works more
Messages or whatever so
You can't cover
Story
Starts talking about how a Morgan suck
Evergreen Terrace
Alex has started a petition
To get him deported as we know from our previous episode
Piers Morgan has to be on his show
Godwin we didn't episode about the actual interview
Of January
Alex on the 3rd
He's very aware any in his next life you can tell he's clearly
He's mostly doing this for Pueblo
Morgan
Sound right
To try to get some
Operation
New York and Los Angeles
Is that cats like
Is that
Did the post if they broke that story
Yeah I find that might have been for a Time
Recognizing exactly what he's going to bring to Piers Morgan show
Be a big thing because we're
Heaven is going to be clips of it everywhere
Describing Pierce's Morgan
Does being like
He's going to have that fights tickets
Motive
Bright
The transparent
Motive
The Illinois State
At this point is considering a bill
How's it going
Has heeded the warnings
Core and
Covers the story
Perhaps the most
Ouija
Looks like
Turner's semi-auto
Like you do with all other is no moderate Islam all Islam inside
What are we going to what are we playing this game
Stream idiolect Illinois
And then they're going to let you know when they won't turn in their guns
I mean this is just I can't
Simulation of that extreme
Gun grab paranoia
Not not not with you
But not with his ID
Hey once Illinois
Outlaws everything but Bowl tax
Right then you know North Carolina
Because North Carolina does everything that Illinois.
And what's North Carolina's so goes the south Florida
We all know California is
Ripped away from the United
States by Massive earthquake
In the next hour
Is an ounce
There's going to be checkpoints permanent all over the place
Machine Gun Nest
Terminus
Checkpoints
Martial law
Fallujah
7 years on
You know I wouldn't to the Machine Gun Nest checkpoints in Fallujah control in the United States
Afraid afraid
The Berlin Wall over every Highway every hundred
Miles will be
Giant
Yeah
I think Cliff is only worthwhile to demonstrate like how stupid
So much of the stuff
He says around
Cockamamie nonsense
The very idea of it
And that the mainstream media
Announcing
These checkpoints
It's absurd
And the way that used
Announcing rather than reporting
So is touch one of those small symbols of
A year f****** full of s*** because yours
State mouth
The government
Who told them to announce the rollout
Play bazzi
Media covering the stuff in announcing
Announce announce its from there into like
Justifying a ton of news stories
An apocryphal stories
But he's been told by either
His coworkers
Or people who know his coworkers
Which is even more flimsy than making up news stories
Yes and this one is about
Employees girlfriend getting pulled over by the police
I don't believe most of the story
Girlfriend
Is a turn signal
Night
Number three
I just don't even know what to say anymore
Number one Hey listen
I don't use any of the cartels
Bright number 2
Drink-drive what am I
Don't look at the backseat there's a lot of open bottles of wild turkey
Three future and watch some of my live streams right
Appear to be quite drunk while driving an automobile
I mean it's weird because he's telling the story about Darren mcbreen's girlfriend in life
I mean if that did happen maybe she did swerve or something like that I don't know or I'm also willing to believe that it
It was over
Frisch's cop that was trying to meet a quota
You know acting
A little bit overzealous light
Alex
2 p.m.
I am also
Well you're almost like
He said the same thing
Alex is telling a story about somebody else realizes I don't have a full grasp
The detail don't really know the story very well I don't listen to
My better make is about myself
Cuz I can like myself
I got three points I forgot the third one
I don't even know what to do
Cool
This next clip is just
An expression of the
The extremist
But he is
Putting into
Broderick around this time
Is it a Mountain Dew commercial
8 boards
Let me live wire.
Come close
Closest ER
Earlier you saying that the Illinois state senate
Going to pass this bill and then they're going to be shooting gun owners in
To do whenever one well
Say hooray
Well I'll be having a great old as an image into your listeners Minds based on
You know that is pretty f***** up
Because it will catalyze the reaction in some way
Weather
Is another Quest
But you can't control that
You can't control how your audience responds
Extreme message
You're putting out
That's irresponsible
Does Mexico play
I think is even worse
Because
It's not about what somebody
Going to do
It's what they're already
So you understand if you listen to this clip
It's not
Illinois
State Senate banning guns or anything like that
We're already at the
Be killing these blah blah
Right we're past that
And that is expressed in the patriotism but they're already
Killing you
Talking about John P holdren book
Eco science
He's not talking about like advocating for
We should or saying that
Eplan
To put sterilants in the water and stuff like that
It is a textbook about ecoscience
Yeah
There are things are like
People have said
This is an option
It's not discussed a deposit
Relevant context
Leads you to believe that
It is not a good idea
So
It's just bulshit he's taken out of context Passage
Just from textbooks
But he hasn't read the entirety of
I mean like
This is happening
They're killing us already
Like if you hear that sort of thing
You actually believed him
Why wouldn't
Makeup
F****** Splinter Cell
Why wouldn't you form a terrorist group against the government
They're trying to
But yeah after that
No it's a man has always been battling the shores dad's true
What's the difference
I meant
Will you take this as read a lot of
The time
Looking back
. we're like
Tensions are really high
In the country
In the aftermath
And there was that gun
Discussion that's going on about like
Jesus's
It's f***** up that this
It's happened before we know it's going to happen again
Tensions are high
Middle-of-the-road Arguments for being against
Gun control
Some people have middle-of-the-road argument
4 gun
Some people of impassioned Arguments for gun
Some people like Alex
Impassioned argument
Gun control
And when you're in that
That's sort of
Temp space
Bringing in stuff like this
Really
Really of danger
Because you
You introduce an idea of a Nexus 10
Threat that's outside of that discussion
Yeah and it's
I don't know I just put myself in the head space with someone who actually believe
That's what he said
I don't know how I would
Make a bomb or some
All his listeners would do that right
It doesn't seem like a far cry from what
He's hoping someone
First
It is kind of a tacit
Acknowledgement
From his listeners
None of what he's saying is
Is actually
True in that we don't see a s*** ton of these
Wars started you know like
There could be a lot of people like
Go to steps into trying
Plan something
Ornaments
I don't mean this in a bad way cuz I'm glad
It could possibly be
Maybe a lot of them were cowards
Maybe there are a lot of people who do believe
Don't have the
Whatever
It would be that way
45% of his listeners are too cowardly to build
45% a Eva's listeners
I've tried to build a bomb
And started about how I stopped about halfway
And then the final 10% have probably gone to a pizza place and shut up
Space on your tablet
I found I found an all too much
Search McCobb humor in
When he says that America's
Do the most f*****-up
Because of all the
Like immediately after
Sandy Hook
There's a double entendre there
Huntingtown
Agreed
That's
Piece of decoration on your
We get back now Alex tells another story that I
Think is accurate
About another one of his employees
Having a run-in with
The police
Shout
Christmas
Yeah I think there's some details missing from that story
I think there's a
Modifier Miss
Missing between
Wi to
They want to stick needles in
What do you talk about is that there are some
Refuse take a breathalyzer
Refuse to do the test
Then they came
Force you to give blood
Part of the reason for that
That it will maintain it will retain as evidence
Whatever and you have not
If they have a reasonable suspicion that you're drunk
Timestamp
Yeah don't do that
Because I think the police had a long enough time we're drunk drivers
Kind of realized they could work things out and their blood alcohol content
Before they can do any kind of test
There is no
The proof of
The underlying
I'm not saying it's a good thing
But that's the rationale for why they do it
I don't know what's going on
The story about his employee
But I don't believe
Story
Know if I understand correctly
She was driving
There are people in the car may have been drunk
Who may have been drunk
May not have been drunk
Will never know
While she was driving
Herself completely sober driving complete
No red flags
They are pulled over by the cops
The cops go in there
And they charge they say out loud they're charging
Who are not driving with a DWI
I think it's the only way
But don't
The people who were in the car with
Really f***** up
And then the police were like
We got to
You know somebody's got to do something there's so much
Smell whiskey
Flashlight
And she gets really from dads
We need to take you
Station
Give you a breathalyzer
Charged
Why
But there's no way that
The story makes sense
But you can end up
Like with the police
If you don't
I'm not
I don't necessarily notorious for
Just dropping stuff
That's not really what I mean
Notorious for doing that
Okay we're going to have to
Come on
If you're pulled over for DUI and you're not
Drunk
You're not going to end
Getting truck
Unless you're addicted weekdays you might want
Got pulled over for
Brother
Do then
Yes they were not because the underlying charge wasn't real.
The cops
I wish we lived in that world fight
We don't so
Bright earlier brought up the idea of
These checks
Set up
Great
Piece of news to back it up some
Trevino
San Antonio Express-News reports
Officers
I'm driving
That's something
He's pretending he's reading an article about how is put into place
The next step after this without it
Is Machine Gun protected Fallujah style blockade
Problem is
This article is quoting from is about
Police Department asking for permission
Sobriety checkpoints
It has no indication that they got permission to do it
Also the local story out of San Antonio includes a ton of information that Alex
He forgets dementia
Reporting
For instance as of 2012 texts one of only 12 country
They didn't offer
Police Department's the option of setting up to you I checked
Texas consistently at the top of the rankings for most drunk driving related
And most drunk driving related deaths
I don't think
Things are related at all
It's a hugely popular state so it doesn't generally come in at number one on those list
That that breakdown
Fatality rate
It's right pretty much all the time is Wyoming
Also doesn't allowed
Conductor you I check
The US Supreme Court has decided the checkpoints are constitutionally allowed provided that they serve
Put in a requisition for your
Machine gun
True
Has to be paperwork
Those the absolute right to decide that whether or not
Adductors checkpoint
Within the state borders
And Texas
However
That doesn't stop them from checking up setting up checkpoints near the
Not on the border but near the border trying to catch undocumented immigrants
In September twenty
An article in the Houston Chronicle from December to
13 discusses
DPS
Hoping their use of checkpoints in the Rio Grande Valley where they were being
People's immigration status
Which would be against Texas law
The police department claimed that they had
Completely different
Very legitimate law enforcement
To which they were told you got to stop
I will be very
Route to take on this
My gut tells me he was
Super camps
I imagine
Kind of ignored it
Maybe not a store
But whatever the case
Antonio what is the set-up whenever setup
For more than a decade the legislature has rejected proposals to allow a roadside checkpoint
Which typically Target drunk driver
During the last legislative session
San Antonio
Police chief Antonio Trevino
Urged a committee of lawmakers
To allow permanent sobriety checkpoint
Do you read that it's very clear that
Did not allowed
Afraid of
Release it didn't happen until about a year later I have to accept
Recorded specifically used to Target immigrants
Richfield
Inconsistent
His world
Resistant to the DUI
If
Citrus like if you
Analogy to it would be
Stop
Program
In New York you know
Innocent people and they're just looking for various there is a possibility of
Abuse up the the stop for sure
Could I have some
Because in Missouri
There were
DUI checkpoint
A lot of the time when I was a young
I had a lot of friends
In the car and stuff like that
You know that there were
You would call or text all your friends be like
Of course of course
Speed traps
And stuff like that
Like going to the Boonville
They gives directions
Live updating
Traffic directions
They also include DUI checkpoints
It's on there
Are there apps
That's no good
You find alternate routes around
Warnings of the
The pop-up one of course
Casino
Was Notorious for
They had a lower
But you're coming off
People driving drunk coming out of the
Casino everybody knew it
Didn't know
You
If you're not drunk
They'll just let you off with a warning if you are
We're going to get arrested
That I kind of don't
The checkpoint is there too
Catch people who
Drunk driving
But if you
You're going to use a
Less Traveled Road
And that's going to buy
Statistical necessity
Lead to
Fewer people
Maybe you're going to get into an accident but at least it's just f****** you you know there are some studies
I was able to find
Did make
Reclaim
Finding
That put in a DUI check
Practice with
Related
Went down like to
Proof that these checks
Did and that is because of
Kind of what you brought up
The idea of going down another road while you're drunk cuz you know there's a checkpoint over here
Doesn't make that driving less intrinsically dangerous of course
You could still I don't know go into someone's front yard
Intuit
Because the last busy Street
You could hit them pretty easily
Yeah the odds
Making a bigger
Wreck on those sites
Favoring over where the
Blockade is
The numbers
Plies
Regardless no matter what
There's I think
American history is boring
You pretty accurate
You're not going to stop people from driving
That is not going to
No matter how many mothers
You know if you can do if you can take as many
Steps to minimize the
Damaged causes
Because you know that
It's going to be an issue
Then
Secondhand smoke
You people are going to smoke but you shouldn't do it in a
The numbers
It. It does
Risk aversion
Or minimizing
But I'm not sometimes
You can hope for
I don't know I don't know it's a little bit of a little ambivalent
How I feel about it
Now it starts
Extra
Complain about Hospital
But
The conclusions that he makes with those credits
What's going on
Hospital
So
I think it is criticism it's not what he's saying but I think it's criticism that the sort of the healthcare
Business
System as a whole
Does absolutely speed on for
People under all of the uninsured
You get it out like I don't know you fall down and break your leg accidentally you can't get anywhere in ambulance come to pick you up your f***
For years because of how much of that ambulance ride cost you any of the emergency room
Your f***
Yes
Fair criticism Alex
A grade not going to help
Situation
Square diamond rings and necklaces
Don't think it's going to help you
That's a child's understanding
Ohio like
Being poor you get f***** by Hospital
I will give you this.
Or the idea of like you got to go to the hospital
A f*** out of here
Body swap
Also like the idea of
You got to go to the rich hospital cuz they're not speaking off them in there is also
But again it is very unfair and cruel.
Like
Oh yeah
We could go with it
As the kids say
Grandma just had a stroke
And she's been in the hospital for
Forever and now according to
According to the rules of her insurance or something like that if she's not showing
Consistent Improvement literally every
She will have to go to
To this side
Nursing homes
Which is just going to bank
Like
She should have gone to
That's a good point
13 episode where he unblocked
What week is over diamond rings to pay for the Uber to get in the hospital cuz we couldn't afford the goddamn
Classic Gift of the Magi situation
Tragedy
Riddles for dumb reason
But he also
He has a story
He's telling about what
Employees
Who's
I guess there
Because he doesn't fly that it
His wife
Recently given birth
Stacy's
Situation with the
Kid
He's not specific
With the details
Also it's a third-hand
Personal story
So I'm not interested in that I'm going to leave all of it aside
And just try and get to the
Contact behind what he's talking about
And here he talks about how
The globalist
Hospitals
Or trying to kill pregnant women with Lexi
Okay
Cause a miscarriage or or or
Just bored
And a
Rashad
Okay
Is going to lead people to not get appropriate help
Yeah that is a very
Stupid
Message Judy putting out
And he was one of the reason
The issue here is the vaccines are dangerous for people who are pregnant but not all vaccines
Princeton any version of the inactivated flu virus vaccine
Same goes for the tetanus and
Pertussis
Vaccine
Tgap vaccine
Provided
The 27th
Pregnancy
Conversely the MMR and chicken pox vaccines have the
The potential to be very
Because they contain live virus
Anybody in Phoenix
Respond differently
Then
Non live virus vaccines
Beyond that
There are other variables that come into play
Primarily related to the mother's medical history
If you have a history of chronic liver disease
He's a doctor might recommend getting a
Titus B vaccine
There's a lot of variables
If a person works
Generally risks are kept
To a minimum
Relying on
His audience just accept his argument
Purely based on Steve
He's pretending that all vaccines have the same
Does nonsense
He's further pretend
A vaccine
Constantly being
So possibly one that was unsafe to give
To someone during pregnancy
Years back
Now is
Because of developments are indeed
Dodo sorsa
Everybody knows
Ever
That's why something that we
Which is that we had roughly 100 years
Before climate change would kill
On account of
That's Medical gaslighter
I mean
Clear-cut absolutely
Get vaccines and now they want to give him vaccine
Not deal
Extemporize
Details that surround
Contacts
Of Medical Care like
It's absurd
It's that it's very
Structure of
What
Say eggs are good for us
And then they say they've got too much cholesterol
Figure it out
Right it does have that without the attempt
Did a joke instead you're just a whooping cough outbreak
So in the next Place Alex
Gets around 2
And this is where it really did show take say
I mean
It's basically like someone driving drunk
It may just take a swerve off of
Okay
Perception
Definition of gaslighting
And that is the definition exist within the info
Remember that
So it is next Club Alex describes has this
Beginning a 2013
Because of
Gun grab
His entire career
Unfortunately our worst analysis is coming true the worst-case scenario is now in full
That is inappropriate cuz
Is that more folks
Serious time in my 17 years old
Scared what about
Beginning of his career was around when Oklahoma City
Write like what about
You undersell
Those other very serious
Things in your career
You are just afraid
Of this person
Is Merida's better
So his his death
Gaslighting
Explode people
Memories and make them
They aren't real
Is fully demonstrated
This is the most important time in my career
Play definition
Perception
Okay well okay
According to the textbook
Yes everything that Alex Jones is
Career
Just trust your memory isn't 911
The thing that you put your career on and is when
Global
No that isn't that more serious
Illinois state
What's 9/11
Stop it
Right now this gun control bill
Fine this next one
Much worse
Information is presented
Please read the caption definition again
Wow
So
That's a that's a lot to remember the vinegar want
These drills was done without telling anybody
National news picked it up and the entire country was like
What the f*** are you doing I don't know if that's true but if it was it's not
What we're talkin about
Covered it already supposed to say Alex's
Although it is funny
The funny farm
About it
I would spend more time on that one but the last I think I'll
Call lava
The last
So I thought I'd look into that
Alex's asserting that there were drills were people in masks were marching people out there were going to be executed
I'm not telling him that
Which is why people let people having break
Efukt up
What else is actually referring to the helicopter exercise
Military
Minneapolis August 2012
It's something that they from time-to-time to Urban Center
Spokespeople commented on how it's important for their training
Karaoke's exercises in unfamiliar areas
The pilots could do a little bit of improvisational navigation
One time when I worked at Groupon the helicopter training exercise downtown Chicago
But I think it was
Constituted
Like you're in this high-rise building and there's helicopters that are like
Going by pretty close to like your window lever
For sure
Why we get 5 minutes
You know what the swing
Everybody everybody
Superman all the all the time
The Star Tribune article about witches
The primary source
Infowars article about it
Tastes like
Three-quarters the article
And calls it his reporting
People in Black Mass
No mention of people having breakdowns
The closest Conn's is saying that
People who saw the helicopters thought they were and kind of annoying
The article doesn't mention
Unimportant part does
Over-reporting
Spinosaurus
F*** it was so loud
The article does mention some on-the-ground exercises
Carried out as part of the
As well points out that the bad guys
Civilians pay by special operation
Play the
No one involved was unaware that it was a
There's no indication that
Even happened away Alex's
And even if they did no one is aware unaware of what was going on
Quite literally this is Alex gaslighting his audience ironically in the middle of accusing his enemies of
Being Gaslight
Now I will say
Mistake of calling everyday
Hangout putting it out in the open
There is dumb
Concern
Give the public enough
Advance
And I accept
There's some argument
Could be made there about whether or not that
When I worked at Groupon there was no advance
Warning
Flyby are wrong
Or anything
And I didn't even understand why they were
You read these articles are talking
I like the idea of
This landscape is unfamiliar it's help
Alright I get what you doing
Also the military spokesman in this article who is
The interview explained
The date formally give
Three days notice about these sorts of drill
Do they found it became a little bit of a spectator sport
We're people would come out in large groups to Choppers flying overhead
And that had the potential to introduce serious.
Military helicopters were going to be flying over
You are cuz they're solo flying you introduced the risk of someone throwing a rock acting like that
Right
Course not everybody but you has like two million people in Chicago or whatever
But they could throw a flare as a helicopter make
.
Bad variable
Now don't try and shoot it down
Does the danger that
People ahead of time
Justify not
Doing it to
Begin with
I don't know
And I think there's a legitimate conversation to have there but it's not the conversation Alex's happen
Execution
Haha sorry it's a drill
Sorry.
That's nonsense
That's crazy
What's gaslighting
Definition
I'm back from break
This is one of the
4 Main
Comes back from
To self with the truth it is time for you to choose a side your list
Alex Jones
That's gaslighting
Gaslighting people truth absolutely
I know that he doesn't
Structure of this show is halfway to get Sadia is insane
F****** thing is all that
I just want you to play each clip and then afterwards play the definition of gaslighting
We might as we're what we might as well be there like the fact that he has the definition of gas like that he's read
On his own f****** show
That's damning clip if there ever was
Like I would
Careercert
The last
Cover
Dating back to the
Alex has been really mad.
The globalist
Eugenicist
He's very against
To some of the Eugenics argument
Don't do it
Population
Yeah
Symptoms
Where we going
That's the
I mean there's nothing truer than I should
Eugenics is good
But boy I don't want to be specific about that
Fireman
Isn't he for eugenics
Against the globalist
Perception
Is
Against
People down
That's
Diversion
Is that full throated lie against but I've never ever
Say
Some of the Eugenics argument is
Richards f*****
Yeah that's weird
Gaslighting
Episode Alex starts taking calls
From Obama support
He wants to do it too
Clown auntie
Never work
Because Obama supporters don't
Listen to his
Obama supporter
Just to get on the air
And that happened what is it called
Was this guy who
Joking
About being Obama
Everybody
This guy is actually making a serious
Deranged
So that's the first call
That's the first Call of Duty
Nothing worth really listening
You basically
Keep a call from the station
One of these
Owner Runner
But someone is it is a filly
We're going to keep you on our stage
No
Oh okay
He actually has
Ideas
Ferragamo is not eligible
Will be the president
But in order to qualify to be a candidate for the United States president
To be the president
You have to have
Natural
Born
Citizen
Voltaren
According to the United
Nations
Where is he really from
It's only a distraction because guys
Started
Credibly races
Conspiracy theories about
I don't care
Do you know how many presidents would not be eligible for the presidency
Let's just go if that was in the Constitution
There is a natural born citizen
The time of the Constitution
Like a workaround for the early presidents
I'm stuff like that
Both parents had to be
Oh yeah
But I wanted to I left equipment for a reason
And that's cuz I wanted to tell you about how I started reading a little bit about Obama's dad Barack Obama
And I found out that Obama's childhood home was located at
25 11th Avenue in Honolulu Hawaii
That's about five blocks from the corner of 8th and Harding
In the house
We both lived
Mookie
Ebi neighborhood in Hawaii like it's very close
I've a hundred percent
Around where Obama's when I was a child
Well your home your home was haunted of course by the ghost of
There's a lot of really weird parallels
Between my life and Obama
Emma's life and if Alex really wanted to I would love it
If you tried to spend a Funko
Conspiracy out of
Red Cross child I lived a couple blocks from Obama's child
At home
How old is
How old are you
Doesn't work out quite well
But my dad was at Harvard at the same time
Barack Obama
Was at Harvard
Then later
We moved to Honolulu
East-West Center
Okay I'll shoot of University
Be quiet
Obama was also at the
Think about all these connections a mile
I don't know what you want to do but do something with that
The greatest reveal of all time
It started podcast with an a******
In all of our photos
Regression software
Got me this nice beard and all of a sudden I'm doing podcast
I got that very insulting and so now here we are
Somehow that I
Involved
That you're that you're
Here's the thing
We ever guess
What the actual
Result
But I want to know why
How old
Filtered fight
Yeah those little factoid
Very near each other in our childhood home
At different times
But the same neighborhood very close
Talk to each other
My dad was at both Harvard and East-West Center at the same time is Obama
2 something
That does sound like an internet
And then it auto-generate Seca
Conspiracy theory based around
More literal fact
So many others
These pieces of information
You were at Harvard MBA
Remember
Smelling sulfur
So I just call her
Radio affiliate goes on
Cuz he like
Your parents need to
Naturalized citizen
For natural born citizen
It's not
Absolutely
For a call
To say
But it's f***** up with your Alex agree with
The caller as if like yes I know this to be
True
It is absolutely
Yeah I know it is said that the laws are not changed you have to be a natural born citizen or your parents at least have to be
Naturalized citizens
Yes
Both of them
It's in the Constitution
Royal auto change
Can try Dilaudid
Is the
Whatever
Which is fine but all of it
Thanos it's not real
I like
It's next level s*** there's nothing here that isn't like emotionally manipulative and
Abusive
So I mean like
Liberty
Freedom-loving
The last thing you want
Unless you're a propagandist
And then the first
If you're a propaganda
What you want to Gaslight your audience
It's about his
What is propaganda
What's the weather
He's going to Define propaganda
So wouldn't he using the definition of
No he
Define propaganda
Defies reality
Information
Propaganda
Real
First of all have you ever heard the terms White
Black and grey propaganda
So
Have you heard the terms white gray and black before
Supremacist
From Carrie cast
Probably heard some of that stuff
She does have the sort of like light and dark
Dichotomy
Light dark
Whatever the case
Not in reality
What she does do great propaganda but only for the gray
Propaganda is not
Information used
To get something
Done
That isn't
Income
Definition of propaganda
The Great Wave
Yeah
And to tell your audience like what I do is wipe
Propaganda
Providing proper
Gaslighting
Because if
If you're if you're there
If you're at the situation where propaganda is so nebulously
Not Define
Has to be literally
Anything to do
And then you
Create these
Substance
The propaganda
You're setting yourself up
As a white propaganda
And because your definition
The propaganda is saying something
Things to do anything
Everybody else who is not saying the same thing
Or grape
Conception of
The property
Because Fifty Shades of Grey
Swell
I showed you
That crime rates
And he's implying there's a causal relationship
Ship there where is there may not be
And based on his example
So you're actually a great prophet
Conception
And all this doesn't matter you're a f****** propagandist
Yeah I know what really
People telling
Youfact
Like that's not
Information is not propaganda
Even he wasn't like
Who actually shows up on this episode
You have something to say about Sandy Hook
Evil
Denotes like beds
Psych meds
Jerome f****** course
Psych meds psych meds
Come in with something really responsive
And it was just like
Yeah this is
This is an unfair a death
Propaganda
Passing it off on your body
This way
Absolutely
Right
From this lady
Who is like
In favor of Obama but I need you to understand I was wrong
Paul supporter
But as Ron Paul was unable to win the election
Paul Ryan
They are clearly going to take away women's rights
They're going to infringe on my right
So what the f*** am I supposed to do
I went with Obama
Like what
She is made the first
Reasonable
I can remember on this vodka
Like legitimately
I cannot think of any more reasonable
Like I said it's still an Infowars Ian are arguing
It's still like a
I don't trust you it's not Romney is a
Boardman
Who's going to take my uterus and force me to make babies
It's not even
Ron Paul
Be better
Right
The closest
Call
Sort of moving the goalposts
Completely unrelated argument
And then finally the collar
Get sick and tired of it
The problem
In America
Alex I want to say something controversial and I don't care if it gets everyone mad but I'm going to say to me the reason this country is going
You know where is because
Old white man who are running the Senate and Congress
We have what 1% of Mexican and it said and black people that are in the congress senate
Old man running the country suspended
You are
Right there alone is
Crazy lady
Saucer
Very depressed
And is she staying
Of course not
The answer is of course not
Respondeat office station
I'll still go along with you
Whatever
The Senate releases demographic information about every single session
This was the
12th Congress
Here's the actual breakdown of it
16.8% of Congress were women in 2012
With a total of 91 persons elected
17 Fillmore in the Sun
Only 81
Congress rap
African American
Not a single one of them in the Sun
There were literally more radio talk show host seven African Americans in the Senate
There are more former astronaut than African American
Former comedian
Then African Americans in the Senate
And 112th session
Cuz I'll bring it
Congress was fixed
2.2
Which is considerably higher than regular
Congress was overwhelmingly
This woman is not far off from scribing the reality that
Accurate
She says that there was a 1% representation of a
African Americans
Congress and then
She says the Senate
Alex talks over her as she says
And the number is actually zero for
96% of
And 82% of
The house
Nothing about the demographics
Congress comes
Even close to matching the demographics
The United States
The point that she's making
Incredibly valve
Interview starts obfuscating
I move the goalposts change the argument
She's actually making
What you see happened
So crazy
Yeah
Alex
Accuses her of what
The Mexican
Congress
To replace archon
Is that what you want
Basically Define
Is gas-lighting her
Is a puppet
Alec we can agree to disagree
No I'm not
I think we should start all over.
You heard him say should we do
She says no
And then he implies that she said
We should bring all these
I was just making that up
This is gas-lighting
Is gas-lighting is audience
Gaslighting
Remember when you said that
It's insane
This is
Program yeah it is it is really
It's to the point
Be careful
We have to also
And you see it everywhere
Everywhere
Because no matter how strong your will is
You are going to have a unless you're psychopath
You're going to have that moment where you like
Wait
Am I crazy
Guess what is that constant like
Drivers should be
Brought up I don't remember
I don't like to know the old white dude
I am in the car
Pictures of Fair Credit
Did he come back and talk to me
Switch the Meg
I don't remember saying
But I you know what
This is gotten a little heated
Brakes
Controls the audience think
Yeah
Hit something
Another
Pro Obama collar
This guy really is
Anti-republican
Which is fine
I don't think it's
If the premise Alex wanted
Yeah but it's what he
It's not the premise you introduced but it's exactly what he wasn't
Let's go ahead and
Fox
Alex I support Obama because I hate the Republicans so much because
The Tenth Amendment
They could have been in the office they could have ran away with the election all they had to do was backup
17 States
Exercise the 10th Amendment
Medical cannabis and
Use cannabis.
Oh it's party to cannabis for industry
Punjab
Are sections of broadcast
No s***
Is your college generally suck
And this guy isn't Pro
Switch difference
This is
Pathetic
Like terms
Also he doesn't
Well I mean
I like that I like
Dave seems like
Sure
I just like his I just like slow Meandering tone
Hurried
Yeah
It is what it is
Is that called
Was that the idea
Legalizing drugs
Whether it's for
Purposes
Clothing and what-have-you
Great
Great if you're a libertarian
That everybody should
These things
Personal Liberty
So that makes this next quick
Really hard
If you imagine that
Libertarian
Cuz I think this wise
Counter to libertarian
A big supporter
A drug decriminalization
No that's not a side issue
I think a Libertarian position on
Maximize
If you drink
A ton of booze
You will poison
Yourself
Everyone knows that this is very clear
You have
Is a personal choice
Is what alcohol
Market to dictate how much
Rizknows
Local
Or federal government that should be able to the business
Between Boos salary
Who's buyers
Should be just because it's a danger to you doesn't mean
Have access to
You are an adult you were a free man
You have the choices in front of you
To poison yourself
It has nothing to do with who sold it to you
The fact that Alex is like
Micro
Managing isn't
Local
As opposed to like the federal government
Libertarian
A hundred percent VA
You drink yourself
To death no one else is responsible but you
You did that you chose to do that
If Subway
Yeah
In line with
Annie
Libertarian thought that I've ever coming
Incontact
I've never heard that
Nanny State put local level
Yeah
I don't I don't know that to be a robust
Part of libertarian
Thought but for being over-served
I can tell you
Generally speaking
They were right
The entire time
Different conversation.
You're a Libertarian should have the wherewithal to be like
That one was on me
You get you get this route
I don't want to do the government over my
Free booze
Not libertarian
You're in a certain state
You are impaired
And you don't know
The extent of what you're taking a
With in literature
Very hard line they like absolute
From everything I've
Is very
Very much
Dry
Which propaganda
Absolutely.
To the dark side.
It's very weird
Yeah
Expect that
But I did
Confirm
Constitutionalist
Compared to the average
More
Helpless
Person who
What Democrats do
Say that you're above the right light
Republican
Regret
It's real hard to
Have that
Your self-perception
Democrats are almost not people
I don't like them cuz they're not extreme enough
Yeah
That's not good
I am literally said Republicans are real
Yeah
I mean it's it's it's it's
The energy
Of the libertarian
What are you
Exploit
Is for the rich
Probably a parcel of liked the idea that
Democrats are into
Generally
Civil Rights Act
Libertarian
Constitutionalist
Not right
So they soak up that enter date
Propaganda
To smallest
They find the Democrat
Policy set
Of position
Completely unacceptable
And so where do they go
They go to the Republican
The middle
Cuz they're not as overt
Know that.
Republic
Represents the best
Is that
Did surprise me
What time is it over
Graphic
Do you think there's
So it would you say that
Verse set of Republican voters on the
Less than
Like it doesn't it
And yet they represent
The best
It almost seems like you're trying
Whatever anyway
You remember Republicans being garbage
Allapattah
You remember
You hate Republicans
They do represent the best people do
Even though they're awful
And they're garbage people they represent her garbage historically
One final Obama
Supporter caller
Because this guy is
Really
F*** in Ark
And that is
I'm a business Traveler
I live in Canada
I'm all around I go all over the world most important things
I think of the United
Government
Whether your puppet or not
Instability
The table is a real sense of stability
And it really makes it
The big difference around the world
The places that I go to
It's really great to be able to come
Comebacks
It feels better coming in
There is a sense of
Steady Hand at the wheel
Let's if you want to litigate the Obama presidency we can go all day
We can do that that's no big
If you want to litigate Obama's stability his appearance of a stable presidency
You cannot
Even with these people like
Trump trying to make
Tsunami wave
Absolutely
Things moving
Of course
Obvious
Coccyx
For sure
But yet
The ability to
Did make a difference
Stability
Pretty good collar
Yeah
I gave him a
Because
I'm never going to
Given Alex Jones caller in a
Yeah I know
Just because
We have some high-quality colors
Potential
8 - caller
If Alex didn't talk over her
Cuz I think she had some other points
That's your
For every color
Not getting an egg
Because if you're is
She had the chance
But Alex talked over here literally everyone
The table is Addie
She had she had a B+ with what I heard
But I also have to
To accept that I could be
Free fantasy book
Alex tacos
I thought Mitt Romney was going to take my rights away and I couldn't have these Edwards
Right
I don't think there's any chance
That that was where she was going
Something else
Could have been like Federal Reserve
But you comported herself quite well
That guy was a really in
Call
I wish I would have
It really
Wasn't
Wasn't that
It was a it was Alex
And it's more important
After the call
Cuz Alex
Realizes he should have
This guy
Empty
He let too many good things
Come out
Right
And
DoubleDown
Episode 5
Smartworld empowering women
I want to be clear deposit slip for a second
This has nothing to do with anything that was discussed in that guy's call or
Jim talking about women being empowered or anything like that psychology
Example
Weird
Gaslight
Hollywood world Hollywood
We all know that so
Not as much as I used to
World concerts
Sky boxes
You're in trouble
Truman
Yeah that one
True.
You do
Like this is crazy
Also possible that
Even as good as investigator in journalist
What does Jon Ronson
There's a pretty good chance
Be impossible to find a person
Because they don't
Astoria
I'm sorry first episode
I wanted more out of this episode
R-Truth
Is beginning 2013
And there's not enough
Dismiss
Or just too much
The idea of a bottle episode
Just done
About Alex
Discovering the
The concept of gaslighting
And then proceeding to Gaslight at every possible turn
I think there's a pretty strong humor and irony
I needed that
But at the same time it really doesn't help us understand
Real pile of s***
It's almost
Cute
A cute the word I would describe it seems like him
It could be kind of ship
Just it's like it's like somebody who turned the page on the calendar and realized that it is
Oh my God I got can't wait to tell you all about that
Yeah we got it
It's okay and then he goes to the next
Things they didn't do in the past and pretend
They didn't hold them accountable
For things that they didn't do
I've always known fighting means and you know that I have always
And have for forever
Today on my word of the day calendar
I don't know
It is what it is
You know what
It's
Always nice when we have
Candidates for people
Who technically probably have
These callers Wyoming
I feel like half the people in Wyoming
Have a murder charge
Yeah I don't know not funny
Probably just
That lady
Doing good
You could go to the Twitter
Technology underscore
You bet it is probably go to what's the other one
Committed crimes all over the place
Go home and tell your mother your Brilliance right there
We are on
Overcast
Libra
How I got over
Do feel like
You called it
Brought up how old
Tire Congress
Think she was on to some
We probably have
And
Based on John Ronson's reporting
Maybe didn't kill somebody or maybe it's a whole other
Almost
Terrifying
Imagine what he's done to people
Probably
Controlling
Alex