Alex
We're couple dudes like sit around with novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Jordans
Jordans
We are good wings
Grace of God and all of the
And supportive ARA are fine listeners weave
Studio recording
In order to get this.
Everybody out there
I was considering it if you don't if you run out of friends with cars and truck great option
It seems like your heart
I recommend
Wonder. They had more employees
Into guys
Nothing is a lie
Wild time for us to take off every time
Nothing ever happens one time
Like a Christmas
I don't even think that nothing important happened at all during the time that we're off
Every Kevin episode no no news happens
Out of the public sphere
There is a lot of stuff that probably in our best interest
To leave alone and ignore a lot of these things out of
Suicides of survivors of mass shootings
Coming to cover it anyway
I'm in some stuff is just kind of like I wish we could have covered it but who cares like chicken restaurant
Acting like assholes
All those things are really is Alex hijacking people's
Social media Presence by going into the spaces that they're in
And forcing them to make videos of him that is free promotion
And all that their social media
Barrel through any other Sensational propaganda
Admission to everybody
Develops into other things
We have one
That has happened in this time
That we've been away there we must cover
You know what I'm getting different reports for different sources on that I am not entirely sure
Don't want to judge him too much because I've moved into the pictures yet
Glass houses stones
It's a real shame
I'm going to have to get dentures
Becoming a medical truther
What we have to talk about today Jordan is that was forced to sit down and give a three-hour deposition
In his Sandy Hook defamation lawsuit
And some
The media largely speaking is getting a number of the wrong messages
As we go along
It would be great and I would enjoy to get back to business giving a shout-out a couple of
New governor supporting a shout
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk thank you so much
Perhaps
Special with the move there was so many
Unexpected things that popped up in terms of household expenses
And out of nowhere this person came through and die
I must say Keith asked the Third
You are now a raptor princess
Start until you're brilliant someone sodomites
Has a Korean
I don't want Jesus Christ
Find know how to read
Abused
Joseph Stalin
Sound level you can only imagine
Sports
We appreciate it please
For this for so long
Losing my mind
That's
First
Okay okay I will
Alright buddy
You keep up
I'm so here's where we're going to start remember
Clip his first clip that were starting
It applies to everything that we here
For the rest of this episode
Do solemnly swear that the testimony about table
He is sworn in this is this is all in this is all legally actionable from here on out
The interesting thing
Forget going there's an important point I need to make about what we're going to listen to and the fact that Alex is sworn in
This is the deposition that Alex is being made to sit in a question about regarding his
Is very important
Although we just heard him be sworn in the beginning of the episode
Perjury is a very different thing in civil cases Ben it isn't criminal cases
In civil cases there's no formal penalty for lying in a deposition which Alex absolutely does multiple times
3 hour session that he sits for
Punishment for perjury in a civil case would require winning the case and then after the fact have your lawyer filed Criminal
Charges for the perjury charge
The best of prosecution could really help for within this case
Is the demonstrated for outright to show evidence
Cross-examination
Even then the only consequence would be the court view Hangouts as an unreliable Witness
Which would be the result of him just answering any questions without being a
Play
Alex knows best
His lawyers know that
So they really know that there's no real Stakes here
The only benefit of something like this comes from the public seeing it
Which is why I'm very glad that this deposition got posted online by the law firm
There's a great deal of value for our purposes
MC Hammer and try to pretend he knows anything about what he's talking about but ultimately
Gold value
In this I suspect
Again I'm not a lawyer but from everything I've been able to tell
This civil consequences for perjury are not
That very real
America's Civil Justice as somebody who is recently
Real person
Lawyer questions and stuff like that
VIP no lawyers don't have any ideas about that
The idea that this is like a huge blind spot of the legal system
It's okay it's kind of knows that he doesn't have to give a f*** you can sleep walk through this
Or anything like that
It would require so much
I think you could in the actual trial but not in the deposition
Who cares
I need to give a little bit of a shake of the finger also
Do the general need it
Media as I alluded to a minute ago
For The Listener to use actually shaking his
Finger wag
In the wake of this deposition being posted I saw a large number of headlines are being circulated that had to do without
Conspiracies
And it's recording the story
Alex does use the word psychosis in a conversation about his journey as a conspiracy theorist
But if you listen to the context
It's very clear that you speaking metaphorically and Loosely about his mind state
Visa Vie his distrust of media sources
The entire quote-unquote
Psychosis narrative boils down to this we're about to hear which is a little over like a minute-long
Literally the last few minutes of the three-hour deposition
So here is what everybody is making headlines out of
And I would argue that that is a great disservice first of all
To the other stuff that's in this and the fact that they're kind of playing fast and loose and it just
Helps him
People lost
Remind myself
So obviously I think it's as a pundit
That you're my opinion Champion long
Nothing whatever wrong consciously hurt
Process
Grow up
Rockwall Texas watching the police steal drugs and then conduct anti-drug program school I think that shouldn't
The police in general
And I was very fortunate to like Roper more things
Krishna process
I'm just saying that the trauma
The corporation's lying so much
Send everything again
I like a child his parents watch him over and over again will pretty soon I don't know what
So what's up long before these lawsuits I said that
I thought everything was it
Conspiracy
That mask
Opportunities
That's right
Hawaiian
But at the same time is the most sensible thing
Listen to so much Alex
Says make sense to me because I'm like audit like I have no
Because of use the word psychosis so that everybody all the headlines are
Psychosis
You listen to what you say
Pattern of behavior that got into where
I think
As I got older and I started more I realized
Default position is not a good way to operate
Now he's lying about absolute perception is not
That's not descriptive of like a mental psychosis or anything like that it's it's
Because you right
Finally admitting that he's crazy
But that was actually a lucid statement very much so looking back on it
Arrow
And we spoke very
Irresponsible suspicions that Alex had something going on with him on a neurological level
I just to see now to operate for so long and know that reporting that snippet of his conversation as quote Alex
Is literally playing into Alex's hand and serves to validate his narratives about media persecution against them
I'm pretty disappointed that coverage
Especially considering there's a whole lot of stuff in here that would have made great headline
You could even make quick fade out of it
Imma probably going to try throughout this to make quick pay
Amen to this proceeding
Now let's get down to it
In a linear fashion because it comes from the m
Of the things
More could be the media watch the first 5 minutes
And then skipped
Possible absolutely no judgment
Mark Richards he's on YouTube now will be coming soon
The prosecutor did a very admirable job
He did the best he could but ultimately in situation like this there isn't really a win
But he comes as close as anyone can
And I do admire that on some level.
And then Alex
That does his first big lie of the deposition
Claim that I started controversy
This is not
I read that correctly
Finessin it says before I ever publicly commented
On any issues relating to Sandy Hook
I learned that others were
Do I have no affiliation
Or relationship
Had already posted articles
Relationship had already posted articles online
Questioning
So there were a variety of articles in YouTube videos
How long is it to ritacca
I don't know I don't answer incorrectly
Longer
Yeah
Is Alex
A couple days
He was out there on his show
That sort of thing so
All these all these YouTube videos
But that's his way of trying to dodge responsibility
About that idea to get to this kind of idea
And actually I think from are looking back on it perceptions of what is accurate
Pictures of Interest there's a base
Of accuracy and what he's about to say about what he did after Sandy Hook
He's just forgotten the other stuff
But he has to say
Sandy Hook
Media
Hakufu shootings Wisconsin cop
Psychic vampires
Body mass shootings
Shut the first episode
7 years ago
Springleaf
Firestorm internet's like no
This is a Prozac
This isn't video games like I was saying I thought like others
This was
Some type of
Series
So the part that's realism focus on
So there's like 15 minutes
Narrative towards that
I could see how he could look back on that.
I was mostly just talkin about gunship
Brett
It's an interesting like it's an interesting line cuz I can't
But it is ludicrous to say like
I didn't also do the other stuff
Supposed
Like view his memory
How things go
Is that that's what he thinks actually happened
Because he doesn't
Remember or understand the parts of himself
They just pop out and then pop it just like
Oh that the whole thing was
That's why they come after the little aside part I think there's a good chance of that
I think they could explain most of his perception
How not to say perhaps
A good theory is Alex's defense
Let me know.
Throughout this entire proceeding deposition
Mr. Barnes and mr. Enoch Robert Barnes
Don't know they're two different barns
Alex in the deposition
Yeah he does a lot
But Mr Enoch is there and he's not supposed to talk
Because it's not a to lawyer deposition and he keeps talking and that becomes a big problem
Because he's trying to lead Alex
He's trying to like
Say things
Tennis player violations
How to Stonewall a little bit
But what is the defense that's being presented at the beginnings of it
In this clip right here
Mr. Jones this is a video mate,
Issues relating
And
Correct
Rewadix
If you wants to go Washington tire for our video
Connecticut
Argue about that
WrestleMania matters edited
I like this guy he's not
For real good lines throughout the course of this there was
Who's making that objection so it still appropriate within the content
But it's to the groundwork in establishing setup
These tapes are edited
Clear because his voice wasn't I couldn't hear Barnes voice terribly
Show the entire tape because you're showing is an edited down version right
Their defense is that if you watch the entire tape
It's going to exonerate
Text Alex
That nobody is going to watch the entire so either in the court everybody watches
Is the entire episode
He's going to claim that whatever do as you said you missed you could watch 3 hours and 59 minutes
But if you don't
Uno's that they are f*****
Contacts
Is that come up over and over and over again this idea of falling back on the idea that the tape is edited
In a little bit
The prosecutor was the first person
To call Sandy Hook a false flag
And then Alex pulled out his normal
You are the first person
To make about Sandy Hook
That's the truth
Text Tucker
We know that to be true
Yeah that's
Mr. Jones you said in your affidavit before you commented on it
Issues
Relating to Sandy Hook
You saw other things that other
That affidavit have
So we didn't just see you commented
That was callers calling
Totally had a bad day
There's no way to proceed forward cuz you can't
Rational reasonable world for everybody
And so yeah you're you're screwed
I will play every goddamn
We're going to have a year-long trial
Let's move on everybody
I might be unfair
The editing Clips together we heard earlier Alex
Quit
Media Matters made the derivatives together and and put out that clip
When is next clip
The prosecutor explained
Video Alex is a little bit like
Mr. Jones
That video you just saw
Are you talking
Were you talking about
Headed those pieces together
Was that you on the
Show me the video that for
4 hours
You going to do that for me
So in that video
Yes or no
You were commenting about
Videos
30 second clips
Well it kind of throws them off a little bit because you can't blame Media Matters not just like I did that I added of the videos
Exact problem position window
What are you do watch a show and a half of yours over it
I'll be so boring great I love right here
Abs
Need directions.
Eddie Alex Jones episodes
What were you thinking in that moment
Series of Bop videos
Got him so bad so I can complain about it
Is the idea that when Bill Clinton was being grilled by his sexual impropriety
What's your definition of
Have fun with semantico game
So charms me when he played
If a sex plug
Spring 2013
Text
You had gone from Siri
True just straight-up telling your audience
What is stage
That's good
Keeping way too much of this in the lawyer is like
I don't care what it says
Answered your question I'm talking about what
You said
It's a it's an insane situation
So there's a clip
Prosecutor plays where Alex says it's
He has a different critique which is just
Richard Jones I'm going to show you a clip from
April 13th Laura
Videoray
Yes that's me on the video
Understand
Starplex
Dismissive this lawyer is of Alex
Is this field of like
Dude you are not my first you like yourself
I've been doing this for a long time you idiot interesting dynamic
I was the same stuff that I was talking about
Who is a couple of points
And I think he has two angles of attack that will get to
Are there really good approaches to demonstrate about Alex
About what you said about Sandy Hook you can prove that case on the merits
He played a literal clipped him for that
But will you can use him as a tool for our other things that are also important
So in this next clip the prosecuting attorney plays
Literally didn't happen
You know that's great
From December 29th
Garden Plain up for me
Search Usain
Research
I know exactly what
Assertive
You do not need to be making suggestive objections about the cons
These are videos are highly
Oyster Bar
That's a great opinion
I don't understand why your opinion is irrelevant
?
Let's talk
Aldo
All-in-one record every objection to every piece of evidence
Zircon
Which
I was a dick
So they're going to stenographer comes in as I hate
You guys are making it really hard to type up
Sweet children
You know what it's an interesting dynamic because after she says that they are like all right let's get back on track
Text the first time
Shut up shut up
It's obvious that you're talkin objections are trying to leave Alex down the road that you wanted to go down
And that's not appropriate positions going
And it is how it's going. Supposed to be supposed to be able to
Right right
This is one of the first instances where prosecutor
Did ideas about the specific narrative that Alex pushed
And one of them is the idea that Alex is talking about how they the teachers and the police had the kids
Walking in circles at the school
And there's a fundamental problem with a narrative that Alex is pushing
Spelled out in this clip and we'll discuss it on the other end
No. This is dangerous
Is it dangerous when there's somebody shooting up
Yes
And so you would think
If
Proper procedure
Just look pretty weird doesn't it
But mr. Jones
You knew that wasn't School
You knew that
Right
Yes
First of all
And you've already chosen no mystery in October
And so I would appreciate it
Deposition
Let mr. Barn
Spoiler alert
That does not
Is a large
This was broadcast
So mr. Jones Mike West
Broadcast
You knew
Question
Skip this
Video of the
Mystery Duck we just watched it
Do you really think I edited his word over.
Appreciate if you kept quiet
You knew that one
Looks like two different shows together
Who is eclipse
From different episode
And the third clip involved
Footage from the firehouse people walking around
And Alex is saying that it's the school
It appears the Enoch is trying to clarify is
Is the video in the audio from the same episode
It absolutely
But in this next clip
He tries to take that little colonel
Prosecution
And if it's pretty f***** up
Megyn Kelly
Right
No mr. Bean
The witness
Deposition
Wear these all
And we we said that repeatedly
Your indignation
You are
Actually I got a question
So
Do you know that this is like listening to a this is an exasperated man
Just who's like
He knows what he's doing this is his job he's a professional this is what he does
And he is deposing a f****** live
Who has to a Tweedle Dee and Tweedle Dum for lawyers right
Is prosecutor
Sounds to me like he's looking at these guys talking is like
Prudential real quick
I'm guessing that he's probably dealt with them in the past he has some sort of like awareness
These guys aren't on the up-and-up
Some shady Tendencies and they're coming out here
Because
There is no point when they try to represent the idea that all of those clips came from the same episode
Absolutely not what they were
That's not what they're suggesting at all and they were very clear about that
You know your desperation
Give Alex some sort of cover to make similar arguments
As the deposition goes on
For the things that you were saying
Because these aren't things
Yep and so that's a problem
So now to the Firehouse issue
The reasoning that last clip it is a problem that Alex
It's saying that this is the school
Representing to his audience that it's the school
Is it in this next clip the prosecution
Rire evidence
The point his audience but it was the school
He had to have known it wasn't
Contacts
On the road
You're later
You showed your audience video
I talked for hours a day
I can't ever want to talk about sometimes a week ago
Can you go Kiss band in the aggregate less than one-tenth of 1% of what I cover
And
Smnm pouring over constantly
Preparation
Barry give me a headache
I just
What question are you answering
You're asking me about a bunch of how does someone answer
?
Put a bunch of pages
I can't answer you a question
Edwards
I'm asking you
The school
No that's not what I do
Okay alright
Defense lawyers when out-of-town
Go to the building learn his name lest he become a hero of some sort
I want to resist that Beto impulse or whatever
So he's not at all
Prosecutor
I would assume so I can comment
Little bit more about that firehouse video and how Alex was reporting on it as they're being
Around in a circle with their hands up
So
The prosecution plays video files leave the firehouse from a helicopter
Yeah the damning question to ask Alex
Let's
14th
2012 helicopter
Firehouse Subs
Elementary-age children
A talking about
None of those people have their hands up do they
Lassie the show sad Soldier complaining
Really cuz you were talking about it
Children
The people in there just throwing stuff up
Nicely done
I'm not sure about what
I was wrongly upset in the past
News reports that was relying on children
Going around with their hands up
The firehouse
Change my mind
Absolutely not true at all
Based on this
I love that is the
It was alive broadcast
And that the producers just play stopping any response to it
Okay no no no no.
It was a live broadcast
What's happening
Franklin
I would do that he looks pretty bad I think in terms of this
Anomaly
LOL almost immediate
Now there's another narrative and that is the idea that it's the story that the school
Who was closed
It was it was a dilapidated school there was mold everywhere
Conspiracy theories about this
That school has been dead for 15 years
Yeah that one was one of the ones that was like wow you guys are swinging for the fences with this
Very demonstrable
So the prosecution asked about that and his response is really interesting to me
I want to show you
First thing you admit now there are no emails between
This is almost 7 years old but I do believe that we wouldn't
There's always some news recovering
Or witness or doors or something so I can't answer that
Because I'm just memory
Troubadour
You just stuck
22nd
Hoops
You were saying that
So he goes on to email
Alondra show a video of the school after the shooting
Had to cut out that were there a redacted cuz it's like people blood all over the walls and stuff it shows in Normal
You noticed any any Elementary School
Does this look like a school that was shut down does this look like a school that is
Condemned
He's a bit look like it's a different pair
Brought up that Alex did push and he can't the scrutiny
Consistently on either
You know what you know it's someone else's fault or this video is out of context I can't comment on my post
Once that's not good enough
And yet remains is that first one the idea that it's someone else's fault
Once that is your only remaining
Avenue of self-defense
You're going to get pushed on it
And eventually you're going to have to discuss
Where did you get that information from
I thought was going to be he was going to
Just turns and points directly he was right there
Be straight up and upfront about it
You didn't know one way or the other
Right whether the school is open
Expert
We're the ones that professors and others that we're good standing
For the ones that we're really doing
These investigations and then I was
Some patients taking what they said
You just take what they said we trust
Has the national Safety expert
Incredible
Mr. Hobbit right
Can you send
Something in the neighborhood
Ocelot
You wouldn't agree with me the top manager
She seems very credible and put together earlier on
Educated about 4 years ago
Defamation that's a fair assessment there's a really interesting trends
Beware the prosecutor seems to be trying to get Alex to admit that Wolfgang halbig is crazy
Buyer admire the gumption
For the prosecutor he's like
Alright I'm going to do this deposition first
But you guys got to give me five bucks
If I get him to say that this guy is f****** crazy he gets him as far as cookie I think
Ebony set a lot of email
So I think that's that's going to set the stage for a lot of the rest of Alex's defense to come there
You still be a lot of videos
I should have not listened to him is even too far for it to go but it's kind of like it was him
That's it
So now we get into this next clip the first angle that I think
Is
The good attack on Alex
I admire this about this that the prosecutor and his approach
And that is to demonstrate that Alex has no idea what he's talking about
Because if you can do that idea that he knows anything
Yeah it doesn't have to be about Sandy Hook
To your full advantage
One thing to do with these narratives that he can just say like
Forwarded it
It's much more robots
When you bring an effusive information
That you should know about
And he doesn't
And in this first clip prosecutor talks about First Responders
The school
And Alex is
Put on his heels a little bit
Michigan's probably went on a break we were talking about the issue
Couple copies
I put in
Second one
Another FEMA visit Alex has a really slow reader read most of it I didn't get two number two
How many how many they were on break
They could have just kept going for him to read I think he said I'm.
There's a couple other times where you try to have him read while the camera is still on
But after 3
Yes I'm going to read that
Don't use your finger are you saying to is 5
At first glance
Bathroom
Sergeant Carlos skating
Maybe a paramedic
I agree
How to check for lice
The victim
Redacted
Florida
The back corner
I thought she
I started karaoke
You've never heard a start
Week
He didn't know what he did
Correct
It's again over 7 years I don't remember love this
Hibachi
Paramedics
What GMT is related to the building
Winning
That approach is really good
Because what it does is it demonstrates a piece of information that was available as of
Sometime in 2013 when Alex
Possibilities
Realities for us
If he did know about it that he intentionally lied about it
If you didn't know about it then it's clear that he didn't look into anything
Exact position that sort of choice about how he
Represent what he does
You can't make that choice
I think so
I'm just saying his lawyers
Instead of doing the same thing cuz that's not going to do any good
Maybe
Some kind of hero
Whatever whatever that circle is Alex
Right whatever
Yeah whatever opposite of telling him to round third cut off cut off
That's the first instance of this next clip
Alex's reporting about the idea
Hobbs Act
The birth certificates and death certificates
Or put under strict access to them
And this this again is another instance of
The other really good approach
That is Infowars process
Because that's something that seems like wow
How did you get to the things you report it
By illustrating diligent at all
Very good attack
The two attacks of you don't know what you're talkin about and you never check anything
Are very very Salient points
And I admire that being the approach
The first one which is you don't know what you're talkin about and it makes life we here
Anything you didn't do the basic
Steps you would need to report something
Can owner play eclipse of the moon mr. juice
February 12th 2015
November 8th
Highly edited
Send the context of
What did you do to confirm it
Objective
You don't have to speak
I like there's a little there's a little more of this clip but I really love that you can make all the
Fair enough
The fact they were sealed
How did you confirm that
I don't want to
Answer these things incorrectly so my memory
I remember
Steelcase ever and that was in the news that they're always lawsuit
And that
The records and reports
Blacked out
That's so I can't accurately answer off of edited
News reports of other people that were investigated
Ourselves
Sandy Hook
Thank you mr. Jones is an indication of I just got exactly what I wanted
Report on this
You're presenting as if you were reporting on nothing
He didn't answer that question
I think the long pause is the
About ordering death certificates or he's never done it tells me
Definitely
So if
Not knowing about the accounts of the First Responders is a great illustration of showing that Alex doesn't know s***
Write this next instance of it is
Beyond The Pale
This is something that I
Flavors are at Baskin-Robbins
I actually might not be able to answer that long time
No this is Elementary information
The idea that Alex is confused about this
He's really troubling
Bridget Jones I'm going to hand you a copy of what I have Mark
I don't remember
The timestamp 12 14 12
Don't know.
It is
That's real bad the feel this prosecutor get a little cocky
Feel him get a little get a little bit of
You might be a little more concerned
Cuz I don't think
Absolutely has no idea what it is
It would behoove you to know what date you're being strategic position it seems like the right thing to do
How do you reset yourself
Jethro
It was in the context of another narrative that I was his foot out that line of questioning
He was talking about that the prosecution was talking about had to do with Alex's story that you would tell about there
Being delivered immediately which is
Ready to go squirrel this
So in this next clip
The prosecutor lays out
When forethought is actually showed up
Doing so
I think he accidentally reveals that Alex doesn't know what date
The shooting happened on and he doesn't know what time of day it happened on
I don't think he knows anything about this
Car sitting at the front
I would imagine
Because if
Porta-Potty showing up
That's what the time is right there
130 right
That's not an hour
Pretty darn soon after
Is it
Is it maybe more like
4 hours
And I was going off of
What I believe was credited National School Safety person who been on national television programs as an expert
What's going on
No confirmation
Whatsoever
Of Mr Talbot statements about the
I don't believe these videos were released for a long time
If they were
Get those videos were released
In 2030
Certainly
Potato porta potties
I just don't know how to respond
Yeah you are more
One still out something and tell me what
Coupon buddy
I guess correct
Underlying message
If this video was I'm 2013.nba responsible to do what you did
You know what that means that means this video was out in 2013 because he doesn't bring
That piece of information
You can just get these these pieces
Cross-examination is the actual trial if it needs to come up
It serves no purpose to bring it up here maybe Alex's
Best defense the fact that he knows absolutely nothing
No I don't think so cuz neck
I don't know because you can't knowingly doing it
It's kind of clear from the deposition that
Either Alex has an incredible liar a debate which is a guy who just
Says nonsense out of his mouth as it cops
I think
I think that the standard is knowing at the time of
You're saying that the time of saying it important
Is the school
The false statement
There is at least implied there
So whatever Alex doesn't know now it's kind of a material doesn't give a s***
Which is even more upsetting on some level
About with the stuff that being discussed is
Jarring knows that he can save these
Eagan fall back on that to some extent and then when he needs to just blame Wolfgang
Cuz he is a villain
Obviously you have course
You shouldn't listen to him
We all do that that's out you're not revealing anything
But it does introduce an interesting question
And that is
If he's just going to
What research did you do
Like what what he says that he does deep research about all this stuff
And here we get another emails from Wolfgang
Later
Most of those emails took care of that but
Does David he does extensive research
This question that the prosecutor does is another great sort of process
Question in terms of like what do
How do you get the lottery search I have a question for you
Do it exactly
I've noticed a lot of these answers you said
What was going on
You did beat research
News articles about case
Hello
Lawsuits involving
Research on
Bloomberg play on email
The day before
Getting ready to swing a big event
Whatever
Is what is what really made me question
Babies in incubators in the happen I just saw
The media so on it so ready
I thought that added credibility to it
Bloomberg
And you said your audience
That there was an email that came out in the wall
Get ready in the next 24 hours
To capitalize on a mass shooting
That didn't happen that's not a real
Is not real
Bloomberg never told his people
Get ready in the next 24 hours to capitalize on a map
Organization
Okay
Upon Alex to defend his his assertion here
Because this email doesn't
Seems like it
Time ago I don't remember I don't have it in front of me
Like most media Outlets we destroy any and all research that we do within one week of
Yeah of the story we don't hang onto it at all if your
For all this what research do you do Alex Randall's a little bit Pacifica
I looked into that email to Bloomberg
Great
Cool
Questioning the idea that Alex has said that there are
I believe there is a
Remember if the actual clip is in this but
The prosecution asked the question of Alex clip
Basically
Are still alive and there are pictures of them other Mass tragedies
He's talking specifically about a picture of one of the kids
That was apart of the Merle that was made in Pakistan after bombing
And it seems suspicious because everyone was like
This kid died in Pakistan
But the reality was if anybody took the time to get into it with
Bingo of this attack
I included a picture of one of the kids at Sandy Hook and other tragedies as a like We're All in This Together healing
Yeah whatever
So
He's asked
He says that it's out of context
The response that the prosecutor gives is one of my favorite things that I've ever heard
It illegal
This is just great
Chris Johnson
Absol
Contacts
There's no way
No way to respond
2 pictures
You can stop if there's no way to respond that's a good weight cuz I don't shop
What context is literally any context that makes you not look like a monster
Wow yeah we were updating ocelo on air one day and that just happened to be
Might have said in the updated version of nuts
Still not good.
Cuz I'm sure that plays going to think I had to revive
Questioning goes into the idea that Alex
A person who was running the honor
And was reporting
Copyright strike against the property
Children
Ecos / Lenny goes over some of that stuff in the eve is American Life episode if you want
Add more contact for that from his own perspective
Alex
Did apparently out Lenny as a person running it up till that point before that
He was running this organization anonymously
Really so Alex himself is the one who f***** apparently so
According to this clip
Which clearly demonstrates this
On air
Call Connor
Correct
And when you learned that
You told your
The owner was run by
You showed address
And you said
Good luck
Mr.
U-Haul rental
If a person
What's a Stakeout
Foundation
And you're the one who
He was running site trying to get people
Anonymous front
No I was not aware of that
We were
Do not take credit for a scoop
He always broke on Infowars and supply
Some reporter
Getting the bed the one time he picks up an address
It could be a crime
Galaxy fold a shirt collards
Turned into a cartoon
Listen to go get a switch.
Like that is the sort of stuff that we haven't encountered in are going over the Sandy Hooks
It's always heard like the idea that they gave out address
To a little bit
Well we didn't cover February in 22 know that wasn't part of our 2015 no
Never
About addresses literally
Jbab address
Yeah it's the stuff
Is even more tops
I sort of set-up punchline kind of thing
Where
The prosecution in the first clip plays Alex threatening
To go to to Newtown
Next clip
Freeplays
Just answer it
The demonstration of Infowars coming to Newtown
This is the really damning stuff I believe especially
Presented back-to-back
And with Alex's responses
Mr. Jones I want to talk a little bit more about that episode on February 12th 2015
And I want to show you a clip
Your message
So for complaining you were going to bring Infowars
Edward Burns
I have no idea what
For complaining
Bringing forward
Koala couple months later
Couple months later
Spring 2015
You said this man
Cage fighter
No
Yes
It's from June 8th
Really difficult
Infowars Alex is going to try and pretend didn't work for Infowars
The courthouse baddest cover up into false flag
Going to get theirs
Through a little bit of it just because the sound is so rough
But at the end he identifies himself and his credentials as
Infowars
Anissa Jones those are hardly the only people
Harassed
Correct
Bad news
Clear demonstration clips that Alex is saying so I'm going to go
No punch back a little bit videos
Copyright law
Credentials
Wards.com
Goes and makes videos where he harasses all these people Alex plays those videos
It's hard to see a connection between intent as action
Is pretty well laid out that's sort of
Linear line
About copyright and the First Amendment
That would be at
So what's even weirder
Is it this point in the deposition
Where weaves
Boston
Vegas prosecutor is just coming into being like nothing stupid you just got that from
All right you don't need to respond to all of those cuz otherwise you're going to lose your voice
You're going to lose your voice
So what's the pricing is it at this point
Alex
Expresses that he does still believe that something's up but something's up
Which is a weird thing to be saying in this deposition
Insanity
See what you think on the other side of
You don't believe the official story
You think there was cover
You think there was a manipulation
You think yes I still think
I think children died
Holly.
Wherever wherever did you watch
Can I go back
Then
More actually the real anomaly
It's just the school system and government trying to cover it
Re-read
From from from from liability
Shooter
Where is helicopters
I still have questions about Sandy Hook
But I've
No people
You know some families they say no it's real
Credible like you did with Wolfgang halbig a couple years ago
Right about that guy in the woods
Back up later so we can just leave that aside
It is pretty crazy that Alex is still like sticking to some sort of a gun here
With the idea that like something
Cuz you don't need to say that
Could have stopped
Prosecutor wasn't going to ask you was responding
Upon himself
Also I don't believe that he's done
I don't think that it's appropriate for the idea of a school trying to cover liability
Like that conspiracy is
Very small
Look at terms of scope
I don't think it merits this kind of attention any of the things that Alex did
It is that words the truth
Like if it were just the situation that he's trying to say
Corporate malfeasance the school district trying not to get food
You have gone too far for true that deserves
I believe my neighbor killed his wife because of course she is still alive
However I must say that when the insurance adjuster came he inflated the cost of his car
There are still some question right
Just about another angle is entire thing and braided
Gross amount
Thankfully I did that because
Fraud with the insurance company
This week
Let me tell you what Lisa is doing in the break room or mine.
Bulshit smoking Outback she's flipping out at recess and smoking behind the building
Crazy questions
Right
So
It's unexpected but still kind of like
Next clip we get to see on display Alex's delusion about the consequences of his
His actions
Because he's directly asked if he thinks that he's wrong for the families
Of the victims and the survivors
You
You don't
Lawyers
Walmart this for fame
Try to get the
No I didn't only question
Government
Not
I do not know I'm not wrong with her
I mean that's that's kind of like how unflappable
Because that's a mistake
Lawyers
So
Would you like fries or what are we talking about here
Wronged them for all the families
To all that answer is an indication of
Like I didn't do anything wrong
Write an unwillingness to engage with the complaints that many many people are making about him
Into more narrative
It's really interesting the way the structure of this went because there were like there were some narratives upfront deteriorate
Some more General conversation
And then he gets more narratives here at this point that it sort of has waves to it
A little bit and I think part of that is because Alex is someone who
You just need slipper you can't nail him down position expecting like you were going to ask leading questions
Exactly the responses you wanted you're a fool
He is really
To this guy's advantage
Because you can go hit this point move around a little bit respond to something he says
Elicit the I didn't wrong people I still think something's up with her
You never really would have expected you would get out of him
And so maybe there's a win somewhere there but we get back to narratives now
And Alex has made the claim
Multiple times
There was a
Please stand down
The buffets in Parkland
Is it means nothing
He's pressed on it and he can't defend his assertion that all
State Police
If you think it's a reference to the state police going public about their being a stamp
I told you the mostest I can remember
You should remember that
Give me a sec
I'm thinking of Life coming over tonight
Metro process
I do remember
That's not a mental process
You know what we really should have gotten hand signals
I really should have got to save me answer because I got
You don't like the idea of police going public regarding a shooting of
Elementary school children
If you are ever going to save if that's the case
Publicly
It really is something you should keep in your back pocket forever
You should be honest the lawn you should
That's the other thing too
We've seen Alex
Pull out these
14 pieces of information on his show whenever he needs to like little things
References
They're all bad
He can't just like rattle off some some nonsensical thing
Because it'll be under oath in on the record
We know that you realize you were on your show you'd remember remember
So the next of the gets brought up is the idea that Alex's said that Rescue helicopters weren't sent but should have been
And ambulances should have been dispatched
What do you know
This one's bad too
How's the weather
I take it you
You don't know
How long is
Hartford
Dispatch
Calm down.
You don't know how long it
Dispatch
Perry Hospital
I was going off how big and others
Professors analysis
Okay that's just how big I
And thinks he's been sued brings up pizza apologize
This is your life
I can't remember exactly
But he does bring up how like he's used bad sources to misidentify the Parkland shooter he brings up
Chobani flip
Alex might have accidentally reopened
Is Chobani lawsuit
Because we we listened to his apology about it
We know that he apologized and we got this all wrong
You apologize to Chobani though right
Call M40 migrant rapist
That was a technical Thing versus Thurman
It was a board member
Lobster box
You did Apologize
The Federal Reserve member which is not an accurate way to describe the Humvee look high up at
Tattoo he's the policies of
The first thing I would do is
That's not it is void is done
You going back in court
Does he have some tattoo right but it was
Another good one
Alex
That should be reopened based on that statement under oath
Underoath I wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't if I was a Barnes here
Little bit larger and louder
Go back to over and over again it's like for them if they don't work for Infowars as billable hours
Just getting words like
A cash register sound
So
Ask about Alex's conjecture about Anderson Cooper
Disappearing
Being a green screen
When reality experts have gone on record as a compression problem with
The video files or upload it
And so Alex gets into this long thing about how he's an expert on on green screen
And you knows all about them
Conversation the two of them are having
Where is like
Align
There's a wheel
Who cares
It's
It is neither here nor there
But it brings up to probably my favorite thing
That this prosecutor does on this episode
And that is
Fall into a f****** huge trap
Nothing to do
Put it Delights me
Service First clip
The Trap is set
Is it only is involved at all because it has to do with our doesn't know anything about green screen
Proves that he has no business saying that Anderson Cooper his nose disappeared because of a green screen
Still kind of related but it's still tertiary that I love it dammit this is great
Here's the setup
One of the reasons that you were suspicious about this interview
In fact one of the things you brought up
I want to play you a video really quick
Something you said
May 13th
About these boots
Number to Jones
You seen
God
It is nice to know that he can smell it he doesn't know what it is but you know what you can smell it
Don't know I don't know
Earnest that like go bad
You have to say right now because I know it's going to come back and bite
I know
Now here is where Alex willingly put himself in
John Simon hands you would have Mark
From the Charles
Broadcast
And this was something that some
Recorded
You've shown
Video
And what
Has received from here
You could see kind of on though
Left hand side
Inside of your screen resistor
Because I left it on
Location
Yeah it's not like
Screen
Computer
What is Robin mark
I didn't get that far
We're Sawyer was given access
Studio
He's acted Alex a picture of another news network with the same backdrop
No
Good work
No they were
You've never seen
No I believe that's
CNN CVS partners
Nice so I take it you never done any sort of research
You've never seen
International Hotel Riyadh Saudi Arabia
Broadcasting from
Shake it on the market
You've never seen the photographs
The satellite setup for the major networks at the International Hotel in Riyadh Saudi
Jayco admits
Charles Jake Osteen
So you're maintaining
And that shot
Closet
And not
They were saying they were there
That shot was in front of the International Hotel in Riyadh
That was not a
Galaxy
The gas mask on
You said
Broadcast
Atlanta
When they said they were in Riyadh
You are wrong that was fun
They were actually
Euclid
When you were saying
That they were not in Riyadh
I think you're mixing things
Okemos
Yeah
So great about this little workouts does to confirm Orion
Enforce
The argument
It's so Salient to the Anderson Cooper thing
Because it's the exact same thing he said that he was pretending he was on location
Studio
And the same thing is that
So it appears to be tertiary but in reality it's so connected
It's such a demonstration of the exact same behavior
That was before you were wrong about that also
Good work
The big question I have right now
Now that we know for a fact
What Alex does
In regards to research is 0
Right we we have it pretty much legally proven that he did not work
Mortar that later
What does he do
Besides talk for 3 hours
He drinks a lot
From everything we can tell
You know I bet he shows up pretty close to when show starts
Probably take some super male vitality
He doesn't show and he's shown up for another show later and he's
Drunk or something like that
That's a 6-hour whatever
Just started drinking it like whenever he gets off there and then whatever happened
How is new strategy is going out in public and
Solar eclipse will go viral on the internet
Have someone follow him for a day
In like a post office
Sourcing issues
The idea like where does your information come from
Answer their guy brings up the idea that Alex said that was a false flag
So
This is introduced into the proceedings the idea that Las Vegas was all fake
All that stuff earlier we heard that the prosecutor
For more details about that earn
That Alex had to sign a non-disclosure agreement
To find out information about safety
Disclosures
Weather information
You suck
What about
General Papa
Chicago
Apparently
Is relevant to the allegations
4 reasons
Was that was that a government person
B2
Was it a corporate
Was it a real person or in
The contract
Could be a problem
There should be
Stop
It's not a problem
I assume that's not real because of course I do otherwise I believe that this is
You know if it is not real
Cuz that could come into court
Have to show the end
In order for the to be enforceable
Because it might not be super relevant
I'm surprised I'm surprised
NBA's somewhere else
You know as a quick get-out-of-jail-free
NBA with wolf
What are you going to do with that job perhaps
This is one instance where there is the illusion of who would enforce
It's ridiculous
Shooter
What is going on
So
Conversation turns into more General sources
But he gets his chatter from
That's of course
Fortune
Yes
Signed random
Import
Freak
4-channel
We reported on things being recorded
Yes ok Google
No
We talked about
We talked earlier about
Miss identifying depart
Last year
I don't remember that
Chatter
4chan someone
Email
Specifically
That there were people on internet
Internet with talk
Future
Videos for situation
They were showing a lot of things
Sources of information that you're going to report on as if they are
Real things are an anonymous message board and
Probably
Research my problem solved
He's a man of the people
So now
This is probably
About the where this thing
There's still a little bit after this but this is the crescendo
The guy prosecutor is trying to ask Alex if he understands why another Sandy Hook
He's trying to get
He's trying to get Alex to recognize that there is caused this
Being something that is randomly being done to him Alex
Really understand what's going on with the line of questioning
And then everything explodes
This goes so crazy
Pacific broadcast
Yes
Are you telling me
So you don't know sitting here right now
What broadcast PC
Pacific
Call know I'm asking you right now it's what I want
Do you even know
What mystery
Saudia if you couldn't hear that the objection that's being made is not the form objection to scope
Yeah this is about
About the problem
Right
Fifth personal knowledge you can answer if you're are you instructing him
Okay
You can go in there
I don't know what the score
I've no idea what
Is there something that you ordered
Weather
What's the fame
Is relevant
Mycase
You know that did the
Don't even start
I would rather you
Extraordinary
We're not going to do this to you
No I don't think so
RFP
I don't think the scope of no mystery knock I don't think the scope of
Direction was identical to the scope of deposition and many many times
No you can't ask questions
And I would appreciate it.
Defending
This deposition
It is not appropriate for you to speak
I want you to
Being obstructive not defending
If you cannot agree be quiet
Are you going to stay and be quiet or am I going to have to ask
I am and if you leave again if you keep peeking I guarantee you I will
I hope you did
Qd2
Call Dad
You need to stop talking you're not the lawyer who sent the request for production
That were
Requested
Related to all that
I'm & broke.
Based on statements by the court
Yeah the judge to do that you have to request them to produce this document of this document in the judge
Will say they need to do this don't need to request this one break
Ask about it
Right right
This is them doing that but they haven't done in other instances because
I think it's a really really bad
Things to have on the record the idea that Alex doesn't understand why you being sued
That is something that is
It paints him in such an inhuman way
That like
I don't I don't know how you could
Deposition
Yeah oldest and asking Alex like you really have no idea
Why these people are mad at you
It would be so ugly
Psychics
Interference
The question was dropped and they moved on to another question
Goal that it needed to
I was kind of amusing remark about how
When I wear defending depositions we don't tag team you guys I think he was talking about like for deposition
I think you might be right too
Another line and that is his businesses
And this is a fruitless lying to go down in terms of this
Belk close to that it's a fruitless line to go down because the lawyers can just say like
Objection based on privacy
Might disclose private information about
It is outside of what might be appropriate to
Ask Alex as an individual
But if that doesn't stop
Alex from accidentally revealing a little piece of information LLC
I want to talk a little bit about Infowars LLC
Have you ever taken money from
Okay
Takeout
Infowars Elsie is it ever had any money
What
Your allegation
Corporation
Nobody else is involved
Infowars LLC
What to do
Was it a gun
I don't know
Sure that is
Without the earlier. I imagine he would at least be able to say
Media operation
That's free speech system
Systems LLC isramedia operation
Alex Alex legitimately doesn't know what it is
Ronnie comes back
Something to do with like
The domains for the website
It leads me to believe that he may have understood what it was when he started or earlier in the business
But now someone else is involved with all that s*** he doesn't
He doesn't bother himself with any of the corporate structure of things
Know what these business is
I am
Cuz he also presented
Existing in the same space as I don't know what Infowars loc does
That could only mean to
That kind of a declaration means to me
Either you legitimately doesn't
Believable but weird
He knows of something f***** up
That's a possibility it's not as likely I think not knowing legitimately
I think just being a person who like
Is woefully unprepared to be asked any question
It's pretty amazed he didn't did his lawyers even like
Practice with him I think they practice on their own
Scrub Jackson we went out to dinner together and objected each other
Solitaire
What's the new name for Dave daubenmire show
Get back to Wolfgang halbig and that whole situation
And Wolfgang at all
Breath Alex is presenting it as like
You want it to appear that he tried to
Which is weird
So are you saying that
Add a resume
We did try to fact-checking
Secrecy
Up around it around
Hartford Courant other
Darkness
Preferred workout
Thanks. We checked out
Recirculation has been
Nuts in public
Most Airport
Okay not the deposition
Not the not the parts where that it's proves what I was saying is not true
We were reading and just reported all that stuff
Terrible
There was so much
I was like alright whatever dude you just you don't want to have to actually say
I didn't give a s*** I didn't look into any more life what's going on
We find out
What time it happened you don't know anything about the building
He doesn't know how far is it to closest hospital with a helicopter is
He doesn't understand helicopter rescue
Turn off
Understand
And that leads us to this next clip
Where he doesn't understand the consequences of his own action
He doesn't really seem to even give a s***
I don't
You don't know that there was a woman
Infowars follower
Federal Prison
Parents
And you know that
Very shortly after
Personal email address
Nowhere
So I did not do what you say
Okay
That's an interesting different denial
This woman angel
Physically or he denied another crime logical conclusion of the rhetoric that you put into the world
Person I heard him
Right
Stock news people in threatens them he doesn't know her name when brought up or it maybe is lying
Doesn't know but actually not knowing
And doesn't seem to give a s*** when it's brought up
You gave out that address and stuff
Not connected I would like to ask you a question
Do you understand causality
Objection from Farm
Thank you very much Alex
Bars likes good workout Eclipse cuz they're just more puncture
Narratives and Alex
Reported about parents not being able to touch their kids
Which was something that was brought up.
And today is like where did you get that information from
Is there one human being
Then you can point to that you got that information from an hour cuz nothing
And then there's another one another one another narrative is
Here in the woods and Alex's
And what he's pressed on it more it comes out a guy in camo pants
Do you think it's appropriate
To call camo pants SWAT gear
You're crazy
Oh my God
Young for a while
Yeah that's true
So I skip-a-long from all this because I think this is more important
Here as we doubt
Towards the end
Assistant on presenting himself
As the victor
Because of course
This is particularly distasteful. But why all this is happening
Only person to question Sandy Hook
I legitimately asked those questions because I had concerns
Corporate lawyers establishment of Democratic Party
How to make a smile
Constipated
Android
Can I see the parties
Dillons
Apologize for that
Seem very same corporate lawyers
Shane all these things exaggerating
Using the First Amendment
Chris Johnson
Corporate lawyer
You and others continued are in the news
Versus Boston
Shawsheen the real disingenuousness
And the fact is all just cold-blooded
Hillary lost the election
I know this is what Hillary lost a light switch went on it ever been sued
Call the corporate media working in tandem
I know you're working with a Connecticut case and doing all that and all that stuff
Let's not and is going to be some other things come in a roll
What are the things Alex
Ever put the final report I needed the report
Hope Davis
What report the official Sandy Hook report
I was put out a local state and federal government
So you you were going to sit here
Online since December
Are there been summer that the reports put out but it was a big deal
Supreme Court
So usually litigated situation of other spring so surprised
I do like that like
I'm just being like
Let's move this on the report came out
I also love that like poop
The state local and Federal
That's ridiculous
So we get to the issue of
Profit in this next clip is making money off of these
Narratives that he's putting out that we've all
Throughout all this he can't defend in the light of day and if he has to
Sleep is that a dead or it's Wolfgang halbig father just going off what he said
I stopped Escape here about the idea that he's making money off this b*******
You made money
From every single one
No we actually lose money on really controversial stuff we can actually
Oh so you can produce
New house
Advertisement separate from
Which of the two don't go together
In the same video
It's like it's like saying the Super Bowl goes to the Super Bowl has Budweiser ads
Give me Cemex money off of the broadcast
Advertising is separate from what is going on in the program product placement
So I'm excited for him to produce
F****** balls
The advertising the content or separate separate
The Superbowl knows ads
Realize is that Alex Jones has pills
Company pays him for each
Hey dad on his own
But it's a separate company actually might make sense it might be a better way
Yourself
Stupid stupid stupid and crazy crazy
Clips left in the first one
It almost flies under the radar because of how awful this is
We will see it doesn't really matter
Which is kind of a downer but that's kind of what we do
Incredibly Tara
You would agree with me
Call Sumter
You lost
Whether it's intentional
Weather
What is the agenda behind
What
So much
Analyze question
So
That's f***** up
You know the inverse must be true
I want to go down that road.
They haven't been
Write all of these things are I guess true
Entire experience of the entire universe yes there's some people who have cried wolf
One of them is probably Alex what the hell
Now the problem is that you're in a deposition about lying about them a tremendous amount of
You can't take that outside of the context
In this deposition
That is very heavily implying
That's some of these people
Who are the victims of the family members of victims of this horrible tragedy
The pain that they're in
Unspeakably f***** up I think
On some level
Anna Anna position
Babies worse
Then him calling these people actors
Because if they're actors
You want to go just go all out
Liquor earlier when he was saying that like yeah I still f***** up
What specifically is up
Nothing compared to this the sort of thing at the ends here
Like this is the headline
This is the headline
In some way
Pretending they're hurt when they're not only to attack him
Bucked up
And in his earlier his earlier statement
Is it a taxable
But even his previous like
I still have some questions about Sandy Hook
Does leave open for him the idea that
Well
Either they had what they had coming to him or they were just you know casualties of War
We're still going after the bad guys
And these people are immaterial
They're just side I'm not sure but whatever it is is bad
That's f***** up
It doesn't matter
Is this house a deposition at
The school
Is closed
That's not question
What other people were saying and
The Hartford Courant headline Weiser cover up wire no documents being released
Taking so long headlines
Weren't allowed
Question
Correct
Text message
Joan
You finally prepared
That you have
Call Ethan
I am not prepared to sign on to whatever you were the Mesa media makeup about
There is no shame
There is no ability to wrestle with the consequences of actions and so it's almost pointless to
If that was all this was I would say
But I think because of the approaches that were made in terms of
Taking the angle of like
You used to work you-do-it Infowars is
Fundamentally flawed you never check anything
Making him so to talk about that I think that's a fantastic approach
Similarly
But he clearly doesn't know about but should the question of if you knew about this that's problem
If you don't know about this that's a problem right those sorts of things are really good ways to approach
Alex
So
Even though we come to the end and it's just like you got the receipt you got the evidence
He doesn't give a s*** I'm not going to admit I did anything wrong I don't care
Whatever like
It doesn't mean that there's not the pieces that are valuable with him still
And they're thinking that he was going.
Expectations were of course adjusted appropriately
Got a lot of material good out of it
Although he probably
I saw the people posting about the videos
Before I got into it
I thought that there was a criminal penalty for lying like a civil deposition
I was like
You know that was the first thought I had and then the second thought I had was like this is probably going to be a dud the approach
She's going to be a disaster it's going to be useless
No actually go through it and see if it is valuable
Is it
It's heartening in Subway's
Covering it with the
Lead of it being psychosis
I lived in for the last 2 years
I think that I feel rust good
As we as we go along
Elizabeth
Yeah absolutely I have missed
After after being fired and then
Going on vacation and not having any
It's been literally I used to work everyday
8 a.m. until 2 a.m.
He's written a lot of all work and no play makes Jack a Dull Boy
Mostly
Simple base about what happened with the job I'll post something here shortly after
But it'll be it'll be up it won't be on our website will be separate
To be able to make those announcements today but we're going to hold off
Have that break and then come back and we're covering material that's so different
The audio is not from his completely different
Same person
Yeah it's very it's very weird but it's a little mad at Alex's show through
On our show and then on top of that
Bike
On Friday
Twitter account it said that knowledge underscore fight I have my own
At the Facebook
Review etcetera share
To intentionally not know the name of this attorney the prosecuting attorney
But whatever I made that decision and I'll stick by
Almost certainly in this deposition
He probably technically has gildedguy
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work