Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody
To sit around drink
Have conversation
Things about
The one and only
The man the myth
The Christ is that I know tons about Alex Jones Infowars in particular
No not at all appropriate
About alley
You know enough to live
Somehow your immunized
Items
You have the appropriate amount of Alex Jones knowledge
Navigate your daily life without him bogging you down same time being aware that he exists
Scared of what
But I do not
As opposed to Be Giants
Cross you walk away
He's like the invisible guy that I
Invisible guy I'm screaming out on the street
If I was a crazy person
Yeah
There's no one there
Whether I'm here or not I think what the listeners
That I just walk in
You finish your model ugly start to
Then I leave
If it's having a conversation
Pre-recorded my Google
Today we are drinking conundrum wine out of California appropriate
And we're in a conundrum
Last week
Alex Jones
Alex Jones last week
Did a lot of nonsense
And I don't want to talk about
Almost the entire week of course
Muslims spread butter
That's the way we do it proportional amount of time
Doing interviews with dr. group about his supplement
Love Doctor Gruber how important
Stop
It's kinda boring whatever but then the rest of the time was drumming up nuclear war against North Korea
I mean
He was hiding behind this weird Shield of
I don't want this to happen but this is what's going to happen
Then they do any of those perverse family
Cease where it goes through the
Not to the extent is that one that we played a couple episodes back where I was like
5 minutes
Nuclear war
Mostly what he did all week
Until of course Thursday
When Trump launched
59 tomahawk missiles at Syrian Air Base
He was so president
Still president
When do you say that
Play mysterious way
I will
I will frost at the mouth
I am I'm afraid I am going if Brian Williams
I would be afraid that I would bite his throat you just start barking lot over then
Yeah
How do you say it's presidential
Desktop goose
That's another product or really selling everything
Bathtub with Ameri Fatman
But it's a ghost
So
I don't want to talk about Alex Jones
But I don't want to cover his perspective on Trump's attack
In Syria
Because it's kind of boring and very predictable. Really all that entertaining
Like we could break down
A lot of lies
In this instance they're all completely undisprovable
It's not really all that like
When we talk about the dentist Montgomery CIA
Whistleblower thing to recover couple episodes
We can go through I can research stuff and we can figure out okay this is what's going on bababababa
Fret in the case of his
His narrative about Syria it's also speculative and based on
You know like
What was going on here is
As a sort of way of
Signaling to the Chinese leader who was here the cops was here
Or he does want to go with name
It's more fun to call him a chicom leaders over.
Is signal to him that he's
You know you strong and help with the negotiation
The man whose further argument is that
You know
This is probably
Trump and Putin got together and talked
And they were saying
Hey
Why don't I do this symbolic attack on Syria
Weather
And the owl tell you ahead of time
You know what you know you we won't end up killing anybody or anything like that
And now
We're not mad attack though
Yeah they killed
I thought there was no death toll for the airport air hammer
Oh are not always in the military
Disagree strongly disagree coming back
Good thing I'm way out of shape
And I might go back to grad school English teacher when I was in high school told me that because he was
Colour-blind he wasn't
Frontline's on
Okay congratulations my grandpa was a conscientious objector
Ended up working at like Yellowstone
I always
That you can be a conscientious
Yeah that meant
In like a literal sense like you got driving hold up a sign like
You know that kind of thing is a Mennonite
And yet a religious
Obligation not to be involved in any
Play Roar
Take notes
Apply to me to somehow
Because
It's not like you just get totally off the hook
Through working at a national park
And that was
Unfortunately you're going away so national parks that won't be an option
Conscientious objector
That's possible
Over
Over that River
You know how you can build walls over
Thank God
His prospective is Trump and Putin got together and have this conversation
Because far back about this fake Russian
Connection
And then we can have conversations
But then also
Hacked into it is
Is it like
Alright
And they're having a plan to get people to stop talking about the Russian connection
Do you understand
Is your
Just building a rush
Can connection
No rush
Connection
Besides the one that you just built
You used in order to
To create a fake
Attack in Syria
Like legal thing
Very very constitutional Constitution
Know you know what you know where where we know where we're at
The Constitution has no meat
Maybe you should
I really hate the idea that Alex
Recipes
False flag
It's really boring
To cover every time he says
Boston bombing
After Sandy Hook
Everything is
Colorado shooter
Movie theaters everything
False flag
Muslim he still doesn't recognize that
I just don't know what 11
False flag
Assassination of John F Kennedy
The
Nixon
Just his exact is birth
We will cover this down the road possibly as things develop but as it is now that's just a boring there
Narrative and I don't have any time or pay
Very not prone to that I have to protect you from yourself
I have to know where the line is
I like it more that way kind of
Incredibly important point
And that is
But everyone else needs
To stop covering Alex
This is the payback
Is that what you say
No I just want to illustrate
And and
And discuss over the course of this episode
The thesis that I've made a couple times
Yes and I think we need to flesh out more because Alex
Whenever
Deal with Alex Jones
Phone history
And when you take him out of time
What you were doing
Is playing into his hands
And if you want to pretend that you're against him
And you like if you want
Opposed
And you play that game
You're failing
You just like definition
I agree
And it's really bothersome
Yeah yeah
It's also bothersome that we don't get more cry
Sparta
My motivation comes from
Because normally I have
Spoiler alert
But
The truth is
They has an agenda
They are part of the democratic party basically
Soros funding them in it
Evil that stuff
Bumpus Bumpus
They are wing of the Democratic Party
You know
Their mission statement is to expose
Document right-wing pundit
Do they have
O'Reilly they have Hannity they have Alex Jones
Other website documents weird
Isis
It's not great that's fine
I think that what you have described
What they do is
Is perfect
They feed the outrage
Where you post this video
Think he's a joke
Anime forget
And then you wait awhile and maybe you said something else
The scandalous
This is a failure of a game
Now
Just to remind everyone
Last week
Media Matters put out
Equip
From Alex Jones is broadcast
Of March 30th
That we discussed
We just
Maybe too long
It was the episode where Alex Jones
Was on-air drunk for 2 hours
I found him in his hand
He's making drinking sounds on the mic when the cameras away from him
He's talking about the four ways to learn at the end of it
Keith Buckley
Did they cover all of that today like
Do maybe a two-hour-long expose
Context everything it's just this
And just to remind everyone in case you haven't listened to that episode
Here is the
The clip that they cover
I can't get enough of hearing this is the one this is our favorite
This is what is covered by Media Matters
I am ready I am now let me tell I'm not against gay people
Okay I love the gray fox
But ship looks like the ark
Kite
Archetype old c*********
With those little deer in the headlight eyes and all his stuff
And there's something about this thing around bossing everybody around
I want to tell Congressman Schiff
And all the rest of them
Hey listen a****** quit saying Rodger and I never use cussing in 22 years with the gloves are on
Problem
You get my face without I'll beat your goddamn ass you son-of-a-b****
You piece of s***
You f******
Listen f*** head
Get that through your goddamn f****** head
Stop pushing your s***
You're the people that f*** this country over
Son of a b**** your hands guide
Media Matters
Here's their heads
Trump threatens to beat representative Adam Schiff God damn ass
An anti-gay tirade
That's not fair
Keep touches on some homophobic
That's not the thrust of what's going on if he was calling him an ass
If he was throughout it he's going back to
The part where he looks like an archetypal c*********
That part is
He's just dumb
Yeah it is homophobic
Is not
So this evening
Doing it
Because ship is gay ancillary to his
Is true anger now it is
Insinuations of gayness as an attack
Absolutely
Media Matters
That's not
Using Alex and Kant
So that's
Sure does
Now if you just play that clip it's like machine
Situation out of context really talk about that
Because it was the beginning of where things got the real singer
He's drunk is s*** on this episode
And within 15 minutes of this he's talking about selling his car rambling about
I'm going to live in a rich neighborhood
Although the headline
Drunken lunatic
Needs to get rid of his car
That's actually a way better
Why did Media Matters why don't you talk to us
Media Matters How many reasons
Just to give you some context
Before that Media Matters
The published an article
The Jewish press reporting on his Jewish Mafia
Which is that's more reasonable
He did do that certainly
200 likes on Facebook
No
The thing with the anti-gay parade 7.9
You kind of get a sense of why they do the things that they do
Alex Jones claims Trump calls him and is happy with his performance
104 likes on
On Facebook
Accurate
You just
You have to go for the most salacious click Beatty headlines
Alakazam
And it's not fair if you're covering this clipped
To take it out of the context of the bigger picture
How to make the same
I'm making the other art
We have the same idea
Taking Alex Jones out of context is wrong
Galaxy
Because the contacts defense
I think it's
It's because the context makes him worse
He's on Air 2 hours drunk
Screaming this s***
Sing a bunch of hateful bigotry
Mildly bigoted
Certainly we we live on a spectrum
Here we are inoculated against because it's so much worse
Yeah
Well I mean
Here's why
Instead of the other
Because
That is a delightful loot
Yeah you could go and get his worst bigotry
I mean you picked it we both picked it out immediately
So that involved
Brock I'm not really against David Brock
It's fine but I don't like
The idea that this is salacious
This is clickbait e bulshit
Is to watch right-wing bigot
And document what they're doing
Hey we're doing a better job than you Media Matters
And listen
Here's the main point
When you play that game
You open up a window that Alex can attack you with
Whenever you do these things you take him out of context
Like the Stephen Colbert thing with Stephen Colbert
Alex can point out you did edit that
You ended my audio
Whenever they did that on Fox news with Megyn Kelly
That he was saying that Hillary Clinton is personally responsible for the rape and murder of children
He sure did
Take him out of contact and when you do that
Alex
It's like you can block a punch and come back
Yeah so now today
The heat Canseco
Correctly
That you took him out of con
Automatically for any of her
His listeners
That takes
Totally
As long as he gets to say so
Thing that is true in
You look over there at
Sleight of hand
No we're not perfect jobs were not awesome journalists or anything like that
But I am hundred percent believe
Even close to a journalist
Neuter my over here just like this
I went to the best
Bike
I went to the best journalism School in the country but
Any journalism classes
You got it
Today's episode
What we're going to be talking about is Alex Jones put out a video
In response to Media Matters putting out a response
Which kind of it
If
Alex were to here
Please just listen Alex
But if you were if you was to listen to that episode of Gomery
There's no response
No we didn't take him out of context not at all
You purely researched it to the point where there's really no
Disproving there's nothing that's delicious
Thousands of people are.
We don't enter the bear trap
There are these out of context
Clips it's just
It's a dangerous game
And
It's the most
It if I were out
If I were as crazy as him
What
Suggest
Is that possibly
Media Matters
Is not so interested in actually exposing with Alex Jones
As they are in engaging in a bag
Fourth dance
Remind me of
Text clip where you at
Al Sharpton and Ann Coulter go on TV
Hey b**** at each other and yada yada yada
Then I go into the green robe and a Jets their best
Yeah like they're playing the game
They're playing one side
The other side
Jaws rating
Clix
Attention
Kitchen drawers money
And that's the choice is Omarosa
I don't think
But be that as it may
I'm pissed off
Someone who could be an ally
And Media Matters
I pissed off at them
I'm vaguely pissed off also it like the AV club
Not super pissed off at them
Cuz I get what they're doing is entertainment glass
But mostly Supercuts of Alex Jones kind of does the exact same thing
The Media Matters posting out of
Posting
Like
Just you let him off the hook here's my
Alright leave Alex to us
Patreon Soros
The weirdest day of all the sudden just a few hundred thousand show up in your Patron open
U-Store-It
George
I also like to thank everybody who has donated a tree on and everyone who has not
Stopped
5 since we switched over from freezing point
That means a lot
I thank you very much
We could definitely expand what we do and I would like to do that
Oh man you did not
A good hours
If we had the money
I don't want him in my house Twitter
I made the great observation that he looks like a young boy from Rio Coco paintings
It's a really good observation
Just looks like he's crying all the time
This episode that Alex put out let's deal with that Paul Joseph Watson
Something really quick
So on the night of the attack
In Syria on Thursday night
Posted
Hey I guess
Trump is not a tool of Putin
He is just
A
MW
What was it
Neocon
Yeah I am officially off the Trump train
Word for work two hours later or so I don't know the exact time frame
Screenshot of his follower count
Hey like this is the first time ever I've lost followers lost like 1,000 followers
Couple hours later after that
I'm I'm off
Trump as it relates to Syria I have not turned on Trump as the media have lied and said
Fake news my own Twitter account
Tech news
What's f*****-up about it is like
Or probably bought
He lost a thousand baht
Probably
Paul Joseph Watson
Is a is a fuckboy
Yeah
Not today
Output at this response
To Media Matters putting out a clip of him saying I'm going to
Kick your ass
We goddamn Senator ship
Commitment
Fill your hand
Tell your
Still my favorite
I've been using it multiple times this week comes back up it's in play
Delighted by it now
The only person broadcasting on this clip he's not the only person who says feel your hand
Wait what
Excited for that
I've never heard that phrase before my entire life
I feel like
Gmail
He didn't and we're going to find out where it comes from on today's
Episode of knowledge fight
So
I have cut out almost nothing from this 10 minutes
Thing I just put it into segments
That's for us to
To digest
Specifically not taken out anything that has to do with contacts
Everything is at
There'll be a couple times you might have to
Pause
Fuel nearby
Here's the introduction and heavy begin
Last year we witnessed the Democratic party foreign government thousands of newspapers
100 celebrities
Are the ones politically influenced
Particularly ridiculous
Embarrassment to this country makes me so angry that this country has gotten to this point
Bojo is wound up where he has 12 I'd like to punch him in the face
Gennaro
Punch the president in the nose
We heard from
We've already talked about that
Opening montage
The his evidence
The people want
To kill Trump
And the Liberals are super
I we did talk about that
Like right after the election there was a teacher
Squirting us work
Or fake gun
Hilarious
Mentally on
Yeah but it also
Empty classroom
Who knows who she was
The video went viral
In quotes because
I don't disagree with
I think we all get one
I think the people burned Obama in effigy I think that Ted Nugent told him to suck
Machine gun
I actually looked up Liberals are actually looked up death threats against President Obama
And there's just like
Three pages full of actual plot
To kill him
It's insane the number of assassination attempt
That were thwarted in early stages but never got any press
Insane
Assassination
Episode
Be crazy
That is assertive
Absurd then the Madonna thing
He cuts off her quote
The part of the
Is guess I'm angry yes I'm outraged
Yes I've thought a lot about blowing up the White House
But I know that this won't change anything
We cannot fall into despair
Yeah
Really changes the quote
Yeah from
Threat to a
Why is
Switzer why saying
You don't
You don't fight fire with fire you fighting
And then the other one the other one is a CEO
I lost the page that I had up
Start up
Who tweeted those things about getting a sniper rifle at Secret Service
I was forced out of his company
Best basketball
You can't threaten the president like that
You can threaten anyone like that
Even if
If you're an egg
I guess out under what I believe the law
I don't think you can do that sort of thing believe in that it's still around
He's forced out of his company that he started which is a huge cops
Even if you didn't even see.
Jail time
I'm here come out later and he was super drunk
Alright there was a drunk dude
Running his goddamn mouth
Yeah well that's a problem with Twitter I've gotten drunk and in my apartment alone I have shouted very loud thing
Things to do on Thursday
For 12 hours to go through
Through every
Possible news
Network
F*** themselves
Because
Immediately after those bombs were sent out they had
Architect Botox
General
Praising how this is the most presidential Trump
Look at these gorgeous missiles
If
Deserves
Today and I retweeted it out them
Ashamed of f****** CNBC that I am
Of Alex Jones
Hours of the propaganda
Convey
Inferiority
Unless we're running up to Iraq war number 2
To the days of
MacNeil Lehrer
I just swallowed I forgot
Lehrer's
As I was saying McNeil
Go back to f****** boring-ass journalist
Yes we need to go back to 9
Just you know what you know what the most
Crowd-pleasing part of the MacNeil Lehrer hour
That weird little theme song they had that's it that's it
We won't
That bag that cat are drowned in the middle of the Falcon Lake
So Alex already
Setting this up his wide
About
But I just disagreed that means any
I don't care with Robert marijuana
No I don't care either
Mickey Rourke
Is Mickey Rourke said he wanted
Time alone with Trump with a baseball bat
I'm calling the big puss you don't know what Mickey Rourke is into anymore
He's really into sounding
Extra
That's a little bit more extreme but
It's even more indicative that
He is
Once again pic
On actors because
He does not know that
In reality so
Why not
Should have been arrested but it's not really an issue is someone running his mouth drunk on
Twitter
Threaten to beat up
Oregon Nation about that
There are a lot of
People on the right
3 years ago in real life
Obama
And then a thing that they
That is the exact
Possible
Alex has more
Alex has more threats
Most newspapers from the LA Times
Someone killed from
I want to kill Trump
Incredible
Literal definition of incredible
It's incredible
The New York Times and LA Times I can't find any
Sentences with their writers calling
Assassination
Trouble
Along the lines of this assassination is taking a long time
Richard costabile
Plans of her
Oh her again
It wasn't her planning it like
Like
I'm waiting I'm waiting for a shipment from Acme
Cuz we're going to have to have to Roadrunner this thing
And I think you got it
That's my theory on that because I can't find
LA or New York Times writers who is
Yeah
He couldn't point out London
Adana map
I'm not sure I could I can but I'm not entirely sure where London is
Nor whales are
How do you know where whales is not London cuz I remember it's real south
Whales at the bottom
Other UK
You looking at me weird
Am I wrong
Oh yeah
Well
What time is it
The south is the south is England I almost said London
So no
No happening right now
What is going on here. Wales
I understand English
Scotland Wales
And then Ireland is over there
Okay
God
I really thought that whales of the south of Italy
I don't think so cuz I have you were just there
I was just there the same sensitive like
I'm pretty sure I'm right
I really don't think that Wells is north
Scotland that part to me
Who's great pod by the way
I'll look it up as we listen to next is Alex Jones
Proponents of non-violence
Mahatma Gandhi Martin Luther King
That's true
Everyone knows
Now let's take a little walk down memory lane about some of the things that Alex has said
He put multiple people in Tacoma
Alex Jones this is your life
Call me right now or no that's there
Disgusting
He constantly tells stories about violence
He constantly threatens
Also
What is the only way to
To solve problems
Like a violent chat like that
It's all about Macho
Get rid of all your fancy pants smartness
You engineered
Telling me how to throw bomb
Utah some over the sea
Also speaking
Whatever that last clip I was
Wales isn't the South
About
Southeast
To even finer points I would have been wrong but
Is it
So now we all know where London
And Alex
Which I appreciate
And I disagree with
Cigarette
Play God day
I don't know if Alex could
He would sleep on a pile of naked
I also don't think that Alex would do well in a hunger
Drink Man
Wild Turkey
Anyway here's this next one this is Alex
Lying
For the fill your hand
Okay we learn the truth
U.s. attorney's another's
Vivian
It's true that they did wait a week
Or so
Except for we had recorded it over the weekend released on Monday cuz the f****** podcast
Yeah wait cuz we're not
Over the weekend
He did that on Thursday
That is f***** up that if they were
Yeah you do you know what they say about outrage
He posted that on Thursday the 30th of March
And Media Matters posted their s*** on the 4th of April
Next week
Yes.nm saying lag time
I don't know why they didn't know about this
Puppies
No obviously they have some employee who's just watching Alex Jones all the time
No they have to
You're literally the only person who just watches
No I don't think they got it
Okay
Here's what happened
They don't have anybody paint
Monday
Converted
There are people
Posting up clips of him whenever he does
I'm sure somebody got it shared it
Sky like a meme
Adventure
This is why we're never going to make it
You can't we have to pretend it was us
If we were Alex we would be certain
True
We have very high-level source
99%
7th grade if we only had one source but it was yours or Jesus told us
So I don't believe at all
Best Buy
The department
Attorney generals or anything like that
What the truth is is these articles are speculating about whether or not it is a crime
To say you're going to beat up
A satyr
Bullshittin of itself to
No in that expletive-laced rant
I'm going to
Kick your ass
He just said those are fighting words
And if you want to say to my face
That I was an agent of Russia
Kick your ass context of a
Yeah it's not like he's threatening to go to
Call me or I will kick your ass
With a hypothetical framework
But he's working it
And I don't want
Dependa
It's not that b*******
Well it's like if Mickey Rourke said he wanted
I think you might have accidentally hit the nail on the head of the
Entire point over this episode
Alex
Eggs for it that recognition himself
But that's the entire that's the entire system
That's all
Hey cattle
Honey pot
Your black
Fuk away
Where can I do a podcast
I'm very frustrated with that
Let's learn about this turn of phrase
I also talked about
People that are saying I'm a Russian agent
John Wayne in True Grit
Yeah it was John Wayne
That makes it even cooler
It's pretty cool you know it's great
I feel very good about myself that I immediately
Without prior Conte
Jacqueline is so cool he can travel to me through Alex Jones
John Wayne
Although it's a little bit it's not
Like we were talking about video
Definitely more aggressive
Yeah but it's also in the context of that kind of
A gentleman
I am going to go after you
It's a hey
Let's turn this into a duel
Mariemont Elementary
Codenames
I still don't think that
Like
Literally
Threatening violence or anything like that
And this is what we keep coming back to like free speech doesn't cover threats of violence
Slander and libel
Yeah
He's still well within his rights
Yeah we would have discussed if he wasn't
When we first covered this clip
You should be arrested for this
Fairway Auto
I don't know, this is something we agree with Alex about it just happens to be
We're on the same side for different
Yeah we are on the
We are always unlikely
Yeah
Azan to lie a little bit more
Mickey Rourke has come out
For killing the president
Thousands and thousands of prominent people
Number them
Mickey Rourke
You want to kill him cuz they want to be alone in a hotel room with a baseball bat
Appellate
It's again we're coming down to this
It's not illegal it's unwise
You should have said something like that
He lived a hard life
He's lucky he still famous
You've been a drug addict I'm not shiting on have a
Likes I still text
His character the wrestler
If that's okay
That's I mean that's fair
Prominent people calling for Trump
Assassination
Is absurd
That's that's
Crazy
That's exactly my point I found an article about that 1,200 people
Threatened to assassinate him on Twitter
But who are they
Who cares
Who f****** cares
What dumbasses say on Twitter
Actually drunk.
Toilet
He just tried to get
A certain account
Yeah that they remembered their is
The government
Lystra
You know what I'm saying like I don't think it's right even if you are on Twitter to say you're going to kill the president or you want to
But I also don't think it's fair to make an argument that tons of people want to kill the president
Tons of prominent people
Based on 1,200 people on Twitter considering how many people are on Twitter
Shockingly low.
Well you should
I mean
I would assume that they were smart enough to
Get a burger
An anonymous
Let's
Recipe for trouble
So this next this next clip is where we really get towed
That was real dumb of them
Wrapping up to this next clip is where Alex
Emperors
Severe bulshit
Territory
To the point where we might have to talk about this next clip for about half
It's such b*******
Literal bulshit
Okay so here you go
Weather
Performance
As I do
Trump and Russia
Define littoral rights
We're going to destroy you with the truth
Information Warfare
Oh no we've got Snakes on a Plane
So
F******
Stupid
Giraffes are art
Never get enough surprise
How do you spell
Fixes Ranter
Imagine someone he's against
On the left
Who was like I don't know if it's real Lickin angry against Trump
AllMusic Marc Maron whiskey
Imagine one of those types
He would never stop making fun of them calling them fairies
Get off that s*** you ass off
Disney the videos
Disease breast milk
In these clips this is not
Tumi
Performance
Performance art is measured
Generally
So we can make contain rage and anger and those are two things
His tools but they're always
Free
Design
In order to elicit a certain reaction
Performance
And most of the time as we've documented over the last four months or so
Whenever he's going off
The point spread in the middle
Especially when he's
Yeah it's the idea is to learn her all whiskey
And one of them is
The only way to learn
Don't let me ask you this question
That's just that I love it so much
Dueling Alex Jones
My point is
It's such a dangerously stupid cop out to say that what you're doing is performance art
Because once you open that can of worms
Now I am open to attack
Everything you're doing
Performance art
So every serious traveler make
You just at home
For now
You don't really have any legitimacy every time you bring up a source you could just be using that as a
Fake prop
Every single thing you say is now no longer credible as it was before
This is a stage
You can't take any of it seriously
Circle circle Merritt
I wonder you know like that you reveal truly the boy
Racist raid from
This is something that I used to have lots of conversations about an abandoned
Lately
And last year's eve
No longer
Necessarily but
Coulter actually performing
Yeah and what they're doing is like
Essentially
The weird parody
The right
Woman goes into the same argument
Whenever you bring up The Boondocks
About
There is that idea within it the ideal I don't really believe the things
I'm saying
Tubidy
Truth of that
Two stomachs
Fred Williams doesn't believe
No he's a mean for you
Pretty man who reads the news
He's not a journalist but doesn't have thoughts or feelings
The Vessel for whatever
Enough
Susan Rice
Problems
Cuz she does have some
History
Yeah there is there are some red flags on her
Completely ignored
Clearly nonsense let me lay it out for you
Aquarium
Wanted
Pretty things and they had people
U.s. citizen
Engaged
Some really shady
And she requested that those names be released
To her
Of the intelligence Community unmask them at her request
Okay
There's no leaking that was going on
She was also the Nationals
Security advisor
She had every right
To do that
It's crazy
African-American woman so that's a nice Target for
Leslie in positions of authority attacking your white male
White nationalist allies
It's insane
Entire story there
But really close to the entire
Tyrone and vagina
For the medicine desperation play
S*** let's make a mountain out of a molehill because
Our guys
Yeah but I read at you know I sent this to you earlier I found out that my dad Ray
Stickley Infowars
Right
It's the same
The same basic narrative
Diet Infowars
Couched in
What's Showman
Gunship
Like the whole the whole Susan Rice
They didn't you know
They don't go as far as
To say she was a spy
They pushed the the same narrative
This means that they were watching
That there aren't they are
In open Rebellion
The whole thing
Nobody
Nobody believes in reality
To be fair
It's just holy different versions of it
Live in the reality of the left
If I have to choose
Even if you are on that side every time
Absolutely every single time
Cuz that right side
Dicey
Yeah
Ark performance
Not fact
Your analysis
Not strong
You can't
Read
Hi
And you now
Shatner
It's happening
So this next clip
Alex is gay
Got to bring this all back to dim global
Really talked about the global
We are always
It directly pointed at
We've been
Globalist
Search
Attacking
Specifically
Play Hilary the episode
Absolutely
Jeep cars
So that's that's a whole nother
21 waist
Agenda 21
Media Matters
He's basically pushing all this
Google all the worlds
We have hundreds of radio affiliates
So I mean
Fair
Legitimate that would be kind of
Like slice him or anything like that
Keep said each one of those words
Multiple different things that they cut out and put
Infowars
Larry's
When he publicize that fake
Tape of John Kerry legitimately was involved
Been involved spliced clips
Media Matters just play the selected portion out of car
If you look at their site
If you look at with the articles that Media Matters has put out
About
Alex
Kicked off YouTube
Oh really
March 27th Google is funding Alex Jones is harassment and hate on YouTube
Under a bunch of Articles like this
Better about how
He's monetize through YouTube
And the insinuation is that he shouldn't be
He doesn't have ads on YouTube
No no no no no
As far as I can talk whenever I've watched
Couple of eclipse video
Pre rolls
Itsmerkey territory and I got to say I disagree with Media Matters on this one too
I don't
Alex Jones
All of the the races
Hateful YouTube thing
Things like it
I would say that
If you are selling ads
Heads on
Races
Then you are directly profiting off racism
Them yourself
Yea though I I don't
I don't disagree with her
Big enough company
A lot of times very stuffed it slips under your radar
And then at the same time
To focus in on Alex
Keep doing it
Horrible
But it's not
As far as
Outside of
I think that Miss speaking about
Tweeting at
Chris Cuomo about his kids
Outside of that was Miss speaking for the most part I don't think
He mad
Let's go after these kids
I don't think you meant that
But beyond that in the time that
It's up in the air but other than that in the entire time that we've done this show he hasn't breached
Free speech
He hasn't he's just that things that are incredibly to stay
Yeah
If Google were to decide that we don't want to be a part of this well within their
Media Matters to say hey YouTube check this out
That's okay too
It's not how I would go about it
But I
No you wouldn't have a podcast
But the thing is if you do that if you are Media Matters and you do that
It opens up the gate for Alex to be like you want to censor me through money
You want to take me
And make me economically unviable
Attack
Something to be said for a slippery slope kind of situation we're now if you put pressure
Google
From Angie
They have a president
Getting rid of certain types of
Objectionable speech
So then you have a
Corporation with a
Insignificant
Control over who gets to say what
Where am I
Yeah
I would argue that there is some
There is something to
To be said for there
Position I don't disagree with them there
I wouldn't say that they were doing
The Rock
But I would say that they are setting
Further
Get out further
Control over media
It opens
Unfortunate box
VIP by Mint
To doing these sorts
And I'm not
Super comfortable with that
But
And if Steven
Even more
Terrible
This is the one thing that
Really drives me saying about all of these
Dugood Crusade
Isn't there always
Who are not the
No
Is
Dumb little things
The f****** lady playing
And flu and lost her job because of a dump
Capital Lighting
Now she is just
A f******
Another ghost
Right
Because the Internet
Point of view
Touch her like Star around eye
And then her whole life
Wholesale I can you can come from it from either side the right
Can f****** your license
Totally
That's not the problem you're really against
You're distracting yourself with a
Tiny little victory
In quotes
You're not
Uniting to get the actual problem
Totally agree with you
Nobody nobody wants to fight the war
I want the battle of the war
Skirmish
Malachite
Don't do the info you just did you just did
I know
I told you we have to start mimicking some of that
Also I want this you are looking back
That's really
Who is this in this situation
It's pro wrestler Abyss
No
One point I want to make is that there's no we hate Alex
More than
I'm certain
We have documented
Things that they covered it all their way worse than anything
He is
Atrocious
Something that is merely
Horrendous
Now I want to flip this also
We have been more
Fair to him than they have ever been
They would never post something like that episode where half of it was up talking about either
Episode
I'm coming to Alex's defense slightly
Ever since that I don't think that these articles that say
Are speculating they should be arrested
Have any validity
Zombie Madison
We're being so much more fair to him and hate him more
Memes
I think
That we're impartial
Edwards dealing with the reality
Yeah I understand your point is f****** well-taken
But Alex isn't
No problem he is a problem
But he is
Do what we talked about
So we just focus on that
Now at the end of this clip
You saying that he has hundreds
What does Rino
He lies about that a ton
And claimed we have a bunch of secret affiliates
Millions of unique click
I went to
Because I wanted to check in on me
Yeah we haven't done that since
What does
Grown-ups things were were drunk
NTB fairy does appear that the traffic to his website has gone up a little bit
He's in about the maid
Viewers the day on his website
Right which is
If you're going by the week
That is millions
That is
Free
A day 7 days a week
2.1
So that is
Both of them
Strictest definition of what he saying
Yes it is
45 million but it's also not because I'm counting unique
Viewers and they go by day
The lot of those 300,000 are going everyday
But that would not turn on
It's not 2.1 million people that could be 600,000 people
You just keep going back to the site everyday
Does he say
The only
The only day that he really had a huge Spike
20th
He ended up with
T4000
Unique views, testified in from the app
So
In front of the intelligence
I wound up on bright
To the go back in there be like oh my God crazy
Yeah
Yeah it's still right around that rains there a couple 25% most likely is of the bot variety
It's impossible to tell
Can't they don't have a way to
Fat ferret that out
80% male in the audience
Where we have
Your 43% is over the age of 45
Which is slightly younger than
Fox news's audience
I'm sorry 53% is over the age
G45
75% of the audience
2 / 35
6% is
18 or younger 6
4 * 18
85% Caucasian
Words
That's a huge number
Who could have
That is not on
That's not irrelevant
Imagine that
3% African-American
20% Asian
Nothing over 10
Percent except
For Caucasian
85%
55% or 53% of them over 45 82% male
What time are you getting up his f****** audien
Albino
Maybe what if it's Brother Ali
Brother Ali
Also
Then I'm not sitting on people who make under the map but
40% of his audience makes of Euro.
50k a year
Lowest bracket
Lowest income bracket
Feel like
80% of the world probably has much less relevant than the 85%
Most relevant 85%
NBA
Michael's white male 35 and older because
Did they do update these statistics
XM Satellite
His number is I believe that I can't remember exactly but I think the last time we checked in
It was not even
Bad
Not terms of race breakdown
I just like that I think it might be losing minority
Which
Totally makes sense
Get the 45 million people watch your stuff every week it just can't be true based on the numbers that I've seen on you
About 300,000
Unique views to your website a day based on
You have to be adding up every single video that you post
And pretending you don't understand that a lot of people watch all of
If you want to do that you're cheating
I mean whatever play the game baby please
Agree
Yeah I know I like
If you want to make the argument that who are you to talk your numbers or s***
Fair enough
We don't
We just also admit that you're stuck to Alex
What about h
So this next clip is more about the globe
Publications of the elite
Department
I mean
There's no way he couldn't have seen that
Coming either
Like the moment he got that outrage
The next day
Somebody was like
Here's what's going to happen
They're going to pick up that clip or one of them put it out there at everybody
The next
Angle
And so on forever and ever and ever in perfect
Here is what I believe is the level of premeditation to this
Annoyed
Be about
Cuz he was drunk
Yes and he was Furious
If you just started
And eventually
So tired
So interested in teaching the baby there's only one way to learn
After the show probably someone did have that talk with him
Is brother-in-law Buckley
Probably came over and was like
Hey man
Now listen up
What's going to happen
Just get lazy
Okay it's definitely easier 48b to C2.
And then
It's checkers
We're covering this clip that Alex put out
And I mean the f****** b******* part about it is
The most recent
Peace matters put out is Alex Violet Adam Schiff remarks were just
Tongue-in-cheek and are performing
So they're going back on it
And he's going to say yes
Cuz that's what they are no response
Impotent
I'm rubber you're glue
Exactly
Everybody's
But more to the point of this
I mean like
The articles
That he's talking about your glue
What bounces off
Peter rubber
John rain
Edit that out
John Wayne
Miserably
He says that
Uno
Comprehension
Globalist
They're saying all these things
Just learn to read out
They're both just the things they're not
Like across the street at each other
But pointed in the opposite direction
Are actually engaging with the other one
In any kind
Meaningful way
I've actually I've actually done a bit of research
Listen to this
I'm riding
About Alex Jones claims that he was a boy
And was doing
I also have reading at the age of 60
Interesting is that you like most evil
Able to read Around the age of 6
About when you start to read
Picture books then and you started
Maybe get into
The chapters like maybe
6 is the bottom range
Elementary books
They'll be in the library with a silver medals on the
Yeah sure you're get like
Shel
Around that
There are Advanced readers were able to read like
Newbery Award winners
Write like a hatchet
Or something like that
I remember
Behind two ferns or Bridge to Terabithia
No that's what I would Hand by six-year-old
Just be like this is what f***
Can life is like
Now I think this is the reason that I breathe
Is because
He brought up his own literacy
And we've shown repeatedly
Of the articles that he discusses
So I did some research into
The idea of
What age literacy
Usually
I bought
Child psychology
The ability to think abstractly
Doesn't usually develop until about the age of app
11 is kind of on the downside of
Interested
If you don't know the ability to think abstractly is basically understanding symbolism and metaphor
The idea of dealing with tech
Using critical thinking
Understanding argue
Imitation
Usually art around until you're about in like 5th grade
Point
Most of education is
Nurturing what's there
I'm being really
Simple but like we're building a base
Yeah
The idea that I was like I was reading all these high-end things
When I was
Probably was but it wasn't
Understanding either that or
Probably all
Many Geniuses have dropped
Community College
Big Lots to begin with
Also
I want to get into it I looked into the dropout rate of Austin Area Community College
You should have dropped
I got it back on that
It looks like a terrible program
Here's my theory
Hold some water
Alex started reading really complicated things when he was young
Maybe even the age of 60
Bucky reports
But he didn't understand him
But because he is
Stubborn
Cuz he's bull-headed cuz he's the Texan
These are things
When he was that young
Thought he was understanding
So then he never bothered to actually
Learn how to
Bingo
That's what your theory is that
He never felt the need
To take the real step into critical thinking
He never actually went through with screams about the rights of
Message all the time he never went through
Abstract
Thought he only thinks concretely
Okay he is lying
Whoodle whatever the vet one
How to say let's just talk
Occam's razor that's right
My schema
My schema my world my argument that
Wood
Blaine
His inability to use literacy correctly
Wood
Bye
Him reading all this intellectual s*** when he was sick
I'm thinking you understood it when I will engage with you on your own conspiracy theory
It's not though
Do we have any corroboration from any other human being on the planet
Nobody nobody
Therapist all they have to go on is your word
Yeah
Afterwards
What's the weather
Please help me
Fill your hand
I think
If we are dealing with our
It's all we really have to go on
We have to take him at his word
By what we know about
Troubleshoot when he was young
Younger and didn't understand
Matches up with
Conspiracy theory
Except again counter Siri and I will I will give you a little bit more
Directly on this one
Perhaps
I'm not well
Never developed those critical thinking skills
Necessarily start reading
Maybe he read them
But he never actually developed the ability to have
I strongly disagree with this
He did read
That book none dare call it again
Conspiracy that changed his life
When he was 12
Right
So that had to have happen
That's a fixed point
In our Doctor Who universe
Maybe we could get in the Tardis and go back in
So much better freezing point
Would know how to use a time machine properly
It would be the two
Yeah absolutely no killing Hitler
No thank you no
No stop installing chairman Mount nothing
What we would do
Is we will remove one book from the Austin Public Library
No one last job no retirement nothing like that my argument because I have read none
Conspiracy
Is that Alex Reds there
At a point when he could not have been taken
Right
That didn't develop by the time he was 12
So all this stuff
If he's read all these history books and all these military history books
Even before that cuz he started when he was sick
Treating them with the same
Undeveloped brain that he read
Percy when he was 12
The one
Yeah he's tried to sell it on Eric Appel time
No he does not like this is the greatest buckets
The best primer in the New World Order
In the same way that
Like WWII veterans with
Crab like
Definitely
Prized possession
And Alex Jones
Signed copy of
I would put that on my wall
Right next to what I assume is
His torso
Pictures of Big Barrel
I do have a copy of it and I think
Pretty soon we should do an episode about it
I mean why not
With a serious
Things to do
Let's do the
Conspiracy episode
Let's do a Protocols of the Elders of Zion episode War develops
Anyway before we're on Pirate Radio
We've got a little bit
Down-the-rabbit-hole here
But Alex Jones gear
To get into
Has he ever gone down there
Red Wings
Willows
Okay I guess he hasn't read
Mr. Toad's Wild Ride
Mr. Toad's Wild Ride Disneyland
Traumatize me of the boy
Anyway we can all agree didn't read The Velveteen Rabbit
He also didn't read
I can't imagine that he actually read anything about World War based on his actions
Cuz if you read books about WWII you're going to run into the Sugar Bowl
And how you're going to run into that cat
And Alex is doing exactly what gerbils
I am a
He didn't have any comprehension of what he was reading
And reading
Took the wrong lesson away from it
Was by his bedside
Gets a little bit more into his idea that is reims or art pieces
So enjoy that
Merle Haggard
You're welcome
Information
Communism
Literally mean
4 is nonviolent
Comz2 often
Defense
Everyone knows that
Everyone understands that
And we see The Incredibles
Offensive finals
I am disgusted by the left
Vancouver
Shopmate of the New Black Panther Party marching around talk about the only good pic of the
The dead pig in
Cops keep killing black people
More importantly
This idea that he has
Felt like
Violence is a metaphor
I'm into it
Because I like rat
I like hip hop
Okay
Xo1 whenever I hear
Rappers talk about
Metaphorical violin
Generally what they're talkin about is
Verbal Supremacy
Yeah they're talking about I'm better at rapping do I'm going to Burke you on the mic
Leave these artifacts
Sure
Actually
Go out there with guns
I mean but metaphorically they wouldn't
It is time to get the
Spell therapist
Jojo
Come on now
I don't know why that's Mike's response to Yule Legend
I'm on now
I think it's my favorite Hangout
More to the point like I get that
I get violence metaphors
4 things that aren't vial
That's not what you're doing
They're literally
You really can't you can't
Mine's how he could believe that
Is not about offense
Anthony is all about
He is always
React
Because you're paranoid
He is always
To an attack whether or not
So of course
Every
Is
Didn't retaliate
When he wants
What's the talk about like I only appreciate violence as defense.
To refer you to ever
Thing you said about Noir
Literally
Shreksophone
Yes
90% of people are going to die
They screwed us over there
Turned
Next clip
Is observative
He gets a little bit more into the violent metaphors
After their Jihad
Plus calling frivolity is Donald Trump
Supporters
Beating them up
I am now committing crimes
Talking about I want to kick your butt or whatever when clearly I'm talking about
The information
Unbelievable
It is
So if you want to diagram that you saying these people have been
Ipang
I'm trying to overthrow Trump server murder
I also they've been
I'm picking fights
Trump supporters
Alright then
They're wrong
Then I was trying to
Say that I committed a crime
I did on
Now here's itsfunneh
Dangerous Waters
No
That statement is totally cool
You twist
You know why
Cuz everything is a lie
It doesn't matter
The argument that he's trying to make is just
What is premises and Ally
The only time you get in trouble with logic as when you have premises
That is where you get into
Trouble with logic
That means that your inference is wrong
That means that you claiming that
Your promises leader
And they lead to a true conclusion
That's okay
Unit 2.
Folsom Prison
It all doesn't matter
Gotcha
So
And this in your summation
What you just said doesn't matter
It's super wrong but it doesn't matter
You're not making an
Congratulations
You have said
Nothing
I'll say this
Even if we want to come
I've said no
Even
Even if you want to Grant
But it's possible that his
Conclusion
The people radeline for saying
You should be arrested or
If you want to grant that is a true statement
The premises were false
All bulshit
It's so delicious it's someone who has the ability to
Think critically
Engaged
With
The arguments of a lunatic
It's so fun that part that clip was so fun
Alex has more evidence that Trump is being threatened
24-hour Save-A-Lot
Bow Wow
Basically says go up murder the president shoot him in the head
Nothing's done
Coffered ceiling
So that again
Monster this is all within this 10-minute clip he's just repeating everything
All those same examples nothing there's nothing
Tons of people on Twitter
Situation for a little bit
Can we say Bow Wow on this
Bow Wow
The song
Oh I hope not
All that wood
Be the worst right
Into my head
That would be great episode 4
Snoop Dogg put out
The song called lavender and that's the one where he pushes coming up to
Comes out
Cartoon vines
Trope
People have been on Twitter calling for the Deaf
There is that
Superman
About it Bunch people got really pissed off
Baba baba
Trump tweeted at Snoop Dogg about like his failing career and like
What world
I don't know I don't know
The words
Trump tweeted at Snoop Dogg
And I realized
You meant
Resident of the United States
Trump
Tweeted at Snoop Dogg
Can we
So dark
Ebro Darden
How do I get to moment bases
In this world thinking that
Things Are
Normal
President of the United States
In response
Bow Wow Twitter that's like
Hey b****
But I was like
You talk about my uncle like that
He's not literally cuz uncle.
Listener for Alex Jones listeners
Connection between the two is that when Lil Bow Wow with Lil Bow Wow is Jermaine Dupri
And Snoop Dogg gave his name
I saw the two of them had a connection
Throughout
In his twenties now he's
Treated
We'll see what you think when we pimp your wife
That's pretty funny
It's still pretty
Right but I'm still on board
Posters the other side is absolutely
Sure
For all of my thought
I'm going to err on the side of Bow Wow
1 guys
I think car washes should be universe
Alright we're going to pimp your wife and make her work for us
Like
That's not
Really
That is
It's just some aggressive imagery unless
Intuit witch
We don't know for sure
We're not insinuate
Which suggests
She was bought at 1
Well the most important point I think even taking medicine
Entire time
Talk about his violin
How everything is a metaphor for the
Without Really engaging and recognizing this is ideal I'm going to pimp your wife
Is definitely misogynistic and I don't
I don't enjoy that I don't think it's right their implications
Infopass
What it is is
Braggadocio
It is within the world of Hip Hop
Like it is
There are feminist implications that we should recognize and be like that
You to give him the benefit
Benefit of the doubt
Comes to his threat
And he refused
Anyone else even though
Slightest
Especially black people
Especially black
It's that it's
Utter insanity
I really don't like how long
We've been going on about
Cameo out of there
Gloves
Bow Wow
Next clip
It gets back to his performance art
I let myself a satirical things Wild Things whatever
You're the people calling for violence you're the people pushing all this crap
Marshall radio show
False flag
Well
I mean
Don't
Higher leaf
Disagree with
Stomach
She said
If you talk about people in Congress they're super unpopular
I mean the fact he was doing it he wasn't doing it on his radio show
He was doing it on a late-night ride
Sing right now you are
Doing everything I can to avoid their busy being unstatic
But the idea
One of the most effective things you can do in terms
Getting people to think you're doing something when you're not
Is pretending you have a big anime
Like you pretending
Is massive Force out
How to get me
Idea that anyone really is trying
Get the FCC to shot him
Absurd
It's absolutely
It's not really happening I don't even
Take me to Mathers
Having that
No government
GolfNow
Like Google is bad enough if you want them to do something about it
That is not you don't want to get you don't want to open that door.
Yes would definitely not be
Everyone knows that
Everyone f****** nose
Not everyone
But everyone who would petition the FCC knows that
Next clip
Does backflip
What's next clip Jordan
Is the end
Elizabeth summation that Alex makes
And
I want to be very
Clear about this
I don't think he's made a point
When we get to the end of this play out
This is how we
The clip
And with a real
Slam dunk of a bird
But I really don't think he's made a point by the
Because I know what I said
I know the intent of what I said and I know that the people
They're pushing for me to be arrested
Calling for the president
Democrats are calling for it
I do have to be careful though
About what I said contact
I mean
I don't really got hurt this country
It almost sounds like someone threatened to sue him again
Because
He's very much
Quick retraction
I know that he's bad for this country but I don't
That kind of goes against his character is he
Yeah his kids
What's his wife
I did I did see an article about family
I don't know
But listen
You grieve meet at the point
If he thinks that someone is an enemy of the country is bad for the country
Advocating violence
Face on his own premises
Yeah well
I mean
When if you if you
Take all of his previous statements together we're in if you are an enemy
If you are
An actor
Advocating violence
Overthrow
In the past
You said the only way that we can buy using around
So if he is to say that now.
No I never ad
Violence
Particular in
God damn he is full of b******* in that regard
I mean it
It smells like
A letter might have
Central much like
The pizzagate
I mean I see
The Rock
Is Coco
You smell it
I think this isn't quite.
Yes I do online
You should ask yourselves
For 6 years
Federal Prison
Good luck with that
I didn't cut that at all I didn't I didn't edit it he immediately dropped a commercial
And after he was like
I hope you guys are fine with that you Hypocrites and then did a wink
Probiotic
Commercial
What where do you get six years exactly
Really weird drop
I don't know I don't know is there like some sort of
Likes
Will put you away
No I don't know
I think you probably was
I'm not sure I don't know what that's about
So point is that is unfortunately an effective video
Like
We had some problems with there's a lot of bulshit within it
Some of the points he's making our founded
I would say on any given
Episode where at
99%.
10 minutes we're at more like 60/40
I would say 70-30 maybe I think your model generator
Very idea
The f****** miracle
And it feels like it to us too
Yeah is the reason is because he does have a diesel
Leg to stand on when these people
Take his words out of context and attack
Is that is
The most
Destructive thing you can do if you're against him
So I beg of you
Stop
Your your point
We all hate
Dear Media Matters
Emulator
You have a much better platform payout
People
Mainly off
We will be thrown to the Wayside
Aldi's Corporate America
Want to do
No they could just pay off on a week ago she ate something
Negotiators they could probably pay us
Knowledge B affiliated
Very similar to Alex Jones
You know I bet that's the Best Buy
My sort of self-serving point that I want to make
Please stop please stop
You're harming this
It's it's a bad way to go
The other argument
Be made there though
Is
His audience
Dumb dumb
They're like a little little little lollipop
So
I mean he is a joke
Like that's true
The worrisome part of it
Now
As compared to
Yellow
A year ago
We were also
And life so innocent
So beautiful
Black man was in the White House
Great we were bombing
Most countries
But not all of them
Play most of the same once again bear
But but now that Alex Jones is
Personal contact
With the white
He's got
Multiple members of the
Well it's shrinking by the day
But that is
Is kind of
Now
You should not
Because if you
Seriously
Your attack
Germs
Wines
Kirkland down through
If you if you look at what Alex Jones
A lot of
A watered-down
Shows up
Yep like that
Take some of that anger and bigotry out of it
It is often
Yeah very similar of what bulshit they
How many times
Has Sean Spicer come out in
Instead like
Well what used to be true that
The witches are used to be lies then
It's magic
It's a John rain situation.
I have
A tremendous amount of fear that
I mean we're in for
Either
Six months of trump or 8 years
Either way
You really need to start engaging
What
Crazy people are saying
Cousin
The crazy is now the fox
Call Susan Rice story
That's nothing
It was broke by Mike's
Yeah Mike cernovich broke that
He is a complete lunatic
Monster ass hoe
Yep we could do
Also about him
We won't
Valparaiso
To please the same level as
Pjw
You
Weirdo
It dick
But like
He broke that store
Trump started talking
Trump tweeted that he deserves
Prize for that
It didn't say it that's right you said
Made up
Nonsensical
And now it's
Fun
And it's not the president
It would be hilarious if that man was not the
Of trump
Don't go to Syria
When Trump wasn't
The president
And now he
He's doing all of those things which
It's far less
For Less
All of these lunatics
The Alex Jones
Mike cernovich
Savages
All of them
You need to f****** pay
10 to mm
They are
Way too influential
Machines to sort of
Kicking your outrage
Machine that you think is somehow going to stop them
Is not your only helping them
We can
Not necessarily stop them
But I think that we are like an ant part of the outrage
No I did not say we're not part of the back-and-forth of
Is the most important day and then everyday we move onto the next
Because we've been doing this podcast
On the same thing
3 months and antibiotic
Is more than what we are
Is like
We can cut through the b*******
We can give credit where credit's due
But episode
All of it is under the roof
Set this guy
Is a joke in a propaganda
But it doesn't mean
Cut and then
Now we're selling the antibiotic
We also sell biotics
You should go into either one of ours Apartments
I'm not entirely sure
I'm not entirely sure how to give this a summation and give this like a piece of statement here at the end
If I understand
Active
You haven't tried to make
I think the point
I've got
The wave
Handle
Only provide
Ammunition
They'll be shot back
Magneto
Like that's what it is
Is just using your own
4 seconds
We are
Using no Force
Where's the drunk monks
Were using that drunken Style
But I really think that if you go back and
Dora episodes
Really busted a lot of
Carneros pretty hard
I'm like
I'm at the end of this episode and the
The feelings that I have is like I opened this up with saying that I'm
I'm mad
The Media Matters
Damn I'm frustrated I'm super frustrated by
People dealing with something in the completely wrong way
Never did I think that we're dealing with it in the right way we might be
Remind
We might be just as dumb
I think I was watching with a lot of my problems
By smoking weed
And that seems like the right way
To meet my drink wine
From what I understand of your point
So far
I feel like you are saying that
Alex Jones is shooting out these bullets they're shooting them
And all you're doing is fighting
Fire with fire
Someone
Is by going out
From a different direction
+ 5
Play fire with water
Yeah
Also I believe
That
Just Shawty
It's just shity work
The idea posting
Valic
I am being like
Here is what he said
I'm at not dealing with him where it is
In the Stream of his show
What's going on right it is just bad
Work efficient headline they should have said not only he goes on homophobic rant
But
Drunkenly goes on homophone
Sleep aid
And noticed
If you click on the story it expands and then there's the four ways to learn clip
The clip of him with a drink in his hand
Dollartree.com
You can look it up on
Chronology
People have been leaving really nice we have
Only three more
Are biotics
Please
Acknowledge
Gmail.com
Knowledge
Underscore that's correct but hey we like to live
Good life
Couple of dudes
Who are into
So you would you call us a couple of
What would it be
I don't know I think it's like
Soul Surfer
Salty Dog policy walk
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work