Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Beverages
Jordan
What was the last time you got a license
Pizza slice you got just a slice
Yep I did I was walking around I had to go clear out to some stuff from my old apartment
When you move
It's never really done
And so I was walking back and
And I spotted
But I like along the way
And I went in and got his lights
It was pretty good
It wasn't as good as I remember that but it was for
Have you ever had a body
I have their too big
You Jeff
Don't forget
They're not good
Chicago if you want
Free drink
Not a bonus
$3 and a lifetime of regrets
Just for drunk people downtown in Wrigley Hill
That's mostly with that
Apache location is for
Pizza Chicago
Jordan Brenner lot about Alex Jones
It doesn't matter cuz we're doing Wacky Wednesday on Friday today
Bunch of stuff from this old apartment
And also I've
Rejoined the gym near my house
The gym started taking a pilates class love which is
Out-of-character as hell
But in it you know so they're still there still some like adjustments
To the move happy
I felt like a good way for us to
To get back into
Good natural rhythm
A good a good
Funtime would be to have a
Little trip down to Project Camelot lamp
Because
Jordan
This Old House
Today
Has gone back
To prison and interviewed Mark races
Weather in Brisbane
Interview
Time
Bark
Which absolutely
Enter here is an out-of-context drop
From Today Show
Clowns are not reliable
I agree
Ivory
Cancel
I love it
That's a very important point
You know beneath all that
You can't rely on a club that you can't trust them
Obviously
Help you move
So unreliable clumsy
And I believe that we should start this episode off by giving a shout-out
Supporting the shower a night out
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Thank you so much you are now apology
Cavaliers
Next Barrett juvenile policy walk
Darren
Text someone who donated on a little bit of an elevated level
So thank you so much you are now a globulin
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket
Donated on a little bit of even elevated level about that
Thank you so much
You are now a technocrat
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much for listening
Go to the button that says Sports appreciate it
Cuz it makes all our dreams
Come through
It allows me to take and talk about
Interview Mark Richards
We are a clone positive show we are not alone agnostic
Podcast
We have no stated that this look like
Jordan today this is super interesting
Different
Sort of vibe Huron project
I wanted to bring that up
Audio stink
Yeah I don't know what's going on I don't know why carries adios very
But it is
And we just going to have to deal
I don't know either
There's no way for me to clean it up and I wouldn't even if I could I already spent
Forever preparing us episode
Carrie has a new graphic that looks like something out of a I don't know 1993
PC video game itself
Apes
Lemmings adjacent old Star Wars
Sims games
It's pretty good the ones that were like first person shooter quality of graphics
That for Mark Richards
Looks like a triangular spacecraft coming in pretty strong and there's also
A disclaimer
No cuz it's girl through again much like Star Trek
Visual View
The disclaimer
Because of the convoluted nature of the case against Mark I miss that
I will say
The case against Mark is not convoluted convoluted
Convoluted
Pretty great mall
Because of the convoluted nature of the case against mark
And as a journalist I'm not allowed to
Use a recording device of any kind not audio or video
Forced to rely on a dull pencil to scribble notes that the same time is asking question
I mainly depend on my memory for reporting what Mark says during our interview
It's entirely possible for me to get something's wrong just slightly incorrect
However since my work is heavily depended on my ability to retain information in whatever form
I have overtime come to fine for the most part my memory recall is surprisingly accurate
When it comes to any inaccuracies I take full responsibility and simply asked you understand
The constraints within which I work
Lastly any individuals mentioned here are based on
Not responsible for the below nor for their accuracy
Further research and sources are available on my
Address Mark Richards to follow up an overview
Of the cases he remembers it to supplement the following
This should be very helpful to augment
My effort below
Once I receive this written report I will include them
That is way too long of a disclaimer 2 basically say
Not nothing that you're about to see
Here is probably true at all and also please.
There's something in this
Come after we have some pedophile accusation
So this
Fake disclaimer plays I like that was
Too long and then guess what there's another water cycle
Long time ago in a galaxy far far away as well be because it just gives Mark backstory
We have a lot of new listeners who come along and a lot of them may not have heard our back episodes
Covering a Kerry Cassidy
Visits down to
Prism to interview a space weirdo
So I guess everyone's benefits
Speed up speed on the story a little bit completely non skeptical
Scary prison
For over 30 years Captain Mark Richards has been and still is a prisoner of the war between
Races that have dominated Earth
For centuries
He's an honorable officer in the Navy who because of his Rebellion against
The Draco and Reptoid
In parentheses the luciferian
Of course he's considered a threat to their operation
Naturally he was praying for a murdered use accused of having masterminded while he was on a mission off-planet in service
Humanity
He was Captain of a Starship Enterprise type vessel
Fighting the war against aliens been told to take over planet Earth I am the only journalist who is interviewed him a
Person while he's been in prison
Point of order the Starship Enterprise was not a warship
Sleeping Beauty
They weren't out there to do battle
Google
Draco right and not engage with
Weird level
So
I was already exhaust
By the time I got through all that
And that's all before we eat
Get to this point
Of all of our
Hi I'm Kerry Cassidy from Project Camelot I'm here to discuss my latest interview
Captain Mark Richards of the secret space program
Force space command as some
People call it
Hi
Find Thurston
Kind of like
It sounds like she's reporting from a bunker somewhere
I don't know what it is maybe she was recording from a backup
Computer or something like that
Or she dropped her computer in the tub
Matter it's not forthcoming audio changes a little bit maybe 6
Equips to sound better and then it sound like s*** again that's not your headphones
Out there
Against a little bit more backstory
It's her to carry talking about how she
She's been talking to Mark forever
Issei Secret
That other people
Mentioned
Because it's not true
No that's correct
I am an investigative journalist documentary filmmaker and I have been visiting Mark 4
Around five years
Approximately once every 6 months
And doing an in-depth interview with him
About the secret space program
And because he is in prison
This gives him the ability
And leeway
To discuss what is an essence of way Above Top Secret
And I believe the government allows him to talk simply because
They believe he is discrediting
By the fact that he is been
In prison for a murder he did not commit
Discredited
This is just good getting up to
She's going to spend about these aliens
Mark's nonsense
That is why
The government gave him
Clearance to do it
Because he's in prison
They know that everyone
The crazy dude in prison
That doesn't that doesn't sound
Speaking when the government
Record
Even if they are in prison
Telling the truth
They go
Let's call it Chelsea Manning all over
They they go hard
Bright bright
Even if they are in
Is it a little bit unlike all the rest and nausea
Is a terrible audio quality
It's different
In that for whatever reason
Carrie decides to get into the
Details of why mark
Is in prison on this episode
Yeah
Yarn that reinforces her narrative that he was off-planet
Rodeo just been able to listen and laugh
Cut the nonsense about like Raptor aliens killing people for chocolate make
Cameos in Jurassic World
Fighter leadership
All that fun
That is you can watch Jurassic world they're laughing at you after
Not all of them.
Episode is very
Because in this episode
Repeating lies about
Something that actually
We happened in the real world
And as such I can research that
That's why we got the disclaimer
No that she gives a disclaimer for we'll get to what
The fact that I can look into these
It's not good news
The story that he was off-planet
I just couldn't have masterminded a murder
Totally masterminded a burger
What credit card receipts from around the day just to prove that he was not
Play they could fake
So in this next clip
Some of the details in the particulars
Is about
The murder
Mark Richards 100% orcas
Good because
Get some really bad
Max wrong
Just like just
Provable facts
Wrong
He is said to be the Mastermind of
A show called Murder
Of an individual called Richard Baldwin
That murder was committed by two young
Boys at the time
Of the age of 18
And Richard Baldwin has been
Documented to be a pedophile
Might be why there's a disclaimer
Because there is documentation
No evidence
You can
Say those things about him if you have that evidence
Short but I can see no evidence of it other than it just being assertive
And that's not good
Pretty much
Kind of
The factual problem is that Crossing Hoover
Andrew
Whose last name
Crime
If she doesn't even know that big difference
The difference between
18 + 18
Terms of legal system for federal offenses
Answer the package
She's f****** up
Is not good
Well I do that
He's not sucking it up so much
Repeating verbatim
What
Does it make it look like
Influencing minors
To do stop
If instead he's just in
Influencing
Kolin all day
Right
Yeah it's
It's a mess
His
No she doesn't know the ages of the murderer and
The guy who went and burgled Richards
There is a slight overlap with
Episode
The dollop the Pendragon
But
Go into all of
The angles of
Necessarily so
Does it does a lot of stuff that wasn't
It won't be over
Carrie starts talking about how this is
Really an attack on marks
It's been going on
This particular interview is concerned with a V case
And some of the things that Mark
Wanted to bring forward about the cut case that are not out there
There's been some interest in the public and in various sectors
And with us
Pacific group that is attempting to discredit
Both Joanne Richardson Mark Richards as well as myself
At this point I really thought you was talking about
The mark Richards case and so we are
Making an added effort here to reach the public with the
Accurate information
Do that job
Talk about a little bit later and he is
Going to release
About
The murder
Baldwin murder
The trailer for it that I watch
Awesome because he talks to people across
The spectrum of light
Detox to Mark Richards
Wife from the time but back when he lets the murder happened
Two Crossing Hoover the guy who actually did the murder
He talks to people who Newmarket
College
Toxic family members of the victim of Baldwin
To someone
At least from the trailer people are all
Featured in the trailer
Someone else
Penpal of marks
In prison
Obscured
For privacy
But you talked about how to use a total fraud in like
Brutally
Here's the thing
Patriot
So it's an entire like
The trailer is an entire string of evil being like
Mark Mark
His behavior change
Right after the murder
Completely different
Yeah I mean Mark told me that is finished
The job he was standing right next
Text me when I did it
Connecticut's to carry into sitting there next to be like
No
He is innocent
He's working
In with the Raptors
Oh you know
I like it stalking about Martha the Joann
And her is like
The truth has a way of discrediting you
I love that I cannot wait for it to come out
Making a murderer
Because it didn't have Kerry insisted that the government was run by
I would be very interested
To get her in more Conte
I'm not going to do
With you on that
Are you forgotten that guy's name but I have it in my notes
You're in a little bit
Carrie talks about how like she knows that marker
Legit
She doesn't know
Cuz she has a sir
Set of skills
Sono
I can also testify to the fact that
As an investigative journalist specializing in Above Top Secret information from whistleblowers
That I believe I have a man excellent judge of character
Cannabis case I can
Say that
Without any
Hesitation
Let Mike Richards
Is absolutely puhi
Claims to be
Scott two pictures of Eddie page
Her to be but like
She is a terrible judge of people's character she has no idea
Hard to find a statement
That wrong
Edit entire statement is
Walt
Incorrect
Spiritually factually
Content-wise
Call trash
I feel like we're going to do that a lot
Get to the murder just yet
Just factual detail
But what's interesting is
Mark has an
It turns out that we didn't know about okay
Mark Richards
He never did have an idea
Who Mark Richards is because you've been dead
There are some key takeaways from this interview
First of all Marcus father's archenemy
According to mark
Bring up James Jesus Angleton
And this is also the case for Kennedy
According to Mark Angleton was instrumental in the death of John F Kennedy framing of Captain Mark rich
Who killed JFK
Who is this guy
Head of counterintelligence for the CIA until nineteen
Market
It was
I don't know
Mark was 29 in 1982 he committed that murder it's so like 75
Would have been 7 years earlier
CIA
First time
Engage with his father's nemesis
This is a multi-generational point
I imagine that
Yeah I'm actually two of his daughters came under the sway of a guru
It's such a such a side issue that I didn't look into it but others Wikipedia
Two of his daughters converted to Alex following us Wommack
School
I like
Stuff that I care about in
Mark's store
The idea that
He was set up by the CIA
Instrumental in Killing Kennedy
It's too much
It's honestly too much it doesn't matter more frustrated
Because I don't know where the Dutchman is
All of this
The Dutchman has been alive
Documents is Dad okay
I apologize
What is the document
The Dutchman
We have his real name now because it does come up
Some of the
News articles about his son murder
Wright was like a major
In the services
But he was actually a military
And all that stuff but all the rest
Ludacris
Go back stories
Play horseshit but the reason that I don't care about this
Is like
I don't want to spend
The next
I don't know
Days of my life trying to figure out if his Angleton killed Kennedy
I don't want to do the work has been put in already
Further I don't really care to do like
Some sort of a thing where like I'm
Defending the CIA
Or anything like that
The CIA in
The 70s
I don't
He's just trying to fix his wagon to that team of anti CIA
Read a book about the JFK assassination with like
Angleton
Who killed Kennedy is responsible for Mark being set up in
Supernatural
Instead of orchestrating murder
Tom and
Really f****** up a cover-up
Takeaways
The second takeaway major take away from this interview is that there are six alien Drive
Play eyes
Currently messing with Earth and
They do not have our best interest in mind
She doesn't elaborate on this
What's the weather
Messing with
Malicious they're just
Walking around
Aliens developed
AI with a sense of humor
The Swedish or something
Yeah I don't know I really wish I knew more about what you was talking about but it's not elaborated on
That that just thrown out there and his backup
AI is alien in nature I guess
Someone were competing
I don't know don't ask me
Don't you dare f****** aspirin
TI-86
Them are somehow like
Like summer on
I'm somewhere on a but they're all messing with us.
Irrelevant
6 a.m.
No names Bill details
Yeah so the next
Listed
Doesn't take away but I think it's
Because I took a plotys class and I'm going back to
The gym
Is that getting help
Update on Prison life and marks hell
His health has markedly improved
Isn't training for a new job
He's headed the optical lab that's
Surprise all eyewear for Medicaid it is a highly technical job supervising around 100
Men
Well as a number of robots that operate the machinery
She is also being trained on computers
The last time he was around computers on a job
In prison was where they were using very old software he says
There's also teaching a screenwriting class
Screenplay
That he believes
Might become the basis for a TV series not unlike Breaking Bad or Orange Is the New
Block
Okay
Now that's a good that's a good fit
Clearly been able to pull a yarn here
Yeah I think that maybe you need some editors Workshop setting
To get some of these potholes out of there
Melbourne Melbourne
Yeah
Creative
South going
Screenplay that class has
Beaded screenplays
I beg of March
Unh
Sacrifice for the greater good
John computers which is good that's nice
So we move on it is next clip Carrie gets in
The murder
Discuss this more in-depth than wherever lies are
Is she
Way off base
In terms of
Reality
Poulan
I read a lot of stuff
Good for him for bringing into
Non-medical biting all of
I would I don't think they put in
In charge of anybody I feel like
Right as we find out about a mismatched
The murder and the trial
Mark states that he doesn't really know what happened because he wasn't there
And the TA was given
Most or all of his info
From this mysterious character
First name is Andrew Campbell
Supposedly at the scene of the crime
Took part in the murder but was never charged
So scary beginning to try and wade into the water is
Discussing hell Marcus
The murder that either
M4
She does not get off to
Strong start
The first problem is that Mark absolutely was there the night
Forensic evidence indicates that he was
Repeatedly whenever the police revealed new details
Contradicted his story
He would just say you'd have one story and then they bring up a detail that they knew maybe like
I was trying to do I didn't want to admit that I had done this course
I would never change
What's forensic evidence
And every sworn statement except
Is the confession of Crossing Hoover
The seventeen-year-old employee of marks
Directing company
Who physically killed Richard bald
In order to explain just how dumb Carey sounds
MetLife
I need to probably give you a little refresher course
On the actual murder
On July 6th
Mark Richardson Crossing Hoover Lord Richard Baldwin
Good friend of Mark
Do a garage under the pretense
Classic cars
Baldwin age 30
6 vintage car restoration
Shop called the classic
The car
Too cool really rare cars that it was working on in the shop
Nazi
He's crazy as it might initially
Martin Crossing
Kill and Rob Baldwin
Ultimately plan to sell all his cars
Machinery to fun
But I plan to take over Marin County
I'm intentionally going to ignore that aspect of this
Create a kingdom for himself called Pendragon
Specific
Because Carrie is talking about the court
And the court largely ignored marks
Imperial aspiration
Mostly because it was completely unnecessary to
To prove his guilt
They think they were very specific about
This isn't really relevant
This is the problem
Do not want
So much more work
Berkshire charge
Right
You already got him on murder
Fun
So the garage Mark cross in the sky
At which point Crossing hit Baldwin multiple times
Physical
Murdered
Call burnout
Baldwin in the Torso but his weapon broke off
According to a recent interview Crossing game
Mark the driver and told him to finish
The job
Mark isn't the goofy eccentric space weirdo he's the sort of cold-blooded monster who can orchestrate
Tom we watch someone
He presented as a friend be brutally murder
Richard Baldwin was in Mark's wedding
Wow
They were friends
And he was there crossing Hoover a screwdriver
And told him to finish and murdering
Razee yeah
That is psychopath level ship
The wedding party
Three years prior
Jesus
So now Mike was charged with first-degree murder and two counts of burglary
Is where are the other seventeen-year-old Andrew
Comes in
Prior to the murder Marquette
Baldwin's house to take an inventory of things
Andrew's involvement in
The story that Carrie is telling is literally only supported by marks word
Is very unreliable
I thought
Mark was a total liar and a douche from
The first time we talked about him
But in preparation for this episode
Including a 131-page interview with a
Least he gave right after he was arrested
And I've got to say that knowing what I know now
It's even more embarrassing
The Carrie believe the word that
Secret space
Didn't mention
He's trying to lie
So hard in that interview
It's so embarrassing when you read over it
Is the police or just being like
Hey man
We know what happened
Work
We're giving you a ticket
Inside of the murder and he wasn't
He was at Baldwin's house
Baja getting the burglary started
Right right
Two charges of burglary cuz they burgled
House and burgled
The garage
So did that
But they're big
Okay
So
These are these
Interviews
AR
So
Two homicide
One from the Sheriff's Office
In one from San Rafael
The cops are trying to get
Understand that they've completely solved
The case even before entering the room
They keep trying to stretch to him but they're only talking to him because they want to give him a chance to do the right thing
And he never does there's 100
31 page interview of decline
Walking in Sanford
We know what hap
We are not implying that they know what happened and then like 30 pages
So they're like
I don't believe
So they started off with the like
We're playing we're playing the interviews interrogation game
Later on there just like to
F*** off we know what happened stop it.
We don't even want to be here anymore
Nothing wasn't involved
Pocopson Marco back and forth no one's really enjoying
Themselves
Who says quote
I don't believe what you're saying
I just feel that I'm wasting my time and if you and I can't
Candid with one another
I think you ought to at least allow me the opportunity to go back to my office
Go to work
Yeah
There are relatively welcome
Why is it they know where lies
So
They said quotes
In addition to what rich is saying I have to tend to agree very strongly with what she said
These guys are
I would like to pop in and say I also think you're an idiot and I
Good cop bad cop
Sick of the b******* cop equally
It's awesome
So
And they make it clear to him
He isn't going to get another chance
His opportunity work with
Will be gone if they leave that room
The Marquis
Keep begging them not to
And each time the cops
I reach their point of annoyance they say they're going to
And magically mark
Story starts
To change
Yeah cuz he's trying to
You keep saying
Stuff like
I know that you're going to
Believe and I
I don't have enough
That I'm I'm innocent in all this there like we don't want you to tell the truth
They keep saying stuff to him like you understand that there's literally nothing you can say to us that will get you out of this
Vicky place
Yeah I understand
Like you know you're more thing though
You know there's not a magic
Word you can say that will
Does work
I do with the judge right
1 pointer asking bark about what rumors
You've heard on the street
Read about the murder
Because he starts
Does angle look like
I didn't I didn't I don't know any
I've heard any
But I've been threatened
He starts to have this like
S*** I better start pretending that I was lying about
Something earlier
He starts trying to throw cross
Open Hoover under the bus
Yes he's called
Colloquial
I couldn't have done it I was
I didn't tell you cuz I was sleeping
He doesn't do that
Implying
He's heard the Crossing
And they want to know
Pacifically about the rumors
But he's heard on the street about the murder
He relates that he heard that crossy had committed the murder
And was telling people that Mark was involved
And planned it
The story that's going around the street
Detective
Who'd you hear that from
Mark
I'm not wait a minute I'm trying to think so you know I'm sure you already know and I'm not trying to lie okay. Texas
Detective we sure do it it's not that hard
They all work for you mark
Okay
Yeah I know
There's so many points you are
Busted
I need you to know that as soon as possible
Something that a liar
Yep
Texas broad my favorite moment
The entire interview
Just drop it on it
Michael's like that
Mark quote I'm trying okay I appreciate your bunch of crock
Bedtime you pick that you caught me in two or three or a dozen lies or whatever but I want you to Emma.
Detective we have Mark all right
Gadget Detective
We have
And we still got you
Later they try
Explain the problem
Quotes
This is Detective
Mark
The problem is you
F***** up too many times
And you associated with fools
Very immature.
Do that Markiplier
There is an acceptance of his own culpability but yeah
Entire 131 pages of this interview
YouTube
You know that we know things
And you know that we know that you know things
They're not
F****** with a trying to coerce a confession or anything they're just like
They are you are really you're on my last nerve
What is that is not what they say about Psychopaths like this
Is that it
It doesn't matter they they think they're so much
Smarter than you
Whatever it is you're saying that fine but not so much smarter than you
I can find a way through this
Yeah yeah yeah
So that interview
Is really it was really fast
Throughout the entire time that we've been covering Markin
Carrie's interviews we never heard his word
Really only hurt Aries and
Interpretation of them instead
See the flick talker and all this stuff
Based on this interview with that
Walk away from
Thinking like
He's not that he's not a master manipulator
The people who fall for him are just
Stupidest s*** well he has had almost 40 years to really get the story right
And I still haven't
So
She talks about in the sex Club carry talks about
Gentleman seventeen-year-old
Was at the Baldwins house while the murder was going on
Interesting info
The theory about
Andrew
An assumed name
Joanne Richards marks wife
I tracked him down and he lives somewhere in central California
That's pretty f*****-up
Here's what I would say
Andrew isn't an assumed name
That wasn't
F****** years old and Mark Richards lured him into a murder
The idea was operating under an assumed name is like a junior in high school on the off-chance that he had the opportunity to help
Set up a notable space captain
Wheatley f******
What's not absurd is the idea that in the thirty or so years since the murder
Because of people like
Like Carrie and Joanne Richard
I don't think the Carey
I don't think the Carrie should be using
Anders Holm
He was a miner who wasn't charged with a crime
I believe his privates
His name does appear in legal filings
And in new stories from back then
Secret
Are yours and marks unsuccessful appeal that was filed on April
But according to journalistic app
I think it's inappropriate to identify him
So I'm going to have bleeped out all the time
Is full name
Just in case
Like that kind of active Renegade
This is targeted harassment of a private citizen
Almost certainly just wants
To live their life
And probably deeply regrets
Their involvement in this
Modern 30 years prior
Cooperated with the state after the fact
After realizing
So
We mentioned earlier that
Mark wanted
How is that a misunderstanding cuz Mark was writing a book called Imperial Marin
Okay right
And so Carrie gets the plan wasn't planning this part of the
Plot of his
His novel
I have to clear motives
That where I stated
In the trial or during the the length of the trial
And I'm
I do want to interject that motive one is based on the science fiction book
Imperial Moran
And I will put the book cover here and be quoting from the back of the book
Mark was riding which took place in the future where as The Story Goes Marin County has become a play
Place
Environmentally sound
And an absolutely Democratic and free Society
It concerns a planet-wide society led by Hero
Run
Gyro King
What's the term limit on here okay
It's a lifetime
Generational
We were focused on creating a better future
This novel actually series of seven books
I was misrepresented in the courtroom and depress as a takeover of Marin County
It's very simple.
Soaked
For Mark's garage
Court was
Play November Rain County
Novel
I should give you full disclosure here I tried to buy a copy of Imperial Marin for the sepa
Because I'm positive that it's really fun to discuss
Play there is
Amazon but there are no copies
Available
That does not surprise
As far as I can tell the only place you can buy a copy of from Joanne Richards
And there's no way I'm giving her a goddamn time
Completely stupid
The chord specifically decided not to
To even argue that Mark was trying to take over Marin County or charge him with a crime for that because
Like I said earlier
They didn't mean to
They haven't
Problem
Reading for Mark Sons
Successful appeal for 90
88 where you tried to argue
Just against it because he was planning to take over the county they lived in
Which
Now that kind of
Imagine that
Charge you with that
Target Bangor
Would require a death
Strange Planet yet
I think really complicate matters
Don't want a brooch
Recipe
Quote the jury was instructed to consider the Pendragon evidence
Solely to the extent that it
Who established the
And Andrew and Crossing Hoover on the other
You are not called upon to decide whether any aspect of the Pendragon activity was illegal
Nor should you assume that it was
The defendant is not acute
Plotting to overthrow Marin County
Foot of crimes the crimes of murder and burglary
And and don't assume that taking over Marin County
Is a crime
You don't know that
For the preservation of absolute
Unfairly biased
Most likely in Marin County specifically that is like
Turns out it's not a crime to overthrow Marion County it's just like one of those old like you can't kiss a horse
The horse on Tuesday
So the prosecution was pretty careful. The whole Pendragon
Because they knew it was messy
To put it simply
They didn't
The overthrowing Marine part 2
Establish
Emmett Crawford
Establish a motive in court for the murder
That's a straw man argument
Mark uses
Pretend he was Railroad
And Carries just repeating
Haven't done no actual research
I heard a few vague
Parallels with Alex's
Currently
Situation
Like that
You getting sued
Freeze coverage
In his deposition
It's pretty clearly established that in early 2013
Has horrible reporting on things will
Which he never investigated
Himself before 4
Similarly
Here is just taking the word of a lunatic
As the gospel
Without fact-checking
Single bit of it
The game carries playing are way lower
But it deserves mention how these people operate
Free watched
Just take whatever these crazy people saying
Yeah
Another intern
In parallel with Infowars
Hi there World pops
Spell the pill
The court did find it some of the reference
Does the Pendragon
And I in the initial trial
Scope of what they were there for
But didn't count
Constitute any sort of miscarriage of Justice
And I didn't really affect the
The outcome of the case
Facebook quote
We agree with the Appellate
Pendragon
Beyond the
Purpose for which it was admitted
Such as the reference
About excluded blacks of the new form of government
Alright
That's right barkskins be a white nationalist
It should come as no surprise
Anybody
Nope
Is he barks a little bit of a racist
It is interview with
He describes the salesman for Montgomery Ward
Video camera is quote
Tall guy brown hair you might have had some Mexican blood in her
There's no
To throw that in there
To the rule
In terms of Project Camelot
There's a lot of overlap
Use overthrow of Marin or whatever
Carrie could be arguing about this Imperial Marin use that as a motive
In court at all that is
False argument
Gary's making
There's a second
Motive
The carry
She said there was too I was just the first one
Second one
Nope they're unreliable
Second one though is
Variac
And the second motive attributed to mark
Is a motive in which they claim Mark needed the money
VTA claimed based on the testimony from Andrew
Let Matt Mark masterminded the murder for the sum of $2,000
This is apparently substantiated based on a paper
The $2,000 number is just the amount of cash
Emma's house
The car is like
The plot itself
Marin County
Is that
He was Baldwin was
Is that he was known for having large amounts of
Garage
Large
Egyptian cats
Yeah
That marks attorney Shapiro and we'll talk more about him later
I got Mark to sign after he was jailed and
When he actually had no
Visible means
Support
So this just really quick what she's trying to say because she spells it out
The later part but
It's not worth listen
Twice
Would you starting to make the argument that marks lawyer
Shapiro
Edmark sign
Piece of paper
What he got into court
Said that he was
Carrie is making the argument
Is he was once upon
But he wasn't before you went into prison
He was flush
Of course
So that's nonsense
But it was simply untrue prior to the death of Baldwin
In fact
Mark states that marks wife at the time Karen
During the year before the murder had spent over half a million dollars on
Furniture alarm
You'll notice that
She said Mark
Mark's ex-wife
But that much money on furniture
Established
Other than marks
And it absolutely
Mark states he was making far more money than was possible through his job as a contractor
I thought it was his ex-wife Karen who reportedly has problem with
Alcohol at this time
Does not seem to recall or has never been questioned
On how often Mark was absent from home
During their marriage
I would go with all the reality marks contracting business was a cover
Money earned fighting in the secret space command
Wow that sure
The murder Mark was telling cross in Hoover and Andrew that Richard Baldwin owed him
A lot of money
He was getting sick and tired of Baldwin.
Hang up
Mark Antony to use that narrative post-arrest interview with
Claiming that he done some home improvement work for Baldwin
What you was owed
Hi-Time money-wise
Cuz he wasn't getting the money that he needed from
But you would present
I killed him I couldn't get the money back
From him that I needed
You can ask that to me alive
But he's not to me that unless you're stealing all of his
So it is trial has shown that in fact Marcotte Baldwin a large sum
Surprise
Creditors
For Mark's Contracting
Baldwin it floated marks
Credit is unable to pay him back
Is pretty firmly established
Part of the motive for the murder which is what I mean actual motive for the murder
He got hit with a much harder sentence
Is because
Pizza
Special
A first-degree murder
With that being
The intention of Financial and Rich
Yeah it was a qualification for that is something along the lines of like
You're trying to get money
Getting that money it's killing
And because you're trying to get money and you accidentally killed somebody
Incidentally kill along the way
Yeah yeah there's a difference between
And this is much worse
Mark's contracting business was not afraid
From him fighting
Secret space
Because if it were
Set up like a front
When a secret government entity creates a cut out front business they make sure it looks like a real business
It's kind of important for the
To actually work
Cuz you don't want to raise this
How much to redo your password
36 of the interview Mark did with the detective
Detective
What's the name of your company
Mark
I don't really have one
We just work part-time doing anything we can Detective
So you're not in the Yellow Pages
No no I'm much too small for that
Secret space program front the very least they would have done it come up with
The goddamn name for their front business
Captain Barker Richard secret space program guy no self-respecting secret space program is going to be like all right look
We got to pay for this superhero Space Camp
Do we need a business to final payment through
How about we haven't brought a completely unregistered odd jobs business where you employees minors
Should we name the companies
Bulshit
The very idea of a secret space program operating this way it's Celtic
It is fixed perfect
Because
What would you name a business that has to be
Do we have any evidence
Anyone
Based on his testimony he fixed the fence but also Hoover might have knocked over that time
A little complicated
Does not everything out 130 pages
Even the slightest oddjob to be simple
Of course the very odd most likely
So in that interview with police Mark even admit
Attempt had nothing to do with
The murder that was probably dead
He knew he was dead at that point
I had a good reason.
I think he was probably dead
Even in that mindset
Which of the fake mines
But these presenting it as I was his mindset
He went through Baldwin's house.
To try and find
He was pretending Baldwin owed him
At that point
Basically just confessed to grave-robbing
He was like
I mean it wasn't great
What was the issue
Started to talk about various
Details
That Mark knows.
Maybe bluffing
It looks like that I mean look I went in
I don't want to tell you this cuz I know it's f***** up I went in
Whose house after I figured he was already dead
And I took that but it was just because
Money I need to make
My money
And then
Sounding story
Police interview
You get a real good sense of what he's doing to carry
Whenever she comes in
Yeah cuz she'll bring up something about Raptors
To accommodate whatever
Terry whenever
She talks about in his
He validates so many things that I already know from my research the greatest whistleblower of all time
Or
To the light
He is a veteran
Sociopathic liar
Robert
Mark also admitted that he use Baldwin credit card after he was dead
Because that's no problem
If I ever died please feel free to use pretending he wasn't sure he was dead
At the point that he was having a credit card
Because
Theoden
And that's how
Who's going to pay off
Some of his
I have $1,000 limit on this card
So you can
Dollars worth of s*** Montgomery Ward or whatever and then I will pay that off over time
It'll give me time for
The money is all both
Credit card
Started buying stuff after he was dead
Mine
Baldwin's got it
Real good stuff
Also marks
I don't know it just was 82 video camera
Mark's wife at the time of the murder Karen
Has gone on record and testified that she was surprised by the
Money the Mark was spending in the days of
Ali after the murder like
When he bought a boat
To take a body out.
To the bank
With the money that he took from Baldwin to try and Disposal Baldwin body
Wow Mark bought a boat
And she had no idea where the money was coming from because his business
Going well
Any old creditors like Baldwin
She also it said that his behavior got really weird after the murder
Including it repeating every Feedly ask
Her if she would quote always love him no matter what which is a bad storm
Before I tell you what the formation that you will always love
Thank you
Thank you in advance I find a baby's vision
Feel free to draw your own conclusions
Society for
Hey honey just is a
Pure hypothetical
What state
How would you feel
Before it
Wright-Patt would you still love me
Okay
How about that
Send a text with Perris
Just rambling about nonsense
To present the idea that
Mark was the
Conspiracy Shore
I know there's a lot of stuff about the case here at the beginning but I'm sure you will get to
Crazy bulshit at the end
This is an added note I believe Richard Baldwin was selected as a victim by the team within the military
And at the highest levels of power in Britain and the US
Responsible for framing Mark Richards
I've come to the conclusion that the murder was orchestrated
With hangover
Selected as the Patsy
Zerli history having been a victim of pedophilia
And an unbalanced character
I also believe
There's an underlying pedophile ring this behind-the-scenes campaign targeting
Mike Richards
It is also significant
That the individuals involved in targeting Mark Richards
Joanne Richards and myself at this time
Come from Britain
And I also understand
That there is
Some motivation with
Which Within
When I believe is mj-12 up
Who gives a s***
Sarasota
Repackage
Which some of the
Hoover his
We're part of Hawaii
Or how Mark manipulated
Murder part of it was that Mark knew that Hoover was
Violently homophobic
And so he told him to Baldwin
When was gay
And that was a part of the motivation that Mark
The manipulation in order to get him
Baldwin
To do his bidding
So this idea of
Repackage that
Has like a pedophile and Hoover was
The victim of childhood
Abuse
That's everything
It's just really ugly
Really gross
It's grows on a number of levels.
In the same way that he was originally f***** by
Doing boring
The prop and then also just
Conflating
Conscious or on a
Like an abstract level.
Equivocate
Homosexuality
Is just discuss
Always always pedophiles to get out of
Any bulshit
Everybody
Blackmail anything I've ever done is probably set up by pedophile
That just makes them
Another connection
To Alex
Zoe
So
About the British
What's going on again
Now is this
Specific
Bradley idea that
The British
Just a guy
So
Next
Most of what she
She says in this next clip is
True
But she's giving a different way that I believe
All indications are that this targeting of March Mark Richards
Is happening now after nearly 35 years since the verdict
And this is because of my interviews with Captain Mark Richards
Revealing the true nature of the alien presence
Secret space program as well as space command
And I believe that this targeting is aimed at further discrediting mark
And
And my work as well as the work of Joanne Richards marks why
If you take the part of it being liked
To cover up the truth about space
Entirely at like
Explain
I am very motivated to discredit my
Insinuating that everybody is
Pedophile
There are pedophiles
And you are hurting bad
Your enemies
With
Is Crying Wolf a little bit
It's pretty gross osher there's another pedophile
No actually there is one this time
Accusation of
Baldwin pedophile necessarily come
Songs for Mark Richard
Yeah I'm not sure that it does eat May
It Max
From
Another guy
The guy who is a guest blogger
On Project Campbell
And a lot of information
The background
In the research
Very heavy
Quotes about the case
She's reading
From a guy
Paul Collin
Who did a report
Project Camelot
Carrie has this to say about
In order to be fully informed you must see the investigation done by kamelot blogger
Call Colin
And I have already
So detailed. And again put the links
I because this is such crucial information to get your facts right
So you need
If you're going to
You're going to know the
You know about reality
You got to
Paul Collins
This is fun because she's spending a lot of
True things like
What do you mean
I don't know
You have to
The reporting right
This is a sensitive issue
Right
Call Lynn fralick
Blogger on carries website
He claims to be a former CIA agent but so does everyone carry talk to you soon
However it
So important that I see is evidence
A researcher would I be if I didn't
Poke around a little
Brecht first things
Reporting
Copy and paste the URL for his report intershow transcript
PDF file
You can't copy from
So in order to get his report you to type out this long string of the URL
In fairness it does lead to an actual page that's
I just brings up to vent a little bit at my frustration about how
Really about Mark Richards Being Framed
Nor is it really about any
Truth about his case
His report is mostly just trying to attack
The character of
Kevin Daniel Moore
The British documentary filmmaker who's working on that docu-series
About Baldwin
Murder
Call quotes
Past involvement with Central Banking
And financial services
As a corporate secretary in corporate
Don't talk
That's bully
You could be a telemarketer if I
I don't particularly care about
Garbage
Even if everything this guy is saying is
Is true
To do with what I know about Margaret
This is a classic
Damaged
Control and you know why they're doing
Because what I told you earlier
Because of some reason
Possibly gas
Kerry agreed to be interviewed for mores.
From the trailer of it
A very good life
Some say it makes her look like a crazy person
Looks at things
Is going to agree because
Cancer
The truth
I'm so this is what an Avenue to get her message
To do that
Interview
Maybe
It makes perfect
It's it's it's a really vulnerable positions
She doesn't have Final Cut
Is about
Probably what you're going to do it
Because she is
If she is insulated by the
Truth right
Does not need
Truth to power
I love your passion
Carrie knows if you made it
Huge mistake
Actual evidence of Mars
Interviews
Crossing Hoover
Interviews with Mark
Ex-wife Karen
Interviews of people marketing
College and all of its going to illustrate the
The fundamental truth
That Mark Richard
Is a sociopath
Who's been calling people his whole life
On some level knows that the producers of the documentary
Really only have any interest in talking to her so she can be the example of his current victim
Narrative
Existing on challenge
She can't argue with Casey
Some effect
She's left to do that all she can do is start rambling about Raptors
So her only real strategies
The painters documentarian
Pedophile Network
Is clearly working
With the reptilians
Mark's Noble Crusade
It's painfully transparent
Get all the facts
By going to this guest bloggers website right is hers
Get your facts straight and him saying
Miriam is sucks for the aliens
So we don't like
Deteriorate halfway through it to a defense
Read about how great
Is boring
Furthermore Kerry Cassidy exercises professionalism
High orders of discernment courage
Integrity
If people want a fair-haired version
Alex Jones like gorillas journalism broadcast
Then they know where to turn there at
Well that was a little bit on the nose
Lower the volume
Just on the fact
Paul Collins article is a
Trash
He gets very basic
Princeton
He claims that Andrew was criminally charged with murder but that is not
True
He goes on to even say that Andrew was
The prison for the murder
Is categorically false
It even is counter to the version of the story that Carrie is presenting on this episode the word listen
He is f*** it up
If you
Kind of really Bass
I can't get myself to engage at this other unsourced
Assertion
Impossibly libelous claims about Baldwin being a pedophile
Although
That's another parallel.
We'd be remiss not to point that out
However I should point out that on September 4th 28th
Paul Collin posted a Blog on Project
Read email from a Nigerian
Quote on Friday August 31st
Really difficult news negatively impacting my very survival is it
Human being
Knowledgeability worldwide
Of course the US federal government
Me to pay back
U.s. dollars
The US State Department
2006 repatriation loan
Did America used to remove
Do they claim is overdue
Handsome I did not repay the US government
Within the next 30 days
Which means all donation money is from October 2018 moving forward
To my bank account will automatically out of my bank account
This means I can no longer ask for donations
Pay my vehicle insurance or pay my monthly smartphone bill
These are
222 hour long days and nights I spend 7 days a week
Researching and writing reports for Project Camelot
If I cannot
He's got a I got a negotiate for better laborer
Can't imagine what he's doing in that time
18 to 22 hours there is no work
Shown on the page
If I cannot come up with their $2,500 each
There'll be no further any worse than I am already now
Homeless in a van without being able to qualify for any public
What's the weather
Text Jordan
Creation loans are not used to remove someone from
Because of the financial hardship
Need to return to the US
Provided the thermostat
From the state department website
Quotes
The department of recreation loans program provides emergency
Attitude Americans abroad with no other source of fun
To return to the United
Bank of America
Temporarily abroad
Proceed events
Illness or ax
Individual sovereignty
From serious physical or mental illness you need to return
United States for medical
Americans residing abroad
Assistance
Escape
Situation
And individuals caught in the
Disaster or emerge
Currency abroad you need to
Should be removed from harm
Also guess what
If you have a good cause like a medical condition
Poverty inability to work
Or something along those lines
There's a really easy to find form on the government's website
Just called quotes repatriation loan waiver into
Referral request
People can apply to have quote the whole or any portion of a repatriation loan
Completely way
Officers will then perform a review and if it's appropriate.
These loans entirely or in part
18 cases were they
Justify a waiver
They often allow deferral of collection
In order to set up you
Consider the applicants financial situation down the road
It's a very forgiving system that set up
The Uso of the government
That is a shocker
Further they ever really easy to find phone number and email address
Very easy to Google
We're loan recipients can work out payment
In the life of there long
U.s. code 267 one section
Covers the establishment of the repatriation loanpro
4 clearly states
But they don't refer any loans for litigation
Except in cases where they are more than
A year overdue on pay
Know where do they say that they'll Place liens on people who don't pay although I do
The collection agencies that you can subcontract I think it's possible
But according to the US code 18
I prefer to just apply
Some fees
And they only litigating anyway
If you're a
Year overdue on a payment
Tired
If you have a $2,500 repatriation loan I'm positive you
You could get it cut down into
Like I don't know
15 payments
$200
Take a little extra and
Drop it down at the time
Vets or whatever
Whatever it is
He's probably
Just had a $200 bill that he
Unpaid for a year
If this is even true at all
So I don't know
He seems real scam
And this I need
$2,500
Post
Is it
Serious red flag
Anthony also posted.
Things on Project
Red flag
22 hours
All he could write
Please desperately give me money is that short piece and it really looks like a Nigerian
Bab also his post sounds like roommates
Used to have
I would love to be your roommate for this apartment will get this all together
In order for me to do so though I'm going to need you to
I think it's a simpler version of that that is just
It's almost like
Here is a crisis give us money
The carry linked to about Mark Richards
Haven't made me any more informed about the murder that Mark totally orchestrated
Give me a chance to learn
Creation loans silver lining
Talking about Mark
Just not true
Around the time of the murder Mark had want more than one Construction Company
He supervised the cruise that reported to him
And he had hundreds of people in the secret space program
Or secret space command
Who reported to him
Mark didn't have a name for his
Construction business he didn't have
To f******
Construction business
It's very clear you talkin about it not going
The business is not going well
He has like
They ask you how many people he has working for him
He says it's like
Egypt
You talkin about how one guy who sold
Begun to who works for him
It is like
He's not working for you now right inside
We don't have any work for it
Selectors
Not a ton of work to do handyman employee 26
People that he has working for him are Andrew and crossy
They probably those the only people on the crew that are actively working
Emporium numbers of 5 other guys
Baby needs
Yeah you'll subcontract out
If you're Illinois Illinois in the Midwest
Act like 13 you'll get your first detasseling job
Teacher at my school who just show up with
Half bus
To be like
They got real busy
I mean I work for my
Myself but I
Bogart
Husband
Weed killer
So if it's nightclub Carrie brings up
She thinks
Is proven marks
In some way but it actually makes
So much
Apparently there is also another young man named Willie Robles
He was not charged but may have had something to do with the murder
Mark says that Robles was dating Hoover sister at the time
Who is dating Hoover sister at the time and was said to go around
Saying he would bash someone's head in with a baseball bat
If he got angry
And this does mirror what happened in the murder apparently
Apparently
Robles might actually be the person
Killed Baldi
In reality William Robles
Is one of two other youths
Approach them
With his plan to murder Baldwin
And sell his shift
Make a load of cash
Attack their credibility
You're trying to cut it
It is true that one of those not Robles the other guy
Was arrested for selling marijuana
The author of Declaration
Swearing that kneeled Robles
We're never offered any promise
Anyway
So that's all a load of
The existence of these two other people is really
The piece of evidence
PetSmart
Additional people have sworn testimony
Identical to the one that he eventually
Carryout
So
Yep
Lizards
Couldn't couldn't rewrite the
We're creatures of habit
It's real nuts
To see all of this
Jillian's
I like it
Tu VI d
That's quite a bit.
It is in some ways admirable in other ways
Real feelings of
The human race
It's Ian Abramson level commitment to affect
So we get back to the idea of Baldwin being a pedophile
The way that Mark learn to Baldwin was a pedophile
Is it marks company was hired to remodel Baldwin's house
Mark screw called him one day at the beginning of the job to say
They found a huge amount of c********* in the house saying you won't believe what we found
So Mark was contracted to work on
His house
Extension
Any fix that fence Hoover might've hit
We're not entirely sure
New wrinkle
And if this is true which it's not
Discovered that Baldwin had
Child
I didn't report him to
It also means that Mark
Disclosure
Three hour-long interview with detectives after he was arrested for the murder
It also means that Mark didn't bring this up
Ever Nordic Crossing Hoover or and
People who work in my Baldwin's house
They were the contractors who were there working on it
Maybe we're the ones who
Carrie is implying sound
Well let's just go and have them brought this up ever
Let you go even
Tiny bit more into making sense
You need money
Right
You have
This plan
And your plan is to kill this guy
You find out that he has child pronography
But you're not going to report to the
Now why kill him
When you could block me
That makes the most sense
To everybody
You don't have to
Yeah
You're a white separatist who's trying to create his own
You have a knife
I really look at this and ISS
Part of an attempt to minimize the death of Richard bald
Of course it's a cruel tactic to make
Coming
Collection of child pronography
Right
Admit
Guilt on marks
Part but subconsciously she's implanting in the listener's mind the idea of like
If he did it was because he was hurting kids
Girl fine with it
Are you really going to do a life sentence for murdering a pedophile
It's insane if
Margarita
Should have gone to prison
First of all
I don't know
Until you prove it
Go fuc yourself
With your stray accusation
That's sort of
We've been talkin about Marc rich
For a long
Play today but for our life
We've been talking about it with that because he's faster
Mark Richards
The gift that keeps on
Doesn't seem to stop yet
Jordan
The whole time we've been operating under the
The assumption that Mark
Was off-planet
When the murder
Rihanna
Says the same thing is
Like you mentioned it in that interview with
The cops
Either
Clip
We get a new alibi
Even I like it I like a new Alibis isn't
Mark's Alibi during the exact time of the murder was that he was eating lunch
With his parents at his parents house
His lawyer Shapiro
Told him that would never be believed by the jury
However it is notable that they could never Place Mark at the scene of the crime
Mark states that he had just returned from fighting a war in the Falklands
In which she was in
In a battle for the control of planet Earth
This was a turning point in the history of Earth and
If we had lost the battle we lost control over
It was a battle with the alien races
Detroit Tiger reptilians and grays
The Raptors
And for more about the Raptors please do see my other nine interviews with
Captain Mark Richards
But the Raptors are featured in Steven Spielberg
Jurassic world and other films
Very specifically
Bucked up
Planet all the time and now it's like
Make a disclaimer at the beginning of the episode said he was off
Lunch with
His parents and his lawyers thought
That exact
Time of the murder as well right and by the way is he was fighting in the Falklands even if you was fighting aliens
Planet
Is our planet is out the window
It was the off-planet
I forgot
Grade school
If you lose the Falkland you'll lose the
The plant everybody
Comeback
That's f***** up
I mean like
That he was fighting off
Planet would be that he was in a plane
And that's off the ground
That's a shady technicality
You could have just asked your
You could have just asked
I don't think I would talk to
Why would a lawyer say that they would believe that
Yeah absolutely
Yeah that's right
Aaron
It's over like a 7
19 year old
Who work for him if it's like there could be establishing
Like if there would be evidence
Sorted out
Also small Point Richard Baldwin was murdered on July 6th
It's the 1982
The war in the Falklands ended on
June 14th
Mark absolutely wasn't
The Falklands War but even if he was he
He could have easily been in that conflict and still made it back in time to murder Richard Baldwin so that's
Is not an alibi
The other month
June 6th
July 14th almost home
Protonix
By the way almost no us
5 Personnel in Farkle
That was Britain and Argentina
Beetlejuice
Keep forgetting come on
Reset like missiles
And maybe a couple people
It was almost entirely the British of the Argentinian
Rebuttal is what ruined my document
It's not zero music
Still does not prove
Doubtful that he didn't kill Robert Richard
This is the problem I don't want to read his book now
Because he's at 40 years to write a good alibi
He's not.
That's true I need a copy
I want to read
Obviously
There's no way
We know
That Mark got setup
We know that
Now
Teri Brewster case
None
Opposite
Swiss cheese
Zero holes
Jupiter in that it is
Is 100% solid
Right
Exactly
I told Carrie
But I think
Awesome
And Mark claims that the rapper
Raptors had his back
And we're at his beck and call
And he was very arrogant back then he was 29
Lauren McLaughlin
About how the Raptors saw him as a hero
He stated it was possibly because of this they framed him for murder
Although she doesn't know that for certain
But it's a pretty good theory
Around in the Falklands these little brat
He's a little raggedy
None of the Dutchman he thought he was right
Americans
He's going to brag a little bit
And then they got to come down
What are the Raptors the reptilians
The Draco Alliance
Does it work
I like that idea I really love it you're bragging too much about your alien cult
Do you have a gas
Hero worshipping
F*** you bro sprinkler murder
The story of hubris
Absolutely
That marks dad was in play
Around the time of the murder
Started and finished it
No worries good but
It's really weird
Pick the Falklands War as like
Dwarf
Did we will lose control of
The planet if we lost
The Falklands War
Because I mean first of all it's very short war
United States
United Kingdom
I did he may have been wrapped
The Peter Falk
No I see
Speed last
Really major world of that before
Yeah I would absolutely
Thinks it's such a big deal.
Put it the routes named Major
And it have to be
So
Hear this next news about the Dutchman
What he was up to around 2
Also around the time of the murder
Alyssa Boyd Richards
Mark's father
Was seen as a hero by the British and American
Air Force and had just returned from fighting a war
With aliens
Kamchatka Russia
Mark has been playing risk
Imprisoned because that's one of the parts
Let's connect
Russia to the United States around
Brown bear brought up recruits
She amazing
They don't actually have the piece
For the rest board you have to
With aliens
Cool right around that time
Drake
Lexcorp carry talk
Talks about how earlier you know how I brought up
Andymark
Is there arch nemesis
Astoria
True man
Dear this is just
This is just whatever enjoy this not true story about Carrie
I have a life at risk
Or some s***
A side-note Project Camelot was directly threatened
Uber forced to abruptly closed down
We were told people would die including us if we pursued an important line of research
Evolving Alex
Document from Angleton files we were forced to abruptly closed down our investigation and fly back home
At the time we had been scheduled to do an interview with a key contact
When we received a phone call in our hotel room telling us
To stop
We decided not to pursue our investigation after being threatened
Source is related to our investigation
Would be tails
As a consequence the Angleton connection to the mark Richards case
Reveals a very high and deep reason
For him having been framed and in prison now
For nearly 40 years
We are very aware of How High the Angleton
Connection goes
With regard to the alien situation
I'm very aware of how high you
Sound
This is b*******
Yeah that's
Ridiculous my firm just like boilerplate response
So that is
I don't even care I don't care at all I want
Anytime I get super dry
I really wish that blackout Jordan
Call
All the time is it
They did absolutely
Fantastic
We were going to
Here's the real story we were going to interview this Soros and the guy was like
I really want to come in there like
I was probably
That would work
Maybe you'd be her next big whistleblower
Terry prison
Mark Richard
Was
Testimony of this
Andrew the other guy
Another kid
True
Also not
With regard to the trial according to mark
Relied exclusively on information provided by Andrew
See above and there appears that Andrew was highly likely
To have been a CIA undercover agent on the scene
Orchestrating events while Hoover was the Patsy
Okay yeah.
Yeah yeah you're old
Psyop operation
Lincoln
So
This is so stupid
This is just
Disappointingly stupid
Beating the ship
It's like Mark would say it
I get that
Total steps
Absolutely
Nopal
Carry a discipline
I have no face of you and I'm disappointed
The idea that you're saying
The seventeen-year-old Who mark
Completely
Lured into this murder plot
Locked up
Embarrassing
Projector
Write out those words
And just projected up on carries wall
Angela Carey
You said that
Yeah yeah
Do you want to read that out loud
I'm sure
Or at least he's willing
What's up times two
She is still saying that like this is what Mark said
Right
You have a responsibility
Full of s***
At least a little
Introduce some sort of
Skeptical
Voice to the
Horseland
Text Cliff you know
Margaret divorce
The murder Burger
Oh that's why I got a video camera not good
Keep the camera
Get the boat I don't think so I think it was
So you got a divorce
But it turns out
The mob made
The mop Karen Marks
Divorced him during the trial Mark believe she was pressured by the mob
Apparently have
Family
Her father who had ties to the Mob
The mod 1.8
The judge fell asleep during
The trial
I don't blame them
Stop blaming
Unconnected clock
Away from that 131-page interview
He's doing to them what he does to
Important takeaway
Cuz it shows his pattern
Like the way he works
With new information being integrated
Trying to play but these detectives are like
You f***** up so much
Stone like absolutely
You still got that same pattern every time or it's like
Do this happen
Don't you get bored
It's a matter of boredom
Compulsion
Like I don't know who are
Compulsive liars
They're not really control of being able
Play Bright
Some conduit Morse for
Squeezing others but the LIE is almost like
A-Tech
Never met somebody
Really
Hard about it
Is that like oftentimes
Consequential things
And we didn't write
Start to realize accused
Can't control it
I mean it's not a terrible
Call strategy either.
Lie about everything all the time
Because then you don't even know if you're like
I know you lie all the time about
I think that strategy is over
Because I think you
Sounds like a lot of me
Exodus finger gun that's the first thing I did
Is like you get a real understanding and appreciation
Is pattern Italy
And then the second thing I take away from
He's f****** boring
It takes forever for them to go
Anywhere Within
Conversation
He's talking circles
Trying to play a little game
And stuff like that
The boring game
Yeah so that's why it takes 131 pages to get through What would
Probably
If I it wasn't
It's full of him being
Now I know you're going to walk out
Boring life
Just tell him we know what happened
Very very short
Yes I do but the point I'm trying to make
But like if this judge fell asleep
I get one
Cuz I'm sure
Yeah I'm surprised
The two cops info
Play but 1.4 coffee like
Let's go get some coffee
Jesus Christ
Yeah I'm sure if there was a recorder in the coffee room serve you like f****** a******
So
All of
Is predicated on the idea
That Richard Baldwin
Is dead
Because he got more
Ono is Richard Baldwin
Leslie Mart
Stated that it is also possible
Baldwin is alive and well and it Witness
Protection
Program
Nope program
Witness Protection
Does work
Mark told me
We have to wait until
Two episodes of Project Camelot
From now where Carrie starts
These things but without the Mark told me
Yeah
If not
Still alive
He was a murder
The baseball bat and screwdriver
Sidibe
Tie down with a motor
From the boat
Very amateur izle
That's why is Bob
Surface
Marco's arrested
Testimony
After you've been killed like that
And you float up
Bread
Yeah yeah
There's a great moment
There's a great moment one of my other favorites
That interview wear
They asked a question
And Marcus
Responding to
News about something
Get Donna cup
Apple day prior
And one of the detectives like
Do you think we were
It's like those moments in like they're really funny joke because it's Mark Richard
Put myself
Situation
Feeling
Earrings
Hold on
Darius
Amazon
Nevertheless she persisted
So little
Little do you know that
Marxism
Absolutely
And it's only
Right after the
The DIA
The defense
Intelligence age
They put out a
Exonerate
Prove
That he was totally
Western office break room
Special net
Every heart was arrested the DIA
Defense intelligence agency put together a report
That refuted every charge against mark
Mark believes that report still exist
At the time there were several paper copies of the report made and distributed
Which was in 1982
And also it was sent to the DA's office
The report was supposedly has disappeared but there are still copies around
And if
Found
It would instantly freemark
Ain't going to happen
Eastsound
It ain't going to happen
My friend
That report.
I can say that with
Almost
Complete certainty
Believable at all I'm going to look it up
Could not
But this could just be a fake
But you just showed you
Your cards that you don't know a lot about the government structure
Comes up all that off
Pretty much just
Military intelligence
It's not something that's relevant to most
Normal conversation
It does
This documentary make
This British guy
And
They're really grasping
Get straws trying to do
Discredit him and you'll see what I mean
See the background of Kam as detailed in the investigation
By Paul Collins
One of the key things about that individual
Is that he has a
I guess it's sex shop
In
Amsterdam
And it's very possible that that's linked
Is the mob and
To the game Mafia excetera
And that's my conjecture not marks
You
Anybody who has a sex
Stop is conceivably in the mafia or working with the gay Mafia
Really forgot
Okay
Yes his wife
Divorced him because
There's a lot of vague mob s*** going on
Divorce the gay Mafia
Shopping apps
Amsterdam
Is there a gay Mafia
Right I know there's a number
Academy Award winners
Weakest
Or someone who has the same name as him runs a sex shop
Completely moved
I do not give a s***
In the doctor
This guy
Track down people
Like this pen pal
Mark's ex-wife
One of the other people that he Tracked Down
Was someone who
To work for Mark
Did not want to talk to
Is very suspicious
Bingo
And one of the people km has contacted is someone who works for Mark
This person refused the interview and his loyal tomorrow
Mark States the only way can't km
Could have gotten the man's name is from the side of the government
Involved
With framing him
This contributes to prove the km has been tasked
Buy them
To further discredit Mark Richards and in the process
Joanne Richards and me
Can I offer an alternative explanation
He just asked
Some people faster route
San Rafael Linda started asking around with contractors like 60
3rd the 7th interview
Different prison in Vacaville
Talking about this
Documentarian finding someone who used to work for him in
Contracting
They're saying
Because he's loyal to Mark although the alternative also as possible 25 to be involved
Which is
SmartPay remember that
Remember that thing that happened that really f***** everything up for you and kind of made people
Will talk to you about it over and over and over and over again you don't want to really really feel like
Okay then work good
Really Bass
Journalistic
Investigative journalist has skills could find out
People who work
Like it we if you go to
To like go to Northern California go round
People go to the
Relevant figures
Talk to Mark Richards
Ex-wife would know some of the people that work there until at least be able to point them in the right direction to find someone who does
He also interviewed The Crossing
Who else work exactly giving me the name
Government
Is proof that there
He's in on the frame job
Nonsense
Km is working for the luciferian
Rebellion also known as The Reptilian
Play
Draco Alliance
That's
That looks
Seferian
Those are those are
We're done with the
Navigate
To jump to the reporting
Cuz you know Mark Richard
No s***
This is Olga
Carrie's making a
I tripped out of this goddamn prison
Doll pencil
She's not going to
Just do that is like
Control
And running interference
For her number one whistleblower
Exactly Piper Piper
Exactly
We get to
They didn't even bother
Talking to
Minerva's in the Wind
We don't know where she is.
Enervate
So we get to
Clip where were talking
Marc rich
Info
Like his is his
Weak right
Not good
Look it's not that excited
But it is
Kind of blow Hardy and V
Okay I like that
The end so it's worth it for that but
I'm not happy that this is
The first one cuz I wanted to come in with a Raptors eat
Chocolate kind of vague
Stupid
Like I said
I enjoy the
Mark agrees with the following concepts
Is that there are many different timeline
The Earth is a hologram and that this whole
Galaxy
Multiverse is in essence
Probably a series of holograms
You see what I'm saying this
What kind of bland boring stuff for hold your horses
Humans have simultaneous incarnations and reincarnate
Time and space are simultaneous
Mark thinks that our brain
Can assist other versions of ourselves on other timeline
And yes there are armies of Androids and underground bases both under under the US
And in China
Underground and he has seen the Chinese
Android
Isn't that great that turn isn't that amazing
Another version of yourself in another reality
Of course we really need to settle this I know everybody's been wondering
Yes there are Android underneath
The underground area is lousy with
Yeah that
Yes
I got this question
Once and for all
Android
Terry's community
More paranoid paranormal
Takeover of the
The Earth
Snooze
It's already
The Takeover of planet Earth has actually already happened
We are battling the 6A eyes ongoing
We are also battling the Draco reptilians and certain species of Gray's
Directly
Big Ray's report to the wraps the wraps report to the Draco
They are using AI as well
And The Troggs
Also unacceptable HSBC
There also are working against us
Tuff Stuff
We are busy
Bright
I need to know where the spiders are
Music piano WrestleMania is coming up this weekend and it just it's like we're in a cage match and it is a handicap
It is a f****** with us
Clearly
Regimen
Rented
Hierarchical structure of aliens overall against
That's not good that's bad really mean
Marley's doctor group
I don't know anymore about the AI
6 AI
It does feel
6A II alone are f****** with the entire speech
Important but it's not apparently
Because we don't get any clarification
So taking it from that
Space
Now we get
Terrestrial
Geopolitics
So this is worried about the you know our relations with the rest of the world
Be at China
Russia
These sorts of places
Turns out Mark knows what
What's going to happen with all three of those situation regarding Iran War yes it is happening
They took troops out of Syria but left the Russians in charge on the ground there
Naturally there are
In this war
Which is actually what I have been saying
And other war with the wrong does Alita the war with China
And the Russians will
Side with us
And there's more about this
Prophecies
Are greater prophecy
Which
She says it perfectly Illustrated
Exactly how that conversation must have gone
And then he picks up on context clues
Yeah absolutely that's right that's my higher-ups
Exactly what you said because you are right
Amazing all of your sources are Justice
Yeah
So earlier
We got some strong indication
Weather
The Pendragon
Excluded
People that's one thing they
Not great
Is sort of racial profiling of the clerk at Montgomery Ward
Not great either and that's why this clip sounds
Suspicious
Sickle cell anemia reptilians are not compatible with this Gene and rule out any
That code for genetic breathing
Food or even sexual purposes
Stop it not feed off the block
Race and not gas specifically off
Parts of the black race
That have sickle cell anemia
Mark you're a bad f****** dudes
You know that other people get
Sickle cell anemia right or sickle cell
Disorders like it's not
Uniquely
African American
It's not like people who
They might as well be black Annie
Mark gopal Mark Mark Mark Mark
Mark
Mark Mark
Real growth
Text Erin other
Fitz's
Different about them
God
Why
You could just not because it's because he's racing
He has a Jeep
Heated feeling that people of different races are
Wow he created
Two space mythology
All this stuff
It's a very convenient
To find some sort of in
Inside your face mythology
That justifies the race
Feelings that you already have
Very.
Yeah
So you wanted to know about the spiders
Did they invent the AI
No
Next clip
I think the
Spiders might just
I don't even really have any later
Don't know
For sure
Is is crawling with Psych
And there have been some reports
In the northern United Kingdom
But here
Carrie has to say
Here's what Darius say
About that
The situation with spiders
Currently
On the planet
I asked him about Sardinia because recently I was
Asked if I would lead a tour to Sardinia
Because there are many ancient sites there and lots of evidence of reptilians
Involvement
However I told Mark that I have declined to go to Sardinia because it
When I looked at it
On a psychic intuitive level
I saw
There were tons of spider rings and Reps
Aliens there
And Mark said I was absolutely right he said he would even go there and his true
Not only in the past but also now
And my apologies
To the people that live in Sardinia
I think it's probably a very beautiful I like
I've seen pictures of it
And I do apologize for this information but
What can you do
Don't shoot the messenger so I've been yet
I love that that is my favorite thing
Search
Wake up in my life
OSHA
Carrie just told me we were covered in spiders
And that's based on the rest of
Just for a comparison
From what I understand
Miles Johnston has a source that has told him
Prepare a spider beings hiding out
In
Play area
North England
Call the Lake District
And in the tunnels there so that is also
Very disconcerting
Formation
It sure is
Through living in the
Spider
Could be
They do live in England
Right but I think supplies
That's not worth talking about that there are spiders places
These are aliens
So she apologized
Note to be fair it doesn't it does seem to be
Adjusting to follow from the way she talked about it
In the UK
That is a ton
Inside
Snowman
I got nothing on that other than
I'm sorry for everyone affected yet as well
Sergenians
Dude
It's rough
Play the top situation
Absolutely
You didn't know about
Are you going to do
So
So Trump is a guy
Marquez talks about him
Mark has been kind of pro Trump in the past
Yeah
You still is surprised
But this is
Phrase wheel
The Trump Administration
They are the only ones fighting for us in the US at this time
But there is something going on right now with that Administration
Not say what that is
Then once again I am going to apologize
The people of Sardinia
Something bad happening
Qualify what you're talking about
I'm going say something's up
Thumbs up
Now takes
Turn in a Durex
I could never have
Why we do Project Camelot up is
David
But this isn't good
Predicted
I asked him if Kevin
Stacy was set up
Degrees is Kevin Spacey is being set up because of what he knows
Demonstration of him yesterday ending her
But also I will
Wonder if it's just
Cuz he was in
Well that actually
Any reason
Not something that I've
Well there's like a
The denial is
Stuff like that
The version that I don't think I've ever heard
I sure just like who gives a s***
Anyone suggest that
Too much
If that's
Crazy
That's wild crazy to carries asking
I do think it's just going to be a space in this
I know that sounds like I'm choking
Yeah it's a bit
Like maybe this is an incidental things we've already talked about
Which she just found out that Kevin Spacey is in trouble for so long to figure out the
Spider-Man was bitten by a radioactive
Spiders
Red Sprites
Yeah that's possible
I don't know I don't know but you know what there's other news
I'll be honest with you towards the end of this
Really Zone
Bitwit
Exclude played I got like it was almost like I got jostled out of asleep or like someone threw a bucket of
Cold water on my Facebook
Throwback
Did I hear that correctly
The craziest
Should I've ever heard
There was a raptor wedding
In late February around the 28th
And Mark says this was a major wedding uniting
Two major Raptor Family Lines Glenmark calls it a great
Love story
There's a raptor weather
There was a raptor wedding and bark is happy for the couple
Why do rappers get married human concept
Why do they get married monogamy is not necessarily a human
Constructor
In the wild
But the formal ceremony of marriage is something
Creative
By the Raptor exactly
Boom
Turn it around
How else are you going to allocate land
To your face
They live in
Well
Subspace
I know I know you're like
This is good stuff
This is stupid doctors are in love
What about spiders that do they get married
What about the dog be
No mayonnaise
I just thought
Contacts that is being an episode where we're talking about Kerry Cassidy running interference for a f******
Murderer
That's a delight
There was a Rapture wedding
Oh and here's an update on
What does socialite news
Ridiculous
So we learned a little bit of the human celebrity news with Kevin
Between two major Raptor families
Back to humans
Celebrity
Because there was a
No
Celebrity world
Not too long
To know about it
Regarding Jan-Michael Vincent the actor who was a close friend of Mark's and died of
Alcoholism because he had seen too much what would too much and couldn't handle it
What's Mark have the utmost respect for him and misses him
Jan-Michael Vincent
That is really one of those biscuits
Yeah there's no Michael Vincent
Uvula
Yeah the Airwolf
Sam's
Maybe he just watched
Or in prison
Current like you died on the 10th of February that's pretty close to Wyandotte
Carrie was going to do this interview
That really make sense
About that being free
Real cool
Clip where Carrie she's giving her audience
Advice that will work
Against her best interest
I want to thank you for watching
And for listening and for supporting the work of Project Camelot
Take care and please use discernment
And to your own investigation
Thank you and goodnight
The idea of it are saying you should do your own research is only going to lead people to realize that
She's full of s*** and doesn't know any
So
Against
Telling people to research
You don't want to be a truth-teller and a tree
Peter kind of person to be like
Don't worry about it worry about it we've all been there I got this covered
Super weird
Decarie decided to
To even get in
To any of the specific
Of marks
Because she has
Such a poor grasp
The details of the
What's going on
Circulates her interact
Tamar so parallel
Do that police interview
It just like
It opens up a can of worms where it really reveal
Like how manipulative
She is by him
And how willing of
Participants
In that man if
Along with him
I just think it's
The real stupid games
It's a little
Would like disconcerting
Cuz it's almost like she's in a one-woman
Colt 21
Yeah you are you are full on willing to do
Anything
Justify what it is that inside parks
To her friend Simon parkes
He's also in that calls as
Three-person
Because he I mean like even in the
The trailer for that
Is The Tech Guys make
Km
There you got some interviews
The people who are in
The UFO community
It doesn't really great to service
We're trying to actually look for people
Go to just pass off
Well you know I don't think
I think there's a fair point
Mainstreet
Quote unquote
Serious
UFO
Don't like Mark
So yeah she is sort of in a world of her own
Yeah
And I think
Drawing attention
Intuit makes
Spurlock's so much
So when she does.
Look this is stupid
You can only hide
Persolog about him
A lot of people are more people are aware
Is Dory
The fact that he's a f****** murderer
And it's hilarious
Date the factory
He's transitioned into this guy's
I know the Raptors they get married they take your chocolate they're fighting again
Other beings
Isn't that Beatles down
About Stargate
Funny on some level
When you when you
Uncoupling
From the fact that he is
The kind of guy
Who would manipulate a seventeen-year-old
Murdering
A guy who was in his
His wedding
And tell him
Finish the job
With a screwdriver
You forget about that part hilarious
You keep that part in
Very upsetting
Yeah there is a certain amount of
Parallel here with
Aj2 in that
It's like
Indict
Because of the
Popularity
Like she's running this
And the goal really for these types of scams
Is to keep them
Contain
It starts getting out
And you start getting attention
Trying to actually
Scary
Bradley's not on the level
Necessarily
Responsible for the overexposure of
Mark know I absolutely
She is
I think it's just a natural thing that's going to come out
Awesome
You don't like the idea of
As long as a
A couple
People start talking about like the idea that there's
This guy
Who got these
Kids who work for
Murderer guy
Then he went to prison
Started
Career in Santa
Are you presenting at
Is real right
Lasers that we're going to destroy Bridges nights
Service Roundtable
Too good of a story for people
Like enjoy or look into
So you reach a critical mass
Once enough people are looking
The story
That like
It's almost
Destined to blow up if you're trying to 4
Flix with way less interesting stories than this and you were still like
The staircase before I turned it off
This is not the time to litigate this
Amazing series
This guy is doing
Probably
What will be animes
About this
The story
A part of the
The story now is Victor
Is
A victim of March
Ovulation
Willingly
And
Also
Defense
I didn't forgot
Nearly within the scope of what I
I could do
Hey we need we need
We could call call Larry
We wouldn't be able to know the name of the
What's not really mean
Do we need to pay back over Patriots
Yeah everybody listen your knowledge by right now
Really go to the patreon we need
$2,500 by tomorrow because otherwise
Black
Very dumb
Learn that we've now
But we did learn about repatriation
Alonzo
More of a
This is dumb in more of a concentrated
Evil
Very hard with her
Hasn't read that interview with the
Detective he hasn't looked at the court records or anything like that
But he's pretending that she did
Eva Lin
Negligent
But I don't
I think the cheese
Nearly pure
Pretending
But she has this information
Right
Information
You still believe
Fuckingawesome
But I still think
But she's blocking about what you say
You think so
Read all that
And just dismiss it as
I don't you read the 131
If you read that
Cannot imagine for a second
But he's not a
I don't think she ready
But
I wouldn't be surprised if she dismissed all of this
All of the court records
Lesbian
Just a railroad job and worry about it
I mean rap
Spock
Because your defense
Murderer without having evidence
Yeah
Will be back on Monday with the new episode but we're also on Twitter
You started a Twitter and I got rid of
Almost
Really close to the
The same tires
We are and we're on
Call go home and tell your mother
Step bro
Tribology.
I know
That guy didn't
Yeah he was involved in
The Palazzo
We all know that he doesn't like shopping Amsterdam that's true
Are you looking up whether or not Peter Falk killed someone
The good people of Sardinia
Most of them I mean I'm sure some sardinians if 12 people play
Most of the population
Technically not probably absolutely nobody
Holding
Alex