Alexandra Thurston color
Little bit
About Alex Jones Jordan
Who's your favorite in the Greek
Michael talked about this before
Normandy Inn
Humanity
The irony of him being married to Aphrodite
Married
Actually got around
To the one crippled the god
Pieology
Norwegian
How about
Don't know about who you got for I don't f****** know you got a famous for no reason
Just to walk that you can get in God because of the words
Alright alright
I don't know all that much about the Norwegian Pantheon but
Like to take a moment
Show
So first of all
And your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Next song
Text Jeff
You don't even on a
I appreciate that very much
Join our globalist
Start song about until your brilliant someone someone sodomites
Appreciate that
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
You don't need it done in further elevated level we appreciate that
Someone sodomites Italy
Has a Caribbean
Thank you so much beagle bagel
I like to shower
Just bored with these Gents
You can do that but
YouTube business
I would say
Came back from rir we break the deposition episode
And then
Project Camelot episode
I would say come back and so
Into the present day of Alex Jones
Something that I wanted to do or kind of thought about doing
Was
Some of the stuff
What happened wow
On break
I took just a catch-up to prezza
Someday as it work
Compilation
Worst
Yeah 3 a.m. on an infomercial
Yeah yeah good songs
Now That's What I Call Music 44
Looking through some of it
I was like well
Get mired down in a bog
If we do that we're never going to get back to present
If we just constantly are like looking back in the rearview at
Something that might have been kind of f***** up that happened
Alex the chicken restaurant for him yelling at them
That's alright
Joe Rogan came on Alex's show
And that's all good and well that's
That's totally fun
Make that not so
Something I missed
We need to talk about all that much
It's two things
First
Is that when Joe comes on Alex's
The show
What's really going on is Joe is being sucked up
Show
Instructor Joe being f***** up
When Alex goes on Joe show that's interesting for our purposes
Because that's about Alex
Show coming on Alex's
Kind of about Alex but Alex's are staying the same s*** he usually doesn't Jose like wow
So who gives a s***
Ivan the second thing is that I listen to
March 25th
Episode part where Rogan was
And it's just a 20-minute
Segments of the one-hour interview
Croagunk
And it's entirely just
Based on the
You want to see the rest is kind of a teaser
Trailer on His Radio Show in order to lure people to his website
I'd rather jump
Tupac closer to the present
Since this will be
Thursday's episode wanted to do Thursday and Friday April 4th and 5th
But there's
There's too much on the 4th
That I had to look into
And I think is very important for our purpose
And so
Unfortunately
Get to it eventually
I forgot my mom's birthday happy Birthday gorgeous mom
That response was not the I forgot my mom's birthday
Well I'm glad that we're going over this.
Both my brother and my mom's birthday
To give them a phone call because as we learned in this first clip
We might not be
Here too long
April 4th
2019 under Hub Dallas jobs
Well I just walked in there
2 minutes ago
But the headline
For the
Has a show in it
To share the audio and video link
And a headline
It's only 6 months away
Total civilizational
Collapse put off this call for six months it won't really true
Concept civilization collapses
I hope you
He will
Introduces into the
Proceedings of the
This April 4th
Episode
Demons
Okay
Visa vie
Kanye West
If you recall not a couple of months
Sagapo Alex
Get Kanye on his show desperately
Democratic altitude is changed
Universe
Twisted Sage
Sworn to destroy all human life
On this planet
Bible stand
Judaism Islam says
So demons are telling Kanye West to do something I don't know you're the guy who knows a pop-culture
Little bit more than me
I do believe
Brunswick
He has a Dark Twisted Fantasy
Demonic sorcerer
This is just about the idea that Kanye was like saying
Slavery was before and I shouldn't said that
Alex's I think he's trying to say
Like
Not saying those things anymore for a bit
Hey give me a give me a shout out for 808 and heartbreaks
It's a what's going on here and
In terms of all the stuff that I like to look into
So I just decided
Leave that alone
But it is
Is very important because it inform some of the stuff
It's coming up
On this episode
Alex talks about
Not the kids toy
And indicates that he knows nothing
About that
By the way everything Plato wrote about almost all of it they've dug up or found
Brought about
That was Atlantis
In the Atlantic Ocean Island said flying machines and an energy
Power exploded
And then four years
Because of all the dust in the air
Really happens like that
Great
Until
Might have been talking to somebody
He fixes boilers little horns a little teeth so you don't get scared
Deal with the Devil.
Plato only talked about Atlantis a couple times
Tomatoes and critias
The two dialogs none of that stuff
Impact the destruction of Atlantis
Telling of it has to do with the fact that they got into a war the atlanteans
Put them down
Are smaller cities
We're able to take out
The atlanteans and then the gods punish them with earthquake
Corn stuff I got it wasn't a white glowing power-source attic
Exploded in flying
Washington all that b*******
Netflix
I love the idea of him just saying like
What artists Martin said I think he said
I think that's what is the location
Okay
I thought all his right ear like we got it
Like the idea of a of an archaeologist being like
Video game missions list
Yeah that's crazy but then also the other thing is I was like
You think
That's like if you read tomatoes
When critias you know why he knows this information
That is B Salon
Legendary ruler ancient Greece
He went and spoke with the
Egyptian
You went over to Egypt
She got the story of Atlanta
This from the Egypt
Came back
Controls that
Plato's grandfather
I believe and that's how it got passed down to check out
That's it's clear the lineage of information
In Plato's writing
The clear he's not talking to Demons
Though it is very important
Again
Dementia Metallica saying that they hide their teeth
So they don't
Thing for them to do that is important
So hold on to that thought as we jump
You never reply.
Are you hiding your teeth and wings from me
I'm not
But we will get into where he go
Get that idea from
Is almost gone
Purposeful
Take down
Of the planet
Not just to the Stars to other dimensions
Elevation
Purposes
They found forms of immortality
We're just a thought
Youfit globalism was always meant to fail
The sublevel
Not the actual Elite the shovel age
Get really high level
Percent of humans will be taken out.
The whole picture
You're told humans are an abomination
God says we will give us a code
I truly forever with him
And be uploaded to the Consciousness and then move on to the next planet
You like wait a minute
Call childhood
The real Illuminati
OSS before that
Total highest level
To see you read those books you watch those movies
Explain something to you
They're telling you how the cow ate the cabbage
What is mouth
The cabbage
Alex loves that expression
Feel like a fool
Ever have
Simply because it made me remember something I'd forgotten
And that I really should have remember
I read childhood
The 1950s
Clark Beckham jr.
But unfortunately
I remember that it was about an alien invasion
Destruction
Planet little bit Gray
Visit the
And when I did I realize that Alex is very well maybe
The power behind the globalist
On childhood's end
Have you ever read it
No I'm not ready okay good cuz I'm going to
But I also
I wasn't
Totally huge on Syfy as I
As I've gotten to like
Late Junior High into high school that wasn't certain my bike up at
Sweeter when I was
Younger but unfortunately because
I read a lot of things
Before I was probably old enough to really
Internalized a lot of them had lost my memory of it
Tana should I read
Yesterday
Because I like
I need to get into this
So if you have it then
The book is about a child
There's a SyFy Network series based on it
Couple years back
Future where the countries of Earth are at the brink of nuclear war by way of militarizing
Space race
Destroy the planet
For the trigger could be pulled alien ships appear and nuclear war gets put on the back burner
These are going to be supervising
To make sure that we don't bring
Extinction
And since there are a ton of spaceships over majors
Humanity goes along with it
The aliens called the overlords are in charge of the major issues of the world at all
The only direct interference that they have an international relations
And other than that outside of the sphere of international relations
Humanity
These affairs
Watch The Outlaw bullfighting
Because the barbaric
And wants to relieve the persecution
One of the white minority and post
Apartheid South Africa
Because at the time that he wrote this
There was a perception of Apartheid
And then it's all going
Go to be flipped in the white minority there is
Be brutally prefer
Call imagine that being
The overlords Clark
Conceived of
Would think that was such an inhumane
Situation
That he would try they would try and rectify that
Unsurprising
The overlords wood
Be supporting
That's the future he did now
It's just fun
So the overlord supervisor Carolyn to the secretary-general
United Nation
Which is where we get one of our first connection to Alex's world
Alex believes that the globalist
The man whom the leadership of the UNR
They take their orders from an off-world race
An idea that is a very basic
Of childhoods
Emma storyline
They're up
Joker Ellen speak
Next to the secretary-general
His physical form
The secretary-general presses on the
And likely won't fully trusty overlords if they
Karelin discusses the idea of his superiors and
Decides to promise to show their true form to humanity
After 50 years
Appointed which humans will have gotten used to the overlords being around and will be so shocking
For them to see
Their true form
When the time comes
The overlords apr2
And they look exactly like the traditional image of.
This is the second direct mirrored Alex's world
He believes that offworld entity
Please that are giving orders to the globalist Iraq
Who don't want you to think of their demons
We heard it earlier than that clip said they're hiding their teeth and wings
So you don't you don't get afraid
The concept of mask the image of looking like a
Frost is an idea
But he almost certainly lifted wholesale from this
Almost in
And it gets it gets weirder
I remember this now the secretary-general in childhood
Childhood's end
The Moon is that crazy who's Ricky
Exactly his last name but yeah
Humanity through a number of years of prosperity and peace ultimately uninspired and
So an artist colony is established in opposition to the overlords
The people are doing
On an island called
The colony is supposed to be utopian place where Humanity can Thrive but ultimately
The inhabitants there blow themselves up with a nuclear bomb which I think is where Alex is getting his ideas about what happened to Atlantis from
That we heard earlier in this episode
If only he was really into banana
Underneath his house
That he worship that would make Justice
Good babe
So I'm skipping over a lot of stuff here but aren't necessarily here to help you
Usher
Into the next phase of our
These are the orders of
Something called the over
Thuja god-like
It's made up of
Of other species
From throughout the planet
Throughout the Universe
The overlords mission was
Facilitate
The inevitable
Humanity into the overmind
Cosmic
Midwives unable to ascend
Into the overmind
Only able to experience of the Divine process vicariously
This also mirrors Alex's ideas about the globalist black and some spark that Humanity has
Something that they are
It's not so clear from that the text
That the Gaillardia
To become one with the overmind
But knowing Alex's
Psychology
It's easy to
See how he would put
Project that onto
Do these characters in the book how bitter about the
They just have to serve the overmind and help
Become one with you
And it's not a it's not like a manipulation
That was something that was going to happen
What's happening one way or the other they were just there to help the process
Let's go smoothly
To us
For something like
But Alex
As a suspicious guy
Could easily read the book if you like
They made the kids
Lack of creative
Like 88
Add arle overlords the overmind
You're asking me the overtime but also to
These ideas from like another book from like the 90
30s
Someone else wrote ideas
That he had read other places
Anything like that
I think the book was good I enjoyed it and everything but I also thought it had some
Structural problem
Exploring
The becoming one with the overmind happens
Because the children of earth begin to
Express psychic abilities that evolve quickly
They become more and more of a unified and
All of these individual children become one
Theater the metaphor
Use the idea of
Like Island
While the ocean is there appear to be separate the ocean disappears
You see them as
Connected
Through
The bottom of the ocean
All of the islands are actually the
That's what happens to these children they all become one
And become
I'm completely a different thing than the rest of
Humanity
The overlords are not doing this to the children they are just there to Usher through the process that's happening with or without
However the misrepresentation that there's some
Do children of Earth is completely alive
I have to go almost there targeting the children
And trying to change them who the water through hormone
These sorts of
Baby ID
All the attacks
Clearly mirror
In a misreading of childhood's end
Any idea has destroyed
The overlords by the way
And the children mature enough to ascend into Oneness with the overbite
The overlords move on to wait their next mission
From the overmind
The next species
With Aiden
Roderick
Escape the chaos on Earth by Stone
Supply ship
It goes back to the overlords planet
He has a conversation with some of the aliens about what's going on
And realizes there's nothing left
At all
He hasn't over this ending with Uvalde
Children there no more humans
Very well becoming Overlord
What kind of an existence would you have if you just went along with them to the next
Planet that they go
Functional functionally immortal
The overlords live forever he wouldn't even make it to the next
Inappropriate
So you have nothing left
Decides to witness the end of her
The end of the planet
The overlord
About to experience
As it
Because they have cameras watching the planet but they don't know experientially what it's
Like for the end of
Planet planet in report
That the destruction of the plant because he realizes
Is that the overlords work
Some sort of nefarious
He's giving them whatever information
Could be helpful to them besides everybody has a purpose
But before that happen
He has this exchange with rash of very
Another one of the Overlook
And said here's something else you've never explained
When your race first
First came to Earth
The distant past
What went wrong
Have you become the symbol of fear and Evil
Rash of Eric smile
He didn't do this as well as karelin could but it was a fair imitation
No one ever guess
And you see now why we could never tell you
There was only one event that could have made such an impact
But at the very end
What do you mean
What are your skies a century-and-a-half ago
That was the first meeting of our two races
You from a distance
And get you feared and recognize
As we knew that you would
He wasn't precisely a memory
You've already have already had proof
The time is more complex than your science ever imagine
For that.
For that memory was not of the past
But if the future
Azusa closing gears when your racewood known everything was finished
We did what we could but it wasn't
Keynesian
And because we were there
We became identified with your races
Yes even while it was 10,000
In the future
It's as if a distorted Echo and reverberated rounds and closed circle of time
In the future the past
Call it a not a memory but a premonition
The idea was hard to grasp
Silence
Yeah you should have been prepared
Proof enough that cause and effect
Good reversed
And they're normal sequence
There must be such a thing as racial memory
And that memory is somehow
Time
Do it the future in the past or one
That is why
Years ago man had already glimpsed
Distorted image of the overlord
The fear and Terror
Erase memory don't make sense
When you think about it be
An expression of epigenetics
And he always talks about the ideas
Being something much
Located in grander than
Instinct
What he believes doesn't line up with anything real
But it lines up perfectly with the concept
Expressed in childhood
I think that Alex just believe the science
Fiction books are real
Childhood's end
A giant
That explains so much
What Alex beliefs about the
Bees that are behind
Globalist
But he's again
And I feel really stupid
No that's stupid but I wish I could remember that book better
Months and months ago whenever you're going through this because I think a lot of our confusion could have been dismissed with like he's just talked about
Can Arthur C Clarke
You think that's real
Reasonable for you to have missed
And let me tell you
Cuz I was like 13 when I read it
No because this is another book
To the list of books that Alex
And that is a shock ever
That's a
I think he was probably super illiterate when he was younger
Like I don't think I think his inability to read or unwillingness
He is probably a more
Recent feature of his life I think probably in junior high and high school he was probably
He was a Satanist
True
Satanism science-fiction
I think if we
We're a little bit more critical of him
I think we would end up finding
Almost
He thinks his real that sounds stupid go back
Like it's just all old scientific
All right we got a new book club
I think we do what the hell
Right
Start with asiimov and move on from there
Isaac Asimov vitamin too hard for it
I think you probably sticks
To be more pop
Kind of cereal
So I think this is crazy credibly stupid
Reading that book was the
There's that
Oh my God
I can't believe I talked about racial memory in this book
It was just a book that talked about racial memory I wouldn't be like alright that's one thing
But the fact that it's the same book where you have
An alien race
The communicates with the UN
It involves
Messing with
Quit messing with the children
The demise of the planet the races and the idea of them
Hiding their appearance cuz they look like
What we think of his demon
Like all of that is so much Alex in one
Concentrated burst
Those nuts
Is a real Revelation from
Hodor twist
I like that
So anyway
This week's Alex ain't got to follow God
This might as well just being overzealous
Just programmed swine
I'm not sure they did they were very
Restrained
Group
An alter-ego
Operations against
But one way or the other
Intelligent
Following orders
Nevermind
They're trying to override it
Lucifer
The globalist commercial break
He's a little over-the-top it's not his face.
Do you like bacon goddamn
Yeah I guess what Alex believes the opposite
Forces in the world are our Jesus
Science fiction
That are real
Great
I don't understand the Imagine
Like it's B pretty embarrassing
Like his actual beliefs that he's a thousand
Do this show over text when I hear stuff like that
What's important isn't like
Debunking
In his world
Because it's
It's an embarrassing Act
To do
I still enjoy doing it
Sometimes never read childhood
But the important thing is cutting
Through the effect
He has on the world
How stupid this bowls
And so that's why I'm glad that this next clip
Leads us into that territory
When Alex comes back
He starts talking about the idea
That you know there's a difference
Between Christian
And non-christians
Even if you are genetically the same
Genetically similar Christian and non-Christian there's a fundamental difference between
Two of them
This is this is going to leave me too
I'm pretty
Kimber wander any other cases all the world
Everything else
Have a tribe that's Christian
But I always produced
20 *
Prosperity
He says 20 times more
Alex is like this, too.
Actions are more productive
Banana mystery
You at the group switch
Because
He goes on to say that he's not even talking about Mainline glitterbug Christian Christian
Which is something that's only vaguely defined
Even buy him if at all
So I've no idea how anyone would be able to study that in order to produce productivity statistics
Real Christians first genetically similar anime
Ideas for a
Computer research study
I don't understand how that would work
What are those BuzzFeed quizzes
What what what kind of person are you a real how productive are you go from there
It's ludicrous I pretty sure he's making it up and I don't really have any interest in
Discussing it
My sense of it because I've listened to a ton of him is he's using productivity there as kind of Apple
Placeholder
I did to talk about
Relative value of
Yeah
I want to take a moment to discuss
Because like I said it falls in line with this thing that Alex does all the time where he likes to create the perception
But if there's a group of Christians living next to a group of Muslims or anime
Invariably the Christian group will be upright great citizen
And the Muslims will try to f*** with
As Alex isn't that sounds right
So it provides
A ton of his writer
Not just this clip
It's something that is a is a
Piece of his worldview
He's expressing in the
Auspices of discussing productivity
But that's not what
Is about
And what makes this expresses
Particularly f***** up is like you responded
Uses the example of Rwanda
The reason is that the problem is there was that whole genocide
Which is perpetrated by the Hutu
Patootie
Well it's true that some Tootsie were Christian
And somewhere Muslim
The Hutu were mostly Christian
But the real issue here is not that
And the real issue is
The religious aspect
Very little to do
With what happened
Against the Tutsi
The direct result of Belgium Colonial ization
Central Africa
When the control of Rwanda from Germany
They found a unified culture that was made up of three
The Tutsi Hutu and floppy
Differences in physical characteristics and traditional occupation
They existed as a single group
In the days of like let's say 400 years back
The Tutsi and Hutu lived in the symbiotics.
The Tutsi herders raise cattle on the land couldn't be used
The crops and manure from
The cattle would multiply the
Videos of the crop
Apps that were raised by the Goo
Go to Farmers
The belgians differences
Groups
As evidence of prevailing theories of the time about Aetna
Superiority
This is to say that the majority Hutu were mostly peasants
Well the Tutsi were mostly cattle herders and up had more property
And had physical characteristics more attractive
To the colonizer
That's the belgians believe that the Tutsi were better people
They provided education
For the Tutsi and
Established indirect rule over
The country through them
Though they were a minority of the population
Making up on the
Country
In 1926 the belgians
SD
Which position
The power and authority over things like
Taxation
The Alita manga Tootsie's all the benefits that came from going along with
The belgians of setup
Were they were the Superior Group who wielded all the political power in the country
The ethnic status quo was reinforced
Internally
Empowerment Group
Began to get organized
Such as the association
For social
Promotion
And the hutus social movement
Two groups that would combine the 1959
Keeshond
The party of movement
To I-40 map
Naturally just made the tootsie Elites a little bit nervous so they started their own
Union Nacional rwandaise
Which would begin clashing with a hoot
Inevitably
The crisis became violin
And many Tootsie went to Exile
Whereupon largely Hutu Rwanda voted for its independence in 90
From this point onward the tootsie that remained in Rolando we're harshly ruprecht minority
Flag before independence
Ugis from their Homeland
Gorilla attacks
Across the borders of Zaire Uganda in Tampa
Part of this was probably motivated by the fact that many of the
Duty at work
Interested in the countries that they
Where they found themselves unable to successfully start a new life
And wanted to go back
The Ugandan government to both Milton a boat and Idi Amin
Establish rules that made the Rwandan refugees
You're subject to arbitrary detention by the police
Amber scapegoated for
Domestic
Which only exacerbated their desire to go
Back home
Between 1987 and 1990 the tubes
The group
Call Deborah
Front the RPS
Attempted to negotiate a quote unconditional return
Of all Rwandan refugees
Angela kordall Rwanda
Is equal rights
The Hutu president
Papa Romano's
Cruise. No more people
Crpf took up arms
Interesting border this past Friday
More of you
Do our country is full
Very similar rhetoric
Does never
Good places
The fighting went on for 3 years
On the verge of victory
When foreign forces intervene
To save the harbor yamani government
These forces
Ironically included the Belgium
Who's 60 years prior he's set up a brutally protein social
Structure only now to be militarily aiding the Hutu government
Repulsing the Tootsie
She from
Returning to the
They don't give a fuk
These people do not
Colonialism
On April 6th
1994 president
His private jet was shot down here
Kigali Airport
Crpf
The Tutsi claim that the Hutu extremists
Adam cell shot down the plane of the false flag against
The course is Still Remains an open question although there's pretty strong indication
The arguments about something
False Flags
And the RPF probably dead
Almost there
Regardless what happened next
Is much less an open Quest
The next 100 days
Between 800000 and 1 million tooth
They were slaughtered
By the Rwandan Army
As well as the government-backed civilian militia the intercom way
Some estimates claim that
7 out of 10 226
Sims were murdered
In the genocide of 90
12 people who are murdered
Which made up approximately one-third of their population
After propaganda started circulating that the
Patois
And abetting
Of course they do
This piece of History
Unspeakably horrible
And the consequences of which ran
Inspired of the direct result of indirect result
Of colonial with systems that were put in place by the belt
Alex and talk about to have a Christian African is great but
Banana Mr Muslim African
Is Barbera
But that the Cowardly an idiotic way to look at the world
But doesn't match up with history at all
Also the belgians were Christian
Consideration about what the Belgian
Did to the Congo
Were King Leopold the 2nd
Countryside
Harvest natural resources like rubber
And killed Millie
Or just failed to do a good enough job
Ammunition because it was really expensive
Back then
So they approve the eat bullet they used was used appropriate
To prove that each bullet
Kill a person
Cutting off the right hand of the deceased
Of course enterprising soldiers started to realize that if they did
Just cut off people's hands they could use the bolts for whatever they want
I'd like recreational shooting
Advise the scourge of bodily mutilation of Congolese
The practice got pretty out of control
Arbitrary bottle
Mute
At the hands of the ostensibly Christian
Colonialist
To the flavor
Use of rape as a method
Preparer login
Torture the burning Village the kidnapping
Children starving
All of that
Because of the Unspeakable horror he's
Subjected the Congolese people to
King Leopold Damascus staggering fortunate
100-500 million-dollar
Which is reportedly made him
What year did reportedly making it 1.2 richest
Person in the world
So I guess we are convinced the Christians
Pretty productive in Africa
Po-boy
Word gotten out about what Leopold was up to and he was forced to relinquish
Control over the colony
To the Belgian government
Ultimately however the Legacy
See if the Butcher of
The Congo has lived on
10 weeks after Congo declared its
Dependents for Belgium
Belgium
General Booth
Coletta coup d'etat
It took over the counter
Empower
Until a few months
Before his death in 90
Seco presided over one of the worst human-rights records ever routinely torturing and murdering political
Reportedly even feeding to tractors
The crocodiles
Purchase power
He'll be hard to draw parallel
2R the colonial days
Colonial
Pecos rule
Snowden
Have a habit of
Disfiguring the bodies of this
You know what I said that it would be hard to draw that parallel
I'll let the Chicago Tribune
Quote ma'buta's critics say that
Compression spring from the colonial history fits that an awful example
Among other atrocities the rulers of the former Belgian Congo use
Used to slice two hands
A rubber workers off if they were caught misbehaving
King Leopold The Butcher of the Congo was a Catholic
Started to criticizes murderous habits and you decided
So also you may remember that Paul manafort Rodger Stone
Professor Christian
Made a whole lot of money lobbying for in representing
This idea is a bunch of Illusion
Alex wants
To portray world
Between the behavior
Christian does being civilized
Good behavior of Muslims is being barbaric brutal and destructive
And this is purely an expression of bigotry
There's plenty of examples of Muslims doing horrible things
History of Africa and elsewhere
But those horrible acts are no moral condemnation of the religion of Islam and it's a
As the actor
King Leopold our condemnation
Christianity and the vast majority of Christians who don't behave that way I don't think
What's Behind These atrocities
Is the lingering untreated consequences
Of a brutal racist
Dehumanizing
History of colonialism in Imperial
The Westin Alex fetishizes committed a crime
Against the native peoples of Africa
And plenty of other places
He's blaming the victims praja
Any for the afternoon
It's pathetic and childish way to view the world
And it's so incredibly important
Respect and understanding
The complexity of things
Like this
To make simple
It's hard to discuss delivery damages
Pastors people in the third world today
And the lingering benefits
Of those damages
That the West has a
Enjoy
It's far easier to say
F*** it we're good they're bad
Because of Islam
But you don't
And it's absolutely
Mirrored in
The way that somebody
People in America
Well you're not welcome because you're not
Working hard
Not because we absolutely destroyed any possibility
And then
Situation
And the fact
He's using
Play eats
Immensely suspicious
Even though
Can't make this statement
100%
Asbury
Important for me that
Specifically went out of his way to
Shoes African
Etiwanda
To make
Comparison
Between
Christians and Muslims
Because he's trying to
His his phone
Racism out of
Because if you're going to
Keeps all of it on full display
You can't say oh well you know in America Christian verse
Is Muslim because we are
He's going to wind up doing
Pause this expression colonialism
Black people good or bad
Essentially
Black people in Africa didn't have or Africa
Didn't have Christianity
Was Brock
Right so I guess
It would be those who got
Program
We're good and those who
Didn't our bags those who submitted to the colonialist missionary agenda
Literally across
The entire world
Bailed on it until they felt they needed some
Something and then just
Pakistan
Perfectly normal
Good stuff
We know that Alex
Individual
Honey hates the globalist
Because they are
Their Collective
Kind of
There
But it depends
Interesting is that Alex
Are we heard him Express similar things
Before he's like actually collect
I believe in the club
Collectivism Collective
Where's my Collective Collective
Talk about that
Pretty far off course
I am the ultimate collector
You want find a bigger collectivist on this planet that I was Jose
Fire system
I don't think so
I'm not sure if those last words really made it feel like Alex thinks he's a Christ
Of the Christ
Why have you forsaken me
Like my people go back on Twitter
Really basically coops all like a Bible story that to Alex's
Struggle to get back to the promised land of social media
I think he does think there is some of that whether or not he would ever put it that way
He's a messiah.
And it keeps me from going on the internet and Fishes that's all the downloads
The Joe Rogan podcast
Possibility
It's pretty packed up
Express with Eli
I'm a collectivist but also an individual as I think
I think that is murky with definition
Certainly but
Harrison Smith
And now that we know the plot of childhood
Guess where this is coming from
Spoiler alert
In history
Scam
The trash
The good they can attach to the overmind
They are the failures they're the scum
Viruses
Weapon
Operating system with a crazed demoniac
Garbage
Daddy said damn the torpedoes
Who's around when the causing all kinds of problems
Refused
No thank you
So you're shaming the dog
Victor torpedo
The other stuff they're like the idea that they are these demons are Fallen
And that you know they can't
And that's from
Childhood's end
The cost of
Even show up
That is also
Directly from childhood's end
The idea that we were having this weaponized space race
And that's when the aliens stepped in because we were going to destroy ourselves
Alex could read that if you like
I don't know
Invade their area we were about to become as great as them
Stopped us from it
As opposed to what's actually in the tax they were going
We're going to
Destroy ourselves
And we were important to the overmind
That we not destroy ourselves
Pencil The Midwives came into a shirt
That we don't destroy
To make an argument about the real world
Which is f***** up
Although there is a part
People that their Humanity
For the Stars
That sort of thing
Like the idea that we are going to be making spaceships
And traveling through space
The Azar race
Not in our future
Our future is to
Become one with the overmind
The Congo we're not going to be an interesting way for it to go into
Overmind
Yeah I think that I think that Alex
This is kind of mad the Corral and said that
And that's weird
Because that's in a book
We have six months left until societal collapse
He really talks
I feel like it would be a lot of your show
He doesn't really stand on a 2 much buddy
Touches on Tibetan
Radio transmission
God
Right now to take everybody out
Globalism
The reason I kept going to collapse the planet
I guess there's not really any more information about the 6-month time frame whatever
What
We did about the deposition
I was very
Specific to
Like to find out
The psychosis
Headlines that are going
I don't think I was wrong to do that
However
What is describing
Reported as psychosis
He did use that word
Is the idea that younger
He distrusted the media so much but
Thought everything they said was bad
What do you saying In that clip is the exact same thing
As he's old
Then he's Learned was wrong
Now he's going out to do whatever
That's not good
What's up
Still do but I used
Wow
I guess it's weird
Be more careful
I don't know why I would
Now
Quite a bit in the middle of
Does this
I think it means he's going to be on Rogan
Dammit quick succession
Really annoyed
I'm not sure if that is what
But I think it is
Cuz what else would he be
And what else would it be hinting at
Really disappointed
Really it's a
Such a bummer
I don't like
Joby
Weird one-sided
Friendship
Getting used by the
How much money is making office one-sided friendship and I think those feelings may go away a little bit
Clout in that like a dumb
World
That dumb Free Speech Free Speech absolution
Absolutism
You talked to anybody
Except people who are actually pretty far lap
It is gross but
You know she's talking about going to LA
Are you talkin about how
How to set the clip out but I'll tell you that I don't believe it
Check the name
Comedy Store was called
I got invited to go
Sphincter
Next Tuesday I said okay I will
Sorry you can't come speak here
About the place where you can do anything you want
I don't I don't know if they have lectures
The Comedy Store
How many people paid regular mouth you probably a lot of aspiring comic
Irvine Improv
Make a note
I love the way
Invited to come to give us
Speech
Speak at The Comedy Store
Joe Rogan the big wig there you know The Comedy Store world
To come do whatever
Joker.
Set that up
No matter what no matter
How much
Protesting
They'll give a s***
I think that might be where they were
A hard right pepitone it's ridiculous
I was going to give a speech of Comedy Store
No you can't do it
So
Going to give a comedy lesson
Yeah I guess
Doug Stanhope how much
The Comedy Store exist
Entity where there be interested in whatever speed she has
I don't know
Who cares
Weird
I guess
I don't know
He's talking about his Sandy Hook lawsuit
I'm stuffy head with his lawyer
It's very important
That out
Because at the beginning of the clip he does say that this is
His lawyers
Not other lawyer
From other lawyers
His lawyer saying this to him
It's very weird
No I bet they are
There's no way you find yourself give me the Mercer
Commercials got a dollar
It's okay I know you get the money from him just give it to me
Why because
Gentlemen's bar
Never built a damn thing in their lives
Crazy jumps operation
Rebuilt
Hours
Wait till his lawyers asked him
Where the Mercer money was
His lawyers his lawyer said there's no way that you're funding yourself with
This pill sale bulshit
Where's the money coming from
It's okay
We're trying to defend you just need to know what's going on you have attorney-client privilege
We just you can't lie to us or else we can't offend you that sort of thing and then I was like
And the reason is
Because the laughter children
I believe you probably might not be the Mercer specifically but the fact that his own lawyers are like this doesn't add up
What what
The deal makes me think
Hey Alex according to your
Revenue
Profit loss
You lost
$3000000
It looks like you
Even doubt and are in the blue
Now this business
And I'm going to use
Really heavy scared
What do you do
Tails
Okay
How many
Lotto
Like
You've never built anything
Did you
Yeah with the merciful
My dad's oil money
Successful and it's not just because he's
He's great
There's actually reasons
How many does a Ric Flair impression
Which is great because we recording this before I watch WrestleMania this evening
Ric Flair
You're looking at expression of the will of humanity
Because I'm not a knuckle Dragon low IQ
Bad wolves
He's created his own
Which is not really
Kohl's on other people selling them
To your idiot
To work work work that out
Great
But I guess we are knuckle dragger
Cuz we don't sell
We should
That's right biggest sexual organ
Branson
So I was just bragging about how you've got to
Feeds to other news organization
What is that DirecTV like
Just trying to brag that other news organizations
But he was
During the break
He was watching
Fox News
Any sauce
Make a theory Theory
About what Trump is doing with the
The Border
Collab
Overwhelmed
Open
Come up here
But it's all just a PR stunt
Dumb
Because the Border
Unless you put major pressure on the Mexican Government right now stop this it's done the country is broken
I think that's for 6 months
He's talking about
Countries in Europe in the US and Australia
Welfare
Laundry
Almost all of them are conscious criminals
Bright movie
Bell
Sanchez
Everything goes back to some Syfy reference that may or may not be like
Actually related at all
Because he's got nothing
He can ramble about the idea that there is a reference to
Paxton we can't remember his name
That's it that's all he has
This is this is
Exactly
Like
Childhood's end
Being behind his conception of the
Entities that are behind
That the globalist
These demon he's hiding demon
Alien figures that
Good but are actually here to destroy the world
It's all
Bulshit
All of it
Just goes back to
Not understanding
The difference
In reality
Assuming that
All fiction
Is just reality presented as fiction
Lesser Magic
Nice if
He just if we just found out that he
Because I
Better if you just go through all of the natural
Disasters in all Paxton movies
Just likes and you know how they're going to do it
Better music
John Paxton Sam talks about basketball all the time
Bway lower
So another indication
All this stuff is
Just based on faulty sources that he's pretending or much
More serious than they are
Like a f*** you out
Get the f*** out of here
But then again earlier we're talkin about all the childhood
And then we're reminded
The stuff that is important
I'm talking about these differences between
Christian Africans and Muslim African
Again
This last clip you talkin about all this vun plan to break up countries and we got to bring troops to the border and it's just
Like alien the movie
You just alright whatever Alex
And it leads to like this
Women
Horor
Smirnoff
A country clitoris is off when they're born
You got the members of Islam two of them
So Alex said in my last clip
And then brings up Omar enslaved
There is a third
Figure that he's met
With the women's March
Play surfer premium unleaded
Islam
Sure distance
Thursday last week
On Friday of last week fifty-five-year-old Patrick Carly carlineo
Was arrested after he called el on Omar's office and threatened to kill her
He reached a staffer who he asked quote
For her she's a f****** Terror
He went on to promise
Quote put a bullet
And her f****** skull
When he was arrested he told the police that he love Trump
Quote hates radical Islam radical Muslims in
The next day after the man's arrest
In Vegas for the Republican Jewish coalition
Where you said quote
Special thanks to representative Omar of Minnesota
Oh I forgot she doesn't like Israel
I forgot I'm so sorry no she doesn't like his real does she
Please I apologize
Trump donor Sheldon Adelson was in attendance where he wore red yamaka with the word Trump on it
Call Netanyahu your prime minister
Despite the attendees being American Republicans who happened to be Jewish
Richmond
Omar's
For saying
Pure and simple there's no two ways about this
These people are trying to get representative Omar killed
Disgraceful
Alex
I talked about that game
How do I store sells again
Cowboy
I told you I was in Isla Mujeres Mexico
Watch for 3 days
Get away from me
Guaranteed
Sure
So Muslim
All Muslims are as guilty of everybody
They're usurpers
They're just
Destroyer
They're coming to
Destroyed freedoms of Western Civilization
This is just disgusting
This is there's no other way to put it
Repulsive
Rhetoric
That's the sort of thing that only only
Leeds
People being
Almost it is
Positive empathy
Betrayal
Like
If the stories
Presenting
True
Based on what he's even talking about right
Right now
What happened was
Some gay guys apologize
Over trying to hang out with the Muslim people
Didn't want to hang out hang out
Usurpers other than outright anger and and
Is the wrong way to
Any interaction with Muslims
Because what you're
From Alex's reflective
It's it's
Destructive of any kind of like
Light
Right
That away for
Yeah it's a it's a
Disgusting worldview
Great Lake
It's the sort of thing that you need
To do in order to make people not
Fuel for a group of
Pretty bad exactly
So are we won last year
About an hour of the episode Alex talks to his lawyer
Barnes good work Barnes and
Is just agreeing with Alex and talking about how like
This case they wear in right now
Is going to be
Free speech
We are going to take it all the way
Court and
Yeah there
Yeah we're going to need to take
This case it's an indication do of like
You know that you can't argue this case on the Merritt
You can only win
Theoretically
If you twist it
Into being
Some sort of a
Case about
Speech itself
And unfortunately there's already legal precedent
The covers all of the issues that they would bring up
You about like
You can't say that
He didn't say these things
About the San Diego family
I don't understand
Quite honestly why he's not just like
Yep I said that
It's beyond the statute of
Or something like that
Probably because right now
If we're talking about
Even go on the
The show
If not
Some sort of
Meant to other people
Yeah probably Barnes to go on it
No
So it goes on Infowars and
He doesn't have some sort of raw like
Defense
I'm going to I'm going to
We got a class action lawsuit
Yeah it was
We can still talk about it a little bit
I cannot stand
Understand
The windscreen
Okay every single
Stansbury says as follows
Inhales are brutal it sounds
So terrible that it triggers me
Excel like Iowa City
We record
Apartment on Sennheiser bikes that I paid
$75 for
5 years ago
Still somehow isn't is obnoxious to listen to
As a millionaire attorney
In Alex Jones is a billion-dollar Studio
And just like I was listening to I can't
I love the idea of reverse ASMR videos
Like
Set of those relaxing
Right
Just gets me to turn it off that's all it does
I'm so a last clip Alex talks about how use liberals
But something changed
I wouldn't call myself I wouldn't even call myself a liberal
I was just americanah libertarian
Americana common sense
Launch obama.in
So something changed when Obama got in
Could you be a little less on the nose
Could you be could you be around could you just be like oh is around 2016
Never Hillary
Isn't defining a
What's the problem
It was argument that he was trying to make
Was this like during Obama's term Democrats
Complacent turned a blind eye to a lot of things
Push back against
There was room for a robust conversation
In what he was bringing
That's not what Alex is saying
He said what he turned on liberals
Becoming more pro-war than
Republican
And the numbers just don't back that up
Princeton 2011 studies
The Pew Research Center a spondon said they favored the complete removal of Truth
Math games
67% of Democrats were in favor of the removal of troops as compared to
243 purse
Republicans
This study is great because it actually has a rebuttal for Alex's likely like first objection
Tibetan is I'm not really a Republican
They're the research included a variable for tea party
Freefolk
With 42%
That only being in favor
After removal
The study has a few other questions in it like whether or not the respondents thought that quote using military force in Afghanistan was the right
Decision
54% of Democrats said it was
Comparison
68% of
Republican
So even that
Doesn't match
In September 2009 Gallup poll looking at the opinions of Obama's proposals
Send more troops
And Afghan
63% of Republicans
Favored sending more
Where is 6
Supercenter
Opposed
So broken
Widely more in favor as a 2009-2011
A November 2015 Gallup poll asked respondents
Respondents supported sending ground troops to Iraq and Syria
56% of Republicans were in Pavers
As opposed to 37% of
So that doesn't
2011 Gallup poll
Approved a military action in Libya
51% of Democrats
The number was still lower than the 57% of Republican
What made exceptions I can find is a September 2013 Gallup poll which asked about support for a military strike again
In this instance 45% of Democrats were in favor
Compared to only 31% of
It's interesting that this is the one instance where Republicans
Pretty clearly anti-war as compared to Democrats
Every sure that there's a
Cool reason for that I don't know exactly what it is
There's got to be something
Adam kind of fun fact reason
Yeah that's for the Democratic support for the war if you want to call 45%
Like outright
Support for it
Find alarm
But if you're looking for an explanation
I think there's a
Prickly reasonable
Seeking Congressional approval
As opposed to just
Attacking
Saying quote well I believe I have the authority to
Carry out this military action
Without specific
Congressional author
Authorization
I know that the country will be stronger if we take this course and our actions will be even more effective
At the time of the Gallup poll the Senate Foreign Relations
Comedian passed a resolution authorizing
The strike
Interior
It seems to me
The higher poll numbers
This attack among Democrats
Is less indicative of a supportive
War and More in education
I felt that this was being handled in the appropriate way
As you can see from the 2015 poll I stated earlier
The Democratic support for a war in Syria was very short-lived
And it turned around
As was the Republican opposition
I was just making s*** up here
It's just his way of not saying
I got really freaked out by the Obama becoming president
You you come up with a different way to present it
Democrats became pro-war
The numbers don't really match that
You could have a different conversation that is similar to that about Obama
Policies
But you don't want to do that
You want to
Say that every
One that happened without saying we had a black
So
I mean that's kind of
Ord
If you don't want to
For the better
Because this one
Right well that's that's
That's a present
A zit
Who are also why I'm willing to make the
Absurd of default
Another one you tell me
Your your argument
You look at it
So I'm going to fall back to
How old is my president
You give me something exactly can give me these
You know
Pro-war
You can give me that right now look at
Because it doesn't make
Want to give me something that does make sense
I'll stop assuming that it's black president
That's where I'm at
So we come to the end of this Jordan and
Thrilled
To have learned that most of Alex's just come from
I'm not thrilled about the where it leads him
In terms of his rhetoric about non-white
Population non-Christian population
Behind disbelief
You f***** up
Like that is if that existed without the
Really dangerous scary stuff
I think we would have a much more fun show Unity Project Camelot episodes all day
And I understand I told you up front of the episode that
I wanted to make this
April 4th
I wanted to cover Thursday and Friday
But I didn't have enough time
Because of
A big episode
And I don't like I'm looking at the time
I don't think it's
The super long at the
Vallarta
I had to read childhood's end
For what I mean by I didn't have the time
Yeah yeah
That was my home behind like 10 minutes
Varsho was me reading a 200
Open Facebook that's why I Friday had to
Do I take a
Baxley
Yeah and if you like that's the other day
If you're basing your worldview on Syfy
But
From the fifties
Just on account of
Undertones behind the Sci-Fi of the 50s
I didn't get out of that from childhood
It's from childhood childhoods a little bit
Sri Lanka because he was secretly
League a band it was much better
Environment
5/4 DS
Forgave
I don't think there's a blatant bigotry in his work is
Something like that
With your premise just not applied
To Tropical
But I just need to unnecessarily.
So we get to the end
Will the background
Next episode of website
Underscore fight
Jordan Burroughs
Route to you
Ber on I-20
Rate reviews
Stribog
Stop please do
We bounced out
And I'll say
The overlord
Never killed anybody
Anybody in the book
Looks like a demon
From an evolutionary standpoint what are you doing with the UN secretary-general
Ricky storm or whatever
Some clothes to match
Alex
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color