Hey everybody
Jump in real quick
Before the episode
Go to give everyone a fair warning
Sing about the
Upcoming
On this episode
Recover an episode of Alex's
The show that has
A lot of growth
Metallica
To say about
Child abuse
A lot of anti LG
Expressing
And if any of those things
That you were here
About I wanted
It's not Blind Side
I know Alex says
All sorts of horrible things
Pretty much any episode that we listen to but
Some of it today
Gross
You know you deserve to know what your
Getting into
I guess
Take care
Controlling
Alex
Alex Jones
When was the last time you watch WrestleMania actually just
Skywatchtv
WhatsApp apps
You're a very nice time watch
Please
WrestleMania
I'd like to give a shout out to a couple of my favorite moments from the show
The Daniel Bryan was going to retain build
There was such a weird
Racial overtone to the building
People like
You don't become
Champion and stuff like that he lost
The weirdest
Storytelling message
I wouldn't put it past the WWE
I wouldn't
Potential
Absent
I expected it
But I did not expect
Okay his whole character is that he comes out with his guitar
And the beginning of his run
You were come out and sing songs making fun of the city that he was in
For a bit and then people started to like him
So people started to like him he started to turn into a good
Good guy for a bit
The people who write the show couldn't figure it out and he's back to being a bad guy whatever
His segment
So what is he had a video there was pre-recorded video of himself playing piano and drums
Different videos interact with them
I think he's in the Ring The Ring playing guitar
Along with himself on drums and piano
It's so bizarre Lisa real
Wrestling has 80,000 people in Eureka
It was I loved it so much I thought it was
Absurd that the WWE
And then he got interrupted by John Cena
It was not to announce the musical
He was the Doctor of Thuganomics
Before before he was all about that like military and saluting
And stuff like that his character was he was a battle rapper
Exact
You recorded an album actually good songs on it
Batman is really good song party turn me around on my way
It comes out as the Doctor of Thuganomics characters
He's back in his old character it's fan
He comes out as a battle rap lines but he says to Elias
Leaves
I thought it was well-executed
Enjoy the hell out of it
Cellulite I love you iconic
WrestleMania 4 stars
I expected nothing out of it and I got almost
Picard but who gives a s***
Fantastic
Special wrestling
When I was 11 or 12
Even then I never would have expected a full-on music
That's amazing yeah it was great
And the fact that it was supposed to real
Like I just tipped my hat
Appreciate it
So first
Jason thank you so much you are a walk
I'm a policy wonk jaison
Got a little English on it
I'm a policy wonk next
I'm a policy wonk
Next Courtney
Thank you so much you are now
I'm a policy wonk
Nobody calls
I'm going to
Timothy thank you so much
What's your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
From the grave
We appreciate it so very much
Someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
These guys do like sport the show you can do that to our website
Some people in our group on Facebook have discovered
Never working towards getting a tattoo
How to sign out towards my
Say thank you in advance
Yeah it'll be great
Signifies
The show episode
Ever getting anything that looks like Alex my body which was the struggle to figure out
Microphone
No it's not specific enough
Today we are going over April 4th I was Thursday last week
We went different directions.
I was thinking of
Beam cam
You're talking about.
I told you that I didn't have time to get to the 5th and I didn't
I also didn't want to
For some reason
Become very clear
Maybe we'll just devour Towing episode
Alex is in LA
All the Project Camelot stuff stinks
I watched an episode of Dave daubenmire like what am I even doing
Insulting a terrible show
So
See the moment of realization that you're at
You're what like 13 minutes
You're looking
This man is crazy
Quotes about life
Churches that he's going to be at
You still doing plus I tried to make sure everyone's in the f****** Skype hang out or whatever
Very bad.
I realize like I was just wanted us to go
Episode
I was just going to go over the part that people wanted us to talk about then
Discover something else
Coming around on Cuban
I think people are kind of missing a little bit of the forest for the trees
She was going on in this episode then Alex
Sort of
Embrace
Thank you Ann.
I would have respect that
A little bit cuz I would be enterprising
Yeah it's
No no
Before Alex gets what he has
Say about you in on the rest of the episode talking about something that I
To go over
But we got it
Fanza
You'll get why
Pretty quickly
Stephen King novels
Love this song by the all over the Western world
Convicted pedophiles
Worse
Disguise themselves as clowns
They didn't call them shelves
Queen
Elementary schools Nursery Schools public parks
Where they didn't pray directly on
Children
Ladies and gentlemen a group in Houston
Has Boston
Their second
Convicted child rapist
Both men were convicted of raping
Year-old boys
They heavily had their identities used multiple aliases
Massresistance was able to track them and find out their real identity
Tracking others I will let you know we are doing it as well
Boots on the ground
Just real quick that he's doing it as well so if you get sued over this adventure
Navigate Sandy Hook we just repeated other people stop
That's good to know ahead of time because I
Could end up leaving first of all people getting hurt
And second of all tube
Possible author
Study of Isaiah
Is that he doesn't know the details
Adidas bacon
Stuff up to feed his narrative
Princess one of the people that talk about
I've committed their crimes at the agency
Concealed and possibly know what actually happened tonight
Probation
Which seems like
Not
Punishment
You'd get from the crime that I
Details of it and Alex can't either
Anita can the people that he's getting this information from
He's making a lot of assumption
In order to make his listeners
That's f***** up
Beyond that this is not the way I would have chosen to start this episode but I can only really follow Alex respond to whatever he throws in
In this case we see that he chose to lead off with talking to Real gross
About to drag queen Story Hour
Play major role in this broadcast from the 5th
April
Friday
Honestly I turn the song like I told you my first nothing else to do
So here we are
What are the reasons
This is particularly off-putting is because
Just make
Things up
He's twisting of manipulating a turtle of reality into something
Horrendously bigoted
Two drag queens associated with the Houston Story Hour the Houston drag queen Story Hour off
Have been revealed to be
Announces take this information
Commit a horrible composition fallacy
Anarcute that all of the Queens are there pedophiles and they're out to get you
Their number issues here just about any of this stuff
Nothing I'm going to say
This episode at all is defending the idea of letting sex offenders be around
An unnecessary risk
And definitely is inappropriate
That is not what I'm taking issue with year at all
Sincerely am
Mike has zero to do with drag queen Story Hour
It has everything to do with Houston
Drag queen Story Hour is not a National Organization with a corporate structure where the crew in each city has the same on different dates
Psych2go
There's a there's a central organization with independent
Cities around the world
There's a page on the website where you can reach out and start your own satellite chapter if you want like a pretty easy process
In March when the first sex offender was discovered
The Houston Public Library released
The statement of the news
About this
In our review of our process and up this participant we discovered that we failed to complete a background check is required by our own
Guidelines
We deeply regret this oversight and the
Make calls or customer
We realized
Running background checks on people who apply to run event
Is the responsibility of the venue
As of clearly discussed on the drag queen story hours website on the page about starting your own chapter
Call Ashley public libraries are schools may require a formal background
Check as this is awesome
For anyone working with children
That said we hope this is applied to everyone
We don't think drag performer should be
Be singled out for special as we have every right to participate fully in our community
So their position. It is
For everyone and we are apart of
So cool
This is the story
It's not a story of drag queens being sex offenders a pedophile
It's a story about inappropriate levels of screening an oversight
Specifically in the Houston Public Library
The Second Sex Offender that was just recently discovered and Alex's responding to
Clip also was involved in
Houston Public Library
So that's my position
Is Alex and his ilk wanna complain about this complaint about is the Houston library not following their own person
That is it
That's the story
Plain and simple
It's so disgusting
And I
I feel the same way about it
Not the same
In terms of
The way
Used
Feel like it
So similar to
A good guy
With a gun action
Protected Harbor
Is that right
That you hear all the time
Sure one time
Great I get it
You're going to try and pay
Painted as though this is what everybody
Can grow
Of course
Because there
And when you get a
Do large enough number of
It's going to have
There's going to be a certain
Percentage of a group
To have
People who are offenders
Yeah
You could do the same
For librarians or teachers are coaches
Absolutely
Is it a problem
For Sophie
That's what you want to do I don't know the stats on it but that very well may be the case
The other issue is that like the actual drag queen Story Hour organization
Know who all of the people who are poor
Participating in the events are
We're in communication with the person who's organizing like let's say
Dusty Attic
Rabbit or whatever and then that person subcontracts out
The responsibility of finding people to
To be involved
In terms of oversight
It's not a problem with the event
Itself it's a problem with
Houston
Houston has a problem
To paraphrase Tom Hanks
Another issue here is that the information Alex
Cuz working with is all coming from a group called
Which the splc list of anti-lgbt
Everybody
Until there's good reason
The group was founded in 1995 under the name parents right Coalition of parents rights coalition
Resistance in 2000
When I roll
Nicole government became clear
The word mass in their name is short for
And in 2003 the Massachusetts
Supreme Court ruled that same-sex marriage should be permitted
And then Governor Mitt Romney was reluctant
Start a fight over the issue
Which really pissed off homophobe
Like this group
Bathroom sets
Who's all equal rights
Expression of governmental
Massresistance passing themselves off as proof family as a group
But if you scratch beneath the surface at all or just look at the surface
It's super clear that all they really give a s*** about it
Meteorites
And access to abortion
Bi-State supports conversion therapy which they call reparatives therapy
Which is the same complaint that they have about straight
Their president Brian has a weird habit of comparing
Support lgbtq rights to Nazis
Like when he said he wanted lgbtq activists
Destroyed
Because they quote
The concentration camps if they could
Or when I don't know about that much more
Benign
The matter
Do the Jews in 1930s
The Christians now
These people are a bunch of assholes
I don't know his bills are like
Also in October 2008 48 year-old Michael Alessio an employee of massresistance
Trouble for creeping around outside West Middle School in Andover Mass
The truth and taking pictures of stood
I'll reach you from Andover Eagle-Tribune
This is actually kind of
I mean it's not cuz it's kind of creepy
If there's anything that's pretty funny on this episode is going to be played
Please set the incident happened at West Middle as students
School has parents watched alivio parked his car got out and began taking many pictures of the school in the students
Police received a flood of 911 calls from parents
I'm suing the school called
A gym teacher tried to talk to Olivia who fled toward the high school police said
When police call him
West Middle School
Almost
Whatever
Okay so he fled please call him believe you said he was taking pictures for a documentary and he would
If you would not elaborate on it
Lieutenant
Olivia was ordered to leave the area because police had no reason to detain him further
Erratically
After yards on 8th Street
Closing is he ran police set
Get removed several items
Before officers finally caught him on North Main Street
Quote he was not completely naked
Clarify
So this guy who's working for bass resistance their argument on it there was like a gay-straight Alliance
Meeting it was happening at the high school
I still think your buddy
Great guys what are you doing this is my
At least he has that he has no reason to be at the middle school
That's the other part of it
Yeah
That's weird
Bipoc
I don't know I don't know what is
Can possibly know except for
Beyond
2018 post on their own webs
Their own website
Resist
Some kind of admits to being alive
Quotes
Our side concocted the bathroom safety male Predator argument as a way to avoid uncomfortable
Lgbtq ideology
I'm still fire up people's emotions
Pittsburgh
To just save the evil shoot you're doing it's not real we just wanted to
Avoid these
We wanted to avoid but still play with people's emotions bulshit the demonized bunch of people in really
Got a lot of people hurt
And I made people feel like
Non-human things coming out in 86
Just being like
Hey guys this whole Welfare Queen I baited up
Roman Reigns
Bulshit you may notice
This is like the day after the
I'm sorry what sort of a breakdown of like
Can we do better what
And I don't know why they put it on the website
Kind of doing a pretty similar thing here as it relates to the drag queen Story Hour
Speed now I did
Uncomfortable murdered
To do it for me
And I didn't have a conversation about that
The kind of dicks were behind the reporting that Alex is operating off
You know we have a guy who ran away from school
Organization
Well it does appear that there are two sex offenders who were involved in a drag queen Story Hour
That is not good
There's also no justification
For demonizing the LGB
Community are drag queens with that information
Which is that Alex is going
Proceed to do throughout the
This entire episode
As we know that highlighting Tupac
Seeing people like Alex never really matters
He's doing is identical he accuses the left of doing today
Bloody murder but how you can't blame all gun owner
Which indicates
But you understand that it's not right to
Group therapy
He knows what he's doing is b*******
Doesn't
Because it creates
Emotional appeal to get his audience to hate
Screw that he wants them
For his own
That's what that brings up
With what the actual
We can't have a conversation
About
Lee's Dragon
Angry whenever you start calling people names
So what we're going to do
That's going to give us a
Foot-in-the-door to call everybody
Let's put it up on her website
Link to master
Regret
Going to be fun
We can
For Alex
Talking about qanon towards the end of the episode
Is important
Recognized
Proper context
Pedophiles a slippery slope
To believing in Kiawah
Miss reports
And they're organized out of New York City directed in England
France
Belgium Sweden
They are
By convicted murderer
They are commanded
By Sinister individuals you cannot make this up
Their Facebook and Twitter pages when they're together a party they look like women
But when they go out it's in full
Disguise
He's just talking about like a drag
High performance outside
I have multiple aliases
Yes they have drag names
It's not like some sort of a nefarious thing to hide your identity
As much as it is
A persona
Or whatever
Wrong about the the run out of New York
Because it was based
Originally
San Francisco
Actual
Group
That runs
The operation
Edwin about that
But
I'm not sure where he's getting this information about the story our being convicted murderers
I'm like to dig into where he could possibly be getting that information from
Open where are you
I think that he
He thinks that Michael Alig
The guy from Party Monster you know that the guy that movie is based on
He thinks that he's behind all of the
Okay I don't see any evidence of that
I don't know that's one possibility
I like that you know everybody's got to diversify their portfolio
Call correctly Alec. Manslaughter
For that was a murderer murderer
Resume let's
The only other possibility I can come up with
Is he's referring to a September 2018 blog entry on Christian Post
The story hours
The blog post includes discussion of Ho Chi mochi
A drag queen who described their Persona as quote
Your resident killer clown from outer space
This is also covered all over right-wing media including post
This person whose Persona is it killer clown from outer space
Literally
Killer Klowns from Outer Space is
Persona
They're not having
James Bond
Yeah I mean if you believe they're killing you also have to believe they're from outer space so
I can find
Like it was
You wanted to be fed more
8 Souls
I can find no other indication other than the Michael Alex
Don't think the other connection I can make in my mind
Even progressively anti-lgbt
Groups
There's a convicted murderer
Who's commanding the drag queen Story Hour
If I were the people organizing these events I might consider suing Alex for what if we get another case of
Yeah because he needs to defend
That's a claim
That's that's something that is not okay
Situation
Investigation turns into harassment
Galaxy might be doing this to yourself again
If at a certain point
Start sending out
Two people who should
Through lots of heavy breathing
In terms of people getting a little bit about the story hours though I submit
Do you Pat Robertson
He got on his show not too far backyard the 700 Club and he decried the mainstreaming of the lgbtq
Community comparing it to what happened in Sodom and Gomorrah
This was the original crime that led to the destruction
Sodom and Gomorrah in ground
It's not just a library that's going to be in trouble it's the whole population
Judgment
Robertson when almonds
But they're reading books
The children
Official version of inclusive diversity
Give me a break
If you read the Bible there were a couple cities
Where are they actually
The men tried to have sex with a male figure
God destroyed those City
So Pat Robertson
Started insisting that this will bring destruction to all of us if we allow it to
If you think about it that justifies
Hurting these people or
Running
Killing them
Father
Tells the mob to
Rape his two daughters
If I remember correctly you remember that part
You got arrested back in
February for showing up to the freed Montrose Library with a gun
In an attempt to stop
The drag queen Story Hour
Attempts to stop it
He was a self-described trump supporter and claimed he was being arrested after he had to
I got arrested and you said it was because
Live stream
Can you hold a gun
Open the air
He did you add a concealed carry permit
So it's just a
Is it a real weirdo
As a police spokesman explained
He was previously banned from filming children at the library
Has been known to cause disturbance
Several officers had to escort him out
So he's up at Middle School
It seems like a bit of a creep himself
Library
Another
Words or learn from my two-year investigation down these roads
Allergic to reading
Eddie Pickett
Might be bringing attention to library and I could see that
Alex
Remember last episode
Kind of seemed to be imagining himself as of Christ
For a second
Just cosmology
I want you to remember that Alex likes to say that he's only in
Interested in
Non-offensive violence
When someone bites them back
This matches that that world
Dodge
God has instruments
Start a list
It's a riddle
Not only for kids you got strung up while you're done
We're going to terrorize
Like
Because you
Deserve what you've done to these children be done to you
That's Christian
We're hunting you
You're not hunting us we're coming for you
We're looking for you
We're hunting you
We're seeking you
I think you figure that out now haven't you
All your threats all your crap
It's hilarious
In killing people
Hilarious
If what you want to chill
Cliff especially parts of it we're hunting you all that sort of
We're going to terrorize
Lyncourt
I know that I'm starting to listen to Alex Jones in the present-day especially through the prism of History
Like I've already become detached from the precedent
I wonder how this will sound like
All those clips are like
Like real bad present-day Alex
Dysplasia
Shooting
Somebody or something like that
Lakeland
Terrible
Possible outcome
You hear him saying stuff like this
You do understand how houses
This process works
Or is Alex or like today
Do you know the kernels of
Like what is what is the role of
Like the radio host
In Rwanda in 1990s
Early night
The people who were like
You know that this is how the process works
These people who are in
Encourage
Quote unquote
The illusion of a lone wolf
Do sorts
Alex has a Rolex
I remember growing up reading the Bible
Turn the other cheek
Forgive even those who
The thing that most people leave out of
Unless you really feel like I
I told you that I want
Gather up
There's read text
Then said this is a riddle
It was this this was also in The Hobbit I believe there was The Riddles in the dark is my real
Where's my real
What is bloated
Drunk claims to be exacting Vengeance for the Lord
Steve Bannon
So if Alex is in the middle of reading a list of like news articles
About
Get out
It's just
Describing to Muslim
Atlanta news
Don't point out
That the people who committed
These crimes are Muslim
That I take particular issue with which we will discuss
A couple seconds
My mom's
Even here there from that
The article that Alex is referencing as hiding the fact
The perpetrators of this crime
Is actually one of the articles that we went over
When we were discussing the reality of the group
How to play around the world
Well Alex is correct
The headline doesn't identify the gang members this woman was victimized by as Muslim
That fact has brought up in the six
Sentence of the article
Is mentioned repeatedly throughout
The only conceivable way for someone to think that they were covering up the
The fact that these
Particular criminals were Muslim
Would be too literally not even
Try to read the article
They just assumed that headlines are all that
Now it Bears repeating that this article was written by a survivor of one of the
These games
Her perspective is being
Respected by how Alex is using this article
Quotes
In Mainland Europe
Conflict surrounding immigrants and refugees
Has been fueled by stories of women being raped by migrant
People have been calling for violent attacks
Anymore
Declared war on his
If anything
Ryzen 80 Muslim hate will probably make groomers stronger their conviction
The drive ordinary young Muslim men
Toward fundamentalism grooming gang
And terrorism
The Survivor even directly discusses Alex's good buddy Tommy Robinson
His bigoted group the English Defence
Quotes for Tommy Robinson and his followers to focus on an entire religion interpretation
Of some scriptures by some people
Is unhelpful to Save-A-Lot
Most grooming gang survivors I know absolutely condemn anti-islamic
And we're uncomfortable with English Defence League protest
We certainly don't want random attacks on all Muslims
You can't cure harm with more harm
How to pretending to be standing up for Victor
Louie's Prime
The entirety of Islam
And the way he's doing it is
Particularly
I mean really think about the
What he's doing is taking the first-hand account of a survivor of the crime
He's so upset about
Lying about it by pretending to that account
Cow covers up the fact that the perpetrators were Muslim
Then arrives at a
Conclusion that isn't direct opposition to what the writer a survivor of this crime advocate
PS4
This is an abusive level of non journalism
And just so clearly indicative of what he's all about
It's impressive in its cruelty and inhumanity
Cuz he's he's taking her account and just say f*** it I don't care what you actually say
Use you as a prop
Well that's because she's
Because they're mustard
It's because they wrote
Violent Islamic
Here we enter the. Of the show where Alex is going to just start rambling about how
Azar
This will go on for a while you'll get interrupted by having a guest
It was a terrible
Confirm everything I can
Until
Taste of things to come
Tennessee shocking footage
Give him a roses
Red roses
Raptor box
I have can I have puppies
It's all coming up ladies and gentlemen
Children
You forgot they're from outer space
Liberalism
Oh yeah
Infowars.com
It's pretty gross
That's for family grows that the content of the advertising or separate
Can forth between the human voice like
Because back
And for
That's crazy
Exactly the same voice uses rally and stuff like that
Material
He's like a road dog who has a s*** axe
It reminds me of
If I'm getting a correct later too old
Combination of
Very real disgusting
I thought
Being surrounded by this
Ironic
Look at how much fun
Like listen to those fake laugh
S*** like that
If you heard that was the first
If that was the first
Clips of Alex is that you
It wouldn't surprise me at all if you were like
He's just being a
He's he's doing this
You guys are just overreacting
Cuz you're all
Maybe because of that
Play come on
Yeah
Yeah supposed to be funny
I don't think
Maybe it's just because I
This is funny.
Our alliances B at Wrestlemania
I don't know
Not much else about it
Consistently
Because you do not laugh
Whatsoever
My jokes are
Terrible smile
Question like do do some people have such bad sense of humor
That they think that's funny
Must be a possibility but I don't think I think it's supposed to be for comedy I don't think it's worth
Perfect I think it's for
Like like directly demonized
He's trying to make that the argument between people
What does a snarl
Beat it into the ground
Not a joke
It's
But what you don't know
It's not over there the demon
They're also a pedophile
To take assault
Army pedophiles
Other supporters rushing is clown
Would you want to know about it what you want to stand up against
Would you like one
People showing world they're willing to do whatever it takes
Father Lucifer to give them power
Probably dodged another defamation lawsuit by just saying Local Houston
The news and that's saying what
Detect the only thing
Comes close to approximating that is articles that people have
About the idea of
And awareness in contact with people of different Lifestyles different
Different races
Different heaven
To not have
Whatever
Take over in your mind
You can't have
Take let's say just on a very simple level
You can't fix it all
Construction workers are stupid
If when you're younger you mean
Construction workers who were nice then thoughtful
And kind have a positive Association
With the construction workers
Victor stereotypes won't be able to Panda
That's the argument of kitten while they're young
Is ever been used
Not in terms of like
You got a
Spread around their experiences
So they don't turn in
Horrible
Bixby
Stewart's original
So whatever
Don't
I don't
Can't be
That obviously
People killed because what you are doing is
Waco Thibodeau book in episode
People
An army of clowns raping kids
They don't have
Is well if Aaron Army
Make our own Army
Bright
A preemptive strike because
Lauv
But yes that is exactly the messages trying to put out
Not realize that that's going
Kill doesn't care that's his place in this game
Courthouse
But does every possible in order to inspire violence
Out of people listening
Toward the group that
Target
Is without Jones
This role is it reach its natural conclusion at the end of this episode
And it's profoundly f***** up
And way worse than anything that has two
To do with you or not
Well I mean
Qanon has the potential to be
That's okay with you
Isaac is secondary
To what he's trying to do to me
And he's doing it with the help of this group massresistance
And so at this point Alex has
Since on
There in Massachusetts
Stretch
Massachusetts
But have since grown
National
Notably Nigeria
Has a foothold massresistance influence
Gay
I meant over there
Hellboy
So Alex has Tracy Shannon
And her first
I would say that the interview where she argues
I think
I think witches are doing
Is that the First Amendment does not protect
That drag
Adult sexual sexual
Bunch of man dressed up like demon clown
That's right that's right that's not what it's supposed to be Forex
Disagree with the
The speech or whatever
As it's not of course
The First Amendment doesn't
Protect
People
Anal sex offenders being around children
Of course not
That's not what anyone would argue
But
The only thing that you can really be responding to his like I don't agree with this
The First Amendment doesn't
Apply here because I find it objectionable
Is she wants to open that box then of course
Good luck ever having a
The only thing
React react
They're always like
The First Amendment doesn't protect this
The First Amendment does
Before we even start with any of those arguments
Before you start doing this
In
Single serve
If the right-wing wants to f******
Put down
A goddamn list of what the First Amendment they think protects and doesn't
Might be interested and we can have a conversation
Blind items
That
Realize how
Hypocritical
And stupid they are
Someecards
I would I would I would love that it's really stupid
Taken at 8
Core
What she saying is that the First Amendment doesn't allow people to wear clothes that I disagree with them wearing
Where is Tulum
Others would hate so you are going to
Bring the force of the government into legislating
Articles of clothing that are appropriate for people to wear
And I don't think that
Should be allowed to wear pants
Concerned about that
Side effects
Queen Story Hour
Begin with just drag it out to
To drag King
But like yeah
You're going to
Is create I don't know a brutally repressed his authority
That has authority over things
People from lewdness of any and all these horribly against unless it's the Tyranny that upholds his bigoted
And the positions that he wants to
Siberian Forest
Which is the status quo
White male supremacist
Sex
Hegemony
It's just for the kid
Look at them
They're allowed
Blued
What's next
Behind type
Raymond if you grow their hair out so no one's confused
Also pink
Color
Oh no
Oh man
Going on is the Shannon
What is involved in here
Cheese
Associate
One of the people whose work
Which is in this case
I guess from everything I can tell
I guess that what she did is okay in some ways
Because because what she did is she uncovered the failing of the Houston library system
So if
She wanted to take this information that you found
A demands that the Houston library system do a better job
Actually do the things that are in their protocols
To begin with
To do
I mean like that is
Okay
It's not okay
Suzanne
Take this and use it to haul quad
I guess
Attack
A group of people
Composition fallacy where these people representative
Encourage
Almost vigilante
Like
Because for example is being used
Used as like
We all need to be digging into all of these people
And stuff like that
So she's kind of discussing some of that
Alex wants to
Mother
Grandmother's doing in
Unless you're supporting Isis show critical supporting you
I want to talk to you about putting you in charge of operation
Because I don't have that much money but I got enough money I think to bring down a couple hundred of these guys
Which
Yeah coming after you again that's going to play well later
Corollary for me would be somebody who
A picture of a
Cop with it
Uniform offense
Right and so you report that
But that doesn't mean that I think
Down every
Every single cop the whole point is that they're so screenings
System it's not really that
Screening system
Should be
Define failing
And you got the problem that you ostensibly are upset about
And if you don't focus on the things that can actually make a difference
It does reveal that you don't actually care about the thing that you're presenting is Karen about
What you care about is attacking a group
That's what you care about
This is another situation
What are
What do you think
The world looks like
Massresistance
What is the world looks like
If you'd if you do whatever you
Call lgbtq people in camp Camp
Absolutely open it's wonderful because
Cuz then they'll be able to
Wonderful Christian Society once they get outside
Be clean
Productive neighboring countries that are animist
Will be declared war on those countries
Absolutely allowed them to waste their land
Pretty quickly once
You think about whatever they would do if they could
It's not it's not all Christian people
Against
The specific behavior
So just to be clear on that list
We fall into
The Trap of
Demonized
This lady is representative of 99%
To remind people listening
Fall into those
Straps
Remembered massresistance Bengals
A whole different
Different
And they should probably keep their clothes on if they're running away from
Middle School at hopefully
Stock quote
They would
Is literally say it Alex
Both believe
That LGB
Leaders from both house but from what I know about pedophiles
They're there their feet
Stop
Going after show
Especially down here and use
Terraces attitude that you can't even scrutinize I think that applies to all of lgbtq community
All of them
Right
Lgbtq
We know what he's talking about
Tri-community
Which seems to apply do you think it is
Subsection of it
So that's great
It's great really shows the card so what she thinks she's working
Which is why this ostensibly okay thing
Which is
Doing the oversight Houston
Library system failed to do
Turn zinc
Credibly bad
Because your motivation is not
Fixing the holes in a system
Or or
Doing secondary check
Or whatever
What you're interested in is is demonizing
People in the LG
And that's the
You're going to go
We're going to be f***** up
As we already
She's allowing herself to be
She probably thrilled to
I'll be doing it
Alex
To do his
Is
Inspirational terrorism basically
Maybe
Demonizing the entire LGB
B2q Community pedophile
She could
Yeah I probably get into Pilates
I'm doing these classes
But they're free
People afford it
Tracy Shannon is a member of this math resist
It's been particularly involved
What's the drag queen Story Hour
In October 2018
She probably lost you trying to get all these three hours.
Violated The Establishment Clause
That lawsuit
Dismiss
Whatever
Progress in the legal system it appears that you switched tactics
Decided
Into the realm of propaganda
Twitter account before she got involved at this Hospital
Tweeting out everything that's in line with the meat that media Spears narrative
Interesting Lee she seems to retweet almost everything Charlie Kirk Twitter
Which is an impressive level of
I was going to dig in and try and find out more about her but after seeing this little glimpse
Remembering that she's involved in the group it literally admitted on their own website that they makes it up
Community
I realize there wasn't much of a point looking into her more we kind of already know whatever 2 weeks to know here
We don't know her
Yeah
Alex
Epsom salt
About Houston
And their mayor in specific
Thank you we can use it here and everywhere
Bison Odyssey more ways than one form I-90 from enforcement
Well imma stop right there
Do everything basically
Everything basically
What
Sylvester Turner the mayor of Houston
I guess
Applying at Sylvester Turner
Tina's compromise
Story hours
In the lgbtq community in general
In order to make this claim he brings up a 27
Super Bowl in RG Stadium
There's a little Scandal around that's
Super Bowl as your funds from the
Up from Houston
Tri-Cities tourism board
To pay for himself and 16 guests to attend the game
However that story was reported by Houston's
ABC affiliate
Currently a month after the Superbowl
So not sure how that could be used to blackmail him
That's just like a like a
Get out
It came out
PayPal
Rationalize
These people got tickets
Are just order something people like that's malfeasance
Music
They were moved along
I think it's standard fare government corruption I'm not boring I'm not for it
But it's not enough
That's the corruption where we're like
You're a scam you know what we're 50/50 on doing it ourselves if we had the
I'm not ignoring it
If I lived in Houston I might be more upset about it but it's not
To make the argument that he
If your piece of evidence
Vicky's
Chicago
Ashley
I have my suspicions that what Alex is really doing here is trying to attack the sincerity
Official who's changed their position on LGBT
Tissues
In 2005 Turner voted against allowing gay and lesbian people from being Foster
The 2002 band
Same-sex marriage
As recently as 2013 he quote voted against the proposal to gather statistics
On bullying Institute
Incident
Based on sexual orientation and gender identity
Which is part of what got him 8
Equality text
However he's since changed his to
Passover 2015
Equality
Asbury vocal Advocate about
Supporting complete koala
When
It's not most Americans called over the last 10 years on lgbtq
People evolve what we want people to do
Uncle reading maybe than 2015 he was running for mayor
Where is before he been a state representative
Your tenure whose position was far less vulnerable to having shity position
Might be a little bit of a cynical explanation for it
What are the case
Alex can't allow the possibility to exist that someone was anti-lgbt
Then learn more about the issues talk to people most affected by those positions
And then decided to change their ideas
And their position
That's threatening to his world
He has to introduce the idea that anyone who comes around
Supporting LGBT
Is most likely being black man
It's a really dumb idea
But one that's low-key far more dangerous and Insidious than it might first
Like that
You can probably breathe fast
Compromised or whatever
Is the fact that he changed his position
These issues
It's from the idea that you
You can't
The idea that you could listen
Make you feel differently
I said it's because their brain
Or their blackmail.
Listening to
Instead you just replace that idea with no no this guy
Is blackmailed
It's weird you know over and over and over again to be a state representative
And he was really anti-gay
When he started talking
Did try to talk
Nevermind
Now and I don't have to
Just think about it
Everett
You might be kind of that idea
You might be asking a little bit of
Like how does this
Is blackmail
Ception work
Like what is Alex actually talk
What's the pipeline
A black male
Squaw Valley
If this is Ludacris
Iraq
Battles
The avatar
Research
He's describing gay people
It's especially people were at the club
Yeah
From all of those drugs they're not even there
There are a vessel for this entity
See this demon entity
To come enter them his research has shown that
By the lgbtq community
Takes thousands of
I would assume
In order to become
Dartford
Only makes sense
If you accept
Horribly
From owed overdosing
And then implanted themselves in their bodies why Alex doesn't like walking
Because you said that the gate part was
Because of the demon
Is dumb
I'm not sure
I don't know anymore
This is after Alex
It has played a clip of the Party Box
That's what he's operating on yeah I think he's using some of those
Those ideas
To inform all of this. Cuz he did drugs
I don't know about you.
We have the conception that these people do all this
Play becomes empty
There their they're
Cool kids
I'm telling you folks
And their arms above above above above
Do you want we want access to children
Zaxby's
What is going on
They're a bunch of people
Become demon possessed
These demons want
So they blackmailed by the mayor's have to go along with it
And they demand access
People's children
Drag queen Story Hour
Not real
It's Alex imagining
In his even in his own telling
Lgbtq people are the victim
Demons
They're not
Alex is fine with that probably
Nan demon eyes in Camp
Ecstasy out of people's hands
Maybe you just really wants a favor of drugs is illegal
Thea's
Ecards
Close
It's all an appropriate even if we didn't find a pedophile
We don't children do not have a job to validate
Adult choices
Intuit
You showed
Far too much of your hand when you said even if we didn't find
Any
Then this would still be bad no because
The story that you're telling is about the sex offenders trying to make the point
Be f****** furious about this
Second
These drag queen story hours are not about validating these people choices
Or Lifestyles or identities
Through children
What it is about
Tation of
People of different identities different
The kids
CNBC
People and not
Thinking that they are so
Something crazy
Some sort of Boo Radley entity
To be afraid of and run pass
That's what a thing it is not about
Those people
Is about
Children
Not develop into being
What they are
Furious about
Disability
Turn on clothes
And reading dr. Seuss to children
Right when you boil it down that's what's going on
It's not representative
Free it's only representative
Because of your opposition
Right lgbtq
Marginalized
This would be nothing
It's just telling a story
Only
Thing that's indicative of you
Angry about this
Is that they are already
Yes
That's what's going on
Maintain the status quo that existed before
Which is these people are invisible they dump public
With scorn
And derision
I might
I might be inclined in this direction
Should be
Be ashamed of it and
Themselves and commit suicide
Or we'll yell at them and then they'll pretend that we tried to
What she's literally saying
I don't care if anybody is a sex
The only reason I investigated
Was because I was already
GoNoodle
That we found a sex without sound
The only reason I was looking into it at all it's cuz I needed more ammunition for court throughout my
This is bad
Alex
For the dark
This is not good this is a short clip
But it's addictive
Of what's coming up
This is it really f***** up
Drunk on the blood of children
Fuchsia
I can't make the faces they make it yourself demonic
Let me have time with your children now
Give me your children
Call you racist
I don't know what happened but if
In the show is where I think Alex
Really was like
I'm going for it
I've already said a bunch of horrible stuff
Plays over my head
I'm going to be as gross as I possibly can be
Blood libel ideas drunk on the blood of our children
This is classical anti-Semitism whether or not it's
Directed towards
People who are Jewish
He's still the same ideas
Used to be Menards
Jewish people for
Conception of the bad guys
Which isn't good
Here's where Alex
Explain
What he thinks the drag queen story hours are
Because he believes it's not about literacy and
Acceptance
People seeing each other as people
That sort of thing
No.
It serves a role
Not really might be resistance that something far worse
That's okay.
He's talking about one of the sex offenders in Houston
That's
Winfield
A demon posing as a woman
A woman against life that nurtures baby
That was for babies
The inner hell it's been rested
Have you been I see you there
Joplin tornado
Is that in the Bible
Adult men will stand against
And one of the men watching the show stand before God
Godzilla
Because you wouldn't protect
Children
Trump pedophile dressed like clowns
Tangles your children truck
I want your children not to run with are the disguises
Phantom
Far even storytimes
Learn to stop
Grab.
Yard cuz the kids moms asleep inside
She worked two shifts
Now bye-bye
Open 2 a.m.
It
Pennywise fantasy
I
Cannot
How funny it is
I feel bad for that Mom haven't worked
To shift
Struggling economy
You got a rapper
The equation
If you want up to heaven and God was pissed off he was like
I do not know you
Dresses when you get down there
Conception he believes that the idea of this drag queen story time
Our
Is in order to make
Kids not afraid of the people who are going to throw them in Van
Later which is
F***** up
That is so f***** up
I mean cuz it's just the way of repurposing what it really is
The idea of acceptance
Embracing
People
And making
Sinister
Which I guess is kind of what he does all the
But it's
It's so easy
I ordered the connection between reality and his why
Are so easy
He defeated it's just
It's so f***** up
Two demonic ideas in the idea that they're only
Are your kids
To be kidnapped
How else are you supposed to respond to it like you said earlier in the episode then like
We have to stop
Obviously this woman for massresistance
Ancestry
She tried to do it through the court system
What are you doing
You got to do
Stop
Well that
I didn't realize so I thought they were
Like a preemptive
Before they hurt
They're actually saying that
Reading itself
Call Alex
Might also
I'm not going to love them in necessarily
Because there
So they still think it's a
Defensive stray
How is the grooming these children
To be picked up in Vans later
Get it in your head and it is not
No
It is what I would describe as absolutely
Performing
But also
Does not like
This is there's there's something that he's tapping into that is deep-seated within him
Incredibly gross
There's some blood Lively ideas in here to again
But this is just absolutely livid
Is a good pal
Doesn't like President Trump doesn't like me
Wait he's your friend and we can ride all day
Torture your children
Big fats
The finger
Not the name of the
Epic Lounge
Sit on my lap
Georgie it's a Freewheel universe
Stark
Kohl's
Show you
She'll float
All tell you
Their religion
Fluoride
BMO
Call chittick eye phone
What a child
Have some love have some
Be a good little person and did they can get a minute
Enrich
These statements suck off your child
It's so much better than just giving a cancer because
You're the parents are there with a child's dying from cancer from the vaccine
I still have love it's just on special
Domino's dungeons all along
All the guys in clown outfits pullback with draft
Looking for Russian dressing
5 and abused
Rip's that child
Gut
The blood off of y'all
Coffee
And then Dracula's women come in
Pornstars
Sexy women want to live forever, they just eat little pieces
Sarms
I'm not entirely sure what blumenthal's
Involvement
New York
And there's the sort of the abortion
Conversation going on there
So I think that might be what
Is relating that to
That's f***** up
Cuz I mean we're already in
Situation where Alex
I made these really Target
Like
I really hope nothing happens
And believe them for sustenance
Dracula
Pieces and
Blumenthal is their leader
Alternate universe
He is the single greatest trauma filmmaker
He really got into The Narrative of it
If he made that into a movie I bet
I mean that was the plot of Manos the hands
The Fate right I don't remember
That's really
Is incredibly
Incredibly bad
It's gross
April laughably expensive
It really
What I'm more interested in
I'm less interested
Weird
Assertive
Fantasies about demons around every corner
Inability or unwillingness
Understand about it
Which was I believe in full name of the the book right though the movie
Registered in the real world effect
When Alex starts taking call
Here is a collar
Who it is
Starts off his call by talking about
Now they're all criminals
So we'll see where this
What the f***
Why is the left show a live Criminal
And I think
Shutdown
A worldwide
Call Lindsay along probably criminal anthropologist
Slaves
Before you and I were on a planet and now it's coming to an end
Try not
What else to do or not going to be employable
Guys Express
Criminal operation the Democrats
They're afraid that Trump
Was going to blow that off
Write this is an interesting idea and it'll come into play later
Trump has finally taken down the nights
Templar perhaps but just call
After this
They get into talking about the drag queen Story Hour and he had some thoughts about it
Mike down for the cowboy that that doesn't
This is also listen to Alex.
Push back
Against his ideas
That is very important
To Alex playing
His role as the inspirer of terrorism
While keeping his own hands
Well
Play the police in my eyes I'm being a cop
Go to the school and Grandpa drag queen
The parking lot and then disposal
If you're in that school your kitten has not stopping it I should have the legal right to go in there and and then put you down
Well bottom line for going to run their plates
We're going to get them God bless you done
He doesn't say how dare you you're at you have now on my show twice
In two sentences
You should have the legal right to murder these
These people because you disagree with their lifestyle with her identity however you want to frame it whatever
This guy
He believes that he should be able to go in there drag them in the parking lot
Kill them
Where did he say
I don't remember
I'm like something that should be reported
He should definitely not
Yeah
Barry Lee Alex has a
F****** responsibility
To be like
He has a responsibility to say
Absolutely not you do not have the right to kill people just because you disagree with them
But you can't
Because earlier in the show he said that they want to prepare your kids to be thrown in vans
Ever going to drink their blood
Beast on their flight right
That's what I think can't exist in a moderate world
It can't exist
In a place where
What your prescribing what you're advocating is
Let's follow the process and make sure that the library is actually going
Through with the background checks that there's
Supposed to be going through so we can make sure that whatever potential
Or whatever potential
Possible
Damage is mitigated
Because
Lick these people like the Houston library also put out a statement that was a
We f***** up
And all that stuff we didn't follow our own process
But in that same statement
We already have in place whenever there's anything that has to do with kids
Any event with children
Nobody's left alone with children ever already there were no complaints about any of these people
Incident but we're not using that as like a way to say we didn't do it
Have other safeguards in place
Deep the conversation that Alex is having
Cannot involve
The correct conversation
It can only inspire people like this guy
To feel entitled
To murder
I think the same issue is occurring
Whatever Precinct
He's working for
But the former cop
Open place to keep these people
Yeah I don't I don't
They didn't go well I think there's an entirely also possible world is not really a cop and just
Even Alex Jones caller so whatever
Without consequence
What should have
Is I should be allowed to murder
Because somebody read a story to my kids while wearing a dress
Written into law that it's fine
Yeah that would get on wieldy real fast
Quite seriously throughout this episode
Is putting a world
The ideas
The rhetoric that he uses
One of the reasons is because it is
Exists with that
This
Caller ID being on the show is not a surprise
Now the caller expressing ideas like that is exactly what you would expect
People who internalize
To hear
From what you saying
So whenever you are saying earlier in the episode
When you hear this stuff how can you not think you should kill these people because they are going to only your heart and your children
White wait until they actually do the thing that you're afraid of
You are cuz bending
F******
Child
Why would you wait for that to happen you need to protect your child
Kiryu making a leap
That is inappropriate
Because all we have to do is go
Get to the end of the episode when Alex takes calls from his listeners
Hear them having that exact same thought
But not being afraid of
That thought it's the right thing to do
So
Whatever that what I'm saying is
This is just the worst
Think if somebody called into was like
Whenever he went you know what when trans people here that kind of rhetoric from somebody
They should have every legal right to go and kill that person
Send that caused the end result of his
Behavior and his language
Is going to be the murderer indii
Community
It's only right for them to get murdered
The loss of recognized
We wouldn't accept that if we had called
If we took calls until Monday to call in with that we probably hang up on that but then spend 20 minutes
Disgusting
You have to recognize that that's a symptom of a major problem problem is something that you ever respond
Ability to deal with
Because you are putting out the ideas into the world that's making people think
Do you have a
Flight responsibility
I believe
To take a step back
And have a bit of an educational
Where do you like guys
Things have gotten a little bit out of hand
I know I said they were drinking blood
But we live in a civilized society and if somebody's drinking blood
You can't just go around
It's almost like a thing where you got to be like guys this is getting out of hand
Why you can't take whiteout
Yeah of course I'm very afraid
The idea that someone's going to hurt one of these
People or kill them
Are any of these stories hours
Is
We have a
Clear example here
Of someone thinking it's okay to
Express that auto radio show
Audit National radio show
Discourse is so toxic
So dangerous
Even pushes back again
It's not like he comes back from break he's like
Wow that caller said something it's just allowed to exist
Something that isn't
Taboo
It's not something that is beyond the line
Yeah I'm so the idea that someone might think like that
It seems
Stay within the realm of possibility to me
And it does happen
I do hope it Alex
Gets sued again
Like I know that when we started the show 2 years ago I very
Asbury insisted about the idea
IFixit Alex
Is that good
Oh boy
Hey that is changed
I do think you
You still was on the right side of it years ago
Any longer
Gino
We know that hate crimes have
Risen
Dad
If not exponentially
Trump
Fieldstone
Energizing excited that it's almost
Possible and more
They were going to see a
Real assault
It feels that way we can't predict
The future it doesn't
Themes
Rough
It seems rough
Call
He brought up earlier that there's a thousand criminal record
I guess it's the globalist whatever
What do they call themselves the Jacobins
Alex is stupid ideas of liberalism from from
It's even
I don't really care to engage with that
I only think it's important
It is another.
It's a teaser
You hear that sort of an idea to like
It turns out he's into qanon
After he brings up qanon
Lisa Alex
To clarify his position
F*** you in. This is the same guy who said that
If you should be able to shoot
Aquino said a reading at the library because he disagrees with them
You shouldn't be
It is a surprise
Wearing clothes
Read not a surprise if that's what his idea is expressed by somebody
Qanon
Also not a surprise Alex
Changed his tune
Look like they're scared by like that
I like that
Manipulated
By somebody close to me that I've learned was bad
The key was bad
Because what they said about
It's tough to eat crow
The issue here is I think what are you saying is Kursi
Because he was super into qanon
He was
Decoding all the messages and stuff like that is writing a book
About the event
Started saving throw courses bullets
There's a whole lot there
And I think that Alex's
Referring to that
Bono
You didn't know that there is
Multiple cues
Or something I don't know I don't know if there are but this is Alex's
To be able to
Except
The bigger picture of qanon
Still
He disagrees with her is inconvenient for him
Absolutely
Suspect is really more of a marketing Ploy than anything else
You're saying absolute
Yeah you know I'm going to stay
Exactly
Before
Tribute certain things to keep
Whenever I want to
And then caller can call in and say something
But I think Alex also is probably signaling on snow in some ways that he's come to a point where you realize it
There's a very real possibility that the qanon audience is bigger than his
I don't know exactly cuz that's all
That's all
To eat crow but he hasn't figured out how to do it yet
So we can assume that that's forthcoming at some point
They'll do a big message about his exact position on Kiawah.
As it is now I think there's some dangerous possibilities with this
Like the idea of that and Alex
Working in
Concert more than they have been
Could be f***** up
It could lead to
That's a pretty dangerous
But we have to see how it plays out at this point I really don't think there's much to go on
Because it is
He's blaming Steve pieczenik or Kursi
And now saying you going to
Clarified later
I don't know
But
A personal level cuz if we
But then secondary
Because now I got a f****** looking
Qanon
I don't want to do that
Alex is out
I'm going to have to go over
When we know more we'll talk
But
Here's the interesting thing
A little bit about what Alex used to say about qanon
I have a little bit of
Sort of Refresher
Will recall 2018 on Christmas Eve
Studio
And you told the world that you told Rodger Stone
Christmas Eve is hilarious
If we go back to the Christmas Eve
Prior Alex also got into Studio
Edit message
For the world
But I am coming to the office
Scream
This emergency transmission on YouTube
Facebook
Because
If this doesn't get made
Attention
This doesn't
Psyche
Globalist have a
Decent chance
Killing present
In the next two weeks
And
The necessary emergency alerts
The Obamacare
Really
Now
Your minds
Never really spoken of
Qanon
Q anonymous
What's going on
Separately
White House
Fox News
Forces
He brings it up to be like
Is is
You know
Whack It Whack
Like at the real sources
In this this next flight from that Christmas
Steve show
He brings up that you do cuz
Started his
The storm
Before the storm
The storm is coming
Riders on the Storm Alex literally says that he
He is the storm
The storm is real
It's called America
Collecting
Fulfilling promise
So he's
Making himself
What the people who are listening
Qanon are actually talk
We are what you're talkin
We are the change you want to see in the world with your piddly online qanon
And the reason
That he was on that tip
And the reason that he was sort of dismissive
Of Cuban on is because
He is trying to push
He's fake intelligent source as the real qanon and it's not taking off
Pageant
Could you play this radio drama
Where's that came out and talked to him and got taken in by the FBI talk to Alex
Depleted Morocco
I meant Zach disappeared cuz the narrative didn't work out
And I'm guessing exact
Just kind of got tired of
Play news role for Alex whatever whatever you was doing this is LARP
Yeah that he was doing just didn't work
So amazing that they thought it had a chance
I don't understand why can't I think we're worth it
Like I said
Let's think about conspiracies
Who are they going to go with
As far as a conspiracy
Qanon
Zach
Viq
But yeah
Also Alex other times building
I'm not entirely sure
So
Alex was mad that
Zach was not as popular as qanon
And I believe that probably one of the main things that he had against
Qanon
Is that he had his own version of it that he was trying to push
And that it wasn't as popular
Yep it is
But it's not
Absurdist next question
Expresses that was
That his hopes
Is not as popular as the other one
Ears on the show ended
Against some little comment about
Qanon gets a million
That's great
This guy's known to us who he is
His boy his face
We talked to him
He's onto gives us to stop exclusively
Which implies that the other one is
BBQ in all that is
Qanon
Is fake
Zach is the real ship
Most of like what Alex
Positions have been about qanon over the course
Of his
Against
Is
Zach is the real thing
Let's get my Revenue stream involved here
Disappeared and he experiences some of the feelings
Zach is real
Even though he's not
In forged millions of Jews
The reason that I bring that back up
Is to show just a little bit
Year in couple months
What's your position
Official editorial position
Qanon
I was
So back in Trump
Mobbed-up
No
Similar trajectory
I thought you meant
Because
After Alex is made this point
To the caller
There's a good version of it
No I got LED astray by people I trusted
He tries to bring Zach back into the
Proceedings
He claims that he's on the phone
But he never gets to him
Because I don't think he actually was
Let's go ahead
Zach
Looks like you just hung up
So let's go ahead and talk to Grant in Iowa
Sure
Does not call back in
And I don't think Zach was on the phone
I think that Alex
I was just trying
To reintroduce the idea that had this guy who was his Realty went on
People's memories
Cuz even right before he goes to him on the phone earlier just a little bit earlier he had said
Indian called in like 3 or 4 months
Yeah why hasn't he called
Dropkick narrative
Is real
My Realty or not
So there's some angles being played it might be a part of why you haven't figured out how to eat
Kroger
Position
I'm interested to see where it develops but honestly I have no idea because Alex is now in Los Angeles
That is making the tour through all of the death-squad podcast
Going through
Christ
Doing
Sales on Joey Diaz is coming up there at least
Turn it down.
Play this out
Diminishing
Quickly
So I'm not interested in any of those might listen to it but I'm not I don't have much interest
I was doing an episode where he gets yelled at by Joey's cast
I guess until
I might bite the bullet and go ahead and do that but I'm not interested in it
Message
Something is important
Point out because
A lot of the stuff is stuff
Seen before
I cranked transphobia anti-lgbt
Messaging the conflation of cross-dressing
Queen
Performance
Folk
That's horrible
Rhetoric pushed out into the world
Before but
Bead Direct
List of how much of this is
He's trying to get people hurt
And then the caller calling intake I should be able to kill these people
I think is a new level of
Demonstrable Danger
Is perpetuating putting into the world
Disgusting for that
And then no one would have let us get away with not
Talkin about Alex
But it's such a small part of this episode
Like it could in the future turn out
To be something major
Turtle of Alex
Pivoting some narratives and
And that being his new Direct
Where we go one we go all done
This could be a small blip and it just be a marketing Ploy on his part in some way to tap into a fertile Market
That he feels he doesn't have access to
Wolfie on that
Yeah
But what's up for debate
Is how
Dangerous the rhetoric of you putting out these David the drag queen Story Hour
Our stuff is as a reminder
None of this
Is an anyway supporting or defending those two individuals
Who are sex offenders
Who are involved in the drag queen Story Hour
That is that
And a failure of oversight
That is all that is
They are not indicative of
The group as
I I really appreciate doing this
Because it is
I think I think it's really important to keep this in front of our face
Citizen in front of his many faces
Because there would be there is an absolutely
YouTube like well we already know how he feels about
We don't even need to we don't even need to talk about it
Because everybody already know
Really important
Coming back up
Just so you're always can
Confronted with the reality of what
People are saying about the LG
Like you've heard him say
Demons
Such an ugly
We've never never really see that be soaked
Yearly
Justifying violence
Answer that does
That does Mark a very serious escalation
And I think that
Could
Is the basis of a lawsuit no matter what happen
Something bad happened
Very serious lawsuit
Copper for
Letohatchee
We've reached the end of this and
The back on Friday
But until then
Knowledge fight.com
Twitter account
Trooper underscore fight on Facebook
Do you have a group called are on iTunes
You can leave a review subscriber
Do the whole thing
Absolute
Leader of the Dracula
Stevens we're going to drink ever
Technically
Probably has
Technically Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color