Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages
Jordan
Who you got
Pyramids
What are you talkin about
What the f*** are you what are you talkin about question
Like a cat
Which is great I love cats
Pyramids just a geometric shape
Not that not that interesting part of the reason I'm going through
Okay
Is just for
We got that River
Goodnight I like it alright very wet
Yeah what about those there's probably
What you mean like in other parts of the world or other ones that are ninja
I don't know
Play Quantum Memphis
Okay great really excited for this
April Madness
Alright well this is a lot about Alex Jones get away from this
The true irony of this is this is the only time I've ever seen you write down on your notepad before the show started
Coming up with a good question
Fair enough oboy
Today we're going to be going over an episode episode
I need to get away from the Press
Cuz that was
Little bit too heavy
Need to give Alex
A little bit of time out time out
So today we're going back to 2013 to
Continue our Sandy Hook
Aftermath investigation
Because the Friday and Sunday but no show on Saturday
People probably on Friday and asking hey Dad what about how Alex Jones
Is LH podcast
We may cover some of it because of the timing of these episode 7 to record on Thursday
Didn't have enough time to get into some of the
More recent releases
May do that for next
Getting arrested
I don't know yet on Thursday I don't know we don't have enough time to do that quick of a turnaround
On Monday
Possible possible I don't know studio for Los Angeles
Genuinely have no idea
It could be bad
For Trump
Quite frankly
Because our ideas
The Trump is supportive of
Extradite
That's really going to hurt Alex's
Trump narrative
Well yeah I think it has the potential to really do real Alex
Alliance
He's never even heard of that Wikileaks before
I don't know
It's pretty impressive
Maybe that'll be
We'll find out
But for now
We will jump into this episode
Does the people who are supporting the show we appreciate it very much
So first Cody thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Next ozzman
Zika thank you so
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much You & I open
Text somebody who joined up
Donating a little bit of higher-level appreciate it very much so.
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
Set me a bucket of poop
More elevated love
Appreciate
So thank you so much
Whoever
Regret
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Google
If you're out there listening music
A sport that we could do that
I realize that with the screaming along with I renounce Jesus Christ
Cord that comes out of your mouth
Is at least six decibels higher than a normal
Thank you
That's right golf clap voice
It's going to get more annoying so Jordan like I said they were doing January 4th and 6th
Pretty clear that Sandy Hook is a false flag
But it's in the same
That the government did it
You still saying
You were killed and all that stuff
But the government went in
Killed Adam Lanza as a Patsy left them there
I all that stuff
But he doesn't really care all that much about it because he
She's now saying that the
The government in the globalist
Use that as well
Start a civil war
Pretty much
Where we're at
As we jump in
On the 4th
I wonder if we're going to see if development of that or maybe we're not yours no context rapper Today Show
Weird
He who laughs last
I don't know
Alex is really bad in play weird
Don't know
Alex has been very tips
Libro Russia and Vladimir Putin
That we've ever heard
On the show
Pretty strongly in
Favor
Russian
Today
On January 4th
Alex's opinion is bought it
About Russia
Weird shorts here's where it starts out all the episode naturally starts out on this team
So that's pretty yak
Yesterday
I was just
Authoritarianism
Andaz
Herbalife
Tire country
I was really hope specific
Do you suppose defaming
I can't find this I don't know what he's talking about
Is it Alex field betray that Arts
Isn't scream
Bloody murder
About the prospect of the introduction
Gun legislation
The aftermath
Alexander hooks
It makes some sense for him to feel that way
If you go back and look over artsy America's videos from the era of 2010 to 2012
With Alex's friend
Webster Tarpley
Gerald Celente
Paul Craig Roberts
Peter Schiff
Announce himself
A frequent guest on the network
And the messages they propagate on the network are the
Infowars
Looking over this archive it.
Imagine a true Ally
Feeling cast aside what he feels like they aren't joining him
In this battle
Which is built up as being too thin to lie
To the end of American civilization
You could feel like
Possible just going to be a little bit of rejection there
Guess
Absent
Weirdo
It does
What emotional trigger could be
Be there
Possible
Arteaga's
Metaphorical mother kicking off
Reporting on Sandy Hook started up justice Lafayette
Start with a little less paranoia
On December 4th
The day of the shoot
Who's from the Connecticut area reported quote
I just got off the phone with my mom
She has some friends who children go to bed very school just picked up the
There's a lot of information what they're hearing my mom says is this guy the gunman
Worked at the school and was fired
This morning one of the victims was his mother who was a kindergarten teacher
And shot open fire on the kids in the classroom
Not implying at the Mothership
None of that is true
Adam Lanza
School kindergarten
She worked in insurance
But wasn't employed at least since her divorce
Exorcist
She didn't have to work
Because my brother-in-law left her very well off
Very well
To which she replied
Marsha Marsha Marsha
She's doing really well if
Sister had to repeat
Very well-off twice
Chewbacca
From that divorce
The day of the shooting Artie was reporting outright Goss if it wasn't true at all about the
The tragedy
Is not cool
Within a week however Liz wall started reporting on houses
Publicly or tweeted
The shooting
About the idea that it's possible
Pointing out that in the 2012 election
Over the over
10.5 million dollars
The NRA spend
Only point
3% of that money actually went towards
Outcome
Either support a candidate who won or opposing a candidate who lost
I don't know if that that's accurate as a statistic
But it's what you was reporting
Doesn't really mean much compared to
Just there in
Message
Hey don't worry about these loud assholes their bark is worse than their progress
Don't worry about you
But that interpretation
Moviefone
Decorative wood art
He was putting out
On December 19th rtamerica Aaron interview with Jim statue
Statue
Control would be effective and it's tearing
Gym Issaquah
Institutionalized
Freedom
In reality gym is a f****** lunatic
It was posted videos of
I'm self online ranting about immigrants
Parasites in Furman
Been burning a Mexican flag
He's posted videos where he literally Advocates shooting black lives matter protesters
In the back on site
Explains for the camera of bullet with BLM written
He posted a video of himself outside a mosque
Augusta Georgia
With a gun yelling
Islam
He's literally told
His followers quote
If someone is a member of Auntie
Tifa people
Lone Wolf
And retaliate against the
This attack retaliate as a lone wolf
Before this appearance on rtu.
Multiple times
It was on the Southern Poverty Law Center's list
Dangerous members of
The Patriot movie
Dudeism
And the Georgia civilian militia
As well as his deeply bigoted radio shows that tended toward
Violence
Artie had every reason to
This f****** nuts
Case was
Text via voice
December 18th
Abby Martin
About how
Analyzing and exploit
Entirely in his Express
RT correspondent
Anastasia
Lament
Tails wrong about the shooting
They're reporting
Just kind of funny because the other guests on
Does a new four days earlier said on our teeth
To work at the school
December 9th
Authority interview.
Good buddy Paul Craig Roberts
The government needs
Steak
We bring in the police
At the end of the interview
Suggest a book may not have been real
These events whether real or not real
Helpful
Take away the guns
Fat to take
Part of Americans
Have they also allowed dangerous
Crazy assholes to regurgitate
I suspected Alex Musk
The other kind of expressing like a lot of Americans are calling for gun control you just got really mad about
Also
This is probably worth noting at this point
At this point in time
Alton for the guests on Earth
May 2012
So you may just be feeling a little bit left out
This doesn't seem like
The kind of behavior that we saw from him
Recently with Joe Rogan
You deserve in wasn't getting
This seems to have worked out in this case just as well as it did with Rogan
Alex
Duarte
All his buddies Max Keiser
This isn't about geopolitics
It's not about gun rights
It's not even bad for you
It's 100% about Alex's
It's Ollie's Express
Wait
Super weird
Alex talks about how the globalist want Civil War
He knew that Sandy Hook
Was going to happen before it
Call Alex
Totally new
You you saying it's news
Because he did
Similar things of the past
Specifically
Is all that serves to do is this
Predictive markers were there in
It's the safest prediction
America
Through
Early 2013 is probably a boulder prediction minute is now but still not vengeful
Mayonnaise
It's like
Playing his
His game of
No matter what happens
I have my
Ass covered on it
Like I predicted this
It's bake you know it
Comes out
Something is wrong it's fake I told
See I told you it was a false
The matter what happens
He gets to say I
Right right
He's cool that way
So at this point in the episode
Is tramadol
Gunn weirdos
His show
To educate
Laprade
French parallel
Is back from America
F***** up just as a way of
Thinking because what they do is they take the memory of someone who died
In Sandy Hook
I've been trying to rewrite her ex
As being like what if she had a gun
Wouldn't have been great
They're not doing
F*****-up gross
One Brave woman did
Victoria Soto
The presence of mind to Hideaway the kids and then sheets
Was out at
If only she had an opportunity
Kill a human being
Gross
That's really bad
It's pretty disrespectful to her memory and it's even more cowardly that they're like
Couching it with like
What is Martin Luther
The King Junior
Oh man okay could have turned around
Shop-Vac bright
What is Lincoln hat
Yeah I needed for that
Just like look at
What's up good weirdo
So Alex
Roast
She's trying to do
Pretty consistently throughout this entire.
You know it
Sort of focused a little bit on his position on Sandy Hook
For a couple days
Just like this
Used to
Defend himself
This isn't crazy
For me to be going down these
Is the idea that there are bills being introduced
In order to
2 take away people's guns
In order for this argument to work in any way
There have to be
Lisa perception
These bills are credible threat
Your gun ownership
I mean like
If you know that there's no chance
Things are going to pass
You don't really have a good foot
Stand-on to
Stoke fear
Right
I mean.
Kind of a rational way to look at it
Ants that would be if you're not
If you get complacent
And you aren't
Constantly fighting back
Pass without anybody
You know you think there's no way that I'm going to pass but if you don't
Maybe they'll do it
Only three people voted for the Federer
Alex is going to say that latest
But not my response to that not the Federal Reserve
Fear about it as a fact
You're sort of impending
This is the end of the world is coming now it doesn't work
If you think like this is impotent b*******
You don't need to be worried about it but let's stay vigil
Work
Propaganda doesn't work with ambivalence
That's why it's funny that even Larry Pratt noses
These bills are never going to
Either in the senate or the house
Esperanza Rising
Good luck
Get off my show I don't know
The opposite of Y
U2 word lie about Obama 3 million times
Come on
Absolutely
Think of that muscle powder
Speaking of Obama
It turns out today
I believe
What I suggest
What episode is probably a large part of why
Are bikes tension Russia
Present
Explanation
And the reason that I don't take it as
The really what's going on is
Absolutely not
Reality
It's just
Yes you are
And they're going to merge
President
Completely crazy
A couple reasons one is it in 2012 that was when
To the presidency
January 23rd
Year ago there were different policy
Reset
Much different relationship
It was much more standoffish in
And hostel
And then you got it
Consider that in December 2012 that's when the magnitsky Act was with
Like there was
It was not good
Between Obama and Russia
It in the time. That Alex is talking about right now
Afford that much red paint to put all those cameras
It you put it on the new one
You don't need a retro
There was over Syria time
Obama and Russia
Did not
See eye-to-eye
The police
The idea that Alex
Suggested means
To me that the truth is something else entirely
Easiest explanation
Is that I'm not on OurTime not on RT
Yeah
Giving
Nuanced coverage
Of the gun issue
And I thought they were on
And I'm f****** pissed off about it
Yeah well also they have
Well that's part of the Pacific Lino's
June 1st
Clips
Isn't he also isn't he
Possibly admitting that
The arm of the
Propaganda machine
No longer part of the episode that I just did
Keep input
More than willing to
Explain
And that is
50 size bed
Run media stop I don't care
I'm not
I'm not doing it where they
Or giving me a message
They're putting out my mess
Right so is he believes that
Interacts with it I don't really
It is possible to go on
State-run media organization
Not be
Waterford
It's not his
Simplistic as
If you're on there you're a Putin
Eeyore
I need that it doesn't
I don't know if you just have to connect
Operation has you on
There's a reason that they have
Have you putting out your message but that message aligns
Whatever their goals are attack given point in The Archives of Art
South River
It's crawling with
Infowars gas
It also likes stage France
Didn't interview with
Cedar did a couple enter
Talib kwali
You know there's a lot of people there
Even if they are asked
Because your beliefs
Lineup
In Subway with a message
They want to put forth
That doesn't always mean
I'm not saying
Sure I'm just I'm just saying that whenever he
He says specifically
I go on there
And save my own message
They don't control
Definitely leaving out the part of
There's a reason they're having me
Specific
Alex
World in
Early January
Less than a month after the shooting
You can already tell that Alex is getting a little bit defense
About what
He's doing
But there's no real pushback
At least
Appearing on the show ya complaining about anybody saying
His callers are if anything's
Multiple shooters
It was helicopters
Those are all misreporting
He is he's already
Internalizing
Some sort of crew
Using s*** sources
To tell the stories that he's telling
He's like no it's all the real mean.
Reported based on
Possibly the root of it was that Artie report if it could have come from other places
The idea that the shooter work
Yams like that around
And
When you realize that that's not
True
You don't need to be defensive about the idea that RT reported it
Irie reported it incorrectly sorry I got the
That wrong you don't have to
Alex
All he has to do is say
I initially got a bad report about this
Turns out that's not
McKay's books
Because he can't
Let me know from the deposition in prison
Ask about this the helicopter in the guy in the woods
A video that he saw
The Backs this up
Misrepresent
If I had to guess it would be easy cops
Sandalwood
And one of them was dressed differently than the others
Running
Pure to be a
Is just something
But you probably could look at that video
You don't have to hit your pillow
That's not
People getting arrested
In the woods
You're wrong
They wouldn't be
That video.
But I think Alex knows that I video doesn't show
Professes but it does
Therefore
Lesbian
That's what I was going off
Everrich
Anyting
Is it cuz he
I don't know
Very
Very few retraction
Burberry website
But I don't know I don't I don't
Experience
Not very
Well I'm just saying cuz it seems
It doesn't surprise me at all that
Just doubled
He's already made
In the first
How could you possibly
I'm sorry I'm not
Use of
I'm justifying
And that also that is part of the just
Station 4
Him saying that they're doing
Get to take your guns
To be doing
As extreme
Broadcast
She's doing
The underpinnings of
If they fall apart
Then everything
Literally has to say okay guys
Calm down
Yeah problem
It's stuff like
This
Wouldn't work so well
Feeling when you packages came in like a few days ago and
It's going I'm dumb.
Fighting weight fighting
Send a fax for Aaron.
Polymers Plus
Amazing
Freedom
Listening her show
And see how they did and I was amazed
Appointment
You really ought to
Infowars.com
Sony only times that I've heard him actually advertise for his multi-level marketing
You very rarely brings that out but
It's interesting
But he does he
Planted call that just suddenly happens to lead to a very detailed explanation
Infowars life and how you should become apartment
Getting this ml
Feeling like you should do more Market
Also in there that like
The way he's like we don't take Putin money like RT
It really makes you think that all of his
Complaints about Russia all about art
Autobot RT there about how he's not on it anymore it really feels that way throughout this
Authoritarian government ilovemylife
Absolute
Buttholes
If you're not having me as a guest on RT I can't handle this whole Russia thing
Sprite
It's been awhile
I've heard from a good friend
Little while
And I'm thrilled to report
I don't know where
Is in Arkansas
No it's old man house phone
Household is bad
My town because
The reason he's calling in
Is Ben he needs to report to Alex
He had Frank call Diane.
Georgia
Thank you Alex and thank you for having your great gift Gerald Celente on today I had something have
Happened yesterday that both of you will enjoy I called Dianne Feinstein's office in Washington DC and whatever Young
I said ask for the gun-control measure Miss Feinstein is introducing today
I said please give her my congratulations I had no idea
Dia she was a supporter of the fuhrer
I said I don't fitler did the same thing to his people in 1934
And then we saw what he did to his people after he does on them so I just wanted to give her a very hard
Congratulations for following her
Her guide
The fewer
Good prank call
Love it
Annoyance
Okay
Right I like today
Within Alex's rhetoric
Would be
He says
The guns have been taken from all countries except for like America
Switzerland
Or whatever you know
That's what he says is like everyone else is taking the gun
Why aren't there more
Is there still kind of a counterexample to the argument
Sciatic tyranny comes as soon as people take away the gun
The arguing
Yeah but look I don't want it besmirch old man house
Because it's nice to have him back
And I'm glad that he's like a crank yanker
He's like spoonie Luv up there on the phone
Congressional staffers
Like it like he called a bit before that got a female staff
I can't talk to you
Right
Love it
So this show kind of
I could say that about most of Alex
The shows
It's a whole lot going already out of the main
Yeah Overdrive
Alex's next
After half hour
After the show is over
He just did
Special Report
From David Knight
Who is working
He's been there for a while
Albany
The report is about
But don't worry
Fourth turning
Disciples
Book about
Episode
The theory of the fourth turning
Starbucks
Written by amateur historians William straussen
Neil Howe
The book argues that there are generational Cycles
History which repeat
A calendar year
Repeat that
Predictable and always follow the same path
Each cycle lasts between 80 and 100 years
Is made up of four turning
So there's the high
Which is a.
Thrivent
Individualism
Happier
Come under attack
From a new regime
New ideas
Values
There's the unraveling
The. We're individualism
Cell-free re-emerges
Institutions
ZK giving way to these new values
That came about during the week
Then there's the Christ
The fourth term
The.
People with old values are
Replaced by this new system
That's kind of a chaotic
What time does usually
We don't have time to get into a critical analysis of this Theory here but suffice it to say many people who had
Explain how many historical events and figures don't fit into their hand
Indeed conception
There's a lot of stuff
That's life.
Enough in there that fits their pattern
You could easily be like oh my God
There's a lot of people are pretty critical
One person is review of the theory is not as critical however
David Kiser Road in 220
Sometime
Quotes
Colleges or
Disgusting the media
Ministration
The former head of Breitbart
Strategist
The White House
He's very familiar with stress
House. Crisis
Has been sick
Do use it to achieve
For quite a while
I know this because Bannon interviewed both Neil Howe and my
Myself in 2009
About the ongoing Finance
Crisis
I don't like to get all spun out I'll talk about us
Steve Bannon
Supervillain tried to take over the world
Inspired by half-cooked pseudo historical prophecy books from the 90s
It's really super a
It is weird though just to say
Steve bannon's worldview
Was also apart of David nights
Worldview
But he was reporting on on Infowars
In 2013
That's really weird
I don't think
But it's weird
Yeah
They were both
They both enjoyed that
Dallmyd
Walking Panama still at break
And if he
What's it called
Then it wouldn't
Surprise me
From him it's not personal cops
Contact with the IP
Entirely possible
No
It isn't
Because like based on what does Kaiser's
Reporting
There is an indication from his interaction
That the idea of
Use to your advantage
Whenever there is like
The new regime of ideas
The old being replaced by the new
If you
Finagle things
Appropriately or
Correctly
You're able to make sure that your ideas are the new ideas that are implemented
Never let a good crisis
ROM
Rob that's right
Never let a good crisis go to waste
I don't know
I don't really care I just think it's
All over the place
Still from the 4th
In overdrive
A caller
He says
If you want
By forcing
You get like a new regulations
Laws for guns
Make sure that they also include something
In the bill to get rid of the Federal Reserve
Yeah I liked it also for poison pill Dan every one of their bills how about adding onto each one of these the gun
Put in there
Flies
Yeah I don't I don't think I would want to be
That sounds difficult
Yeah he's
Is that use on one
Drive time to let it all hang out
Maria Ines
Jewel-Osco down the street from a strata Marina
It appears that that's at the root of it
Lumping in art
With like China jackass co-star awful
Which we know isn't view that he's going to
Keep for long
Three weeks later he's going to be
Something so trivial
I don't know if it's at that point when he's allowed back on
Something
So I don't know
I'm not sure what
I was going to Slit its throat
Yeah I mean it
It's just so
When you have
Something like that it makes whatever your
Professing the problem
Variance
Operator
Caller is last one year from
On the 4th
Caller calls in
I want to talk about Adam Lanza
Does Mom
Alex says something that's
It's in line with his progression
Hi Alex
Alex a few things
How come there's been no real consequential journalistic wedding
Adam Lanza's mother I mean after all according to the Press you play the Central Podcast
I just got out of the publican
Descriptive
Is there a nail and I don't know I mean
You said he has proof but he could have
Think about the Aurora shoot
Because just cuz
Contacts
Yeah yeah we have proof there's not
It's really hard to nail down proof
Selfless
I don't
Who is based on
What's it called
It's script play the script script
But like
You saying that something is scripted does
Imply the present
Still it's not good enough to nail down that is in line with the progression
Where we know he's going to end up
So you can see that here already
I mean what are we
January 4th
Just less than a month after he's already a week
Or so before this
Suggested that Robbie Parker was an actor
Because of the way he presented a little press conference
And now you saying the whole thing
Conscripted
So
Yeah
It's quick
He got it over
It happens
You think it would be exactly
I should tell you this
You get the caller
Who's bring up the idea that there is
Pennsylvania
Who is like going to
Everybody would like
Guns are free
You don't want to do that I know a lot of
But
He's about to give out this guy's phone number
Police phone number
And I was like no no no stop stop
He said it was hard to give it out
And even be on the show tomorrow don't worry about it looking
Advance Auto
And I would have lasted so we can but it's just
Call Kevin
But Alex
Built it up on the road
There are
He's going to have the police chief on
Bob and here is Alex
The beginning of the show
Announcing
We're going to talk to
Tessler
And
Has-been nullification
Nullification short of secession
Systems
Whatever
The sheriff's do
Notification ideas
Phuket
Alex's unlock more counties to secede from the Union
Alex's highly-touted
This is an interesting
Catfish
The show is part of Alex's parade of gone weirdo
Your gun out of your law-abiding hands
Leaving out only the hardest core Criminal
Out there having
Oh man we can't have that
I should tell you that
Two years probation
Turns out that on May 5th 2016
Kessler tried to buy a gun from Dunham's Sports location
Relied on his application
Ask yourself what you lied about
In response to a question of whether or not
Charged with a crime
Carrying a possible prison sentence of more than one year
You said know what the answer is definitely yes
We're available
It should arrive in fresh in his mind.
December 20th
December 2015
Six months prior disorderly conduct
Making terrorist threats harassment charges
Pushing a guy
S*** about his daughter
And telling him you better watch your back I know where you live
Which Kepler Then followed up with by continuing to send the guy harassing
Yeah
I mean I think the
Just a really Hammer home that you know
The charge was allegedly the result of a complaint filed by women who attempt
How to deposit Kessler's Hopper on the road
Apparently
He did not take kindly to
From the republican-herald
Kessler pulled alongside
Language recording
To the criminal complaint
What are you doing you're lucky my kids are here you know what would happen
The woman said cancel the cancel
But suddenly stopped
Pulling out a firearm to show her
According to the complaint
The woman said she is
Seriously harm or kill her
Especially since he act
Did that way
I'm not 100% sure how these cases ended up in court
But it really doesn't matter they were pending when he tried to buy this gun absolutely lied on that application
These outbursts occurred in 2015
He was fired as gilberton police chief in September 2013
Everypost
The videos on YouTube
He is no longer the sheriff that we should call
Because you
And referring to a dummy that he was using a
Speaker of the House
Which one
Pillows
In one of the videos he says quote Democrats are the most
Vile creatures in this country their vile
I don't want to call them people because that's being too kind
They're scum
You go against
Take me to Lithia transcript of modern-day Alex Jones quite frankly
But these videos were so bad for business
So embarrassing
Even the oathkeeper stopped working with Kessler after Outlets began covering
Using hot water with
August 2013
Can't clear you was probably going to get fired and called for a council meeting
He took to Facebook at that point to try to rile up
Baked Melissa folks
And you know what
German article New Republic
Over 50 people including a few out-of-state militia
Members 1st call
They set up what gun-control Advocate Michael moral of the Statewide group Keystone progress called a quick perimeter
Around the council
The heavily-armed crowd clearly unnerved
The few townspeople who showed up
You know why there's not more residents
The threat
That's why
Because they're afraid
One lifelong resident told the high morning Valley morning call
Call Dara Fraser going to have their Windows shot out
Gilbert
Call Kessler.
And said his wife is afraid to
Stop In The Boro
So you won't his wife won't even stop in town
He's the only topping that's it
Legitimately living in Wild West times and he's a black police
David Carradine
Securities that the only
Aspired take a Polish to Philippe
After 2020
No more president
Militia guys to set up a perimeter outside the council meeting
People into like
Don't fire that guy
He does have a militia of his own to
Michael Merrill from Keystone progress
He told the Huffington Post
I've been organizing for four decades
I've faced klansman a klansman in Kentucky
You tasted Bosnia
A police demonstrator
That night Gilbertson with more frightening than any of those
Situations
Display Force didn't work in Casper was ultimately
The biggest reason for his termination
It turns out he was firing guns that belong to the burrow
Is a videos
R5
Easier way
Opponent
Good we got it but
All kinds of
He unsuccessfully ran for Sheriff
Airplane videos
Production
It's the worst horror movies with get out
He had one other move up
Sleeve
But that's going to have to wait
It's a little bit later than
Miramonte
Before he got himself fired on Alex's show the future
He's about to step in all because he's
Complete lunatic
2011 shot himself in the hand while he was at a bar
Happy Frackville recreational complex
Would you like to young girl needed to get surgery to remove a BB from her leg
Which might not be relevant except the guy who is
F******
Videos of shooting
Guns all over the place
So what does that with a p we got it kind of makes
Do you think maybe he's going to do it with Daddy.
So he's coming up later the show
KB deck
Send.
Said something in this
Is
And
In fiscal year
2011 going to your legs
And
Ambercare on air
Talking about
4000 real
Cool
Alex
Suggested something like that
Should be taken off the air
He literally said that if I said the cat like people in gangs of being killed it doesn't matter
If I said something that offensively
About this like not a couple months
Alex
Worse
What Arabic
I don't know you do that
50/50 auto
Pretty bad
He's alerted me
He's read a lot of things
Of things that you do
History
Historical
Thomas Jefferson
So Alex is batting average
With quote how much would you be willing to bet that's not a real quote
He started saying the words
Let me ask you this
How much would you bet that it's not a real quote 100
If you said everything I own congratulations on your net worth
Thomas Jefferson Foundation has investigated that quote quote the people will not understand
Importance of the Second Amendment
Until it's too late
Baton Rouge
The Jefferson ever said
They consulted all of his collected papers
Correspondence
Insomnia
What's the idea that it's such a
It's such an awful stupid quote
Out of their way they're like
Well maybe this time
May have read something one of these obscure documents
The Thomas
What else are they doing
Beer in any public forum until 2000
7-minute appeared in a book called
A revolution is coming
Bigi name at Carson
It was written
The book of the fictional Novella about
Virginia were pissed off about Texas so they started
Interesting
If you go on Amazon you'll find this review with the headline
Pretty silly
A cheap short novel Revolution
Anarchist
Fantasy
Shallow and uninformed
Jefferson quote or two thrown in for good measure
Amazon reviewer knows more about Thomas Jefferson
F****** Alex
Who claims Jefferson is one of his Heroes
Defense
It possible that reviewer could have worked at the Thomas
There's if there's a real right we don't know
Read everything
Perhaps
Showing up
Tell you more about this guy
I really thought that was this guy is the gift that keeps giving
What's up late last night
This is so much more about him
Figured out like
What this guy is about 90
That's only the stage being set at exactly
Exactly
Okay here we go into the shop
I want to salute you sir
Thank you very much for having me on your show
Alex is thrilled to have this guy on very highly of
Alex first
Please in the
Make sure you don't razor
Too fast I have a really
Itchy trigger fingers
I've lost a few few friends were in the military
Go to Quick align elifi your argument the best assault for me to shoot you so
Self-defense
Kessler talks about
The world
And I've been contacted by The Oath Keepers
Pennsylvania
912 guys
Remember strong throughout the country
912 that's where Glenn Baxter to Target sell co-sleepers a tea party adjacent
He's just a big Tea Party Guy
I should be known about him
I cannot stress this enough literally in
He's just yelling horrible s*** about people and then firing of a semi-automatic rifle
At like a pile of dirt
It's insane
He's just screaming about like the UN needs to go away and
Wild
Free viral
Back in like 20-30
But like
There
Dave give you the appearance of a man on him
So it's like the Clint Eastwood's lecturing Obama
As a chair
Except he has a gun that he's firing at the chair after yelling
Is too old to yell
Racist movie
Visa Direct
Whoever shoots first loses
We want to see
If you want
Physically
Correct. You're right on point there more
Do you understand even kind of aggressive in a little bit violent
Do they take your guns or when they're
We got to do this before they even start
Where do
But I should tell you
But if you're not political now there's no way you're going to be violent later so if you want to prove that you're ready to be violent
Political weird sort of turtle to it
I don't really understand
I don't know if it's
Like anything I would label is like
Eva LaRue
Weird
We don't allow anybody into our militia
Who is
Also put a
Gun control
That would also abolish the fat
If you don't do that
The Throwdown
Yeah
Movies playing
To nullify laws
And all that good stuff
Yes it's really not
There's no substance
Hey.
Globalist occupied government is doing a bunch of stuff that we
Fuel is illegal
There's much more important issue
Like the fact
Kessler's Maher supports
I hope everybody gets behind
Marilu Henner
She's pro-second Amendment she standing behind me on this
She can also push the council into adopting this
And I just really hope
That's interested
Already
Interesting to hear that Mary Lou Henner
The mayor supports
Is a perfect
Story WhatsApp horrible career
In 2011 he was sued by councilman Robert Wagner
A counselor arrested
Strip search
Handheld Wagner in prison
6 hours
What hat what is
He left a voicemail on a machine which he admitted quote wasn't pretty
Wagner called Kessler
TVs in front of
But he couldn't reach
And left a message that got a little bit
From Neighbors
Carrollton
City Council
Some Squad
Wagner swore good bit in the voicemail
He wasn't threatening or verbally harassing the mayor or Kessler in any
There's a pretty open-and-shut case of Abby
Powersport Kessler very literally arrested
For exercising
First Amendment rights
What year was awarded $15,000
Both
Sportscaster because she's Justice
Is f***** up is he
It's not clear whether or not you directed Kessler to arrest Wagner but it is clear that you
She signed off on me rest
Which is completely without probable cause
Constitute
Purelyhr Italian
So what was the
I mean I know why
Arresting him for harassment
Hey guys just harassment
Is Ebony year-and-a-half before he's appearing here as a guest on Alex's show
And holding them up as an example
Full of someone who's going to
Constitution
Literally example of a corrupt cop
Position to deny someone else
Their constitutional right
Over pettiness
And just him flexing
Port of call Gilbert
Nick Cage.
Interview relay
What makes appearances
This guy is Kessler on the Alex Jones Show
Is that about a year after he got fired is gilberton
Kessler
To doing some bread Rehabilitation
By claiming that is
Videos where only made
As part of an undercover operation he was involved with the Fed
Love it I love what they were trying to do
Which was
Appeared on Fox News Radio
I was sent out for what I can't really say exactly
Weather
I can what I can do to find out who's who and what's what amount
These groups groups I'm talking about Second Amendment
Group militia groups
All sorts of
He told comes that he didn't
So he was playing the law
He's been embedded in 20 years something like that
Videos of We lured out some dangerous element so I can publicly declare on
Snitch
Final video of him standing in front of a
Mission accomplished Banner
Crazy
Is literally insane but this guy is like now's work with the fan
Love the swing for the fences you got to give
Swing for the fence
I love it I love it when you just
Really go all out
I have dog whistle
Just say that you've never even heard of Assange
Give me the Home Run I don't believe this guy at all
I don't believe any of this
I think he's 100%
About working
Stop that.
Videos
But his story about being undercover working for the feds
This is just his way of trying to save
She was trying to work
Hangouts
Reality show that
Signed contract for
Wasn't happening
He wasn't making any money
I just think it's really funny though like no matter what even if he is lying
He is
Like if you go through message boards
All of these like
Communities
F****** snitch
Right exactly
Interesting to because like I don't believe them
But if you do
I bet he was working too
To root out
People who are dangerous
Part of being on Alex Jones Show might be part of that Outreach
Might be trying to ensnare dangerous people
If we're going to do it let's do it man
Nowell no
List of
Suspects and arrests that came about as in as part of this investigation
10 + 5
Is this the only thing that makes
Stop Believin
What's 100%
But makes it more robust than just I was making
Videos where I shot thing
How you lower dangerous people
Is that he was trying to build a militia
The idea is that like that call for people to join
That's how you was fine
Itsfunneh
Alex Goes Nova covers in the future when he's on out
Stuff that happened before the time he's on Elsa show
You really should get a sense of like this guy no no no no no no no
Through and see what his record is
Started out like
Ballistic Sheriff
Things better
First partner with Denzel
Point of order
Gilbert
No it's the county not the burrow
Episode
He starts to get some calls
The news for people
Illinois
Legislation
But much like snakes
Hi there reintroducing
This is an emergency
These people are criminals
Because this is a dirty trick flow
If you know any history of Illinois
Say they're going to they're going to bring the general assembly succession in the house tonight at 5
Rainbow
Federal Reserve
Next flip
Remember Joseph fair when it came on your show and he talked about how he was afraid that
Barack Obama and his controller zagline people up and basically do away with him
Remember how you played on The Heirs
Barack Obama is a hard-core communist, understands power
Why
Are you saying that
Alex
Eli has told Obama
True
Search Larry Graham.
Relation to that at all
It's just a line it's me again
Bill Ayers
Alex tried to ask Bill about
The situation of Hazzard today is homely
This is ridiculous
Cuz even the real version of it wouldn't like
If Alex wanted
Just report
Whatever his
The fake version
Larry
You can say that
The FBI Files include
Bill Ayers Towing
It's just like three layers of lies and have had the opportunity while the Weather Underground was
Being investigated like this
No idea
It's not
So we're going to
Already
They want more
It's earlier Alex
Is the Thomas Jefferson quote
It turns out that everybody
Kind of does that
Exit
Infowars
Including
His voice over guy of God
Every form of tyranny
Thomas Jefferson Alex Jones net worth
The context of that quote is about like being against
Religious
The idea of the church
Thomas Jefferson's quote
What about the church
It wasn't about
It wasn't anything like that it was
This is also a form of tyranny over the mind of man
And I have sworn Eternal vigil
Yeah so everybody's kind of whack over there
Infowars
About
About Thomas
God I bet they're more stories
Sylvania
Oh
Insane like I would
I want to see a documentary on
Interviews
Lunacy
Absolutely
Don't get reported or probably the most
Awful
Pirate weird
You know we're only at like
Through this
I feel like we should do something we haven't done in a long time
And that is
I realize that we have
What
I didn't we have some messages from the from the phone
We've never almost never open Light which is where the calls go through
I feel terrible about that
Ansel
People with a little bit Place one of these messages let's see what happens
If you ever come down
Phone number
Message
Hey Dan and Jordan it's Rachel calling from beautiful Seattle Washington
Wanted to tell you two things one that I recently got a bird feeder
I really think that if all the alt-right dick heads and docu
Just like sat down and
What's the bird for a little while
The world would be a much better place
Everything always tell your sister every time Ted Anderson is on the show
Picturing like
Mitch McConnell mixed with like Doug Dimmadome
Anyway
I love your work and I love you
I think she's right on the bird feeder
Readers to solve the problems of nothing
Creative Solutions for problems that have been going on for a long time
I love it
Why not
Cedar's forbath
Yeah
I also we should say phone number is 530 neon nip
For people who are curious if you ever want to call it
I'm not sure if we're going to be having the time cuz generally UPS
Tokyo pretty long
So I know
I haven't listened to any of you
So I don't know
A tune-up
Hey Jordan guess what it turns out that messages that are more than a month old getting erased automatically Buy
So much for our plan on going over
Old messages
I'm sorry
Hey we
Totally
Absolutely
Are these are the guys from
We're not going to enforce
The gun laws that
Washington
Just passed are they just doing the same
Kessler thing
I don't know I don't know enough about this
Specifics but maybe it's their Kessler right
Like the the Constitutional Sheriff
Movement or whatever
Over that accept together
A sheriff after
I could do that again
So give me more
Give me more places to
That's what I love to do
Bunch of assholes
Yep
So if you are 1530 neon nip
We will hopefully do this again to actually open up Skype
From time to time
This was a little bit shorter but I'm glad
To do something that's
Not about
Presence
Google Talk
Map
Oh yeah
Dickhole police chief
From Pennsylvania
Who
Is just
That
Story of him
Being passed
Like screaming obscenities at the lady
And about to drive away and then
Because you can
Can hear the wheels turning in that story of him being like
I bet she's not threatened
Maybe I need to pull out a gun
And make sure that she gets
The message
Allegedly I don't know how that case
I don't know I couldn't tell from the article that I
Whatever
But
It's f***** up
There are
Sounds like
Yeah and a lot of them
Don't have someone like him as their own
Thank God
Stories out there that we
We just never here
And that sounds like
Towns that have
The f****** police chief
Who is that
Real power hungry
Power
To I don't know whether it's enriched himself or like
Crush
Mild descent
Or whatever
Corruption that went under Joe arpaio's Iron Fist
There is an interview this guy Kessler
Cold Case
Joe Arpaio
About Joe
Before we heard about it
That was a large enough
Place for people to
Attention
At least he had a
Group of police officers working
Yeah
You just like to imagine that everything runs well and you know like we have all these
Some place that are great
Flextop
Stuff like this
Nothing but
Like I suck at least at least we can
Chicago Police Department
Not interrupt app
Bears
So
But next week
But until then
Highway website
We do it what side is now.
We also want
We are on iTunes leave a review
Please do that
Abso
If you're looking
Through this
Robert Wagner
Yeah
Who is this
Robert Wagner
Is it Robert Blake
Cuz that would also make sense.
Councilman Robert Wagner has never killed any
As best I can tell you just
Strip search
For exercising
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color