Alexandra Thurston color
Jordan
Who's your favorite game
Thrones
Easter to everyone right we're on our way
You know
People are excited
You know it's
Sardis
Where is Blizzard in Chicago
Snowing in the middle of April
Chicago's great
Snow in April I remember that
I'm not I'm not dodging your quest
The first season I just decided I don't give a s*** about
Daria
Story about who's King
I don't care about your guys paste
But those kids have something going on
Panda Palace
And for the rest of the
I have been proven correct
Danny
Don't care
Fair enough. He's alright
He seems more interesting
I meant Danny with a dragon
Enjoy that
Snow with his
Rejecting of all that pallets into
Bulshit
Yeah I mean
Don't care don't understand why anyone gives a f*** about that
The story
People that I hate the most are actually
Stark and all those
41 Pacific
Baby
No re is the best thing about Game of Thrones
The beginning and ever one-sided I was
Oh I'm sorry you're omniscient
Great it seems like a good day
Spoiler alert
Anyway
D2 of Game of Thrones end
Just kind of plugs into a tree
Schematics of the Death Star
You were pretty surprised
Before we started recording that I have ever watched
I didn't
Full disclosure
Do you know who is aggressive
Singing the show audience
I appreciate it very much though
They would like to start off this episode
People who are
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Crystal
Krystal's
Usher
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Appreciate it
If so
Thank you so much you are now a globalist
Don't get mad and tell her you're brilliant someone someone sodomite sent me a bucket of
Somebody who took their donate
Similar Christopher
Thank you so much
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Morrill elevator
Appreciate that
Fantastic
Carlton
Natalya brilliant someone sodomite
Has a Caribbean
Google
I don't want to hate black people
Jesus Christ Charles
Would like sports
Appreciate
YouTube sign up
Transport the show
I think it's pretty easy
Get the image in your head you know you hear six names listed off
You could easily get the idea that were like
Duck jumping into a pile of coins
Continue to support
The show in
To WhatsApp
I hate every element of it
I hate every except thinking people first
That I believe is only good
Right
Hiring keep me from doing what I assumed that was the case
If you're going to be going off on
Should I just text
The word abroad
Pre-recorded
Episode on Wednesday
For Friday you never know
Segura send you off in
InStyle
Unfortunately we're going to do
This episode over April 12th
20 nights
That's Friday
Well I need to know what Alex was
People are clamoring for our insight
It isn't
It is
It feels like
The president is
Is trying to get a house representative
You have put that.
The president is officially
That doesn't really come up although Alex
Dumb s*** about to Omar I'm not I didn't
Include any of those clothes
To the actual news.
The day
Steris trailer blah blah blah
Move on but there's other stuff you know like a songs
The rest
No those
Alex
Gotta have a
Take
Never heard of
I'm going to swing for the fences on this woman just hate
Interesting taken will get to it down the road
It's a this is a pretty boring
For the most part
But
That doesn't mean that this next
Didn't
Almost entirely ruined
Here's where we start at the episode
And I will explain on the other end of this clip
A metal
Wouldn't be here right now. Assange
The best Men rotten filthy jails
Mozik Rida Pisa Pisa
Hung by those I tried to please author unknown
Putting on a shell wall Revolutionary War
British cell wall
Dan read a book
Freedom fails the best man rotten filthy shells
They tried to please
And the Jolly Green
But I'm rushing back to the information
But here's the thing
For a moment cuz I want to discuss that quote
Correctly
He seems to be getting better or least this is a better version of
Unfortunately he's completely
He says that the author of the quote is unknown and it's about written on a cell wall during the Revolutionary War
That isn't true that doesn't sound
At all established
It was from a March 28th
47 letter to the editor of the Wall Street
Lawyer by the name of George Hiram
Attribution given
Did the quote as it appears online
Support
One place that differs
And it's attribution
Book
It's called The Impossible Dream
A self-published
Communist track
Published in 1990
Dan Rather
I was hoping to track down a copy of this to read over
This is one of the only places that I
I can find where this quote is
Is attributed to
Author unknown
But unfortunately on Amazon
Cost $400
I wasn't willing to pay that $400 to get a copy of this book so I decided to
To see what I could learn about the author of 1 km
Initials km
It turns out that this is
Is K Maureen
And the more I looked into her
And I was
This book
Is where Alex
The quote from
The first thing that led me to suspect
Is it he has listed as a member on the website of the foundation of
Economic education
Oh that's not good
Was founded in 90
The first modern
Specifically setup to promote libertarian ideas
That's what I thought
That seems like
And furthering that's
Suspicion is the 2001
2002 president
Was Mark skousen
Brother of Joel skousen
A nephew of w Cleon skousen two people that Alex is all about
Call traffic but I've been waiting weeks
To bring it up but unfortunately
We've often meant
Is stupid books The Naked communist
Capitalist butt
I recently
Discover he's written a ton of books
A lot of them are weird fundamentalist Mormon
He published a book called
Do you want to raise a boy
?
It's not really there's no emphasis given to any of the words but there's a lot of different ways
Could be
You want to raise a boy
You walked
Do you want to raise a boy
The book includes
Sometimes boys get into bed sex habits during the early team
The first
Homosexuality
Wait for it
It starts out with masturbation
Then the individual
The partner for Mutual sex
Play these practices are destructive to the personality
To the point where he becomes involved in various types of sex crimes
Speculative
The moral degenerate is responsible for
Vicious
Sadistic sex crimes on record sexuality is
Cultivated
When homosexuals are arrest
Conduct by saying
I guess I'm just made that way
His family are really cool
Is that the reason that he has a
Cleon skousen got uncles
Books are always beat naked black
I bring all that up just because it's heavy
President
Couple years with Mark skousen
I just need an excuse because I've been waiting
That's
Banks named the more like
Evil
Down bad
Murdering every tailed I'm not positive any relation
Ee absolutely
Takes him so much
Koch brothers
Add donors Trust
Donors Capital fund give hundreds of thousands
The dollar store
It is a part of what's known as
Peacock Network
Is the Astro A10
I bring it up but it's not part of it
Kason build
Back on track
Tamarine
Eating is best known for disseminate
Purporting to be evidence
Outside meddling in local politics
Before
Heroes Act
Concerns to the
Who operated as a local
Watchdog
Council
On inter-governmental relay
Orsi's
Gir
According to her
I've been receiving the output from California Council on intergovernmental relations
When I went before governors
Local government reform
Testimony
Ccir
Meddling in local governmental affairs
After my appearance there
Ccir reports
Coming to my mailbox
Friesen see what happened
They took her off of
Besides after she testified against them
KK Disco
Fugees
Like what is as far as a larger
Place inside of
The government
Body of
The council governmental relations
Play just like a little like the cat and the County government and Diet Coke
City government
It's just like a
Let's or coordinator
That I get
Buried
California it would probably be tough for me to say
Has to do with coordination
Government
The cheese lady who goes
Some earrings
Agitator
I don't even know she goes to the meetings necessarily but gets the documents
That's intense
Conspiracy that
She stopped getting these
Report
So according to heat
She shows up at the ccir office and picks up the reports she was missing
Quote
There was one box near her death.
Studiously avoided
Well she was gone I picked up one of the documents from the box she had not looked into
It was titled
The politics of
Change local government
Reform
If you're keeping
Score
Essential element needed
To create a nefarious
And attempt to keep it away from someone
Whether or not that story isn't anyway
Story are not accurate if I'm
From these sorts of weird eyes
Government sources
Documents
Book on
Control techniques
Okay sorry sorry apology
Spell appalling negation of
The principle of self-government
Publix
News politics
Shooting programs
The report itself is a 220 page analysis
Pictures of local government
It is not a mic
In any sense of the word
The preface specifically state
It's quote finally a report
Tries to be objective
Put another way we do not want us
Any state
We do not Advocate change restructuring of any kind
What community does
You should remain up to the jurisdiction
Leadership
We do feel however that
It's time
Perform the ways in which change occurs when
So what's the change
They're talking about
Obviously
Thanks
By the federal government
Take over the local
In reality when you read the report it's super Broad
It encompasses pretty much
Kind of altering of local
Call policy
But one thing it's
Particularly
Is how to deal with
Growth
Princeton
How did the local government
Windy City
Absorbed
Leon incorporate
Rated areas on there
We're going to get into
FEMA camps in Murder
Not really
The report
Describes
The problem
Problems common to cities
Neighboring
With some unincorporated urban areas
Here I haven't developed
Haven
Wichita
Cancel route
So because they are part of
The city they are unincorporated
Their places
Impacto Versailles
They don't pay back
The city the service
Afforded
Rug the connection
Right right
But it's alright for
The city to go to war with
Annexed territories
Israel
Another question I ask is like generally speaking
And so what happens when
Negroes
Beyond the confines of the county
How does that
National structure of
Cooperation
It's important to note that this report
Did not advocate
Keep Change Change
Even a actual
Is happy
Stick to the idea that change
Is even happening
Tactic of
Scholarly
They started by sending a quest
American local government
Beneficial
Had this to say about
Significant
Which responded
The questionnaire
8%
Restructured reorganized or modernize their manager
Instructors in Submariner in the
The motivating factor most frequently mentioned by in
Instigators of change
Level with cost of
And I believe that a better man
Would save money and deliver better quality
They are already changing
There's a lot of things that already happened
Without any
Intervention
The federal government or even the state government
Cause and effect
Right
Reacts to
Ultimately the report
What happened except outside
Climate for
Which could include
The collapse of government
Pacific Pride
Catastrophe
Natural disaster
Corruption in local leaders
Or financial troubles that are overburdening
The count
To your whatever
Probably called every one of those
F****** called that doesn't cause drain
This is
Uses of misinformation
Conclusion
What you does
Actually
Similar to what Alex
She claims that the report is
Is advocating
Creating
Climate of
In order to push
Evil Legend
Gestation but that's just her paranoid reading
Case study
Positive
Probably could have been helpful that didn't work out
Workout
I've been similarly there's like 12
End up
At this one felt threatened
Found
There are circumstances
They described
A climate for change
They're usually require
They're saying
Baywatch
Trying to push
Through this
Unwanted
Because there's
Need a climate of change
To do it obviously they will precipitate
The collapse of
The government
Catastrophes like a natural disaster
Civic crisis
False flag shooter or financial troubles overburden
System
All of these things
Paranoid world
Supplies
To all of the primary sources
Very similar mental processes
Is going on
Cindy
Far and wide but it only got a little bit of traction
The paranoid right-wing world
And caught the attention of a local politician
Globalist
Mostly because anyone who were read the reports
She was citing his evidence
Was full of s***
But this is what makes
Indeed
Right-wing world
Of course
So then in 1990 she wrote The Impossible Dream
And I was able to find a PD
So I could pay $400
I had the same situation I was really interested in this book on
In New York
And it turns out there's only one book that's ever been written
About them
And in order to get a copy
$50
I couldn't find
I'm so interested in so fascinated by it I will never be
So
This book is just a
Pirate like a rambling pile of
Litter robot
The theory of evolution
Do animals ever lived
Has made an impact on History Warehouse Cuban have
Are
Did she drop a microphone whatever she wrote that has an artistic flourish it's literally a narc
Give me the cheese making against evolution
That's not good
Uncertain
Mirrored in the pages
From the book's introduction
Quotes
Here's a bit split over patriotic resist
Socialism
Communism Paragould this worldwide Revolution
More real that apparent is the true goal evidence in every react revolutionary movement
Promoted
Actualizing every conquered land
It explicitly stated in early.
Feudalism
With the revolutionaries and Total Control
Of all the resources of the world including what
Alex talks about the globalist
Being office human
That is something
Pretty Jermaine to his worldview that I'm not actually totally honest I've heard people
Talk about Nick
Victoria way
Many other place yet
That's weird
There's just so much of Alex
Like ideas at the forces of taken over
The schools in the media these nefarious forces
Arguments that
The globalist forces employed the hegelian dialectic
No problem reaction
Fallujah
The stock market crash of 19
Plan to bring
Governmental control
That's in there
Define liberalism
And conservative
Who's actively resisting the revolution
Fingers at the Bilderberg Society
Federal Reserve
Give it to me I would have been gone
She claims that a minority of Congress voted to establish the Federal Reserve she doesn't say Surya
But it's
And she also says that the Federal Reserve is evil plant
McCarthy frames immigration ism
To take over the country
Destroyer
Decries globalist meddling
The quote Internal Affairs of roti
South Africa
Jubilee
She believes
The plan to take over the government
Your standard newworldorder paranoia
Is cribbing from the
Explains a lot of it
However
Anyone other than Alex
We argue
For instance you keep saying there's a war on for the
Of men which kind of generic
As well do
The inscription on
The Infowars family crap
She also uses
Particular phrasing that I often hear Alex
But I never really here anywhere else like
The term end
Maine
In the analysis
In the main
That's very specific phrasing
Another thing is that she discusses the oil crisis
Piece of evidence that it was
Planned conspiracy
Is
Wendy Williams
The supposed chaplain
I've never heard
Anyone except
And Alex take that guy serious
Really even most Patron
Conspiracy
Message boards I've read call him a scammer and a charlatan
That's a weird
Similarity
Also
Keaton argues that the rise in suicide rates
Among youth in the 90s
Is attributable to what she calls in schools
The Peace of Alex's ton of time
But I've never really know where he's getting it from
But it's literally spelled out in this weird self
Facebook
I'm not saying this early that he got it from there could be from another source
But it's something that I don't really hear
From other place
The idea that
Teaching kids
About the dangers of
Suicidal
Suicidal thinking
Causes them to commit suicide
That's
And even though it's an impossible book to find
Essentially
Alex's
Cleon skousen
Marvel Universe
That does seem like he would have a access to a copy of that
He has Reddit
Because there before that
Times of the internet
Super Wendy's
Today like
Today and
The the means by which a lot of
Patriot militia
Communicated their word like
People would order books
From
Self-publish Outlet
Eikenberry
This book being
Part of the
Assertive literature
System that Alex had access to this for Alex's
Bercerai
I doubt that
Couldn't
Removed from getting a copy
There's a possibility that it's
Impossible
Yes but it's not definite
Really freaky
Like a blizzard
Legitimately
Was on page 50
Where's the picture of
Every year since 19
57 around the Ides of March
The curtain goes up
Around around of weird Royal
You Americans recognize significance in the
The sequence of events
Justly realize our relationship end
Subliminal in nature
Gippy American
People alert
What happens to those
Like Joe McCarthy refused to compromise with
The rights begin with a saturation reporting by the media of a rash
Stream District Court terrorist activity
Americans recognize this
This campaign for what it is
A classic
Example of brainwashing
Holy s***. A month ago
After Christchurch
The shooting in New Zealand
After that Alex
About how the Ides of March the globalist plan all sorts of things
Eversource
Which
You're a goddamn which did you miss
So I think it would be a huge
Cute stretched
Took a toll
Inspiration from the
Local California politics
Document
Quote unquote
In the 70s
The entire global
Honestly book
Pretty boring and
Iris
Used to believe that Alex has never read it
And here's the thing
I've never heard him reference
Ever heard him say the name km
And yet here she is
Writing a book
It expresses a ton of things he would go on to preach
A good five years
Before he ever got on the air
I don't know what this means I don't know what to make of
Places that I can find the quote
Is referred to as being attributed to
To author unknown
And for the part about it being scrawled on a revolutionary war cell wall I think I was
Imagination
Alright
I think that's what it's called
Is Alex
Weirdly misattributed a quote
At least I had the suspicion he miss attributed a quote
And then I read 500 pages of nonsense
Book
We clearly have some
Like that
Ides of March part is really really really f***** up
That's almost like a fingerprint comparison
Forensic literature
Analysis
But it looks weird
It looks like Alex probably at this book
Is there a picture of her
Cuz it was self-published
Do we know we do know they don't exist
Cuz she was part of the actually don't know that
Could be a pseudonym I've not seen a picture of her and it's very difficult
Specific about her other than
She's left a footprint with the FBI
MC self-published
Facebook
Exist
Someone who is a quote-unquote watchdog
In the seventies
California politics
Yeah I also found a site for
Show called
Sweet Liberty
That promoted
Her book and her.
The politics
Unfortunately they also sell a bunch of books
Zion are real
So they're Pez dispensers
Sara Lee
Even though there is a lot of that in
It's at least a JC
I like learning
And so I don't know about
Or anything like that but it was like
I was reading a book
Never talks about like this
Picadillo
Points of interest
California
And stuff like that
Expressing through that like
Climate of change in the
The politics of change
Right.
Is definitely what Alex thinks the globalist
Pneumatic acid
Effects of it are very similar
With the like
There's a Polish there's a there's a new polish I would assume
Sorry about that.
But now let's get it
Rambles but nothing for a while and then guess what
Confirm
Terrible
You read a 500-page book
Instead of
Really
If the episode I don't have time
S500
But let me be clear
The book is only three
How do I
Alex
He has another one of his lawyers
Civil rights lawyer first
Country with some of the top people out there
Very honored to have Norm status in studio what is he also is representing me in
Connecticut
Anti-free speech
Sean fair today
That is why
The entire time
Why
Also
Restarting
The elements of my prediction
True like I suggested a while back
You might see Alex's
In the present day is
Bruce
Where he just like makes his whole show about his own legal trouble
She bad like
Let's train of nurses
Become
Multiple episodes where his lawyers just come in
I've got
Super weird
This nor Pettis character is a real douche
You got in a little bit of hot water
From the Connecticut Post
Quote
Local attorney North Patterson posted Monday photos
Three white hooded beer can
Around refrigerator
To his Facebook page
The caption read
Clock stores
How to explain this b******* by
For the sake of provocation
I like to drop a bomb and then watch it
Explode
In the comments
It's more it's more than Bloodsport
Alex is goddamn
Troll
You know what you know what's worse
I would have given that a solid
Plus
If he didn't have the brown bottle hat
Like if you just have the cord
Right
Effort to make sure that
You weren't in favor of
If you somehow make the me but negative
Then maybe
Brown bottle hanging is that the one that's
Beyonce
Into you should be arrested
People started
Let's face it if you're white you can't be right Alex's goddamn attorney of the white
Control
Why didn't you just say
Guys I'm representing
You know
Stop it
Maps
Who's known as madame
Alex's good buddy Charlie Sheen
Picture of the Gateway pundit
We got to see where his bread
You know that that's I think he's figured out a way to latch on
The right-wing grifters
And make money off them
Yeah it's like a it's like the lawyer for Elise like the lawyer The Wire
Avon Barksdale
Everybody knows what he's doing
He also represented the New Haven occupying camp
What's a counterexample
To these examples
He's doing now
As much as it is
Distance of the weird
Trajectories a lot of people took after Aki
For example
Kessler
The guy who organized
The United right rally
Charlottesville
Occupy before
It wasn't broad appeal
That's what I'm saying
Motives
Got involved well I mean it is the 99% versus the 1%
Yeah there's there's no
Just because this is always
So f******
Fun
Quote cigarettes don't kill people
People do
We recognize the claim at once
The transparent nonsense
So we text a backhoe using the proceeds
Healthcare
For those destroying the
Why not use the same public policy
Gun violence
I can see the hidden agenda
Power I'd repeal the 2nd Amendment
It's an anachronism
Alex's lawyer is a goddamn gun-grabber
Jesus
In a response to
Clearly like I would repeal the 2nd Amendment
Norcos
Suggest a mechanism you'd like to put into play
Inherently dangerous product is placed
Stream of Commerce
All those who introduced the product can be forced to
Share the liability
For the Honda product causes
Why not treat guns in this manner
Suppose a firearm is used in a murder
Asasi 250000
A $10,000 fine
The cellar
Each registered owner
These
Catch the attention of
Trucking in bartering and firearms
It might also inspire a sense of Greater accountability
Responsibility
He concludes by saying quote
You'll have to pry my gun from my cold dead fingers
A friend of mine said not too long ago
Fine
Nice a game on
It's time to get serious about done
Control gun violence is a matter of life and death
Don't expect me to fight fair against
Beer
Against the fear your gun will kill me
We're listening to old 2012 2013 episodes in our Sandy Hook
Investigation
1 things that we found that Alex's
Completely obsessed
With the impending gun
To the point where he's on the border of incitement
I take it there's a Civil War coming
For taking gun
I find it completely hilarious
That is new lawyer in
Sandy Hook defamation trial is literally one of the people he was saying was
To destroy the country
A pic office oval
Alex doesn't say anything
Billable hours
You tell you my personal beliefs at all
So long as you hit me monthly man I'll say whatever you want me to say
I mean
I just don't understand how you can end up with someone as your lawyer
Is someone who advocates
For something that you are publicly saying
Going to overthrow the country
The freedoms
I would get rid of the Second Amendment
Seems to be the only thing
He actually cares about
Interesting question
As far as
ACLU is
Absolute
Other races
Good lawyer
You know Alex is going to let him take his
Cuz he can't be that good of a lawyer that there's not someone else who's as good
Alex
Consider that a variable everyone is clamoring to work
The issue is if this guy is someone who advocates
To the repeal of the second
Alex doesn't want him
To be associated with his big
First Amendment
To get rid of the Second Amendment
Henrico Court
Liquor store
Little boy has First Amendment precedent-setting case but he's involved
You don't want this guy wants to get rid of the Second Amendment
I get a win in the Supreme Court
That only makes us much closer
Hookah
Alex is stupid
The lawyer if
Is taking
The case on let-go
Free speech apps
Whatever
Or whatever
Impatient
Although stop with the racist
I'm actually going to move that back
250000 dollar $10,000 $5,000 that's like the flat tax
That's a terrible
I think it was just sort of a broad idea
I'm just come back when you get a second
Soffit Fascia
Norm pattis
Is also a lawyer who represented
Candace Owen
But not when she was Candace Owens
When she was Owen
No
When she was
High School
And she was the victim of
Some racist
Harassment
Sexual harass
And so she
She said the people who were
In her butt
She reported this
School
Take care of it
Her parents sued the school district
Take care of it and respond appropriately
Ended up winning
$37,000 in a settlement
Was her lawyer
I don't want it
Because I don't know all the
Details of his
I did find
An article about it so I can
Save it it's a real thing
It certainly
And I believe her I believe Candice
That stuff doesn't mean that I don't believe
A the chi
As a youth
Was the victim of
This sort of
Horrible harassment and abuse
Yeah I believe that
Even though she is presenting ideas right now.
Perpetuate that very same horrible abuse that does not mean that she does not deserve to be protect
Does
Say things like
Real hate crimes don't exist
Yeah or hate crimes are all hoaxes and that's okay
And so with the know this about her before
History
Oh yeah sort of ideas out
People
Put those ideas
Used to come on Infowars
Regularly
You know
That this
Stop happens
You know you were
You know that other people also are and they aren't making it up
Yet you are helping a system
Established
And normalize
Get up
People to hear your story
They would say you were mine
And that sucks
I'm not entirely sure I don't want to litigate any of it it's not important other than to say
Fit learning that she has
History makes
Her look worse
I believe her and I
High schooler having to deal with
I also my heart goes out to her after hearing Alex talked about her
Rabbit ears Westchester Harbour I got busy we never got it done
She's awesome
Super sexy super smart
That's right integrity
What's number one on the house
Weird
It's always the first
Comes up whenever he's talking
These women that like
Like her are part of his side
Is always
The first thing
Every reason every anchors
Is blonded
Long time
Those comments at you
Hitler just wanted to make Germany great wonderful National aspirations
I don't give a f*** about saying that
Rationalizing
Hitler I just picked
I just sense of nationalism and
I still think it's just
Stupid
So take
Evil out of it and it's
Conspiracy
Alright
What's going on
MCs
Grifting the very people
Who hurt her as
Easiest to grow
She's a black woman know that
Omarosa is gone
Reveal in 2 years when she's the president that you was f****** with the white nationalist
The most Progressive president
I get done with all that
Alex is talking to his lawyer
Some more of this patent
Paris
And out they start talking about the Eisenhower's farewell.
Might be
Some
Revisionist history
Recall Eisenhower's famous famous warning about the military everybody quotes
Everybody always see only person controlling
The military-industrial complex
No point Eisenhower's final speech
Does he mention a breakaway Society
Does use the words a quote scientific
Technological
Using it is very
I've never discussing the balance
3 main
To be involved
Technology
Trolls it
If the government is not involved at all it runs
The risk of becoming
Captive
To the scientific
Who would have full control over
Early modern
Which government
Was dependent
Similarly the government
Involved because
Intellectual
Curiosity with
Money
Which would lead to a likely dead
Innovation
Contact
Is very clear
There's not a problem with Alex
Eisenhower's literally advocating
Speech for the things
Alex
The globalist
For instance he talks about how the world is
Smaller
To become a confederation
Mutual trust and respect
Global government
Pretty much where the countries of the world RC
Seen as equal
Eisenhower literally also says quote
Disarmament with a mutual honorary comp
Did you bring imperative
He was trying to disarm the world
Do something that Alex is worried that the UN is trying to do
Through their non-binding
Rewriting
So much
Defense
You know likes industrial complex
That's great
Running it
Yeah we were running it we would run its own well not even
Stupid Alex Azar
Because he always does
It's the same behavior that
He's assuming so much of what
Of Eisenhower
And then citing it as gospel and that's inappropriate
It is always fascinating to go back
Look at
Things that presidents have said that they
What you know we weren't able to
During the
And the way that Facebook
Open Google and all that stuff
Run ever
Is there also
Stifling innovation
Themselves
No he didn't really do
Much
About
Any of that
If you know Carter's
Carteret
In terms of what should have happened
The government
They were able to actually accomplished
Because of all the info
Like the
Industrial
Sure
Hispanic
New radio host
In House shows
It's going to be launching
Real there's no chance
I mean baby
Harrison Smith
House show
Whatever
That's going to be
Bonanza
Be f****** Rappaport
You know like
That be fun
Larry Hagman
Right
Bland
People who are doing the fourth hour are now going to do a show
Both Stone and corsi's salaries off-the-books
He can hire some Flo Rida
You know that
For quite a while after he got let go
Contractor whatever
I believe that is
He's not working here anymore and now I'm free
I didn't know that Buckley doesn't work there anymore I don't know
I just know that he's not there anymore
It does explain a lot cuz I was wondering why
Inspirational videos
About how you like whatever you put your mind to
Yeah might be posting these videos and I like
I don't know
Water Tower in Chicago
I'm not sure of cases but
Next clip where Alex
It's a little bit about that
Paul Joseph Watson
Mother talking
I don't think this is very interesting
Quite frankly
How much more of a
From Alex
In terms of Assange
Because it seems like something he cares a lot about released
It's just kind of like listen to this
This is very underwhelming
I don't know who's got it with you likes the Russians relation
The corruption
Order the song to do it at signs get it
Mush
False
If he doesn't let us get out of prison
Sao Paulo
Not all that important
Because it is essentially like
Trump
His administration
Is looking to extradite
The United States
Means that there wasn't any coordination
Between
Emily quilt maybe it's a nonsense
The truth
These situations really is
Is Trump is a narcissistic
Aspiring Authority
Metal history
Right so
What's going on
Alex Azar
Just pathetic
Because
Trump told him to release those things
Now he's being persecuted
I'll still like Trump but I'll do it with a little bit of Shame if he doesn't let it go
Where is the line man the line
There is a
Alex
To get to Paul Joseph Watson pumped up
Fitworks
What would you quantify this cuz
Lamborghini
True train we have the info
You feel like watching
Yeah we won some battles and
But we basically won the argument that's the time that we're driving
That's not why
Like his response was almost like
Yeah goes alright a scarf
You're angry
I think it's the azzam
Trying to get this
Other person to recognize and
Fetal
You feel about what you've done
Like it's two people at the end of a run
We went through a lot out there did we left it all on the field
Him like
Having done that tour podcast
Ambien like
I got my message that I could possibly
It's usually about
Is
Look at how great I am but even when you say I want to salute you
To feel the way that Alex is a
Express
Fillmore
Justified in entitled
Always
Gear of April 12th
Reveal
Who is hosting the fourth hour on this
Episode
You're listening to The Alex Jones Show
Hope he doesn't come in and we just listen to this song.
I only kept that in I don't give a f*** about what Nick begich has to say
That's very weird
Infowars
You know where Nick begich
It was on April 8th
Project Camelot
I just stood up I was so excited
Within a couple days
He was on both projects
Hosting the fourth hour of Alex
I just
Introduce this
Exhibit
In terms of these worlds are not different
Yeah
I know you got excited there
Project Camelot
But like I said the beginning of this episode
I do want to send you on your vacation in style
That's all I do have something special
Oreo
I went back to the well
You're going away for awhile it's only right you know you go out on a real high note
Send it right now
There's so much more to experience
YouTube channel
Green Pastures
Just because
Entire episode
There isn't still
Amazing
From Lionel
Some of this
Please remember that Lionel is now a qanon promoter
Invited to
Goddamn White House
Goddamn
So I think we should have
Automated
Take you like a website
Degenerates
Madlib
For Lionel it it would be the exact same thing
Actual ones are weirder
I think
Be blown away
Looking for an honest man
I'm looking for someone who actually like mine
Desecrating Old Glory is begging for money
So real quick he has a picture up of like someone who's panhandling but it's like doing them
Doing mine is stuff with her with a hat outfit
Feel about living statues
Similar vein I can't stand mascot uniform suit
Navigate to Pennock
Don't waste my time showing me the apps that I know you practice and I know you'll do
Tell me ahead of time how you're going to find the card or whatever
Mystikal
Stop Magic
And a real magic
I feel so similar about
Watching some videos of my life Magic
Real
I think he is very infuriated
We're working very hard on their craft as opposed to
Making a deal with some sort of deity you to gain power
You are entertaining
Great Is Awesome
Every time someone has to be on the street
It brightens
It's the best
Can I have a dollar
There's a video of the guy who won the world close-up Magic
Championship switch
Great to know that that exist
What was
Incredible
I don't need magic to be real
To know that
What that guy did
Is Magic
You know what I'm saying practice and dedication you have to put in
I mean whatever amount of time Lionel this b*******
Isabella toriel
What is nothing compared to what you have to do to be able to make a card disappear
Who have a craft
I hate mine
I think I think a reason the Trump invited
PIX11 which is
Is it New York
Like watch like before
Qanon
I'm not entirely sure but yeah
How dare you be mad
H-E-B least everyone's problems
Moscow what happened
Minol
Time like Vaudeville
Harrah entertainment
You got a lot of
And then in the Next Generation after that
Do you like there was a lot of jokes
It's about mine
World world
Sure I made this was probably
89 years ago
It still was irrelevant
Making fun of my
Do you like
Brick
Will Ferrell
Great
Ron Burgundy
What is playing
The significance of a Ted Baxter character cannot be overstated
1970s
Partly that of Television Broadcast News
Cronkite sign off until March 6th
1981 11 years later
Charles Collingwood
Robert
Richardson
Eric sevareid
1927 Yankees
These guys were venerable and venerated wise
Distinguished
Respect
Brighton
Myself
Exploded
No these
Custom print
Out of the blood and fog of war and no no comparison today
Andrew Ted Baxter
At the height of our love and respect affair with these broadcast dude
The news anchor.
News version of the potemkin village and its idiot
Like
I mean
There was a great character
In the Mary Tyler Moore Show
Parody
So is
Why are you mad
I guess I'll be making fun of mimes
Hearkening to like this new version of news parody and is good as my
Virginity
I wish things were the 70s again
Why aren't all of his broadcast just
Lovecraft
Story
Character Randolph Carter
T.i.
EDreams
City of the Gods
But it's forbidden
Humans to go to
So he tries
Adventures
Do cats fight
The city of Cudahy
It's really hard at building a city
And they didn't want people in
There was a city of the Gods
Right now
So much better than
Of the Gods
Adapt and went to his City
It was Providence
His memories of
You're so beautiful
To this dream
Exactly
Mega Lottery
Complaints he has our base
Because of
Him
Idealizing
His child
Wyandotte
I will see you then
You might as well just not far off
But he also Tristan
Some other interest
Areas
Mimes and magicians and mascots
Butterflies
The three arms of evil out
Gone
Terrible
About
Amazing
Dispensary
And the granddaddy of conversate
This guy
Manolo Blahnik
No monster Jimmy Choo
Man was made famous for miserable self-indulgent narcissist
Ford Angel constantly complaining griping Crainer Cosmos
About why no one gets it
No one loves
Dubai these torture devices
Confusing challenge
Disfigured and gnarled claws
So now you showing pictures of like mangle
The screen Wichita
Hammer told faith that can double for a hoof
Cracked
I'm sure Lionel here
Just come on over.
The world
In some cases
Clydesdale quality Toby offenders
Varnish
Call more attention
I'll tell you why because there was in The Illusionist
How to pair of sandals are cute
Translation
Expensive Chinese numbers of leather
Switch console
It distorts and could torture Gates
Sports Authority display the silliest examples of locomotion
John Cleese
Call Stewart
There you have it
And I leave you with a simple question
Running your own f****** question look into the history of women's question is
Stupid
History
What is it
Years ago men for sale
Actuator the oppression throughout this time
And that's why
Haha
Did you not think about this
Play I guess it's valid of
Shoe designers make
Perpetuating
Continue that tradition
Set the women on sex and the
Mercedes fault which is not
Events theme song
Seems to be resting at the
If you allow pardon my use
Other word of love
I feel like maybe
Qanon now
Maybe it sort of a tradition of his
Career that you just spoke
Tucson
The wrong
But you can get away with
Asking a question
That you could have
Answered
Like you're it
After you've already given your dumb opinion what was the why didn't you ask questions first and then looking
Do it and then be like oh hey guys complain about
Bring up the Chinese
You could make your report better
If you try
Little bit of time
Thesaurus doesn't have to think any can still get a TV show
Totally
As much as any more
Vines used to be
Wish I found one of your
No
Play this episode of Lionel's report is
I would describe it as him
Trying out
Material
New York comedy club
Periodically
Jokes
We trying to do Joe okay
Miscellaneous
Where do bugs go
ETV news
Are these others
I'll tell you that it was one of them
Worst guns of buildings in Chicago that you can just go and look up
The website
Unresolved bed bug problem
Like what the f*** are you talking about well I had to burn a lot of them in the
Fire
Another joke
And the dead daisies
And the birds it was showing up
H1 N1
Uber calculator
Look how little you can weigh
Local commercials
Jordans
I love that one
Must be a local New York commercial and I guess that as a joke is just sort of
Like it's based on recognition
So I mean I guess that misses the mark for us in
Chicago local work
Also I didn't even
Composite cuz I didn't realize that
That's unreal
Where is the joke
I'm confused
What is what is
Trying to
That was still a continuation of the
The bedbugs bit
But yes
Yeah I guess
Elvis
Whatever happened to all of these horrible things
We all know about them now so they don't I guess maybe they got sensationalized a little
Who killed Opie
People
Children
I don't know so far I wouldn't
Who
Who buys all those knives at 3 in the morning on QVC
Jersey
I said Manning on the back
Are you
Are you Eli Manning
Who are you wearing a jersey that says you are
Yeah that's your fault
I've heard variations of that it opened
Is closed
You need
Well
I would I know why you're doing it but I would
I would caution you to resist the urge
To boo him
Cuz we might miss some of this
Securing the Crickets in the route you know I don't
I think they were like
How big is the second clip with something he said there was
I meant move. That was my favorite thing that's ever happened
Get to this isn't
Eclipse or anything
Analyze
Still waiting for someone to be charged with a crime
I don't want nobody to speak Spanish
I thought you when you have a translation underneath
In Spanish
Did you know that Kenny G and mr. G were related
I don't know who Mr Gs is a local New York celebrity
Those jokes crime one is like
Alright I guess
For something like if you're you know you just need to
The pad.
Throwing that in somewhere as like a
I need to I need to Pivot or whatever to come from
Because he also has a
Retarded videos that he's put out these Channel
Or hate crime is like a distinction that doesn't deserve to be involved
I don't want to say that he ignores the idea that people of
Target
Proper position of like I am a lawyer
Videos
You shouldn't be charging
Charging them
With a crime
And then him
Open Mic settings
He's doing real
Absolutely
That's f***** up
Many of these sound like premise that friend of the show Mike Wiley would throw away
I would even
Put it on one of those notecards nursefinder
Beautiful
Did Carly ever find out who was so vain
Bruce Springsteen ever find out who was Dancing in the Dark
Did
The Clapton ever figure out who shot this year
Whose tears worth it
No they weren't
Okay
Do you need a page-one rewrite up app
Uncle Joey
An interesting
April, could pull off.
Like you would have to be someone who's like
Deeply absurd
Ridiculously deadpan
Yes
But I could work
In a certain
Because
Your character would almost have to also be like
Kind of stupid
The joke is about you it's not about what
Is f****** stupid
But even I'd like that still put that one in the middle
Tell me exactly what I'm supposed to do to keep a video diary
Whatever I'm supposed to do when I use Activia
That's all I'm going to say
Whatever happened to Esteban
That was
Blockbuster
I think he's referring to bowel movement
Was Jamie Lee Curtis doing the whole you'll s*** right
But not because
I think it's funny but just because like I had Dyke
I heated
You're broken.
Little funny
Just like I can't fight it anymore
You know like if you had an open mic.
2:00
It also cuz you flashes on screen two pics arrested like he did look silly
I used to run an open mic
And my favorite comedian
Never got a laugh from the crowd
I could not
Stop live
Terrible terrible jokes
And the crowd would do nothing and then turn and look back at me laughing like
Who the f*** are you
What are you doing
Like that's a hundred percent difference
I actually enjoy it on that same level right now where is Esteban.
Alone
Kind of
Kind of funny as an observation
I'm not
You're talking about someone who's very good but isn't
Connecting with an audio
Complete up
Nevermind
If it wasn't lying
Now let's get back
How do they show traffic report on TV
By the time you get home and it's all change
Is it drive you crazy
911 call
Are the person calling a screaming frantic at the cops hair
Esoteric
Sword
Are you wearing shoes
I think if you had a better performance
Could work
Comic
Workout 1000 tops
I think that 911 calls
Myconnect
It sounds familiar
The kernel of what you can work with you need a better act out you need a better question than are you wearing
Specifically
Be better
Something there
Words start with that one
Work with that one
I'll give him I'll give you to pull that off
Now that's true
Open mic
Woodbine
When did you last eat
I need the I need to go back cuz when did you last eat was still a continuation of the 911 show that was a joke
Because if that was just a complete non-sequitur is still just a part of the 9/11
Done that joke
Snarled
Couldn't
I mean it has to work off this
And then you ask
Well
Is he wearing a
Kimono or something something along those
The more I think about it the more I actually don't take it
Can work
Because if you do that like what are you doing
The swordplay
Wordplay
Is he wearing a cleansing mask
There's no punch there around
Like what's your sign
Hitting on you
Express temp service
Concern I guess I'm
911 operator
But like
I don't know
Yo tengo
Yes that does that
The number of other directions.
Weird joke.
Cashews
When did you last eat
Was Marie Langston really the unknown comic
I didn't realize I thought it was another
Yeah but I guess I would say that
Atomic or whatever
You keep that is the third one
The first two are bad
You keep the unknown, cuz the third one making a normal make it a normal
Really specific
Is no good the first question
Close to it a 911
Are your windows
Or something like that
Sure
Something like that
We spent way too much time on this year
100 *
This is horrible
One day
I want to see a computer screen that looks like the ones they always showing the movie
Another one
The older man who actually think
Andy Rooney Martin Scorsese Spanish moss
What is a change of perception
I just left because I'm tired of deconstructing taking his jokes
Across-the-board
The comic books
Lovers theme song to give you like
3 funny
Everyone
Nothing Landon not in the room not in this room that would never fly
Anyway
Anywhere
Anytime baby
Maybe
Couple decades back
Was King Magic
Maybe
Be the funniest guy in the world
It's possible
So it's ironic
Tumi
But he just did
Boring
Portable attempted show comics
No not okay
Boring
Boring Hall of Fame
Or interest level
What's the weather
His picture is listed in the dictionary
Whatever
Sex act in detail
A little spicy for the Lionel report
Just say the word
So Chuck Todd
Text
Red Roof barely retained his seat
Harry Reid
Man who makes my skin crawl when he speaks deliveries
Ben Stein
Who's
Something
He was a Nixon
Ferris Bueller's Day Off also
Circle books that how to destroy your life book
Also be
Terrible terrible
Yeah I know he's very
The trajectory of his career like
Speechwriter for Nixon
A game show host
I think you just
Referring to
Dumb
Kind of purpose
There's a bit of a
It's an affectation
Ardex nominee the poster child for mandatory sterilization does Android
Who's the funniest stillbirth I give you carrots up
I would rather drink bleach or liquor hospital for listening
What year is this
Vegas
I thought we circled around to like a begrudging respect
4 Carrot Top right
Who was the head of the board
We got carrots
Chairman of the board
How's that board spell bottle
Text the secretary of the department
Who makes me feel anything but Napolitano
Glass the pizzazz of a soap dish
She couldn't lure me out of a burning building now
Stultifying NBC's ex-fbi
Looks like you survived
Profile suspect after they've been arrested
Brilliant
Text Harper.
The Kardashians
Anything of worth
Ever a complete
And total waste of skin finally
The granddaddy of them all the Big Kahuna
Amanda redefined the outer limits of sheer heart-stopping boring I'll give you Alan Greene
German play in heaping Mass
Black hole
And are they are if I left one out
Email me
Quick look like The Grudge
Boring
Categorically not boring
A criminal profiler
Alan Greenspan
He's ahead of the fuc
Federal Reserve
Play saxophone
That is not boring
Fascinating
Irrelevant characters
I'm going to go right back
Orchestra
He is wondering where that's about it
That's not boring
Man
It's just to have a conversation with you
Yourself
Not boring
They don't have a magnetic
Personality
Held against them and in any kind of
Successful
When they're not entertainers
Like someone like
Carrie read or whatever like
I'm not being entertaining to you is not his job
The Kardashians whether you want to call them and all that stuff
There's might be some coded
Possibly
They're not boring
Is entertainers
I don't know I don't
Probably
Don't like I said I think we circled
Live mostly
Super into that
But I don't know the parody of Carrot Top more than I actually know Carrot Tops cereal
Open
Universally they're like
+ 2
She kills from start
To finish it on your head
Has really good writers
I don't know how I feel about it
Generous synonym
And in front of the actual crowd
Whatever you want
Take that away from him
He's boring
I might be bored
Performances
Miss attributing a quote making me read hundreds of pages of a book
I'm not a good barometer I wouldn't get on PIX11 yell at people for being bored
I know that my radar is off it's yours Idol
So is yours everybody's hero and they're on
So what I would do
Describe
Orange
Lukewarm
So far
Turn this off right now
Go to another
How to talk about something
The Unofficial
Is their belief system in this might be motivated
The organization Consortium
Global politics
Changed
Just a green
What day was it here
Isn't composer
What
What is it
Google
They just heard anyone
Shibboleth like a war on terror
Provides a background where you can superimpose why then
Distortions on
A seemingly innocuous veneer of legitimacy people
But if you're interested
It's a U1 non-binding plan that's been around
The report entitled the first Global Revolution published in 1991 listen to this picture
Don't tell your friend
Is searching for a new enemy to United
We came up with the idea that pollution
Global warming water shortage
Would fit
Here's my big toe
Dear someone bringing up of that first of all
It's like 350 pages I bet you haven't
That's my first
Is when you bring up
The club of Rome
Because if they say yes
Then I know that they're an intentional liar
The context of that quote
If you use that quote as to say that these people made up the idea of climate change
Then you don't hear you're either intentionally
Or you don't know what you're
We talked about this a bunch of times
Absolutely like a mark
Propaganda
Just to demonstrate that he has a lot of
Of the similar
Like even though we at we laugh a lot and yeah still laughable
Even back in this PIX11
Yeah
Man
All I could think of
Where is Esther
Who knows
Here's a clip
From 2010
Where
Lionel talking about
You know
Make my skin crawl
Winsted cause my soul to Chase
My mispronunciation
And you know they drive you nuts
What start with the granddaddy of them all
Irregardless
Consummate double negative that is known by all except the grammatically
Next time you hear irregardless
Try this
The regarding your misuse of the word or
The regarding the matter at hand
They won't get it
Welcome to my world
Call here just to amuse me
Famous by President John F Kennedy inaugural address
Do later corrected
That's not
What's your country can do for you
Ask what you can do
Pure Country
Language
The past tense of sting which
Is vinaigrette
Vinaigrette
Denoting the diminutive form of vinegar
Then there's
Supposably
Which is able to be supposed
Fingernails on a chalkboard
Yes
Ready Coddington
Bush 43 mazes word famous
Bush supporters
Almost unanimously Jordan was
Well Jimmy Carter said to do
Well that changes everything
So
Great
Yeah so he's working he's only six years past one nuclear or nuclear nuclear app
You still mad about it
So
For PIX11
3 minutes
Time frame
Take over all this time Andy Rooney spot
YouTube archives
Most of the mispronunciation
Irregardless
You bet
So you noticed that around
You stopped appearing in a
At that time his videos no longer have a time limit
So he can just go as long as he want
Where are you know
He gets fired or it just isn't doing these
TV reports
Goes crazy
You still
Let me just say that this is one of the First videos that he puts out after
Deleted the studio
Mispronounced words it's a hobby of mine and I think I'm not the only one
Who's this
Incredible Delight in finding
Fault
Those people who destroy
Confused
Mispronounce misunderstand Miss state
Power
Big
Bigot
King George
That was
Nuclear
Nuclear pertaining to a new fuel
What are you doing
It was called a check
C a c o e p y
What it was in correct pronunciation of Nevada
PIX11
Word
If I put on
Farfegnugen
Pronounce the word
Somehow
Chief
Transposition
Of letters
Foliage
Spoilage
Calvary
Weird
Huge
Mispronunciation perhaps
If you're talking about the wrong
Concept pronunciation is dependent upon that what you mean
Ataturk
Editor
Realtor
Versus realtor
Jeweler
Or jewelry versus
Jewelry
Again little transposition
Basically
Perhaps because of my
So I was born
Feces
Goodbye
I couldn't care less
We must speak
Is I couldn't care less
What's the point I couldn't care less
That Germany who won the world
Couldn't care less
Well
Supposably
Supposedly supposedly
To be supposed
Which I don't think is what people
So does this one every three months or so
My God
Supposedly supposed
Zicam
Keep that clip in
Is to demonstrate
Without a time limit
Without
F******
So bad
As long as he wants
You just instead of having like
For synonyms
Yep yep like what
You got any more than that and you ruined
I always think about you like the idea of
His own in control of his own thing
He's like
Without
And management
The idea that there was a program director who was telling him
Just shut up about that
Exact created the essential
Where is Carrick
Disabled
Tubi
Good
Or at least
Entertaining
I cannot come off like a
F*** it like
Horrible dick
In the same way Detention of Lionel
The people at the desk
He has this
And that seemed so I'm bringing him on without those
Traffic
So
Too much of his post
PIX11
But I want to leave this
Disabled
Does
Have some bad idea
Weather
Project
Club
Really stupid ideas
Qanon guy now would ya
Stupid as hell
But I would
Doing him a disservice if I didn't at least tip my cap to him
Transgendered
In lgbtq
I'm sexuality and gender
Destroy the absolute
Human sex
Necessary
It's all gray and there are more than Fifty Shades of Grey
First sexual
If you think the Spectrum administrative
Sexual preference
Is physical mental emotional
Spiritual communion
This is particle physics showings for multiple dimensions
Sexual
No
Inter-gender
Assume arguing the doctor and she tells you
I'm not doing for you
You're a woman
You think your genital accoutrement make you a man or woman
Seriously
What you feel how you
Sing yourself
Even your shoes your walkie-talkie your likes dislikes your voice
Genitals don't determine that
It's your internal gender identity your head your brain the little voice that gives you
The go-ahead to be
This is been going on
Tuesday 1 so here is it
If everything is on a continuum
As I most respectfully submit
What is real and the truth and actual in
Are they
How long are you are
If we decided lard
When did question
That's the problem
This one. Not allowed to marry or Gator be with whom they want her
Go to the restroom they want Dora
Take to the prom movie
FATZ
It's not there
It's Society with a hang up
Relax take it easy
And you passes on the phone
So,
Attitude
Crazy
What's what the f*** what the f***
On the right tip
Unseasonable
Characteristics
It's pretty wild
2010 on
New York television
He's up there espousing
Most aggressive people
I wonder if you still forgot
I wonder if she still believes
Because like
The Alex Jones
Qanon world
Like do you think this tolerance
These people don't have
Problem
Yeah if you have a problem with them
I'll be good
I can't imagine that being
Still
Apart of
He's on a real good
Trend
Wayback
Homosexual rights
Lgbtq
Seawright
Consistently
It's it's weird
It's really weird
Who you just assumed
Did leave these things but he does
Because it's like
You do get
Should have to
Realize how interconnect
With so many of the things that you believe in the wrong
Ynobe
You can't
Cognitive dissonance
Maybe maybe
Like there's a lot of things that I see
Steve
Like he has a lot of videos about like talking about how you
Punish people for bullying
That's a horrible bully
Bright like the idea
You shouldn't
Illegal to insult somebody videos
Consistency
That with his ideas about free
Tubi
Chipotle
He's coming from now
It's weird weird cat
And I think
When you add the
Uncle of like his
Later career Intuit
But he's weird enough
Just look at PIX11
Yeah that's
You can
Have both trender right
And cute
I think that you could probably make a you could probably find a way to make
Make it work just because cuso4
The culture of it
Is very
On the right
Conservative
It's very
You know like if it's the sort of thing
Except like Trump
People being in the military
But I don't know how you square that I can't imagine but I don't know I don't know enough to say
His newer videos
Boring and I theme song
3 hours long
University sororities
Sources of
Supposably that's how it's supposed to be for not so exposed
Peace out
You have to bring this to the end
Food stamps
Call back in the fat
I salute you
Wow
Have a great day
What happened
Season X
So don't bite off more than you can
Chinchou
Even the devil wouldn't do
When you let it all go
I'm just going to go around I'm just going to go around looking for
Fiat
Video for Toby Keith
What happened
And a f****** about
And I just always loved
Ideas
Chorus
There's things down here the devil
Is just about people having
Really should have done something
F***** up
True
Active self into a devil do
I mean
Right
Provide
Food and Health Care for the poor
Yeah but see that doesn't work
Cuz you
About providing food
Yeah I really I mean I guess it's probably or
How it bothers me
Hobbit version
Eldritch Horrors
That would have been great
You can't even really kind of
You can really taste lately this guy banging his wife
Before that. Com
Jordan
What else do we
Facebook right
Describe to the whole thing
I mean like
Progressive
Stuff like
It really does feel like this is leading
To death
The net is a Megan
I don't know
I feel like it's a dangerous
Trend
And Lionel is a part of perpetuating
Sole ownership
Any deaths
It might come out a few or not
But in honor of his Progressive stance
Trucking hockey comedy
I must say that Lionel
Has never killed
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color