Hey everybody dan here just wanted to say hello and give you all a little bit of it true
Confusing
Based on the fact that this episode a couple weeks back
So there's something that may sound a little bit
Like for instance episode I say that I just signed a lease
When I at the point that we are.
Zipso comes out I've already moved
This new apartment
And also Jordan makes referee
Prince to the idea that we just
I recorded a emotional
I'm at now I have foisted this episode 35 to listen to
Upon him
And that is because we recorded this right after we recorded the episode that came out
Where we talked about Alex Jones is coverage of the Christchurch shooting
Idris healing
Damn so he's still reeling from that a little bit
As we jump into this
Episode
For a long time now I've been getting messages from listeners
Reached out
Express that they would like for us to cover Stefan molyneux
I'd like us to take a look at our thoughts
Watch the number of his videos and
Most of the time by I don't find them
To be something I really
I have much interest
Been covering
I think a lot of people who do shows that are slightly different focused than us have done
Great pointing out of
Things that are wrong with his world
There's a lot of coverage
You can find a vet service stuff
But I did think there was
That speak to me and I thought that it would be something
That snow was worth our time
Episode
Here here
There was a part of me that felt that this would be the beginning of a longer series
About him that may be forthcoming in the future at some point
It's an open question at this point but for now we have this episode here
That I hope you enjoy
With the who-knows-what Kubiak
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color
George
Whose last time you signed a lease finally got it all taken care of it like to thank everyone for their thoughts
Some prayers and concerns
Have been not real Hasselbeck
I will be I will be
Something that I can make it through
Keystaff
You know our recording
Bedroom
One-bedroom Studios
That sort of
I don't know over a decade
Assertive have kind of space
Experience
I'm excited for that
You know what I just realized
Interesting turn of events
I have lived in this building before
Laundry room
Is the quarter machines there
Grocery store
The customer service area
Get a roll of quarters so far ahead
I've been on top of that
It's nice
I just
Girlfriend
First time in my life
Beautiful
Apartments
Unessential
I don't like the rest of this apartment and honestly I fix the washer and dryer
Too much space you know
Variables
Limit other parts
Very much
Support of our listeners
People who signed up
First to give a shout out to
Do some new donors
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Richard
Thank you so much
You're now technically
Someone sodomites
I don't want
Just Sports
Goodnight
Appreciate it very much
The world
And instead of giving shoutouts to people who do donate we just finally got
Could never imagine doing that sort of shity
Or just anybody who we are showing you're not paying us
Fuc yourself
Review
Caribou
It's the van molyneux
Look at it this way
Bring it up the wackiness shirt
Evil monsters
Really struggled
What to do about this
Like requests from people to like
Hey you guys should cover Stefan molyneux
I'm aware of part of the internet
Lives and thrives
How do you solve a problem like Maria
Write absolutely to talk about
That's one of the things that kind of works in his favor
Is there anybody who wants to be like problem with this guy
Hours later you still haven't of what makes
Is Joe and what he does
So incredibly dangerous
To be honest I do not know anything
I've seen people screenshotted
Tweets or something and it's like
Tamia
Who's trying to be provocative
This is
Little bit of that going on with him
The criticism that I have for him
I have to wait. She is just outside of the scope of what I can
Today but
As we begin
I can't give you a little bit of information
Number one
He's bald
Okay I am out that's alright
Beneath the surface look
Stefan molyneux
Cover in a single episode
In reality it was outside of the framework of an in-depth
Week-long series
Do that because I fear it's dreadfully boring
Resisted covering Stefan molyneux because of stories I've heard that he's super litigious and really interested
People who uses contacts
I'm not willing to let the fear of that possibility stop me from covering someone I see in the white
Media
I've reviewed irrelevant Fair
Use laws and everything on this episode
Criticizing
Providing commentary in the clear
What compelled me to make this change my position
About
To cover him to be like we got to do this
Is that in December 2018 he released a mini documentaries
That should scare the s*** out of any
Thinking person
In the world
We'll get to that in a little bit
Cuz you don't know anything about
Self-described philosopher
Messages to YouTube channel and his internet radio show domain radio
Okay so I don't know you might have
First of all molyneux isn't real
History from McGill University Masters in history from the University of Toronto
Degrees in philosophy
I guess you could have been a philosophy minor but so was I and you don't see me doing the six-part series on philosophy 101
Like the trial of Socrates
Damn damn damn
Do you think the original Plaza
Original original
Okay
Go to the philosophy it was easier back then
People hadn't said a lot of those really basic already laying there
Early philosophers didn't on the vine
Outside
Important things about it like philosophy education is
Like the history of these ideas
Is and stuff like that
And I didn't exist
Tradition of philosophy
There's a real dangerous ideas
The background of all of them as well
That is a lazy and bad philosopher
Uses words that sound smart to dump
Attempt
What's use inference to make arguments or diagram a sentence
High school debate clubs and teams
Which should come as a surprise to Noah
I've said it once and I will say it again the only people who stay are pathological
A deranged psychopath
To feel that they can train themselves
Do use language of the weapon
I would not not his school's valedictorian
You know I would
Painting
Literally debate
With such a broad brush
Without logic philosophy is
Everybody who enjoys Debate Club and stuff like that
They're all the same person
It is one of these
One of the biases that I've had in my at my stereotype
And I have never been wrong anytime I've met somebody who's like
Called Caribou systems in 1990
T5000
A listener of the show is written
Difficult access
Opera $800,000 for his share of the business
It took 18 months off work to write a book
Revolution
Which was self-published on December 9th
Amazon
1099 dollars
So I'm going to have to pass
First editions of like
Emily Dickinson that are cheaper than
Oh I feel like I was attacked
What's the number of books over the years of titles like the Gods
The art of the argument Western Civilization
And Aunt Ruth
Yeah
Because harpercollins and penguin books are run by Dirty collectivist
He's afraid of a note
Letters that would come from in trying to actually get anyone
Publicist literary agent
Is daunting
The temp is grown into a full-fledged
He has books videos podcast podcast behind paywalls
Process
Of new recruit
Accounts that I've been able to find people who have left freedomain radio
Feature the same point
When you get out of a libertarian anarcho-capitalist
And discussion
But it's
Remember the community who experienced
Refusal to accept criticism
Is narcissism grow is the show got more popular
80 clear projection about emotional issues relations
As the main driver of that chain
Why doesn't sound like any call later I've ever
Now I need to tell you about the
The documentary
Documentary called a philosopher in Poland
For Houston
Experience. Countries 100th anniversary parade
What he actually does is something quite different
Okay
Now that
It's for a documentary
Seems kind of
Fun and joyful
Nation celebrate 800
Yeah
And they would have
Positive way of viewing
Sure
Nations do batshit that happens
But at the end of the day we're all the same
Taken as a whole
Is profoundly f*****
It is not about going
March
Cruel indoctrination
Absolutely
Dyke
Rear demonstration of a man coming to terms
With being a white nationalist
100-year anniversary of the Third Reich
Restart the documentary
To learn about
Diversity of Europe is always
Pan-european family history from Ireland to England
And my family history bleeds Eastwood
Can I find Poland
Incredibly fascinating
My notebooks. Question that I feel like
Until I get some answers how is Poland
Able to preserve its culture and its religiosity and its history so passionately
Is it constantly refer to in the mainstream media press as
Opel phrases
That it's not
I'm an empiricist I always want to get the fruit
It is all true
I totally get it because every part of that is a red flag
The true diversity of Europe
You like a version
You also come to the idea
Ultra-nationalist
The documentary itself you already know good
God damn well he's going to make peace with those things
Wait
I love those
Xenophobic
You know what I say
Probably good
Turn all the stuff that's really apply here as we go along
I think one of the major reasons
Is it when he went to Poland
No one yelled at him
Like they like they generally to in his daily life
They love me and I bet it's totally not because
Here is him discussing that just a couple minutes
Here's something else we did which I'm telling you my friends would be impossible
To do any other place I've ever spoken
And that is
We put out a request for anybody who wanted to come by and chat
Three social media open to the world
Could have done this in Canada could have done this in America
Australia New Zealand
So
Meetup
Nice little town hall
Yeah okay
Maybe a bad example parallel but like
You can say the n-word at a Klan meeting and no one's going to yell at you
You understand that's true different circumstances you can do different things that are unacceptable another place
Right
Xenophobic ultra-nationalist
You get yelled at
In other places
Hate those ideas
Eliza has he is polishing
I believe that's his
Main goal in life right
And share ideas
It's good to share ride
Town Hall in Sharon
Different races are variable in quality
Pushback from people
Most places
The address online
For this Meetup
He describes where he goes
Let me show some footage
Is at a bar
Describes
Discuss
International
Hahaha
Place
Where this guy headlines
Revolutionary ideas
To be discussed
People twerking
You know they're just objectivist
People like that can come together and have these ideas and the great
It's in the basement
Headquarters
In Polish
These not recur reading are a space
Call the freedom Lounge
Quote the first right formation Center in Warsaw
The idea of a place to organize right-wing politics
So they can talk about it without
I'm more concerned about the fact that the founders of this Lounge
The right-wing formation Center
This is a place where rationalist objectivist
Can come to discuss ideas
That is an act
Whitewashing intention
Look at it
Discussion loving polish Patriot
It was funded entirely by the Warsaw enterprising
I think list
Demography
Is one of the two primary areas of enter
Warsaw Enterprise Institute webpage
The Warsaw Enterprise Institute
It was created with conservative and free-market youth in mind
A place where youth organizations will be able to organize their events for you
Use the in-house television Studio to develop their professional careers as well as for socializing an Entertainer
The freedom Lounge is part of a strategy being employed by the Wei
To facilitate propaganda and social recruitment towards hall right ideas
This isn't some cool coffee house being full of revolutionary thinker
It's a well-funded hard rights
Think Tank created
Space
We're fascism
Confessor
Which
Explain to me
How what he said
Makes sense
Like whenever he's like
Xenophobic
Fascist
That is a meaningless sentiment unless you are a person
Color or something along those lines
Coming into a place where with a fashion
Everyone in that bar is
Tiger documentary
That was the moment I read one of Stefan molyneux tweet
Heavily implied
A lot of different
Would be shocked if he's met a black person
That's Wei funded organize and run
Far-right
Politics formation Center
Please work
Really cool kids who like a
Market get together in
Likes discussing the free market no idea
Barone's
TV
The pack
I'm sure someone exist in that mold but it's kind of comical
Imagine.
I believe was the original working title
Narrative
He give this speech
What is shock
Here is his response to it afterwards
He's just so amazing
What's the well
We were in a glass-enclosed area face
Talking about philosophical ideas
No fear
Crazy people who want to shoot us
All the other things that have happened
Other places like Ghana
Experience also we talked about ideas all night
Without anyone
Normal or
Clouds intellectual
Discussions in the Westin
Politics of sassy
Is wonderful to have that so
So wonderful
Face of just wonder
Because
There's no way that it
Because it looks really following this
No fear of crazy
People who might send bomb threats are others
Bombs with minorities
Well
Actually talking about his last like bomb threats in
Fearing for his
Really more talkin about
Disrupt
Like if I were to go to some college campus in the United States
Give a speech I will get that Milo treatment
F*** you
Assistant
Everybody was concerned
Or concerns for them out or repressed to a level where it never
The conversation about
Human rights
That just doesn't come up
You discussing meeting someone
This Bar
This is the only place where I'm going to make a leap of logic
That is maybe irresponsible
But I think I know who it is
I'm not entirely sure but I
I think I know who it if you were making a leap of faith I would say it was
It is
I met a man
In the freedom bar
To the man who was organizing the entire
Now they were facing
Opposition
WFAN.
The matter Wausau
Cancel the entire Market to dancing timer
They were engaged
Any significant legal battle
Try and get the mic back on
So he meets this guy at
Was canceled
Which will get into in a little bit
That's a big first question before you end NES
And their culture back
The mayor of Warsaw
Cancel the March
Here is why the mayor of Warsaw
He's talking about
It is one of the only other people who interviewed in this documentary
This in-between I believe this guy
Whose name is Lucas worth
Here is a little bit of his
Estefan
Liberal
It's like
In Poland
The. Of collectivism during the year
. between like sayings
When they say these words
These were
Preschool
Remember that 2015
Who is a person who
The in-between that connects upon molyneux with
The guy who
We'll talk about the next clip
Sure this guy whether or not
Whoever them between kind of
This guy is named Lucas Ortega
If you Google him you'll find it complice photographer
Which is great
But doesn't really explain his involvement in this documentary
To understand
You have to go past the
First page of search
That stuff
To do if you do you find a really crazy coincidence that Lucas wore chica is one of the primary writers for the
The people who built the freedom Harley-Davidson chatterley ER
On January 1st 2019 published
Amounted to Liberal indoctrination of school kids
He discusses a textbook passage about a pyramid
That describes different levels
The lowest floor of the pyramid is verbal acceptance
Which is absurd
Are we obliged to everything we do not like
It looks like it because this layer receive
Exclusion language
Parentheses out-of-focus
Category arbitrarily interpreted by The Lacs
Parenthetically
We can't even gossip
And even making malicious jokes
According to all ports
All these behaviors lead to violence
While the top of the pyramid is extermination
So to put in a nutshell maliciously joking with a friend I'm aiming for his extermination
No
He's making a
Dumb
RAR all of your pictures
Hoods
Culture battle
We hear from Alex Jones
These
Making younger people aware of the consequences
Directions
That sort of thing is to indoctrinate exempt
To be all about that I don't like
Lucas wrote
You start to see the picture
Coming into
There's there's
The beginning of a
Pretty solid pictures
Dismissive the dangers of drunk driver
Alcohol
These the same
The same source of
Permeate
Enterprise Institute an organization
Incredibly hard right there fingerprints
All over this document
Or the fact
That they keep popping up all over the place
Poland
Makes me pretty suspicious that it's because he was told and not to mention
That's kind of feeling that I
The idea
This bar that he's as the place where we can have this
Free conversation
Is entirely funded by them
And run by them as a right-wing formation Center
One of these very few people interviews
Photographer
Outside of him being a pundit for the Warsaw Enterprise Institute
Is just a photographer
I don't know why he's in the documentary
Wish you hell is this wonderful
You might want to give people a little bit of history about who started
We were in Austin
There's no point
If your perception of this is a heroic
Important
Free Speech Wonder
The world
Here in Warsaw.
It would behoove you really
It would be an ugly
Thing to just say like
And thank God the Warsaw Enterprise
In your world
They are nothing but unless you recognize
Stephon
Recognizing
How's are all over this documentary
Would make
This is 100% a propaganda
To the Prager University haha
Goodbye
You can stop right there
Yeah
So I don't know if Lucas is the guy who connected
Did Stephon with
This guy is going to talk to
Who's trying to get
The Martian running in earnest
HVAC guy
And
Start tomorrow
True the Center of Warsaw
From the bridge and the March
National
Devon
The land of what is March's going
To be about
That's all good
1st March
Southwest
And then Southeast
Northeast
And then Northwest
And then we go back down north south
And then Southwest
Domingo
Over
Northwest
And then Southwest and then we March back up
North
Are used
Selfie
And then go back down one more time
It one more time straight
Can do this pretty much
I think
You know what I got
Bosa
The primary interview subjects
Documentary
He's credited organizer anniversary March
Interesting
Ser
Which is pretty easy and free simple f****** for someone to make
He's only got more right-wing as his career has gone on
He's currently a member of the national movement party
The party that only came into existence
Open 2013
Has been a force of hyper nationalism and xenophobia ever since
With a little dash of LGB
Folk don't deserve rights thrown in for good measure
They trace their roots to quote
Active before World War
Shifting Poland politics
To the extreme right
In recent years
Along with a couple of other parties that are silly
Or not surprisingly are also involved in organizing
Trace our history back
To anti-Semitism before World War
Yes
All right that's not a ring
I believe a little bit more into that a little bit later in the oven
No
The key in an interview with this known to talk about it
Android
Critical coverage of politician party
Brought up
Tracing his lineage all the way back to a World War
Uncool
Backwards just
Really uncool
And part of that is probably because
Office
He's done a good deal of work to democratic power
Andres Judah
Injustice 2
And refusing to give their rulings
Official state back
Is just a puppet of the real power of the Polish government
He's the leader of the law and Justice party
Which doodle was apart of
Until he got elected
Independence
It really still being under the sway of
Prison School
Hazing
Is a hore nationalists who aspires to assert
Complete government
Control over
Who controls the moral Revolution
You super bad news
And you had the party that elected Duda as well as their current Prime Minister in Poland
Bypass
But in reality
All indications are that they're actually getting the March
Motors Direct
If it's not a problem
Peterson stats innsky periodical against the Communist Party in the 80s
Put it this way
There are no longer checks and balances
The power the parliamentary system is dysfunction
The Constitutional Court in
Judiciary
Paralyzed
New laws passed by the parliament
The government is supposed to publish sentences
The Constitutional Court to the journal
For them to become legally effect
This is required by the Constitution
But the government by not printing
Paralyzed
The Constitutional Court which has been reduced
It's a very dangerous time
Because I'm That Kind of
Evil people are the first to realize that there are no longer consequences for their actions
In this vacuum in Poland
Fascist xenophobic group
Growing empowered
The very rapid pace
Since 2015 to be there to push back
Against the mob
This all came to a head of the Independence Day March 2017
The year before this documentary is shot
Which brings us to the reason why there isn't
Going to be in March this year
According to the mayor of Warsaw
There's a real reason
But here's what Kristoff bosox says
So there is no
Until we went to the court
Concord councils of the constellation
Always
It's not that far right March
National conservative
Tomorrow
Organized by Grassroots to write
Organization
Libertarian
Spencer rice people
Nationalists
Traditional Catholics
Monarcas
Walmart
National pride
Answer
That's something for important
Say anything
Is literally called
Okay remember the videos that came out 2017 dependence March in Polish
Horrifyingly large group of people
With some real f*****-up sign
Portable fan
Pure Poland
And refugees get out
It broke out all over the Martian
Buy a new station from Power
Tommy Robinson made the trip from the UK specifically to be there for that
August 8th March
Andy edel a language teacher in Poland describe the marches quotes 52,000 mostly football hooligan
People in Black Mask March behind large banners that read Islam equal Terror
And carried signs with slogans like white girls
The symbol of the National radical camp
An ultra-nationalist polish app National
Group active in the 19
Who Define themselves by their fascism
Anti-Semitism and elimination is
The world war
Their party was outlawed by the state back then
But now in 2017
If its independence date March
As you might imagine the objects of this work
F****** terrible
Marched alongside outright
Fascist
A celebration of national Independence
It's been characterized by people with
Text Amanda
The politicians are like I don't want to be okay with it
I don't want to be
Who are also racist
Colin Kaepernick doesn't have a job
Your word we use ours
Happy about that March Optics individuals that came out of it and people
That's really scary
That's
Strolled around the organizers like Christophe Bostock
Nationalism
President do decided to make his own independent
Kmart's to replace the
Organized
Hibernate
Specifically
Under threat of arrest
Tatoosh anality take
Replacements 2015 environment Poland
Worthy
The same thing happened in our country
Are fascists and Nazis
This is a large-scale problem in the world which is why has no surprise
Fascist also marched with signs that said God
Which is a reference to polish song
They were quoting the song
They're quoting Trump referencing the song in a speech that he gave in Poland
A few months prior
I just sent you the March was published in politico's European arm
It makes it very strange attempt to minimize the fascist
Nationalist of the fascist
This is really defensive guy trying to defend
March and he's starting with 10%
That's not a good sign 60,000 total people
Nothing
An argument that this is really about how the EU is desperate
The quote use the threat of fascist
As an excuse to push
For further centralization of bureaucracy
Sedation
Probably worth noting that that defense that article in Politico was written by
President of enterprise
I didn't want to pull because I knew this was coming because I did the same thing to you
Whenever I did my climate change episode
But
Everywhere
What's going on with this March
It got way out of hand
In 2017
This
And then they came up with the sanitized version
Is agreeable to everybody
The Nationalist still got to be apart of the March the government got to celebrate the 100th anniversary
Everyone got the
Come out in
And it didn't appear
Dear to be something so f***** up right
The year before right nobody screams killed the Jews everyone is like they were talking about the Blues
Any other
Thanks
Oh good work
He's really excited
Go to this
See that hear that
Without thinking
Part of why you're excited to go to this March
Did you know what happened to 27
It doesn't
I don't know how to encapsulate this other than
He saw the image of what was being reported in the 2017 March
So he comes to the 28th
With the idea of like
Is it as bad as everyone says
And obviously it's not going to be
Is bad
Because the government has stepped in and said we will arrest you
If you have racist and fascist
If the government didn't do
Do that
Control some of those aspects
So what you're seeing is actually the opposite of free speech
Being represented manifested here
And it's a trap
Because the van molyneux is going to
He's going to see the margins like everyone lies about them
Yeah yeah yeah yeah everyone is just so full of s***
The only reason of that
If that is the case is because of State
So
I don't know when he made the plan to go to this
But he knew
Before you made the
The plan to go to the March
That the government was going to
The clampdown on
Hate speech
Maybe
Orville worth
My supposition is also
You know it wouldn't have mattered it could have been a shitshow like it was in 2017
But he still would have made the same documentary
With a different.
Documentary
Call antifa colon
Turn into a victim narrative esposa Lake isn't this
White ethnostate wonderful
That's where we're going
People around
It's f*** out of here
Stefan molyneux claim videos
He's not really specific
And it's not
He thinks with his name is spelled in the Polish way which is
Nevermind
Give a s***
How exciting
Take Play Take Park
In this polish
When he's not pulling
He's not he's not involved
With their country at all
Express
So here
You're able
Celebrate
Beanpole
You're able to celebrate
And everything is survive
And everything it will account
In the future
Unironically
Without having to deferred other
People's feelings of a couches feelings other races feelings you can just celebrate
Who You Are
And where you are
I really wanted to
Like I could return to that brief window of my
With celebration
There before that she was talking about how when he was a younger man
There was that
You could have
And being in
So he's like now
Taste
Who's the Sun
Remember so romantic
Being proud of
B b
It's
Does what
Just what
Did she think what he just said
Because I feel like what he just said is you're allowed to celebrate
Like when he says without having to
To defer to other races
Is like wait
Do you mean without having to consider what other people think
.
Part of this nation
And you don't even have to think about how rude
Like I kind of what you just said right
As long as you have a
You don't have to be concerned about other
Races in what you're doing today
Right
Again it's important to note that this is the 28th
Which is operating with strict
Order from the government
This isn't free speech Haven is he wants
It's a March that exist
The full expectation
If you show up with your
Like I said earlier this is a very literal
Representation of repressive Cinemark
Studies
But it definitely helps
Create the visuals that you need
Name of the ultra-nationalist he's hanging out a really just super into Poland
Xenophobic
Right
And now the worst manipulative
Censoring speech
Present this place is a Bastion
In his next life we get to sponsored of wrestling with the idea that you
Collectivist
To a very serious
Individual
That's defined
But you can find probably a decade
He's worth of videos on his
I would say you should have taken down some of them and thankfully I've got copies of them
But there's so many things
From his career one of the biggest pizza
Obsession
Individual
Who is Severus
Why you when
Went to Poland
He starts to talk about how we wanted to challenge
Dualism
Whether or not there is
The possibility
Collective
And that's f***** up
Given what we know about the collective
But you hanging out with
Call boy
My individualism because
Individualist know that I am skeptical if not
We have people
That 2,500 years ago whoever can live alone
Britain
I've just kind of shattered something within me
Has arisen
Before and I can't tell you how that I have
I've never been to before
I think this clip is a perfect encapsulation of how big is he
In this clip Stephon claims that his long-standing position of being an individual
Shattered
By being around these people we're all marching in the same direction and are there for the same reason
That's bulshit
Have you ever been to the pride parade
How about the Puerto Rican Day Parade
Any of these parades that I've been to in Chicago that are equally moving
Engage with
What I need to do
Christopher consider one of his deepest held beliefs
Collective
All that took the shadow that was
Be walking around in a large Collective of only white
People that is all that is happening here in anyway
I was a
Rugged
And then
Collective
F*** you
What but I didn't I didn't want that to be thing
Any more than you do
But the moment he started saying like I've always been an individual
Is tonight's finally found a collective
Hey my head was screaming just
This is the same thing as Alex
Once he realizes why
Applications of
Rex 84
Slipping on his
Because those beliefs are conditional
Those things
People have built their entire
Careers personality
Philosophies
Whip as soon as they recognized
This works better for me
Yeah it's soon as that
Being absorbed in the whole of America
Whatever I want to be with my wife
Yeah
It's so sad it's such a
I argue
Dafont
Is that he's a lazy bad philosopher
Baby I will be at the collectors that they were the kind of collective
I would Super Bee ones that exclude people
Creeped out by afraid of her
So
I think in that last clip there you got the sense that
Stephon was about to cry
You kind of
I don't know if you could pick that up
You could definitely see some
In his like
I've never seen a collective
Bright starts crying
This point Unity disquiet fry
Iskcon resolution
Celebration without getting it
That I have put up to defend myself against criticism
Have Unity
Against criticism
It is an appalling thing to take away people's history
2 take away people's Pride
And it is an appalling thing to take away their Unity
Because I've never felt it
More stronger than I do today
Divided
We thought
Music
Kickback in a roll of the March
Shitol
Who name is
Career
Intention
I realize what my career is about now
About this
Like
It's not really
These things
To get to that place
I think it's just a realization
Look like
Alright let's just get real battle ready
I've been to the gay pride parade and I felt zero pride and I felt like I was being attacked but I go to the
Nationals parade and I realize the collectivism is great
Forget what
Super clearly a very specific
The footage that shows of the parade
In Poland
Like it is all white
But
I don't think that all of those people are
Or anything like that or out for the anniversary of their country
Parade in Warsaw
And everybody loves the f****** parade
Everybody who was in the previous
How to escape
The
The character of the March itself
Again
Not an indictment
People there or the city of Warsaw Poland even as a whole like it's not the people's
Sport there
There's something
Scary that's happening there
Yeah like when they showed me roll of the parade was it like fun parade
Flyers and stuff
I remember growing up I was
In the marching band
For the
Town parade
That we would always do them
Cycle March
And I remember
People throwing candy out there were floats
It's mostly just people walking with Polish flag
Yeah and some music and people singing
Patriotic songs and stuff like that
Becomes night
We're leaving to dance
Flyers
Carnival is the best
Really advanced
Then you don't understand how joyworks phone would say a little
But the
It's all just people with Polish
Which is
Only come with your red and white flag
Okay
Already got our first
Is he saying
I apologize
Let's call it
He is saying that
The people who have covered the parade in the
Have gotten
Because this parade that he's at
Currently
Does not reflect
The coverage from the
The previous parade
He is not admitting
Does not reflect at all the previous parade
The circumstances are entirely
You can have the white nationalist horrifying parades at the
Covered perfectly
Also have
Comb parade in
But they're not mutually
Exclusive
Express
Really is that
What was being talked about in the 2017
And all that stuff
It was just a bunch of collectivist coming in
Scoreboard
Cancel celebration of
Whatever
So at this point
Morebeer all the parade
Jennifer aydin
More
Heroic
Contemplatively
Estefan molyneux is it a graveyard
Start waxing
Poetic
About Poland
I already don't want to
We're not going to listen to
Because it's
Like it is
Whatever thing
You could be trying
To bring into the conversation
We know yeah that is
Suck a horrible time
Including the Polish
Like everybody did not have a good time
In World War II
Rhapsodic
About Poland in WWII
Yeah
Blue Point Beer
It really doesn't
He loves to whenever people critique him on Twitter and stuff like that
His stock response is always not an argument
Disinfected
Blowing hard in a foot
Graveyard
About why
Dislike
Is white nationalism that you
Coming to accept
That's not an orca
Not a crying breakdown
His ideas
Is philosophy
He's mine
Particularly about the idea of collectivism
Being bad
Is there a benevolent Collective
Is there a good version
Collectivism
Have
I'm collectivism
A death with no redeeming characteristics
Pictures for me
It was a cloud with no Silver Line
It was a night without a door without a man
And
Almost like trying to
Square peg into a round hole
I have to face
Pathetic beautiful collectivism of the poles
And find figure
Cigarette into my mindset of collectivism
Ethan my definition of collective
Been found wanting
But I am an empiricist and
I also respect emotion
And if my emotions react positively
To the
Beauty
And strength
A Polish collectivism
I can't just dismiss that I can't just say well
That's just a silly throwback to Medieval tribalism
I speak Spanish
I bet stuff
Square
Publisher Steve
Right
Does everybody not
I don't understand how is it called
Because it's very clear that he is a pompous pretentious f*** who should shut the hell up I don't have any
Criticism
No that's that's very real
You talk some more about this
Benevolent Collective
Have to recognize
About
Is being surrounded by
That no one yelled at him when he had that show
Strong leader great treasure
Has been with house
A great treasure
Has been turned into a customer
And collectivism
That is beneficial
Bike racer
Compliant
Collectivism
If you drive app
Benevolent
You
Atomized
Then from there
Tribe the pier
There
I have
For the most part
Over the course of my career
Papa
Because you think
Collectivism
And therefore those who have organized themselves
Does lions have a great advantage
Skip
I lack
A community I like
Shut
The fuc
Being out here
With these wonderful people
Who are
Organizing and filming
And recording
Is it buried
So that's something interesting
To me because he has people who are organizing
There are other people
And I'll tell you that at the end
He has a credit
Feels like the credit
There's nobody mention
Credit
Who could have been
The camera people
There's only one
Title card
Ending credits
What is starring
Stefan molyneux
Right and the other one is
To the White
No it's all interviewed in the documentary
Breitbart writer
Cuz at Breitbart writer does talk about polish
Fusillade
Is the only person who doesn't
Do your on camera
He doesn't think the Warsaw
Probably
A handheld
So he doesn't listen
No credits for the people who are actually working on this week
Strike me as very suspicious
Employees
UEI
Don't walk credit well that the fingerprints will be here
That we brought you here
To do this propaganda documentary
Alright
And it doesn't necessarily
It's the dude
Tourism board is really influential with Stefan molyneux
Took you heard there
This benevolent
Wonderful been
Unofficial collectivism
Which is great benevolent the more I want to
Tribe
You have
He's talking about
Being in the studio is a solitary exercises
Just me and a camera
Back in the days
This videos you can find at the zoo
Car with a camera on him
Just driving to work
I got whatever
The Dragon
Alright I'm going to work
I'm on the way let me tell you about collect
He's always
Singular
Sting
It's always been
He's about
Next clip
It comes from him being an auntie so
F*** on some level
There is strength in numbers
There's strength
There's power
In the trunk
The enemy with faces
Empower and organize
Well Finance
Maybe they tricked me into fighting alone
So that I
And everyone
Would you please
Even from
You take any of the ideas out of
Goddamn boat
They tricked me to fighting alone
F****** cry for yourself your ass
This is so frustrating because it's like in your college philosophy
Puppy class could just have started a cult
If you try hard enough with an atom British accent
If you've ever been in college in a philosophy class
Bolognese f****** stupid
Pretty smart
It's just not the right kind of until the
Apparently positive things about awful
People
Able to analyze these ideas and come
Conclusion
He's smart in the way that he's able to
Package
He's smart and he's able to present these ideas
Astounding the less crazy than the X
Cruise
If you want to go back to that
There's there's definitely an
It's just dumb.
But in the next clip you back in the graveyard
Stalking in the graveyard
Clips a little bit longer
Listen to it
An accidental condemnation of what
He does
People he's around
Simself do
And their effect on the world
It was natural for us to hate each other why would so many
Woods
And fox required
Why would we need
From the black cheetah propaganda
Why would we need to constantly
Before
Just propaganda if it was natural
Come from
They come from the language we imbibe the language
The hatred
South
This group
Are your friends
Listen to language
At this point
A good end of the documentary
I'm so sorry for my career
I'm the one who's doing
These graves are the result of propaganda
Yep yep
Step further
Instead of just strength
Results are we the Baddies
I do not believe
I believe that we can live in much greater
That would be
We collected much credit
But to live in Greater peace
We must be very very careful
About the language
Describe
Our group other group
Common humanity and we must be taught
Disgrace
From language
Beef grades
Come from the seeds of hatred that is owed
Sophistry
Alright
The syllables of sophistry
Analysis is kind of like
Finger himself
People like Alex
He's doing it with
Vegan version
Do you like
No no no we're the ones who were right
Hugo Boss to insist on multiculturalism is the sowing the seeds of sophistry
Disgrace
Is that we used to talk about ourselves disagree with
Like if the Martin Luther King jr. speech was given by Strom Thurmond
You be like
So what you're really saying underneath all of this
Beautiful language
As long as the
So
Because we've been calling Stefan molyneux a white nationalist
And maybe that's on
Fair
It's not unfair because
We are free to call him
First of all
I've always been skeptical of the ideas
A white nationalism identitarianism
And white identity
However
I am interested
And I couldn't help but notice
That I can have
Peaceful
Free easy supplies and safe
Discussion
In what is essentially
Call White
Country
You just told real hard
No one yelled at me so white supremacy is f****** awesome
Call me names
Is that
White nationalism is good
Because
Nationalism is good
And we need to separate ourselves from
It should be for whites
Should be for blacks
And never the twain shall meet
Now
Hey historically
Maybe when they're are all white Nation
Could be
Could have something to do with why we don't do that anymore
As long as it's always for good
I think it's pretty much
I've been resisting
The ideas of white nationalism
But but but
I'm an empiricist
And that mean
Did the free exchange of ideas as possible as long as everyone is what what a f***
Level of
Terrible things
When you have a conclusion you want to get to
Working your way towards it
Because anybody who was an empiricist
Would consider alternative
Like I don't know
What if I was in Poland
For 2 days
Parade
And a bar that's run by a group
What if I'm only seeing what they want
What what if I'm not getting the full picture of what it's like to
What is IMO means
The
The the Warsaw
Diversion
Of what
They wouldn't accept
Does blindly in be like
Nationalism
Wheat
You're trying to justify that
There been so many examples of that where it's been.
Well-known writer and
China or wherever
Will bring them in and I'll have a tour guide
Castrating their entire thing so when they write the
Holy s*** it's overwhelmingly positive
Because they just showed him the version of Nazism
Broadcast
That word is satirical and comedic in nature
That minimize the idea of the Nazi
He's being evil
Talk about how like
I did
Know what was going on
Nazi collaborator
Said it was because of the
I don't think it's as extreme
Example
Yes absolutely
Situation
Political
And culturally
Going on
And he is
This one specific time
Coming up
Look at its campus
Coincidence
And the fact that you do
Bring it up at all
Like this is an interesting organization or anything like that
Now I think I think
How many.
Discard his
Ridiculous posturing
You cannot be in a
If you do not also true
We all
At the end of this right now
I think we all understand
This conclusion
Any
Conclusion
White nationalism is fuckingawesome
These people that are extreme
As evidenced by
But that still leaves
Question
News
Cry
That's weird
Why did Stefan molyneux cry at
That March
Because that's f***** up I don't know
Yeah but he's not like out
It is emotionally resonant
But he's not like Alex
He's not unhinged
Yeah Alex fix crying
Or even Doves Cry
Sometimes
That is not part of his present
That seems very strange
Yeah exactly
Describe what happened
In this next clip
Supposed
Or not guilty
And guilt
Has been so infused
Into
The hearts and minds of Europeans
A resilient strong
Culture that is resistant
Collectivism
It's something that moved me more than
I can probably ever
But I hope is encapsulated
In the footage
That you're seeing
In this documentary
It is
Is encapsulated
Yeah I mean you're totally right
Because that's what he cares
So f******
Is the worst
Mostly because everybody
White guilt
Is just a horribly profitable Vending
The people pound
In order to get resource
From
Lucky white male tax
I did something that should be enormously resist
Unless you down as to why it should be resisted
Look at toilet
Look at the glory the celebration Topeka
Everywhere
I did not see one drunk person I did not see one fist fight I did not see one crazy
Protester out there threatening violence
Because their ideas
That they don't agree with
What's not to love
About something like
For Jordan
Evriholder
Indictment of his capabilities in that Realm
He's a wonderful Utopia
You describing these things he's seen as being a result of
It's very clear
That's the premise
Those things only exist because of non-white
Yammy
Concrete versions of Azusa
Whatever
Michael
Ascribing cause
People around
Streets to be cleaner in no fight
Clean streets and no fight there's no history that would suggest otherwise.
Where he tells on himself
Is the
That's where he tells on himself a little bit
Define
Concrete terms
Right
As opposed to in empirical
Analysis
The streets are clean there weren't
Those are them
There is one
Whatever
The people are civilized
Dog whistle in the same way it be like every black person I saw
You know what you said
Right you know well what you f******
So even if he is right there
She's not right about
Do you have improved the causal connection but
Between the things you see in
And the fact that everyone there is
30 sloppy
Junior varsity level
Philosophy
If I've ever seen
That is not an argument
I suppose the only way
And I don't know why I'm somehow on the side of giving him the benefit of
As if
What he meant was he
Homogeneous
Like that's the only way that you could
Has more of an argument to stand on because
Because his argument because all of the people are like
Each other
In the same way
Right
Let's call it white.
Then if there was a
Let's call it miseducation
Rate and we know how well it is when
Spawn does all the time
They hide their bigotry
Electrolyzer
That's everything
He does
And the Philosopher's going to a hypothetical
All black country
Experience
You just wonderful
I think the same way
Is defending
White nationalism
Identitarian
Absolutely
Metaphor
Degree in history
Metaphors are really something
Veteran is this one's all right though it's about keeping the fire
You got you got to go get one by the fire
Existential crisis what are you going to do
Oh I don't know
The salamis
Holiness
Western European culture compared to
The seriousness of death
The Polish culture
Darkness
And something I will take
Take me to Mike hold on WhatsApp
Freedom
You say
To have a fire
You need to go and gather the firewood
You need to light the fire
And then my friends
You know what you need to do
Did he attend
Into the Woods
If I were to keep that fire alive and pass it down
To your children as your father's
Passed down to you
Is keeping that fire a lot
The Westin
The rest of Western Europe
Different about him
When the fire
History of your civilization
But it begins to diminish when it begins to die
There is a great temptation
Too close to that fire
And to stay close and too warm yourself in the dying Embers and fading calls event
Rather than go out
Into the woods to gather more
Wood
Repeat that fire and bring it to life
It is so easy to take that 5
Imagine that the fire is not something you need to protect and see but it's like the sun in front of its own accord gives you what you work
It's false
Headed to destruct
Fantasy to imagine that the fire will last
As long as you and your ancestors
Have wanted it and as long as you and your descendants draw breath
It's cleared the specifics that he's talking about but it is clear
Fitbit
Close
He's so emotional
Experiencing like he said it himself
I'm suspicious of white nationalism
But I'm an empiricist
And what I've seen
I had pretty cool
So if his conclusion comes to
The fire of freedom is really delicate
Woods are
Whatever the firewood
Whatever the fire itself
All of it is about
Preserve
In the best
Rephrase that
Your culture
White
Culture does not exist black
Yeah
Popular
And he totally is
80s
He has
Is
Turd polish version of
Every every
Presented so far
Variation
Of the
Whites are great
A different
Flowery length
Urinating thing for him
Duke
Because if you know what
Talking about
No matter how much flowery language
You're still trying to say the n word
You know like that's what you're really trying to do
Is it long and passionate speech about the Polish
Struggle in World War II
Fine
Lotta folks
In acknowledgment of what
Vanos
Duda doesn't come up by name at all the documentary
Injustice party comes up
Kristoff
Someone Envy National
Party
The fact that
UEI is so
Deeply involved in
Assertive
Justifying
The acts of the democratic Act
Of the government
AR
You know behind at least one of the interviews
He's doing and the bar
I just can't walk away
The documentary without
Looking at it
This is
Basis of
This is something that was playing
To Anixter
Yeah there's no way that
Would exist
It's so consistent
And the people who would be
Publishing articles
Politico
Justify
March
That became such a
Embarrassment
These National
Yeah
Overplaying your hand
Did the all of that one
Back to a single
Like I don't
The documentaries only an hour long
Like not like
It sounds like he talks to a wide array of people
Yeah
There's there's the interviews
Firefighter
There's the interviews there's him standing in the woods in the snow talk
Thursby parade self
Emotions on a train
And then there is
Tiger documentary
1 interview
With somebody
Marshmallow shooter
I'm the receiving
So much
Bigotry
There's a unified front
Seems less like a
Documentary and more like a propagate
You bet how to find MZ
Liberty is not constant is not a force of nature it is not a force of gravity it is not
The element of physics it is something that must be protected and maintained and kept
Every single generation
Poland
Remembrance what the rest of the West had forgotten
Which is that your freedom
Which type generation to Bill
The fires of Liberty that keep your civilization warm
Remember that
Difference
Between Poland and
Stephane has demonstrated
Is it everyone is why
Yeah it seems
Empiricist
Population
Napoleon is 100
I think it's the version of Holland
Yeah
Fundamental
Different from any other place
He was kept oyster.
In
White pepper
Protest white nationalist
And that is enough
For him
To say like
They are keeping the fire alive
These are the
It's insane
All the more so because
Man if I were the worst surprises
Scour the entire f****** country
To find any non-white person
Object
No matter the price
Sister whatever it is
What it doesn't
Couldn't even get one person to stand
In the background
Non-white
People that I could find
I'll say that there is a possibility way in the background
Anybody
That wasn't
Indifference
That is what change
Stefan molyneux
From being
You being like
Oh okay
Freedom could disappear
Herrera
You could tell from the sound effect
He could use an Editor to Pare down his
Federal Credit
Stephon a documentary after the entire Corpus of the work is done
But coming back on camera
And pleading with his audience
To give him more money
We can do more of his
That was just an act
He's realized that he doesn't want to stay in his Studio
There's a big world out there for him
But he needs them
To pay for it
Do you mean to call
To provide him the money
To be able to do
Incidentally in August of 2018
Stefan molyneux made another trip outside of his Studio
Hemet Lawrence trip to New Zealand
Speaking to
First attack
Is all entirely rooted in the ideas
The people like Stefan molyneux his maid career off of spreading
His mentality isn't new
But it's something
Made so much
Who is validated white terrorism
Excuses for Timothy
All the way down
The present day where we seen Alex Jones
Excuses for this terrorist Act
You making
The good idea
Hey
We talked about all the time
It's always important
Recognized
Ecosystem
Stefan molyneux comes on
The show comes on that much
But he has been
Fairly regular
For a while
In the same
Anti other
Yeah
The bigger picture of it
Anti
People ride
Possible
Not to be this
For himself
The world and declares himself
National
We've known
Spawn
We know
We've known for a while
And we've been criticizing you
For it
People have been criticizing him and say
Hades
You're a piece of s***
That's why he gets yelled at speaking engagement
In this Enclave that's very safe space
He's like oh my God
It's all white people
Fuckingawesome
Isn't this the best thing ever
He comes out
And he recognizes
And that means two things
No s*** you are
F*** you
How dare you
That people yell
When all the documentary
And say
I always was suspicious of white nationalism but I'm in a system
Pretty good stuff
How dare you
How dare you pretend
The people criticizing you didn't have a point
You were before you were ready to admit it
Not the best Wacky Wednesday
I mean we got plugs but I'm really trying to like
In my head
Episode
Struggling
Kill anybody
Teacher
Complaining about how all the
The parade 2017
He was a bunch of
The football hooligan
Twitter
You can download
Review all of those absolutely have already decided
Who is going to be
Language
Probably
Alex