Alex
Smart guys who are sitting here
And we're going to drink novelty Beverages and not talk about Alex Jones
Today necessarily also Alex Jones related
Welcome
Look personality
Dasani sparkling
Oh yeah
If you're a
Those tall things
Little bit
Feels good feels
Important I should tell you that Marty DeRosa filling in for George day is sponsored by Dasani
But
When you hand
First
Sprayed
And a lot of times with cuz of the parakeet novelty beverages I was pretty
Coconut
Yeah
With
Yeah your kiwi sure coconut
It's going to take
It has that risk for sure
I got screwed recently because I'm
I'm such a sucker for anything that seems like that's different
Yeah I bought a 12-pack
But it was sparkling water
Orange vanilla
I was like
I've never had a vanilla sparkling water is going to be crazy
And it was kind of gross
Bright pineapple
I'm so Jordan is still in Mexico
He is on vacation
That's what I heard
Instagram pic of him on the beach
But I trust him
I am so I could I you know
You & I we discussed
Something we wanted
Sure which was
Pro wrestler extraordinaire was injured
We talked about doing a episode of that's what they want you to think
Harold conspiracy theory podcast
And holding on to it for once he comes off the injured reserve
Just celebrate his return
To the WWE
Episode
He's back
At 8
He's a he's a bad boy now right
Even better than you
Sure
Can all over the place to Sky music
Do you think that the hugger is going to go going to go evil
Interesting predictions
About
Sort of I don't know how you feel
My relief
Not what it wants
Well this is one of the reasons why it's kind of difficult for us to get together
To do an episode of that's what they want you to think anymore
Ostensibly sat down and
We talked about some sort of
Conspiracy theory or paranormal type thing
I would research you would be like
The reality would always be disappointing behind the
The sort of fictional versions we have in our head
You never get
Any
Play finality any resolve
Never also
A lot of it is like
Well
If you break it down
And also
I feel like
Yeah I'm just
It's like it was all the nuke
Let's not
But people
I believe stuff the right
Anymore
The other thing too I think about the
Stuff
Is that like we now know where a lot of it is gone
You know like a lot of
SeaWorld have funneled to like really ugly online world
And becomes
And s*** like that
Those girls murder out of it Slender Man
Spaghetti
Weird
What are they called
Creepypasta Creepypasta
You're saying it wrong
I'm staying wrong s*** all the time
Creepypasta spaghetti from now on for me by the way
Itrade
Most of Mike
Conspiracy theory
Series for a mortgage
Gentle side of
Abandoned malls
Oh wow
That just have
Like maybe
All the flagship stores
Is it still lacked much
Church's Chicken or the church
I guess that makes sense though
That present
Canada
Yang gang
He's malls
More than
Amol
Haven't got no awareness of what
I've listened to that pitch I mean likes
Teach people skills
Lifelong learning
The fancy Mall
Northshore
Do you say up north
Cubs
And this mall
Was interesting.
They a lot of the stores
They had laughed like big stores
I made like a virtual
Reality play
Was gone
They replaced it with
Dispensary
Music
Play swear like
Concert stage
Your kids
Can go there and
Play
Rockstar
Sounds fun
That stuffy I watch instead
Yeah who killed him
It's probably better use of your time
To some extent as opposed to like you hiding under your covers
You too much.
My car blew up
Thanks board
And it caught on fire
It wasn't like that because
We were doing our conspiracy theory
The Lincoln Lodge in the show that week
I show up and you tell me what
Dan my car blew up
I got a quick
Look up Newark
My car blew up
I didn't have
Sort of rudeness to tell you what the time that I thought that was in second
You're an it sure
A lot of people
In it
Sucked into those sources.
To the Arctic
Wang
Wa
Wang Gang Asian
Asian long hair
Cool dude and he does a lot of
Remember enough
This guy post
Oral history of Fortune
Goof
I'm looking for
Cool stuff lately
It's so funny
Because I feel like the last
Different play yeah I think the last time we actually didn't
Restarting to Denver Airport
Oh yeah
Maybe more funded by
Various wrestlers have been on Infowars I have crushed your feelings about
Oh that hurt
Yeah and then
Bi-Rite woodmayr
Someone told me
Recently
I was just watching
I Mean Gene Okerlund shoot interview
Bressler
Or wrestling personality
Hotel room
Hey sister tight shot on there
And they take a picture
Deposition
I'm in the idea is that there
To telling the truth outside of characters
There was a a window
Early
Tended to
Or 2,000
Humana drug given drugs
Sleep through half of it
Just real f*****
Triple H
I mean
He's so Charming so funny
No no
Classic
He go to the Eugene
Not a big deal
Fellow Hall of Famer Drew
Somebody
Bono and
Cuz I just did a bike.
Didn't have all the facts invest
We asked you and you didn't
You didn't want to do the shower and then block them
So
In the research they done they were
Cute RV races
Annabelle
No Macho
High School
And they were doing the pledge
Allegiant
And there were
Parts of it
Topology
Dylan
There you go
Never happen
For me to find another wrestler who's been on Infowars
And it's just you know it's no good
Do you think they're shows that Jesse said no
I bet we could get it
I bet I bet we could get him I never Spark
The fun friendship with them then then passes away and then you write a book
Or I can drift
Say that he beat me up at a bar
Or I beat him up
Not entirely sure how that check out
Jesse Ventura
I don't know I can't really find another wrestler
So what I was thinking is like what about Professor Griff
Gosh that's no good
Sounds like Billy Corgan
Wrestling at the owner of the national wrestling Alliance
Cupboard that is well
It sounds like we are really up against a brick wall
I found something that blew my f****** mind
Yesterday I got to give a shout out to a couple people who are supporting
The show
And we really appreciate the first of all Mike down thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Diet
Name sound
Could be wrestlers
Everything about wrestling
But I do love a name
That sounds like
That's a wrestler
Because
I was I was
Sew-in Razor Ramon and
Diesel
Timer
They can't be
Diesel RZR
Character traits
Somebody was
And then find someone
Surreal memes
Scott Holland
Call of that
Those are really good names
Like what are their names
Scott Holland
Well there's that guy humorous right
What when Austin
Hugh Morris
That'll be funny
I hated that I hate that name
Drive me nuts
When Vince Russo humongous close
Very close
Vince Russo
Who was AAA
A writer
Caprock
She's just
Right
His idea
Hugh Morris
To think about
Really
And Vince Russo most of the stuff has
I think
Oven
Hugh Morris
Huge ass
Hugh
G
Rection
Amanda was paid
How much money to come up with
G reaction
Okay
Of course
And thumbs down
To Rob
I'm a policy wonk
Watch the new Game of Throne
I wouldn't give any spoilers
Okay
The guy on Berry
Wonderful I have no idea
You're right he's the most delightful person on television
But the most delightful person that I can think of is Kayla so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next Wallace
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
So far
Somebody donated on a little bit of
Elevated level
Thank you so much
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
IFA
A policy wonk
Myself right right
Long-time listen
I always wonder is Jordan
Doing that live
Or is it
Report yelling over the app
You told me
It's clean audio recording
We're creatures of habit
Verbal tics
Everything
Taylor Swift
People point out that
Cuttlebug
My buddy
Got a lot of friends
I told you I found
Crazy that this thing happened and the surroundings
Okay are pretty wild
Alex
Infowars Nightly News
Where I get all my
Course
Edit comes 2-U Circa early 2013
And this is a report
The Voice of America
What is the most trusted
Bar X
Deron McBee
He comes in
And he sets the stage for what we're about to
The WWE World Wrestling Entertainment
Amazing Tea Party
Villain Jack Swagger
Received email from Alex Jones
Yeah right
So we we have set ourselves in you know you can tell what time. We're in now
This is wayanad Zeb Colter and have become characters
Alberto Del Rio
Yep for the title for the world
Do you want a little bit of this the storyline of this as it happened
Yakko at
At the time Jack Swagger
They like those College wrestlers big big beef
From the
Nebraska or something like that
Yeah corn-fed
Colossus before just sort of like American
The All-American America
Came from the character that you would be
In early 2013
Managers have
Bobby The Brain Heenan
Fugees
Jimmy Hart
Jimmy Hart mouth of the South
Sedona
Play jacksepticeye while Jack Swagger's on
That was
Major list
Haha and you just
In wrestling
It doesn't play
Unfortunately if you're a bad guy cuz then you're annoying the audience disrespect
I can tell Vincent
Am I still talking
When I say that I'm saying it
Through the lens that I Nova
My comments about like him being a villain cuz that's annoying
Stuttering
Right
Alright so
Jack Swagger
So they grabbed
Dutch mantell
My Farmer
Wrestler
Farmer Booker
Besides helping
Great there's a walrus mustache
Zeb Colter
Obviously
Coulter
The dab
Uncle zebadiah
Ann Coulter okay she's a right way
Clearly
The Japanese not very subtle they're not very subtle
You know
Play Mohamed Hasan
The Middle Eastern
And all sorts of fun stuff
So
They bring them in
The promos basically
Yeah we don't want anyone
They they have
A mirror of the rhetoric comes out they have the Semper Fi flag
Flag in the background
Did they put their head I when everyone in the building 2
To put your hand over your heart
The people
Now in wrestling
When you have a fun chat
And you say it every week
Andre Linda
People's heads
When they're at
What do you think they want to do.
So unfortunately eating out of his hand because
So what happened
All the sudden
The bad guy who's cutting promos
What about this Mex
Chicken man taking our jobs in art
Titles
An hour
And you have 30
And they went
What they normally do
Too hot
Pivot
And they start adding
Other
People I will ask tomorrow he's a foreigner why I don't know and then eventually they
When Americans
I'm blanking
Del Rio with them
United me which is the thing that wrestling loves to do with
Well if
If we're bad why is he with them
They were
They added the former enemy
Yeah
What time it is kind of
How can we be bad
If he's with them
The real America
Cesaro in magic
Time I know it was getting
Nothing with
With wrestling to especially back in the
There's no need for character consistency pledging their allegiance
Usher
This country is Wrong
Had you comes in and get your stuff
Iraqi sympathy
Don kernodle with
The Russian
Or just free age
Is that okay
See I think what you're describing in this storyline is like
After the point where at
Yeah it's fairly fresh
Which
Really
Is when
Outside of it
But like this
Being your people on Fox News
They're just like
That business strategy
Come up a little bit later
Cynical
So ironic
Because
There's a wrestler in
Oh no I heard about that
He's cutting
Kind of what could be
Construed as white National
Promise
Which is like
Good
You know they might have done a thing of like
My savant
See how it
Go see if we can get away with it if we can get away with it
Because they want to
Claim like we Mara Society
Right and they've done it before
They've also done
That was that was right there
The nation of domination
I don't see it being so crazy for them to have a white nationalist character
Your place yeah
Dover New York
European wrestler
What is not an act like my girlfriend
Introducing
And she was like
Like his group is rink
Yes, General.
Yeah and I think that's the thing with
With wrestling is it
It's like saddle or something like that
Orion trucks
Contributor
JBL
Jumping
She got in trouble for
Goose-stepping in Germany
Royal
4 Dead guys in a******
But they loved you pushing the envelope
Like that
Going back to the Muhammad ahsan Khan
If you ever watch those openings like vignettes pleased to introduce wrestler
Rudy's
Little mini
Commercials for the wrestler
And they brought
Mohammad ahsan
And Sean tavari
His manager
In
Again
You know
They brought them in after
You're too after
And at first it
It was kind of like
Hey man
We haven't changed we are
Are you guys change the way you look
Lori Lightfoot
It was just like
The music is exactly like
Like the music in
Team America
Evil bad guy
Just everything about that is
Cringe-worthy
WWE Universe tends towards
Enter the WWE Universe sorry
Entropy towards minorities becoming Villa
Without a lot of
Careful attention
That story will end up being told if you're not careful
With WrestleMania
A lot of pee
About how
Years ago
Booker T
A program with
Triple H
What is mugshot
Criminology
Write very much you know avail
Racist.
People like you yeah
Me
And you were like
Triple H beat if it was crazy
Wow
Yeah really thought that everybody I remember we all were just like
That's gross
Just wait and see how every
Plays out
That they're like
I don't to talk about it
Nothing's going to change see how it
We haven't done every use Waitin to see Triple H was so f***** up
All but certain the Kofi was gone
Bangla cuz they literally
Had to let Kofi win
Delphic.
There
The only
African-American BB champ
What's the Rock
And I mean
That
How many years ago
So it's just like and it was very important
I was really
How
Boo
Gelato
Market America
Working friends
Wrestlers were
What color do you want it
The deal
Visibility
Not
Real this production truck
Everybody who you swipe your debit.
Annie Twitter.
You know you could have just made some of the champion a long time ago right like
That's what I would say why I love wrestling
We would have had to wait this long for
And it would have been awesome
United
You know
They are
And rosemary
Cancel
Not at first.
In those vignettes but when he came out he
He was always cute I like that that's a hover round
If cuz I mean he might have been the right guy
After this he was let go and then went
Impact Wrestling
And their slogan
The time was making
Great again
Like
The slogan you got
Arapahoe County
Strategy
They are introduced as xenophobic
And there are bad guys to begin with
Popular
To the point where they do start getting a lot of people who are in that that sort of right-wing world
Yeah liking them them after release a video where they explained
We are characters we are doing this to create a response
Do you know Dennis like
The Mauler would say that
You know
I've never seen anybody especially in the modern times and happen like that
Which is another
Very nice. Shonda value I mentioned earlier
Came out
Then they had to be like
Moments are real weird whenever wrestlers have to be like
Hey yeah I don't want to be killed for this I don't I don't want to encourage something really dangerous
We have crossed the line there's the famous
Mid 90
Where
They Crucified the Sandman Raven
Crucified the Sandman
Who was that
Olympic gold medals for wrestling
Was flirting with
Coming into pro-wrestling enable
Ucw Wilshire
Business
Any thought that was like
F*** this I don't
If you show me on the show I'll steal you
And call him and had to send Raven out he's like
Hey it's Scott Levy the character I play the character of Raven I didn't mean to really crucify the Galaxy's heartless. Edited
But that's when you don't
Get baby girl I don't know I don't know what I would call Heat
They're complaining about complaining about
Got so f***** up in terms of
Appropriate time
To break character and try and help people understand
This is storytelling
You're not supposed to like us
This is f***** up
Infowars
But it's not just Darren mcbreen
Who's going to cover this
We've got a special interview L correspondent
And when I heard
It blew my mind
Infowars reporter and former wrestler bionicdance
Chance to sit down and talk with another former wrestler about this latest campaign
Americans who opposed
Big government
As domestic extremists and even
Terrorist
Here's dammit.
Sowega
I love it
I can't believe he disappeared
Talk about male vitality
He missed that opportunity
He could if he was willing to go on he was willing to kuttanad for the another one of those guys here back in the day
With cane
Libertarian
Easy-Bake Easy-Bake in the pot businesses
Cannabis industry all that all that stuff and more
Character might have been more accurate than his male pornstar character
I think the stuff from the pornstar character I saw him
Wrestling show this Mania weekend
Alfred Joey Ryan
Penis Park
And things to say
Absolutely
Pornstar
He would come outside hello ladies music
Talk about the big valbowski
Chicago
Beyhadh 2
It was not
Not very subtle Chicago hot dog
Spencer still ketchup
I remember storyline where he sexually terrorized by f****** his sister
The gross character
Because it seemed so titillating
Group almost chopped
Subpoena dumbass Chapa-De PR
Chappie chappie.
Sisters or daughters very racist portrayal of sisters
Strip It Off
Found God and dispenser
So
WWE coming to ungodly and they needed to
When chick is hot
Derby hat
Calling Audible
Vietnam or the
The USA Network
Amanda
The brakes on a little bit
Ivory
Steven Richards
Yes
I can't remember who else
Anybody else
Golden Cannon
He was a cop
He was a cop named after like a real racist cop in the past
Telegram
Depressing cell phone there's there's a
.
About it
They were called the right to censor
RTD
But at the time there was
What's the parent
Who is the rat
Bike but also cleaning up the rack
At the same time power and it was like you don't want to
Dissenter you guys ride
Turn in your favor
They all wear white but I'll dress
Black pants White Bear Lake sale shorts
Sleeves in blackjack
And they were all like
Don't do that and you know like stable came out in the Bikini they would put a potato sack
Your body basically trying to get you
21 and not like people who want to send
And so it was like
Keno dual-purpose
Is very strange
Yeah dynamically
His career
Yeah
Overbooking 2013.
He is picky about his appearance of either
By Sandy Hook families for his death
Amanda is harassing coverage
It is deposition Alex tried to play Down Tampa. Wasn't really an imp
Alex would have to come out and say that he was a quote bad person
Not entirely sure what that means I don't know how that's you're a bad person
How much are valuable
That's very childish
Tell everyone hear me
Yeah
You can easily find a dondie's LinkedIn page if you want to by Googling it
If you do it appears that hasn't been updated since
What's 26
His username so is
I don't work at Infowars
Infowars reporters his
Is Heather is just an Infowars logo
Now here's a new Twitter handle the real damper dandi where is bio says former Infowars reporter
Ats-2070
In March 2014 testified in front of a Rhode Island state house meeting about guns
He introduces himself by saying quote my name is Dan patandi I work for infowars.com it's the number-one alternative
The media in the world
He goes on to yell at the panel for a quote
At which point he was told to leave the building
When you first started saying that I thought we can be a wrap
My name is Dan Vaden Taylor
Showed up and yelled at everyone around but it was a false
Boston cuz I know the other guy went to stand
Walking around Boston
Centipede like this didn't happen a back article about guy who yelled back at him
How to protect
Wolves
How can I write
I'm in July 2015 brine State Beach in Rhode Island
Branson beachgoers took place on the shores
He had an Infowars microphone
2015 Dan badonde made a submission video to be on the 6th season of WWE's top
Yeah
For the shop
We would have gotten a weird crossover between an Infowars reporter in a pre Velveteen dream Patrick Clark
Hulk Hogan
Yeah well what's my little bit
Weird Firestorm of strange things
All this is today
He left his idiot run around to bother people at a Gallop Statehouse meeting
Because I created controversy attention and content for Infowars
Because Alex never gave a s*** about the consequences of his
Or other people's Act
I'm here
We find a bitter
Which I couldn't have imagined
Can you try to be Russell
Somewhere I reached out to
Twitter in wrestling
I bet thousand in 4 years
Is DMX and his
Dresses
Yeah it's still surreal to me though like I never would have imagined I don't know as much as you do
Like locker room stuff
You you're saying him and Cain were two guys were known as libertarian
Yeah you know I never would have thought that of the big valbowski
I never I never would have thought
The day would come when I would see
A wrestler who I was able to file
Nothing that matters
Beginning
I will leave
For you of what's going on
Current news
Some recent news
Allison Croghan trucks
Mexican restaurant
Chewy
Rush Limbaugh
WWE Superstar
Okay
First of all what we get from that you're right
More wrestling videos
Sounds like
90%
The wrestling podcast
Justin Bieber
Breakdown bra SmackDown
Guns
He has a laptop
I was on Skype
On this laptop
Video camera
A Dandy sitting next to a laptop if you look closely there's a microphone sitting next to the speaker
Audio recording
Val venis sounds terrible
Text terrible speaker on a cheap laptop
Now
If you pay even closer attention
You notice that behind you notice that he's in a room that has glass windows
If you look through those glass windows you realize
He's at a public library
Wrestling posters on the wall
I really appreciate it room at a public library
Microphone next to the speaker on a laptop
If you pay even closer attention
You notice that right behind him is an old man a Google
10 pack
It's too far away to actually see what's going on
I'm left with the
Idea that maybe he doesn't have a camera
And the library has a camera that he can
Okay
Or he doesn't have the internet at home and he's using the internet at the library in order to make this
Interview with the valbowski happen I believe all of you
I don't know what it is but whatever it is it's not good
Yeah it's not streaming professionalism our journalism
Or anything like
I know it's tough and then also the quality is not good
Next to the computer
Like if I were Alex I'll be like look Val venis is a huge start this is a big guy and I'm glad
Came through for the Nightly News
The quality of this is no good
Myself myself
Also
Mr. Bernard
He was trying to make it seem
Like Alex
Was
The top rapper
Glenn Beck papers 100 slide back
Was the king of the castle at the time Glenn Beck was
Red hot
And this was when he was riding High crying right now.
Chalkboard
Yeah
Price for it not yet and then made that public apology to her after Trump got elected
Become even worse than he used to be now
Notre Dame fat guy is a f****** a******
But again Alex now
No
Did this is classic
Is turning Alex into the main story but maybe Glenn Beck is far more popular than
Yeah
I very much remember
Basically
They wanted Fox
Alex
To give it away too much
But Val venis understand
And he explains as much
A little bit later and it's about this
But you know what they're doing
I'm about to have you tired
The Patriots
Wichita
I also forgot to mention that the Skype video Val venis
He's in a car he's driving somewhere else videotape
Serious what are we doing here
Liberty moving right now at the Grassroots
So he's not happy about that but
My response to that would be like
That's the equivalent of some liberal or someone on the last being mad about Daniel Bryan
Akiko character parody this is storytelling this is
This isn't demonizing the environmentalist movement
These people are such snowflakes for sure
The wrestling characters
Like you said they're they're the true snowflakes in a lot of these senses of toast like
Volume
Also
This Patriot movement that is based on the United States Constitution
Especially for America board for anyone else
Yeah very much a localizer
Think they'll might have been one of the rest
Also
Val
Edge Chris
The Bahamas
That makes sense
He does say something or like there be at one point was like
Text Nicolette heck
Break
Engaging with the truck taken care of each other
Send to talk a little bit about the
Storyline
What's going on with swagger
Liking the story is a little
I have a couple of pieces of very bad news for Falconhead
First is at the border when people are
Stuff like that
For that purpose
Bad news
Segments of the Tea Party
Not afraid
What you'll notice was a lotto
Wrestlers
Time valve
Probably
I mean I would say
Still been
So interesting to tell kid one more run
End times
Wrestlers who
At one more good run
Left them they won't go hard on the door
WV
You know very political because they want
They all wanted braces
They'll want that one last
So a lot of time
If you watch shows
Nancy Grace
Bedrock
Stop
Part of the company
Of course record everyday
That guy did a bad thing
Another never
Former wrestlers
You probably have some bad
Great company
And that's usually an indication that the
You never know the WWE was the biggest game
So I mean just from that perspective
If subways
Death of these folks
WWE
But you're hearing that from Val venis like some sort of settled down real hard on him praise something
I like
Didn't even have to say races
That's true
You know it's more xenophobic
Then racist if if we're choosing
I'm not I'm not positive I remember the entire Android
You know
Writers in
To racist
At 1 are we still
You know like this wonder if they are racist
Find that hard to believe I bet there I bet they're there
Arguing over
They scrapped the promos
Yeah
Hey USA
Can we send
Okay
I don't know
Teasing or not
In terms of like why are you using Glenn Beck name
And so he explains that exactly
And there's an interesting irony that as he's explaining
This phenomenon
Darren mcbreen is facilitated by playing this interview that took place at a public library
In a parking lot outside of
Weather and making a big deal out of
A story out of it
Val venis distance
Like his
Hey if I knock this out of the
I'll be honest
I would beg
Two different just because of how little he seems to give a s***
What it what does
Maybe
I would have done better on
I have no evidence that he ever actually made
Brodus Clay Fox News contributor I almost did
Greg Gutfeld
Are the red eyes help people getting it on show
O'Kelly's cell pop
I mean he's much better than a lot of other people on that show
I watched a couple of his like man-on-the-street bit
God bless. Val venis
I explained a good marketing strategy
Turn on Jack's light
They are
Rush Limbaugh
He is against the Federal Reserve
Yeah
Clear Lake
Of course
Banba dandi Euro aspiring pro wrestler you should f****** get the business
You should understand what's going on I swear when I
Talk Ali
Here are just like
Ollie's rest
Or like
What's this on YouTube
Hey Stoney the wrestling guy like
Unlike
Ben
You think if if he was like almost a parody of what ya would be like it Infowars
And they're burgundy and we can talk about the you know the Iron Sheik and that what he did for the
The right-wing movements
I will mention out twice
People want
Alex twice
Absolutely about Alex twice as much and absolutely
Powerful that's
You can't reach any other conclusion
It's touch love me Daddy
Reporting
Says like
Talking points from
I'm going to skip this next clip
Come on let's hear it
Val venis talked about some of his political beliefs
Ask him about what he thinks about guns
I thought I'd slip in
Slam this weekend
WrestleMania
Do you want to know about guns
Okay
Super opposed to anybody having any restrictions on the right to have a
Question
Logic could be used to say
Have no laws
Attack anyway
Right
Bombs
Yeah but you know if you just only criminals will have bombs
It's not a good liar
Now we're like work that idea of life
Like
Wrestlers all got
Concussions at
I not because
Wrestle
Money from the dead
Exit it's a dump
Very considerate
Chicago
Isn't true
There's a recent study that came out in out of Stanford 27
There's a study that this guy did
A name
Looked at
Pass
Right to carry laws
Foregone
They found it
States average
13%
Increase in violent crime
Excluding or other relevant variables like that in the years after they post it
Or are they
So these sorts of ideas about more people having more guns means less crime
It just doesn't Stack Up in terms of the real world
So
Switzerland
Cesaro Joy
The Real Americans
You nailed it
It was not very funny
The argument that they always have but there's no crime
Whatever you think there's another reason
3 PayPal
PayPal
U-val probably Alex promised to help it expand
Sports
I'll take care of it
So it's important to remember that this is happening in early 2013
Yeah which is really wild
First of all
Alsco
You know what
I could use a guy like
I'll send him down there
I'll take care of baby
Yeah most people after
Reporter contest a relation
He hired an
Badonkadonk or whatever his name is
The guy in Seattle through the coffee on
The pro wrestler I have wrestlers
Okay
I knew that he was like a wrestling promoter and maybe a clown of some sort
I wasn't sure
Prove that it's fake but if you've heard I've heard from a search
Sources
Okay I willing to believe that I have no reason to believe it was real but
Whatever
Yeah do that that's what you would do
I heard so
Vedonde
Ask Val venis
What the final thoughts are
Wonderful groundbreaking interview
Glad you can see folks
This is a debutante
Clearly proved that the Liberty Movement is under attack by a character
Totally
I think that that last with those kind of like the best
Indication of what you're talking about like Val trying to be like a little bit of a tryout
Because that's that's pretty
Real sure
The idea that someone who has some sort of vague celebrity being like
Yeah there should have been a gun at that school killed that kid who's shooting everybody
I don't know
I wonder if it hurt any
I don't know I mean Willie Nelson smoked a lot of weed he still talk to Alex
Jesse Ventura smokes a bunch of
We still talk to Alex
It all. Those two are people who don't put up with all of Alex's.
You take it easy
If you have any
There should have been a gun
Hook
Teach finger painting or maybe multiplication
Teachers that sugar
Professor
Horrified by the idea of like people
If you had a gun
We befriended
Chicago
Also great comedian has a bit about
You don't pay me enough to
Be armed and try to take out the buddy yeah it seems insane
People have of like
What the ideal situation is if that run
I don't know
What about a stray shot
How do you say
Feel about
Me know if you were
Defroster
And these buildings
How often should be arm wrestling at Madison Square Garden
Allstate Arena
Nearby Chicago if everybody had a gun
The Georgia referee
You know like
Navigate to Farm down there
Georgia
Exactly
But you'll never hear that all you'll hear from
Beyonce's got armed guards
Badonkadonk
The argument about like people having arms are like celebrities guards and stuff like that like
What the problem is
It wasn't like off-duty cop social studies teachers their license yet
Is Eddie's teachers and the lunch lady
Right with God.
Yeah we just had a guy at the hall of fame
Luckily
You didn't have any weapons on a knife a gun
Yeah
It's crazy
So that your final thought on Val venis
I mean
Course classic
You know old wrestler a little bit of an audition for a job maybe
I'm going to make sure I do all right I get my catchphrase in
Cases about you
Set a table
Short interview
Apartments
Thanks Val really didn't
Give a s*** and wasn't very albatross around his neck
Alex and then maybe just dance
And Val pilot
This is like a
Every other wrestling d****** I talk to you
Are you in the library it's just like
Feeling when I listen to this of like
At the beginning I kind of was excited
In that restaurant
Get your name out there you never know what
WWE attacks
Yeah say anything like
Still available to come back
Martinez has been fun
It's such a fun time
Crossover of
But there's a number of wrestling fans always get
I get messages a lot of the time this is an opportunity for
You can learn a lot
From wrestling
Alex is just
To an extent you out there
No doubt it
Strategy of trying to get people to talk about him in order to get publicity what Val venis
Is exactly what Alex does
Alex is like Bret Hart
During the Stone Cold
Steve Austin Feud where
Bret Hart was a bad guy
But he was at
Sekiro
Alex
Is bad guy
Lavender outside
Everyone else
That person but you people
You all know
You good American Patriot good fight for being attacked
By Zeb Colter in
I'm doing the right
Flattered
This is a good way for me to also
Symbiotically get press
Because they've said my name
The opening to attack they'll probably makes
How to send the wrestlers
Another show like
This week
Good morning
I don't know if that ever happened
Not men stupid
He never comes on Alex's
Again going back
Real Americans once they put out that video.
That pretty much
Hey man
Yeah
And what's what's temperature
Sing to me
Is that why this is early 2013
Not pretty soon
In art
Covering
The Fallout
January 8th
Corso
2013 right now
But this is coming up soon
Zip codes are in Jack Swagger doing this stuff
We're going to get to see how Alex respond
So that'll be coming up
In the 20
13 investigation
I'm excited to see how that plays out
Right angle
Exciting
What's up
All over the place
One.com
Protect me.
Grumble grumble
What else you got
Go to Twitter
Yeah
Fan of the
Thank you
About that I want
I said you know
I know you text me Alexa
No
Great
Grapes again
How do I sound like a week ago
We got to get out of here before we do
Somebody
Albivis probably not killed anybody
Probably not
You know what
Cesaro definitely has not killed somebody
Even though he swings people around like crazy
I can go on the record
Del Rio who-knows-what Duchess done back in the day
We know what I can
Can say for a fact
Antonio Cesaro AKA Claudio
Signal
Have not murdered
Alex Jones
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color