Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody would have acknowledged
Beverages
Alex Jones
There's a problem with you
Your question that aren't so loaded
Lead me into a plug about how we have shirts
It's not interesting
Quest
Okay
One minute into our chaussure
Alright we Hampshire
Not long as I'm not even resent it I was thinking
Hiking in your duties
Oscar questions beginning of the show
Marketing opportunity
Apologize
Your conversation pop-up like
Someone on Twitter.
Replay the song on it up
Made me realize
Oh that's right I had a big italo-disco face
Was was on the
Certainly
Plug-in shirt gross
Crass capitalism
We currently have one
Design available that is
Knowledge fight on it
With a note stuck to it
Call Larry Nichols
And we will have another designs
I don't think this is the best
Possible we had to do
Call Larry Nichols
Episode
We'll be going over most of last week
Alex's
April 15th
16th and 8th
And
Because you were on vacation last week in Mexico
Cathedral of Notre Dame
I already built it
Might have that backwards backwards
Rebuilt
It said something
So today we'll be going over those episodes
The 12th
Give a shout out to
R&R sporting show
Christopher with a k
Text Little Timmy baby
I'm a policy wonk
Little city baby
Casey's
Thank you so much
Nickel
Keanu
I'm a policy wonk
Somebody
A little bit was donating on a basic level
Thank you so much
You are now a global
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
I sure like these guys
For sure we would be
Adventure on April 5th
Which was Monday of life
Notre Dame caught on fire
And we will get to that a bit in the
Of this episode
Most of Alex's show on the 50
Is him
Complaining about
Are you
You're nothing else is going on in the news
He's giving off a scent
To me that he's very afraid
There's if there's a Feeling
But he's very worried about him
Starting to get afraid of that
He sent Billy Weaver and Kaitlin Bennett
Penn State gun girl
Outdoor rally and
Kaitlin Bennett
Kicked out answer
She's making a real
The two of them on to talk about
Bernie rally
We're covering their
But it is important to note that
Most of the show
I'm not kidding around
I would say good
Percent of the show Alex does
Anna Bernie in French
I believe is
Indicative of how he's kind of lost
Himself in the character
Yeah
Is Impressionism
Is just getting
Getting Wild
Stretches of time but he's really trying
Has Bernie character in realizing
Like I don't have the
Yeah I can't stay inside the impression
Real disappointed
At its most
I was listening to it
I know that Notre Dame is on fire and
What's going on here
Does he have a
Picture in picture of Notre Dame burning as he's doing this
Found out yet
The news hasn't broken
Or whatever
Next
Talk about how he's always right
What you said
Nike pin
So you can keep in mind
And as we go
The pleasure scares
Charlemagne
Broadcast
Architecture
Zerohedge
We're open
What were
Killshot
Part of the conversation
Somebody's talking about you
The context of it
Is that
He needs Trump
To really Act
Internet
He doesn't
Is going to
Diminished
People in operation if I don't have access to those people
And I will go out of business
I need Trump
Now
This is a
Soviet takeover
Whatever
And we're the only ones who've been right about it all along
Social media
Nefarious thing
It's not
I want a crush
Like Alex's
They also have
Real girls play
For you
And your family
We can now take it away from you
Two genders and family
Your mind uploaded to the web
That is the agreement
Give up your physical body in this week
And of course the top scientist
You must
Facebook
Service First
In terms of getting you to kill yourself to be uploaded as a false
Coco question
Your
Entire brain is uploaded
Is program
2 minute perfect
Exactly that is there a difference
You know
Discuss by greater minds than ours
I don't know I don't have a position on it
Because that what I was talking about is s***
Misrepresenting comments made by like futuristic chocolate
Well there's a possibility of uploading
If you imagine that is a possibility but you probably have to die
In order to do it
It's not like I want to kill you so I can upload
Prospect
People like
No I mean is there is something whether or not it is part of like
An intentional advertising model or just go to the side effect of we didn't know was coming
Social media
I think there is something
Dangerous about the ideas
Living on these social media platforms
Now your life is so different
Without them
We all need to take a look at
Gets the same
Conversations a little bit
So Alex is mad
Censorship parsley because it will you be enforced
To kill yourself to be
Really wants
Get back on social media so we can become a clone at next
Arguing to get back onto the flowers
He's not making any sense most important I just kept it in
Kinda to give you a
A sense of how the beginning of the show is going
As opposed to wear it
I'm so here is Alex talking about
If you doesn't stop this
Alex
If the president doesn't
Of course the election
Lucifer
So hard to trick massage
Alex character is
Early on before Alex
Was fully on
As we saw in that 20
Stop
There was this
Galaxy
Who's the most evil person in the world
Gordy's The Greatest
To work with us tonight
Look sometimes
It's true sometimes
You never know which way it's going
Messed up
So it is easy to pull out
Even be
The most resolute
Reminded person in the world Alex
Presented as though
Like he doesn't even have that big sarcastic
Voice to it
It's literally him like rest
With the thought
It's not like I'm going like
Just being like
Yeah
He could be the worst
Notre Dame Notre Dame
The news
Alex
Church got the music
Are there scorpions in
I noticed they must have someone new behind
Alex's intro
And it does not Fade Out start fading out earlier than it does
Turnover in employees
Houses amateur hours yet
Disassemble
France
What we're dealing with
So expect
Alakazam
Response that this is a symbolic sort of things
This symbolizes the West
Because at least he's not putting any blame on anything like already said like outside
His play starting a firearm while they're staring at
You coming in
Part of it is
Because
He is really into
To doing that Bernie
And he doesn't want to suck
He wants to keep doing this
I don't know
Sometimes you just
Suspect something is going to go a certain way
You haven't even set
To do and someone in the audience
Heckling
I think that's how he's because Bisset
He wants to do right
His bucketful of Bernie impression
I hungry
Will you could actually get them
Questions
Spotify
I am Superior
Serious
Islamic toilets early
Hunchback
I love the idea that you like Notre Dame and I wanted to go to Paris
Well where is it going to live there is a sense that he's like
Very strange
Speedway
Here already
Close after
Break is already started to mention Islam
Surely yes
He's connecting
Those two ideas is on fire in his audience
Over about that
He said something
Kind of sucked up
Sort of like
More restraint than you'd expect Alex
That sucker is inflamed
Anyway so maybe it's better if just totally Burns
Yeah
Better than mamas
Casper
Were the Crusades
Literally what alligator say
Better for this to burn than for the islamists to take it over and turn it into a moth
Bucked up
That is really f***** up
But it does give you a sense of the world
You know what the state of things are
Is it is
In the past when we've seen Alex cover stuff
On the day of the Boston bombings he's screaming it's a false flag
Speculating pretty wild
Here we have on April 5th
He's not doing
That much
He's a f****** saying this long sucks
It's just it's very strange
Also his reaction
Very much
Smaller tragedies
He's never expressing any kind of
Regret or sympathy
Like this is such a strange thing for him to just
Eenadu
You know what is beautiful
I don't know why but
Maybe I don't know
To do the Bernie impression
Drive to score points from that
Right
He's got Joe Bannister
Partial
Why would I give away
The show before I'm ready to do it
Yeah I'm not sure what it is but there is something going on that is
Is what you're describing the
That sort of response
Very unlikely
Maybe
He's getting his
Rubbing off on him and now he's gay
Sing some sort of human emotion
I doubt it when are they are they talk about
Logan Paul's
It's because Caitlin was also on Logan Paul's
Not too far back
It's not really important
Anything they say ft Alex
I just I just I just I just
The script
What
Almost
Bad children
How old do you think Logan Paul
He's 24
What's 9
Irresponsible parenting at Beth also
What kind of like syndication did Alex have in 2000
Northern California
The NorCal market for a long time
Fire from there
Undoubted
I find this incredibly difficult to believe
And also I should say I looked it up Logan Paul
Just turned 24
If so I have even Logan Paul's parents
Irresponsibly they raise this child
I don't know Logan Logan
Just answer
Please just an
What is
Is 4 +
Globalism
So here's the last clip from April 15th it again
This is a demonstration of Alex
Characteristically cautious
It is coverage of Notre Dame
Never know
Some parents are going to be mad at you for asking questions
Or something like that
Presenting that is a hypothetical
That's not
Really restrained
Alex Jones rhetoric
The ideas like I kind of glibly and dismissive
It was an accident
Maybe won't
I quit
I expected it
Forces towards the future in order.
Makeup remover
Jump into the AI in
Teleport ourselves all over the universe
Given all of his rhetoric
His world
Should be like
On the 15th
Although
Alright the 16th he got the Bernie impression out of the system
April 6th
Tuesday April 16th 2090
Global
Broadcast
I'm your host Alex Jones
Obviously the tragic fire of a very important historic question site
Interrupt
Left of Islamic occupied
Burned
That's the ground but into an empty
The Ready Set
Incredible response
U.s. news Fox News
Anyone offline
Under French law US law under UK law under common law
Big fire
Is investigator
No s***
And that's why you don't really have to argue on
The only people who were saying
And that sort of thing are people who have invested in
Behind what they're arguing
They're arguing that
It was Muslim
Not that it should be invested
That sort of thing
Investigation
What they're looking for
In favor of
Even as they're saying those words
Instead calling for Noah.
Just like you know what
Let's chalk this one up to bad behavior
Let's not even worry about
Or or whatever the globalist
Biggest fire that could possibly happen
Eiffel Tower might be bigger
Imaginary visual
From the top
Patently
For this argument to be coming
People who are
Let's be honest
Noted islamophobia
If there is any
Voice
Publicly saying
Stop investigating
I don't think we need to look into this one at all
Probably an electrical
Go to tell you
Take me to never was not on fire don't look into the
Don't look into it
Who won the Falcon playing right now
Smoke bombs
It's completely absurd
Alex Alex wants the perception
There are people were saying
So if he's still not really saying
It was
Whatever
Around that line
Nicely
MMS next clip
He's trying to imply pretty heavily
For behind the fire
Thousands of cars burned mod
Screaming Allah Akbar
And they're on a Jihad
The UN reports that there have been
In Europe
Churches attack
Burn down
Most of those
And I got the report here with a view in before it's
That Christianity is the most persecuted
Religion in
The world
Alex's
Archbishop
Bernadette
Before the UN that was were
Repeated as a talking to
Point is if it was something
The problem
Christians
It's just the point that I'm trying to make it slippery out
Didn't say that does Catholic Archbishop
Has been repeated all over blog
Interesting Lee
In June 2018
Research Center released a report
The Christians were the most
Harassed by a very small margin
Airport
Look at the Grouse number
Only the number of countries in which
Happen
They found the Christians report
Countries in the world
Coming in at number 1
Islam came in at number
With 142
Opportunity
I'm a write-up about the report in the express
Analyze That
A Christian person
The world which found that most of it is found in
The asia-pacific
And that quote
India Nepal
Sri Lanka Target
Christian's the most
The picture of Christian persecution
Is a little bit different than people like Alex would like
Romans making lions eat
But
It's not it's not a totality of
Interested
The EU Parliament
He hates so much actually put this out in a report released on December 4th
They are currently the religious group most harassed and intimidated
Throughout the world
He can't say that I came from the EU though because you would have to explain then why I Godless globalist
Demon organization
Would put something like that in one of the reports
Talk about everything
Christians
The most persecuted
I wasn't all that curious about that be
We talked about that
Really curious about that number that Alex's
Decided about the
Churches being attacked in Europe in
The past year
The feeling I had was that it definitely
Could be a real number
Obviously even in the best of times some houses of worship
Two-faced
The grocery ality of modern life regardless of what faith
Albeit people worship
Dick movie
But something felt off about
Alex
Reporting it
Europe is a
Cute with a large population
Citrate
I know he's misleading people about the UN report saying Christian
Most persecuted religion in the world
I didn't know that he's exaggerating the number of car bird
What happened in France
And he's intentionally not telling his audience that most of them were burned as part of an insurance frauds
Good reason to suspect
This Thursday might not be accurate
Yeah wasn't
Sure
Claiming that this number is reporting is coming from the UN
Which I can tell you right off the bat
Is not true
One thing
Is it if you try and find out where he's getting this
Information from
Tana possibilities
Does a write-up in the gate Stone it
Institute of sites that
Number does a blog entry
Christian Broadcasting Network
Works website there's a report on one news now
There's a post on the Middle East Forum about it
The number is all over the
You and of course the most of us means United
Nations but where he got that number was from
His Uncle Nick
Oh that could be
Nope it's not Santa Claus
Should I just mention Christian Broadcasting Network
Gatestone in
Do one News Network
Release form plenty of others
What do they have in common
Probably owned
The Bursar
They're all relying on a single source for reporting their number and it's not the duet
It's a block run out of Germany called Politically Incorrect
News
Or as these websites
T.i. new
So it's a 3 million illegals voted tweet
Level of
Show me original post on
3 attacks
Christian churches in
Symbols were registered in France in 2018
Symbol very different than when Alex has a pimples
Property damage
Is 185 more violet
By comparison around 100 synagogues and mosques
What are purely factual level
But there's a reality
Here that's worth discussing
Because it's a reality that right-wing media Outlet
I mentioned earlier they're using a reality
I put the story
Outrageous
My hatred Manga Rock
In this Pi news blog in
There's no
Information about this 1,000
Tax number
Navigation
Where the number comes from
Or even specific information of what sort of attacks were included in this
Statistic
It just has this number of attacks
What were register
It doesn't even say who was doing the register
As it turns out the number comes from a report put out by the French Ministry of the interior
Which does say that there were 1006
Christian
In France
This is used to argue that there are by all these
Media operations
Waves of antichrist
Attacks and fix
What is on the rise
Yeah
The problem with that
Is that the same released
Interior Ministry points out
Anti-christian
Recorded
This last year was only a
2% in
That's an increase of 25 in
It's not the 185
Increase the pi news was a ledger
Also perhaps more importantly
This report points out the 2018
Teen size 7
54% increase
An anti-semitic in
Which probably seems like more important as a headline
Entirely unmentioned
MPI news
That's really odd you think that they would want to provide some context
So they would know
The situation is going on
As opposed to
Sprint
Small fact that would support some sort of attack
Nothing in the interior ministry's reported think about the people who
Committed these acts
But it does
Quote the obvious truth about the Antichrist
Fury and it's origin is permanently
Clouded
It's not for Traders who are in danger of being author
Ostracized
The desecration
Christian symbols with immigrant Imports
They are accused of hate hate speech and racism
Do people who baked the connection but
Christian
Anti-christian the text
Immigrants
Import immigrants
No problem isn't a news Outlet
Like its name might suggest
Overtly anti-islam
The depot which go so far
Bugs and buttons that's a quote islamophobic and proud of it
The guy who started the blog stuff on her
I was quoted in ideology of
He's very clear and interviews it doesn't believe that there's any
And literally
You're all Muslim
His website
Stomach parasites
In 2005
The Danish newspaper
Poston
Controversy
Protest
Luther series editorial cartoons of
Muhammad car jumped on the bandwagon
Much more
Attention of a large crowd of monster
I put his blog on them
Quote media critics
The phone I need my sister
It's an open racist gathers daily in the
MPI,
Ontario area
He goes on to say quote
T.i. is a forum for
Defamatory
Slanderous abuse
Threatening and sighting in
When confronted they have a really great read
Going to be honest
With you
Exit they make
So good about all that stuff on higher claims
Because he's pearl is real
Are you racist because Islam
Regarding this plausible denial
Roku
Perhaps this
Explains the greatest
Attraction of Politically Incorrect
And a multitude of smaller butt
Similar site
Islam provides
Steven Lee.
Legitimacy
4 old
PR news is a bigotry
Depot.
They've been constantly criticized for posting absurd and not true stories
To demonize Muslims English Banker no longer allowed to distribute
Piggybacks because it might offend Islam
It's very much like Infowars
The pattern of just posting whatever they find to reinforce their predetermined position regardless of whether it's true or
The thing is none of this is to say that they 1000
C3 anti-christian Acts
Statistic is incorrect
You know
What's important is how a publication like
User the stat
Octopus Outlet is a long-standing
Dementia
Because
No way you just be official reporting so
Suggested these anti-christian
Carried out by Muslim
Or even by immigrants
That's an interpretation
Is being added to a real number by a bigoted publication
Which is better Outlets
API news as a source
Without the primary source
T.i. news claims
Churches were violated every day the past year because they were simple.
The hated infidels
Ultraman Islamic
This is editorialize
In the past week has been pushing its
Insinuation that the Notre Dame fire was Islamic arson
Attacking the story from every conceivable angle
Headlines like where are the Muslim donations for Notre Dame
Missing from that article is the fact that Kamal cup Tani
Be president
The Council of mosques of the Roan had already come out and said quote we call on Muslims
France
To show their solidarity by actively for
Participating in the National solidarity campaign will be launched
Rebuild this place of History
Of our country if it's
The prayer so dear to our Christian
Brothers
Single Muslim
Speakingout
This kind of activity there's no
We shouldn't
A hundred percent
I don't hear them
The same thing you're not listening
I don't believe that any sort of attack
Takbir property crime or assault or even just make
Anthrax is acceptable at all no matter whose
This isn't an attempt to minimize the
The real anti-christian
Accident happened
He's on the Thursday larger number of Acts
Against Christians than there are against Jews
They're Muslims it's really simple
Exactly what there are more Christians
Intentionally apps
Something mosques in France
40000 churches
I can say with certainty information
But I can
Exactly the same way Pi news is trying to
They're putting the same spin on real numbers
False conclusion
What a camp
For sure is that Alex has no idea
About these just make
Can the UN part of this
The numbers game from the French interior
Even though that
So
You know
The thing about this
Strikes me is
The propaganda laundry
Technique
You know what I'm saying
Like so often with the 3 million illegals
Voted in this election
It starts out as a
All you have to have a some idiot with
Like bees Pi news
Who were going to make up some b*******
Slightly more
Trustworthy Outlets who just
Cited as a source knowing that you're not going to go look at it later
Report
If you go back through the second
I'm in there is laundering going on
A couple of
Specific examples about it they will talk about
As we go along
Alex talks about how
Islam is
About
I don't know
Wow
Write an article saying Jones is making up
That Islam attacks churches it's like Shane
Joan just making it up
The foxes will try to get in a henhouse
You understand what he's trying to make
In his audiences
Mine
Connection
Natural predator
Animals
Do
Of their very nature
Are you trying to
To compare that to Muslims
Attacking churches
As being just a friend
Character trait exactly
Read into them forever
Without having to overtly say that that is
He's trying to get across.
Which is deeply
So that's what's going on
On Palm Sunday to Easter as I said
What a few months ago
I said Islam is attacking churches all over the world
And I said his mom has said on Palm Sunday through Easter
They're going to burn up and bomb Church
I guess what they said just last week we're going to blow up in French
I just had a public plot
Notre Dame
You don't want to talk about it
Only saw the Christchurch mosque
Attack
I said
The media won't cover it
When we see
Churches and blown up
And shot up
Or islamists run over people's cars
Or trucks
Screaming Allah Akbar
There's a lot of
Four-wheeler
Response
Just get to this next
More
Back in the coffee run
And the kitchen
There was Fox News Chang
Well
Arson expert Fire Department
But we know
It's not arson
So he says there's no investigation
The government
Not Muslims. Arsenal
That is done
This is an attack on logic
They looked at the
The fire was only going for an hour and they said
No
Islamic Terror because Islamic Terror doesn't exist
I don't think they said that
So Alex knows what
He's doing here
Go together
Terms of building up with
The Narrative video
He's trying to push his
He's playing his role in
Each production that
Has been run
Times and the right-wing
See how it works
The first thing that's important to point out is
Is it the statement being made by French authorities
They works
It's fire wasn't arson
Everett Islamic terrorism
Creating a straw man
And fight with instead of doing any real work
Prosecutor Remy Heats with nothing shows that it wasn't intentional
But that was just based on initial information
Available
That wasn't making any kind of definitive state
And Heights the acknowledge that there was a
Investigation
Like when my apartment burned down like
6 years ago it was an accident
At the fire department didn't still do a week-long investigation just
Investigators do
By Wednesday the prosecutor's office it interviewed many of the workers
Well the prosecutor's office does not rule out any hypothesis
Nothing
Investigation
Highlights of criminal origin
Accidental causes remain are privileged
Investigators were allowed into the building they were initially
They were allowed
Safe
Able to begin their work by late evening on Monday France time
Which is daytime
Em4us
As they began their preliminary best
Navigation
Conceived to be pointing towards the next
Battlestar to the fire like what Alex
Play Mandisa
People on
Twitter
Probably some pundits on talking head shows did
Because they felt officials
It said that there was no into
Keisha that this was arson
Nor was there any reason
To put blame on Muslims are immigrants
And you know why they felt the need
Do that immediately blame it on Muslims
Immigrants and they were probably going
To start some sort of f****** mob immediately
Constantly and aggressively
Please wait
Not just
People
People like Alex
The day of the fire Paul Joseph Watson posted an article on Infowars that the headline quotes
Notre Dame cathedral in Paris on fire worker claims it was a deliberately started
Certain of that
It was just about getting the headline out there quick
It was still early and get a chance
If you sold enough doubt before anyone really knew what was up
The article was entirely based on what a guy named Christopher Hale
Paris who works
Notre Dame
Cathedral staff
The fire was intentionally
If you breaks out what's going on here
It's Paul Joseph Watson reporting on a tree
Posted by someone
He doesn't know who is your friend
Who told him that some other unnamed people told him that the fire was
Renton accident
Is not a good basis for reporting this is
To the possibility this is straight-up gossiping
It also doesn't help it hail followed up his tweet with another saying quote I should know he has zero evidence beyond what the staff
Substantiated rumor character
I don't know
Qualify
Unfortunately something demonizes Muslim
It's what they
They do
Because make no mistake about this
Cuz I'm not just saying this loosely
Paul Joseph Watson was trying to imply that Muslims at Notre Dame on fire
He ended his article by saying quote also take note of
The names of those who were celebrating
The fire by Rihanna on Facebook video of Muslim names
Smiley faces on a stream
Of the fire which I guess is a Smoking Gun
I don't care
He'll deleted his
Because he realized how it could be misused
He didn't believe the fire was arson
Piece of Gossip you'd heard
But in the wrong
That could be very dangerous
Unfortunately the wrong hand
Found it
Before he could delete it hit Paul Joseph Watson used it is covered
Point the finger at most
Can you imagine how
Frantically
Once the fire started
He had to have been
Research Refresher
I just need one
I just need one, I know it just was
Enough air
He'll got to learn an important lesson
I regret that I became an unintended tool for the worst parts of the internet
I think what's remarkable about this is how quickly
Desire to blame
Clear accident in Paris on the Muslim Community
From a tweet that was up for 10
Infowars
Multiple fake Twitter accounts created
To look like Fox
Sweet bulshit
Likes Alano Mars responses
The fire was too fake
We're posting videos of Notre Dame on fire with audio
The push to play Muslim
This fire was very
Strong and involved
The campaign
We talked a lot about this because it's super important
People like this pack of assholes know what they doing
They're doing
Amino that it only works
If they works
They know fully well that if they do nothing initially
The investigation comes back with proof that the fire was an accident
But that's not nearly as a pet
Effective they will squandered an opportunity
Rile up Their audience
With this speculation
Nearly isn't packed
I misunderstood I thought you meant
And afterwards doesn't matter
How to do the cover-up Ark
Not as
Emotion
Initially in the investigation
X Factor with proof it let's say Isis that Notre Dame on fire
The visceral emotional
Responsible have worn off
On the radio
It'll be hard to whip them up into
The same level of
The stereo they were able to hit the moment after an emotionally resume
And listen problem with the cover-up
Vindication and being always right forever
Guess who's a nautical now Notre Dame
F*** you you know so this is part of the game that's being done and this is what Alex
Is
Engaged
His own webs
Posted
It is based on
To try and claim that space
Early on
F*****'-a
You're the worst right respond on Twitter or
Respond on these talking-head shows this rank speculation
Specifically
To point the finger at Muslim
When they respond by saying
Hey look you know Dalton
We don't want to get into that sort of thing
Yeah
I was afraid of an investigation it was an accident
When in reality
Just a f****** stupid
The dance
Who played what I actually
I actually cried
Yesterday
Because my girlfriend I just started
The Twilight Zone
And they hadn't liked her first four seasons were dropped onto the net
So I was like all of The Twilight Zone
And when we got to the monster on Maple
Do you remember that one
That's the one where it's this idyllic
Little night
Eisenhower suburb
And all the sudden just all the power goes out
Moment everybody starts picking
Can get each other and I
Just watching this going like
This was nice
T2 whatever
That this was recorded I'm crying because this
The same f****** s***
It's like Twitter turned into that
Entire place all day everyday
Respond to things better and not let
Autopilot
Watching Twilight Zone episode
Jordan if I didn't point out that we're recording this on Sunday and late last night
Multiple bombs went off in
Churches and hotels in
Sri Lanka
Time does recording many of the details are still
Materially reporting any
Nope throughout all this last week Alex has been yelling about Isis
We heard it
Before
Easter egg
Well maybe what ended up happening
Right we don't know but that might be
Write on a technical level about that prediction
Mainstream Outlets are reporting a no group has taken responsibility and it's unclear who's behind it
Complete assholes like Robert Spencer of jihad watch
Cowboy one of Anders Breivik most-cited resources in his Manifesto
Are posting things like reports suggest that suicide bombers might have been
And then he says people's names who I'm not going to repeat cuz I have no idea where
Trump
And it could possibly be playing the cigarette people who I have nothing to do with anything
Fifty-fifty at best
Here's the thing
This is awful and complete tragedy
Exactly
But if you smoke
That doesn't
The perpetrators of the
Days ago I thought
Horrible brutal terrorist
But has no place in our society
Leave a long history of killing civilians and terrorizing population
I work against that is a valuable
Google
I still think that today
Minimize this or not care about
You all knew that Isis was capable of that
A month ago remember when they put out YouTube videos
Cutting people's like literally decapitating people
I never would have expected this Behavior out of those
Right
Yeah exactly
It's not to minimize the damage that they've done know how can you possibly use this
As some sort of
Extra amplify
Application of your hatred of Isis information comes out
If it does turn out that it is
Attack that was
I will
Field
You know this thing
One more one more
Now at this point Edward recording this on Sunday
An article with the sub-headline
Quote Islamic suicide bombers launched
Attacks on
Shepherd Church
About the attack
Which is actually just a copy and paste of an article
Zerohedge
God dammit
Your problem
Islamic suicide bombers
Alison Infowars just added that to this article
The closest
Zerohedge articles
Cost of this is quote
No group has yet claimed responsibility for the deadly Easter morning attack
Those Sri Lanka
Christians as a sizable minority of about 8% have reported an uptick in person
Threats coming
A Muslim
And majority Buddhists population
In the country
So
That is the closest that the Zero Hedge article comes to
Alex Jones
The sub-headline
Quote Islamic suicide bombers launched
Tax on 3
That is not in the source
Material that is Alex adding
A hundred percent
The only coverage
An attack so far on Infowars
Another copy and pasted article this one for Breitbart
About how the pope denounced the
Cool violence
That's better
Kind of silly that Alex run Astoria
But I'm yelling about how the pope is involved in the global child sex
Extravagant
But he's free to run his business Howie's
The problem here is that the Infowars article has this headline
Quotes over 200 dead by Islamic suicide bombers hundreds more injured
I think you can already guess this
The attack was carried out by Islamic
Suicide bomb
It's not even a Breitbart
Story gets published
Just a copy and paste a report from the associated
Depressed it's mostly just about how the pope is praying for the children
German
He's around the world
Replace vial
Are very basic level
Superbad
It could turn out that this attack remembers of Isis
Alex has no reason
Other than to push the narrative
He could editorialize something like quote I bet this was suicide bomber
But he's not doing that
He's copying pasting other people's articles
Conclusions to them
Even if it's hunched ends up being accurate his journalistic track
Actresses are unacceptable
I need to be ashamed of himself for doing
Is Bartos
Respect and flip
Is he literally copying and paste
Like he's not he's not rewriting posting on Infowars
The text of the article
Byline
But yeah it's just
I don't know if they have
Agreement where he's allowed to do that or if he's doing it
Without permission I don't know that Alex
Used all those artsy articles.
Marty wasn't super happy about
But I don't know if you could have an arrangement
Zerohedge
I don't know it's really really f***** up that Alex is taking
Stories
And adding his own self headlines
Have nothing to do with the content
Of the story
Is his source
It's
It's framing
Of the story
That's inappropriate
Is that something
Opening practice
Two-story too much
Time spent
Focusing on drugs are researching his practices
I know that he does write his own
Pretty stories and sometimes their B
Sensationalizing
Sucks but I don't know if
I don't know
Like
Something of a progenitor of this type
It could be it could be that Alex has taken his game and gone much further
You see what's going on
The initial thrust
To control the story
Control the story
Box it into our narrative
A story from the Associated Press
The Breitbart is copied and then Alex
To copy from Breitbart from the copy from the Associated Press
About the pope praying for the world
4 piece is now turned into
Sub-headline of Islamic suicide bombers
Committed this
With no other
Gross
Listen
Picked up
Get picked up by an amplifies it with three different
Watson was doing
Immediately after Notre Dame
Was caught on fire
It is their business practice this is how this works
But of course
Islamic groups and we're going to Target
That's
That is absolutely
No one
Cuz there are investigators the best
Specifically
Please don't invest
What we would prefer regular people
Like he's not going to be able to go into the cathedral and like look at he doesn't he's not a f******
Fire Marshal
Press pass in his little cap
I would like to investigate this
You can investigate
Tweets
No one's going to stop you from that but like
Just the very idea that he's presenting it as anyone is saying
Stop invest
Towards the people
French officials or something
I'm soaked
Because Alec
Just like we talked about earlier
He does see this as
Something of
A crusade
Because a modern-day Christian
We got videos
Lookout app high rise window in
Running around
Molotov cocktail
You'll have 500 is running around and they'll just go down street
Is that Bernie
You just presenting islamism
It's not a it's not a good way to look at
Alex
Call
To worry is the idea that all of these folks are
You're coming in
Right
They're all
Are coming into country
It'll be bad enough if they just had it will but the reality is
Is to Alex they're part of a bigger
Plan
And of course that plan
Is being run by Soros
This group is funded by George Soros
Natural Nazi collaborator
Well what they're trying to do is to get enough of dumb people to go out the tack white folks
Start shooting back
Second cause of Civil War
So I understand the Pawns in this minorities are in the good news
Bunch of professors that's the good January last year
Secret
Internal documents
How to have
In Maryland and other cities attack
Reprieve
Starbucks
McDonald's
They are actors
Yul Brynner
It's this is all just b******* that he's making up editorializing on those fake
Contractility found on Fortune
This is
Completely ludicrous fake documents that he found as evidence
Global
In order to cause minorities to attack white people to cause a civil war
This is f****** stupid so bad I'm trying to understand this plan
You get professors
Right
Wearing all black that's important
And they
Knock over trash cans outside of Starbucks because there's an arrangement
Starbucks
Maybe they haven't baby there are always
Maybe there's a f****** billion of them
Maybe they like you know
Locally-grown
Boutique coffee shops
I don't know it's stupid it's all just a stupid fake Soros antifa document
That's a Harrison Smith found on 4chan
It Alex is just
Gracefully pretended is real
Cuz I get looking like the very f****** idea that you would make
Make someone sign a non-disclosure agreement in order to be like part of a
Criminal
Conspiracy
In order to overthrow the country and start a civil war is laughable this f****** idea is not
Nonsensical
Anybody involved in that kind of a criminal conspiracy would know that
In no way protected by an entity
That was it was weird with Steven Soderbergh left on Ocean's 11
Sign an NDA and they had to do the whole thing
I was really surprised
Underpinnings of the police
Reinforces
His ability
Horrible
And you just laugh them off if they
Reinforce
Assertive the things that hold up the big
Which is
The bomber
Alex
Get sidetracked by
Cuz he's got it
Most of his peace
About the Notre Dame fire
He doesn't talk about it that much
Of the big news of last week
He gets into some other stuff
Here's one of them
Potable
What's wrong with this picture right here
Torrid.com
Putting American flags on police cars Sparks backlash
People don't like
American flag
It's a racist evil symbol
Sounds like that rid of that flag
Sounds like
So a lot of the reporting on this story outside of even Alex's
Stupid show isn't pretty
What's the mark
Circle around that idea that the flag is seen as an intimidating symbol to immigrants
Or some s*** like that
Septimus reporting
From the original story in LA Times
I just wanted to repaint Laguna Beach police cars with an image of the Americas
Can fly grinding through lettering on the doors will return to the city council
Tuesday
After some residents
Deemed it unfit for the artist
Community
Though most of the comments made by residents in recent months were about the squad cars newest Tech
Online reaction in recent days characterize the debate
Supporters again
Mater
Thoreau said Monday the council is
Quote decision about the brightest colors
But but the issue has evolved into a broader National conversation about tape
So this is like
This is like they have two graphic designers and one of them is like an American flag with a big
What does a smaller American flag
That's it
American Woodburn
The design scheme looks quote aggressive
Candy with designs
After idiots started attacking heard leaving more than 150 message
Just quote via phone call text
Voicemails and emails
Explain what you was talkin about
I don't really care too much about the
Design other than what I said
It's bad art I'm being attacked for that because the narrative
Feed the fire of division which is what our culture has become
Sojourn
Laguna Beach Commission
Who designed for the
Mayor pro tempore literally looks on the car
Better on paper than it did on the cars
So they put together a council meeting to sort out the artistic issue
The fact that they were having a council meeting to re-evaluate the car's design
Was intentionally misrepresented by people like Franklin Graham
The Christian Broadcasting Network FOX News
Protect
Because the flag was never under attack
When the flag is It ultimately removed from the cars all these Outlets
Culture battle
When in reality it only existed in their head climate change
We need to go this can't be this is
We're done
So I'm out
Congratulations dumbass Patriots
The flag from yet another imaginary threat
From what I understand
Customary celebration in their culture
A times like these
Cheeses to make up
So I look forward to
Alright so
We we have the new design for the cars
American flags going to be on
I think we need to
To take it back though
I took account
The car is a ridge
Orange
So I don't think you want to put that
The only complaint that I saw from
Mike primary reporting
About the
The flag
Itself was from some
My buddy who was
The point that
The way that the red white
Blue of the flag is presented in the letters
Ice in police
Display three letters are mostly read
There was like a feeling of
This aesthetically doesn't it
Feel good
Different
It's between the pool and the ice
In the color scheme
Which
I certainly
See what they were saying
If you look at the cars it is
Ice is
Predominantly
It sticks out more in the eyes of the police
Word based on the design
So even that could be an aesthetic argument less an argument at the flagship
So whatever
Who cares this is all bulshit
Ridiculous
Hate that
So much
F****** b*******
Imaginary battles
Imaginary victories
Because Alex is never wrong and
He's very hard to pull
Guys calm it down
So here's the next one
He gets to
Clip of Tucker Carlson
Talking about Alana Omar
But Mike down
Because what Alex
Tucker Carlson
Gunship
Assault
Everyday
Many ways things were injured growing up in a refugee camp
Quotes
When you're a kid
There is freedom in knowing that you were accepted
Representative Omar is incredibly disgusting
She's here to conquer the country and thesaurus
Anger to do so is pretty dangerous talk
Aggressively anti-islam character of his
Entire show
Play this clip of Tucker Carlson being a
Dick and then
Which I find a Presa vintage
But I want to address the propaganda
Autocracy
Performance
She never said that America is
People that she feels threatened
Demonized
Are the articles
It's challenging
She says of living at present
Where is Heritage
Just constantly criticize
Everyday a part of your identity is threatened
Demonized
And vilify
Trump is tapping into an ugly part of our
And freeing is ugly
It's been a challenge
To try and figure out how to
Continue the inclusion
How to show up every day and make sure the people who identify with all the marginalized
Kerry Hill represented
It's transitioning from the idea of
Resisting to insisting in upholding the value
We share that this is us
Society that
Was built on the idea that
Start anew
Celebrate
Immigrant heritage
So you can already see the twist
He's done by a cherry picking
Deliberately
No matter what you
You do no matter what
You say
6 words
Rip it out and say that you hate America
Even if you're into even if
You wrote an entire novel book about how
America 100%
If you even mention of fault it's going to be like
If you don't love every single part of America especially the part where everyday on Twitter
And then whatever you f****** turn your TV on at night Carlson says that you're a terrorist
In-N-Out
Bright
Assault on her part of it
Is doing here because
What you talkin about is
Pieces of your identity
Assault
Threatened
These pieces of yourself
You were proud of and are proud of an are apart of
It's a different thing
It's very slightly different but it's important
The cheat sometimes
I can't go to work or it's hard to go to work
Message there is what he was
Misrepresenting
She saying that it's a challenge
Chance to try and figure out how to show up everyday
And make sure the people who identify with all the marginalized
Representative
To go to work
Figure out how
To carry
This
Temptation and make sure that the people who have these identities
Tucker do you know what the challenges
Dealing with your boss
She never got discouraged
By your b*******
Stop showing up to work everyday
I will fight
She never says that things are easier for her growing up in a refugee
America is a black Muslim
Registered
He just
Conflict
Society
Wichita
Girl child
Who just survived a f****** Civil War
What you said
Introspective
It's not judgemental
Not bitter
It's completely reason
Tucker Carlson is absolutely one
100-percent twisting
Taking everything
You said in this article out of
Image that helado bar hates America
This place is long for the days of the refugee
Where everyone around her were black and buzzing
The passage
Discomfort you felt better identity
12 year old
Is part of a paragraph that also contains Omar quote
Optimism
Their father grand-father imparted to her after her
Her mother died
When she was 2 years old
Quotes
Today does not
Determine your tomorrow
Her discussion of her experience with a hope
It was an expression of
Natureware society and
With each other
We twist this into an over
Xenophobic
Absolute
Disgrace
Only surpassed by his commentary on it
That's a 12 combo that I that I
A real bummer
I'm interested to know
Nae can't be true but
The writers for Tucker
Richarlison
Knows who they are
Right I mean they're probably
Tucker Carlson isn't extemporize into extemporaneously
Writers over
If you did a lot of the right
Where's my real ones
Putting this s*** out there and bake just get away
One of that like some sort of writer or some form of writer found this article in Vogue
Brought it to the table
Yeah that's interesting
Focus more on Tucker we would know those writers
Yeah I wonder it just seems like this
Exorcism
Kind of gift
The face man
For the 17th
See what happened but I
Or the entry
Because
The 18th
Thursday
The Mueller report
Episode
For Monday
If we're covering the present-day while you were on a f******
Beach in Mexico
That wasn't getting
You f****** s*** stolen from
That definitely wasn't taken
Yeah I know my girlfriend the Mustang
Lucifer
You're going to love the story and I gave her the whole long list of like internet articles
Read about it
For 5 minutes
Did you give me a list of the articles about what the actual symbolism about the artist father run
Edwards
Just making sure you didn't just go
Murals
You up
Denver Airport
Security twice though in that
Vine
Fair enough
Two ways
Notre Dame was on fire
Have to be part of this
Get back
We're moving on to the A-Team
Makes pretty clear
He hasn't read it but
But he knows what's up
Latimer here on my desk we've already been scanning through it
It's really just confirming everything we already knew
Giant
We elect a president
An overthrow
The election of the people
So
Cool
First of all
Kind already
Like months ago
We knew what his angle
For this really I think this is probably a little bit
Is
It just came out
Everett
If I were him
I probably would have had someone fill in
And taking an hour or two or whatever
And no more about it
Instead what he does is just
He basically did a bar
Whatever I wanted to say
Let's not worry about it I'm going to give you shorts
Reinforced whatever you want
Namely that is
It's basically a cover-up and the Democrats are the ones who were guilty all along
Hillary uranium
Yeah the Mueller report was always going to say what we said it was going to
It's not all that interesting
But there's a couple things to do come up and its coverage
Char
Interesting eating of themselves
Less about his
His feelings on the the report
And yours one of them
Different ways to say
Say balls
The Democrats Rod Rosenstein
The Bruce
The cojones
Meaning of the testicles
The short hairs
The balls
That's pretty fun
The Tulips
Do you know what I'm saying
Alex
Do in lieu of actually knowing anything
About the report
William Barr press conference
About the announcement
That's fine
His justification
For doing it
The best comeback on the other side
Adjust play the press conference end-to-end
With a few stops
Open contacts to it
The best
That's what I regular old smart new show would do so weird
Press conference
Because that's what a normal smartpress
Brian stelter
Absolutely
So Alex doesn't
Kipling press conference
That's
York Times
Two-piece about me the next hour cuz it's show Illustrated
Panache
In WeChat
The consolation
Prizes destroying Alex Jones
Of losers that are hurting America
And prosperity
I hate America
Sounds right
Listen York Times article analysis talk about ism
About his death is
The headline is Alex Jones under oath is an anecdote to the Post
Truth age
Hey Gardino my feelings about this article already named leave at the premises a failure
So wherever it goes from there doesn't really matter
Quote the hundreds of thousands of views on these videos
To their appeal as a hashtag resistance
Consolation
Emprise
Maybe it's not habitually lying president but at least someone is getting called to account under
Application of America
This isn't talking about destroying Alex
Trumped if anything it's expressing a very understanding
Little desire to see
Be forced to exist
In space where they
Not lie
Of course the fact that Alex being under oath is ultimately
Meaning listen
Simple deposition
And the fact that he knew that and
Need to lie Pretty consistently in the deposition
Should be evident
What's that if anyone took the Alex deposition
Consolation prize for
They're not dealing with reality
So I don't
He's going to get back to complaining about it later we'll see what happens
To him sooner
Complaints about this article Zoe
The times
Is that they talk about how Alex
I got grilled about things
Hook
And that was
They say that I'm making it up
Camouflage
Newscast
But show it all eyes are rolling
With everything I say
This is
A little bit later about something we're about to see
See things go way off the rails
It's towards the end of this episode
I completely blows my mind
It worries me
But also as it like a sketch
I think it's hilarious
Also
Philosophy professor
Mark
Pronounce this
Lamparello
That's real talk
Police while I was just trying to
Call
Is a terrorist
That I had
Not just among
Philosophy professor.
Burn down
Leo zagami is
Illuminati Insider
But you also is one of Alex's big resources
Catholic narrative
It's about the ideas
Sex chapter
Church narrative
What's the through line
Throw it on the wall
This guy Barclay a ellos a 37 year old college professor
Who's simultaneously also
Student desk
CU NY
Pursuing
I can find no evidence
What is a leftist
Anybody
Pursuing a degree in philosophy
Stefan molyneux
As someone who was a sloth
I can detach
There's a lot of philosophy
A lot of directions
I'm not sure but nothing I can find gives me
Whatever his politics are was arrested after walking
Patrick's Cathedral in New York
Two bottles of lighter fluid it's a barbeque lighter
Those long lighters
I would call this by the police who are able to clearly
Thrown out of the the cathedral Basilica of the Sacred Heart in New York Newark New Jersey
Prior
Because the scene at the church and refused to leave after repeated requests
Ultimately on the floor
He was arrested for trespassing
Resisting arrest
With a court date scheduled for May
He arrived at st. Patrick
Funeral on Wednesday night
Suspiciously purchased a one-way ticket to Rome
Shows leaving from Newark on Thursday
You don't so cancel classes
Supposed to
Call claiming that he was sick
So
Emily is very
Upset with the investigation is still ongoing is still in progress
Doesn't look good
There's a very decent
I was just going to
About time saying that it was that is what you said
What is motivation was is anyone's guess
White Witch
To cover this
I'm in his article about Mark
From a heavy
Call about him
Twitter and underneath
Completely out of
Video of a Muslim Church
Which is plaintiff
Either from 20
From August 4th
Depending on which part of the body of the article you look at it
In the article itself
They have two different things for the video
You look in the artist video that is unrelated to this particular incident
Unrelated
2DS story home
Videos
Permit account whose name is storm
Trooper with three American flags after
That's pretty much a Muslim
Did the United States
Is Venus mostly just
Read tweets from Mogadishu
Interesting is that
16.6
Thousand followers
And yeah whatever
Self
We struggled to get any kind of
Which makes me think is accounting
Kind of in a facade
It just seems like a
Voice article
Concludes with the Paul Joseph Watson video about how Muslims were celebrating the Notre Dame fire
Based pretty much entirely on his crack investigation of Facebook smiley faces
That we talked about a little bit earlier
Well here's an Intrepid reporter
Interested in the story about Mark lamprell
They're only interested in using it as a waypoint
To what they want to talk about namely that Muslim
Even though that has literally nothing to do with
The story this article is supposedly
Also you know how I told you that a war story about the
This guy's really just
Copy and paste
The article includes this passage
Forgot to mention there are two
On Reddit
Quote response
Story in 2018 about people disliking President Donald Trump more than
Merkel
He wrote quote all I know is it the French just like us for something
We must be doing something right
They think they're so much more sophisticated and culturally alluring enough
But secretly they're jealous of us in water.
Never forget that fellow Americans
Oh boy sounds like doesn't sound like a demon left really doesn't sound like a leftist
Demon left us to hate any leftist Dino that would say something
What's the French just like us
Yeah usually reluctant usually
Surrender monkeys ironic
It's a it's a fun little switch up
Interesting is
Absent from any of his coverage this guy went to Saint Patrick
Cathedral in New York lighter fluid lighters
Try and talk about these unrelated
Muslim
Fire
Situation
Of Muslim
Other
The coverage is really seems like
Don't talk about the show that I've heard or it on their website
Week Holden
The 21 year-old son of a sheriff's deputy
Setting fire to 3
Historically Africa
American Church
Doesn't Louisiana
Matthews has pled not guilty but
The fire marshal has provided evidence including cell phone tower records showing the Matthews was
Ff3 churches
And images recovered
His phone of the church is on fire before firefighters arrived
We have got to get a higher class of criminal
You know it is until proven guilty
That was
Three hate crime charges have also been filed against
The prosecution is indicated they have evidence
Motive
A search of Infowars website for the name Holden Matthews
Yielded zero results
The same is true of newswars and Paul Joseph Watson stomach.
Not at all
Did you know they're small operation
The time to cover all the news
There's a lot of other stuff that they didn't cover why aren't you talking about that
Like I in Chicago
Are you kidding me we don't have time to cover that why would we cover these historically black church
Churches being burned out by white supremacy
It slightly less relevant to the
The topic is other articles you're writing about fire and
The intersection thereof
With right now
Never expect
But I would expect him to
Use those as act like it's a false flag
Muslims really dated
Other narrative
Cuz he's always
Here's what they're going to do they're going to come for him to be like
The drugs he plays video games and all that stuff literally every episode
Maybe I missed
Stupid if you
Researches website
Nothing
So now finally Alex
Give two bars Prescott
And the FBI
Leftist groups were funding the fake pee pee dossier BuzzFeed
Michael Steele
Yeah no I see mentions
Thedirty.com
I don't know
I mean it comes up in the report
The press conference
I don't care for us to listen
Too much of Alex licking Trump's boot by proxy lavished Praise on William Barr
This press conference about to release
The Mueller report
We know how he would respond
Who was taken in response
Is there report
If the report finds serious wrong
There's no real world
Is the definition
Trying to hold Sam's slipping through your fingers
His idea of like a holic's
Yeah this is the direction he's going
There's not a whole lot
What is Aries
Super predictable I'm not all that interested
I kind of feel like covering it is like rearranging deck chairs on the Titanic
There's something more important that we could be doing
Mainly discussing what the hell is Alex thinking supported William Barr
What the f*** is you doing
Oh Dad
What's getting the history of William Carrick
Pretty f*****-up stretch of time to be in the CIA
Watergate was unfolding all around president
On top of that just released the Family Jewels reports the outline of the CIA totally
It illegally spied on
Pizza purses
Like members of the Black Panther
Women's rights
Israeli Embassy
Are various anti-war
Your response to these Revelations
Republic
Position
Congressional investigation
Good messed up time to be in the CIA
Also 1976
CIA
George h.w. Bush was named director of Central Intelligence
Interesting
How is May 9th
George h.w. Bush appointed William Barr Deputy Attorney General
General on around that
Time for HW that William Barr would be
Parallel
Attorney general report titled
Which operation of justification
Explode in the decade
The 1992 report is laughable in its
Ranging from things like we shouldn't release people from prison early because some people commit crimes after they're released early
No one goes to prison for their first crime they're hardened criminals by the time they go in
The basic point that bar is relying on to make his ark
Incarceration go off they cause crime to go down
The years of 1992 and numerous academic studies
Have not been kind to this
In 1992 the US held approximate
People in state and federal
Later that number was almost 1 million
Can people hire
In all fairness the upward Trend begin for bars
And even more fairness
He still has blood on his hands for how the report was used to
Prison industrial complex
Is one of the sections in his report is about how we need
Need to build more prisons
His solution is literally counter to one of Alex's acceptable firmly held belief steaming civilized
Authority for asset forfeiture
Literally used hundreds of millions of dollars from its asset forfeiture fund
Have the office of National Drug control policy
Special 44
Construction of new federal prison
Criminals to pay for prison
Except
Except for a lot of that stuff steak
Itsfunneh
Can sometimes just mean Injustice
Do you mean you mean the evil one of Alex's websites Prison Planet
Architect
Who advocated using civil asset forfeiture
Construction Amor prison
Is now loaded as a hero too
All it takes for the worst
Monsters take a rehabilitated
Alex Jones the stupid cowardly empty
He stood over a dress shirt
It's collar on button cuz it's big neck is
Too f****** thick
He's always the worst the worst
William Barr
Owosso
Effectively being instrumental in helping Bush cover up his own involvement
This life New York Times writer William safire
To give him the honorific title cover up General Barr
Almost it's almost like there was something in his past that
LED Trump
Choosing him as the attorney
I know it feels like that and honestly
There may be something to it but
It is it is like
Yeah
Wonder Woman
Attorney General's office
Has he started
Working for a lot of
Since
How It's Made
Attorney General
AutoZone website
Oh yeah
Steve Watson Road Norco on December 10th 2018
Is Attorney General
The article quotes
But I can the first things I've learned
Very very true
I'm disturbed
Civil asset forfeiture
Without a conviction
As far as I can
William Barr
Has never appeared in an article on it
Infowars newswars or prison
Planet before
2018 article by Steve Watson
Completely ignore or dismiss
Pre Trump career
The idea that he has this all this
Intense bag
It only appears in this December
2018 article by Steve Watson
And I know
Archives of articles on newswars
Kind of Newark
You can find stuff from
Like early 2000
You so preoccupied
What William Barr advocated for
Something about odd Bella bedfellows
Cuz I believe Thomas Jefferson
William Barr press conference
Does being completely exonerated
Ofcourse
That's the talking point
But he's also pretending to have some sort of an awareness
Like he's listen to it already
Which is kind of undermined by his response listen carefully
This is
Very soon after he starts playing the press conference
At the special counsel
Report makes clear
The Russian government sought to interfere in our election process
For the special counsel Starr investigation
So that's gonna leave it
That gives you like
If you just listen to that it kind of gives you a sense of how this goes
There's not a ton more other than
The singer
So
Jordan I think I know a lot of powerful people
Away from the Mueller report
The stuff that I'm most interested in is all the stuff at 3
Corsi mileage
Quite honestly I will come around
Trial start
A lot of this is stuff
What will see you
In that report there is a
Not reliant on the Steele dossier
The possession of the Russian
On October 30th 20
16 Michael Cohen received a text from Russian businessman
Risk.
Stop the flow of
Perm Russia butt
Just so you know...
Georgi said tapes refer to compromise and tapes of trump rumor
Be held by personas
Associated with Russian real estate
Conglomerate
Crocus group
I'm not real
I'm just saying that I wasn't about it just got a whole lot cuz that's not the
The Steele dossier
Text messages that they recovered from
Michael Cohen
What if I remember correctly though
The theory that they had for that was they were f****** with Michael Cohen
Shut up a pizza
Guys were actually just
F****** with Michael
Invisalign
Pauses at bars press conference
Bank of
You don't really know what
First the report details efforts by the internet research agency
Ties to the Russian government
Is so social Discord among American voters
Information and social media operations
You don't watch RT now it's the most leftist
Alex
Mueller report is real
Just evidence
Republican
Conservative
Like I tried to bribe them
To lie about Trump
Really don't think so
It's only proof
That they tried to pay Republican
But I read it
There was a lot of proof
Nope
Sorry
None of them
Independent
Sound effects I have to fall asleep to thunderstorms every night as a white noise machine
Americans and their enemies over weird
That's the
I don't know
It's up dehumanizing
Still like I guess
Their enemies they deserve
Whatever
Bigot
I'm not saying what to do with that check you nowhere to go to the bad guy it doesn't mean that's not literally what he say
You know we know from living long enough and know enough history to that
That's the directions to sort of rhetoric tends to take pens to go get better
Like it's not like you
Start from a position of
This group politically disagree with
Members of our society
And then you're like
And you know what two weeks later I think they're great
Towards that never ends with
Look these guys aren't Americans
There are enemies
But they've got some pretty good ideas and I think we should hear him out
That goes
Alex
You can always listening to this William Barr thing
The reason I yelled BS
Earlier
But wasn't the Russians it was the Democrats who hired the Russian
Alex does not believe it was a rush
Talk about a little bit
Where's the beef will see what he saw prophet
Where's the proof that I send the report
As we know it
Cotton on
Amazing
It isn't made
Conspiracies without having to take the risk
Narrative
Hillary Clinton is actually in bed with Russia
And so she's sold off
The gru0 Russian operative
Manager
Please email in an effort to
Do you understand how stupid that sounds
Both of those
Arkansas
They're very difficult to hold as
Famous Amos
Professional cognitive dissonance would still have trouble with that
Kahoots but also
Hamster
He's done this
This makes sense that
It wasn't Russia behind
She's actually Secret
Just stated Stockbridge leaked the information
Wikileaks on Hillary killed
In the present-day he's being sued by murder
Cautious but creating more of those situations
It's been pretty clear that they're sick
To keep his name out of his mouth
But
Is that explanation for the Providence of emails goes away he's left with having to accept that Russia
Email of the person that they were working with in order to help the person who is running against
Which is a tough needle thread
Alex needs the Seth rich
Narrative
He has to be
So he just uses the part of it that you just
The idea that download speeds work
Too fast
In order for it to have been
You couldn't get this over the
It had to be a flash drive
Memories download
Right
We didn't have the technology to put things in the air
Information from William Binney
A man who
Public Storage Chicago
He began appearing only on
Conspiracy shows and eventually became
His credibility is
My favorite examples from our show Alex's show pretending that he had a copy of the classified
Devin Nunez Memo from me
Latest and very old
Betty White
Benny is part of a group called the veteran intelligence Professionals for
VIP
It's unclear how many members of this group there are
And honestly who gives a s***
They were formed in January 2000
Inspired by
The intelligence that was being used by the bushes
Administration to go to war
Their first effort stands up to historical scrutiny quite well
The wrestler work is scattershot
What are the reasons for that is that their members often don't agree on that
One Wing of the group were released a memo about
Released
So they're like The Strokes
You know they had a really great first album around
I would agree or disagree other than The Strokes first album
In July 2017
Someone who only
I'm not making that up the forensic
So this people argue that there's no way that the DNC files were copied by a
Because the size of
Copy
Sprint possible to square with a physic
Impossible download
How many reported this
F******
Who naturally this
I gave it to you.
The credibility
Here's this group of Veteran intelligence professionals thing that it's literally impossible for this to have been hacked
So therefore
Even got the forensic cater to sign off
I mean
What
Sentences to use
Alex started promoting this narrative let everyone know that William
Leatherback and it was
Impossible that Russia hacked
Unfortunately people started to do some examination of the claims
Complete
The forensic cater cater
That's what
Klein Center
Technology
Did analysis and found that the memo
Some really faulty
Assumption
He found it while the claim that the download speeds required to copy all the
Formation in the time allotted
Using Comer
Internet
Connections available from like Xfinity
Say you were
Pru so speeds
Those speeds variety of other digital Communications configuration
A high-speed business-grade internet service provider an interoffice local area
Communications
Servers with
Cloud provider and even said yes those speeds would be what you did with flash drive also but there were other possibility
It would have to download it
10 megabytes per second and we don't have the technology
All these possibilities were just discounted by the VIPs memo because they were working
Towards the Flash
Flash drive conclusion as opposed to
Considering all possibilities
Is a good reason to
After the memo was used as a basis for an article in the nation other members of
Navigation
Speak up and point out that they didn't agree with it
The conclusions being put forth
These other memos chastise the writer of the original memo for not including any qualifier
Dissenting views
Nor offering any alternative Theory
Representing their argument is a quotes
They some of their feelings
The bottom line
This rips memo was hastily written based on analysis of third-party analysis
The Friend Locator
I've been thrown against the wall
What would stick
There's only one reason to hold on to this
Impossible download
Be documented this
Husband on on it
The only reason
Conspiracies long past their expiration date and
It's bad
It's real it's really bad
That's what I was doing
David Naughton
Confirmer
I wasn't good
The idea that in the Mueller report
Chances of trump
Clearly obstructing justice
As I read it
Which is
What are the
Justin things everything I
Keep reading about
So all lacrosse
People bring a lot of Their Own
Yeah yeah
Basically
Muller concluded
Obstructed
And
Conclude that there were
No collusion because that's not really
Would be impossible
Impossible to prove
Because everybody was lying or destroyed
Clear him of Illusion
Conspiracy he said
We couldn't prove we were unable to confirm
Saying we were unable to prove that this mob boss killed everybody because for some reason nobody's testifying
I was looking over like
Trump's answers to questions
Whatever at the bottom
Isaac
You can find text message
Your emails and stuff and help
Build
More understanding
Just read it over Trump Sukkot answers as
Who didn't think that was what's going to happen
Just like I don't remember if the truth
And then as far as the obstruction
Total of 11
A based on every kind of
Prosser
Acute Oriole review of that
If they had
They would get a conviction in two weeks
Right right
You wrote them a conviction
To actually convince him because it
With against the justice
Department memo
Right right
Started from the point of
We are not going to convince him of a crime
Describe and then Congress
If you were a functioning tomorrow
Receive
Yeah so yeah
Trump did that
Obstruction that are reference
Constantly
Hello stuff for Alex to get around whoops
The area obstruction
Blue
America
Guitar Blood temperature
You would have struck Justice
You at
What's play that out
Alright alright
Be like Alexa
I always loved it so much
You don't know who that person is
My favorite part
Are so ridiculous just because
It's like
Every part of the Mueller report that isn't a
A direct
Look like proven obstruction of justice is always
Because it was
Go commit instruction of Justice you possibly can do you like telling McCain
Fire
Notes
My other Lords don't keep notes
You're the notable
Yeah
Distinction to that like
Obstruction of justice doesn't require an underlying crime
Obstructing justice
For whatever reason
For his body
Showing your car whatever
Enemy
Globalist coach Warren to conquer the nation
Well I mean cool what are you doing
What are you what are you doing
I mean you're telling people to put up signs anime
You're saying they're sworn to
To destroy the country
All right you know
Now you don't want to
Executed innocent man on death row so you make sure that everything is taken care of we have to leave all you have Democrats alone because
Whatever is whatever the case
That's pretty
I made some of the people that he
Clearly
Media Democrats
There are people who
Maybe some of them work for the New York Times
True
Show many New York Times article on the front page of the website
That would be
Is true I will always err on the side of Truth when he says he didn't read
What is there so many front-page stories in the New York time about
Because you read them
Such liar
It's crazy
I don't believe it Alex's
Ever been on the
Maybe like when the Sandy Hook
Lawsuits broke or something like that
But I can't imagine
What would I say
The over-under is
Is 3 1/2 *
You think so
That's why I took the under
If I was going to lay odds on this one if I was
Vegas betting over unders two and a half
Alright
Somehow I want to have this over under B- one-and-a-half just in case
Just in case they
They put him on the New York Times front page one time and then
Ripped all of them off
A couple times
Him being on there
You think maybe I could really like
Oh he wouldn't be the headline
Under the fold
I don't know seriously
Exaggerating
Wedding announcement of the f****** globalist New York Times
So Alex got a call from
From The New York Times
Reporter who wrote the story
Video I think
No nevermind
This is about
Talking about that New York Times article the writer who called him different guy
Different guy
He's on the cover of the New York Times
The story
Also
They said you need to
Operator conversation
What
Detroit Bass
Against the Republic
Point of order Alex's at this point turned on trop like 4 times
Call me again
New York
What's the reason
What are the three
People say things are off the Record
Agree to it
Right if part of your Converse I've never talked to you
Need to bring that child deals with off the Record
You made you made the both like
Remember scaramucci's article or is like I thought that was off the Record
Why would you think that
Also a lot of the time whenever things are off-the-record you're not allowed to talk about them
Not just who said so
He's holding to some sort of journalistic standards
He's making a voice modulator so we couldn't even tell
Who the person was
And the first thing the guy said was
New York Times robot
That's good babe
That article
About himself
The New York Times
To talk about
Consolation prize
Unfortunately part of the text that said
Does he have commanded us to see Jones you know we can't get drunk
Controller consolation prize in Westbury
For the horrible miscreant
With one of their people just got caught trying to fire bomb
New York yesterday
There's no evidence that that was one of the last
One of their people
Open up there's no indication that I was just making s*** up something like that
Does classical logical fallacies
F*** off with that nonsense
The reason that Alex is talking about this
This article
It's really stuck in his craw is the idea
That the article is pointing out under oath in the deposition
Provide any evidence
Of the claims that he was making about Sandy Hook
Particularly the incident of him talking about there
Someone arrested in squash
Deer in the woods
So Alex is decided
No Alex no
This next
God damn it burns get in here where are you
Next
Clip is
There's something going on here
Article
Well
Newscast
So you just end up playing the clip city-based
2 conspiracy on the first time what's going on
Credibly f*****-up
He's talking about there's something up here is that he is
Now found out Chris Murphy
Blumenthal
Classic vaudevillian Duo
Murphy apparently ran on
What
That's what Alex is alive and then
Is like related to somebody works at a business of some sort
Conspiracy
To our attempt because of Sandy Hook because there's some grander conspiracy but also Alex
You to know that there's a second shooter that he believes it's still all the way okay
Just trying to add like Amicus brief
Is he trying to get a class action lawsuit you have a class-action defamation lawsuit
You could
I think
You know he's
Propound
So why not make the
Everyone
I don't know because it's not what he's doing isn't illegal
Like
Second shooter
Stupid KFC double down which is not illegal
But it's f****** stupid
Play zeze
These videos
System news articles
That justify his like this
I will see how good these
Grill
This is an article on
Skeptoid
Is a blog post
There was a drill that overlap with the shooting
Shooter drill
Also Alex
Not want to drop
Article as it very clearly says the idea that attacks on drills are related
This Theory seems to have caught fire thanks to a post from Alex Jones at the light Mike Adams
Conspiracy
It goes on
Also have to realize that for the few times drills and Terror attacks coincided with each other
Conducted without
Or anything unusual happen
You just don't hear about them because there's no reason to
Nothing happened doesn't make for much of a conspiracy
After all
Well the headline that Alex
Read
Used to look good for Alex
Does point the body of the article is actually a condemnation of his world
Try and exploit
I feel like this is a theme on
People really
What is a stupid
So he comes up with another piece of information from you know
Right around
Sandy Hook
Cites potential
Suspects
A witness
3 months later
February
He's spreading
Wow
This isn't
Suspicious at all
This article came out on February 5th 2030
Only 54 days after the
Shooting reasonable to believe that the investigation was still very much ongoing
Healthy ideas
DEA thought there were multiple
Suspect
Totally accurate based on the article
The article goes on to
The quote to a public affairs officer
Whenever you conduct an investigation you don't speculate as to where it's going to take you
As I said we're going to look at every single thing every piece of material and we'll take it from there
The article explains that the
The DEA was concerned about
To the case because it would quote identify person
I'm cooperating with the investigation
Navigation
Oh yeah what is their names got out and some crazy conspiracy website which
Just go
Give their names out maybe
Mixer people
I thought that they were
He didn't specifically say that it was dangerous because the secret other shooter would get them
Their safety
Is your point
Conspiracies about Sandy Hook we're already running
Fullsteam
This isn't the basis for
Conspiracy theory
Conspiracy theories flying around her pretty
Very easily were able to stop.
Nasyid
Talk about in the article that the idea there could be other possible
Talk about other suspects in the
The shooting for possibly investigation
Or something like that
The idea of online contact
He could have had
Suspect doesn't mean suspect in the shooting
Necessarily
More suspect of a larger investigation
Is another
Entirely sensible
Interpretation of that article
That we've seen where
The shooter was
The only crime you know they got their guns legally they got all that stuff legally
It was just the the one crying
But they're also tons of other time
X wear that one crime
Was the culmination of 15 other crimes
That had to happen
To get there
You know
At this point alexplayz that video
Helicopter
Footage of the three cops
Together
Pierced
Cuz one of them is dressed differently than the other
I thought you was just going to show the footage from Rocky
Before we're Rocky and Apollo Creed we're running
That's one thing
Nick begich takes over Rocky
Great
So Alex plays this video
Proof
Black shirt camo he's in the grass
That's not true
They don't have gun
Nonsense
The videos of them
Is casually walking
This guy at all
And we already talked about that what's going on
So big ears
I'm not sure how I feel
What's
No Doubt
On the one hand I think this is
Kind of funny
But on the other hand
Scary about with the consequences
Could be
Based on Alex's Behavior over the past week
I'm pretty convinced that Alex Jones
Is confused
About what happened in late 2012 and early
I get the sense
But he doesn't remember the arguments
Most likely because you just can't get him
Now because he was confronted about making up
Members in the woods
Deposition
He feels compelled to go back and
Confirmed himself that he wasn't
Just making that up
Which is a pretty good impulse
Can you find the video
3 cops run
In the woods that looks
He finds this video of a man said he saw the police
Please walking a guy in camo pants
Squad car
He finds this
All these things are examples of
The concept that were taken out of context
In Spanish
Helicopter footage of the three cops don't show in
That's very clearly amiss
And also has been
A responsible way for Alex
The cover this would be the show these
And explain to his audience
It wouldn't jeopardize his legal case right now at all
Eddie would still Chivas desire results
The deposition was wrong about him
He was basically
He was just responding
People who they got it wrong
That would be
Totally fine
It would be humiliating at all
It would be a sensible way to
To present this
These people in this New York Times article or lying about me
I was wrong conclusions that we were led to but it would based on this visit
Alex isn't doing
No no
I get the same
He's having his mind blown all over again
This is just a
Started
There's a second shooter
I'm just worried that what's happening is that Alex watch this helicopter video
His response was
We got that wrong but
I need to retract my apology from a couple of months ago my God I was wrong
I think he's forgotten
That these things are all explained already because they're
There's an energy about the helicopter footage
DEA
I'm inside the multiple Shooters argument
There's a there's an energy behind
Drills
A text
Confluent
I don't know if he's going to but I'm worried this is going to
What is rubeola
How to say the hook denial
Blumenthal and Marie
Murphy Murphy
So that means that he's
Still looking for more evidence that it was to find a new way
To do the same
Amstaff
Present himself as a
Intrepid in the line of
Outright libel slander
But it's it's really weird cuz when I heard
When I heard him first say
Like much earlier the episode did like I found all the stuff that the proves that I wasn't lying
And suppose I could never go
Play that s***
Wow you're not explaining why you were wrong
You're playing this stuff in it
Reinforcing an argument
Question things
But there's a cover-up
Sewage
Well
Private lawsuits are an attack on him probably from
Colin Murphy
That's where this is going to go
Ikea I don't look forward to it
I see him on his bed just throwing
Hundred dollar bills in the air lighting lighting a cigar with a Bernie wants Benjamin like this
This is insane total mess
Call my God what an idiot
Calls if you wants to take calls on the Mueller report
He's not getting a lot of good
Stuff
It's his listeners
Maybe
He was talking about you know I know that
Maligned and what have you but
Would you you're being delusional if you're looking at this
Report you're not imagining Obama's
Can Furious everyone on your side would be
Got to go
I'm so angry at how effective that that line has become
I've just him
Look it was obstruction he was just mad
Stink a lot of people
Look what we need to know in advance
Is that yes
Maybe he obstructed Justice
But he was out of frustration
He was angry
He was having a tantrum
Yeah it was mad that it's legal to commit crimes when you're angry and frustrated with people
Exactly
Alex don't have much time for that guy
Quickly as I thought he would but there's a very short call
Another call and this one he is way more into
This lady is
Democrats are the demon party
I renamed the demon party because they can President Trump clever
Will you know Alex God knows what they're doing
Retired firefighters that I watch on YouTube is it he's from Florida his name is Mark
Taylor
If you never heard of them look them up
Response
Mark Taylor
I don't follow
Complete lunatic
That's right
You probably most notable for releasing a movie called The Trump prophecy in 2018
The movie was based on a book he wrote about
Can 2011 election was ordained by God
Interesting Lee this book came out on August 23rd 2017 and I can find no evidence
Suspicious at all
You know what you tell people the prophecy then it won't come
That's just that's everybody
Taylor claims his prophecy that was confirmed
Funeral
But if you go back to scalia's funeral when they were carrying his body up to
There were two signs that were given by God that the confirmation of Merrick Garland was not going
To happen
The two signs that were given there was a
The reverence
Quiet
The background at the bottom
Steps
Well when they got to the top of the steps
And what the Lord was saying don't fear America
Help is on the way
The siren
This being reserved from my anointed
From the Trump
Train
Crazy
Nut you do it
Enlightenment when a crow dropped a pebble
Into the lake
Channel
Taylor
Mostly
Completely insane qanon
Just last month he released this prophecy
The Lord's Prayer
Another Trump coming
This morning and in the dream I saw Donald Trump jr.
It was just a really quick snippet of it
And then I thought
JFK jr.
I knew it had something to do with JFK Junior and it goes on to say that.
Going to run together
Cannot be true because they believe you
Another big problem for the DJ
Situation going on here is that even in Mueller's report
Donald Trump jr. is not
Investigated and indicted committed
It's a good day
What Marine Le Pen being legally a fascist
You know it's like
According to a real person
Christian Broadcasting Network website about the Trump prophecy
Divided nation right now so I hope this film can be a way to Baby Pointe 14
Is actually an office because the will of God
And the people who are
That's something you might do if you were interested in installing a theocracy
Which is totally
Which is healing
Everybody else went to everybody who has been hurt
Ventec
Insanely
$2000000 is what
2 million-dollar budget
It's all on the screen
I'd like for you to try
Well are we
Gross or net
I don't know
Cuz I'm ready to go with net I'm going to say
-2 million-dollar
No
It made 607
They have an elevated bottom
How much
Desperate 10 be like buses of no church groups
There's a built-in
Is a good way to guarantee you're going to make
Pile
You got an audience we could make a movie for likes
15 grand
At most
And make six hundred
No we couldn't
Cuz I'm not doing it
Also in September 2018 Mark Taylor other internet
Are going to declare martial law
Iview martial law under this Administration
That was their plan all along but are now we're going crazy
A.m.
So excited that people like
God dammit because he calls himself a prophet
Supposed prophecies
Trump is the leader that will lead us out of the desert
You know all that sort of s***
What
Global World Government
It's demonic is going to put us in FEMA camps
There were power but now that's actually really good because we can do it to them
Yeah there's another path
C-walk similar paths
Yeah you're absolutely right
Yeah I like Mark Taylor he's a good guy or whatever I thought that was
Dismissive
Yeah because it usually is kind of recommend other people
To me this is my show what's the point of fighting right but
Weird fake Christian prophet
For Humanity is destroyed Jack Dorsey will be destroyed
Thunderbolt
White shawl
Can a process
Jack of Twitter
She didn't say he was a prophet
He knows Mark Taylor is I don't know
Seagame sohee
He's jumping in on that prophecy
She was talking a lot about demon
Guns and stuff like that
I'm not totally sure but either way it doesn't really matter it's just illustrates
F****** world
So connected
So f*****
Why
Gas-lit like this so hard life of Alex
The Democrats have no bottom
You
I can't
Where are we
So weak
Weak-willed
The present
Committed
The Democratic Leadership is like
Let's let him
Run roughshod over the country for the next
18 months and then
The forest
Hayden
Sure
There's not any consequence
Cranston the globalist of power
Alex
That's true
So right
They have no bottom
If you if you don't allow Alex what won't you do
If you take Alex off
Facebook
Absolutely
The political aspirations of
Someday they will people keep Point Mark Taylor prophecy
These globalist
Interesting is almost
Of coverage
Stories
You know Notre Dame burning
Aspire was built in the 19th century
Doesn't mean it's any less tragic
What's it from
11:00
Feel like I'm minimizing I don't mean to
Spitfire
If you want to enjoy the Notre Dame
Therefore you have
You know the Mueller report coming
Sammy's great
Yeah or no
Really at all
Alluc in the aftermath of note is to make everything about
Is that all you have
Aftermath of his mother is
A very predictable this is a cover up for what
Hillary Clinton was doing need that report
Pocket matter
We'll see what happens
Most excited about the prospect
Sandy Hook
Actually I'm not
Cuz
It's not you can't enjoy it
No
Like I said it's
Hilarious
People's lives
It would be very very funny that this
Stupid assholes forgot the
Conspiracies
But he was telling Emma
Got very excited about the New Year's Eve
Is right this whole time
People tell me that I was like
Go to the Sandy Hook victims houses
Dammit man
Itsfunneh on paper
Yeah
Not funny in real life
Now I walked myself
Full circle
Zaltrap
You know what's interesting
There's a very real parallel
Notre Dame burning down but they're being a perfect digital
Recreation of
Inside of a video
Isn't that
Anything isn't that
Exactly like
You dying
Food for thought
Food for eyes
You can buy the new shirt and call Larry Nichols
Federal Building
Missy Elliott I don't expect anyone to be able to remember that stuff
Yep we're on Facebook
Leave a review at
Cetera
So I guess
We come to the end of this
Anna
What is Bernie impressions
I don't know if that's true but you know what
Who does that impression
We probably had
Alex