Alex
Sit around
I don't know where that came came from but it
That look on your face made with you a lot
Wake up Olaf
Dark metallic dress
Vanilla in the house then I've no idea what it is
Bring up what novelty beverage
But this time I thought of you because
How quickly I often
Find novelty
Is that you came in with this orange Vanilla Coke
Had it already
A quick
Do you know what I almost
I generally end up going
Just as an
To get out of the house almost
Like all end up at the
The store or Walgreens or something you know
I have a lot of excess
2 what's new
I tried to Eminem
Cuz I thought it would be like a Nutella filled
Yeah it's not bad but it wasn't
I nearly it was between
Orange Vanilla Coke which I just took a taste of it is absolute it's not a whip
Today but from my
My first voyage with it
I can say it's not a
7-Eleven
Branded Sour Patch
Soda
Looking at 10
What if I hurt
To feel alive
You did get that cotton candy energy drink
Should have been way worse
Subtle flavor of cotton candy
I know a lot about
Jordan
Today is my birthday
Well when it comes out
If it'll be coming out on my birthday
No different than any other time
You look great
F*** you
Yeah me what can I do I can rent a car now is that okay
President
Yeah whatever it is 35
I'm on my way
I'm heading to the government
Day of my birthday
To take over the last year
35 is benzo
Instrumental in helping create this thing
That can be my job
I'm very passionate about never
Facilitated
Makes it possible
Makes it so enter this year with
Something
I'm far more meaningful in my life then I had years ago
They would not be possible without them
I'm so
You know what I was going to get it
I was going to get to talking about appreciating you as well
I need for thanks
You didn't let me get to it naturally and now
If you if you think of wanting
To give me anything for my birthday
You already have
But if you do want to
If you want to find the door
There's that on the website
Dollartree.com
Navigation bar
The shirts
So you can find. That's up there with that
Wonderful
In appreciation
Like to start this
Episode does Badoo
All of our episodes
No
Weather thank you
So first
Text Brian
But with a y
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Young bae
Thank you so much you are now apology walk
I gave you
Next
The Soros Foundation
Soul vampires little long
Why we thank you so much
You are now about to walk
Thank you for a citation for definitely not being globalists all vampires
Next
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
Thank you very much
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
Jesus
Thank you so much
Just for the show
There's a link that says support
On our website I was right there, quite there but
For my birthday
There's only thing
I want it for
What's that
So
I decided that
Cheetos
Too much time going over last
I was considering doing the Wacky Wednesday
I have more info
Try and that is backing
Empath
Early 20s
Alex Jones
He was up to
In the aftermath
Ice as the fee
We were about to get
For my birthday I want
We do
You'll be going over the days of January
Out of context drop
Seem to be like contradiction
I don't
Okay
Darwaja rapport
I really really don't like Cameron I love Jon rappoport
We don't have any clips
Cuz my dad
Was in
He was in New York
He was going over
Do Piers Morgan show
Work
36 will commence
Dargun
He acted like a big old baby
Went home
Maybe I don't know
I don't know how much that was a stage
And enjoy what we
What's going on I don't know it's hard to say if you want to hear our coverage of that we went over it like
Like a year ago
So we have an episode
Let's goes over Alex
Piers Morgan interview
I think it was from December 31st
Of 2017
Go back
Find
What we thought about that interview
You'll never know what we think about Mike Adams
Cuz we're not talkin about it
Alex Gibbs
Excuse for why
Episode
Hours
35 minutes ago
National Airport
Hey Alex
We landed 35 minutes
I sent Austin to Alex's Studio
35 minutes before he's on air it's just literally impossible
I would say our Mack
Do you think we landed
35 minutes
Get off the plane for another fit
Splitting hairs
But you know what
People's good
Energy
Feels good
Nailed it on Piers Morgan show
Auburn
Shamas
Not sure where I put my wallet
I wanted to thank you
In your wallet
Notes in your wallet I wrote plan to
Napkin
The airplane I put in my wallet
My wallet
So I forgot to
Said I really think
Harris wittels
Give myself about an
Yeah
I feel it's always presumptuous
Give yourself a name
You can't give yourself
You can give yourself a b
Imli allows at
The height of
Hubris
Himself Curtis's
I give myself a B on that
Unheard of
That's the
Icarus levels
Can you imagine
Giving yourself
100%
I don't need anybody
Good job
A+
Uno
Rocoto
He's the only person who's in charge
A+
Piers Morgan
You know what
You know what he saying
I was awesome
I stood up and I told him
Hollister
Interesting about his
Piers Morgan is he kind of admit
You only started
To get him deported
Has Morgan deported for attention
But it's nice
First Amendment
Obama
At the end of the show
Respond
Signatures
What are most important values
Morgan wants your guns
Afraid
I knew that this would be something that would
Was explaining
About
Strategy
Oh we'll talk about Glenn Beck and Alex Jones
Publicity back
For that
Alex knew the Piers Morgan probably talk about how Alex
It's going to be great
I would give him an A minus probably disease
Yelled a little less from his listeners
Episode
Some people thought he look like a buffoon
It would it would be
Chakra see where I
To criticize anyone for amount
That's true
Not me I could pretty consistent
Appling way to talk about
Critical perspective
Was a Yeller
Is very very loud
And people would
Distantly
Insulting
Make me feel like s***
Animated me
It turned into
Complex
Just why I have a deep voice
But I try and see
Much softer
Nowadays
Later in life
I worked
A job train
In that clip to saying that the Obamas
The administration
I was forced to respond to his petition to pour Piers Morgan
New York and Alex is going
To use that
2 thread
Conspiracy
Piers Morgan Giddings the Obama's to respond to it
Because the NN is full
Citi
Specifically and everyone around him more generally picture Alex's
Episode involved
Stories of his time there
There's poo smeared on the walls around
So long it's just he's rambling
Was water up
Media operation now there's s*** on the wall everything is it just repair
Is there was nothing else to talk about I probably might have kept
Have some of that
Where Alex
6 planes de Paul Joseph Watson
But he is all over the Press
In the United Kingdom
Gotcha talk about Alex
Would you leave to Alex to talkin about
Books written by Churchill
A startling confession about whether or not he's read those books
On the cover or close to the tavern
Winston Churchill
You read all of them
You want to know the history
English speaking
I guess I'm in Wonderland any other
Speaking paper
There's three books
Television
The story of whatever
Alex is asserting that the British Empire got done sucking off the UK or whatever and then it moved over here
Uses as a source for this
Three parts
The three-volume history of the British Speaking people
I read one of them
Alex
Your whole thing you didn't read everything
Admit that you've only read one out of the three books
Chinese food
My perspective
Entirely
White
You still haven't
I don't know what's going on
Has like a couple books
I'm most of the science picture
I don't understand about it all who cares
So like I told you.
Who's mirror on the wall
Interesting Falls version
Of him going
Go to New York
That one comes in
He tries to turn this into
Thriller novel
Elmore Leonard
This is not
This version of
Alex is going to
Other women
Shopping mall
And
Jersey
I hear there's a lot of candy in New York who got to get out of there
Because
New York
This is
A level of paranoia in
Just
Fabrication of what
I can't remember which movie it was an extension
Yeah they are what movie is nightmare
Thinks he's being followed
Just a guy tried to go to Chili's
The time that you
You decided to put your evidence publicly forward
Of someone following
Being followed
All that sort of bulshit so like
I just hear this and I'm like
Story if you want to put that into six
If you want to write that into some sort of a novel
That didn't happen to you out
Parallel today
Backstory
Island
People who have no hands
And their faces were weather chest
Bananas
You're some big ole Explorer and you feel like you got to tell peep
Maybe you just want to do York and shattered a Morgan that's fine that's still a
You know what to
At least slightly on knowledge
Most of his audience
Probably never been
Canton New York
Maybe a little piece of it that is
I know that's pretty f***** up
Border
Yeah probably wouldn't come back and be like feds chasing a wire
Their version
Falsified versions of the outside world
Might be closer to accurate
New York
Course
This country
From Texas
The first
York
And part of that is just due to immigration and settlement patterns
Pretty much everyone
Europe arrived.
East coast and not all of them ended up heading any further west from there
That's normal
That's a good explanation for why the mafia and they was formed in the Italian Community
End up being in other cities outside of the East Coast
But that doesn't mean there wasn't
Huge organized crime operation out of Galveston
Beginning ammonites
Is a bootlegging operation eventually grow into involved
Protected by bribes to corrupt government officials
That's a good call on her
Closer Alex grew up the Civello crime family was in operation
Dallas from
Neatly covering the gears went out
Would have been living
Dallas
Interesting laid the head of that family Joseph Civello was friends
Jack Ruby
Dallas Nightclub owner killed Lee Harvey Oswald
Superkilen JFK
There been strong indications that Ruby was involved
So I wouldn't
Also also
Song that Alex sings very frequently commercial Eastbound & Down
Roundabout in trucking
There's a line in that song
There's beer in Texarkana Atlanta
But there's beer in Texarkana
And the reason for that not granted that movie is
About Prohibition
That movie is about how Coors didn't have preservatives in it
Tasted better run Coors
From states where they could get it to Safeware it was illegal that preserved
That's why
That's what I really don't remember that being
That's why they have cores
About
They don't necessarily about Prohibition but it Harkens back to
Because I like in Texarkana and around there
Was
There's a history of that in that part of Texas
Organized crime of some sort
That story is more interesting than
Just a guy who needs to get preservative free beer
Crossover is
Because it has the archetype
Elvie's beer runners
From prohibition
It came from
Supercross
It's not all
These families
Along with the eastbound down all the time
Still crazy
E-waste
A lot of time
Looking into
Most children
Organ failure
Most
Fluid
What
You can go pull up Jordan
Okay alright
RX300
Didn't say that
He said 350 said 35,000
2 years
In the middle
You know sometimes it's a lot worse
Sometimes a tire
But that's
KT man
Last year the number of deaths
Flu and flu related complications
Like that
That's official
I would have been more
He said we talked
And just ended this
Adapter
Most children die
And just I put it.
Around a little bit
Find even a Nutty website
Play the flu every year
Ridiculous
No idea where Alex is getting this information from
The guest
The woman who comes on out to show itself
She does sound like Ground Zero for crazy b******* like she called herself a doctor and she sells a $35 card that says I don't
Similarity without
General stubblebine
Who Alex loves
I did also find a post Barbara loaf
Another of Alex is stupid anti-vaccination
Suggested
600/750
Influenza deaths
Record
This post
Information is it
Formation it
To doesn't match this
Conclusion all
The information she links to isn't even a chart of death totals
It's of death rate
So the table might
64 but that doesn't mean 864
That means
864 / 1
Seems like
Like what she's misunderstanding cuz all the information
Stupid that it doesn't say what
Venezia's
It doesn't
She also opposed
Table from Mercola
It does backup harasser
But the problem is
TDS anti-vax Outlet
Depot and Burkholder using the same
DC information as
Thesaurus app for
If I had the
Was just an intentional or possibly more worryingly
National misunderstanding
About the difference
Definite death rates
Even so her fake number
Weis what Alex is it what's going on
Bottom line
And what they're saying
The flu kills a whole lotta people particularly children
That's the reality
Working anymore to try to figure out where he got that 300 number from cuz I can't find anywhere
Yeah
Also also
The very concept
The very idea
Call Madison
Acrostic
Entire United
Aspiring
To blame
On the fluid that had nothing to do with
With the flu and only 300
Children died
Of the flu
Worldwide
Conspiracy
Would be
Unbelievably
Yeah
More than one doctor Whitley
Please come out and say
You know what I remember none of my patients
I think there's probably a conversation
She can have
These people wouldn't be willing to have it cuz it would be nuance
And it would
Go get them excited
Understanding a little bit better how it works
In terms of like flu-related top
Occasions
Better understanding of why those two
6 are lumped in together
The flu and flu complications
Like understanding that better would be a better you
I think
Be better
To do that
Not really
Oh
Play something that they fight tooth-and-nail
Creating existential dread
Fake
Plot against
White people
So stupid
That was kind of a little bit out of left field because Alex's
Bring that stuff up and ranting about it was also a little bit
Out-of-left-field
So it just came up
I know he gets back.
CNN
Aaron dykes
Is in studio one of those reporters
Is sitting around with him
I'm not sure if you
Clip or if it's later but
Know that Alex has a little bit of an audience
Studio
Turn over the table
I said that
Alright man little vain
Lil Wayne
If they went out of their way to make
Saturday
First of all it's
Crazy that Aaron dykes
It's kind of like the globalist
Already we're comparing that to Alex
I would give
To the response if Alex was like
Now hold on that's getting a little bit crazy all I did was go in there
Have an argument yell at this guy
Only is he like reaffirming and doubling down on the idea that he's like
Price for doing this
I can't believe you thought about that earlier
Manifest
Messianic beliefs about himself
Yeah
Jerusalem syndrome
So f****** bad
Yeah
Do you want to go to Israel
But I've heard of that.
I don't know if it's
Very similar
I talked about how much Madonna came back
Right right
Alright
Alex
Discusses what happened
The end of the inner
Morgan has version of
There were detectives follow me everywhere I had to get out of that City
Scared for my life
This also
Piers Morgan tonight at me
Ground
Pretty soon nobody going to want you anywhere in the world
Dysphasia
Lyrics
He just looked at
Alex
2 weeks prior to this reptile
David Icke the f*** out of here
I just think that he's wearing a plastic
Sick mask that I can remove to see his face underneath
Of course
Open space was twitching with fear about the
Integrity
Drinks vitalik manifested
British accent
And Alex
I will believe the first
Pictures of that story
Are we done here are you a coward
Piers Morgan
Yeah sure whatever
It definitely feels like whatever it was
Jordan
We've been doing this investigation into the days after because I wanted
Do have a real long-billed
To find out how Alex felt about the endives headquarters
That is not why we've been trying
Figure out when Alex
Goes
The full mile
And being very awful about saying
Any bad so far
We've heard him
Pretty strongly believe
That it was at least
A false flag
And as much as
The governor
Mainland
The do it killed him as a pet
Or whatever
So far we still believe
Yes
At this point Alex is not
That would make you
Think otherwise
Here we go
Ears with Alex
Happy birthday.
Music that literally sounds ominously like he's about to say
It's really good
Yeah it's almost good production
Oh no
So much so that I didn't notice it like I just felt itself
Oh no this is the first indication of where this is
Oh yeah
This is where the crisis actor narrative
January 23rd
3 weeks and a half three weeks
This develops
The course of the episode
Cuz now that he's got
Most of this
Time is been about
Target
Piers Morgan
Good on you
Have fun
Right
The middle of the shower so
He starts getting in
To Sandy Hook
Text
Calls
And one of the callers
He gets
Actually brings up
But it's not yet
Yes have you noticed how all these reporters
When they're when they're supposed
Seen it seems like they're standing in front of a screen or something like there in a studio
Like whether it's foxy
CVS or MSNBC all the reporters when there's
I don't know I mean to me
Smoking marijuana
Yeah they even had a director there in one of those tall chairs sitting there I mean
At the rank in the military
Run the drill
Understand
Any idea
Set bad
What does Big Sandy Hook narrative
Dakota
What he talks about is the idea of Anderson Cooper's nosed
Disappearing
It's interesting that his justification for believing
This misunderstanding he has about the Gulf War
You know we talked about is no
He was confronted with that information in his deposition
You hear that you hear it.
Pieces
Narrative
Here before he has what he needs that narrative for which is the arguing about Anderson
That's fascinating
The defenses here before The Chronic
That he's got a narrative
Later on for standard
Cooper no
Not that
The idea that his callers are feeding
Internalizing
I think I seen
When is
That the caller isn't even talking about
Anderson Cooper Center
Or anything like that
He is just talking about this in general
Alex
I don't know I
I've heard this conversation
As just
Suffocation
We don't have not heard
Certification for others
As just a standalone
Only exist
And Alex is rhetoric at least in the.
Something about
Cooper
To hear it without Andrew
Justin Cooper
Is weird
What is the color of
Who knows
There's if you have some people there but somewhere actors
That's not good
Dipping the toe
Now that we've talked about actors
77 bombing and others
Because we're going to discuss
Why that's f***** up
You're in a little bit
Who is the professor
What does that mean
He was tenured
Before we get there I want
A little bit
I think this next life is really s***
PetSmart
Got that smart
True introduces is
How do you know which ones are taken which are
Do you know like the idea of like somebody survivors are real
But you know what I'm saying
During the idea that some people were actors there and then
All that does is give cover and allow people plausible
Permission
To say anyone
Anyone
Exactly
Didn't know everyone has to be
Guilty
Is really the only thing that you're going
Allowing everyone to be your f****** actor
But without having to take
Responsibility for that and still be able to hide a little bit like
The fake one
Right
If you don't to be harassed
Or if you are real victims you should be on our side against these other fake people
Maybe one
Totally
That sort of thing is so f*****
Batman Tyler alter
What you hear in that clip is Alex does believe
People died there at 7
People or actors
But that's a facade
That isn't good
To me that clip
Is him
Adopting this
Even though he's
Some people died there
Who cares
That is
Window dress
Now I still don't think that he's as far as he's going to go but this is a
Watershed
Episode
But I think
And maybe part of it is because he's so tired from going
New York City's not being cautious
But also the timing of it does match up because an article about this professor
So maybe it's just one story
It's about a week after that
Professor started talking about
Sandy Hook
I think so
Once you open up
Open up the victim
To harass
Bright
To be harassed
Functionally
I'm saying some are actors
For all
Who who's going to receive
The consequences
Is already
A hundred percent
Show you know I don't know
We can look at those we can see like oh wow okay here's where the dam broke
Basically
But I don't know
Like I don't I still don't
I don't know I don't know if it's okay for him to say these things
I'd rather
Court of douchebaggery I will pronounce
Guilty
Call her now calls then
He's gone in the car
The car and Alex
Gives what appears to be a restrained
Amerigo's real bad
Yeah well. That thing is a mama msad15
I understood that the AR actually stayed in the car can you clarify
What actually happened with what we actually use
My Good Ol Boys
South Florida sun-sentinel professors Church controversy by
Dispute
4 conspiracy theories
Diversey
Call
If you believe believe is he Rambles even further off course
Doesn't really get back
2 after his
Contract
But the caller is calling me whether or not this done was taken into the school
Doesn't know
At this point
Ary
Makar
But I know at this point
I don't want to say what I think right now or whatever
Should have been his lying
Or entirely
What happened
Let's wait till the information is out there that's
But without missing a Beat
After he says everyone's waiting
For me to say what I think
Goods back to the story
Of this Florida Professor who says
And then the article says that he's a conspiracy theorist and Alex attacks the idea that
What is what gets him off course into the
Ted Bundy fantasy
He has a weird first person
Narrative
Literary devices
It's great to be a
But from time to time
Maybe you're just talking about what you
It feels a little like that
Philo personal
Has the most
Infowars
Exactly
Imagine what an Infowars
Caller would sound like
The speed of the
Trails off
Infowars voice
Yeah B
Unless interested in the collar as I am Alex
These thoughts
Whether or not it's intentional or
Completely soaked
I think that it's a pretty strong and
Navigation
He believes
Is mirrored by what this professor
From
A structural standpoint how's that
That train
I went down the tracks unfair assumption
He was
Reading through the Arctic
Whenever It Came Upon them question
Why he was saying
Right
Considered a conspiracy
It's kind of like
Can get another pretty strong
Alex
Professor
Control
Really gives me a strong
But Alex
Is trying to
I think he feels like he's responding the way he does a lot of times when something new comes up
Turn off this for a long time
Almost trying to one-up it like we saw him do that with qanon with the fake Zach
Yeah this is intelligence
Reclaim
The cube storyline
He feels like he's getting ready to do that with this
Professor is come up in his world and saying like there's these crisis actors
Who are actually what's going on
I think Alex might take that as a little bit of Anna
Front
I feel like I've known that forever
Yeah
It sounds like a
Normal kind of progression for him
He wouldn't he would never have gone that
It's possible he would have gone that far but the impetus is almost always
For him to like
Kick the kick the ball another 10
10 yards down.
Because somebody else
Went a little bit further
Evolutionary arms-race
For him going back and forth with
Evolutionary and motivation or
Just like acknowledgement that he has internally that if he doesn't he doesn't have a place in the market
Like whatever it is
You know I need to be more extreme than other people or else what good am I
I'm not interesting
I'm interested in someone
Sorry someone is coming in with this level of crazy
That's I'm screwed
So Alex keeps bring up his Florida professor
Florida Atlantic
The guy's name is James
I believe that this episode is the official beginning of
Crisis actors
December 9th
Episodes from 2012
Adjusted Robbie Parker was acting
Like an actor
It is Prescott
That's pretty trouble
Traduction
We have we have Alex taking these ideas much more
In late December 2012 number very obscure blogs were starting to propagate theory that victims
Survivors of
The shooting at Sandy Hook
They're basing this off of website run by a group called vision
Do a crisis actors
For hire
They offer the experience actors who could improvise within the framework needed for the drills
This isn't anything new there were usually called role-players
The past
And they've been used in
Any sorts of situations
Forever
The only thing that was different about the
Is it the name was new
Crisis.
And it was
It was way scarier
And people latched onto it
It really isn't in Fort
I was reading over a bunch of emergency
Responders
Discussing
Role-player
Crisis actor
And one of the things
Especially for medical First Responders
You need someone who can
Because yeah you know like if you
You're running a scenario where for training purposes
You have people who are
First Responders who were showing up
And someone is like I have a heart attack
That doesn't help them diagnose now on the Fly
My arm is jingling in this otherwise
Diseases or a condition
2%
Allowed
Situations like
Is obvious
Exactly what you would do
And it's not something
That's uncommon
Or hasn't
For very long time
But they calling a crisis actors
Add these people offering
Them on their website
Maybe
People create
A bunch of bulshit
That's okay December 2012
These weird obscure blog started talk
And at that point most of the attention
Should be paid to the sort of ideas
Some sources that were decidedly on what I would call
The Project Camelot
Motherboard did a little bit of a
Deep dive into
The crisis actor RV
Kmart from where particularly one-place
Websites
The post said that the hook was a drill alongside the
The suggestion that quote
The timestream aspect is more
Compelling given the interval of 7 days prior to the
December 21st 2012 solstice
Ritual bloodletting is Beka balls method for internal power prior to especially when
It's important
Right idea being a part of a lot of websites like that
Apocalypse
Types
A lot of sorts of ideas
Speed of this Theory germinate
But it wasn't
Auto January 1st 2013 post on his blog James Tracey Road
Quote after such a heroine event why are selected would be family members
Students lingering in the area in route
The offering themselves for interviews
A possible reason
Working under the direction
Federal authorities
It in coordination with cable and broadcast network talent to provide TaylorMade crisis acting
It realized realized
Berkeley drive home the event
Tragic feature
James Tracey by virtue of being a college
Professor legit
Heading to a world of
Things College professors think are worth considering
It's a very big difference
To have a lunatic
On-time stream typa blog
Even though you can have lunatics your credibility
Yeah
The veneer of respectability of plausibility
With the inclusion of a college professor
As well as amplify
Theory well outside
Security that it was
Before
As motherboard points out quote
A search on Google Transit lines
This timeline
Searches for crisis actor only register on the site after Tracy
These blog posts motherfuker
Right
God dammit
Closed
Alex Jones disgusting
The professors Court Reporting is a major
So the crisis actor
Narrative writing
Troubling development
To see this
Even Tracy's writing about the topic didn't raise it to a level where you might call that sort of an idea culturally relevant
What does signal booster
To come from a theory be
Being discussed
Any credibility
Alex's show
Huge
Support strong
Where is absolutely necessary
And maybe we should also
Tenaya major shooting happened
Then 10 years worth
Fired from his position at FAU
His post
It wasn't a First Amendment issue in the firing was accurate
Correct
Cu the professor the rules
Needed to report other sources of income to the university
Which is blog qualified
The two brought in the required
Limani
Additionally used University equipment
Recorded
Podcast
Without reporting that
They fired him for not following the rules
Not because of the
Disgusting
He said well not follow
There's a difference
Argument is Alex
Somebody's questioning techniques
Sending Lenny Posner a certified letter demanding proof that his son was ever alive
And that he was actually his father
This was a response to
Depositor filing a copyright claim on one of the pictures of
What is Sun The Tracey was using
Pushes conspiracy
When positive didn't agree with b******* demand
Tracy Guzman non-response as evidence the people are covering things up and
Did they have something to hide
Is it they didn't have
Something to hide how hard would it be to prove it there with you
Exact
That's how hard it is
Is go f*** yourself
Exactly
Tracy was involved in was harassment
He was directly harassed
Some victims band
And Alex Jones gave his idea the platform and helped spread them
On January 8th 2013
A write-up
Founder of
And since then
Tons of Art
Rain
Egyptian
Not sure exactly what what's going on there
I don't know
As recently as November 27th
Infowars has posted articles
Discussing his firing as being a free-speech issue and
Simplifying the perception
Of James Tracey
God dammit
This is all loaded bulshit
I would say that I bet anything
Tracy will show up
The cast in the near future
But they'll be unfair because I already know that
Of course
How could you not
We got the
Of course
The meme kid
Yeah
This guy
I will say
The only thing I have
To say regarding Tracy
Aspiring
Is that yes
He probably did
Get fired
And you did not follow the rules
But
There are probably could have given
I'm a slap on the wrist
As opposed to
Completely firing
Denying a school shooting is probably affect her and why they
Enforce those rules so strongly
I would say that it possibly
One of his arguments is like because I said these things and they wanted me gone
You f***** up even worse victims are actors and stuff like that
Because otherwise yet
You open up the door for them to fire you for cause
Where is it
Are you then you could sink this ship
Because you're so f******
Stupid
I told you to keep in mind the 7/7 bombings
After these blog
Started to talk about crisis actors
Use data
Sandy Hook
The idea started to work
Backwards
People started to make theories
After
These ideas came out about past events at them
When those actual event
Exactly
There are arguments that are starting at around this time
That
2 past events
As opposed to
We talked about it
Bulshit
I call foul
I want I want pictures
We can't do that
Alex probably did talk about the idea of
Like
He did you know we talked about like people doing the shootings were an actor
Those sorts of ARG
Used arguments of
False flag
Whole cloth different party
Who's doing it to rile up
The party you think it it
There were actors who are victims
And stuff like that
I don't remember hearing that
In other time
Games prior to
Turn Alex's coverage of other
Really interesting because it never occurred to
Like
About whether or not I'd heard the crisis actor narrative
Sandy Hook
Because I was always just
I just assumed if we had heard that if we were hearing the prices
Narrative
That means that
Probably heard
But I don't remember anybody you're right I don't remember anybody
They think they were after 2
I don't know if I would be
Real stupid
To sit here until
Absolutely
I bet that those sorts of ideas did live somewhere
The popularization of it in the application of it
It's a past event
Absolutely
For certain that Alex is 100%
But I know that the conspiracy world
Engageny
Savior
Do some of it
Rewriting
What is narrative
To fit this new hot
Conspiracy angle
Yeah that's
Because it's just
It seems like one of those things
Where
And it is a fun fact
Everything started
Golden neighbor fortnite
Team 10
Vision-box organization
Offering
So deep
Said before
Before this point
Behind it some of them
Could have existed
Invariably
Not to the level that it did afterwards
Was hanging around
Conspiracy blogs and message boards around this time
I do remember it's like taking off like wildfire
Like I remember the idea of Crisis actors
Coming up and it being
Like new to look into
As opposed to like being high key
Yeah that that's worth
It's really weird to think about
More looking into this as we
We go along
Because now that it's in
Alice's
That boxes that box is open
It's never closing
Until there are no more
Yeah
Lots to talk about
I don't think this is
Call me Gary
I promise to Jones House praying for you last night
You went in the video
Can you put it on late at night
A couple
CNN comments that tie into a
Sandy Hook, even though I know you said you don't really want to
Confirm
Shrimp
That's a damn to that
Respond
Now that's a no-go
Whatever Smoking Gun
News about Sandy Hook
Usually
You would assume that that is him saying
Aurora
He's trying to
New York
So go with it everything that you believe is now go with
People prove their children other children
So his next clip Alex gets off that
Charlie Sheen
You was on the phone with
Denise Richards
Charlie Sheen
The phone
And he accidentally insults her without knowing it
Talk to her
Charlie Sheen sitting there ever sit around his pool and he hands me his phone he says they talk all the time
How is it going
I got pictures
Bongos click
And then
Is it, guys definitely saying
He's on heroin
And then like a month later I'm in the grocery store
And it was that pug
The story cuz I am
Asian gentleman that I worry about my God
Denise Richards
A year ago
All I hear is guilty conscience
Alex killed that dog that's why.
I have it from good DHHS sources
He called her and gloated about it
How's your dog doing
Dogs
They come up
You more than
Statistically
Reasonable
Music nut
You think about
You think of
I don't know
Not outside.
Do dogs die when they're around
Yeah. All you doing is cutting out every time I was talked about a dead dog
Not proof recently Alex talked about
The song about Denise Richards
Okay
Legend
Amazon Logan Paul show
Logan Paul's dog
Allegedly
Know what I'm saying is that he talks about dead dogs even more than
We talked about
Pretty wild
Earlier you said that you know 13
Smoking guns
Sandy Hawkins
You know
Aurora
York was fake
It is next clip you gets a like
Really fundamental piece of
Information wrong about the Aurora shooting
It makes me think that maybe
I'm not going to trust you about others
Murder
The reason that
There was a bunch of people
If you don't know how many people died in this event that you're weaving a massive
Conspiracy about
I don't believe you
I know that it seems like a trivial thing the difference between 12 and 14
But if you study this stuff
If you're researching it the way the Alex says
Then you know that
You know these trivial details
Like if you and I were extemporaneously talking about Sandy Hook and you said that 29 or 30 people die
I wouldn't that was
You don't know anything
About it
Navigation that you don't study
Yeah you're not putting forth some
I'm sort of the crazy
You have permission
To be off
About slight
Because I didn't really tell you I didn't really read into it before I would rather you know details
Dumb
It's a damning indictment of your opinion
About XYZ whatever my theory is
It sure is a damning indictment
For sure
He
I can't I can't handle this trip
Correctly
Wiki marveling that there were a
Murder in
Murder
But only
In his words
Does he not realize that if you open
Fire on a
Close movie theater
You have committed attempted murder on everyone in that movie that he doesn't
Understand
He doesn't understand
Come close to getting a reading comprehension
Stevens
Attempted murder
I think it's probably just dumb
Little own it just
Attempted murder
Gets back to complaining
Talks about how art
Is criticizing
A little bit
Authority
This point cuz he hasn't been allowed back on yet 2016
Good back on Max Keiser show Stillmatic
And this is some of the other early
Conspiracy mirror
It's on
You're misinterpreting all that stuff.
I mean artista
The school
You can't defend yourself
For making a
Conspiracy out of
Misreporting at the immediate
Aftermath
You have to
Giving out you have to be enough of an adult
To understand that some details are going to be
Bierock particularly in police
Because they are raw
Just people responding to
He's over there
And when they say two Shadows that could be the two reporters
What do Oregon flying over
There are exclamation
For all these things
In the time before those explanation
Are publicly known
Alex is able to
Do this sort of b*******
At least
We don't really
Good to know that
Shows the
Spend all the time debunked
King lies in
I really promise
Sancho's
You know why we're bored
Cuz we don't spend all of our time
King about Piers Morgan
Like
And I mean that specifically and metaphorically and literally literally
Would go up
But more metaphorically
Kind of embarrassing incident happened on
Where y'all at
Piers Morgan
I know you spent most of this episode
Just talkingshit on Piers Morgan
Everything like that guy the f****** a****** they tried to kill me and doing
Play tried to f****** kill me I had a staredown with him after the interview when his producer was cry
And I told him that you'll never take down the Republic all this stuff
If we did that metaphorically with our everyday life
You know like to go all the way
Creative
Fiction
That's something I turned it into like
Truth purple ship
Probably have a lot more
Small talk a lot more
What are lying all the time
Grocery store
I went to Home Depot to make it out of there
Plant
Drove
South Bend
Very successful
Expand a Morgan British
And also he
Calling him a
Snot-nosed
Not talking about like worshipping the
It's not in his nose
And stuff like that
Hillary loses track of what
Fertile job or whatever whatever Supercut of all the times Alex
Snot-nosed
Morgan Smith
20 seconds
Indicative of a lot of
He said snot-nosed probably a hug
Episode
Drinking out of Piers Morgan
Mancino's
So we
Imagery
I can but I can
I don't enjoy it
I think is
The turning point
Alex's
Cover
Cuz we're seeing the professor
Introduced
Do the preceding
And we're seeing him
Amplify
And respond to it in a way
That indicates to me in adoption
Exactly how it plays out
January 9th
Which will get in
Send stuff
He really just continue stalking about Piers Morgan
God dammit
He doesn't even have
Lego the whole Sandy Hook
Book stuff is tossed off
It's just like oh yeah this is
Well it's not as big of a priority for him because
What book is important
As for him
To get attention
Self apologize
Kotoko battle
Or whatever in support of gun right
There's much more publicity
Be at this
In him doing stuff with your Morgan
Then there is in Sandy Hook stop
Put that a little bit on the back burner ignoring it necessarily
Speakers on the 8th
It was talking about
Hang out of it
Much as they can
Make their argument with the same source
Stupid
They're so scared of me
Throat throat
Most people are in
Interested in the conversation
I'm drinking out of everybody
Appearance of the idea that he is the biggest thing in the world
Biggest story in the country right now
He's the biggest store in the world
Conan
That's not making you said you're not the biggest story
Do just we're really easy as a Target
And maybe the writers wanted to go home
Writes itself even have enough jokes until you just said
What else is in the news today oh Alex Jones is a dick
A little bit of
Because that's exactly what Alex
Metastasized
Stop making fun of him and
But I also don't think there's anything wrong with me
No game but
He also if you don't understand it back in 2013 every reason
Do not understand
A very very forgivable thing
In the world
She has a relative of somebody who died Aurora on
To talk about how I know
Did you get the call
Late at night a Morgan has somebody on
Who is the relative
About how
You know
You don't want
People
Experience
Of waking up
Recalled that you loved
Eddie's specifically says that I would never want out
Experience
And that's why we worked
To keep guns out of the
Atwood
Possibly do something which I assume a personal insult not a threat
Gotcha
It says about this guy
Whose family member was killed in Aurora
He's talking about last night he was a hanging out with his family there was a storm in Austin
The internet's not working so well
I feel sorry for his loss victims
Sandwich from Aurora
I feel sorry for his loss or whatever he came off as a super scripted actor
That's a man
I feel sorry for Denise Richards pug or whatever
Right
Ulta
Okay
I mean whatever
Hey comes down to this idea to like there
This early and Alex's getting comfortable with it
It's so you do expect him to say stuff like that
Partially or fully
Stage
Entirely sure where the money
What's the angle we're going to go
Until this episode messerly really
Nail down
Articulated
For someone like Alex
The difference between saying
Partially and entirely staged
Is negligible
The effective it doesn't matter
Exact your inspiring
The same sort of
This isn't real
You can't be
Be trusted as right as a Survivor is a family member because you might be
One of the bad one
I feel as
Episode
And Alex
Pretty consistently
The hook is
Partially or totally staged
It doesn't matter
There will come a point where it gets to like
This is the whole f******
You will get to that point in his rhetoric
But this is this is
Yeah but that's what I
The consequences
Are the
Right so it doesn't really matter what the difference
What's the difference
Specific words
It's still going to result in the same harassment I think there's Nuance for our like sort of academic
Realistically
This is all this is already
Which makes it all the worse that Alex
Next
Declares himself
Statesman
And unfortunately
I agree with that Ted Nugent doesn't get the whole picture under any bus please
He's not answering his calls
Yeah
The whole
Or is he talking about a specific
This dude doesn't leave s*** anymore he's too old is retired from the house
Is interviewed
Much about Cindy hooker any of that stuff
Talk s*** on Glenn Beck a little
Search Cadillac
This episode so far being just Alex s*** talking other people I hate
He sucks going back sucks
Go fuc yourself up Chris Morgan
Call I love you but you're worthless now is all f****** May
Larry Pratt
I'm gone owners for America on again
And it's just more like
Of course nothing
So we can skip over that
Piers Morgan's episode on the 8th
Did include
Really inappropriate
Piers Morgan
But I also think it's a
Now I'll get into what I mean on the other side of this
But I think Alex has one of his own
Complaints
That I think it's legitimate
But he's also making way more out of this
I didn't shake my hands busy
See my Facebook
With a semi-automatic
Uniform
So the first thing I want to point out is that Alex
Clearly understand the consequences of word being said to audience
The way audiences are going
Hear them
When he is Target of it he clearly understands
This is a threat to his safe
Argument of I had no idea how people would hear what I said
Ifucking window
You know exactly the way people will hear your words
Okay well what if
Crazy viewer appears Morgan
A theorist
Shows up at
Cuz a Morgan's words
And I will never
Sprite
It's on sale
I think he plays this clip way too many times on the episode
Auntie editorialize is on it in terms of like
Uniform it's okay they all this stuff
The guy who wrote Friday Night Lights
What are writer
He
Is
Is bring a gun to a boxing match
Shootout
But the end
I do think
The first the lady who responded
Might have thought
Ahmet puncher
Like I don't think that they're laughing at the idea of shooting
But Buzz bissinger I do believe was saying
Saudi idea
They're all like
Has existed chorus of laughs about murdering Alex
Might be a little unfair
I think that that's important
For clarity
But the larger picture of it
That's f***** up
Is it appropriate
Like I don't think it's right
For a Morgan to not stop
Like I know that we all hate Alex
But you expressing something like that isn't that is no place on
My Shout
Working at in and out of the show I don't know
Behind the scenes of edited out of Archer
Not as many as you might think
You yell
Is not okay
Have a good point at least
So I kind of think
They made
Recovering Alex
Is illegitimate
Pretty good Alex's bake
You making it poorly
But I think it's a legitimate
Inasmuch as
Peterson is
People f***** up big f******
Alex is capitalizing on it
Nobody
Stop that
I think in making a big deal out of this
Because it's an unforced error on.
Is really fun
This next one is not
I don't want Alex Jones
I get the phone call at 3 in the morning
The one of his children has been shot and killed by somebody shouldn't have
A handgun or a
Rifle or a automatic weapon
Is
Aurora Survivor
Who was on the show expressing that ideas like I don't want out
Get that phone call
Even if I disagree with him but this
Should have to
Rheostat
And Alex
Because he's a f***
Idiot
Interprets that is a Veiled Threat on his family
Which is nonsense
Does he
I mean cuz I'm almost on the edge of feeling bad for
Why because
Is that dumb
Well am I don't know because
Purposeful
Bulshit
Or if it's
This guy genuinely
We cannot under
Stand
People
Not wanting
Process I think Mikey lives in this world
Is expressing empathy
For him to
It is like
You're trying to kill me like that so lonely
I think it's entirely possible that that is what's going on that he has to
Interpret every
Sing that doesn't fit
His like sort of
Skewed worldview as
It's sort of recontextualizing a little bit
I think that's entirely possible
But I honestly
There's another possibility
That possibility is
He knows that what he does is inappropriate
And so every time that there is
The possibility of creating
A victim narrative
Himself
He needs to capitalize on it in order to build up
The perception of the scales
Or that he's in the right
Kill my kids their eyes
Twinkle when they say they don't want me to get a call at 3 in the morning
H b at my family member is dead
Their eyes are twinkling because they secretly are saying they want my family they want to kill my children
Why would I behave in any other way than the way on.
I think there's part of it is that is rash
Analyzation
Whether it's to his audience
Number to himself
I suppose another party
Would just be
The idea of
His
Anime
Wanting anything but
Total Destruction
And reveals his own
You know
Opinions on that is
For his enemies he wants nothing but total.
Well you know
Creating a perception that is totaled
Destruction of him
All all manner of Nyssa
Perception all sorts
What is if you're up against
Something that
Destroyer
You got a lie a little bit in order to get people against
The truly evil force
You know that sort of vacation
Could be peace
Train through all of his
Forever
Annie opportunity
To create a
Some sort of
Victimhood
For himself where it doesn't
So did it does fall in line
Scattershot or if it was something right
Overtime
Just part of his world
Write your shoe that you really can't answer without
Stampy probably like
What is the ID
Strategic or pathological
I believe either but whatever the case
It serves
Earlier in the episode I
Do you that I think that
There was a
Piece of this
Didn't go
Super Wells
There's a couple called that Alex
On this episode that are like hey man
What you did was more
Productive towards the goals
Arpino putting forth
You acted like a crazy
Gone owner
There's only going to be used as an argument to take away people's gone
Yeah
It's my fault, man in the arena do not understand
Right so that jerk-off motion
Response to most
This episode is about 3 hours
15 min
3 hours
Generally shows
3 hours long
But if you wants to go into overdrive heki
Keep the show going
Clearly he intended to key
But he got a call
It was along those lines
The idea that you are
You know you're acting
Pretty much right after
In overdrive now
Full discretion of
Press the button and then do whatever
Where this guy confronts him
About
Quintessentially fit every single stereotype
Sliders
Murdered
No you're the one that's always ranting about cointelpro and that's exactly what you were doing
You were controlled opposition dude
Well you know what a myself and I believe what I did was write getting mad at him so I appreciate your call
Goes around
One form of psychological warfare they engage in
Show
Build a organization
Sophisticated
Clip earlier Alex talking about
Like people talking about him on CNN is
What is a threat
Recognition of the relationship
Audience
Babies fully aware of that
Part is real
Because it's an awareness
Understand
That
People criticizing him are helpful to
Why wouldn't
That sort of thing
In order to
I will tell you why
Because while listening
I realize that he is a loser little
Who is throwing a tantrum
Criticism from people that what he did was
Wasn't
That people who are for gun
Control are again
So
I think the point here is that
This is a good explanation of what
With Alex
Because criticism
Of him to work in his favor a lot of the time
Dude I got to go in Bishop
You're controlled opposition dude it's a good it's a good catch all
It's a good catch all and it's
Defect
Really sounds like his feelings
He really sounds like you
You having that moment
It's probably why he doesn't Court
Because it's like
Like criticism on a very real personal level.
Personally I know but taking it personally allows him to
And you like Sanger
You're a lot more than most other feelings
CID
Feelings whatever they might
Maybe about anything else
For saying that
He's controlled opposition
Greenbelt lake
What
You going to do what I've done I'm great
I think
I don't know if you see ghosts
I don't think
Narcissism
So I think
January 7th
Nice
Stretch
I think of the down
I want to call it down
Now we still got to wait
Yeah but it's
It took me was December 4th
Who's the shooting
And now January 8th
Can say definitively
Starts to
Internalize
Re report these a crisis actor
If that's if that's
I mean we're done
Timestretch
You got to still push forward and
Houses develop
But I'm glad
No words fail us intellectually
Interested
Satisfied on some level curiosity
We know this point is
Mark
Consequentially this is when he said what we expect
Another one
The result of
Some crazy person
He already knew it
Also come into play
He only is starting to really talk about this
Sauce and put it for
Because he has the cover
We thought it would be Wolfgang halbig but it's not
It's James Tracey
Who is the initial
Source of him being able to like
I can talk about this now.
This guy is
He still wants to presented as I've known this for a long time
I need that cover
This scares me in terms of
The investigation though just because
I don't want
To find out that the
Six months are him s******* all over different
People that he doesn't
Piers Morgan still sucks
And then six
Slater there's somebody calls in
Did you know that
Sandy Hook we're crisis
The whole thing
Yeah there is
These words
Just don't work
It would be frustrating
Tremendously frustrating
If it is a loss
Like I cuz I
I could see an outside chance that most
Official for like at least a week is about.
Easily see that
Stories about Charlie Sheen doing that episode
On that with Marty
The WWE is about to introduce the
Patriot character in early 2013
So I know he's going to get sidetracked
I do
I do wonder how
How much
How
Consistently he will view Sandy Hook
As the primary thing that he
When
Because of his ego
It's an open Quest
I just want to know if he knows Emilio a
You know Charlie Sheen are they
April is the Boston bombing so like
Coming down the pike
Boston bomber
Inspect for sure
From the day
Yeah it's whatever your frustration in whatever I'm worrying about being frustrated about
Is possible
So much
That's going to happen
Stretch
Early 2013
That this is going to be
Sucks
This is going to be drafted
Whatever Enzo
Website
If you want that go to that website
Do all that fun stuff
Where on Twitter
Underscore
And I'ma go to bed
Go ahead
View
It couldn't hurt
V8 any help with promotion
Cuz we're bad at
Wow
I'll tell you
I'll tell you right now
Okay what are you going to
Guarantee
Denise Ritchie
Beautiful little pug
His life ended before his time never killed anybody dance
Anybody but one guy quickly
Probably has probably
Is Alex Jones
I love your work