Galaxy color with your Japan I love your work
Beverages
Jordan
Did you have a child
It's interesting not really in childhood because I moved around
Throwing up in elementary school and moved
Boston Cambridge
Hawaii
Missouri
Shipping School
Start
Each other
High School
Exactly
I did that
Discovered nemesis
He's as being really productive
Strategy in order to motivate myself to do better in class
I would also
Well
One guy one of my classes wearing
It's what I would do that I've never talked okay
How do well in the class to do better than the fun game you can play the only time that ever like I was ever
Anything confirm for me
There was a guy
The glasses
Who was just
Real Annoying
Early entry level philosophy class to ask stupid questions
The professor gets annoyed with everybody
So he was my Nemesis in that class
I hated a behavior the swastika
Monday
Is doing somebody exercise
Working out in college
A little bit
My liked songs are
And I'm like
Really really
Monster underneath
It was it was it the clown
It's the truth
You hear people breathing really hard when they're lifting
Healthy supposed to breathe
Just like
And I looked over
And he has like one bar of weight
Is over doing it for attention
This guy's annoying everywhere
Typically remember
Kind of like my animosity
For a purpose
Situations
Is the show I know a lot about Alex Johnson
That is absolutely required
I don't care another personally
Restaurant of the show
Situation
Is that out of the studio Bullhorn in Washington
Proceed striking himself act on Twitter
He's been out of the studio and we have like Owen Shroyer filling in
The last couple days
Buddy
Studio on Monday
We can cover that
Halfway through
All he was doing was gloating about the idea that a Muslim group
Did commit the ACT
Chewbacca
Exactly what I thought it would be
I would already kind of talked about that events on our on our way
You know my birthday
Another one of this s*** ice can't do it
And then beyond that it also has a Wacky Wednesday thing that I've been working on
But
I need a little more time
So
We are back in the past
Iraq
There's some there's some stuff in here Monday through Thursday
No this is Thursday through Sunday Thursday Friday Sunday
You might be wrong about that
Are we getting any tamales today
Nothing that are d'alessio
We'll see what we get an artist though but before we do
Joseph thank you so much
Veronica Mars
F*** off
Is your Kristen Bell
Next Market
I'm a policy wonk
Think about it
Christine finally I'd like to see
Columbia Missouri watch the number of episodes of Lost
You're now a technocrat
Someone sodomites
Couldn't button support the show and guys we are
Of the way from me getting this tattoo is very fragile tattoo
I'll give you an update on that my brother is designing as we speak very likely I'll be going to get it this weekend
Because inevitably we will end up over the phone
They are forcing my hand for this dumb joke that I made about getting a
It's going to be
It's supposed to be
Standard English
Actual words are a better way to go
In terms of that
Now maybe I'll get to misspelling tattooed on my itself somewhere else
2 time is a little bit of a slog
Walking through molasses
I'm not going to lie to you
There is a lot of talking about
Okay his show is almost entirely become about how he went to
Almost all he's talking about
There's very little other Kant
Kind of got to a point where I was like
Almost
Just looking for out-of-context drop
Enjoy rapid-fire
We can let these breathe and enjoy a little bit
Avatar complete
Yep
Set my timer
Do you know who lives there
Okay cool score
This comes on the Tails of him having Mancow on
Do perfect
That's not giving it Kant
It's just
Apropos of nothing
And they talked for like
Half an hour about f****** William Shatner
Being a great guy
I guess that sounds nice good friends with William Shatner
He's apparently a living embodiment of how you just got to keep
They did not bring up his wife
Their coverage
The last out of context
Believe me I want nothing more
This
Me too me too
I want nothing more than that you should follow your heart
Quit
Year on January 10th
2013 episode with Alex
Who's there
Fictionalized versions of going to talk Spears mortgage
Should have the walls the whole Studios just Bedlam also
You got harassed by cops
Chase to the airport Newark
Or whatever
He presents a slightly
Elevated version
Enough that you're on the top
You can see little kernels of
How the narrative
Is starting to
To evolve a little bit
Next clip
To the story that is absolutely
3 globalist in a hot tub
Play the song
When you're angry musician mess with all the street
So here is what's different about this on the tap
He had a little bit about how he had some allergies
And stuff like that before
Much of a new introduction
Use for white yelled a Porygon
Important thing that's different about the police harassing him
That was never
Whenever and I quote
Police or whatever are popping out of the dark
Before this Alex that only been talking about the police harassing him after the fact trying to walk him out
Alley where they were a hotel when he came back
The reason that you bring nothing they were harassing him before
Not said
Is because Doug hack
Of the Northeast
Network one of Alex's weirdo
Heckman was on earlier in the show
And he was talking about how
They were following a massive with Alex the whole time
And it was all the plan to get him to a Starbucks where a lady was going to cost
And then I could take him down with this new quote-unquote
Information
And Alex's Incorporated that was only telling of his experience
Intelligent
Alex's individual experience
Of the past has now changed
This is a mark of bulshit
That is
So that's
The show
Did Doug Hagmann being boring to s*** and telling Alex that he had secret sources
That he was there was a takedown
Or some s***
Alex
Begets
We have to break
Through break at Breakout
Interview with Gerald Celente
Cuz there's big news
Chris morning
Nature of society
We had
Who are these people that can let you know
How many shrubs in Texas
At least his voice
As compared to a lot of these other f****** dumb dumb gas
High School
Real California
And Alex break the news
We're talking about
People are on drugs
He's interrupting is pretty
Pointless interview is going to be a planned Financial
Business
Breaking in with his news of the schools
What happened was a student at high school brought a shotgun to school and wounded two people before being talked into putting his gun down
Surrendering to the
You don't claim that he didn't remember anything
From the point where he was at his house
Until right after the first shot was actually fired
But prosecutors introduced
For instance after surrendering to the police told them the correct number of shells
Later claimed that he had no memory of loading
Things like that are pretty good reason to have a little bit of a
Suspicion
Skepticism
I don't remember anything
Call boscia
Be quiet if only Elsa because you posted like
I hear it that the shooter had written
Short story that involves
And the day before the shooting
He posted it online
Indications
Premeditation
VIP of like I don't remember anything that happened
A little bit
Dubious
Alex and Gerald use this as an opportunity
Just no doubt about all that shooting
But they're particularly interested in doing this with literally no evidence or even any information about the shooter
Psychiatric medication
Which caused him to carry out the shooting
I was trying to figure out if this was what
Jason my research led me to dr. Peter langman
The psychologist and expert on school shootings
Monroe to paper regarding the
That's flying around that School shooters are all on
Redo the opening paragraph
Their numerous websites devoted to the belief that psychiatric medication
Pensacola school shootings and other acts of mass violence
I've seen claims that virtually all Rampage shooters were on or had recently been on Medicaid
Based on my research these claims are not
Open cases lineman research 7
3% of the Secondary School shooters
High School shooters
They looked at we're not on psych meds nor have they ever been
The shooter at Taft High School is one of that 70
He was not
Whatever
The reality is that a pretty sizeable majority of School shooters are not on psychotropic medication at all
And even if the statistics were flipped it wouldn't prove causation
Because Jordan
During the same
People on drugs like Prozac went through the roof
Prime rate
Dropped
These are burner pills argument held any water
Severely spike in violent crime rates from that night
1880s to the current day
And that just doesn't match up with reality
So
That's all I'm that's all I'm saying
I mean what else
Response
What is an obvious
Play bad face
Argument
If it's coming if that's your
Mediate
The news of another
Your reaction is
Is not like
Oh s***
We got to get people off site
Sleight of
Spell psyche
What it is is an attempt to claim the space early in case
And then it builds up your narrative
But all these things are fake
Or there
People who
Do you think Madison
And then when it's
Not true like in this case
You can
Pretend
I hope people don't look into it
Or you can just ignore the fact that you
You said that that was what's going
This is what he does
No matter what you end up being able to reinforce
Narrative
Without any Costco
So
He breaks that news
Because Gerald
Is there
I thought it upsetting
That made me very upset
Contacts wouldn't help
That was apropos of almost
He means that it is
Become a fad
Hurt animals right
Which I was alive in 2013
I remember I don't think it was
Ever she
Call the black building up around
The news
Synchro
No
It wasn't even like a
Real Spike
Happened
Please be a local news story
Even like a Michael Vick
Connection
Michael Vick got in trouble in 2000
I got out of prison
I can't I don't know what this is further Evidence
Alex Jones May have killed some dogs
So Alex and Gerald
Versation
Back from break
And there's more news
About the bakery
Field shooting
Northwoods
Shooters
So
Let's just
Established
They have a drill
Not really okay
Lying about representing
Also I know from
Looking into this
He's going to going to stop here
This is going to get
This narrative
Yeah I'm certain
Right so what are cornerstones of rationalizing and reinforcing
No one died
Sandy Hook narrative
Annihilus narrative about other events
More generally
Is the idea that there's always drills overlapping with
That it's very consistent
Route conspiracy
Alex all the f****** time
And I'm certain it'll be pretty easy to put together on a project
Drill
All the goddamn
The idea goes like this
Nefarious globalist want to pull off this fake shooting order to sway public opinion
That's a noble gun-loving Patriot
But it's difficult to get all the pee
Pieces in place till 4
That's they conduct drills
The event they plan to
Quote goes live
Which shooting or
Send it to a fake shooting
Depending on what day you ask
That's largely the way that
Narrative is
I don't understand how
Drill
Today's date
Forehand
That is a problem
Problem
Is that is that like a
I'd like a dry run of the way
Is it like as possible
Like a dresser
Hey my buddy
So I don't know exactly where his head's at
It's just something it's like
If you're thinking the idea just generally sound stupid
It is
Yeah but it works
Because it relies on
Exploiting 12 great shortcoming
Susceptibility to ascribing mean
Coincidence
There was a shooting drill at the city about 20 miles away from Newtown
That's a pretty wild
More than a coincidence
When its uses
The consistent pattern
And that's why it's important to apply to all and any
Situation
That comes up
Because on its own
It's part of every single event
Then that's
Suspicious
And then you hijack people's mine
With that sort of thing
This is why Alex
The super quick to say that this Bakersfield shooting shooter
If you wasn't before doing any of the facts of the case
Regardless of what the reality is
Constant reinforcement
The idea that
Becomes what they believe
The success of the narrative doesn't depend on fact only on the appearance of a pattern
Built on the exploitation of coincidence
Combined with just outright malicious
The latter is what's happening with the baker
Crisfield had a drill
Version of
Alex reporting reporting bakersfieldnow website
The story doesn't say that they had a drill at the school that actually literally says
The training took place at a dorm
University
A two-day seminar concluded with a simulated gun men's stocking a dormitory at San Diego State University
About 2,000 participants
School districts in universal
San Diego County Los Angeles
Bakersfield
Participate
They practice barricade indoors hiding escaping
Confront
Somebody to argue that school district not providing this kind of training
In the aftermath of Sandy Hook might be them being negligent
Which is where
This part of the
The Narrative that there was a drill at the school would be reinforced by a January 11th article posted on Fox News
Which became the subject
Inappropriate editorial
The headline California school practice lockdown drill minutes before shooting
Which is barely discussed in the body of the actual article
That is
Very misleading
The second paragraph
Just 10 minutes before it happened
Andar
Teachers were giving us protocol
Because of what happened
Oscar Nuno student at a high school set
It's probably super unfair to call that proof that the school had a drill
However
Stop online conspiracy theorists from using that quote to justify their contention
There was a drill at
Taft High School that overlap
The shooting and thought it's
Completely fishy
Increase the troops
Surprised no one
One of the most visible names pushing this theory was Shepard ambellas
Stuart internet weirdo who would go on to become an Infowars employee
Who's most notable contribution
Seems to be him successfully convincing Alex that there were helicopter
Firing on civilians
At the Las Vegas shooting
Last year
Isn't it interesting
Still helping.
Open up the world
Story of a
Ohio Alger
That sounds right
Yep
0 face that Alex won't find that article
And then go from there
Which was the
The article in the first place
For everybody
And that's the entire point of Alex on the reporting that there was a drill
The school in the article actually said that there was shooter training
Diego State University
There's nothing suspicious
There's no evidence of any drill
Description they could very well have just been teachers telling students what they do
Which makes sense
This was the first week of January
Coming back from their holiday break
Right before which there was a terrible school shoes
All this makes complete sense in exactly what would happen
In a normal well
Reasonable
Absolutely
You know I
I didn't
Really make this connect
When we talked about proper
And Alondra
Being you know that
Crazyblox
Gets Amplified with
More and more legitimate Outlet
It also
Like Fox News
Publishing
Means
Crazier Outlet
With the credibility of Fox News today
Exactly I think Fox News is probably on the
Capricious side of appropriate
Wrong to make that the headline of
The story considering that most of the article isn't about that
That's irresponsible
Is this quote from this
Which they could twist
Into being like
You know there was that they practice new lockdown drill
Fortunate
You know like
It's it's bad
They're not as evil as Alex
Unless it is with the cognate
The people like Alex will take that headline
It is it is it is and that's f******
If you look at it in a vacuum
One time
Concerted pattern
It just doesn't look good
But you know what does
Gerald Celente is ideas
In many ways what is it with all this
The other trans researcher
Aubrey
It's this is something that Alex
Definitely
Much more extreme version
What I would like to see as part of the next Revolution
Is secession
I don't want a gang of I-35
Goodnight
Misery
Friends
Destroying the nation
I wonder if he's still
Supports the sachet
I want
Stopped like couple years back I want to wander
Estranged
Doesn't he live in New York
I don't see a problem
New York voice
Allstate
Ulta
What's the dissolution of the Union in
Secession he wants to dissolve
The federal government
I've been reconstituted because federal government has become invaded by the
Definitely not.
So you believe that the federal government isn't
Entrenched
Have the authority
Because the
To dissolve the federal government and I bring it back together
Before
I would never work
Is
Create
A ton of different countries
That would also unsustainable
Create
World as we know it like that
Asteroid
Political Valentines
Wisconsin having to negotiate trade deals with a f****** united king
Baby talk
So in this next clip Alex gets a call
From a guy
And he's complaining about Glenn Beck a little bit but in doing so
Snapshot of what Alex
His listeners think
Tutas Reese
Chris what's your take on all this
Something that you protected from
I'm a one-year listener first-time caller
And that piece of garbage going back is only
Thinking about doing your homework and doing your research and last night I did my research and went on YouTube
You call 911
On the spot
3:30 equals iWatch
Some YouTube games
Really travel
Really
Stupid
The presentation
Couldn't continue his listeners
Subscribe to more rigorous methods
Fact-checking
Yeah that would be
Item
I don't like
Like living in a world where
You can say I do
My research
I went to YouTube
You have covered all your checks off
Abu
Stupid are you going to go with citing your sources MLA
Coronavirus
64 video player 69 and I got to say
How do I put
You're not going to get a degree frame
Sale
Most of the show is just Alex talking about Piers Morgan
Launch more clips
I felt it would be
Sort of redundant
I'll bet this episode ends with Alex
Going to retransmission
Which is what he does
You don't know what I mean
Is show will Air
And then
Vcm stream
It'll just restart whenever his show on
Yeah so he is going
Retransmission
The interview with Doug Hagmann
The beginning of the show so you know that if you're listening
Straight through
He's promoting the interview is going to start as soon as
The show restart
Just listen to
Transmission on a garden on 5:20
Was just allergies
Well he's confusing
X-Files spin-off show the lone gunmen
Call Alex results
Normal for him to
Think of
Security confirming source that they are stocking
What else is expressing their is the same thing people who believe in like stalking
There is a phenomenon where a lot at like if there's a form of paranoia where people believe that
Stop
Jack Hackman
Is lending credibility to Alex's idea there was a New York everyone was trying to get him
That's bad
I meant for Alex to be like the things you see in movies
Really make
Crystal clear
His break with
Dealing with reality on realities term
It'll be interesting cuz if I agree with Alex
Principally on like issue
Nuts
Mexico and people were like
That I would be like
I got to get a new
New co-host or I got to get you
Help
More entertaining
Exploited your your break with reality
Good mental
Literally doing it
Sounds crazy
And then he says
It's just like in a movie
Which makes him sound crazy
So it is
Is obviously
I told you they were trying to make
Give me sound crazy
Because I just found another piece of the gang stalking stuff to is the idea of like
Not too actually
Stalker
Elicit the reaction of you saying you're being stalked by everybody
I would discredit other things you have to say
To do
Bright
So are we to the 11th
Thumbs up the show with
I don't want to call it
Cuz it it
No it's not that uncommon
Starting to show with a sales pitch
Is a little bit
Common and I think it actually illustrates
Something really important
But I want to talk
January
Texas
Texas Revolution
T-shirt
Bear arms shall not be infringed
Just got put this t-shirt up for sale
I'm just looking at the church I was wearing this morning
T-shirts
Here's what I want to say about that
What is it
Pieces of
The Sandy Hook
Lawsuit
Is about Alex's
Profiting off of his coverage
I didn't make any money off of
I do think it would be hard to
Tres necessarily
But I think that this clip is a pretty good illustration
Exactly
Is profiting off
Now
Did the
Intrinsically
Super Evil behavior of the crisis actor
Stuff is only starting
Visible to the sir
But Alex
Is making a lot of money selling these
It's the best seller shirt that he's ever had
And he's only been selling it for a short. Of time
The common take it with an AK-47 on
Now
He's selling these shirts
Explicitly
Through the coverage of his show
Where you staying
Is a representation of his rhetoric
Come and take it
You want to take my gun
If he had
Which is audience into a frenzy of like they are immediately going to come
He sure wouldn't sell that well
The rhetoric
Serves as a de-facto sales pitch for this shirt
Important is so strong in the
Time that we're looking at your the beginning of 2013
It's because Alex is using the idea of the response
The people are having
Sandy Hook
That is his rationalization for there about 2
Right so he is using
Sandy Hook
Excuse they will use
To take your gun
Which is what he is using to fuel his rhetoric
Which is what is selling these sure
So on a suit of tertiary
Second third hand
Level
His response to Sandy Hook is responsible for this shirt being a best seller there is a pretty clear path
Through that
That's not making me crazy
He's not dealing with Sandy Hook as a real
Either manufactured
He's what
Behind his ability
To Market this shirt
In the way that you
Successful
And I enjoy it so I don't know is this
Is usable in any way
For the lawsuit
Does profit off
His behavior
Directly
Jessie
Whenever whenever he's
That fear of
Collapse
Gold sales
You know that will go
One Step removed because
People believe
Baby pigs
Saying these crazy things
Isolating them
Create
Yeah
To represent
Being apart of
Did you do that
T-shirt
Clearly
I'm one of these guys
Yeah it's like
Removed
From amore
Crystal clear
It's just as
Absolutely
It's a it's a good reminder
That
Like there is
The principal
Can also be
Automotive
With that argument
Courses
He uses that regardless
You know right
Whenever he's
I suppose the only thing that may
Makes this one different
So soon
Suggest they are cap
It does suggest that
As opposed to a shirt that was
You know he's been yelling about gun-grabbing
90s Usher he makes
Doesn't have the same
Closeness
Yelling about gun-grabbing forever dozen
Mean that it takes on the same character is
Has
In this. That we're looking
That's certainly true yeah
Yeah Gunn talk
In this time
Consistently Stewart Road Larry Pratt
Other gone weirdos it's almost the only issue that he's even covering
From the
Time right after Sandy Hook
January 11th that we're at now
To the time that we looked at whether S2000
Obviously there's shades of guns
Everywhere but it's not like
Know your rights
Focus
And it's focused
Cuz he believes in what he's misrepresented about
NFL
Yep capitalization you ever monetize
It's very direct
Fisher
Has a Latin phrase on it
Interesting
Doesn't know how to say
How do you say that in Latin
Tom and Chee
Now here's what I have to say about that
Is way too late for Alex
Do not know how to say molon labe
Vernacular
It's like him not being able to say Posse Comitatus
Which is insane
He doesn't know how to say f****** Bowl on
Both know that he is illiterate
Especially in foreign
It is trash
Is
Just
Wall-to-wall
The only things more interesting at all in that show is the sure plug
I'm not being able to say molon labe
3 hours long
It is
Just
Such dog
It was one of the worst episode ever listen
I don't know if 13 other hours of yelling
Maybe the 11th would have been fresh
Maybe it would have been
Investigation
Think about it
To the 13th
The Sunday
He makes it even more
The connection
Two stages removed
Constitutional republic
Firearm
I'll call on you forever
Now that's an interesting Theory
Eggs are the only ones who can defeat the globalist as opposed to the idea of like
Ilottery
Ciara
Seems like
I don't know if you met my
My dude Oakham I've only ever read it
I've never heard it pronounced
Occam's razor ever heard of that guy
Okay
Suggest that may be the simplest
Simplest explanation is ever
I'm already off the rails by popsicle sticks
Be gone to college he might know about that
But that does not stop him from waxing poetic about college Years
If it starts
Everybody everybody
You didn't go to college
You working two jobs
Bucket junior college for a little bit and dropped out he's expressing sort of an archetype
But he didn't wave
College is a Viber member correctly
And Edna offer on-site housing
I think I don't know it's all
Community colleges with that way in Columbia Missouri
Have dorms
It's cool.
Baby lived in a hostel
I don't know man
With CIA
He's trying to co-opt other people
Experiences
You know what it's like for us
Right
This clip made me X
Alex
Is excited
Okay
I will say this
Tomorrow is
Very nice fish by the way
Got a big gap
Tomorrow
Big guy
Who could it be this is Alex's so excited
My boy Ron coming on
No
Is it the bells no
For the next half-hour where you try
Charlie Sheen
Do dogs die now
And who's other than celebrities
Big
The politician
A big politician
Obama
Go with rainbow smash
He is nowhere near in plant or the energy
Oh my God I just don't know
Dammit
I don't think they open that one
TuneIn 23rd
That's not right
It's not Papadopoulos it's no one involved in the Russia
Is it is it somebody who will
Who will not surprise me
After I know it
Is The Impossible
Alright I'm going to swing for the fences
It's not
And also
Because this this guessing game
Hundred percent needs
I want to see just how low you can go while still being way too high
Sargon
Avocado
No
20 question 20 questions
Let's play five questions
Is it
Like like mainstream
What's the cure
No okay
Are they unknown
Yes
Alex is so excited about this casting so crazy
Big fish
3 questions
Okay so it's not YouTube
Sort of
Is it
Under
No
No no
Is
Would go on the show
Is it
No
Famous
Yeah
It's someone named Michelle.
As far as I can tell she's notable as being a viral video
Obama Phone Lady
Really that would have been pretty tough for you to guess
Cuz I don't know what the f*** you're talking about Obama phone
Well there's that idea that Obama was buying for
Stuff like that
Because he promised them phones
Stupid
She was in a video where she was the Obama Phone Lady
Alex
The big guy
Big gay
Let me let me
Ask this question
Why would he
You say that
It's possible that the boy
I don't know. Maybe like
She missed a connecting flight maybe she missed the show or something like that
She's going to be
She comes in and I believe that what she ends up talking about is a ton of like
Ideas
Helped illegals vote
Sure you did public
I committed a crime
Federal amounts of a federal crime
Going to cover the 14th episode but I knew I could not
Possibly
Not tell you who the person was
Could you expect
It's
Nothing
Alex is so excited about nothing I'm terrified I don't want to
This episode
August 14th that's
YouTube
She's better the whole episode
Alright Alex
Next clip Eliza
About primary sources
Course and then again manifest
He doesn't understand the difference
This is social engineering
Bertrand Russell other weekend
Sylvester Stallone
Demolition Man
Cool
Predictive programming
Movies RV demolition
Is we will finally really understand what the
They don't look forward to that
Mystery results
Do you think about Bertrand Russell that he's talking about is a book that Alex
Severely out of context where was talking about the
What would have happened if the Nazis had won World War II
And became a technological dictator
Any idea of the type of world that a nefarious
Evil
System with the
Help of Technology
It's not talkin about we should do this
It's a thought experiment of what we could have
Had things gone
For what
Lucky is not the
So already
Talk to Piers Morgan
Say that
He did what he did because it was right
Later edition of the excuse
Alex has another version of what happened and what lighting
A Morgan
You can't use as a
Forever that's not new
Beautiful position is tired of being lied to
Well it's like Bruce winner is Bruce Banner in The Avengers
The trick is
He's always
I'm tired of Alex lying to everybody I wouldn't yell at him like
Piers Morgan
But I'm equally
Sick of Alex Lyon
You're acting like a child
The reason
Coming up with f****** excuses
And like rationalizations for why you behave the way
Is because he can't come out and say
I knew it would get rating
Even though he insinuates that he is keenly aware of it
He has indications that he knows exactly what's going on
Platform where I can access
People who would never listen to my show of their own accord
Acts
Super dramatic and interesting
People talk about me and bring it even more viewers
And if I make an ass
Myself
Piers Morgan is going to
Show when I'm not
Navigate to The Daily Show
They're all going to make fun of me
It's an interview
Disappeared
Whose uncle is Uncle Road
Fun stop
Cleon skousen
Total weirdo
But like
Even makes the point that like in the days after Alex is on Piers Morgan show
Larry Pratt was on again
Hey Ben Shapiro came on
Pre-fame beds
Shapiro
It's about not wanting control and no one was talking about them being on but Alex being on at 1
Because you made a pageant
10-0
Of it and that's really all
He can't come out and say that because it's cheaper
Ideas
But that's the reality
He can he can definitely
Wow so you want to raise a boy
So you want to make up
They got a whole series of so you want to but only for right wing
2009 Alex hated Michael Savage
You're constantly calling Michael weiner
Cuz that's his real name
And all this stuff
Alex likes
He didn't say that
He said when he was on set I know that Michael Savage's
Text anything like that
Road Warrior music
Knows how
Damaging it is
To have people harassed
Stalk you
So this is another pillar of like his
Self-defense is about his behavior Visa Visa
Just really
False
Perceive
Then I being harassed
And stuff like that
His idea that people are
Clearly him
Writing a novel
Yeah oh yeah
The idea that he's
Able to tell why that would be traumatized
Really makes it difficult for him to Discount experience
So many other people have had
Who were on the other end of his rhetoric
Now on the other hand
If he
If he is lying
And he's aware that he's
As opposed to not really being able to tell the
In reality
Then
Connect
What about peep
Sandy Hook
Albuquerque Airport
Probably
At least subconscious
Just leave
Somewhere in there
It would make matches with his f*****-up brain
It would make sense
Position of him
Like just
Absolutely not caring or understanding why this
People are
. they were lying then everybody
Their house was an agent of the government
Subway the same way that he is being followed or
Yeah
Just hit me while you were talking
It might be a little bit unrelated but
About 50 might be slightly off
Episode
There is a real sense of how it's done
Like I don't think that's absolute might be water under the bridge and taken as read by everybody who's listening
Something is very strange to me
Alex talks about what he did in Sandy Hook in the deposition
You don't want to show now covered it
Yeah
You know
This Behavior
Was a big deal to
People on the other end
Right like that
But I think spiritually he might not be lying
I think there is a
The sense that I get from
But he doesn't give a s***
The idea that people died and that it ruined
A lot of people
I don't think there's very
Very little recognition
That he gives a s*** about their their pain
Secondarily
How he gets so distracted by
Basically talking about Piers Morgan
Really covering anyting
Talkin about
How there were detectives
Walked into a wall
It indicates to me that like what key wants to talk about is his
And he doesn't care
What about San Diego
Along with his view of
School shootings as well
This is his first rodeo
Like I assume there's wonders why it is it
The Sandy Hook people are suing him whenever
So many other parents have
School shooter
His
Into that
They're trying to take our guns
So it's almost like
It's muscle memory for him he doesn't
Tickets
In the same way that correspond will have a different
Concept of
I'd like what super important as as
Proposed Visa v a bomb going off
You know
I'm not I'm not saying that it's super weird
Considering his psychology or anything like that
Yeah that's all
Go back to the
This time it just get vicent
He doesn't
That's that's more like
You would hope you'd hoped
To hear more
Somebody
It's mostly about himself
Is the opportunity to talk about himself
And create a third of the heroic
Version of
Of his date
Prioritize
Write me Wiley talk about her like I do want to talk about myself journalism
So
What are the others
Is a
Sort of a betta fish
Being able to go back
4th and time
Is B we can
And see if it's true
Present a couple months back
Talk about an episode where Alex is talking about how
Because if it's super thick now
Terrible sleep
Percent oxygen
Diminishing in his brain when he sleeps
Yes to sit on a chair and barely able to sleep
You have terrible terrible sleep problems
I wanted things that I've always wondered is how far that goes back
Become a part of
His experience in life
And put that possibly
Explain any of it
Deterioration
That we've seen in the years I can't
Say that this is evidence of
But this next clip is a very strong indica
Okay Summit Alex Jones
Did not suffer from any of these problems
It 2013
Which is really creepy cuz I sleep
Wake up sometime
Paranoid
Consistent throughout
He used to eat can sleep through a freight train
Baby wakes up a little bit
You guys getting older that certificates is nowhere near the level
Traumatic
Sleep
Experience
But he talks about in the present to
His word
Dramatic shift
Not to say that that occur
Or
Development
And his
It is hell
Pedophile
Sure fun facts
So in the early
That would be part of the pop-up
That V8
There'll be a little bubble
The pops up and go
In 2012
I didn't say that
So probably going to
Piers Morgan
GameStop
I wanted to make very clear that Alex had a very
Complained
Piers Morgan's cast on the next night
Alex
Cure for cancer
Buzz bissinger did say that
Use language that
Very clearly
Instead Busby
People wear
Actually heard what they said
I just moved along episodes of our show
Yep absolutely
He's not doesn't happen much more time
Let's start a fire
Yep okay Bubba got that right I could see the other Gaston Piers Morgan
Show when they were like yeah
I'd like to see the boxing match
Sevilla
As Buzz bissinger comments
Actually were thinking of what they wanted
How to say next that they were just laughing 100%
Absolutely
Something that I was about to
Performative conversation
Easily could explain
Not agreeing that I would
B shot
Because they missed what Buzz
So
Whatever the case
Complaint is making too much out of it
But now on the 13th
Beer on January 13th
I think he's crossed the line
Because now Alex has
Successful
Into a
Victimhood propaganda it no longer matches the actual
Hugo's on and on about
The reason they were saying
Like that it's okay for murder to be done by officials
That's
Is it okay
You were right to complain about buzz bissinger and maybe you should have filed
Some sort of an action
Like I don't know what would be appropriate
To doing that and I
Situation
Do something
He doesn't want to do
He wants to turn it into
To this narrative
Where they're all like a great
Great
Yeah that's not that's not
The bimbo and the host
No no no no
Oh yeah
Sure
He does like to eat
This is why it's very difficult sometimes to agree with her
Because the agreement that I have is the buzz was that a lie
Could easily be twisted into appearing that I agree with this
Yeah what he's doing now
He is now taking his narrative that I could have gotten on board
That I'm no longer on
Manipulative you like about it
Now in this neck
Clip
You successfully transmuted another piece
Next day
Piers Morgan
Gunshow which I was never on board with
Further
That's not at all
Close to what happened on the
And the way Alex has presented he's making it seem like buzz bissinger
And the other people in the same interview were talking about nothing happening
Stated earlier in the episode 8
A completely unrelated different interview
With a family member of someone who survived the Aurora ship with killed
The Aurora shooting
It's not like the idea
He's trying to present that those two things are
Connected
The couch
We popped and I hope nothing happens
Because
After saying that said
He's basing this on
He's not that at all
Grieving man
Compassion
And saying that you
Never won anything
Write somebody who would
Justified
Wood
Understandable
Should he say that
Alex
Deserve some sort of
This kind of
He would never say
I don't think you could understand the emotional places
Understandable
So
I know that we talked about this stuff already
The last episode it's not new
This one part is a fair complaint this other one is b*******
We brought them up as I wanted to show you what they've become after a couple
After it goes through the wash cycle of Alex repeating it over and over again scene
This is what comes out the other side
Morgan interview
And then the next day Alex has the
The sort of rough version of his police harassment that he suffered and that's her.
Over the next couple days
Thomas More
There's no wrinkles added to it as it goes along
To give you some sort of a
Seemingly official backing of your paranoid fantasies
Fictional retelling of the events
And that's what comes out the other end
Complaints about the next day show on Piers Morgan
Yoder's
Diversion
Immediately give it a couple days
Tumbling cycle comes out the other side of Polish Rock
He's going to move forward
The perception
Set
Did they want to shoot
They were
Insinuating they hope my kids
Which
Thanks for that out of our mouths
Years Alex
You would not expect
Is not old country
Call Me Maybe
I'm going to call
Keep very much owns The Big Chill
That's super weird
Sort of out of Alex's
Range
Footsac
Always
The hips don't lie
Sakura is informed me of that
Weather
Shakira Hips are not
But your hand
And pray
Alex Bragg
Like the last action
Craigslist
I believe there is about that
You should not be publicly
Out of line with
But I think it's also really in
Khepera's life
Actual movie
Because we would do that too
It is much as movies aren't real
Expressing is
Is
Just touch it
Enmeshed
Inability
Present reality as reality
It's so messed up
What's up
Movies
Baby in their lives are like what you imagine movie stars live for life
Or a movie about a fluid
As opposed to Alex being like The Bourne Identity
Very much
The show
You start
Call
They're all pretty boring
I'll bet against this call from a lady who ran into
Dianne Feinstein
I believe Gloria Allred
Abortion rally
She doesn't have much to say about it
Alex editorialize
It's on her
Celebrity site
Sure
90 or 91 I was in Burbank California
At 8 I was
Abortion rally and I persuaded Matt Dianne Feinstein and Gloria Allred
And they are exactly what you said hard as nails
You name it
Really can't believe it
It's still
You promoting this
So f****** hard
Cannot be the Obama phone
Fireshow almost
Theory
Billy Corgan connecting flight something like that
Also by the way this lady
With her complaints about the Gloria Allred
Is not a negative
When I was a kid
Basketball team
They were there
Jose outside
Jumper artist
Three-point man
Stole three pointers from everybody in the big eight
The big eight
Is that guy tough as nails
Cuz you scrapped you small and mix it up a little bit
Small person who's still getting in there
Yes4all
Shortcoming
Absolutely
Like that
She's tough as nails
So I agree with this lady just application
Everybody knows the demons are also tough
Sure that's 121
Second-story demons
Demon Steal Your Girl
Episode of a holding pattern
Alex is so excited about his
Piers Morgan
How much attempt
He's getting from
It's so much of it is very negative
Like the Conan
Booty
Northlake
But Jon Stewart is talkin about the idea that
So what's going on
Because I replace the clip of Alex
Screaming about
Oh I see what's going
Your fear of a possible dystopian future
Is
Stopping us from having a conversation about artistic
Being present
I told there's like
It's a lot of
Negative attention
Alex is getting
But he still able to
To use it
Needs to do well for the follow-up
To Alex there's a cert
Percentage that Argo
Misconstrue all of this
Coverages
Dammit
Right
His victim narrative all the more effective
The Daily Show
Jon Stewart has a point
Play
The Daily Show coverage and then scream about a little bit
Yeah literally has nothing to lose if you're
Listen to Infowars you're not watching
The Daily Show every night.
Look at that liberal crusader
It's interesting to see
Here in this time when
So much is going on
Hook
The conversation
What's going on
The world
Just be Alex
To just
Just suck his own dong
Grotesque
Ask navel-gazing
It-it's
Really bizarre
A little bit in preparing this episode
Because I
Really invested
In this 2013
Yes.
A little bit
Literal masturbatory contest
I mean
It is what it is
I can't handle it Monday show
Like I don't know what I'm going to do
How many weeks
Lose my mind I just
We'll see what happens
But I'm excited for
Think we got through
Most of them
Alex's
I'm awesome cuz I was on
Website.com
It's on our website
We also are on
Twitter
We will review
All those things
Tell afraid to eat one teach one
Something along those lines
Alex
Imaginary
Play virtue of non-existent never killed anybody but one guy who has is that imagine
Alexandra Thurston color