Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We are couple dudes like to drink red wine
Surrounded discuss
The merry ways in prankster it's days of Alex Jones
Now that is running through the woods
Deanza
Bringing all sorts of weird awkward feeling
Alex Jones
From Pam
Alex is never having fun
That's a good question
What is Alex do for fun
That is on brand Americana and manly and I
I think that's where he lives
Call Nelly opportunity.
My dad was an awesome it's warm most here my parents live
Move down there and every time I go visit around like Thanksgiving my dad's smoked turkey
Out in the old smoker
I expect you'd like a lot of but I would still have it
ISO today
We're going to be going over something happened
On the April 11th
Tuesday episode this week
The Alex Jones Show
Okay
A little bit of Conte
This
Is Fortune smiling upon me
Alright
This whole week
The last couple of days
Sunday through Tuesday
Have been
I only talking about cereal being a false flag
Insisting that every piece of evidence backs him up
Even Putin false flag
Cool
Great source
Spectraforce there's an interview with Ron Paul was on RT
Cereal is a false
Keanu
I left the libertarian for a while now I'm back percent chance this was a sod
Hey whatever
0%
Hundred percent
DNA testing
It was not this good never be certain things in life one of the ways to learn is not
Also he has an interview that he plays conducted interviews on the BBC with a
Former ambassador to Syria
Peter Ford
And he's talking about how America
Alex Jones
School funding
Yeah
Bucky says
Former UK ambassador
Whatever in 2000's
Is basically saying
That because Trump has bombed them after a gas attack
It gives
Any Isis members there
A really good motivation to fake another one
If they want to lure us into war
He says that the interview
Alex Jones insist
That this is proof that the
Gas attack
Have happened
Is a false flag
And that this guy isn't even saying it
Technically
Actually say that
Okay
Further
And he has been roundly criticized
Buy tons of organization
For being pro-assad
He's very impartial a possible explanation
Doesn't implicative
Time-in oh that is very true
Which
I am not
Thank you for clearing that up
I would say
The Holy War
Exactly
And Irene
What we're saying is Ford
Giving them
The plant I'm sure they thought of that already but that means
Because
Posada
Super Bowl record
You could say horrible wreck you could also say
He has one of the best record
In that he's
Really good at it
So
Alex has been making this argument
Across-the-board
He's doing it in order to try and defend Trump
Sing the Trump
He's just doing this as a show of strength
We kind of went over that a little bit on the last episode
And he's been blaming everybody
Put started with Kushner
No Steve Bannon is called the globalist and a cuck
He is a cuck
Whether or not he's a globalist is yet to be
So he's like it's Kushner
Jared Kushner
That's what we call in from now
The carpenter is like
He's a secret Democrat
Whatever
Then Alex
Switches
You know it was Ivanka
And now on Tuesday show
Ivanka is Kutner in Tucker
Sick for very long
Alex like it's Tillerson
Everyone's getting the blame everyone
Everywhere
Joseph
He's an excellent CEO
And
Is very heavily involved. That is very real
He has no feeling
So he's just evil
Capitalism
Personified
Bullion interested in Staffing the state department
Which seemed so odd if you don't want to do the job
Just for you you're a billionaire that you're well actually Mike cernovich hasn't
About that Mike cernovich was on last week or so he was breaking a big scoop
And that is
The pedophile
Pedophile Army
Compromise the people who give out security clearances
The reason that all of the jobs
In the government
Staffed it isn't because Trump hasn't
It's because
Whenever he does try and nominate somebody
These globalist
Pedophile Elite
Controlled
Security clearance people are like no no no no you're out of here
Is maybe the dumbest conspiracy theory I've heard it's wild
Is out there so anyway I don't want it I don't want to talk about
Like I said
I didn't want to cover
We're going to cover today
Was the today
On the show
April 11th
Alex Jones had Michael Savage back on
Michael Savage I think it's starting to smell the roses
Okay so he's gonna bail on Trump
Not so much but he's starting to realize oh f*** we got screwed he's laying the groundwork
Definitely starting to be like I trust Trump but I
He's going to f*** as he's getting into World War 3
I don't understand how you don't
You didn't see this,
First of all
Big B go hard on Tillerson and they're like
Loyal CEO of course he's interested in this pipeline
Do you know that we all do this
Connected to Goldman Sachs and all this s***
Golden election
Once Trump started nominating people
You get a Goldman Sachs people in
History of fighting the globalist
Has been doing
Snooze
And then it got out of their control the dump
They were selling people
Before they didn't realize that
We were Liars
Yeah yeah yeah
Especially 112 president
Oh no
Real weird alt-right hangover I think
There will be anybody
Eternal slumber
I was fascinated by this Michael Savage interview
And I regret not pulling one clip from it because
What happened right after
Michael Savage interview it was like
Kneeling down
Like I don't want to cover this stuff I know where 10 minutes into the episode now
Everyone talked about what he's been talkin about
But I don't want to do a whole episode talking about this
Cuz it's so wet
His don't care
I don't want to talk about it with episode
Warriors
Please
Just give me something
You know like Jesus
Alex Jones works in mysterious ways
You know what we're going to be
I want to save this
He's sober
Okay alright one of the craziest thing I've ever heard of power Alex Jones full force
We can tell that he's not drunk
Regret not pulling one clip from the Michael Savage interview
There was a point where Alex is like
No we got a cellphone that's how we always talk calling
So that does that does confirm our theory that
Alex Jones has Trump's phone number
You think they'll the premise
The President's chief of staff is holding his phone hostage
Answering his calls for him on his personal cell phone
Seems absurd to me
Most reasonable response to anything
It's been going on but nothing that's happened is reasonable
I forgot
Definition of rearranging deck chairs on the Titanic
Cleaning the administration's
Better
No
Secretary
Young
Translucent about sorry
I want come on
Because it's really funny that Alex is like
That's f****** hilarious
But
Like a little
Thank
God
This happen
Alright
He came back from break
Ali's doctor Savage
Michael Savage
Savages mad
Furious Alex Jones
Alex come
Back from break and I apologize also
That I don't have an out-of-context drop for this episode
But quite frankly
All of this
I have cut this up
Into about 1 minute second
So it's more digestible
But I want to make this clear
I've not got a single f****** word from the 13 minutes
I have.
Any contacts
I have not ended
Yep that you chopped into one minute
Yes absolutely
Start
I believe me it doesn't stay on this topic for long
Collaborator
The forwarder
I wish well on everybody weather in Israel
Japan
Venezuela
Falling down
Nope
My own personal freedom
Also you know how nobody's ever saved a drowning person never
Yeah
Like a Miller
Fred Miller's relistor
People say I'm anti-semitic hello to the Rhythm
When I say George Soros
Anyway
The board important
You were are guitaring
This is the second instance on the show
That he
He was karaoke
Along with it song
What is on the show
The show was on
Wasn't it wasn't like they were this is what he does every time they go to break is just
Karaoke
She's just singing along with this song it is awesome
Anything along the lines of
He had to have known
There is no he had to notify Airport
I am so Furious
Because I was watching the episode live
I can't wait to cut this clip
I can't wait to get this
I'm not go back to the rebroadcast
Big-hearted
So I don't have I don't have
A copy of it
They edited out his karaoke
Karaoke this song
Earlier in the show
He karaoke to Amarillo by Morning
Play George Strait
They come back from break earlier in the show and its Amarillo by Morning
A great song yes
Amarillo by Morning
America
You can tell it cuts because the song Jump
And he's like
My daughter loves
You know she's a
She's like why this man doesn't have a time and he's like
Honey it's a story
The song but it's a story
Battleborn
Alright
I'm legitimately Furious that I don't have an audio of that
And
If we could get this show to take off and I don't have to have a job
I could just get it live
Cuz I want audio that we can play Alex Jones karaoke
That is pretty much the Holy Grail
Because they didn't want people grabbing a hundred percent
Because what if I show like ours exam
Outsmarted us this time
Baby
Schematics for talking so much s*** on very specific Jews and lying about them
Especially in relation to their Judaism
You can't save someone who's drowning
And now again
Anything this is exactly where the next.
You can't save a drowning person
They're trying to call you under push you down
German Shepherd is great dog named Knox got hit by car on
Where is this song
In fact
You can take a nap
Friends house with swimming pool
Someone
The pushy wonder when you save them it was that way around
Future for Humanity
You think you can't save a drowning person metaphorically
Let you drown
He has an inverse ability to use metaphor
Try to make a simile here let me go with the exact opposite of what I'm talking about
And then after he tells the story about the doesn't relate to his point
Listen I just want prosperity
Why don't you talk
Don't track
All over the map
Well
That is
At the very least
Oh yeah
He's not traded for
He's not ready for Trump
Tonight because Mae
People's actually pay attention
He's in an abusive relationship
With himself
Just keep going back to chop like
Minute clip
Is evidence
Then you can't handle doing his own show anymore
And that's why you've been having so many goddamn gifts on lately
He's having Rodger Stone on almost every day
He's having Mike cernovich on all the time
Jerome corsi show up a whole bunch
Savage
He's been on twice in the last two weeks or so that's a big gift for that world
That world of crazy wingding
He's not
Cons of coal
This week to really want to call
And I might
I might start Baba Booey
Okay bro
But
I want to make this public statement to
Alex Jones
Stupidest s***
But compared to his callers
She is a goddamn genius callers are f******
It's so stupid
One lady called in the other day and was like hey
They supported Trump I never voted before
I thought this was going to be a big change
Why don't you get that
Why don't you
What's wrong
Eddie asked her like
She brings up the idea of this pipeline
You know you want to get to Ron
By the Russia can get the oil and what have you
Angie
All you do is talk about all this other stuff
Are you talk about false flags and all this s*** why did you talk
Alex Jones like man we have covered it
Scrambles to find any Improvement
Governor
Just a little clip
I don't like so much
I'm into it
Joya
Metafit metaphorically
So this is how this goes on
Let's see what else you want to talk about
Yeah how dare you not before Wars
Your corporate shill
Fox News
Oh no
At least China and North Korea threat
All sects of muzzle
What's the weather in Payson
The best place in the Middle East
Grab some basic freedom
Huh yeah but the Bulls never recover.
Assaulting people
I don't want to save it.
Didn't that one point be a wonderful place to live
Not
To the point where
You know it sounds almost killed as many syrians this week
What
We were so close
He's so close cuz we agreed with them
The beginning
The world war
I'm looking at knowledge fight going no we've got two things we agree with him on maybe raise that up to 3
Used to be a good place I should change that
You're right correct
Lost my thought I don't know what the first time in 30 episodes
But just completely lost a thought
He's clearly talking about
I wish I seen before we
Regime-change
They were a lovely liberal perfect place
All Alex does is talk about nuclear war breaking out
With North Korea and the
Fox News World War 3
Hoo-boy
That
Doing it wrong
Yeah
No you guys don't like you want to attack
We have to
Pretend
First we got a false flag are not like pretending the sources that are really high level
He keeps also
Sources who are really high-level telling
It's just a mash-up of different words when we get into the right-wing areas
Ail
Mix and match
Inside the White House source
About as high up as you can go
No it's
F****** fan
Three would be answering his phone
We could have been Gavin with you on this one I think
That is exactly how it would be hates pretty
Well yeah that's why he's really mad that previous is answering the phone and giving him information
Is priebus just the fact that.
Is this talking to him
Yeah I guess so
Just because previous answer the phone alright
Right whatever
The goes on
Israel Israel
400 lb
Israel
Is it in
A capital
Thousand
The princes get billions a year
They got whole cities
Whole cities that are air-conditioned
One Refuge
Israel
Really really doesn't understand the whole israeli-palestine
Olympics
Killing Palestinian
You're even misunderstand leave the b******* that he's saying
Saudi Arabia is
Refuses to take
Single
Refugee
A particular the Syrian refugee
Right about the syrians are going to Israel.
What's the Siri
Now they're Palestine
Basically
Was
Giving him
0 sec
Saudi foreign Ministry officials claimed that the nation has received nearly 2.5 million.
However the BBC reports that Saudi Arabia has lied in 500,000 Syrian refugees
While Arab News reported that Saudi Arabia was already home to 500
Thousand Syrian
Okay
What's what's the saying that
Saudi Arabia is lying about
Refugees because they're already
That's an addition
Yes
Cerium Turtle rack
Saudi Arabia tell says it's 2.5 million
Somewhere between it's not zero
Because it's a million times more than
What we
A couple months
Old man Trump
For old man Trump got in the house
We're taking in some
A great mistake in
Severe
But now
Clocking billions of Prince's getting billions of dollars air condition cities
Attempt
Didn't you say
Like they have three big Erica
Content
That house millions of
He's talking about like refugee camps
It allegedly ran
This is something I haven't researched but I don't think is true
I can't
But he likes to make the claim
Like Saudi Arabia has the
Giant refugee camps that are air-conditioned
I am just for Giggles they don't let anyone live in
Pretty funny it's a great prank
Pretty funny prank
I should have thought of that
That's true I really got to raise a lot of money
I think you thinking of a Spartan
Get billions of dollars a year
You just get billions of dollars this year
Saudi Prince
Trump's kids got millions of dollars just for being fake news
Fake news what are they are they just some sort of royalty
We should get rid of the estate
Let's just try and keep track of what he's talking about
How this all fits
Like from clip to clip
It's going to be very difficult
Even Clause 2 Clause we're dealing with
Completely different but I want to keep track of
This is literally there's nothing that like
Okay
I could see Alex
Wishing
Been like sitting here before you came over
I just been giggling and taking out all the words that make this make sense
I have no time I just got off work
Uptown for the
Here's here's the next clip and I want to say within about 2 or 3 clips
We're going to get into
Juice City
Juicy stuff
But we're still a little bit in the Preamble which is this
I called this Manna From Heaven
I'm still
Wait till the dog's name is donk
Not
For Israel
Because I'm not in Israel George Soros
Israel
What what's up where you can see it
Call Jose
EXO
If not
For or against Israel previous clips from this very episode
Sure
Jewish newspaper
Because he kept talking about the mafia led by George Soros
But they're attacking
Everyday
Because
Not
Anti-israel like
Restore
So is he saying that's a Jewish newspaper
No.
Control
Anti-israel
I think
But if you're really trying to track his
That is what he say
I was really trying to do that
For Israel
I get to see the
He begins to see
Play the Jewish newspapers in Israel
He's not talking about some American Jewish new
Israel attacked him for what
Israel
What is this
Which again is an anti-semitic Canard
Really screw up as it is old
What do you mean
Well I mean the globalist is
I don't think he gets that
I mean
That's a good point
I think that he thinks they are different
But they're not
I don't think the globalist exist
Yo
Texas
I love a pixie stick
That's so dumb
But that's unbelievably
More to the point I do I mean this just came up
Just now and I
You didn't
Quite understand this premise
But Alex doesn't understand
The globalist
Controlling the world
Is Finley failed anti-Semitism consciously
Anti-Semitic
And that choosing to ignore that
No I don't think he knows
You think he has no idea
No
Based on his inability to read
Based on his complete lack of self-awareness
I think that he read this dumbass book
When he was 12
This wild hair up his ass about the globalist
He's gone down that road not realizing that every single Cobblestone along the way isn't
You have no idea
He's that dumb
He is Mister Magoo
He is an intellectual
He's become sick
Successful you have no idea
Get it and think he gets it
Of course and if you were if you were listening to Alex Jones regularly
Community
The only complaint they really have about him is he's not enough
Man
If he
Were George Soros
Seen the two of them in the same
No
There would be a f****** dinner party
The worst
Like a drawing-room mystery dinner party
By the end of this night
They're trying to get Alex to shut up didn't work
Is Neptune
Incentive to kill dad
You did not you are not the murderer
Yeah
Despite all this convoluted nonsense and being a complete idiot would you need to know I do know that
Busy as a man
Principles
Conscience
Official song
Going on
Marshall running line
But I want to do cuz the flesh I'm guilty for that
I think you're talking about hookers
The Flash
What is that
He's telling a lot of truth I don't think he wants
What's the talus by my conscience
Sometimes
My conscience is so strong
That I have to do things that are bad for my family
What the f***
Hey sometimes I get tempted by the flesh
I've done something wrong I feel bad about
Like Vapor multiple abortion
That's being a coward
What is the weather
I don't know
Impact for multiple abortions
Yes because
Yells about responsibility
F***** up that is f***** up more evidence of my argument absolutely no self-aware
So the idea that you wouldn't know he's being a big anti-semite
And if he's
He's always
But you know what my conscience sometimes tells me I've got to pay a lady for sex
She's got to go to school
Education should not pay for college
Wow
You're not doing the right thing you are an absolute hero
Nobody nobody
Mila
Prostitute
Damn that's who is without Dan what would they do
I prefer not to use
I apologize sex-worker
I just wanted to make that clear lonely
I just don't want some
Take me out of
Like everyone else
Contacts all the time
Great Clip of heaping
The compulsion to lie about him is strong
Cell phone
100 bus newspapers a day
Everyday sometimes 1000 there's papers
Thousand
Every major NBC ABC CBS NBC affiliate
Weak-minded people on the street
It don't know that's a lot I got to sit there and watch them to stain me and everything
It doesn't hurt me when they're hating me because of my Hugo
It hurts him so bad about your victim
This is gone
How many clips that was number seven not keeping my not all of them are a minute-long
4 minutes into the clip
We're only four minutes into the club
VSCO places you could not possibly already I'm already gone through a weird emotional rollercoaster
Billionaires Arabia
Air-conditioned tent
Jewish newspapers are attacking him
He's got no positive or negative stance on Israel he does have a pro-israel stance
Wild little bit because he
Feels like
And don't feel it
Realized
It's so crazy
It's it's absolutely it's so delicious everybody thinks they're the hero
I mean everybody but some people got another the villain
Even if
Navigation
He has to be megalomaniacal and say
Sometimes every newspaper in the country I did some research on it actually
In terms of daily newspaper
20 / 1,331 Daily newspaper
In the United States
Daily newspapers
Have a cup
Well the New York Times Did you that profile
That's one
And then we got
Washington Post Maybe
Snapchat
Austin Chronicle
No sir
I think it is
Toronto Maple Leafs
Maybe
We do not know where hockey although congratulations on a Cubs season starting by the way
Has nothing to do with anything
Get to our absolute
Globalist
Even though even though
If they did the Ricketts
Rickets is a disease
Right
Anyway
There's no way a hundred newspapers a day are talking about
There's no way
Perception of Victor
Everything is intact
You always under it
Paranoia
Combined with
That's kind of megaloman
Maybe it's not just said
People are attached
He's a victim of
Tire system
Which gives
Him that info
Flavored important
Instead he wants
So badly
Describe
That sort of thing is I kind of mental illness
That's probably
Would probably describe
Paranoid
Interesting
This is going to make this trip a little bit uncomfortable
I think about
Whatever you like to be that them cuz they're slaves
Austin Texas
Is a big shot a homeless people
You're the city dun run them off
They got rid of mental institutions like 20-30 years so there's
Schizophrenic and people all over the streets
Almost every major four-way stop
Downtown Austin
And there's a whacked-out asking for money
I don't get by a con artist so they're out there
Listen to relax or whatever a diabetic I am somebody but I see those kids running
There had an argument for themselves
The wind
Cheese's
That is
If you were self-aware he would have
Have to have been like
Their butt
For the grace of God go I
I am so much like these people so tone-deaf
Those.
No doubt everyone is being brainwashed
By the media think I'm a liar everyone
I feel bad
Because they are so misleading
So to make myself feel better
I go it I go and look at
He gives away
Not
So are you really
They do know their own
He's talking a big game about how
Fix the VIR the homeless problem is in Austin Texas
If I pulled up some
Statistics
The number one city in America for homeless population is
New York
70 5323 the last
Count
Surrounding county is 41000
94 go down to
Chicago
That's like seven on the list.
Just too many
So
Austin is smaller town I think
Relatively
Urban Center City
Temperature the climate is much better than Chicago
Homeless population
Where we are far more regularly
In contact with
The mentally ill about them shutting down
Mental hospital
The part of town that I live in
They say ROM did shutdown
Palmetto hospital around here
And it spits absolute
It goes all the way.
I can understand what you saying
In terms of experience this wandering around and seeing
The tragedy of Life gone wrong
I don't use that as self-care
That's not how I make myself feel better
If you are asked
The phrenic the made it out
I don't think I still would
I think
Kind of Econo like that small-town homeboy story except for adults
They look at Alex
A boy jungle
Bizarre to me
But that's his response
What's the feeling
Mentally ill homeless
Is like
Hey you know what
Feel better about the
Rest of the body
I guess you explain in the other rest
Let that play and then we can
Get back to this
I realized
Here I am conscious
Aware of your political systems
Did the Saints know probably nobody else is
Every now at deeper I go
The connections the discernment
The trust I have a people
Only intensifies
Alameda public
Schizophrenic
Mia Restaurant
My class has had
The basement kid
What
I did not get up now and take them
Down
Cuz I realized
Does that make it better
Does he think these things are actually happening
Does he think these thoughts or connect
Did he
Okay
Go to a restaurant
With him and his family
Anarchist
I can't
It's within the realm of possible but it's very unlikely
He wasn't hit on the back of the head
At the beach
Imma kick your ass Alex Jones
Marcus Barrow
G over the dick
Americans supporting Trump is like
In my mind on the list number 8
Really rank
If he
Yeah
Really convinced
Things actually happen I imagine he was out of the restaurant someone bumped into him
Like he knocked over glass accidentally and he took it as like
With the frisbee
That's my new Gabriel of golf
He loves extreme
Pennywise
I also want to say to that clip doesn't make his dance on
Viewing the Manta
Toledo any better
No no
It provides more ammunition for him being person
Everyone
This but me
Like a person without mental illness
Jon rappoport so he can tell them that the dsm-4 isn't real
No don't worry that you fit this diagnosis
More time let's just go down the list
You tell me which thing
Okay persistent feelings of paranoia and everybody's out tonight
Oh that's not off we're not off to a good start
Even in this scenario Rappaport
Number one
How is Alex
Years that they did not hung up
Maybe more importantly why is this driving
The better microphone that doesn't like
Totally showcases
I don't care. Do you like the headset
I got it cool
Is it
It takes
Enhance
To put this whole set
Together it's possible
Like the set decorator from the atom
Who's just like
How do we make
This room looking
But Mordecai
Just slightly off
And unhung
Have you super weird
This is the closest that we come to you and I being like on Mystery Science Theater
Driven nuts by John Rapport not having no painting
How do I hang it up Rappaport
This clip
Is about to take a turn
That you cannot possibly four
Of course not
Crying after
Again
Okay
Alex was just talkin about
Who doesn't want to beat up people
Who are dumb
No
I guess I don't know
Evidence
You certainly emotionally and verbally
Especially these refugees
Hold onto your f******
Cuz this is weird
I'll take this
Pollo Dominican everybody else been holding my Patriots
I realize something
Fundamental are species on this planet
Oh f***
The species is destroyed
Natural disaster
Species
Everything I survived this is Troy
That's not the crazy part
Does not
I just wanted to stop there
To point out that he
Just realized
Willits thought about that
Greece
Remember
Yeah the world ends.
Do you think he thinks his listen
Maybe he's trying to blow mine
I think that's more along with people I think
He knows I think he's
He feels like he's the only person who knew that
You idiots
Threatening nuclear war
Everybody
I imagined him as the fake deep guy in a smoker Central okay
Horizon
The world end
All history
Dallas
Dogs
30 super f***** up
Because again
We've been talkin about Saudi Arabia having air-conditioned tent Israel
Everybody lies about Alex all the time
This is so weird
There we go
It's up for me worrying a
Long-term War
Yep
We got to leave okay
Alright
Now I see what's happening now I see what's happening
Is obvious
We put we connected all the dots with that one sentence
Everything makes sense everything makes perfect sense
We have to
Destroy the planet we're on
To give us
Proper motivation to get off
And spread throughout the Universe
Destroy the planet we're on somebody
But come to power who will
You still at 8
Yeah but that's not out
No no no no no no I don't think so
No I don't think so either but he doesn't know that he's
Upon
Elsa
$5 fiddle
To get off this
Wow
Ourselves
The global time
I don't know cuz he always talks about the globalist
He's afraid that they're going to go to space
Elysium
Because he loves movies
I think they talked about that
I mean
Fast track at all
It's time
Listen
Get your ass tomorrow
Therapy
Put your you agree with me right I mean like
No he is just all the time
On the cusp of a break
This is his brain kind of spinning around like a like a washing machine
He's on the cusp of figuring something out
This is Alex Jones
He's had to talk to that lady on the phone that I told you about earlier and Buckley
His producers going
I got nothing to do
Talk weird about how much victim and then talk about space I guess
You and you just ripping straight off the Dome
I don't know cuz I know I know where all this goes
I don't think
Started it was talking about
That's not how it ends
Middle
Paper B
But like I don't
I don't know I don't know I'm listen to this
I don't know what the point is
I know how it is
I don't know
Who's leading up to
We need to steal billions of dollars
We need to use them
To stop the Israeli globalist newspaper
I'm criticizing Alex Jones
What do you build an air-conditioned tent
Spaceships
Planet
Shoot the whole message to Alex I'm not to look at him anymore that's not what he said I'm putting
Does Netflix
To get off the planet
It's award
Made me so bummed out
And it might be an explanation
Super some of his toxic masculinity
Unfortunately
F*** is that big fat
Plants beautiful I love it
Just like I love mine
Mommy when I was 6 years old all God
6 years old she kicked me off for lap
You don't get any more love
That's coming out soon
Oh you just figured it out
We just got the we just got the flashback he's everything to Rosetta Stone
That's like the
Whatever they do serial killer background that's always the moment where you like
I don't know if that was one incident that happened to his mom was like
You don't get love no more you don't to be a mama's boy
She said you don't get love
He said she said those exact
Zach makes you think that it's probably an actual memory
Yeah using a
Like
A line of dialogue of hers
And he's not being over spinel releases
Specific like he normally does when he's
I remember I was
Choose
Dress right
Chair rocking back and forth
Dementia
And I think that long pause is more ineffective
Say that
Actually really emotion
Then that's another indication that something
Thing is b*******
Is money starts fake crying
Stuff like that
She's not overtly like
I watch the video he's not overly likes Pig crying like
Play song about
Now that's
What happened
Really bad for you
Yeah that's that's
That's a
Peter likes
My mom was not the most attentive to my needs and what have you
But she wasn't nearly that
Like
I am I'm still dealing with it as a thirty-two-year-old time like I'm still in therapy talking about how
My mom was
Way too distant
I'll be real with it
I really
No it's fine
They feel uncomfortable
Jordans
That's always the best answer I have no f****** idea who knows
Definitely had at least
Emotional abuse
And you know he's
Clearly Hero Wars
His dad who's a
CIA dentist
Have some sort
And so it kind of makes sense
A lot of these really
And and about masculinity
And the idea that
His maternal figure would be like
Don't be a p**** you're a man
That reinforces even
Further all of these masculinity
I can't imagine
Although
I dunno
The one is mom threw him off of lake that was a
Which is
Maybe Alex Jones you started you should have started relating to your mother
Read military history
What did she like
Probably a lot nicer
We could ever have
Alex is such a liar
I have no idea
Call Evergreen weather is Mom was the perpetrator of
Some sort of child to be
Adamstown
He was younger or not I don't know
So regardless of our reality
Has very little bearing on this show.
Is the weather
Something
Cuz that you don't you don't come on are on your f******
Nationally syndicated radio show
Lego goosebumps
Specific
So you don't get love no more
You would remember that I bet if a neighbor's parent told you that you might complete it in your brain
There's all sorts of
Or grandma or something like that
This whole time
Breakfast
Okay
Theory
I'm listening
His mom
Died in
In childbirth
So he is always had this
Resentment
Women for not being around
He was raised by a
You taught how to do all of the
Never had a
Female experience wolf
Yep very much
Is bad when actually married
Striker Martinez right now
Future
Humans
Cannot even imagine what is in store for us
Chimeras
Successful
As the heroes
Play the Cornerstone
Everything we do after this
That is unlimited
We have to escape this test
Destroy ourselves
The other test
I'm not sure what that mean
You don't escape
So we have to stay
Yeah
No no
If we destroy ourselves
Which Wich
Know what
Start
I can't it's 40 seconds long
Our destiny
That's right now
Future
Humans
Cannot even imagine what is the score for us
What are successful
What did he just say
Spider-Man
Humans
Imagine
Humans cannot imagine what is the store for us
But I've noticed about him a lot is
Like whatever but
He makes me really mad a lot of time cuz he has some similarities to like Dusty Rhodes
I love Dusty Rhodes
They are not ham
I like
It kind of makes me think of a hard time from oh we're just arose
Rate
He's a working
In class hero
He's everything I love
Alex
Is the power out
What is sum
Text Luther
The verbal symbols
Yeah I'm pretty sure it's just everybody from
That's what they say
As the heroes
Play the Cornerstone
Everything we do after this
That is unlimited
We have to escape this test
That is literally the definition of
Every generation
Is
Looked back upon as being
The Cornerstone for what happened
Time for the Next Generation
The set the table for the present
Like this till we make it
They'll still be like
You know that got soccer
Pretty cool
Maybe let's go with Galileo
I've lost track of what you're saying
Because I'm excited about what about
Figure out how he thinks history
Time is a circle
He watched
You know what I think he's watched her.
From Texas right now
I mean the other has all his beliefs about the elite sex rings and what-have-you certainly matches.
Anyway
Actually is not what I'm super excited about but
Sees it through
Foxy's it like
Sex workers
Right now I don't remember
Lindsey Graham socks
Instagram people like
John McCain they want temporal power
Instead of chivalry honor and building something true
Because others won't stab you in the back
But because you're going to Trailblazer plant the path the future
Is interesting because f*** is he talking about
Isn't it interesting that you stammer in kind of
Screwing up words and more than when he's drunk
Stop.
He said
We will be the ones who have laid the foundation reset Blade the foundation
He f***** up a word in that sentence
His insane like when he's drunk
Very clear
I mean it does go back to my argument
Just filling time
Someone
Cancel
I don't want to go back to the collars
No we're not.
I really just got worried that his name wasn't
That cuz it sounds so stupid
Ziering away from Trump
Oh know what's going on
Karaoke but then I'm going to talk nonsense
Yeah that's all
I know built this up
Velvet up this next clip up quite a bit
Yes
Don't say a word over this club
And we're already I could already sensitive
Cuz I'm going to just stare at your face
Cuz I cuz I want to
Try and sent the exact moment
That you realize what he's talkin
Because it's on clearance
But then it becomes clear
And you will
Revel invisible
Might be a slight indication that he listens to wash
Or
It's possible he seen one of our
One of the two
Okay
Oh man.
North Korea of the things that are happening
You can see
How much danger does planet is in
That's why I get guilty when I get angry or say things tongue-in-cheek
My dog dies
My dog just died the night before
Blunt
Rosemount
The story
My dog has died the night before I've been up all night long bury the next day my parents they were on vacation was there doggies be my dog's tail
A h playing that a heart attack died
Aneurysm whatever was blood coming out
That should have gone to work that day and I shouldn't have been up that night either Ian or at work
Call me Russian agent find you another.
That was me just sad about my dog
A trip that somebody calling me stuff I'm not that they really make me that mad
Here's the here's the even crazier whenever he said he had to beat his
Well
Cuz you don't
So he said instead of him
Yeah he was just sad over his parents.
Heart attack
Is that what happens when I think not
I don't think it is either
I don't understand the visual
Drunk for 2 hours again
I have pictures of the cup but he's drinking out of
Power Tower
I've never seen
Breaking news exclusive email when Alex Jones
Or drunk because you said about his dog I would totally fine
Totally fine as long as he owns up a my dog. Only thing that
With him
The truth in there is I shouldn't have gone to work
Really good boy
He wasn't going to work
No special report he didn't have to do that.
Also when he says it was at 11 at night he's lying
In the middle of
2 hours earlier than
No that is kind of like I've been up all day
And now it's 11:45
Yeah so you want a timestamp
No I don't even have a dog
Cat dude.
My point is what I hear that
Holyshit
I got so excited
Cuz this is
Minute of
Tangential nonsense unrelated to anything
I bet he says
The world is in danger
A long pause
Crazy locked and then I looked at you because you were
Because you had this weird Rhythm thing where every second you were turning your head a little bit
Because of my hair
Forever
Shouldn't have gone to work that everything
Heat
Talkin about
Ways to work clip there's no f****** way that's
I mean it
Recognition of his own mortality
Yeah we might emotional we might have more
But also the idea
Grizzly like Jesus
Describing it is
That totally makes sense I get it
I get it
If you're sad about your dog and then you start
Screaming
Obscenity cuz the gloves are off and then you get homophobic
You talk about wanting to sell your car and then misaligned Muslims at 9 a.m.
That's the part that really should have been in
Ears
No more Americana
Who wasn't great is it
There was a link to that episode
Carlos Beltran
Rarely used
Coward just own up to it
Well but imagine if he said
I wouldn't respect him so much more
Listeners
Who's to say
That's a good
A pound
Krowd
He's so into this weird
Version of Christianity in like
Demon
And what have you if he wants to try and use it
I could see him by cuz we're never going to let
VSCO
It's so well documented
If you were to Twisted he could defeat Us by being like a problem with alcohol
You know the Lord is helping me with her
You can win over even more people
In the same way that is we said he has a problem with
Sex workers
Temptations of the
The Flash The Flash
The Flash
Speak
Anyway
I think you now realize why
Needed
When I was walking home
From the Train
Yeah I heard that
I heard this I literally yelled holyshit down the street
You a******
You f****** a****** Alex
He does not go more into his dog
But
He does say something at the end of this clip that I really want to get into
Yes please
There's a very good chance
There's a very good chance we're having to Clearwater
And it's six million people are going to die
Foxes world record
What radiation poisoning farm-raised
But they're going to survive
The Bible says the planet will be killed
Look up in the Bible
Just a little guilty that I don't have a flash
Convince my family
Disease
Family to go to space
No
He's going to he's going to talk a little bit more about it in the neck
Clip
But what he specifically talking about
Yeah I know
But what I want to take away from that
I think is more important
Is that his family doesn't believe him
He is crazy
Stop problem
This time he is right
No
I cried wolf
My fears think he could be right and that in terms of the global situation
My more rational brain
Knows that wheel
Most likely deescalate.
That before it happens
Surprise a lot
No I I would have said that
A year ago
The gloves are off Thunderdome and the gloves being off means we're all going to die
Yeah
I think more specifically what I'm saying is
If I have to choose between
Trusting Alex or his family
I got to go
That's a tough nut
To crack right there
That again
His spouse chose to be with him
Typical
I don't know
It's his personal life is very
Tough to disentangle
There's a lot of stuff that I have no idea
Of course not really that important to me what I mean is
Woman did choose to be with them and now I don't know if that means I can trust her
One will ever loved either of us
Certainly not me
No crazier
Three-bedroom in my parents house, I'm not a little bit more
About
I believe they heading
When was Mexico
How many tries to get he tries to
Poetic
I think he realizes and pick it up
10 minutes
I've been all over the map of got to try
And get a little poetic
Just a normal guy
Throwback
Michael Savage
Then we just
Where we going to look at those are seeking power
You never even had thought
Functionaries
A corporate
Hungry
Seeking creature
Directed by millions of souls are unconscious just
Looking for salvation in believing that I dive down some rap
Find absolute Nirvana
Twilight of the Gods
What is the end of humanity
Zoe
Go from
Hico from there's a
Nuclear Winters
We don't want
Do you know why
We like having friends
And restaurant
Restaurants regular regular
We like going out to restaurants be like
Every single time
I'd like when he talks about going to get a meatball sub
He's a great Broad
Wikipedia
The first thing that Alex comes up with
Because if you listen to Michael Savage
And you even talked about going to a restaurant
That's the only thing I think about
Cuz he is a artist
What it comes to just talking about a great sub
You did very very sad but when he starts screaming about like a chicken parm
Get out of the way
No because
Dr. Savage behold his Doctorate is in
Meatball subs
Basically the doctor of nutritional medicine I didn't realize
So you basically just have a doctorate in
Going to Subway
We mailed
Speaking clearly to the peep
Alright
Then I tried
Everyone who's against us wants to kill the Russians or the Chinese
My friend
Blankets
It's be either or that's unfair it's so stupid
He did this earlier and I didn't bring it up
Disagrees with him w
War
It's f****** stupid absolutely don't want war
Trump is
We don't want no more
We don't have to
Yeah
Aspirations
Apt
So then he goes
The Inferno on
Each Pro tanto
We look at those
Power
Who never had
Functionaries looking for the corporate rat
Twilight
What was he trying to say
What he said it's a beast
Is there a part of the Beast
A corporate speaking thing
Like OU lost track
Bring up the Beast that kind of has that
Sofia the Beast is the globalist
It's a group of the globalist
So all of these people are willing their souls into the larger beasts that is
Globalism
Okay
I have to make a delineation globalism
The trend
Towards their being a global community
Goodness of
Economy
That sort of thing
Is a real thing
Globalism in terms of Alex Jones's definition is not a real
But his fake version is the Beast
Said he's referring to
Also not Hank
McCoy
The car
From that one movie where the car was called the Christine
What else do we got what other base now it's just
So is everybody
Selling themselves Ibiza global
I have no idea I've never heard that before I swear to God you made that up just now I think it might just be a WWE
Pay-per-view I watched one
Japan
There we go that much
Yeah sure you got into Stanford
Wrestling reference is already a very good storytelling medium
And Dusty Rhodes
Defensive I don't even really like that wrestling that much
You know it is a great method of story
I love death
Kathy Rhodes
I remember this obscure pay-per-view
Craigslist Tampa
I'm fine with that
What is he trying to say
I mean what was the
What was the Goddamn point
Of that hole we look at those seeking power who never had
Is Lindsey Graham's the John McCain
They are trying to
Facilitate
The end of the world nuclear war
World War 3
Maybe I might be giving a little bit too much credit but I think this is what
It comes from
We have the
The um came about Nations before World War
Attempt
Ideas of these Global interfaces
Are these bodies of of
A bunch of government
And a bunch of representative government men of the world
So we don't end up with another
Holocaust
Or we don't end up with another
War to end Wars as it work
Yeah
Galaxy Theater
Okay what happened was
Because evil globalist
Started World War 1
So everyone would die and be horrified
And then they start the League of Nations
To take sovereignty away for
From Individual countries
They put solidated as a whole from the world and then they can enslave the entire world
Now that didn't work out that time WWII
And the Jewish Mafia propped up Hitler
In order to do the the crimes
Sean Spicer
Around Passover
I hope it gets hit by a truck
F****** Focus we need to get rid of trump will get the f*** about the dumb f****** frostbites
I agree I agree
Emirates conversation
Internet
Orange
I don't give a f*** about everything
Get rid of trump and then week
You can deal with United pretty crazy
I think
Did the talking about Spicer stuff is important to taken away trumped-up
Because what he's doing is
What is known
Sort of
Ambivalent Holocaust denial
There's the transit people have like forgetting pieces of the Holocaust publicly
It's either intentionally dog with lie to these white supremacist groups that have
It's just part of who
In that
He's not he's not trying to exploit anybody
He's just that
Sebastian Gorka is a literal Nazi
Genoa
The the Holocaust statement
That's a trump
Put out the Collegian mention the Jews
There's just a trend of anti-Semitism that goes
That's why it's important I think
Yeah because it does go back to Trump
It's a bunch of people that he surrounds him
Southwest
Either have no awareness of the reality or deny the reality or are literal.
You cut the snake off at at
And then everything else goes Cumberland
Yeah but sometimes you know like if you're fighting a boss in a video game sometimes it's take out his arm for you
Metaphorically speaking
Different
You got to get through the first one in order to beat the game you might have to
The world
Amen
We were texting and
So that was my specific goal I've got to be before the world ends
Good2Go everybody with him talking about
Twilight of the Gods it will be the end of humanity
Professor Christian to believe in the
The Twilight of the bolts
Especially that's like Viking language
The book or something like that
And all of the citation
This is the last clip of this
Weird ride we've been on
Starts up
It seems so unbelievable
I have
At the beginning of this
Enjoy where it goes
And although the Twilight of the Gods
What is the end of humanity
How many phone calls
If you want
Water filtration systems 40%
Water filtration system
Don't you do it don't you Twilight
Filmy on waterfall
Filtration
I know that this is like we usually just play like always going into a sales pitch
I want you to shut up
It's so f****** sad
Supergirl
Other products infowars.com in Foursquare., 888-253-3139
Support us and we'll bill will move forward
We got the children's up
Toothpaste is fluoride-free with
Yeah. Everything is silver Solaris X1
Thanks
Fortnite.com
888-253-3139
Calling so long
That's a nice reminder there at the end that he's the head of colors
Multiple
Jesus
I love this world we live in
F*****'-a
Insane
Man
What
Fuk was that
That was manna from the gods
That was me saying I don't know if we can do a good episode today
I meant God smiling down upon me and say oh yeah
Make hay
That was that was a hundred percent like
I don't want to get biblical hair or anything like that but that was a moment when I doubted
Myself when I was at work today I was like
Listen to the episode I don't know I don't know if we can do it I mean this Savage stuff
Kinda interesting
Could really don't want to talk about Alex's take on the war what are we going to do
The necklace happened
Pickup
Bring up sky
Big
Up somehow
Somehow this is
Turning you back
I believe in the great magnet
The law of coincidence
Who cares listen
But it's
Group of bulshit here
This is going to be really fun
Synthesize
What I'm working on
I was when I was putting this together when I was when I was cutting the clips
Like I said all I did was
I did not cut out anything
We're going to end up having to do and I think we have along the way
Critical analysis
Text in a different language
You have to try and figure out my shoe
What is the f*** is
Is going on your face called
Just say something
Is the author really ink
Control what is their name
What's going on here
So we start
Phaidon
Studio
In the background on Skype a picture
Lays on Hound
City confused Rob do
Notre Dame record for Studios
LOL
Thursday's get it right
Spider-Man locket
I don't want to take Alex Jones out of
Don't f****** pretend you don't know what shows up
Alright
Jon rappoport works for an hour
How else is he going to afford those.
Alright alright
That's Doughty Arabia
Has
At least
300 princess
You talked about whatever I first started taking notes
Still
The first one is really
Which is about everyone
Asthmatic
You want to talk about because
Hoagie
Open
Now the second one get rid of cuz it's
Justin talked about his dog
No yeah
So yeah
No but then you're even cutting out the other thing
They came before that
Fox news and media is all on World War 3
Best mainly because I agree with
But then
Steatorrhea is in it
Well
He is not advocating
For World War 3
He telling you
Prepare for
And I do not disagree with them
Are bald
In let's go
As I tried to say to each and every one of them individually before you got back
Yeah
Critically
The only thing that matters is somatic
Syria is in
Those are two interesting ideas
Cape that I'm I'm going to pull
I apologize
I'm now just I'm a student
Wreck at your lecture the only thing that I do think now that you reminded me
That matters
Is not
Now I will tell you this
I will get to know I could not
I was surprised when you starting your critical analysis literally crap and and
Rodent-like is that is
To me that is the key
Alright
That is
What is the central metaphor
Popeyes
Because
His
Do you can't save somebody who is drowning
Whereas this dog
Cannot help
Even when they aren't
Interesting
Now
Metaphor going to be flashed out throughout the course of urinalysis
Alex
Alex Jones
Is the dog who is trying to save you from drowning
Even though you are
Hanging out
Closet
That I would go I go a step further that he is exactly that
But he's also
That dog
Managing to drown you when you aren't in the pool like if you engage with that dog
The dog who drowns you with a battery
A night unlimited amount of money
So much billions
Which suggests that their total worth
Is more than the entire GDP of the
Which is being printed a job salary
Thing that you are related to the king
Yeah if is he saying that there are hundreds of princes
I believe you believe that aside
Has hundreds
Saudi Arabia
I misspoke
Alright
Wego from Saudi Arabia
Refugees
To Israel
To Israel but I'm trying them on his on his writing
Alright
We go directly from there
To Israel is a good guy
But they're opening themselves up
Palestinian
From
Not Palace
From Syrian
He doesn't have a positive or negative View
Of Israel
Immediately
Following that quote
He has a positive view of Israel
But his at his actions imply
It's not on the fence
Jewish newspapers are attacking him
Broward Jewish refugees
Array
Do do a little actually he's always trying to do the right thing even though he cannot think about it
Even though he's conscience
He finds himself tempts
Did buy the Flash
Right I must f***
Hundreds of newspaper
My suggestion there today
My suggestion there
He is guilty
And he believes that
People are gossiping
Oh man
I'm not criticizing his
His thoughts
They are getting into the salacious details
I think
I think yes
I think he is not talking about newspapers
I think he's talking about
People he knows
Talking
Or maybe blog
Exactly
Expedition
The things that they say their critique so that like
Why won't he go after Israel which kind of does match up with the tone that he saying
Thinking person thinks that I think crazy conspiracy blogs
Which
Once again
He kind of
Want their approval in the same way they want
Everybody's
Sure
New York
Then we go directly to
Schizophrenic
Immediately following him being attacked
We go to him remembering
How he deals with that
Which is by giving
His people
Money
Some of them
Stomach
But I really think that that wasn't the
Pointe Pacific Apartments
He even based on his words
When he goes and he
Refuse the schizophrenic
It's not about giving money that's not the point that he's making it's like I go there and I realize
Everyone is
He goes need to cease
A like
Cuz it's from him
That
Everybody is attacking
To him immediately giving money
Now there is a mid
Point there there is a midpoint
That I don't think matters
Because I think what matters
He makes
Himself feel better
By doing what he thinks
Is the Christians can I end
We go directly to the species is destroyed through
Yeah right
That goes from the schizophrenic to the species being destroyed
His
Hero worship
Money
Jewish newspapers attack
Trying to do the right thing but sleeping with hooker
100.3
100plus newspapers are attacking him at all the
He is been talking
About schizophrenia also people.
Family
Always under attack
Flips into his mind skitzofrenix
Then we go directly to the ultimate
Schizophrenic
Fear is that he's the only person who can save the species
He's from destroying it
The Stranger
How much he loves
This beautiful plan
And Mama will never love again
That's when we get into that
He goes through this emotional just
Just every every possible Spectre of emotion
Mostly feared
Beer and abandon me
Bitter
Then
I had the baby some of that came from mom throwing him off
A boy keep coming back to like really empathic
Pac-Man
Like you're an alcoholic get help you feel bad for you
Alex your mom didn't love you enough
So bad for you
Certainly
Definition of the word
No matter what angle you look at and that's coming from me
People have tried to be stand-ups for a while
Most empathic
Adam hope
That's the thing that kind of
Threw me for a loop
Cuz we go directly from
Was him telling us about the
The future that coming
Guitars
Exactly
Either that is a hopeful moment
He really wants to escape his
I actually think
That
Where you see hope I see the reverse
I think that he's saying that because he knows
Science fiction fantasy
Getting off the planet
Especially
The next 51
Gloom thing
Getting IP I think it's like that is never going to
I hate positing it as
The other alternative
Means that we're too
I believe
Alex Jones believes we will get off
What many believe the Trump is going
Going to cure everyday
In that regard I believe he does
Okay
Lindsey Graham John McCain
Getting us away from chivalry and honor
Of course shirts Shore
It wasn't the chivalry Don Quixote
Maybe a schizophrenic
Very good chance of nuclear winter so we come back down
Hit that bottom right there
We can
Family doesn't believe him anymore
Feel like
And this is this is my ultimate
Kind of
Synthesis
Of all of this in
He believes
That he is trying to save his
His family
And they are reject
Yeah
I'm back at Monk
Don't look you just gave me was so possible
You thought I wasn't going to make it back there
Also was knocked the dog that died
The night that he was drunk on air
Now
Absolutely
Proud
Your thesis
Is interest
I don't think
Accounts for everything
That that is
Underlying
Psychoanalytical critical theory
I mean if you want to look at his career at 8
I made it got to go back to that s*** with his
You are really
Overly
Get back to the root of it
Where's the income from primary relationships when you're a child being severed in and being being
Vulnerable and threatened by like this
This caretaker doesn't love me anymore which is exactly what
Describe
Like this idea of Abandonment leads to paranoia
No maybe it's being
Triggered by the idea like
I want to run away to the Cayman Islands
Let's get away from here
Calm down
Triggered by that I think so
Adjust this
And it's not just
His immediate year fight
Right but I think it is
I think it is the Trump
And this
Please also abandoned by Trump in the same way of feeling abandoned by his family
And his
And he abandoned
Because they
But they're at the very least they're starting
To change their mind
A lot like Michael Savage
Exactly
Everyone is leaving
That
You know it's fat
Much like a dog
For the last 20 years or so that he's been on the air
As he's been ignored by everybody
He's been doing nothing but
Drawing more gravity
Everyone's coming to him
The robbed the world of the world
Like all these reporters
Leanne Macado's
Shroyer's
Overtime they've all gravitated
Towards his energy
They've come in
What f**** him over
Is
Finally latching onto a politician
Yep
Jumped on somebody else's with Trump
And
Because of that
Because of the
Mental gymnastics
Badoo
He ends up alienating
Steve pieczenik
Who is his
His source for a lot of his narrative
Rodger Stone probably going to pray
Two of them still singing
I want it before I tell you
I'm fascinated by your narrative
I think it's possibly
Accurate
If not
It's at least very
It would be a
Great
Play
I would love to see that on stage
Like I would love to see the like first
Being the sky
Full of
Vim and vigor and like
He has a family and he learns about the globalist
The second is there is a mutt
Better story to tell about Alex
Truly a tragedy
Greek tragedy unfolding are we the chorus
Alright I will go to the assholes
Aretha furies
Worse
Exactly
The other day
Rodger Stone was on
And he said that he has a guy
Who's about to die
Who's the source
That wants to spill the beans on John McCain
He's going to give Infowars the scoop
He's going to give them the exclusive
That
Insane
We don't know what is on Mondays
Haha
What's going on
Rodger Stones immediate reaction is
The best man for the job
This is not a story it robbed
Who is the best man for the job back I can't f******
The other the other options
Somebody needs to take out the trash
Who is the best man for the job I thought you meant as a host
Puppet I don't know sifl and olly get them in there I don't give a s***
He has that you have
Big story to break
So I can get Rob do on a
The most
Easily suggestible format
At all
Like if you have like let's pretend
For a f****** hot sex
Nima
Raging massive Rock
This is a real story
And there is a deathbed confession
About
John McCain
Can be verified
And is our to set
Is going to
Destroy his career
And his reputation
What's the temperature
Let's pretend that okay I might have to put a lot of thinking caps on it
Pantheon
Of Infowars reporters
I would say the last person I put on it
Is Alex's son
Because he's a child
He can't hang
Are you still on the roster selling I weird things to put your cell phone in to get radiation
Which is great glad to see him being off printer.
She's the last
He's the ladder
This a real product
It's
Is the name of the
La Jolla
After this thirteen-year-old
The last person I would send is robbed
He's in,
Yes
If that's a real story
That's a career
Whether that's a big scoop
Yeah you want to f****** send that to somebody who can actually handle one journalist
Took down John McCain
And you got to give that to think like might have a career in there
Might have potential who can accurately research follow-up
What is Ashley Beckford like I said I've never heard port
She seems to have a much better head on your shoulder
She still has
It's it's it's very difficult
But she doesn't seem like as much of a dick
Is a lot of ugly and McAdoo doesn't seem like as much of a dick
Maybe it's because the two of them are women
Possible
I would send Owen Shroyer
I hate
But I would send him
Okay kind of has
He kind of has
Yeah
You got the wild
We were the f****** rob do
Again outside Lee Ann McAdoo probably
Like the women who work there
No it's not even that
Supercharged
Squire we Pro women on Infowars for obvious
Reason the people
No I mean
Culture of toxic
Masculinity
You and I
Recognize that immediately as being the most
Damaging possum
Base course we're going to prefer the women on Fox
What they deserve better
I'm scrambling my head
The reason that I say this about Ashley
That I think that she's better than the rest
Fieldpiece
Does
And the way that you interact with people is still
I'm still Infowars
You can tell that her brain is a little boring gay
She seems to have better Improv
Call chops
Is dealing with a situation
Exist
More than other people
I know that's kind of abstract in a little bit vague
But it does you can tell
If you watch her
Any watch a million
Never heard her name before she's a rainbow snake
She plays rainbow smash
Improv
She doesn't
Leastwise not a back-to-back right before draft
My point is
If there's an expose about JonBenet
Can't cut it that's good advice
Houston
Don't send
Dinicu me up
I was just about to say
Do you know where Rappaport with my brain
A picture
Where he has been hiding
This whole time
I would give you like Batman
Any amount of money
To see him interview this guy on his Deathbed
Unobrush
With an unhung picture
Defeat him go
Anywhere on the field
And then like like a game of where's Waldo
We just see in the background that I'm hug picture
Gorgeous
I've never seen John Ray
Stand up
She might be in a wheelchair I literally have no idea doesn't matter
The matter
Pennywise
Yeah I thought you're rambling outro but like I don't know how else to correct
What does it mean
That doesn't send us down a rabbit hole of what
I think it's you're not far off in the ballpark
I think he's not
In the ballpark
I used car
Watch what I'm writing down right now
It is
Alex Jones
Nonc
Apollo said knowledge underscore site
You can check
Review We Love review
Podcast before also real website
It's knowledge fight.com you can go they confide all our Archives of episodes
You can find a autobiography of Alex Jones also some documentation of his
His mama text him off his knee
That is going to be written up in the near future
I also have a new documentation
Coming out I think it might be out by the time
Circumcised
About Hillary selling uranium to Russians
Thoroughly researched
Check that out
Spoiler alert
Gmail.com
Rimowa assigned wine bottle
Send us your address
Also we might give us your name will throw the wine bottle at the window into some sort of body of water
And hope it makes it
Also I'm specifically talking to you drew
Thank you for your interest in a shirt once more people
We might get some
Because there's one person who has emailed me to polish
A shirt
Are exposing
No lot of people hit us up on Twitter
Outside
Anyway
Just saw ghosts in the shop
It's been a lot of fun
Hello policy Knox
Holding
Alex