Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Beverages
What's your first name
I don't know I don't know
Little person remember a whole lot of
Like I said
Large gaps in my memory from
People talk about how they remember
They were like 45 and some
I am almost
Nothing a lot of my earliest memories are things that have been wreaking
Constructed from like
Pictures that my parents have earliest memories I'd like a baseball
When we lived in
Cambridge mask
Real young under the age of
I remember the picture of it
You know those things like that
Yeah I think that's
Completely
I don't know
Jacob
The earliest one
And it's also tough
About any memories right now.
Because I'm on almost no sleep
From people in my new apartment complex keeping me up until four 5 in the morning
With their bulshit so
I celebrated by getting a bath bomb never at never used a bath bomb before I give you my review on that
Some Sultan I like I used to like a bubble bath
Never explored
Bad review
Well I mean it's fine
What have you stolen enjoyable
It's called a bomb
Adjuster
It's a sort of Pisgah little bit in the tub
I really expected to sound like I don't know what I expected fireworks or something
Celebrate
Couple days before May
Love it
April 2026
Alex's just got back
From going to Bullhorn in Washington DC
Yelling at the Capitol Building to write it back on Twitter absolutely house that goes
So horribly wrong
So horribly
Maddie
People who make this show possible who are sporting
First of all
I'm a policy wonk
Daniel Tiger
Don't like how
Just here it might become less predictable with my
Next
Someone sodomites Italy a bucket of poop
Thank you so much
You are now attacking
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Make it so much better
It's probably not him know Ron Artest
Sports.com
What up
Crazy stuff
This is going to be this is going to be bad
So enjoy a little bit of fun
With this out of context drop
Fortunoff
Knockout the rapist sleep aid
That's enough
That'll give you some stuff for where things are at
Do you have to buy a bottle of like brainforce you get a bottle of knockout for
For free
2% off it makes you think
Yeah kind of
The framing of it is really bad it makes
Hundred percent off
Good
Good stuff
Fire it out of a cannon
Let me give you a little bit of a sense
What's going on
Alex has a business model he talks about how the money stream is not doing great
The money is not good to mention
Really need to take over the world
I can do a day
Not a multimillion-dollar big
Yeah yeah yeah
So
We begin on the 25th
Alex
Is talking about that what happened
While he was in
A little bit of a
We got to have an impromptu
Absolutely
Authentic
Not set up interview with
Let me know soros's Sean and then did some trading with them on
Wall Street to offered me
Going to join the Dark Side
That's a separate time he offered me a hundred fifty million in Bitcoin backgrounds worth a dollar apiece when it first came out
He's talking about Max
Kaiser you ran into Max Keiser
Trump Hotel
You ran into
Max Keiser
Nominally otherwise
He's a journalist
Speedworks rrt
The show on art
He's a beautiful man about town I think you might be
I think he might have some connections in Media
And stuff like that
Alex
Guest
He's one that actually probably has more of a
Careers
Everytime you tell me
He's a journalist
Hazard
A guy
Tried to sell me on maxpoint
I can't actually have a job
If you were super into Bitcoin
Pretty profitable
Good amount of money off it
I don't think it would be that weird that you might want to f*** around and start your own coin
Even if it's not like something you think is going to be the make you
Your nest egg or whatever it could be fun
Cuz it's hilarious been out
I'm not sure that he sells Max going as hard as
Or we pretend he does
I speak as a joke talk about it probably more than he does
Okay still net worth
Okay just the time we've been paying attention
Different stories about how the globalist have tried to get him to come over to their side
He said that Fox News Executives of operative
Million-dollar contract
He said that vaguely described people have offered him tens of million dollars to turn on the Republic and all the noble Patriots
30 represents
What are you super f***** up doing that Reddit ask-me-anything session he also seemed accidentally admit none of that actually
Even happened
When he responded to a question about being offered tons of money
By saying it never happen
The new version received presented
Is that a Soros connect
The person is definitely not Max Keiser
Overton millions in Bitcoin
As the fabled payoff
For him to sell out
50 million
Something like that
Until January 2009
Both in terms of
He told the stories
And in terms of weather stories he
He's telling our set
Likes it when you tell the story of the present day
These stories were step before January 2000
Before
Yeah he was telling stories
It took a year after that point
In January 2009 for any recorded commercial
Directions to happen
When some dude.
10000 Bitcoin
Which would be worth approximately 40 million dollar
Crazy
Fun it wouldn't be until July 2010
It wasn't until April 2011 Bitcoin value ratio with a dollar
Fluctuating wildly
Probably because it was completely unregulated
There's a maximum of 21 million Bitcoins that can ever exist
Circulation
The system and how it works
Could have offered Alex could ever exist in late 20s
And it would still only be worth
$2000000
Alex
Idiot
Even if they offered him every single Bitcoin at the point with bitcoins worth a dollar each that would only be 21 million dollars
Which Alex by his own like
How much money I make and what takes to run this operation that
You run out of that money at f****** fast in existence
Nothing
I hate I hate
Because every
Read more about it like the mining bit
I didn't know that there could only ever be
21 million
That's part of what makes you type there's only like 17
See million in circulation right now is look like
One of these peoples chief
Complaints about the idea of like Fiat Quran
How gold has a finite amount theoretically in the universe
Same thing with Bitcoin there is a finite amount of them
Which
I guarantee that they will always have some value or whatever
I guess
I have a sense of what
Actually going on here
Alex recently ran into
Where he mentioned he had offered Alex 10000 Bitcoin
In the past
Would it would be worth 50 million dollars today
It's Alex response that is 50 million dollars
Alex knows that this makes him look stupid for not taking them
So you need to create a reason for him to have not for him to have been skeptical.
Associate the cryptocurrency with it at 10
Chapter globalist payoff
Alex is a bimetallic hard-currency guy from way back
He showed legitimately only exist
Today because of the investment of Ted Anderson invite his resources in the lake
So at no point while Ted was still Alex a sugar daddy
Could he ever have cozied up with an alternative currency
There's no way that would have thought
But just because Alex is in the pocket of a gold and silver salesman
A lot of people in his orbit
Cryptocurrency Skippers
Over the course of his career it's been very
Frontman
For pump-and-dump Stipe
A very very much appears that way based on looking over the people who try to
Seduce Alex into Bitcoin
A number of his gas
Who tried to get Alex
Which would lead this audience to buying up with
Would most likely salad that elevated price point leave Alex's audience holding the bag
This is something that John McAfee is b a
Particularly criticized about
Promoting coin specifically to raise their value providing opportunities for people in the know to capitalize
Something that people talk about a lot
In Bitcoin forums you can find people
Discussing this openly
Like this commenter who said this
On 9 p.m. on Christmas Eve in 2017
Quotes
You need to stay in tune with his tweet
Whatever one is
Doing for a while now
Are you need to be
Be fast on buying these coins that because you might get stuck in the middle
Too slow doing it
Just keep looking at his Twitter account you'll be part of his pump-and-dump
Of course the reality is
Matter of minutes
The people watching
Twitter for clothes will be too slow and they'll be the ones who end up losing money
When the dump happen
Before they're ready
The role that McAfee plays in these operation
Almost certainly one that appears that Alex has probably been offered
To play
But not by the globalist
For whatever reason maybe because he's loved hard currency too much
Maybe because Ted told him he couldn't
Cuz you just didn't
Become worth a bunch later
Alex's pretty consistently resisted the invitation
Chance to enter the
Cryptocurrency world
I don't know if it's to his credit
Bernard
But it's interesting to
A little bit weird
Makes them look stupid
That's what makes it look stupid now to have 50 million dollars he could have on the table when he
He's begging people
For money cuz he's getting sued by everybody
Stock in 90
72-in
10 billion dollars
Future video.
But also in the video Max's saying like if you just taking this thing I'd offered
Free right now
So the presentation
You
Because of whatever
F****** foolish ideas you had
You don't have that money
It's part of this partially presentation
I think most likely the issue is Alex
Does obsession with hard currency in the Bible
Metallica
Because Intel
Late 2015 Ted Anderson was running late
Taken away
That's probably a good chance
Dad just told him no
Like you can't have both
We both involved in a Bitcoin nonsense
Gold and silver
Is there any way to regulate.
Open dumps games
Is not a reason is in the regular
Is it the Wild West
Right gotcha
Episode
About Charlotte
What are the reasons is because he's being sued and
He's been trying to pretend that lawsuit
But it is not recently about it
Proceeding
Answer in order to
Going to spend a decent amount of time trying to
Reclaim the narrative
Is talking about how Millie Weaver was there
She's a great reporter and
She knows everything
Millie Weaver is going to join us as well
She was in Charlottesville
She left with the police collide
White nationalist
Broad Strokes
Version of The Narrative Alex
Will be selling
A little bit of a
Is it smart to talk about a law
It is if you're talking about a fake version of it
It's fine to talk about a fictional like straw man version of Lost
It is very clear what his strategy
Obfuscate
He went to Bullhorn at the White House to get himself back on Twitter
Albert
Crazy
Is the owl Alex's Bullhorn in the White House
Trump is having a meeting with Jack from Twitter
Now in this clip Alex says that he didn't know that that was going to happen and it was just coincidence
I honestly don't know what I think
Synchronicity
From the airport
The White House
It was a
Ongoing then
The head of
Twitter would be in there
The fox house was able to
Orlando
How usable are properly
Krowd
I want to convince them
Yelling for 1 hour
Bouncing off building
It was extremely successful
President
Flash
I was going to the room or the meeting was actually taking place
If I believe nose
Dorsey was going to have a meeting with Trump
Or if he did I have no idea
Either is weird
It's got to be one or the other
It wasn't on his official schedule
Even though I don't
I don't know whatever
The rest of that clip
On YouTube
Play Gordon Ramsay or Daniel negreanu commercials for like masterclass
Program
Are you bragging about that one of the few things that I think
Internationally recognized expert.
Yeah that is true
From way back
They are all in the Hall of Fame Glee as much as I don't believe he knows how to read
Or analyze contacts
He could teach you a goddamn thing
Howard 100
Percent I recognize my limitations
Picture of a water snake
You bet it is
Alex tries to
Reinvigorate a narrative
You know he's used a lot
Little bit lately
To resurrect
And that is
The Trump was spied on
The party last night
Because Trump's bringing it up being like a i w b on me
William Barr is also being
And so with the one America News Network
What's the name of it
You bet there is
They played
Some sort of pre-packaged
Kidspeace
The evidence Alex had forgotten
About Trump being
I was really excited
Because like
I want to know what you're talkin about
I got less
Excited
Obsessed on
EFax
.
Trump campaign
OneAmerica
He told me
About how the British government helped the Obama Administration.
The Fourth Amendment on the 2016
Campaign for them
Larry Johnson
It's so funny to me that I was constantly yells but have no one has a memory except
Because his audience
Never try to have another swing making Larry see John's
Something like a legitimate Source on
In case you forgot Larry Johnson and probably most memorable for being the guy who tried to spread the hoax during
2008 presidential campaign
Michelle Obama
While appearing on a panel with Louis Farrakhan at Jeremiah Wright's Trinity
He pushed the story although he admitted that he'd never seen the tape
Just talk to me
No such tape exist
Pointing out that
Michelle it never spoken at Trinity
I never use that word
Never materialized Johnson blames the McCain campaign
Potato
Just bullshittin
Interesting Lee Larry C Johnson was the main source for a ton of stories
Recirculating about
Be quote-unquote waititi
Rush Limbaugh use Larry as an as an excuse to cover the fake story sensation
But what I find more interesting is that Rodger f****** Stone appeared on geraldo's Fox show
Comment on it
There's a buzz which I believe now to be credible
Did some indelible record exist
The Michelle Obama allegedly made which are outrageous at bat
Including some reference to white people as white
Allegedly
Rodger was using Larry's
Larry's own blog No Quarter
Posted Rogers Fox news interview presenting it as evidence that the story was legitimate
Looking back through time
What you see
It's fascinating
Is the same players playing the same game
Weird I hate
I hate it
I hate
America very weird
Here's a big story
Michelle Obama called somebody a honky
That's it
That was there but it wasn't it wasn't true
Commenting on Trump saying the n-word that
Trusting Tom Arnold on this cuz I would advise
Be careful. Tell model
Oh no I was
If we are going home right right right
Which one
Which one is worse
I'm actually angrier if Michelle Obama didn't say that
We've been over this
Perhaps more seriously and more relevant to this episode of Alex's show
Larry C Johnson was the source for that the claim that the British intelligence group
Gchq spying on the Trump campaign at Obama's request
An outlet to pick up a story and run with it was Andrew Napolitano
His show on Fox News
This claim was so unfounded so not backed up by actual information
So inflammatory
Literally almost caused an international incident
What's wrong
The clients
It legitimately threatened our International intelligence-sharing relationship
Some of our longest held
The closest allies
Form to the aftermath of world war in hopes of averting a World War 3
In the Fallout Fox news release statements condemning the coverage
It took Napolitano off the air for an indefinite vacation
So he would return to air about a week
Here are some important things to remember about Larry seat
He retired from intelligence work in 9th
14 years before the first iPhone came out
8 years before the release of the f****** Nintendo GameCube
People born five years after he retired can legally buy booze
So he was in the game
Two people who knew him when he was Intelligence do not think highly of him
They're very frequent criticisms
Threat of terrorism
The pre 9/11
Emmy award-winning investigative journalist Peter Lance
Who worked with Larry had this to
To save him
Is one of the great empty
Do you suit
He's emblematic of what goes wrong in the Aging
Emblematic of the attitude that let 9/11 happen
It's not like there isn't evidence to back this up
New York Times op-ed wrote on July 10th
163 days before 9/11
Judging from news reports in the portrayal of villains in our popular entertainment
She's about terrorist
They seem to believe that terrorism is the greatest threat to the United
It states that it is
Becoming more widespread and lethal
They're likely to think that the United States is the most popular Target of terrorists
Almost certainly has I the impression that
Extremist Islamic groups
Cosmos most terrorism
None of these beliefs are based in fact
Whoops
You know what
The New York Times
Three days after
After 9/11
Whoops my bad guys I mean I missed the ball on this one
Terms of not allowing yourself
Be caught up in
Invitational
Japanese not making
Is the reality that
Being stupid
We should be over so paralyzed
There's a certain way
Your
They seem to believe the terrorism is the greatest
To the United States
Three days after
Couple months
Before 911
And the bad luck
Please don't feel bad if you are presenting yourself
Larry C Johnson is a member of the veteran intelligence
Professionals
Along with William
You'll be surprised to learn that he's a member of the organization to release a very sloppy memo
We just used it the Cornerstone of the Seth Rich conspiracy
Fingers on that one too
I mean you lying
Pretense
And the veneer of some sort of credibility for working intelligence for a couple years back in 93
State with confidence all sorts
To Crazy Bowls
As long as it aligns with what other people need somebody
Just a crap
Dammit
Racket
All this is to say that Larry
The f****** idiot
With really long track record of
Completely wrong about every
Close to doing
Just work the Unabomber was in the middle of his bombing campaign
Tonya Harding was a year away from father Nancy Kerrigan
Hey Kurt Cobain Tupac and Biggie we're all still alive
Long time ago
Literally no reason to ever trust something he's reported without ever
Things that he's claiming
From Secret sources
And stuff like that you could not
Trapani
And you can see the danger that can come from it
His ear
Maybe cuz it's satisfied Trump's ego he believed repeat
Potential to realign
Geopolitical at Alliance
Is weak
It's definitely fun to laugh at him
Any age we now live in
Someone like him could literally start a World War
So it's important to look at him as not
Just
A joke
Yeah these are very serious things that are being
Played around with
Is like reigniting the story based on Larry Johnson
Being used as a source by one American bad
This is very this is
Stuff we've already dealt with
Dunno
It's not it's not great
To see how they just
Keep throwing the same bolts
That was actually comforting things that
The Mueller report
Is the realization that
Just like that
Just
Obviously
Bulshit information
Theoretically could have ruined
We have with
DC over and over and over again in the Mueller report
So many times
You took it literally
Would be like the end of the world is
As we know it and everybody around
Just like
We're not doing that
That one's just not going to
Many other people around the world may also
Upstate you know you know we're like
Not good we're going to listen to that
Please everybody in the world has this sense of
Okay we know what you doing
We know what he's trying to do in
Not let everybody
Complaints about Obama
Deteriorating
Soft power
The real comedy
The rest of the world
President says that's usually not a good
Nuggets
Alex is bringing back up this Trump was fired on narrative
Is evidence there is the one America news network live that way
Who played that interviewed Larry C Johnson
So bad
Noted intelligent
Official
Larry seizure
Tropicana
Back when Kurt Cobain was alive
Grunge with cool
World Trade Center first bombing had just half
What else
The dream team had just won
I think it was
We could just be like
But thankfully Alex has other information
Eddie gets a witness
H clip one more time
Never plays
For Obama
They can't
Cover
Their butts anymore
Unable
To do it
Email wants Trump actually.
We better follow all the laws on surveillance
When she been quarterbacking it
Long with others
Full-time
The time
All turned out to be true
Infowars.com
2 years from now today
Shut off the air
Demonized
Appreciate
Others
That's an interesting way to phrase normalizing awful content
No
If he's not going to you know come with it I'm not either
I really only want that to sit here as
The globalist
Cuz he's so far ahead of everybody and
And he's right about everything
I told you that he doesn't play that Samantha powers
By that assertion remember that
Is powers on CNN
Information would disappear
Athena people who see
Found out how we knew what we knew about
The Trump staff dealing with Russians
Try to compromise those sources in
Samantha power
Yeah there
Whoops
This isn't her
Not surprisingly is big old zero.
Since early
Anytime
Because
It's kind of
This is a clip of Evelyn Farkas
Defense for Russia
Ukraine in an interview on MSM
This Marcus is not discussing spying on Trump
Champagne
Preserved
She's very specifically talking about how there were a lot of
Intelligent
That have been gathered about Russia and their Adventures into election meddling
Might end up missing
Straub's people got into office
That is what
We Preserve
This was specifically stated to be the basis
American intelligence agencies had intercepted
Indications of Russia
Beneficials
Gremlin
Discussing contact withdrawal
That is why there I was concerned about the sources and methods of
Collecting information
At that point it wasn't clear if you were handing over intelligence data to the people who the intelligence was about
This will compromise literally all of the
Intelligence capability about Russia and related
Her interview on MSNBC with specifically.
Discuss a story in the New York Times to come out a few days prior
With the headline Obama officials raced
The Preserve Russia
Cantrell
So it's not like this wasn't already
Your conversation is being had in the media
Nothing Farkas is thing is even close to a bombshell
The New York Times articles
This interview is about
Specifically says quote
Pharmacy
Senior Obama administration official said the efforts were Direct
Goodbye mr. Obama
So Alex
Actual real report
To the sources that he's point
Contorts
There's one more reason to Discount pretty much everything about this interview being
Accidental admission of a grant
Evelyn Farkas resign former deputy at the
Secretary position in
September 2015
At least four months before the Republican National Convention
Candidate
She wasn't even in any official capacity during the
2016 general election
She's just expressing
As someone who had experience
In the
Was
That's it
There's nothing here
Okay
So he's
Making knocking sound
Sing that he's playing
And then later on big living
They did all the things that I do things
News-today baba baba baba
Isn't it
I don't
So here's the thing about the whole spying
Issue
For me
If they
A fire
Intelligence analyst
Keeping an eye on Russia's election
Then
You claimed that they were spying on you
Right
Over here when you came into the picture
Not we were watching you and then Russia showed up
Right it's a it's a little bit like
If you got caught up in the spine
That wasn't
They didn't start with you
Right
You're if you say that
You got spied on
We were
GTA
Yeah you're cute except
Looking at you right
He makes it a picture you know you could have accidentally or intentionally come into the
Circle of people that work
Surveilled
Yeah that's my understanding
Let's races with that attracts entirely
So
And he's got some
Insider info
Information Jordan
He has sources
Okay
Are they
People that we can't definitively say how its talk to in d.c.
This is crazy
Alex
Doing
Throughout these two episodes
The 25th and 20th
Well here's a good news
People I talk to
Ginnifer Goodwin
Just don't say my name
Goldilocks and the Three Bears story
Write my name and the other one so it's all off-the-record
People said we don't give a fuk say whatever you want put our names on blast
What
I was just like
Alright well is Donald Trump
Really suspicious
I'm no snitch
What
What are you doing
Is lexcorp
Well
And the next clip
Kind of implies who they are and I thought about trying to figure out who he was trying to suggest
Just like I don't give a
None of this is real
One person is a close friend of the president and talk to him routinely Hollywood that
So I thought
Well I thought Rodger Stoner Jerome corsi the first one
What is a friend of trump
And that made me think like well course he just sued Alex
Probably not
I'm in Rodger I don't know where he is in the game
Anymore
So I don't know it doesn't
I could be
It could be Max Keiser
Trump
I think he's trying to imply it
Stephen Miller
Somebody who make
I think it's I think he's trying to
Stephen Miller
Specifically on the
Memo
Dealing with
The Briefing he got
Beforehand
What's one of the Fall
Russiagate
Who was involved
Europe for the CIA
And the clintons knew that you work for them
Baba's
You see Mallory Clinton saying I'm sick of these Crooks
Got all the Intel now he actually knows how they sold us out
Keisha Scott like total proof
For the Deep state
I don't know I don't know if those are specifics Alex
Edibles are vagaries
It does feel that way
I'm telling me over and over and over again that this lies
And did you get like the sense of what is a big news
Lock her up
I mean it's
Election season is heating up of course you got to bring this narrative back it works so well last time
Yeah wasn't that works real well
Of course
Corsica Walker web season
Do you think they're going to try know they're going to try it in terms of the
We're going to
To do something
You know
That would be Alex if they do
Katie-bar-the-door because
That's trouble
That's when we know that like we have crossed the Rubicon
This is this is much worse than it was
It would be if one of Trump's
Major re-election platforms was
We're finally going to put Hillary in prison
Of course
I think you'll do that
Third-born evergreens
Some people are always going to want to put Hillary in jail
Got to do
Alex
Pastor reiterate
Permission to save
Tell you what
But just to give the little breadcrumbs
Crumbs
Specific qanon
The idea of the little clues that you leave
Those are breadcrumbs
Using that terminology
I don't think that's an accident
OSHA
Because that's also a huge part of the world
Pretty much anyone
Close to supporting
Trump is also kind of into the idea of Jalen political enemies
Mostly
Yeah
People Are People
Breadcrumbs
The clues about who these people are
One of those drums
Someone was caught up in the Russia investigation on fairly
Alex
So
Here's the
Alex even knows this
Difficult to happen
And so he couches
His reporting on it very carefully
But now it's coming to a head
Hillary shot her mouth off other things
Mobile
So
Do you here in there I mean there's The Sensational end
To dive,
That just being like what
Habit
You know uses this as a rallying cry to get the dumb dumb
Yeah I'm bored for this election cycle
Then what happened
This is my new your noses
Of course
It never see
Cease to amaze me whenever I stop by
What's going on
One political party
Is
Centered around
Lunatic
Legitimately wants
To lock up his
Political opponents
Wants to create
A Grassroots movement
Right and the other party
Knowing full well
Barry leader has committed crime
Is
Constantly saying well we shouldn't even get rid of him as president
For political reasons
It's weird
A lot of times
Glaring
It's so bright
You really feel
Despondent
Feeling to have especially as we enter now
Where I think I want you earlier maybe before the episode that
Bad
Here's where
Real bad
What is this next one
There's a part of me that actually is glad that Alex's
Is this over
Because it's so overt
I'll because he's over it leaves very little room for him to be able to defend
Next clip here from the 25th
Is where it's at
Islamophobic
Muslims
It's quarters from Muhammad
What
The magic number 10%
Porsche
Christians are
The country out of their neighborhoods and then they'll move on to the next
Operation works
Is a rationalization for ethnic cleansing
Simple
Alex isn't talking about radical terrorist who happened
To be Muslim
I want to talk about demographic race as a whole
He's talking about every single Muslim in every country is being part of a growing problem
Affiliated with
The terrorist groups
Simply by virtue of existing within that part of the groin
Yeah consider the implication
Sins of what he saying
He's saying he wants Muslims make up 10% of a country's population they're commanded by Muhammad to start bombing
If you believe that then the solution to the problem is to keep Muslim populations below 10% of any geograph
How are you
I guess one option would be forced deportation
Displaced people and make sure there's never enough of them somewhere
To scare you
Of course the USD 1.3 million Mexican-American tonight
4 with a very racist lady named Operation wet.
The consequences of that action
What American city
Listen to Mexican heritage
Forcibly displaced
And unfamiliar parts of Mexico where they knew no one
Generational wealth
Completely disrupted
As were the families themselves
This is Addie
Deep state
History of the
65 years
Does not work
And the effect it has on people
Communities is equivalent to Terror
If history shows us that he's forced deportations based on religion or ethnicity
Make sure that the Muslim population of an area never
So you never have to
To deal with you no kidding
Down below
You need to enact ethnic or religious
Reading limite
Which seems like something Alex would be super against you spent most
List of his career yelling about the horrors of
China's one child
This is necessarily imply the need to set up a hierarchical system where US citizens were Muslim
Human rights only so far as the non-muslim government officials allowed them to
He advocated for the
Totalitarian nightmare
Acquire a ridiculously powerful centralized government in order to be put in place
Ultimately
If a problem you think exists in the world is that there's too many Muslims and once there's a certain number of them they kill everyone
Did you are soft
This 10% number he's rattling on about is arbitrary
It's just the focus of his bigotry
But if you was Alyssa
Accept the premise
10% is
This magic number where trouble starts
How easy is it going to be for Alex to turn around and say
I had it wrong that number Zacks
7%
Once you accept the logic of any number that number can change to
To suit a propagandist
Swim and no percentages ever going to be low enough
For someone like Alex a number of Muslims
This is
Really
F***** up
I can't say enough
This is
The introductory
Step towards rhetoric justifying
And advocating for ethnic cleansing
This is this is the sort of language that really really
Gets people hurt
We're well past
Here Alex things like that
One of them things
It's just awful
Obviously
Cleaned of West
Surprising
He follows it up I think
Things like this
Call to prayer
Christianity
Who are these people
He did it because of the guy they were chosen because the threat he seemed to think they pose to the white race
Has blown up a year
Banda burn down in France
And there's almost no coverage
Alex is basically defending and just
Define motivation
Of the Christ
I think
I think what I would like
Because we know with Alex
We know what his goal is
We know what that the goal is basically to make a lot of money
General
But four is lisp
What are the what are there
Working for
What are they
Are there
Leaving and do they know
If and if they do know what that is
Are they trying to act
Do that or they just
And off
I think it's over and over again
All of these
Situation
Where the people on the ground probably just
Just want to live
A good life
They want to live a stable life where their values are
Are accept Community where they
They can live
Reasonably healthy
And Bobby
Employee
Some capacity that they feel gratified by
But
There are people like Alex
And their people you know propagandist
Of all of all varieties
That's a create scapegoat
And they're very very
Howling
Powerful
To exploit
People like Alex
People like I mean historically there been hundreds of him
Yeah and what they do is they
Create this
Perception
XYZ group is the reason why you can enjoy your life
The way that you feel like you should
Whether or not
Obviously
Very real reason
Are able to live
Comfortably in Happily as they would like
Albert
Distracting from that by scapegoating
Some population
Is way easier
So you get people to jump on board with your scapegoat
If
If we can just deal with that issue will have what we want
We will have that thing that we
That's the motivation of a lot of people who buy
Yeah they're conscious of it or not
Very quickly transmutes
Into like
Outright hate
Is Bassnectar
I was I was
Concept of the brain virus
We talked about over and over
And how this is
This is an act
Disease
Like you were saying most
People really just want
Outright
It's not unique to one place
How do we treat regular like like
Because we don't we don't know what the Cure is
Take vaccines for actual disease
How could we ever
Convincing
People to train them on
Finding in
Discovery
Like
Huge thing
Still on the 25th
Alex
A little bit earlier talking about Charlottesville and how everyone's actors
Whatever
They're all probably
I think what he's doing is
I think you could barely call it
Wholesale revision
Joe Biden launches his campaign on the LIE
Nazis were very fine people
Charlottsville
Now
Office
And a suit
Shelf
That the Democrats killed the woman
That a heart attack
The white supremacist
Journalist
How do I
So the first thing I want to say is that like Alex complains
Katana by Joe Biden announce
Charlottesville
And
Caribbean life is great too
F*** off
I'm so Alex also though I think probably more importantly for our purposes
You completely misrepresenting what he's being
I'm sued for about Charlotte's
Fli
Alex isn't being sued by George Soros
Shadowy globalist
Conspiracy
Being sued for saying the Democrats killed
He's being sued by one person whose name he knows better than to ever say on Aragon
Because that person has been
Very consistent public
He's never going to settle this lawsuit
Brandon Gilmore
Call
Including allegedly his own dachshund
As well as
Late March
US District Judge Norman Moon ruled that Alex's Publications
As well as those of a number of other defendant
Were the cause of Brenda Gilmore's alleged injuries
And as such a First Amendment defense is inappropriate
Is only late
Ever feel safe standard
Put simply
This lawsuit could
Big trouble for Alex
If the judge is already made clear that first amendment
Complaints aren't relevant
Well until appeal
Perhaps
But he doesn't really have much of a ground for defense
It would take up the case
Because they
Certainly be like
And stuff like that
Realize at the court already
What precipitated that harassment is things that you and these other co-defendants published
So that argument doesn't work either
So
I just I just remembered
I ate it sounded it sounds so Bernal coming out of my
Mouth cuz it
So it's something that we've just normalize but
There are appeals courts that are
Completely
Sprint that other appeal
Depends on the judges.
If you can open to interpretation
Established law presidents
Things like that I mean
In
Ideology
From appeals court
To go to the seventh Court of Appeals
Because it's going to give us a ruling that
Isla
But I don't oppose to the 9th Court of Appeals which we know is
Is going to give us
Different rules you don't get really too
Choose though because they're over different
Like District
In the United States it's not like if you appeal
Or whatever
Do though
Is that they find different
Ways to
2 Berry Court that's going
Favorable to that there are differences but I think it's probably
Slightly less
I think I think that the idea that the ninth circuit is
Some sort of a
Liberal Bugaboo to conservative politics
Is probably
Conservative talk
I think the other ones that are
The liberal
Sure and I pipe
Much less than
I think most of it probably airs towards
I'm going to put heavy scared
Jordan
On the day of the United right rally in Charlottesville Infowars headed very serious
This problem on there
Alex could and would be totally fine defending
People who were protest
Protect the statue of Robert that's old hat
What's a little bit more of a difficult to pull off a large group of
Yelling Jews will not replace us
A blood and soil
One of the things that's important to remember about this rally is spelled out in its name
About protecting the statue
Preserving history
But it's probably worth mentioning
In May 27th
Richard Spencer letter rally for the same purpose
In July 2017
KKK held a rally against
The statue's removal
Will there
70 the unite the right rally was held at the
The same
A place for the same alleged purpose
Involving both members of the
The clan and Richard
It's not hard to see what was being united
This confluent
Of things was a major problem
Alex
His brain doesn't work so well when he's associating himself with literal Nazis and white supremacist
Is it kind of makes his the last just cause everyone they dis
Agree with Nazis argument Fall Apart
Yeah if he's actually
Just hanging out with
Did like those Nazis are great
But
At the same time
He can't not have a,
Culture War battle that's unfolding in front of it
Particularly one refills
Confederacy is possibly under attack
As we know his family literally fought for the Confederacy
If he comes down squarely on the side
You know that's kind of a dead-end for him
Narrative
Particularly after the protests turned violent
Conversely there's no way in hell he's going to land on the side of the anti-fascist countertop
A similarly note
Is audience is going to let him sit this one out and say I don't know what's going on here
Literally the only path available
Guys at Charlottesville
Three bad guys
They were agents of the club
At 1:42 p.m. James Fields Jr a legit Nazi from way back who was photographed at the rally proudly sporting
Vanguard America
Shield rammed his car into a group of counter demonstrators
Injuring 19 people in killing Heather hair
The evidence is overwhelming that this was
Intentional attack
And all the conspiracy theories
Explain away his actions
It's some kind of a victim in the whole thing
Haven't thoroughly.
I'm still life in prison
Absolutely
M-43 p.m.
You had a rally that Alex can be there support nor condemn
It has led to a murder
Position in the marketplace
He needs to find an angle to make this whole thing's bake
Needs to find that
What do you landed on
To discredit the person who shot
Footage of fields Cara
Who was Brennan
Alex's crack team of researchers
The same ones that just generally report as fact whatever bulshit they find out 4chan
Dug up the fact that Gilmore and previously worked at
The state
In the u.s. for insta
This was all it took
To create the narrative operation
To make the Patriots
Adding to the conspiracy was the fact that Gilmore worked
A yellow campaign
And the fact that Gilmore workroom was proof
But something was up
Corsair yellow hadn't held an elected position
2011 when he handed a two-year run in the House of Representatives
The 2017
Democratic
Primary
I would use these pieces of evidence
Spend the conspiracy
The Brennan Gilmore with evidence
State Department
Was active in baking the events of Charlottesville
The accusations are wide-ranging
Come back to Alex
Associate
The Gilmore was a Soros operative and had something to do with the chaos
But the rally
Obviously these accusations are true
So Gilmore stewing hour
It looks like there's a pretty piece
Decent shot of casework now
I base that assessment on the fact that Alex in his lawyers and had to resort to
Really we
Like recently they tried to claim the gilmores a public figure
So in order to prove defamation Gilmore's lawyers would need to establish malicious intent
Gilmore's lawyers were pretty quick to point out that Gilmore is not a public figure and wasn't
By lying about it spreading
Is the reality of the Lost
That Alex is
Cities trying to
Misrepresent
Create
Talk about
Because he knows better than
To talk about it
For real
Cuz he does that
Just make the lawsuits that might work
No Alex Heather hair Vite of die from heart attack
Is a legitimate
An overt example of him using a
A very traceable talking
This is something that is only expressed on Nazi message
Boards and Outlets
Ability for
James field
This is a winking joke
Speakers know the people who say they know that it is
True but it's used to signal to each other that they approve of fashion
Murder
The talking point is based on a Mitsubishi
Heather hairs mother made
Two reporters in the immediate aftermath
When she said Heather had a heart attack
What you meant
Expresses the doctors
Told her that her daughter's heart it's
Stopped at the speed
This hair later clarified
When Miss Harris gave her initials
Express uncertainty
It was said that you was waiting on the America
When that report came out
Clear that Heather died from blunt
The only people
Who would come anywhere close to suggest
Heather died from a heart attack particularly in 2009
Are doing so
Two very specifically signal
Do white supremacists and Nazis that they are on their side
That is
Code
And Alex is using it
Now I also accept the possibility that Alex's
I take it there's a chance
Researchers
Yeah I have you quotes
Are using this code
And Alex doesn't know that
Cuz Alex doesn't do any preparation
Right
I think that there is a possibility that he
Is unknowingly
Speaking white supremacist
Sister Nazi code
Bonaire
McKay's then the people who were doing his work for him are intentionally
So
That there's no good way
For that
No
No I did not
I did not even
I just assumed
Run-of-the-mill can
Conspiracy theory that
Everybody does
But yeah why would anybody
Just otherwise unless they
Make sure Nazis
And
It's become almost
Is important
What's
Transmitted when it's
Not to the question of police ordering a
Handling Proto
Metallic seems to think
Is all he said
That's all my coverage
Are you saying that they cancelled these protesters
Counter protest
This is a little bit more of an open question that I actually wish
It was
It's one bums me out a little
There are valid criticisms of the
The police department close to what Alex is claiming
But the context
Distance around again
Information on the way Alex
Presence is narratives
Make it so
Pretty much Albertson still pretty much
The police chief in Charlottesville as well as the city spokesperson
Explicitly said that there was no Stand Down order put out that day
ACLU speerise
The police were hanging back and waiting for violence
Breakouts
Clear the area knowing that violence was an avid
That's
Seems fairly plausible but also hasn't been proven
An actual stand-down strategy
Anything like that
Employing it just seems like
Seems to match with what
Weather
Is still in
Is not based on evidence
You have to you have to prove what would almost certainly
Only be
Something that was
Generally agreed-upon
Is it in action in like Following the Leader I guess
Since they found for it comes from yournewswire and
Uncensored
To completely full of shake
The two sites feature a quote from an alleged Charlottesville police officer
Surprise
We were ordered to bring the Rival groups together
As soon as they were in contact with each other we were told to stand down
It was outrageous
We weren't allowed to arrest anyone without asking the mayor first
We weren't even allowed to stop the driver if he sped away
The event was being set up as far back as at least
And it went like clockwork
We want to do our job and keep the peace but these m************ in charge really want to destroy America
First thing
Hell of a fake quote
Implants at least May
Rally was so it's sort of time all the Rally's that happened to Charlie together
As part of the globalist plan
You know you know if you've read it
If you read enough news
To feel for when somebody
Gives
Too good a quote
He has a real good one
But it's also
That's the same story that all of the
Made-up quotes
WhatsApp app
Didn't get any coverage but all those websites
And you were saying it's a really good quote but there's one piece of it
You probably don't understand
The quote
What are the reasons
You can tell
Is obviously a fake
Is because he said that they weren't allowed to arrest anyone without asking
Singer Mayer
This is a misunderstanding of how the city of Charlottesville
Structure
Any cop with any information
In about the department of operation
What absolutely not make that
Mistake
Charlottesville operate
Under a city
Manager form of government where the air is not voted into office
What is selected by elected
Councilmember
The position of Mayor is largely ceremonial in terms of
The duties literally no authority over whether or not to arrest anyone at the protest
This is a glaring
Example
Insider info
Clearly disseminated to produce a false narrative
If not to report
The mayor is just like
Presides over
It's not inch over the police
Right and in 19
Might as well
I'm not that's not fair
So you understand
This sort of information
Would know that
Together quotes
Obviously that's so obviously fake that it
And the thing is
That fake Anonymous cops bulshit story doesn't match any other document
Reality
But it does closely match up with Alex's spin on the rally
I have almost zero doubt that when Alex says the police
Come out and admitted that there was a stand down
Literally the only thing he's basing that on
Is this bacon automatic
Conspiracy sites that is interns frequent
Steelcon
I'm pretty sure
Yeah that sounds right
But now here's a little bit more
In March 2018 a foia request public
Dave before the Charlottesville rally
In the memo there was discussion of how the permit for the rally
Been granted with a
Prediction of 400 people attending
But intelligence
That it would be way more
People than that
And that violence was a very likely
Explicitly officership
Keep close watch of crowd members were exhibiting Behavior
Officer should make arrests when appropriate for unlawful Behavior interviews issued Fleck
Text cops as
Restraints
This plan was not followed through on
Owing largely to shity communication and contradictory orders
Seem to prioritize police officer safety
The over civilian
Police allocated Manpower and horrible fashion
Heather seemed to be almost no coordination
Responsibility
Do the Charlottesville Police Department
A Virginia State Police
Who serve basically at parks
Security as opposed to getting involved in
The crowd control
Which was desperately need
There was no Stand Down order
Terrible police
Going on
Police chief Al Thomas
I was alleged to have said quote
Let them fight it will make it easier to declared unlawful assembly as their rally was started tutor
Ugly
But even this doesn't constitute
Also Thomas insist he didn't
Say that his position was
Play doubt
Either way
Either way that helps position
No I didn't want him to die
I wanted people to see if he died
Either way it's almost resigned in disgrace by the end of
Good call an investigation done by us attorney Timothy
Heafey found that the city was overconfident and their ability to deal with what was coming
And because of that it's failed to
Protect our community in Myriad ways
Stand Down order
Like
Anonymous
Who is quoted in your news
All the stuff is is
It's nonsense
There is a more complicated reality
Behind the lies about
2 is like he's a little bit closer to reality than I like him to be on this
Cuz it it would be nice
Just be able to
The reality
Most likely would
And in their decisions
Season in their failures
To manage
The crowd appropriately
They did end up
Having
Demonstrators
And the people who are awful ended up in close proximity to each other which is a
Upland appropriately and followed the plan as was stated in that
7th
Really
Not have gone that poorly
Probably
Functional
You know
There's a big difference
There is a
Supreme
But
He has other evidence
Then
This fake cop
On your news
Of all the things that could possibly happen
Like
I don't think I'm looking forward to
To hearing about the Sandy Hook lawsuits as they progressed
Probably
Real
Lucky you're not. Fun
Charlottesville
Equally they are not equally maybe I don't know I don't want to put a scale on it it's also a traumatic
But I do think there's potential for Alex
Really embarrassed
Open court
If he follows through with this strategy
F****** pray he died
Collide together
We supposed
Would you be very powerful
Google
He is going to introduce
F******
Bogus ask Soros antifa contractor
Spray that he chose that
See how quickly
Sir
Mr. Jones
Oh my God
This is stupid
This is very
Second
The evidence
That you were providing
Is related to something
That has nothing to do with this situation
Is a hook
I think I begin
Get your dog into court like could
I mean not just because of introducing it but because I think obviously the court be like
Nah
His response to that I think would lead to it
Contempt of court starts screaming about how this is a store Rose cover up
Teacher bullhorn class in prison
He does also seem like there's a part of me that thinks
So he believes that those contracts are
If you would go so far as to introduce them
In court like I don't think you would pull that sort of the block if you knew that they were bulshit
Yeah he
YouTube
Embarrassing chapter
Like the Optics of him
America
Absurdly
Trying to argue in court those are real
Holy
That would be amazing Underoath where did you find wow this one guy
His brothers stuff
Yeah I know it sounds stupid
Previously
It feels better on a radio show
Can say anything and nobody's like
Deerfield
Court thing on the radio
When will be able to
This one done
Can I come up to Moby
Can I come up
Topix
Talk about how Trump
Has
All of the best movie
He has all the moves at his disposal
Like he's playing poker with the globalist
Yeah
Listen carefully to this and see if you can
See where my mind was like
That's too many cards
Couple 12 couple of
Fors
Are they playing
Roblox Roblox Roblox
Play Royal Flush he has them
The Shiites
I have three problems with that 40 second clip
The first is that there are no one
Alex
There is no one if you ever one you have a f***** up that card someone's cheating
Yeah
Having a bunch of deck
Also probably cheer
Hundred
Probably cheating
No collusion
Third
Or Joker's Wild
Because if so if you have a handful of jokers got a royal flush
You got a handful of Joker
If Jokers are wild this is Amissville
Instructions
What card is that what's going on
Ohio having a 1 1/4
Is it play it low
Although
What what occurs mean
What is this what is this poker game where in one side only has a
A few cards
Honestly
A couple of fours in a couple of Queens
Not a bad habit
Queen hacked
Terrible
Play No poker in my time to know that
Also if I'm global
And we're playing poker
And I have a few cars
My thought is going to be
I don't want to play
This game so I can play a different game
And you can have fun with
With your car
You got to know when to hold them when to fold them know when to walk away when to run
Mister Rogers Neighborhood
About what to do with cards
Alex Express his fictionalized version of that Charlottesville lawsuit
MLB keep the same
Because we get another impression a new impression
Yes the death is on your hands
Obama
Hillary
Alexander Soros
Not a Democrat
Cameraman
Who's work for Hillary
Perfect
Kill the woman
The Suites
Illegible
It's Alex Jones
He's the bad what every with questions things
Impression of Ralph Northam I believe the governor of Virginia problem is like
The time frame
About is like
Before he was
Northam didn't get into office until 2018
After
I don't know what's going on there but I think what I want
To point out here very important
Alex's
Re bringing up
Use to kill babies
Kind of rhetoric has been pushing late late last night
Ever recording this
Friday
Or Saturday night Green Bay
Instead of The Correspondents Dinner
They're not allowed to after their Sailors got embarrassed last year they're very mean
But at that
By the way
Is alphys
Dubuque the Alpha's mate
Do the snowflake dinner
Green Bay to hold one of his
Totally not authoritarian
Rally's
Trump talks about the idea that after babies are born
Wrap up and then they the mother in the doctor decide whether or not to ask
Executed yeah
Mirroring Alex's rhetoric something
Windows
Narrative
Which are Trail in Archer
But do you see this
Is going into over
The ideas
President Woods
Push
Infowars narratives
Screaming crowd
Of crazy
Is there
Academy Sports
Didn't even need to be
Needs to be used
Need to be ratified get clearly we're not going to use it
I mean for not now I don't I don't know I can't imagine
Eddie just like
Use a specific
McPherson
Person
Jerry Lewis wins the next election as a Democrat it starts running around drunk with a lampshade
Water is policy positions don't know anymore
I can't
If this isn't enough I can't imagine a scenario where it would be
Even then
You're too dumb that's 24
Yeah
Make a pretty robust argument just from like
Whether or not
Mental deterioration
You know that's
What you're doing is it
0 dangerous people weather report
The rights workers
Who now have to worry about tons of people believe in that they're executing babies
I bet it's Justified to shoot and bomb them as has been done in the past or whether it's
Muslims
Who have
People who were emboldened by Trump like Alex coming out and expressing
There can only be under 10% of the population Muslim or else
Yeah I just
You could make a pretty robust document the Trump being an office
The danger to
To the safety of
A lot of people
But of course if you tried to make those arguments Alex and his
Propaganda cohorts
Would be like
Yeah he's a danger to the globalist
And that's really what they're afraid of
So give me we're just in a dead-end
Yeah
It's so disappointing
Whenever you
Like whenever you read Twitter saying we can't
We can't get rid of
Natihei
Is our algorithm
Is it up with Republic
Likes to bet guys
Guys come on
You didn't even work that right
We can't get rid of this
What republic
Yep
So this is
Was not super surprised by hearing Alex
Talk about Charlottesville to where he was
In line with
This next
Stretch
Was crazy
And that is that I think Alex
Is trying to present the idea
White supremacist
That were at Charlottesville
We're not only actors
We're not only operative
They were all gay
What
Did she look at all these men and look at their behavior and look at how they're acting
This is the
Acting Club Tennis is the drama club from surrounding universities and
I mean
It's
Basically a giant dress up party with a bunch of gay men
I dressed up as Nazis in their giant jussie Smollett the man
Did you just
I think I'm sick
Wow so when I heard that I was like
No it's all a bunch of dogs
Wow so I thought that was it
I was just so handsome today
What
Colleges
And they dressed up
As Nazis
Let me just look at the footage
This is not something I've heard him say the idea that it was a bunch of
Your stuff is like
Be alright I expected
Riverview Alex
He is
Very insistent about the gay people
Alien sister
I think he muddled
I'm not sure but let the forensic analysis
Analysts were listening decide on that one
A butler
Nelly wadling
What are we doing
I don't know what we're
What is still bad
You still mad about these imaginary
So he doesn't have to deal with the fact that there are a bunch of love
Four Seasons
Okay
This is like him getting super mad about how much degrees of David Duke
Crazy that is
Okay
Here's here's here's what we're going to do Alex
We got a new angle
This way you don't have to say that you love white supremacy
Call him gay
Done
MoveOn next they're just actors
What
That's a lot of people who have been identified
Rally
And are not Democrats who were recruited from area colleges
So this
Well there were a few white supremacist Roomba
Doing assertive disparagingly
Everyone else thinks are stupid
A butt
Much like
Dos Toros
T4 document
I would love for him
Jordan
Here's the Not Guilty by reason of homophobia
They are at all
I guess the Staind
I don't know
One piece of evidence
I think it's probably
One piece of evidence that these are all
This is evidence
For them all being gay I think part of it is that they're wearing button-up shirts when they were holding tiki torches
Looks like they were all in golf
Do very much Alex play some video
This is
Listen to sort of definitive evidence
But these are real.
I'll just run around
Oh yeah
Slipknot everywhere
If you're following this he's basically saying that the way they run is way too gay for them
Alright alright where this line of thought
Yep
Looking forward to the Charlottesville tended to really happen
Who was running
They really miscalculated
Funds by gentleman
I'm needing to sell Prada
To fund his defense is still
Kind of activity
Like it's still sort of the Prelude to I need money
The idea that these are all secretly local colleges
Can program
Listen up
I got one question for you in this deposition and remind you you're under
Are you an undercover Democratic operative
Who's gay
Cyanide pill
This isn't going to work out well.
It is probably going to work out well with him getting some money
From the people that
He has left
I need money
I'm so excited about this
Really on the wrong
Able to V hell
Please give me money knockout is 100% off
If you know every
Disappeared
Tennessee death row
He's operating
As a
Way to get Bryce to cover his bulge
Later part of a lot more
Come from
Ayuda publica
Stop go back to email like that sort of thing like you might be considering that is a
Very likely outcome in the short amount of time
But the good news is cast
Since Alex is early days.
Just doing the podcast
It is if this show is any evidence
Probably have to sell some boats maybe not be able to have all that great property
About to The Standard
You could get a one apartment
Wouldn't that be fun
Across the hall for
Terrible I think the only few things would be worse than
The neighbors I currently have to ask
Knocked on your door is like my equipment gone down your mind
All right now
3 hours
In this next Cliff Alex talks about this Democrats
Pretending to be Nazis plan
I want you to listen to this
Think about how overly complicated this is
As opposed to the idea that there are actual white supremacy
Athanasius
You're the Democrat plan is to
Have left
Step 10
Then
Call Monty
And then claim a race horse
From Soros group from
No.
Why they don't want us on air or you on here
Alright absolutely no pensarte real
There is a thing where like
I know in like
TV and movies people be like I won't even dignify that with a response
But in the real world
Delta Airline
Ever the Soros group
I would say
Not responding to this
Good movies
Goodman
Yeah and then walk away
I pointed out that to Alex
Two of them had a little talk about
But it's just Alex playing his interview with Max Keiser
Play the interview
I don't really care Alex missed out on
50 million dollars a Bitcoin or whatever
The only thing I really care about is this
Clip from the interview with
Coronavirus
Advocating
The Democrats should just concede the 2020 election
Look at all these Pro
So when I was younger I was very against George W
And
You know what
Protest the Iraq War
And I didn't like John Kerry but I was
B a b Porta carry metalx
At no point did I say George W bush should conceive
Because that's f***** up that's crazy
Cuz that's kind of similar to Alex's
Cancel the election
And stuff like that
Who's going to win with like very normal countries have
The only difference
It's between him being like Obama's going to cancel the election
Isn't his kind of being like a choice
Understanding
The same Obama
To cancel the election by giving it up
And Democrats
To cancel this election
Whatever the case
That's really f***** up anti-democratic idea
Here's the problem with the
People change
I don't like it
So how about they just quit
Ice bucket
Alex gets back to talk about how he has both resources
Tell you who they are
Just amazing
And I just give us until
White Justice
Why give me
Aries
You know the only thing that I could imagine is possible and I don't think
The only explanation I can come up with
Alex is trying to rope-a-dope the media
Into saying like
You don't have any f****** sources and then he pulls out
What's happening
He's playing it close to the vest if you will
Only explanation that we as I secure and
Think about like what could be going on
That's the only thing that makes sense other than I'm making this s*** up
Reveal information
Besan people asking
Question
One way to play it is to just tell people who the person
Especially when they've been given clearance by their sources and adds to the report
Another possible strategy
Would be to
Actual sources
You can say my name
Create a my name say my name
Window lights on a radio show
You can
Information
And then make a big deal out of how you're not going to say who the people are
Knowing that everyone knows
You lie all the time
Covers
Guys f****** make
Shut up
He's a big old liar it's just another example of it being a big old f****** liar with
The thick neck
What you can do is be like
Mainstream media is getting a little better
So
Pull out your name of your realsource you get to be like the mainstream media
Always
Headed that way you can
Sword of reclaim all the times you've been lying in the past
Feel like I could have done this
Or something like that
A propaganda coup out of it
A potential strategy someone
Could be employing like that someone falls into the Trap
Maybe like they're fake news they say I live their life
The globalist plan with the Charlottesville
Like
Somebody conceivably could be that
Weird
But I doubt it
Episode ended with interviewed Max
Kaiser also spend
Large portion
Beginning of this episode
Playing
Andy's interview with Trump
Fox News
Alex plays autonomy
And here it is Alex
Setting up
About to go to that
The first
To get to the Deep state
The fact that
They are pushing for
But I know they have the evidence because I was there researching and watching it all
We were the first show to say
Up to this point have the evidence
How's the Evelyn Farkas
Larry's
The loaded Bowl
I know Alex brings up the
Of things that we've covered on this show
At our complete
We then received drug enforcement
Sure
Whatever you got in the office are private numbers
They got zero attention cuz
It's b*******
You didn't get it from the DEA you got it
Dennis Montgomery by
Through the hands
Joe Arpaio
You know who else Larry klayman who is now suing Alex
So we're all that information
10K from propaganda attempt
By Dennis Montgomery
Whistleblower who
Jesus Christ if you want understand that go back to our episodes investigation
Involves trying to intimidate a judge it's a mess
Don Meredith
So
Do you have Larry C Johnson Evelyn Farkas nonsense
Larry you got the the traffic
1st and Alex's
These as reinforcing that narrative
He doesn't have anything
Trying to say that the globalist plan Charlottesville
And I have the proof
With Soros
He doesn't have something real
Start with this
That's like if you are a stand-up and your opener is
I don't have faith
Minute 3 is going to get good
You don't open
Which if you have something better
Yeah and that's what Alex is doing
Who's doing it
A terrible set over and over and over
So it is next April 26th
Alex talks about how
Covid-19
Bstock
And talked about the last time
This is crazy
And
Because you're better than yourself
Clash
You just have to understand
Because I know I know Alex will keep it up will be talking a lot more soon
I don't care about the
Go to certain people
Certain people
Miller
That's why I wanted the people he
Pretending you talked to my dad because he specifically
Is implying Miller watches
Show
Eva
He's smarter than to think Alex knows any
I could Feast even though I want to use Alec
In some way but not respect
You know yeah
I think that he could see him as a useful idiot
And maybe your fellow Traveler
In there
And white
Ethnostate
Creating but I can't imagine
Like I would say Miller would here like
Cicero's document to be like
That sort of thing
I don't know where we are with him
You know I don't know I don't know
I just texted anybody
Anyone would believe Alex maybe I'm blinded by
Is a person
Thousands of people that are mother and Vegeta
Together to decide whether or not
KB
Everybody
Yeah fair enough
Really
Shocked at The McNay
A gesture
Trump didn't need to call him
Bright
They would want that
Call me anymore
Your staff to watch a show
Actually kind of feels like it might be a sincere feelings
Need to talk to you as long as I can
So
Sort of Twitter was abuzz not too long ago about the idea that Alex
Who's teaming up with qanon
We heard earlier him bring up like I'm leaving
Wendy's bread crumbs
He sort of executive phrases that Harkins
2 qanon
Mistake
Some people about
And that was it Alex's not teaming up with Kayla.
You can't because qanon
Even if Alex warms up to qanon
Do not specifically. I did not know that brings up in this
Mama
No one knows who qanon is it's a bunch of people on 4chan
Yeah I mean it's a jumbled mess
Qanon because I qanon doesn't like him
So even if they can find common cause in terms of
Benno putting forth the argument that there's a bunch of rest
Coming Hillary is going to get locked up you know there is overlap
To some of it
But I would never
Qanon to hate him and be on the same
And there is the problem of course
Where's Alex
No Trump
Who are you no one knows who you are
And that bleeds into this next clip where you complain
Who is
So you can hear their Alex use the term breadcrumbs again that is a piece of
It's so sad
Just leave me alone let me go out there real person
Just doesn't stop
Whoever it is magical
You're starting
You know our names
She was just a secret
So
There's a dangerous confluent
Two of them
Can be can be pretty bad I think the negative
That effect
But the possibility of the two
Assertive
Audiences
Merging in the idea of Alex ever being like
Q is legit
We got a f****** go on board
It's never going to happen because of
Ego
It's just impossible
Well it struck me that
It's been a long time since I've heard
Such a long clip of Alex
Whining
Well that might be because of eclipse I choose
That's entirely because of the clips not afford them to me
Quit the loser little tickets on their first and I saw the
It's not it's not a good luck
That's sad look for him because he's supposed to be like an alpha
Forgot I was right about everything
Is not pathetic
And I think it's Alex
You should just be doing FM radio
We are
Hollywood trash everywhere
The dreaded
And brother-in-arms
Those against love freedom and Common Sense
Alex Jones
Guitar
There's nothing
I didn't have any large political Ambitions I am the scourge of perverts friend of
Patriots I am Alex
If those moments that are like
You and far between
I would say under
What he does
The rest of it doesn't come close to making up for it I love
Cuz that's the kind of thing you don't hear on other sorts
The shows like if you listen to Glenn Beck or Sean Hannity's radio show
There's no moments where they have their humanity is like
Honestly we can laugh all that moment
But on some level it makes
Look at makes the bad things
Because where is the humanity
B b
Assertive
Shines through in moments like that
I was like aesthetically liking music
Individual personality that's allowed to
Exist on the show then so many other political talk shows
Which makes
Kind of feel like
Muslims can't ever be over 10%
The population
It's coming from
As opposed to it being like a
Political talk show
Which makes
I think
The humanity
Yeah
You think so I looked kind of why I like to step kind of why I like to play moments like that
Electric it makes it worse
You know like it this sounds very this sounds very gamergate
Kind of
Listen
Go to the way he talks about that talks about The Highwaymen and and movies
He's just got that kind of like
Joy towards collecting something that is
Under a
And then
That is part of that like fun
Hardrace
Or whatever
You know
Him being presented as a person
Can be funny because of the
Seismic shift
Yeah but it also makes
It worse because
You're saying
Yeah that's more
Alex talked to whole bunch about how Trump is going to lock her up
Whatever
Who plays
A ton of that
Or at least of his show
He plays at Hannity interview
Anthony says this
Switches
I know that I can't prove this to you without playing the last hour of his show
Just play
He did give you the benefit of the doubt
Look out to commercial we laid it all out in the last hour
You just played a softball propaganda interview with Trump
Sitting down with Sean Hannity
That's why maybe it's
Flat a little bit in the room
Time sorry
Alex
That's all
Well alright
Play alt-rock playlist interview for Hannity
The real Thief
To talk about how Trump
Is giving up
A lot in order
To be president
Like as businesses or suffer
Sure miss clip
Makes a pretty compelling case
The trumpet
Profiting off the press
Justin
You want to see
Liberals
BuzzFeed
Sneaking around in there
Wild
To do with that
Exactly my style
Remodel house and I said yeah
Wow
My friends
You certainly are
That's
Face out of
Is but Sprite that's in
Bootlicker
Approach
Hotels
Static is so good I'm going to make my house like it
My wife said it's great Gavin Trump Hotel
Pretty much
Expresses the idea that this
Bar in this hotel is become a hotspot
Profiting off Amendment
Nobody's doing that
Nobody's bothering with that
Nobody's bothering with just the regular doing crimes lot of like profiting off it like
Alex is one of his
Most ardent
Supporters and he argues consistently the Trump doesn't profit up
Presidency
Very clear argument that he is
Absolutely
Nope
Isabel
So in this next
From the 20s
Alex brocato for another 40 minutes
From The Blaze
So he was he was really fun in this one parallel to go into the office
Parallel to the 2013 stuff that we're looking at
Interesting
Weird intersection
Cincinnati
At the end of this week
This Saturday the 25th
26 Riyal into
The idea of his intersections with other media figures
Yeah so whether it's I talked to Max Keiser at the Trump Hotel
Or I didn't interview with Eric Bolling
Or you know Trump did this interview with Sean Hannity and he saying a lot of similar stuff to me
There's the same thing with Alex being obsessed for a week
Back in the past of he wet on Piers Morgan
Pinchot
So there's a little bit of a like a navel-gazing grind but Alex is in
There's not a whole lot but on the 26b says this
And this is like
Again
We talked about earlier
So overtly awful
Excusable
Measles in frittatas
Whooping cough but it doesn't matter
Another shot
Are scams
Are Trojan horses for other things
Legal
Water in high jeans
Screen
I will say an hour
And that so long as we don't have immigrants
And we just starting out
There will be no.
I don't know up
I want I want
In fairness to Alex but I think opposite
About Trump saying people should get there
Internal
Consistent with his
Liza
Information
What is a Styler propaganda
Claiming the immigrants and asylum-seekers are spreading disease and causing outbreaks is a time-tested way to
Dehumanize a population
To treat them like things with no right
What means
Comfortable
We killing them because if you don't look at your community sick
This is something that we've seen in history
Never a good time
Yeah
Information
Whooping cough immigrants coming
Nazis and white nationalists online or spreading memes
But any epidemiologist
Research
Easy will tell you very clearly
That these outbreaks are the result of people not getting their children vaccinated
And I will tell you that they are getting their children vaccinated because they believe the b******* people like Alex Jones
Donald Trump
I've been telling them for years
The substance being here doesn't even deserve to
Discussion at McLendon
And it's not even the first epically Alex is made in this episode of our show
This Frederick deserves condemnation denunciation remember
The next time a white nationalist terrorist commits an act motivated by fears about immigration
Rhetoric like this allows those fears
Sofia feel real
It's a fuel pressure
And it allows the responsive murder to feel Justified
Whether it's packaged as arguments that wants Muslim
Make up 10% of the population.
Or if it comes in
The form of argument
Refugees
Central America or causing outbreaks
No matter the particular shape it takes on any given day
The message underneath
Is the same
People who are not like you are a threat to you
And you're right. An unbalanced ethnic
6 Powerstroke
It really bothers me it bums me out
But when we here
Like two different
Pictures
Two ethnic cleansing
Within a two-day span on her show
Two things that are
Really
Reminiscing
Of
Propaganda that gets
People killed
It it's really really hard for me to step back
Maine
My position
A coincidence
Then somehow he doesn't realize
The sort of things
I don't I don't know
Veneer Falls away
At a certain point
I like, I'm a huge fan
Of the first
Just want to set get that out there
Long-time lover first time
Can you do
Well I mean that might be why he's on
On the side of the line
Is I take the probably you can
I think that I think that probably is on the wrong side
No free speech
It's not on the wrong side of free speech
That's their latest movies
That are inspirational
To see these sorts of things
To make people feel like it's
The ticking time-bomb
Until there are enough Muslims around they will hurt
Every one of these immigrants that's coming in
Smallpox
You know about the idea
Estimated leading to three emerging
Into things like polio
Alex is rhetoric
Person
Who's coming here illegally is a potential
Tocabe
If you introduce these eyes
I mean
You know that there's
Some percentage of them we were going to
Rightfully interpret
People existing is a
I just don't
There's
There has to be a legal
There is a difference
Justify
Cleansing and calling 4S
I get that
But it feels like you
Have one without the other
And if we were to get rid of the justifying pie
We wouldn't have the calling for
I don't know
I'm not I'm not a
Choosing a lawyer
So that makes me pretty mad
Because like Ice-T a deterioration
In the present day
Sing like that
ICA quickening
Downward
In terms of the Howard Danger
Whether it's
Like when we talked about it I think was maybe a week or so ago when he was talking about the drag queen bingo
Reading the drag queen story time
Vampirism
And then an hour later he has a caller who says I think I should be able to go in
Right
Into the parking lot
Island
And subsequent episodes
He continues at the rhetoric
That he was
Think about that
Storytime
Stuff like that you just
You recognize
Like
It's hard to phrase it any other way
No he doesn't care that a collar literally said
I should be able to kill the
These people
And it's reinforced by the rhetoric that
Alex
Has died on the show and continues to
I don't I don't
I don't know what to do
I don't know
I mean turns varsha I just weekend we keep doing what we do
Put like a
I don't I don't
I don't
I become very uncomfortable with where this is like
Legal
This shouldn't be legal
Mission be legal
Yeah
I don't I don't know
Where the line is still work
Do not know how to end this episode at all I'm not feeling
Optimistic
Into despair
I think a lot of this stuff looks real bad and part of the reason why I feel a little bit more gloomy than usual
Probably because the f****** neighbors keeping me up all weekend
I think that there's a there's a possibility
Moving forward posit
Every time
Listen to hours of Alex in Fresno
It just
Man
Man this show is bad
This show is dangerous
Like beneath the surface of the like
CertiFit sensible political talk in like Trump is awesome
Kind of stuff be soft
Pictures to ethnic cleansing
Being buried in there
Are really really f******
Troubling
And I just I just don't know how to I don't know how to not take that as you're easily as it deserves to be
I just don't know how to respond appropriately
I've never thought about being in a position where like
I see what is left
To its own devices
Could easily spiral into
Alright Muslims aren't allowed to breathe
Yeah I don't know what to say to that other than go fuc yourself
I just never I never
Expected that I would be in a position where
Someone would be
Expressing
Maybe I'll be better at it next time
For now
So I don't ramble more about how I don't know what to say about this
We got to watch
Review of website its knowledge on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
We are on
ITunes you can find us
Download the
You could go to the website and finding out
Like podcast aggregators
Stuff like that probably listen to us on app
Some stuff like that that I don't even f****** know exist
Some of that is just how podcasting works
Always like
There's a bunch of places but also I appreciate people there a couple folks
Two products are 10
Lumosity whatever the f***
Add put our stuff up there
I appreciate the heads-up I sent them an email
But I have no idea how any of you listen to our show
I know about three things that exist one of them too
Thank you very much appreciate it
But will be back
But until then
Max Keiser offered Alex Jones
$10,000 in Bitcoin
What guy who has
Technically
The guy who turned down
50 million
And that's Alex
Alex