Alex
Who's your favorite movie
I don't like scary movies but also talked about Like the Wolf
Real monsters I didn't like
But I did like the song The Monster
Okay
I want to talk about my
I want talk with something real quick
No I knew about all of Boris Pickett
Other songs
Swim
And the sequel to The Monster Mash and the climate Mash
Yeah okay
A long time ago
Kind of credibility in my trying to clean. I don't feel like I can talk about my
Love of the idea that he just
Captivating Go song
Because
Point that out
It's not a novel observation for me and that's pretty much my relation
Zip with monster
Who's your favorite universe
Classic movie monsters that's what came to my mind
There we go
1 time for a live show I wrote the holiday show
Pick of the Monster Mash 2
I don't remember
I don't remember exactly but it was like
Facebook podcast
About to the Monster Mash song parody
Wilson Pickett
Long-lost
Incorrect
That's correct
Which will be a humdinger
As I told you over text
Regarding
Banner
I don't think that I can over selfie
Wonderful
Send a message
You're not a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
I could do
Thank you so much
Begin to get in touch with no Cafe
Service
Watch The Postman
These are all right I was thinking it was
From the movie The Postman
El Postino
He was also in Waterworld, Connecticut
Also finally
Although much like a paper crafts
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean
Appreciate it
About Argo
Crossville
The tri-state area has been randomly hit by measles so you've heard the bad news
The bad news
People people have
I we are now below
That's exactly like how my life goes
Cousin
Going to get this tattoo
Butts
I'll get to that
Maybe another documentary
People are interested in that
Could
Maybe we don't have the technology
Wacky Wednesday
For you
For you for you
Yeah
Okay you know what you know what this is
One of the things that I value
About doing Wacky Wednesday
Alex Jones
Being able to tell stories
Google to get into
And
What I'm about to
Present in front of you
Is a
Literally insane
Things I learned about
Something I was working on it still
And that is
Are you ready I am never been more in suspense as to whether or not this is truly a hump day
It's awesome.
Last episode of Adventures
Convicted murderer Mark Richard
Music actually
A secret space program
On that last time do we look
Tell Mark is full of s***
After
Trailer for that document
The story of Mark Richards is absolutely wanted
More attention
Is it true crime
Angle
That's a love story you know both with Mark and his wife and with Mark and the Raptor princess who's in space
No alerts for the high card
This story has it all really it does so the ideal humidity about it obviously I'd like
But
I got very excited about the possibility that someone who had the funding
Interview people involved in the murder that Mark committed
Carrie I got really excited about that possibility what we could
Compliment
My tone was very positive about
On the trailer which
Hilarious Moments Mercury cast
He tries to convince the
The filmmaker
That Mark was off-planet when the murder happened and is friends with raptor
But the more I thought about it the more something
Fit right
Who was this guy making this documentary
Find out the guy who makes the documentary is even crazier than
What I realized
Aries accusation that he
The dildo salesman
Cast of The Reptilian
He's right on that I realize what I really
He knew about it
Is there anything I tried to do on this podcast as much as I can
Especially
I don't know nearly enough about this British guys making this documentary about a subject that we've covered on our show pretty much since we saw
Started doing the show
So I set out to learn a little bit more about this guy
And that's what we're going to be talkin about here today
You're convinced three children to murder
He's mad at Mark Richards cuz he took his record
If you take Kevin at his word here is his rationale for why about Mark
This is the first docu-series
Orbitz kind
Communities that are represent
As well
To the communities
Is a credible research
Two people
When people trying to explore
There's a greater reality
And when it's met with misinformation and disinformation
You know that's something that I can't
Cooling right now
Show The Office
What's this song
Some of these so-called whistleblowers
Use that you may seem like
Little bit overly capricious
Like you're being a little bit overly judgmental based on
What you assume is
Going to happen
Like what
Write well but that means I can mean a whole bunch of different things
If you take there are credible researchers in
In the field and people like Mark
Derrida service
Abby's always people who are actively searching
I think there are
People who aren't crazy who are into aliens
And stuff like that
But just boil down
Blind Center
Motivation for making a documentary
He reiterates that here in this next clip
Why did I do it well it was
It was just to try to
Give us some contacts in the stories that are out that nowadays
What riches is one story
There are so many other stores how many how much disinformation do you think there is in the field
You get the sense that this is really how you presented the motivation
Embarking on this documentary
About Mark Richards actually being a murderer
Joanne Richard
These people were full of s***
And helping him push his story on the map
So
Is this Fair
Is this complete b*******
Only time will tell
You know a couple hours ago now
You have a pretty good idea in a couple hours
Kevin Moore has a YouTube channel
What he posted a teaser trailer for his forthcoming
Show called The Maury Show
This is a show that he was trying to sell to people that was vaguely a spiritualist talk show
On which you would interview writers and actors from the UK
As well as astronomers and political Act
Being a pretty normal show
But just with a slight undercurrent of new-age
Yeah what time
As far as I'm not going to buy into everything you say
Trying to get into
Like a non-aggressive new age
Nonsense
Threatening
I can enjoy that for a little while
While I'm bored
Matthew's Baldwin
Interview with Stanley Kubrick
Musician
There were a few apparently
Playing interview
Pretty quickly
Turned into a conspiracy new age
Theme
Became the clear focus of the show started to talk to Freemason
People who called themselves color psychic
Okay I don't know what that means
No talking to a bunch of folks wanted to tell you how imminent UFO disclosure
Right around the corner
But all the while straightforward
Would still make appearances
And you would have interviews with guests like David prowse
Who played Darth Vader
Add that Jo Frost from the show Supernanny
Kernel of tethering
Back in 2011 America's collapsing economy
With frequent Alex Jones
Bear
Paul Craig Roberts
Possibly worse or at least certainly more boring
Kevin also had an interview with Jerome corsi
A few years back
So you can see
Just one
Appoint
Similarities
There's overlap
Shirtless
Through
As time went on
Towards
Spiritualism stuff take
Tweet Center
Becoming the primary topic of pretty much all of his videos
We're talkin about constant interviews a psychic
Astrologist to past life regression
Kevin Blanchard interviews with
Big names in the field
David Icke
And on January 29th
2012 he posted an interview with Kerry Cassidy
3 herself
It was mostly a softball interview about how Project Camelot was a portal for whistleblowers
But ultimately the content
Nearly as enter
First thing is the fact that it is
Right so we're not going to listen to
I will tell you you can go
He is in no way critical of her
He doesn't push back against her
Sort of
Very
Nonsensical
Also
On June 10th 2012
Kevin shouldn't be judged too harshly about this aspect
Called
It was a FEMA drill to promote gun
Control
Probably should sleep or not.
Jim Fetzer the literal Holocaust denier
But maybe that was an open question is
Publix at there was about as not
Sympathy at this
Okay so there's a possibility
But this dude has Renee
Previous life
And is
Making this documentary
As a as almost
As a wave
I love you thinking
About ideas
Impossible
Whatever kind of plausible deniability you might have about like
The late twenties
12 interview with him
You don't have it anymore you should take that s*** the f*** off
Cuz he goes around
Content but snobbery contact
Workout is at
TV talk-show it lived on
You're a tell Kevin about it
Leavenworth is magical
That's on YouTube
I guess it's podcast
Can't find it.
Distribution strategy of this
But I don't know how
Widely distributed
Some sort of like Satellite Channel
Possible from what I could tell was pretty short-lived
Late night
Weirdo show
We are in the present day 2019
Kevin Moore has rebranded
Into a voice of steps
Decision is making the documentary about how Mark Richards is a murderer who defrauded everyone into
He puts up frequent vlogs
YouTube channel that often
About how is documentary
Is going to undo all the damage
The curry is done
Still makes me wonder how
Stop
And that is the secret space program
Opinion
Every minute of my time
So I would say
You know he's not really taking the high road
Project
Understand an excuse a little bit of that Agro tone
Benny has
In that last clip about like you notes
Worth all the work
Similarly
Exasperate
But he's addressing her and Joanne Richards
In this Walk That You released from April 9th
This is what you should have done in the first place
Embarrassment
Gets hot whistleblower
I understand the idea that
Ghetto carries been
I'd like to cheese.
It makes
Exasperate
The way the carries responding to him
She said that like really inept
Almost incomprehensible write-up about it
Harassment
For us
People completely detached
From the reality of all this
Who's the funny story
Crazy guy in prison
But for other people this is
Real life
Richard Baldwin was a real person who was murdered
His family lost a loved one that day when barking Crossing Hoover killed
Mark and crossings family set
How to deal with the pain
A relative committed murder
I don't have to carry and work through the stigma that comes along with that ever since
Has Kevin Wright
Squid from the introduction
Trailer for his documentary
Mercurial Jo-Ann's who has a negative effect on the people most hurt
5 marks crime
Leonid Stoltz
Surviving member of
Susan Baldwin
He was devastated
Books that Carrie and Joe
Giving me
The platform that they are
Dispute
His misinformation
Make make sense
I figured something like that would be really funny
Ruby kind of hilarious as well I don't know it turned out that on March
28 2015 Kevin Moore gave Joanne Richards
Formation about the secret space program
And heroic
Husband Captain Mark Ritchie
I should be clear I'm not calling him Captain Mark Richard
Kevin Moore credits
In the video that he put out
Captain Mark Richards
That's even in the description of the video Captain Mark Richards
Which
He credited Marc Richards as a captain when he interviewed Joanne
Play the little bit ago I don't know how
In our community and that was a big red flag for me there
Hold on to
Inter-Community
Joe
To New Age and spiritual
So Kevin Moore is now working on a documentary about how Mark Richards is a murdering people shouldn't be treating him like a legitimate
Information
So I feel like maybe it's in our best
Pinterest to check in
Etsy just handled himself when he had the chance
Either push back or accept the b******* that marks wife was telling him when she was a guest on his
Show
I figured you probably already guessed that if you did a good job
Complete f****** idiot while Joanne Richards lies to him about her murder her husband
Space Adventures
Is pathetic
So are dispersed Cliff Kevin
Introduces Joanne as his guest
For this episode
No Joanne riches is the wife
Democracy
Who claims he was in office
As well as variac
Chris PACE program
And US space command
So right out of the gate
Maybe this is just him like giving her the benefit of the
You know
The part in terms of Champions interview Style
Talking about the actual murder
Somebody who's lying about
Interested
He's not a murderer you asked about the murder is an open question
Okay is or isn't a murderer in the question
The work of the liar for that
Don't establish
The truth of the answer in advance
Scuse me
Yes or no question
This is a very strong indication
Kevin is either
The worst person at his job
Or you actively participating in what Joanne wants
What's to do here on this
Tell me
A bit about the background
Story
Of the
Because I believe this well
That
He wasn't even he was away on a mission that's not good
Oh that's really not good in the cuisine
Establishes that Mark was off-planet now all Joanne has to do is say yes I O
I agree with that
He has done the heavy lifting for her
This is a collaborative interview where Mark Richards murder is
Or is the end result
But the audience is being walked towards
Blind
Stumbling through this f****** interview because maybe what he meant to say was
I believe your story is that he wasn't even off
I think when you're talking about stuff like this
Little more careful
Probably a couple years later you take the horsepower that you do
Against
This very person who your interview about yourself
And tacitly
So we both know the murder happened
And he wasn't around for it so tell me more about that
Completely open to the idea that he was off the planet
It's been whatever narrative she wants
Lackadaisical about a murder victim
So now then to go to the murder of in 1982 a murder happens
Here
In one of his cover business
Mrs. forget his military stuff
Was
Remodeling people's houses or or whatever
Doing a remodeling project at a friend's house
And the guy also had a business
Restoring antique
Cars
What my husband didn't know at the time was that the guy was also
The filming child pronography in his house
And he was a drug dealer
Sajid
Go to lunch well then leave
Kids that works for my husband cuz my husband had a
Cheddar's
And had a habit of hiring
Basically juvenile delinquents
Ali's kids
Kill the guy
And
When they started getting in trouble or whatever they just said my husband
Masterminded the whole thing
So what's up
He allows Joanne Richards
To assert
The person who her husband
Was responsible for murdering
Was a c****************
He introduced murder into his life but it's not really that big a deal because the Dude is a child pornographer
Degenerate
Hired child delinquent then we all know that
Murder solved
He allows Joanne
To say that
Which is not backed up by any
There is no
Proof.
That's slander
That she's committing against this guy is that
Kevin doesn't ask any follow-up question
She doesn't hold on
Because anything
Grapes
Richard Baldwin
At the same time
Is part of the Corpus of information that's being presented
To do his listeners
Which makes me remember this clip
From just a little bit ago
You know I met your sole surviving member of a family
Susan Baldwin
That Carrie and Joe
The platform that they are
Wonder wonder if you discussed your own behavior in that meeting
In this next clip
You just allows Joanne more about it
Something
Any.
Interviewer
What
The f*** are you talking about
Do they change the date of death of the Vic
Turn three times to make sure it was a Thailand Marquess
What okay what
Can you back that up in literally any way what is death
Alibis
Go stupid
Check if you read the transcript of the interview and Mark got arrested
Any Alibis he had
Not
He was eating a sandwich with his parents or something like that backup alibi
Bulshit
No absolutely not
So in this next clip
Jojo
Discusses the idea that
Mark was off-planet
Whenever this murder happened
Close attention to the way
She's talking
You might get the sense
Mark
Say that
Antigo interviewer
Might ask a follow-up question
About like what are you talkin about
Who knows
He has Alibis for the other day since
He might even have an alibi for the day he was off on a mission but
Now at least
Implies or will say I
Probably wasn't there
That's not good
Fly
Interviewer worth their salt okay
You
I got to go
So is there any reason why
As opposed to
Specifically
You know and I know he
It's trying to tell me I was off doing something else
You know and I can go do that within an 8-hour Spanish
Oh really okay
You can't and won't tell me where he is
Where he was or what he was doing or how he got there
I strongly believe
He was not
In town
The Day of the Dead
Let's go let's go let's go
Briefly summarize
That
You understand that that is not a follower
What is the amazing what are the
Set me up
Pretty ball yeah
Images wallpaper
Everything you told me is true
Let's summarize what it is
I mean
Basically just comes down to I chosen to believe that
Do this
Tell me where he was
Which I would argue it
Just speaking as myself is the definition
Wasn't there
So I believe that Kevin as the interviews like
Well yeah
Let's hear about
Cool
Sound
Great yeah I mean that's a pathetic
I'm interviewing of
Sympathetic level of Base conversation
It's very bad
He's trying to get to the
Score of
Information now
He's been in prison
For quite a while what's the
Accidentally
Reveals that like
Why now because
Maybe the first 10 years of prison there was still a chance of him getting out through legal channels
Exhausted pretty much all his legal remedies
And after 10-15 years of prison he was pretty tired of prison
And so he decided Well I'm just going to start writing this
Stop that I'm just going to start
You know sharing some of this information that can be leaked out there
Because number one people will think he's crazy so they won't believe him anyway
And who's this little wife of his you know she must
Be crazy if she believes him
That's just
Exact
Diversion
One of the store you expect
From her butt look like
Excuse board
Imprisoned
Yeah he's like writing fantasy novel
And she's like no it's
Elvis legal channel so he's kind of made peace with he's going to be there forever and he realized
Is that without that hope propelling him
Real
I don't think that's an offensive thing that she's
Push back at Aldi like
He's not just writing like
Syfy
Considered
You are also exploiting him for a cottage industry
Is an interviewer that might be a bit Brusque
I think a better question would be
Are you
You sure
Starts going off about how like all these
These countries work
Together in
Can aliens work together with all of our countries
Because
There's the appearance
Seems everyone's work
Together like
They did in the Cold War
Put together behind the scenes
Here to be because
This is a nonsensical idea
Clip is important
Because
Listen to how Kevin
Responding to her ideas
There's a collaborative aspect
He agrees with her and builds on
Points that she's making
And when we were having the Cold War
Most of these countries were actually work
Working together when there was
Even though
Publicly say that but you had this agency that work together and told in
People from
Many different country
The different militaries working together against a common threat so
You know they're all working together but they all have to keep it
Because I don't think the whole the world
In general
Handle the truth
No absolutely not
Some of the reasons why
As well
In the story
Endorse
Like marks
Information
Explain why can't
Peter to get along but actually received
Secretly working together
And also
Agrees with her in that week
We cannot handle
No
Nara
Was there a code red
I don't know
As far as what she's talking about
Richards
Just another weirdo since
I'm going to bed
It literally everything I own
Smart
Then they're out
I bet that she gets them in for my
From Carrie as well
Community
Or whatever
This one
Because
Just got this in my bees
I didn't have a lot of Men In Black
Right so people like Mark Richards dad
Deducted
Was just a man of me
Would you rather
Skylar
If I recall correctly
We're hanging out with Winston Churchill
When was 18 years older whatever
Weirdly too boring for me
He was really rich and really smart really cool and so he took on the role of being a man in Black
Because like you wanted to help Humanity
I wanted to help the country
Reply
He was working alongside someone else
Heard of before
It is comical to hear of in this context
You know we didn't have a lot of Men In Black or whatever so you had rich young men or Young Rich Man
Who wanted to help the government
Select Barry Goldwater and
Actors and told people where they wanted to help
So there was a lot of
If there was that
Interesting stuff going on under
Nobody knew about this
Doing stuff as a teenager and after the war
He was involved with investigating
Dealing with alien activity and UFO sightings
Barry Goldwater
Champs
Totally
Okay
F****** crazy
So like at least
Kind of make this a fun version
But you know what I think though if you ask him now point-blank like
Amanda black
I'm not doing any
You better go right
I think is probably where this interview is
Is the most irresponsible
Not in terms of like the content
Murder victim
Richard Baldwin was a child
Without any evidence
Deeply response
Baofeng
I'll bet you could do if you're covering this story
Interviewer standpoint
This is where it's at
Tryon
He went to Vietnam
As a lieutenant in the army
Before that
She went
Sheila an Interstellar treaty,
But we can come back to that
So he was doing
Early on
He wanted to the Vietnam as a lieutenant
Came out a captain in the Army and then
Move sideways in
Michaela
Captain in the Navy
So his
Current rank
Is Cap Navy captain
So here's the thing through some problems with the story
Jump rope Navy and State
Talk about
Is the problems here at the story that Joann's tell Kevin about her husband's alleged military service
Should be asking follow-up
Lessons about Indians
That you just took
Actively participating
Spread dubious bulshit on his show
He really doesn't care to push back on it at all
The most glaring problem
Became a captain in the Army moves sideways
Probably
Well that a lateral move
Is ranked both branch
Anything about the services would think going from army captain
Navy captain
Where is a lateral move
Achieved after reaching the rank
Lieutenant
And first lieutenant
In the Navy Captain is an o-6
Position after ensign
Lieutenant Junior grade
Commander commander
Moving Sideways from the position of army Commander
Lieutenant
Tomorrow
Easycap
Then one would need to be promoted
Three times along the way
What is a pretty sizable job
The second problem is that she's just which branches of enlist
You could just do on a whim
Well it is possible to switch branches
Not very common
The process is really pretty complicated
There's a saying that I ran into a few times while looking
It goes like this
It's easier to join the military from the streets and from the flea
Express
Would you have to consider
He's not just the Army but with boats
Branch of service
Cultures differ
Missions
Let's go through
Someone who reaches 03 in the army
Likely a different set of skills
203 in the Navy
And there's no real
Skills
To be transferable
This isn't to say that it
It's never done
But it's pretty rare
And when it does happen
It never comes with an arbitrary 3-ranked promotion
Just so you get to keep the same literal title captain
We're happy to interview
We love to have you give me a list of skills
Okay you can run very so I talked to Raptors
Okay that one might help
The story of Joanne is telling indicates a lack of awareness
The military were
A lack of awareness
Captain isn't the same rank in the Army and the Navy
And a lack of awareness that there's literally no proof that Mark was he
Never in the army
Orange
Military records show that Marx dad Ellis Orthodox men
Join the Army in 9th or the Air Force in 1942
Military records also show that he was involved in for plane crashes during isn't list
Between 1943 and 90
Teen 52
From the report about his night
Bad pilot
The canopy exploded off but not by the pilot and the tail section broke off at the turbine wheel set
Very well
The pilot was dragged along the ground and slick
Deep Cuts in a brain concussion
Also breaking his
This plane crash led to Ellis being leaving the service being partially paralyzed
Newspaper articles about Mark's arrested
Trial include quotes
From Alice and they all mentioned that he was disabled
Which makes it very unlikely that he was going on Space Battles after night
Fifteen52
Or that he was fighting adults
Sea bass battle
Years later is Marcus dead
Elvis died before Joanne ever met mark
So all she really knows about him
Does what he's told
So she can believe all this b*******
Battles of aliens
It was
Personally
Right
Like remember when Willie Walker
Walking on a
And then that's not
Dallas pets
It's not it was in a bit
Fayetteville
Mark is almost certainly making up his
He claimed to be served in Vietnam
Mark graduated from Dominican College with a history degree
He was born in 1950
G3722 or 23 graduating
Undergraduate program
Right on schedule
19 seven
33 he was arrested
Insurance fraud
The charges were eventually dropped
It's pretty strong proof that he wasn't in
Vietnam
There's literally no proof that Mark was ever in life
No documentation no pictures of him in uniform
No medals are stripes
Short of some sort of a bombshell that they're just not showing anybody some reason
It's pretty easy
But this is a case of
Stolen Valor
Unmarked Spark
Lift out that possibility
The second Joanne said that Mark moves sideways
From army Captain to Navy
It's an absurd state
Kevin doesn't bat an eyelash
He doesn't have to follow up question
Because he's an active
Participate
In platforming this b*******
Welding
Established that he was in fact about the captain in the army
Maybe we can just move on right
Please give a summary of the rest
Whatever
Participant
Reinforces that as
He tells people to go listen
Two other interviews Market
And even like you're a child and she's been there twice now and just is
Anybody
To visit him
I don't want to stay at
I try not to put them on a pedestal
But you're just in all of the wealth of information that he
Tino's
Yeah
Gregory
Soho react
Wait he saw her
Very Berry in
First time John listed
To meet him as well
Listen to
Who carries interviews with Mark Richards
There's video outside
Vacaville the first time
Zecharia Joanne
She thought that you'd be able to video record stuff store
Who's videotape
Yourself in the car
Turn off camera and then turn it back on whenever they got
So he knows the kind of bulshit that's in them
If you're not
After 3
Interested in trying to
Get a piece of it or something
Send
Schoolboy what's going on
There's something
Though there is something
So I don't know if you remember earlier
Interstellar comp
And what that was all about
Braces right
They're coming here they're going to decide whether we get to go to space
They're going to decide
Taking our jobs
Experimentation
I'm too or something
Prince of the UK leave some alien children
That it could have gone in
It was fascinating so Mark is there
And
Teenage father in 1950
To Matt a Raptor
Which is a reptilian that was originated here on Earth
Dallas was in that terrible paralyzing
Plane crash
Mark might be trying
To recapture
It looks like
Evan Healy vault
Dinosaurs
Tall guy
With a long tail and long snout Lots
So big
Sharp teeth and very sharp claws
And they became friends of 1952 when Prince Naga
Came as an ambassador
Forgiving forward almost 10 years and Naga is at this conference
Checks out two of his children princess Linka and
Crack
Are we still doing the markets to me
Gets to me the Raptor
First of the first
Time
They thought it was
And he becomes
Really good friends with Princess Linka and Prince Cragin they were several years older he was sick
707 going on 8th
Summer
And they were probably
You know there were several years older
They just became great friends and marks
English friend
Titania was with him
Average humans that were there decided they wanted to have this little experiment in
She will Howard the human shoulder going to react and get along with the alien
Children
Fortunately that the Raptors didn't
Eat them so that was cool that is a real cool thing that happened
Eat the children
You win some you lose some
She's just she's just rolling over that with her
I was watching your reaction so you got real f****** like
Shrugging
Talk about
When she said there a couple years old in human years
I'm glad you clarified because I was going to ask my
Different planet to work
Earth rotation around the
Hayward
And probably
I I think my
Favorite subject
Here is
Do you think Mark is real mad
People know him
Name is Mark
Because it look at the names of my playlist
Mark the whole time is like
And as we know one of the main characters from his book
Super important to recognize here is that
He doesn't ask
Any f****** follow-ups after that nonsense
The ID
When is
Presenting
Did Mark as a child
To a conference
The UK
Where he made friends with raptor babies who might have eaten him
Because his friends with rafter royalty few years prior
It was like
Okay
It's not a it's not a good energy all right what was the conference
No she doesn't
Like whether or not humans could go to space
Brenda universe
So I don't understand
If that is what the conference
Is why there's the possibility of being
Eaten by Raptors
There's always
Conference on
There shouldn't be a chance
Because it's
There's no Raptors
F******
Every time there's a security council meeting
You wouldn't want to take that appointment
The appointment
We're going to have some breakout sessions right now Terrence
You're going to be with the roofers today is almost a princess Linka
Cool
So we learned Raptors
We already know that
But at this point to a couple of the other races
And here
Excited to learn about the cat
There's a cat species
And they're basically scientists and artists and archaeologist
You know about the one he talks about the most she's at Contessa
She comes here to the planet
Because she's trying to discover evidence of
When and where her species has been when they visited her
I hear that
Right
First of all feline Contessa might be a new rank
Feline
The others
I hear that
I can't not hear it is Mark
About litter boxes
The cats like to dig
So they're archaeology
I heard as his veiled
Sexism
That is because those are the jobs
Considers to be more feminine
Maybe
It's possible Association of cats
Sweat Franklin
I'd like to go on a date with him sometime I was there for one semester in college I thought I was going to be
Archaeology
Find out about dog
Is old on
So is every other alien species of a feudal
Structure
Like she's a Contessa like there's no it's hard to say
I think it's because Mark likes that kind of fiction
Ethereal Legends stuff like that
Dude dollars get into dogs
I do not like dogs rather be around cats and dogs
There's just something I don't trust about
To say
You were right b a
There's a dog species that has a huge base here
Prepare basic their hole
Existence at me no Merchants there businessman they love
To work with humans just
As a matter of you not being capitalistic
Dog aliens are capitalist
Interstellar Merchant
Of course I should have seen that one coming
They still love to be around
That is true across
All aspects
Steven Universe
I'd love to be around people
Right but it's all because of capital is
Dogs.
Do we are we going to get some Mos Def and Talib Kweli from the buyer
And their intellectual
And great
And I love that
And they're always looking for a buck
Traders traveling cups
Systems
System selling their Wares nonsense
So innocent Joanne
Elvis selling VA.
Pretty much all natural disasters
Or just cover-ups
For math
Abduction
Kevin response
Absurd notion
Being said to his f******
Face
And so a lot of times and natural disasters will happen
Because there is either about to be or there's just been a major calling
Humans and they just took kidnapped thousands of people and
Very negative reason
It's usually not because
They want you to be their best friend and go to school with your kids
Fight about it Miss if people
Talk about love
It's not
It's not positive
Well
Whoa
You think this price of
Evidence
Where they've gone
Who's took right
Who's
Boost.com
Oh boy
So she went
Recover from
All of those just disappear I get it I get it
We're at we're all talk about the Malaysian plane
It's 2050
I got you
But come on
It's not like there's a ton of playing
That's not what
Yeah I mean interpretation
Bad the fact
City doesn't push back in
Anyways
Is really bad
Also
Forced busing
I think that might be part of it
Could be you know what else
Terrorism
And they also work with that terrorist groups
Which one
So for example when you hear of a terrorist
DVD maybe at a shopping mall
Or maybe in a middle eastern
Country for example
It's not always
50 human terrorists that are at fault they're awful
Send working with
Alien
Terror
Bad guy
Call them terrorists
Yes
Nearby
Talked about the
I want
You back on
Got to come back on and then listen to the plug
I mean I know we weave weave
We haven't covered
Soap
Again I would I would recommend
Emma put links on there
Carrie cast
You just woke up
If she goes a lot morning
Depth
Go on my website
And will you put up the link for that EDH
Hcad.org
Headquarters
If you go on my website and click on product
I have descriptions of all the different reports that I sell
That he's written about his different missions and Adventures in
I'm going to sound like
But their true military mission
Planet summer off-planet so
Whatever you want
You can get
Has been
The old way through
It's the least you
Wow you obsequious prick
This install that we really need to listen
Interview with that
Just playing the entire thing
Kevin Moore does literally push back against any of the things
Joanne rich
Pictures of telling him
He believes
He doubled narratives and is not in anyway exercise
We're looking for evidence for any
He even establishes that Mark was away on a mission with Richard Baldwin's murder
As an answer to an open question
Kevin established
For her
Something like that makes Kevin
Claims of carrots
About how Baldwin
Seems very
F****** Halo
I want you so I just
Here's the thing
The burright look at Kevin Moore's videos
About his documentary
You look at the past
You look at this stuff the fact that
Use actively engaged in spreading these stories
A little bit rough
Disclosures
While he's talking about
This documentary
I used to believe it I haven't heard a word of that video
But he has far too many for me to watch all of them
Okay
So
How are we
Before we get to that
He's an a******
One of the reasons
Clip
Free seems to be saying that part of his
He's doing interview for this documentary
Is digging into the validity of Mark and Joanne
Marriage
As well
Contact
Montgomery Clerk's Office
End the marriage certificate
Documentary
Jo-Ann's
Mariemont
I will make my own checks as well cuz I'm going to go down to Alameda where you hide your previous marriage
I'm divorced should be there as well
My riches coming soon
40 amazing secrets
Mock
Riches
Unless unless she's like
Con woman with multiple documentaries about something else
It's not about Mark Richards in his murder that
But one thing to remember is that Joanne by her own admission
Has
Married and divorce
Several times
Because she
Pretty awful marriages
Getting married and divorced freaky
Play can lead to some nominal confusion
Especially to external Observers
It seems like Heaven's trying to take that and make it
Suspicious
Vindictive
Their marriage has nothing to do with this documentary as it's being presented
Whatever
Expose your wedding certificate
Although it doesn't strengthen his argument that Mark is lying about the murder
It's just an attempt to hurt Joanne
Yeah
I suppose the only
Only way that that is not
Complete and total dick
Move is if she is like a noted Conway
Traveled around
Right
She's not funny but I will look
The TV where owns Volvo
Beyonce
Some subconscious level but it's not
That's not essential piece of what
The birth name
Is 1
And then the other name did he uses
Faucet
And if you look in the like
You can find her going by that name
Probably
Previous marriage
Her husband's surname
1997 you can find records of her online going as
Is Joanne faucet and then she gets married
Has Joanne Faust
Richard
So it's there's nothing suspicious here as far as I can tell supper
For him to justify this not as B
Like him just
Being a f***
Is real high
Yeah he needs to establish something other than
Winking
Bugging us about I'm looking into you
Gross
The reason
Suspicious
What are those has to do with the
The fact that in May 28th
Moorhead
His interview with Joanne Richardson from 2015
So I suppose he could make the argument
In the intervening
Change of heart about
Matter
He's now working to right those wrongs like you suggested earlier
Interview with Carrie took place less than a year ago
If you pay attention
You start to see shades of
Deception
This interview happened before he started working on his documentary about Mark Richard
But he uses footage from this interview for the documentary
This footage is enter
Now Jordan I'd like you to take a listen
To this
From the trailer
And he's in constant contact with the raft
And they are now working according to him
With our military
Will Sandlot riches didn't commit a crime there cuz it's
Well okay
Absolutely friend
With the comes to Mark Richards in particular
There can be no doubt that Kerry Cassidy has no objectivity
She's personally involved and invested in this story like no other
So what you're telling me
Music I like
Alright from how the clip
Kerry was used in the trailer you get the sense that Kevin was
Confronted her about how Marc was actually guilty of the murder
Pitchy foolishly insist
But he was Frank
What's the clip that plays right after is meant to drive home that
Intended message
Now
Let's listen to
Of the actual interview
From May 2018
In the case of Mark Richards he's constantly talking about the rap
After being
The Raptors having gone through a certain amount of evolution
Since the time of the dinosaurs broke off from that
Actually left this part of the Galaxy
And I all of this is in the market
Interviews
I would apologize in advance
Just a few of the sink
And he's in constant contact with the Raptor
And they are now working
According to him
With our military
And
Protecting human
Whatever you want to call
Downloading
Look humans can go through portals
Right here we could commit a crime hat
Okay
Absolutely
I had someone email me
His wife wanted
You don't know one thing
I was in that time when those motives 2
To play
This guy is guilty of
I didn't reply to him cuz I know he's guilty
Taking over exactly exactly
And again to be a lightworker that they've taken over and is now working for the Dark Side of Me chords are so prevalent
You can think what you want obviously I'm not nice.
H & H
Wish I could get him on camera
For the prison won't allow it
You got to ask yourself
This man is is been in prison well over 30 years
He's he's
Guinness 60s his failing health
What you know he's
She didn't commit the murder she supposedly
Mastermind
Why is there non-parole
At this point in his in his life
Well I would say poodle
And the prison itself he was
Basically treated as a Navy captain that he he
He is and was trying to be in prison now
About now that's why I was
All you need is
You know tomorrow someone will come along with Kerry Cassidy
Jubilee
I've known her since they can lie through their teeth
If you do it means nothing
What do you want to do
Discernment this is the
Sort of land we live in
And I stayed a people
Do you expect truth
To be delivered on a silver platter
If that was the case
What would be the point
Some people do
So I think you can get a very clear sense
Exchange
Disney accurately represent
That's bullsh
So
The Oaks from less than a year ago has that
Is because
He did when he talked to all of these
He was a softball interview.
Hip2Save is Jordan
And you know me I don't ever want to be coming to Kerry Cassidy
Defense from everything I've been able to tell I really think Kevin Moore is doing our girls
But I think he's doing
Nothing about what he's doing
There's even something about the whole thing that feels vindictive and
Dishonest
In some way
Something must have happened
Between May 28th
The present-day Kevin Moore on this
Trajectory
But I can't pretend that I have any idea what that thing would have
Beat your life no idea
Well she wasn't
Could be
These people
Shame because I wholeheartedly agree
Masquerade
The story is perfect for a farcical documentary
So long as the subject matter is
Treated with the
Respect the victim
Loved ones
Desert of course $300,000
It doesn't feel like a farcical documentary that
Interested in the subject
Mattered
So he's gloating in these logs about digging into their
Personal lives
Gross
The part of that feeling I have
Information
Remember how I told you I thought you were going to continue
I told you that it 2011
Kevin Post
His first YouTube video
The trailer for his
TV show The Maury Show
I kind of forgot
To tell you that in the disc
Scription of that video Kevin also announces that
Quote
Has now started his own International Psychic service
Support the Maury Show and get a reading
Money
Going on for at least
So he is a psychic
Running a psychic hotline
Running a hotline psychic
Now he was just the Mastermind
Kevin provides a link to book in for a reading
On PMS psychics.com
Witching hour
To channel.com
Delivered
Mediums working
For Kevin Moore
Or at least I assume they're working
Considering the Kevin's face is the logo for the website
They refer to him as quote the owner so looks like it's his
Chairman
No employees offer silver level readings for $100 an hour
$100 an hour but Arthur's silver level
It's 129
Vicious
And if your hours about up in the more important information for you
Don't worry
You're not going to get charged for an extra hour
Platinum reading reading you are going to have to paste
$6
Let's see how much
How much would a 30-minute for the other lights.
It would be an extra $240
Rite Aid for Silver and Gold
Under $60
More than if you just bought another hour
Lying if I said this
It seemed like one of the biggest scam operations I've stumbled into accidentally over the course of doing the show
Say what you want about Kerry Cassidy
At least she doesn't have the temerity to associate yourself with something
This overtly predatory
Looking over the website it's almost a parody of a new-age cash grab
With multiple how to how to pay link
Like you can pay with your credit card or PayPal all over the top of the page and most of the FAQ section
Is dedicated to payment option
8A temperature
Bva concerns
The people who might find themselves feeling
Skeptical
You think I'm lying to you
I will tell you
Exactly why I am not lying
$6 lookup
You can pay with PayPal answer Skeptics question
Readers are experts at telephone
To you through your voice vibration by picking up variations in The Voice
Much like radio waves
As your face can't be read during phone call
Jordan
They could be even more psychic on the phone
Love that spin
I decided to dig around a little and see who some of these mediums are the Kevin wasn't playing
Others at least 30
36 mediums that Kevin
Since to work for him
On the phone which alone seems like a
Sounds probably more like
But I don't know
Use their bios
David
Just just
David channels
Mostly female
To Define themselves as reptilian
Empire
I maybe put my favorite part of that
Is only quotes
Empire
You can trust Cal ask
Because he's not fully Affiliated to the baconian Empire
You just Associated enough to know what's going on now I'm more angry
Is he playing both sides
Enough
There's Earth Angel by the Penguins
It was featured in Back to the
She was
David fields
Biblical names
I guess grounded
You know this stuff is true
Cuz he's just
We really just learned that quote
Her test reading blew us away
Which inspires
All right there's also woman named Galaxy who can quote
Which I think is
If you need that store
And she's like
You don't really
I know that because I can't do it
If I took phrasing extract
Who claims that she could Channel.
Literally the others
Vials are pretty boring
Unfortunately
Also it's just kind of hard to talk to top of guy who specializes in
The goddamn Thundercat
Yeah but you are archaeologists and Poets anyways what do you really want to do with that
.
Some of them offer psychic readings
Specializing giving love advice a reading tarot cards
Some even claimed that they can use Reiki energy
You over the phone since it's all energy
Distance
So what's the deal
Here's the thing
A lot of Psychics employees on is an alien channeling hotline
Have also appeared is Gaston
And show interviewed about their psychic
Of course
All is October 3rd on his October 6th
2013 episode he interviewed rash
The psychic
If you want
To talk to
He's had William Schaefer as a guest twice
Kane Show
A $129 an hour William
You can tell you every
Need to know about yourself
From Reading from the akashic record
Fizz
Very shady
Yeah
Very upsetting
So what you're saying is that
Carrie needs to
To do a counter documentary about how to shave
FML cannibalized we are right now
But we don't have the great music by the great strings
Yeah it's true we could use
Kevin Morris operating Miss Cleo style psychic hotline
80 possibly stealthily using his radio show to promote
People who offer services
Transfer money on it
Right foot at least he's not running around acting like
He can contact otherworldly entity
I'm self
I mean if this guy
Make a documentary exposing
Lies of Captain Mark Richards
I care so much about me
The integrity
Who's serious-minded evidence
Bass researchers in the
Community
To be the bearer of obvious news
Cool group notice the one
Okay I watch the number of is channeling videos
Milltown
No
No no I don't care what are you asking me
I watched a number of these Channel
And all he's doing is talking with his little bit and appearing slightly
It has the feeling of you know how you like if you watch her band the lead guitarist make that pain look while the top solo
He looks a lot like that
In the first channeling session release the entities that were speaking
Particularly interested in
Kind of bragging about Kevin
Straddling
Mobility strange
We come to you
As many
The gift
Of Kevin
Is the gif
To be able to
Channel
Multiple
Entities
Being
Sorry I should have written this
And that is
Approved
In this special
Time on planet Earth right now
He doesn't need to
To change his voice
Different way
Is him saying I can't do characters
Bailey's l.ron Hubbard
I wrote this to myself of myself rescue with different
Are not done bragging through
Apparently
This is an agreement we have with him
On a deeper level
At a time
Beyond
Now
Beyond the universe
The place
Welcome to
Is
No
Quickest there Kevin
Something pretty weird about these sorts
The people get into this
Kind of thing they just go on and on about how bad that
Ego is got a free yourself from that go
Through them
Really seem like they just want to stroke their egos strange kind of goes on in this next clip
We are most grateful
For him
Agreeing
To take us
And himself
On this
Courageous Journey
It is only to spend
A few months
For him
No
This truth about himself
And Vista
On a paw now
Fenugreek powder
Out of time Beyond now
When it was agreed upon
Thought this would
Come this
Gift would be known
He could have said no.
To the skiff
He could have walked away but
Sure sounds like
He understood are the deepest
Odyssey School
The importance
Of the work
That needs to be undertaken now
At this
As we said
Special time
Planet
Yeah
C unit
I really think of it as actual other entities
He's speaking. Would not have that kind of apart
It's Channel
Interviews
3 seconds
Bullshitz crazy bulk
The truth
Is
Just
Having
Flatout Vols to do this
Absolutely
Crazy
Brash
It's almost like to have
A level of
Confidence that is all
Magic
I assume that he's not reading this
Is rocking back and forth
Extemporaneously
Without
He does smirk
Got a couple point
Well I mean it's interesting things to that like a channel and kind of his
The built-in
Self-defense
Genius
Map to save the world
Did I just do that
In the middle of it
But there's the built
Disrupt the Stream
There's all these little things that are built in order to like
Defend yourself from it ever really being verified
All this s***
Interesting is that this is one of those situations where
Is almost like
It helps
Trying really hard
If you want it
Go wash them
They're crazy
So you might notice
You've known about these gifts perfume
Obviously
What he was
A few months ago
What make you think about that a couple months ago
It's possibly unrelated but
In August 24th
5 months before this
Kevin started to make a ton of videos about Edgar Cayce
From August to the end of that year 19th
31 videos he posted on his YouTube channel
Knox
We're about Edgar Cayce
Put some
His existed
Regularly posting videos about New Age
Spiritualist
And yet released exactly
0 videos about Edgar Cayce
Until then
Clearly the topic was a bit of a new obsession
And for him
Edgar Cayce is a guy was largely
Considered to be one of the founders of the new age
He was a real weirdo from the early 1900's who would Channel higher-level entities while he was pretending to be asleep
They pretend not to have any idea what he said once he woke up
Important is clear everyone started writing down every
He said while he was pretending
Be asleep as become
He's called The Sleeping Prophet
I will get to it
We could spend all day
We could spend all day going over Casey's nonsense
Complete bulshit prophecy
But he made that you give you aside like
He claimed it Atlantis has been destroyed by a death ray
The US would ReDiscover that death rate
He also prophesied that Atlantis would rise from the ocean
68 or 19
YouTube
The California would fall into the ocean sometime in the 1960s
That didn't didn't
Escape from l.a. I remember
You famously predicted that 1933 would quote
Be a good here
19:33 is largely remembered as the year that Hitler became 10
And Nazism started to go while there's also
Year of the Great Depression with unemployment
Most metrics definition of NADA Goodyear
He prophesied literal Armageddon
He predicted the Christianity would become the dominant religion in China by nineteen
68 almost there or wrong 2011
China was 2.6% Christian
Percent does not exist in a good relationship
Cheap with the oppressive government
This list could go on and on and on the horrible medical advice
But he would give out.
In fairness
Pretty much everybody was
Totally but that's one
Study people who cheat.
Be stuck in the time frame of the understanding and conventional wisdom of whatever time. The person who's Chan
Materialism
Where people are from
The same
Group or whatever at the gift
It's almost as if
Weird that
In Scientology they looked a lot like
B-52 bomber
They should look like a B-52
Schneider
So what's important here is that in August 2014
Kevin Moore started
Videos about Edgar Cayce
Interviewing people about him
Is that a couple months later he coincidentally
Discovered
And he uses a talk to Ed
Just For Humanity that only
But it's not like you things are connected or
Anyting that's just me
Two separate things
Pretending they're related
I might be
Or I might have watched a ton of his channeling videos
And heard him say this
Just
Shooting in
To this party
Cool
I have left on this
Sonic before
I bet I know who
A long time ago
I have left the foundation
August planets
How long to
Time ago
Some of you would have known me
Casey
Etiquette
And I am one of the guys
True Cafe
I don't normally come through
So this
I've been there with him before his books
And I also comes through
I'm Different situation
But just a pop in to say hello
Just dropped in to say hello guys I'm traveling
A basin
This one is like
This
Kevin the f****** I don't usually do this
So they're really credible credibility
Incredibly fascinating
Like this
Disease with
Spreads
Jerusalem syndrome
Some people go to Jerusalem
And they end up thinking that they're G
That's right it's just something it's a phenomenon that happens
Exactly why
People who get who are they kind of
Unhinged
And maybe a little bit ambitious and get a little of it called the new age
A little bit
It stopped and then they started
You've got this Kevin Moore who's
Pretending that he has
Edgar Cayce
He talkin through him Wilcox
His mate
Career off saying that
He's the reincarnation
Of entertainment
It's just this
Frequent Worthy's
Con artist
Use him
In order to reinforce the
Legitimacy
It is almost like
It is it is almost like they are being conned from Beyond
The grave
There is like
Like metaphysical thing going on here
I would not
Doubt
That it is aggravating fuckboy
Bright that goes would be conning people left
So
In the same way
Flattered
So maybe is
AKC is f***
That black man you're so great I love it
Europe the best
So good at it
This dude is a great a scam
His history shows a real pattern new-age beliefs
Spiritualism as a business
Model
He runs a psychic hotline
He's tried to establish himself as a super important
Coming from Edgar Cayce
As well as other less recognizable he named entity
When it suited his purpose he's been perfectly willing
Sunquest
Ginobli platform
Cassidy
And allowed them to spread misinformation about Mark Richard
Even going out of his way to help them.
Like from the criticism
And now that's all chain
Needs a heroic crusader
Stop for fact-based investigators in the new wage world and expose Mark Joann
I'm sure you can
See how this feels like it's
Sweet bulshit
His motivation
Can't be that he's offended by what they're saying
Because he's been apart of saying literally the same
Thanks
He can't be interested in defending rigorously
Play research tan
In fact
Communities
Because Mark Richards being a c
Has exactly as much proof attached to it as him channeling Edgar
Perkasie
Something is up here and I think I might have
That we stumbled onto a
Clue as to what it is
Obviously I can't prove any
But I have a bit of Suspicion
Kevin Morris
Who is not making
Documentary
Out of a concern for the
Nor even outages
Sincere desire
Wheelie insane and awesome story of Margaret
Is he
Making
He has
As best I can
I believe
When Kevin interviewed rash
The psychic hotline
Employee who can talk to Jesus
He brings up a particular Lament
That I found variant
I mean obviously
The Haunting about this
When I say hi
Of myself
With with
Amazing guest
To self coming
What icon
Heart-wrenching
That... The mainstream
Shows
Alright
Audience driving
An honest
To shame because
I think Pizza
People already
So
Tennessee in expression
Deserved
3 bigger than I am
The show
I think I'm pretty great
My later channeling work
Kevin Morris YouTube channel his primary means of
Distributing is material has 63,000
Subscribers
Is nothing to sneeze at
Project
Escribers almost four times
Evans audience
Get a few thousand of them like an interview about robots
3 weeks ago
Lisa
Is 20 / 30
2000 Vue
Well over the average on
His channel
Drives traffic
Project Camelot is a larger aunt
Get a bigger thing
Kevin recently did an Indiegogo campaign to make a documentary about how channelers are totally real
Which
Cross purposes for someone who runs
Psychic hotline documentary feel like it's a bit of an extended commercial but whatever
In the in the time of the campaign was active
Eclipse
$15,000
Ending up with just a little bit over 27
10000.
But what I find
Suspicious
Is the fist total came from only 80
You to donors
Which is an average of about 304
There are red flags all over this crowdfunding
The campaign but I won't bore you with the number
I did some weird map
Just does not make sense
Is all kinds of people
Claim Rewards
A prizes or anything
Leads me to believe that
Yeah I'm Lois tears $25
So there's probably a lot of them who were
Baloch
So we have probably 80 below $25.
29 prizes
Out of those
People that were actually claimed
Shrek
There's a lot of reason
Do you have
Some suspicion
About what's going on there
But no matter what
Even if everything is above board
Who wanted to make his documentary
Compare that to carries failed Indiegogo from 2015
Where she was trying to raise
Where's the starter Network
That was shooting for the
O2pur Huber
She had 189 people donate over twice
Also running a GoFundMe campaign
To get a two documentaries made Mark Richards one and what about you
He also wants to launch the international spirit
Campaign on GoFundMe
His only raised 527 lb
From 9th
Teen donors
I'm not trying to
Just the cabin is getting dark money
I'm suggesting that it looks very possible that the donations.
Indiegogo campaign
Came from a
Sponsor
Most likely Ozark Mountain publisher
A new age book distributor the cabin is acknowledged as a sponsor regularly in the past
Andrew runs ads on his show
It seems entirely possible that you launched
Crowdfunding for his documentary
No one was interested
His sponsor stepped in to create the
I have a strong suspicion the Kevin Moore is not motivated by preserving
Everything I've seen gives me these
Strong indication that are much more likely
Explanation for all of this
Is the Kevin wants to take over Carrie cast
The share of the new age bulshit Market
Dispute
Equivalent of a situation where a mobster is extort
Bring the store owner
Sure you got rid of the mobster extorting to store owner but you only did that so
So you could pray on that storeowner you
Yourself
Yeah
At least that's the sense I get
A British guy
An exorbitantly priced psychic hotline for the better part of it
Really cares about misinformation being spread
Misinformation
Possible
You just got to decide for yourself
I am
Dead center
50 on one side 15 on the other side.
I feel like
But one of them that I come away from all this with
Is
Like
Get the f*** out of
Get the f*** out of here
Wiqui
Are the ones
Marriage status a****** at least we're better than that
Like to laugh at Carrie and enjoy and have fun and then whatever she says
Things that are like
But there's no
This is such b******* for one reason one reason
Very idea of what
He's doing it so stupid
Because
There's no way that you're going to bake this documentary about Mark Richard
Like people are black
Oh my God
Project Camelot
We are going to go in
Be smart now
You're not going
How to turn people in
Into like
People who actually read book
Make a vacuum in their life
Whatever Guru vacuum is there a yeah
Did enough of them will come over to you it'll fill that Gap
Bummer
Fascinated by like
You know it's just bringing those channeling videos
Into my life
Thank you I mean if you don't look into any of this stuff that I like I didn't
Initially you just be this documentary for this trailer for The
Phuc yea
You run the very serious risk of endorse
Someone because you like the idea of this documentary instead of looking at like
What's going on here
Been realizing you runs a psycho
Hotline
Channel Lent
Kathy's
He's just as bad if not worse
I think he's absolutely worse than carry at least for that bike channelling hotline
$1 an hour
Minimum
Hotline
He's crazy
Like that
That to me is is funneling
Your audience
Towards something
So much more destructive
Then just a stupid idea that carry
Evan maybe her hilarious album
He can't possibly make that much
I assume
Knox
Possibly make that
I don't know but
It doesn't matter to me
If if
He doesn't make a lot of money off it's not for lack of trying and it's not anything
She's not doing what you doing
Exact
To be a big pile of s*** making a
Defrauding people with psychic
Small business owners life
Your do it right now he's an entrepreneur
He's trying to build something from the ground up
I mean
Your mouth but
What's a cardigan
Yeah course
I mean come on
Just anybody
God those channeling videos
I don't I wouldn't have wanted to place so long
I swear
Even if
Was proven
Factually correct
That he was Channel
I'd still be out on that
F*** that
Videos
Justin
Channeling
Do you
Feel similarly weirdly defensive
About
Carrie was real mad
In that clip of the interview that you played with
Her and him whenever
Just brought up
The fact that
Mark Richards murder somebody
And she's just cut about a map
She's our friend
This is the difference
Listening 2 hours upon hours upon hours of
And then me just hearing what you showing I don't develop the same emotional
Okay that's fine and I don't actually have that much
I know your feelings
But I do feel protective
A little bit
Much more
Craft
Kevin
Much more malice
On his part
Like what
To do with this
Stuff
Doesn't strike me as
Positive
And he also seems like he's probably a lot more enterprising and a lot more
Yeah he is
Probably
Got into the Heights
Ever get to
She made a
Like a pilot for a
2 videos
Everything glitches all the time
The dogs bark in the background as much as I do
You're worried about it
I don't necessarily even think that it's innocent don't put that word in my
Impotent
If you act like it's
Fiction spiral out of control that much further
I do think he
He could I think he
He could
Videos out of
Purcell f******
Stuff like that
Presumptuous on the other mobile
Someone who
Like put multiple videos
Themselves
I don't know
What you're capable of
Right
The other hand
He seems most likely to overreach and then
Project Camelot
Not going to dental caries mounting a defense
You know I don't think no matter what
That's the other thing
Yeah that's the other thing about why this is f****** stupid
If you intend to show
Misinformation parts of the
Space Community or whatever
What the f*** are you doing this
Quite honestly you're going to make this documentary as everyone is going to be operative
Defenses again
Kind of truth-telling
The end result
That that being presented as his motive
For this
Little suspicious
Yeah especially since
The people that
Finding out there
Isn't going to go hahaha
You got her
The feelings a little bit longer really know where the feeling
Come from
There is death mask
Look I don't know I made the ceiling today
It's not it's
It's not a defensive carry for her own sake
It's
It's a defense based on what
Anybody being the target
Something like this
I would probably be like this doesn't
Seem sincere
No matter what
I don't know it is always kind of funny the idea of like
Intersect battles
Community
External view would be like
One survived
If it's obviously project
There's much funnier territory there
I'll probably still watch a documentary but I've got a stream
Arthritis
Up to you but I needed
On Friday
With a new episode
Yeah
Thank you
Knowledge
You can also get a second
Say that they will give you investment advice
B Capital stock market
Space stock
You could
Do that or you could get like
Right now okay
Because what are the Giants.
Perfect idea for us
How would anyone ever confirm or deny the value going up or down complete control the narrative
I predict
Someone will eventually
Like that
Resource
Futures in like asteroids
Dab asteroids
Futures
Anyway we have Twitter
Betrayed
What else do we do
And many other podcast
We are told
I got to say Jordan
What are you got to say
I have to say what
The archaeologist
Feline space
Contessa
Never killed anybody
Tell you that
Spirit resonates that she has never killed anybody
Cat alien
Innate
Contribute
To the totality
Information of the universe and I respect
But she's never killed any
Probably has
I love your work