Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages
And talk a little bit about Alex Jordan Jordan
You got two new pots tell me about him
You know I've got a little bit of a green Soma lately
God damn my cat is apparently trying to eat them
Now on my windowsill anyway my point is just to apartment that I have
Is a pretty nice windowsill with a lot of good amount of light
This provided
Ono throw something
Okay
She's down
The problem is
Experienced was me freaking out that Selene is going to eat
B flat
Before they've come to growth
How do I am grown tomatoes
Is lettuce
Flowers
Some peppers and
Process you live and you learn I've never really grown
Play indoors
In those sort of like
Germinating
Wade
And I was having a lot of progress with them
Play some over a lot of them were clearly dead already
Top of them looks okay
Can take with me into the next
Grow some plants
Boring as
Really the Highlight was the sole mean
Learning a lot about
Jordan
To be at the end of a week
Spinach
Sorry I just don't know I'm still struggling with whether or not I should have thrown these scissors at my cat
For the record
Thought about it
Richmond
Maybe more fun but also still a lot
Then we come to the end of the week here and I wanted to
To jump back in
To 2013
Defecation
Who's up to
In the aftermath
According to reporting on it
And I got way more than I could have ever bargain
But first
I need to give a shout out
Do some people who have joined up
Supporting the show
So first
Glenmuir now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Glenn
??
Of all of the wrong
I'm a policy
9 gal chairs
Next
Goofy cat
Somebody donate.
Does an elevated level
Appreciate it very much
So G
Pran
Why and
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
Black
Jesus Christ
I guess so much Brandon with Ally if you're out there listening
You would like sports
We would appreciate it
Help me buy more plants
My cat can
Friday I was worried about it
Yeah because you never know how shirts are going to come out
They look pretty good
Concerned background black
It's underneath
Vti
The Note 8
Watch the black
On the shirt but it looks great
T-shirt store International hour liquor
You know you're overseas
Could not do that
Will get that update
What happened on our last episode
I remember April
January January
What month are we in January 10th
2/13 2013
And Alex is really obsessed
With the idea that only
Gas
It was the Obama phone made
Today we're going over January 14th
Davey Obama Phone Lady showed up
Infamy
Yep into here's narcotic
Text Rob from Today Show
Healthways
00:00
Oh no oh no
Alex
She's talking about how like
He didn't even say it was
I don't want to
Jinx it by saying who it was lest something the fall through
Right
So Alex
Open
This show
Exact same mood
Hump
3 hours
We do not have any
This is going to be
You might have recognized in essential problem with
Beginning of this episode
And that is what Alex
Seemed to know her name at all
Here is another clip where he just refers to her as the Obama Phone Lady
And I and I want to go home and see them tonight
I'll have my wife come meet us for dinner
Husband
What's a cigarette
Quest
What is the Obama phone
Goodbye
He knows enough
You knows what she stands for in the
Conservative media
Alex
That the Obama Phone Lady
Ended up
Are they
What's there
$5,000 bounty
So he paid
$5,000 for one of his listeners to go
To fly her to Texas
He's in the hole for this
How do you know how to get ahold of no one
Had her name
I bet she was just someone who appeared in a f****** viral video
Alex is like really trying to do the email address
Do you have a computer
You wouldn't have been able to get ahold of her except by some buddy on the ground and finding her
Alex has to give that guy
And that's such a bummer
Riot
Yeah
Yeah but
Unfortunately it doesn't
Fuel that great
Once she's there
She's a lady
Her present
A little bit
Diamond cufflinks on
Short sleeve shirt that's not respectful enough
That's all I had back there my wardrobe I sent stuff way to be clean
She coming
He's a character
I'm not respectful enough and yet he still had the Obama phone
Are not
This is the beginning of the Falcons
Maybe half an hour 40
Alex
I can't believe I deserve to be around her really do is the most
I have ever met in my life
It is
So Jordan in order to fully understand the context around which the Obama
My phone video
Which
Peters
It existed in package
When it was released
It's important to remember a couple of things
First
The video was posted and went viral about a month before the 2012 election
What was
With each passing day
His campaign was in
Need of an October
Prize
Becoming
In fact the opposite
Had come
On September 17th 2012
The series of tapes of Rodney's $50,000 a plate private dinner
I do large portion of the response to them where is that Rodney gets
Straight up f***** himself over
Out-of-touch fairly resentful rich
Prick speaking
Freely because he knows he's surrounded by
People who are the same
People ran with internal
Reporting was this
All right there 47% who are with him
You're dependent on the government who believe their victim
I'm super leave the government has a responsibility to care for them
Who believe that they are entitled to healthcare
The food to housing
Do you name it
That's entitled
And the government
Should give it to them
He goes on to say quote my job is not to worry about those
After a lackluster Republican National Convention
Considerable bump in his numbers
Attacking Obama
And focus on what
We could do if you
He was elected
Then almost immediately this tape comes out to the surface of him telling a roomful of multi-millionaires
Almost half of the country are people
He's not supposed to
Care about as president
This is a huge crisis
If you recall
It looked bad
Because this was cuz it was bad
Because that whole thing was so insane
People have largely forgotten also said this
In that video about his own wife
Quotes we use and sparingly right now so people don't
Get tired of her
Like a real guy
F****** car
And drove
And then try to get a job
Drop
How is How is
Of your car driveway and then America's just like this
Did you laugh about it
So Romney's campaign
And the perception
Complete assholes
Slightly richer with starting
Come up with something
Compelling
And what about a week later
What are YouTuber named
The real freedom
Posted a 44-second video of Michelle dowry
Who is now known as the Obama phone
Yelling about how Obama gave her a phone
And he should.
President
Even more
Here is the
Complete audio of that
Obama phone
How to give you a phone
Okay what's wrong with Romney again
Obama phone
People bombing president
You know
Give me the phone give you a phone
I think it's over
Repeat
I think the video might be shorter than 24
I think that he's just staying
So if
The problem was that Ronnie's face
Have been attached to the idea that 47% of the
Population was a bunch of
Freeloading
Inconsequential
The natural solution to that was to make someone else's face
Is living proof that Romney was right
And if this person
Percent she's a Welfare Queen
Bingo
Real 327
76 heads
Scribers on YouTube
But that didn't really matter
His video was posted on
September 26th
YouTube
And the very next day
The video was the top link on The Drudge
But the headline
He gave me a free
Free phone
Pretty much make careers off just reading drudge headlines
Griffin Arthur
The message was clear
As conservative commentators were quick to
This viral video 2
2 defense of Romney
These horrible statement
It was very clear that this
They existed in of opposition
Into each other
They pushed the idea that this woman
Was the face of the 47% that Romney was criticized
She was proof that Romney was right
And the attacks against Uber really just
The cover-up
It's important to remember that this video went viral for to Ruiz
2 Reasons
1 people laughing
Many of whom were doing
As expressed by this poster on Stormfront
First I thought this was a joke but it's real
Racial inferiority on
A lot of people just thought the video was funny in an absurd way
Sure
I believe that there are people who thought this is funny
18 Andres
Large portion of people who thought the video was funny
Thought it was funny because how closely it mirrored there races
Stereotype
Oh yeah
The other reason why this got really popular
Was that there was a coordinated
Media blitz
To push this video in an attempt to help the Romney
This was be bandaged
To stop the bleeding from the fundraiser videos
Entire media operating
Operation
Appears to have been in like Alexa
Yes
There is there is a pipeline
Stop the bleeding
So this was pushed the grass
It was top links on drudge it immediately became the Boogie
He-Man of conservative top talk radio
The video and audio reply
Play all news radio shows
Infinger wagon
About the entitlements
How this woman
Is proof that there and Randy and bulshit was right all along
The second group of P
People these people were using it as a bandage
Stop the bleeding in the Romney campaign
We're using the video for political points
Hey wants Romney lost
They didn't talk about the Obama Phone Lady wants their purpose
They were using her for was gone
I'm sure she'll be brought back up and passing when the midterm come along
But looking back at the coverage of the story it's clear that it
This is in the right-wing media just as a Hail Mary to try and help Romney
When you see something like this
Where's story of the media is so cord
For such a specific
The kind of speaks volumes when a certain outlier continues to
Cover that story where its progenitors
I've left it in the dark
Alex Jones interview lady on January 14th
Why do while after the election
If you if you get ahold of the Obama Phone Lady
You don't turn down that call
It fixed up
Contract says imma give you $5,000 for
Her before the election
Does kinda sound right now just from the first
Opening B
The fact that he does
And did not bother to learn it
Prior to having her I think he knows it but he doesn't
Well I think also it could be one of those things
Her name is Michelle in
Obama's wife is named Michelle
I'm guessing himself while he's on are like the warmest color
Obama's wife
Something like that look like an a******
I don't know I think he's probably not
Spend five grand
Strawberry farm
Most of the right-wing used her
Okay
The coverage of the Obama Phone Lady video with full effect
And I think the people were right to make this jar
I would like the Atlantic Ram pieces about how racist
Everyone's
Responsive
Lydia was
Distinction that the video itself is
Nor is the person who recorded it
Posted it
They assert that quote the racism comes when drugs Rush
Do a mental calculation
Enough people would just be this video they would support run
Because it plays on the same races
Stereotypes that are usually trotted out this
The article in the Atlantic goes on to say quote
The point of the video and the reason drudgen Limbaugh hyped it is to say
This is what Obama voters look like
Poor stupid after your money
The video subject wasn't picked up because she happens
To be black
She was picked up because she
He is black
Lee Atwater strategist for Ronald Reagan and George h.w. Bush
Explain how will this work
Back in 1981
Better to talk about cutting taxes and fussing
Because it's quote a hell of a lot more abstract than Edward Edward
And isn't the same as another video
Long after I ate clearly
Serve its intended purpose
Of driving people to Rob
Alex I'm not saying
The n-word n-word part
Is Alex's
Intended purpose of this is an Obama supporter
This is what they look like
Is that so
His goal is to use her as a architect
Yeah, supporter
Comes out
He reads off teleprompters and he looks really
Really smart
Makino's things
This is what they're really like is that what he's doing is it's almost like
Create
A straw man
And then it was brought to life
In the form of
Part of why Alex Hester
To pretend he's so excited
To see her at such a
Celebrity
He has to walk this really fine line
Of like overdoing it because if he doesn't
You just going to yell at her
Yes
Mexico
Artificial respect
In order to safeguard himself from very relaxation
That you're having your on your show for nefarious reason
He's excited as a way of hiding
Text Alex talk about how he's going to hire
I'll just be honest with you here
Obama Phone Lady
I am to try to
Okay that's a little Patron
Need to schedule
Get into comedy
It's a good thing
Obama was re-elected
Otherwise she might not have a phone with which for him to
Spoiler alert
She wouldn't
One of his
Introducing
Talkin about her
But you should get into comedy
2 into voiceover work
Express
Natural
I don't have it
Okay
I thought about how stupid messed up
She could get buck
October
You see all these things were like people who are on reality shows and stuff headlining clubs
Some sets
Somewhere but it wouldn't work
Amy Schumer
Started doing that
Before she
Last Comic Standing
Is a stand-up show
The reality show that is based on
Temptation Island
I don't know
Be great on Temptations
Whatever
My point is this
Did Alex Azar
Hilarious
Trend it's going throughout day like I don't really
I don't really care about any of this stuff
I'm just Alex being stupid
Important
Consider how he
He's rapping
What's up
Because it's like
Realtor
Anyone
Anyone who's ever listened to your show doesn't think
This is a weird Alex
What are you doing Alex
It's the
He's going over the top in order to Wells
Because
It's building her up with the also added
Piece of
Patronizing
Are you talking about
The educator one
And that comes up in the
Help somebody
We can probably try to help
Situation going on but it's not
Cuz it's not better
You can't
Help
Schoolboy
Message of that movie
A lot of messages
Voicemail joke
Play app
How do you get to a small-time, club
Beretta Cougar
So it's probably important
For me to know that there's no such
Outside of what
Meme creator
What's behind this because there is a little bit of reality
I'd like to generously call this
Understand
How is the idea
These programs
The help people with low income
At the phone
Easy telephones are considered a utility
That's such the government has what's known as quote a universal service
Requirements for them
This is laid out the communications Act of 90
T-34 which reason that access to wire and radio
Where is Central Perk
Of living in B vent modern
Society
Should be offered access
The programs that are sprung out of this
Later all centered around the under
Understanding
Access to a phone
Is Knotts
Some kind of watch
It's pretty much a necessity
3 in today's world
Connect America fund
Was established to promote connectivity to rural community
Then in 1984 the lifeline program was started by Zen
Reagan
Which a.m.
To quote ensure that all Americans have the opportunity
Insecurities that phone service brings
Included being able to connect
Two jobs family an
MC services
There's an essential piece
Love to ignore
And that is ultimately cost Society more to deprive people of access to phones than it would to subsidize
And the only real argument against
The program like this is
Is rooted in cruelty
And appeals that quote people like this
Just don't deserve
And also it was
They also love to ignore
1996 Honda President Clinton
Program was redesigned
The people who qualified for the benefits
For a cell phone
Crazy
That's just a modernization of the program
Psychological
The program doesn't give out free phone
Feisty
Myth
It's set up to cover monthly discounts on phone service
The free phones that may or may not be giving out or giving it to
Discretion of the cell phone
Provider
That company may offer a free phone as an incentive
But that's not the government's doing
The idea of giving out phone doesn't
Entirely up to
These companies
Also the money for the program doesn't come
Comfort up from packs
Husband
That goes
Most people's phone bill
Include the small fee to go to the universal service
And this is where the money for the
Do USF is used to make sure the girl communities are able to call the fire department
And some of that money also goes
How to make sure that
Just because you're poor
That doesn't mean you can't
Also called the fire department
Some hardcore
Conservative makeup
Complain that
Pay a dollar and their bills
The government should
Force them to and I have great news
The government is
Forcing them to
Their phone company
Cfcc requires Telecommunications
Companies to pay into the universal
Full-service Spa
But it's up to the individual companies
Decide whether they
Pass along those
Sister their customer
So is your package come up into this be
This phone
Don't be mad at the recipient
Access to phones don't be mad at the governor
Phone provider for making you pay their fair share
They wanted for it that's
The company's Troy
They have to pay
To this Market that is a utility it's just part of how the
System works well there's another while I was working with the hearing impaired entire
Series of programs set up to get
That will
UniverSoul Circus
You don't have to pay for those
It is all taken care of
No it's
Do you want the company to have to pay
Or do you want them
To charge
You for it
I think that's probably the only real conversation here your phone bill
Are you mad enough about it
I mean I think a company should pay but I also don't mind that I'm charged
That's where I'm at
I would like the company to Japan
On it it's
Seems like it's bear respond
Possibility I also recognized
Great help
2 bucks a month on my bill
For this until someone point
Makes them mad about
People get mad about it
Do people like Rush Limbaugh make people mad about it
Fictionalized version
Of the program itself
They're using propaganda to make you mad about something
Let's go back even further when
We didn't even have subsidized
Right
Not on fire how much more money that cost ever
To pay for it well if you don't have a phone.
How are you going to pay for it
A job if they can't call you back
Right you know
Two-cycle Vape
This Is War
Attempt to disrupt the cycle of
Of inability
And I don't I don't
Theory
If there are abuses within the system and stuff like that then that's
Coupon greater regulation
To sort out or greater oversight of the program
Long is the program
Scores
Created
New Challenger
Programming
Not all of it
But
That's not a result of
Obama
Or anything like that
I find it acceptable to be
They're calling the coverage
Of the Obama Phone Lady in this whole thing
Is it the coverage doesn't
Discuss the reality of the program like we've been discussing
Yeah it just seems like they don't care about the reality
People went
About this
People like Russian Alex
Just accept the false reality that this woman is God video
Which state uses
They aren't using the video is an opportunity to argue against
The lifeline program
In fact
The name of the program where the Universal Services
Respond come up in any of the coverage I've seen
Explain
Soar program
Parents that they want to
Obama is the f****** phone
Arguing
People like Alex videos
Send a f*****-up message
Basically this is what we're up
This is the true face of an Obama
Supporter
Stroke
The Flash out their coverage
They're basically attempting to log modern
Is you sucked out almost immediately
As the Atlantic article about this
Points out quote
The video wasn't on drugs because drudges advocated getting rid of the probe
It's racist because the point is
Portray poor black people is stupid and lazy
If that's what it comes down to
That's what Alex
Need
To present on this show
Within the con
Text of
And I'm having her here too
To help her
Which is
Probably even worse
Especially considering even the people pushing this race
Has me mad already given up
Yeah by this point Alex's
Continuing it on
Well past its expiration
Alex
Talks for a long time
I guess
Talking about night
You remember the quote from the book about
Being able to overthrow the party
I just like it whenever Alec
What's brings up one
Books that he believes are real
Then he accidentally
Completely misinterpret something
So let's see if you can pick out what's wrong
First the song Choices
Only there in those swarming
Disregarded message
Population of Oceania
Did you pick out what the major glaring problem there is
Well
Seems like that
Support for
Oceania is not the United States
England
It's also South America is also Australia
Serie A 1984
The idea that he's presenting it as
Just the United States
Oceania does what he think
Wholesale discount
I don't know
Half of the rest of the world
I don't know I don't trust the rest of yours
If that's what you're taking away from this
I mean I would give him the benefit of the doubt
There because I would
Doubt
Mention well because outside 1984 Oceania
Lights to
Australia
The game of Risk
The word has a greater context
Anyway I was lying he's not done talking
About the Obamas
Some of the ideas that I was breaking up
In my inter
Obama phone
That's her first name
Michelle
We have a tide
An hour from now we can also have some of your questions
Austin Texas
My argument
This is what they're all like
So Alex said that she's going to be on in an hour
She shows up
Barges into the stew
Obama Phone Lady
I know by my phone lady
Represent Nom Alex Jones here today
Walmart
Oh boy
To be here agent
I don't know
She doesn't
Studio immediately
She's hanging out like in the booth
Something like that
At a certain point Alex just yells at them like a
Not
Weird
To open this
Do you have her in the other room
Celebrities
Present
He does get into some other news
Who asked about
Sandy Hooks.
And Alex respond
F***
Next clip this caller asks
About the
Who was
The people have described as being like an actor
Now
Mike down man
Listen to this response that Alex gives him
But what I wanted to talk about was Sandy Hook
Somebody that believes that there's some fishing it's there and I think through a couple things I'm not sure if you've seen all these
Have you seen the video where the little girl's father
Camera
So he's
What he said about
It's a clear indication
He knows
What's up
Consistent to ascertain
Because the furthest he's gone is sort of endorsing
Obispo
Professor Florida University
Professor who's advocating
They're all actors
I don't know how
Respond
Like this you know I am not going to
Say
It still tracks with the idea even if he's advocating For What the
Professor say
Because the professor saying
It's dumb people were at
This guy isn't
Terrifying is that Alex is keenly aware of the ideas it
You're in heavy stuff
Stressful
People respondents
Surprising
Sometimes there's nothing suspicious about the idea that this guy
May have nervously been laughing
Before he got on camera
Like that's really scary cuz if you have that awareness
It's the fact that he does
Later make it something
Suspicious
Means that he knows
Yeah fool well that he's lying
Easy little bit giddy he's acting like a little bit like a real person
I consider that as a possibility
Need the tempers language cuz Obama Phone Lady is listening and if it was all fake
Maybe that would
Or something like that
About that is possibility but
I don't have enough evidence
It's the back that up it's just weird
Good mood
Color does not like that
Response
You keep pushing
Moreover that side of like
I'm not going down this road
Which is even worse
One thing that's weird about him is that his daughter
The end of the day she had a Facebook page
That one is already looking looking for money
It seems kind of odd that
So quickly
What
Editorial position
Very severely
I think he's going to flip his script
Yeah
Water
Pretty much the entirety of the information
Because Obama Phone Lady is going to come in just Duty go and they talked almost the
Higher
It's a very long interview
Really boring
Will explain what happened
But a lot of it is just Alex
Badgering
Is this Alex
Info on thirty-year-old suing his parents to stay in their house mode
Get to that
Yes this is Alex and Mike rotundo imma give you $3,000
A pep talk
Impulse that he has
Definitely has more of a racial
Where is Rotonda
I feel
Galaxy Express in the building
Weirded out by this whole thing
What is happening
She's awesome
Absolutely awesome
I just did
It's over flattering
It's it's manipulative
Reliving his Pretty Woman
Or whatever
Don't I don't think that
Play Eye of the Tiger whenever she
She comes in
The tiger and then gets really defensive
Even though
Cornea
There's so much to love about that clip
At the beginning of it you can tell that he think
The chorus is coming another verse
It goes to the First Defense
You here where you roll the windows down in love it
The Obama Phone Lady she showed up yet
She has the eye of the tiger
You're on the air you want to talk about
Just got everything that was on at 2 a.m. while you were driving and just
Just that clip you be like
Is a good night live
College radio
It's so f****** silly
Coaster parody
Lady comes in
You know that's all good and well
This is the first step that I want to play as their interaction
Is one where I believe that they both keenly are aware
That there's more to this program than the idea that Obama is giving
People phone
They're aware of it but they refused
To operate with that awareness
If you understand
Okay. Kind of aware that it's a racist
Yeah
Okay
I have seen
Last year win
Some things have
I know you really didn't
Once I
They show me that
Ask for when Obama
It was it was Obama phone
No but you want to present it at
Because you can talk about the idea that cell phones were included in
You plan on the click because you don't want to make the
A bipartisan say it was started under your conservative god king Ronald Reagan
You want to make it look like it's only Democrat
Did is the Democrats are giving you free
To keep you on the plantation because they hate you and all this.
If you incorporate
The greater reality of it that argument
Completely falls apart and you can't do this propaganda
She is here as a tool
For Alex to use
Any
I mean I'll be honest
Yeah well it's pretty bad
But
For most of the time Alex is just trying to get her to hate Obama
Okay is just going on and on
Don't you know
He uses drones
Okay alright if I had Baloch sitting down right
You know all this
The same argument
For someone to
Throw in his face now
So it just
It just feels like I'm trying
To get her to not like Obama
He convened brag about getting the Obama Phone Lady do not like Obama
And it's annoying
Is a front man for some very dangerous
Part of the New World Order
There's a lot of that there's a lot of Alex just like a lot of his normal talking points
These are also trying to be like the Democrats hate you because you're black
This clip
Encapsulation of that especially because of How It Ends
And I want you to know
To put you Six Feet Under
To kill black people
Alright
That was longer than I thought
Kill all the blacks
Rhoda commercial and you
You can just have the last
Forward no matter what
F****** insane
Democratic party wants to kill you all right time to go to break but I'll prowl
I got a story
Well I guess you'll open with that when we come back to break right
Or come back from Moana bathtub
Is interesting
Michelle's phone keeps ringing
Episode
Which Alex would never put up with from anybody else
Needs visitors
The present
Right there
I can't talk to you
So you wouldn't allow he wouldn't allow that
That's absurd
Present
Fairing
While the same time trying to attack her
With all of his propaganda
In order for the outcome that he wants
The outcome but he wants here is present is bad
To blindly and
Stupidly
Was out there
Screaming in a Romney rally that Obama was going to give us phones and all that
I have managed
To show her the light and the truth
Write in the same way that like Mike Rotondo is embarrassing thirty-year-old who suing the parents
Taking them out of the house
Alex Warren
The end result of that to be like
You've got him on his feet I got him in this apartment because I am able to
For you
By using my principles and applying them to you
Such a valuable
For him from
Propaganda is willing to put up with
Her phone going off multiple times throughout the interview
He's willing to pretend
He's the biggest celebrity ever to butter her up with flattery
To make her not
Fuel on guard about the idea that he's just
Just bummed
Stupid ideas
And knowings it like okay I'm going to stay that Margaret Sanger wants
Kill all black people you don't know anything about this
And I know you're not going to look it up
Like manipulative Fox
Used when they go on Rogan
Show
The maximum amount of research that anybody can do without the program is a Google search
Appearance of something little
Call Bob on Google
Your arguments going to fly
And that's what Alex ends up
Because he ends up talking
Think about how like Obama promised there wouldn't be any new texts
Urbino taxes
And there are tax
So you like one of his interns
Those things
Shows it to her and then she's like wow
And because he's been beating her down throughout this
Entire episode
Once that receipt
She's like
Wow Mama. I'm not going to vote for him next time
That would be a possibility
I would also say that
Phone going off
During this interview
Is
A win for him
Keep saying Obama
Keep bringing up the very thing that
He wants everybody to
Associate
Yes and associate with
It does help
It does help but that's also why he's not behaving
The end where it gets
To put some of that is important because
To know even in the middle
In the middle
Where we're at now
She's not responding superweld
To Alex's
Apartment
Digicel
Because it's very aggressive and he hasn't
Lying
Sushi
Kind of like
Alright and Alex is interpreting that as like a
And we're Donaire but it really just seems
Like he's being a dick to her
She's trying to
Be polite
Come right back
Here
I just think that there's
Like there's a real strong feeling that
Protecting herself from
Cuz when they come back Alex wants to ask her about Gunn
Her feelings about God and later he indicates
Did they talked about it last night
Flown into town
Position already
And she knows that he's probably going to yell at her
If she answers the question
You can see how that plays out
Where do you stand on their arms
Have faith in God
Well
Tamia
Ensalada 92
Cool
Last night when they talked about it you probably got really Adam
Talking about guns
Going to go well
I don't want to answer your question
Because
What it could
End up with
Hey that's why she's cool
Is because
Whether it's on a
Like a conscious level or subconscious level
She has a sense
He's going to yell at her or there's going to be
She doesn't go the right
Path
The things are going to go bad
When you hear her
Receiving
These questions
You can hear the
Thoughts in her head just go
What possible
Good outcome could there be
Why does it matter what I think about God
I was in a f****** video
Exactly so I can stay home
And then he gets to yell
Right right I can even doesn't know what I'm talking about origin
Joke or something
Yeah
You could tell there's
The feeling of truck
There's no wind for her in that
This is my favorite the entire thing
And if when Alex
Even better than I the Tiger
To her and
State IDs
People so they could be able to
Alex think
Accidentally stumbled upon
Proof
Beautiful alien being allowed to vote
I'm going to deposit after the park
But it's so funny
I think that this is
It's Unbecoming
I had plenty of people telling me
Cleveland
Install free to get up
Illegal
Iraq
Because he's from here
You said two years and I said
Wyoming
I think you have an ID from Wyoming
I don't think I think because of her feelings about middle easterners
She thinks that Arabian people from Wyoming
Are foreigners
Okay
The other Necedah middle easterners
Is informing the chief
Or whatever
What does really
Ohio resident with a Wyoming
You need to update your ID
To register to vote
Describing the process that she was involved in as
But because Alex is so f****** suspicious
Wyoming oh I see
This is just an out-of-state ID situation
Sauce bad out he's decided that it's yummy
Helping people yeah but now Alex is reinterpreting all that is a negative
I wanted to make sure
But when they been here in America
A license
They've been here so long
They were citizen but
No because they still here
Been here long time
Right
He said he almost
4 years
He never vote
And I said
Have you heard about the problem of illegal aliens voting
Trying to make the conversation about that
Does Alex is even like
Is a popper
I'm sort of an admission that she was involved in helping
Immigrants
Voting ability
This is what is built on
And she was doing everything right
She's doing everything
I would say is that her Prejudice one little bit
What okay
Is it
Hold on
We call them
Discriminating in a
Malicious way
Gorgeous
It does feel I mean I don't know what the line is but yeah
Maliciously you're not been going to go like
Let's go to the movie help you out
Most likely
The right place
It's possible I don't know enough to
It's not as bad as our
These are taking
Calls from listeners
Who want to talk to Obama
Obama's
Okay
Yeah Michelle you
You seem like you're a believing woman you don't you realize we're in the latter days I'm sure you do from all of finds things
Well don't you look up
Obama
And November 5th Illinois State Lottery winning right God was going to give us an indication
This man
Is on the wrong side
Battle
44r soul
And look up
November 5th
Illinois Lottery
The number that came up for the Pick 3 3 and I check this out myself on one of those
The numbers you know
OK Google
Wasn't obvious
Made myself a
Edit had Obama
If God was going to speak to
It would be
The lottery
Does working
Mysterious ways
Guys
I understand that you want to present the idea that these are the end times and Obama's evil you have to understand
Lottery numbers
Just if you break it down you look
Crazy
Color looks crazy and you mean like yeah you know what I saw I was in other lotteries
Alex is making it worse
Man if it was
Every Lottery
Now we're in territory where I'm picking a little it's a little harder to
Three numbers like everybody who
Get the gas and the brisket
Stop
Whatever
Who
Keep this in because it will really sounds like he's reading a
Alex and Michelle
Michelle if you haven't seen the Obama
Deception documentary
I recommend did Alex get you a copy of that as well as all of his other documentaries
Magazine as well as access
You know she can wow do to the universal service fund
But who cares
What eight
Implants
Lot of consecutive plugs
Yeah
Also
You know I accept the possibility that it's just someone really well
Before getting on air
Even though
Come on
Plug-in
It's a little suspicious
All the colors that are calling in are essentially along these lines
Either lunatic
To think that God speaks through the lottery
You got to hate this Obama guy
Call
This call makes a pretty good point
Hey how you doing Michelle
Hey how are you
Do you know something Michelle the only reason why you didn't speak round
That's only reason why you there
Before you got there
Prince Cream
Soundbite of yours
Over and over and over again to clown you
And they and the reason why he's trying to get you to say things because he needs
Clown you again when you leave
And and and and
Clown around
No
He was right on every point
Guy is a hundred percent
Alex's having her onto clown her and an ant
The audio so you can
Clown her later that's absolute
Look
Don't misrepresent what I Stan
Even video came out
She seems funny I bet you'd be really interesting to talk to
Alex
Let's listen to how you covered first come out
Some of the clips of Alex talking about this after it was posted on drugs
Here is Alexei
Is just pathetic
The Nazis
We're inspired by her so she's not not since she's a Nazis mama
IPhone
Politics
It's hard. Obama phone
Give you a phone
Pathetic
So it doesn't seem like it
Xvideo
She sounds like an
Evil version of Elmo
Elmo gone bad
Elmo real quick
Elmo Elmo
Styling a bunch of people
A bunch of
Point of order you never produced any of those
Play Baby Kaely
Elmo
Jillian
I don't know what to do
Voice
Define her as a talent search for comedy lines
She would be the biggest sensation in
Country
That was that
That's not great
Pretty f*** a defensive
Yeah I just have a question
He let his kids
Watch sesame
Globalist programming
That's a weird thing to
Nobody's trying to get across
Gross
I thought I had more to say but I don't
It really just doesn't match up at all with what he's trying to present
He's laughing as a literal
Which is slightly
Well she's around in this January 2013
She is so funny she
If you just
What
Small-time Comedy Club
She needs Alex right for her the brains of the operation
She is a clown to him
Text Cliff Alex talks about these are all from September 29th
Wendy's video Broke
But this woman is
I got an Obama phone
It's sad
So his version of it is almost like
It's not even good to laugh at
Beyond
This deserves reproach
Clips from the Alex on the Nightly News
1240 calls
National
Then again some people like to laugh at that lady
It's very very sad that
Their hopes and dreams are to elect someone who will take from others to give to them
American Nightmare
So I just
This caller while he doesn't have all these clips that his disposal necessarily
I think he's making
Pretty FairPoint
Defensive about it because
Exactly what
What he's doing
It should be pointed out that on September 28th
Quote a video clip posted by the charger port has since gone viral which shows no papa supporters semi in coherently
Blathering
But how she's voting for Obama
Because the government gave her a free Phone Tracker
Underscore
Both simultaneously stealing their entire economic future
Quote
Once you've recovered from the hilarity of the video clip The Awful Truth begins
Future quotes
Freaking
Lincoln death
The delusion that these people are living under
Knows no bounds
Paul Joseph Watson article on a weekly racial
10 kind of because it might be unintentional entire economic
Future has been sold down the river these people have allowed their votes
To be bought by a free phone
For the course being sold down the river is in reference to
To the slave trade on the Lake Mississippi
I don't know if that's intentional but it
It's very weird
I don't know it could be nothing could be a lot of
Is there a lot of regional
Different idioms that
Trace their lineage
So December 11th 2012
The video was cited by critics of big government as a reflection of the typical Obama supporter
Someone lazily dependent on government handouts
How to vote could easily be bought with free stuff
Lazily
First off
She is very cold here
You understand
Made Crystal Clear what
Even even in that video.
She's not being lazy like she's
She has to go.
What are you guys doing
Just nothing that's real about what Alex's presenting about his
Engines are in the present
Because on January 15th 2013
Alex posted an article on Infowars about how he woke up the Obama Phone Lady
Because she came around
It's enough of a propaganda win
But he's able to
Super 10
But he's
Succeeded here
But ultimately it doesn't matter
Because
The only people who cared about this story cared about it to push Romney
That's the only reason that it made it on drugs
They were using these Welfare Queen races bracket types
And stuff like that but the purpose was
Find it was Romney
Is right that article on December 11th
Animated team articles about the Obama Phone Lady passed
Alex on the explanation because Infowars doesn't operate in the entire
World that the this funnel does cross-purposes a little bit
Sometimes have
Their own druthers
They follow their druthers
Recycled viral content
Yeah
So
Clip here and it's just one of the weirder things
Michelle says
View towards the end
They're talking about how
Police are out of line
Which is a FairPoint
Example of why
Is really weird see if you can catch what
Attention
Hugo
The police is watching it all
I've confused
Cleveland you can walk around naked in Cleveland Heights
You cannot
Police station
Metaphor is
Cleveland Heights place that they're cops
Constantly discriminating against black people in Cleveland
Play oh I think I think you could probably make an argument the witch
She's saying what you saying is that there over police
Cleveland Heights Cleveland
And possibly hours in Cleveland Heights such a police presence
You can't get away with
But it sounds funny it sounds funny but there's probably like a reality behind it
Emojis described
Well if she's trying to argue about the
Over policing
If she's trying to complain about not being able to walk around naked
Because the Cleveland cop saw you walking around naked they still have some
So I mean
Beyond any like
Fine points
They're behind the nudity in Cleveland
Argument
I don't know
You kind of get the descent with that's kind of as good as this interview could ever be
Really you don't like
It Alex
Sublevel knows that when he's walking into is
Either going to be
Him getting hurt
Hillside
Things
Event
She says
Stuff like you can't walk around naked in Cleveland Heights
Right
Alex is already
Presented
Is that himself up in such a
Situation
That he wins kind of no matter what
Although is a pyrrhic victory
Like I don't think most people listen to our show or you or almost anybody
Because the Obama Phone Lady video with
Specifically used for the Romney campaign
But it was a media arms
Supporting the Rodney King
Campaign
Better than
Especially associated
No kinky
Almost 100
He left it at
They're just there to clown
Which would be
Reusing
Walk-around
Forgot to add
Also they're using you as a
Hopefully they
Convince everybody that
Look even the prototypical
Obama voter
Steve-O
Will will
Abandoned
Right
For Alex
Nope
I was a little disappointed because I
You know I'd spent a lot of time
With the Armada episode
Atlanta Wednesday episode getting into the
Play flyer
Channel
Do tell you don't have to
Forgot
That the next episode was the OPA
Bike work on the episode I turned it on and I was like
I was like this is going to take
The entire episode
Really
For us to learn
On that level I'm actually kind of happy because
Ultimately
That
What Alex
She's up to
What he like
To do how he operates
Butler
It's not even happening in the contact
What other what other conclusion is there too
To draw
Alex
Is trying to create a
Racist caricature
What do you mean think about the the The Welfare Queen parallels
Obviously
The image of the Welfare Queen
Is used to try and push through
Unpopular Legend
Dysplasia
But it's also used to deflect
From
Sort of ideas of Cruelty on the right
Trying to help
These Welfare Queen
The state that they're living
Myth
To make yourself look like not the month
Monster that you are
It really is very parallel to what Alex is doing
Her in this way
In order to human eyes
Himself
I'm willing to reach out
This person who's such a f******
Typical Obama supporter of manifestation of everything I hate art Animas
It's the
I don't know
That's a bummer and I'm glad to be
He passed it cuz
I don't want to I don't want to suck it
About this I know he doesn't hire her I don't think she shows back up
On the show ever again
I think this is probably the end of
Next week
Until then we website
Correct we also on Twitter
Bowser want Facebook
Best
There's so many of them and aluminum
Responding within a couple days
Ignore it
Like that before
Like fuk you I don't give a
Obama Phone Lady hasn't killed
She definitely
Isaac
We would have heard about it if she killed
Absolutely
Technically probably has killed
Somebody
Make a clown
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color