Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan of your work
Alex Jones
How do you feel about public displays of affection
Otherwise known as
I think that there is a scale
Reconsideration again if you're like
Making out hard bass grope in public
If you're drunk
I kind of give you a little bit of a path
Not a 12-pack a little bit of the boundaries
Taking out and getting handsy with each other in public I just that less harshly than over
Call say that
A little bit of a what you doing whatever
You get overcome by the spirit
Kissing in public
No big deal. It is what it is I don't know
I would say it's totally fine if you're going to have some light public displays of affection
Natick people judging too harshly about that
I don't know why they
The point at which it becomes like this is your personal world
Who use their intimate Partners pet name
Because
It's letting
Something
Private be public
It's not private
Can't be public it's that you're forcing everyone in public to engage with you in that private
I think I just I think there's something a little bit inappropriate about that
A matter of scale and if you're drunk
It's totally fine
Update
I figure I should go ahead and let everyone know
Hi
Super hot pepper seeds
I don't understand it's growing right now
All the peppers that I have started a real strong
The peas are going real strong I've gotten a warning
Tomatoes are whiskey mistress
Overwhelming
So we may never need to cross that bridge where they are a problem
All the flowers I planted are doing pretty good
I'll let you know more developments
Hotly-anticipated episode
January 12th
2013 everybody let's
No we are doing May 2nd
And the day after Alex Jones got kicked off Instagram
Was Watson
Getting kicked off Facebook
Charlie speaking I don't like to have any knowledge of Alex
Alex Jones on Facebook
I think most of the presidents.
I don't know if that's
I think Alex will take it
Today's there's a lot of really sucked up
Stop and I actually honestly
And they could get very easily
But I totally understand
We started the show reading all of these articles
You guys have
Right
A little added contacts could make this
Like I hope we'll be able to do this story and we'll get to that
So first
I'm a policy wonk
Next will
Willow
Next to the poop thank you so much
I feel because if you would have been
You can only donate for so long
Later I thought about his body
Ewok
Somebody donated on an elevator
You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Until you're brilliant
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket
Thank you so much I like this
Do that but we would appreciate it
Like I said
F***** up stuff in here
Trends
Disentangle
But before we actually get into that
Instead of an out-of-context drop
Commercial
It's because you got to enjoy the new one
Okay this
Is one of the craziest things I've ever heard on Alec
Officials better than an example of what I'm talking about
The best a children's
Dearborn pizza made
That isn't insane commercial commercial
I don't know why
You're going to lose Santa Claus when he goes to bed that's insane
Talking trip balls
I don't know why he's trying to prove me out of the beginning of it
The burpees I don't want to know what's going on I don't know what this is a selling point
Towards the end there he says that fish oil is basically what your brain is made of
Which I had to touch with my doctor friend
Set where I pretended that I believe you
Doctor
Let's go
Was it during operating hours
And it turns out that that is not accurate
Wrist deep in fact check
Prioritize
Forever
Laughs about Alex's krill oil sales pitches
Favorite parts of somehow is the over-edited
Is only acceptable if it's a one take situation
You're getting weird but you only had a minute to shoot a commercial
50 minutes
I want
Cheraw
Forget Rock krill oil I want
Shelter Dallas
Tape on that
Alex Alex
Tim fruge over the shaking his head in the corner
Barnes
Creepier creepier about the krill
Grand Mesa
This is our first complaint
About the Tchaikovsky
Uncontrollably
Weaponization
Josh Windham most
Demoralization
Operation
University
Junior varsity narratives that he's kind of let slip in favor of
Just yelling General
Backup
Chinese own all the movie theaters
All the movie houses are owned all the schools
And I leave this
Is because
Alex
Doesn't know he's kicked off social media
Until about halfway through the show
And I think that because
You see.
Entire
You get Clues as to
What's going on and there's a couple of days
Pieces of information
And I
For the storm I really do know I heard that
Contacts
Years ago
Alex talks about how Hillary
Rachel Maddow
Any argument that Hillary is openly asking for the Chinese
To interfere in the election
R22 as opposed to ironic
Going on
Rachel
Maddow Show
He actually said Maddow that time
Someone named
Being compared to Mancow Chicago Rachel Maddow
F*** you
Russia flag
Chinese
Chinese communist
Position on it
Clip of the pump
Imagine Rachel that you had
Democratic nominees for 2020
Is China
Why should
Have all the fun
Tobacco
Conspiracy
Democratic
Incredibly
Here is what she actually
We can listen to this entire two-minute clip
Thought that he had edited
What appears to be jumped
Terrible production
To the point that Alex
Intentionally never plays
Looking for trumps
And then and then passes them to
Whatever the new Wikileaks happen
Dentist close
Nothing wrong with that
Russia
And are still doing according to Chris
Stafford
Current FBI director
Star Electric Systems
We're worried about 2020 he said
Hey
Sour contest to let's get the Chinese Inn on the side of somebody
Just saying that shows how absurd
The situation we find
It's like if you believe that
She saying
Really
It is it's
Here's what Trump did
And I'm just putting in a
Alright
You can make the argument that what she's actually doing
She saying like
Putting
Something like that never played that last fireworks
The situation
She's not in any way
The recent this is worth mentioning is that
Never stop talking
About how people use edited clips
Of him
Valerie
Night owl
The show
Short little bit where she was like so
The rest of it make
Makes it worse
I guess we're the
There's something
Hear that
Normal Infowars listener with Alex's
What context did except for the end
Especially the fact that Matthau says
Unhelpful
So earlier we heard Alex complaining
Tricom
Can control all the movie
Movie studios
In the United States
Understand about that
Is first of all
Yours to not
Because reality says that it's not true
What you don't know
Is it in the past
Alex's
The film fest
Have you ever learned
Haha
Major Film Festival
Money
Terrible anti-American stuff we can
With each other
Alright
Southpaw
Filmmakers
I imagine baby drunkenly someone
Like
Willimantic
How emotionally raw is working
Kind of
Oscar bait
And everybody knows that the Oscars love somebody
Alex
Reality
He has further
From his own personal
Hollywood
The Chinese government
To Motion Pictures
International Market
Michael Bay's entire reason
Does the Chinese government demoralize America of Emerging Markets overseas
Use for our film
Alex is never gone to Hollywood to be a movie
He's been into movies
They're both directed by Richard linklater
Chartley's veljohnson
Driving around Austin
So stupid
Conceivably see a conversation where he could
If with linklater where he could get that later literally being like
Hey Charlie
In a couple of movies is the like Richards
I worked in intelligence 30 years ago
Do you work
You have the veneer of credibility based on
Venus come out of Xperia
I think a lot about what Lee Majors thoughts on Films
Sure
Later in the episode Alex gets the news
Kicked off Instagram
Facebook and it will discuss the ban when it comes
But in this next clip
Before any of this has become public
Like before the news broke
Alex
I believe gives us a hint
As to what happened
Behind the scene
Serious diseases
Paralyzing
So that that's not true
He says that he got a warning
Of some sort that he was going to
I guess this story was
Taken down
Does going to be taken down because
Erroneous
Sprite
Knowing what comes later
Really proved
Anything so I just left it outside
Prosecco
And I'm glad I did
Because it's better
Stuff.com
Cuz he doesn't have much
This caller seems like
Everywhere I go I start up a conversation about you what is showing the world order my wife thinks I'm nuts
Why you talking to high schoolers
About the New World Order cooler at the local bar
Stop trying to open their mind redpill them
George Washington Middle School
Global
Did the police come
PowerBack to
Real sensible people Behavior
Squaw Valley
Conversation with
About
But they have
What's course of action research
I don't know if we want to
We can certainly
Middleman selling horses in the country
That's not good
The tools in the past
Where's that they wanted to give
Hillary Clinton
If she works
It would be a dick
You're going to hate it because I use them
What what
Yeah right
Can't be that hard to believe anyone's that stupid
Call RC
Processing thoughts
Decently well he's not like one of those callers that I feel bad about
First Response
I can't imagine people of any
Good
Gaither
Mental cognition
Thinking that
You give someone dictator powers
Then you get to take them away or they give them up because his
But that is not
Generally the past
What somebody has the kind of powers
Dictators
Powers you can't take them away
Ignition right
To I don't know
Yeah directions
Loyalist forces within the military
You have
You
I can't imagine anyone
Thinks they know anything
Expressing an opinion
It's really fun
Obviously they were going to make Hillary
And thank God that we got Trump in who is not a dick
But
Clearly they're not isn't
I meant
The f*** out of here
To give him complete and utter control but they will reserve the right to take away that control
That usually works right lusional box set
So stupid
Expressing like this
Sort of language
I want you to hold on to that because he doesn't clarify that until
Quite a bit later but he does
I do I do
You like they are clarified
2 minutes later and be like
Now I only meant that political it's a little bit later
For now
Violet
I'm not one of these guys who's advocating
Violence
Terrorizing everybody
They're so excited
Nerd
There wasn't so much agree with that guy but it was
Overthrow our f****** government there are
What are you going to do
Whatever you got to do
What is that mean
What is the coded language
Transition of power
Next week we get to his explanation
Where are you talkin about the idea that I wanted to capitate people
Of any realize I can't let that sit there
And I only play this because I want to be super fair to him
Never said
No be super on Thayer
Called for the decapitation
So only in the interest of fairness and because I don't
Deer Valley
Discussion
Offensive action
President
Whatever the president does
I trust I support it
Not an offensive violence guy but
Yeah every options on the table
Stuff like that because
Yeah there's a lot of weight in the sentence
Because
Also has
Butt meaning
Today
Things are on the table because there isn't
Show all options
That's not great
I don't
Really stop for a second
Listen to
I don't care what
She has my tree
0 people in government that I trust
But
To hear that
Now what is great
Go back from taking care of family members who are ill
What have you and I don't really want it is what it is
Going to bring it up with may come up here
Is that
Exposed
That she hasn't read the news
Because I'm like Rip Van Winkle
Watch the news
Wow
So if you haven't read the news in a year I don't care too much about Alex's bulshit
I would say that it makes this even more performative
It makes it all the more crap
Yeah the idea that you could
In 2018 or so
Just not watch the news for a year
Tomorrow is the end of the world the globalist they're taking over you obviously don't
Believe that
Saying something like that is
Really f***** up
You do that's so different from what you said a year ago whenever I stopped paying attention
It's crazy
When is it going to end she's like Rip Van Winkle
For 100 years and everything was this thing
Infowars
So in this next clip before the rain comes in
Disorder promoting that she
He's going to be a studio
His immediate response is it
Exactly what you need
I need him.
Knows what I'm doing
People are looking at his website
I need help
Drudge
Because in this course
He doesn't have an angle on it yet
I haven't read anything about it
He just knows the people are talking about sex
Who kicked off stuff
Drudge
Comment on it till the 4th hour but I'm still going
F****** talk about stuff
It's clearly related
Like in that last clip for the last week but a little bit earlier when I told you
Do you give these indications of what was happening behind the scenes
About
The idea that immigrants
And like I said I waited a little bit longer
And Alex got even more over in this clip
And it tells me everything I need
This is what's going on
You just got to
Pretty much
Has he got a warrant
Important
To point out that Alex is making
Super clear
He got a warning about this
He's literally because of his coverage and have you
Use blaming immigrant populations
It came out of nowhere Alex tries to defend himself
For reporting Trunews the reality of the world
ABC News
40in measles outbreak is a foreigner which is called A outbreak start
Face solely on that headline
Probably feels like he's reporting
Glenlivet measles outbreak started with a foreigner as the headlines today
Central America
Those are the imaginary disease
Is masses that Alex obsesses about after all
It's that Foreigner
Actual article
The main point of the story is not
Daniel Salman of Johns Hopkins
The foreign individuals involved in the u.s. measles outbreak are not illegal
Quote it's people have enough wealth
The travel
There's been ongoing measles outbreaks in Europe for years and it's largely because of vaccine refusal
There's also right now a bit of an outbreak happening in the New York Orthodox Jewish
And the source of this was was traced back to an individual who
Which is a super common thing
Not catching measles and Israel but catching interesting cuz
Does while on vacation
Navigate exactly the sort of thing
Providing travel alerts specific to whatever country someone
Necessary precaution
But you just went to Mexico I'm sure you had some
Warnings of
Get a diphtheria shot or whatever
Make sure your current
Is important
It's not a perfect system warning people travel
The government
Preparedness
So sometimes people go to a foreign country catch something and unknowingly
That's what this ABC News headlines
Discussing
Misrepresenting in order to creative propaganda
Has to be stopped from entering country less they infect
Everyone you know
This is why social media companies would issue Alex a warning
What he's doing is very
Very Danger
Dehumanize immigrants
Chords that need to be repulsed
Well when you reflect on the early stages of Nazi propaganda
One of the things that deserve to be discussed more
Which it's not but it could be
You still need to just
Got the more is the
Hatred of the Jews
And not these other
Homosexual
It's far more important
To make the public not care about them
The quote from the Holocaust Memorial encyclopedia
Quotes
Proceeding new measures against
Propaganda campaign
Created an atmosphere tolerances Island
The goal was to encourage passive
As a vehicle to restore public order
Demonize Jews also served
Prepare the German population
Context
National Emergency
A harsher measure
Such as mass deportations
Eventually
If you replaced with immigrants are Muslim or drag queen Story Time participant
Alex Jones propaganda is indistinguishable
In formula from the early stages
The Third Reich
His tone and rhetoric is getting ways
Scarier
Platform
Volume
It indicates
Strongly that they were giving him a very undeserved benefit of the doubt
They're trying to warn him expressing ideas
Your rationalization
Past atrocities
I was representing an actual story
Remind have done it by accident
Suspicion is that he was given the opportunity to make a correction divided misreporting
And when he didn't
It became clear that he was intentionally engaging in a demonization
Regardless
Of the efficacy
From social media
Is every consequence
Everything short of actually hurting or threatened
He deserve
He deserves to be
Unwelcome wherever he goes
Public
We're at a restaurant
Everywhere
He deserves
Like this sort of behavior
Maybe I'll walk through the streets
Maybe we get some
Except make sure that next
We understand why it makes such a big difference
The idea that Alex's for this
Before because it gives a clear path of what's going on
He's
He's creating this propaganda narrative
Based on a misreading of a headline or the body the story completely contradict
What are you saying
Yeah I mean it's just it's very clear to me what Alex's accidentally revealed
Later try and take hold on this story
It's very clear to me that he got a warning
You refused to change his behavior because it's more important to him to demonize
Wrong in such a dangerous
Marginalized communities
He doesn't give a s***
He moves forward and when
Free speech
Prize all his
Pathetic
The episode
What is
What angle
Can I take on this
It's really interesting
Is that
Is going to be far different
Alex
As we go along
Before we get to
Too far in
Care
About this until we see a little bit more
Like if
It is effective
In terms of
Diminishing is platform
Yeah I think
For the Public's health
History has shown that
He's been able to
Flout every
Bandits come so far
So until there's some sort of proof
Ethika
I have a very hard time getting
Excited
About
Some sort of ban
Well the only thing about it is
Okay
Facebook you opened the box
What's the size of the outlet that you're going to be
Tucker Carlson has said
Similar s***
Are you are you going to have the balls to go after somebody who's at Fox News
To see where it goes
That's the other problem with
So is that
Whatever Direction it does go
Wilkin
Confirm
Narrative
Yes absolutely Tucker Carlson has
Breast a lot of these dangerous ideas about Muslims
You know you kick them all social
Confirms Alex's
Screaming about how they're coming for you next
Yep they take me out and then they're coming for you next
So
There's sort of a self-fulfilling prophecy
Alex
It's like
If nothing happens then
He wins
All those things happened
He gets to pretend he was
Still come with that
Narrative that they're trying to
The band everybody
Either way
Yeah
It's hard
It's hard to
Grimaldi's
You know why
Googly and McAdoo was there
Alex Alex
Red Lobster
Weird
Real soft awkward laugh
We are having a little bit of conversation
Online empathy of the world
Realize
He's own fan
People who were his fans and then turned on him that he is using as an example of empathy
Exist online
Your mom
Washer with hard I mean everybody here in the studio
Sweetheart
Yeah
People need to stop and like realize the energy in the world and end
Compassion for each other
A little bit of
Hippie instinct
Before she came in
Bubbling back to the surface and the time that she
She's been
Not at
An awful thing
We should have towards other people
All of those theories about Alex
Having an affair with Leann him hurting her any of those
She's gone
No one who criticizes Infowars other than Austin know who Lee Ann McAdoo is
No one knows who she is
No
None of your enemies
Know who your staff is
Nope Shroyer getting yelled at by a little finger
No one knew who
Child
No one knows who David Knight is
No no one knows
Any of these people are
Until they get sued
Like
Like right now
The courts know who they are
Trying to attack Alex
Macy's.
They were his fans
And his ex van
Who have toxic
Expenses online
Talk about how ex-boyfriend was black
And stuff like that
We would say that
I don't think that one was us
No
Personally at all
Observed message boards
And places like that
Are all sore
Infowars fan
Who think that Alex Dodgers the Jewish question
Stuff like that
It should be ground
Punishment
Along the lines of a slap
I think that with a straight face
Requires a slap to the
This is real life
A bucket of water Maybe
Kohl's bucket of water
No
Because I don't endorse his
Physical violence but
I'm for it
Some people online conspiracy theories
Well I don't think Jonathan really wants to
They're still wrapped up in this and probably
I don't get the sense
Listening to
And I'm not letting her off the hook
Is not as enthusiastic
Participate in this is Alex Watts interview
She's way off base
In terms of Russia
I'll go with you on it
I'll go with you halfway but you need to look in the mirror
And see
Those people
Exist
Without
You
Oh yeah like without this
Infowars propaganda
So you saying that
Infowars not created a rabid fanbase
Conspiracy theory loving lunatic
Go off at the drop of a hat
Screaming about all kinds of different violent action
That they want
Infowars employees
Not employed
To go take care of her
Environment
Create
If
Boy I don't want to say goes around comes
It's not quite that simple.
If people get these sorts of
I'm not for it but
Got you got a wreck
Big knives what the soup is
II
This week these are the ingredients
You don't have to
You should before
But that's
Can you help me
Doesn't really work
Yeah and we're in the city
We're in the soup
Alex
To finally figured out how he's going
Louis Farrakhan
Imposition
So Alex decide
Fit everyone
Is being claimed
To be an anti-semite
Night Moves
That's a good
Express
Different thing
It's just that
Patriots
I have the right of return
I like that
You guys are mean
Reno from going back to like 2009. Alex was very
Grill
Ideas
In order to make accusations
About
People Legion
It doesn't matter
Call Vincennes
He was completely denying the fact
His ex-wife
Heritage at all
Now he's totally fine really been a big part of it and two crying people are talking about the idea
It's sort of Poker
Fun
Piece of Alex's / Atarax
See how completely
Inverted
It is in the pocket of Israel or anything like that
Convenience
He is
At this is this is an easy way to let himself off the hook
For all of the wild lettuce
Deeply auntie
It doesn't mean that most of it ideas
Like that doesn't let you off the hook for those or
If it was the early 1930s
He would be demonizing Jews all over
Of course
You're a popular to demonize he's going to be on the 4th
Where were the populists
Have you quotes
You will go
You're looking at him over the course of the year
South
Anyway
He's decided the story is going to be
That's why he was
Kicked off
Alzheimer's that this was all just people calling Zucker
Herberger
So
Gets a little bit heady
Talking about how she was out like
Get outside the city
You look up
Stars
If we have
This would have been
K-LOVE a unit
That sort of thing we can look up to
How small we are in the grand
Alex Project Camelot
We were able to flex back in the day
People were able to see the sky like that
It would really put how small we are in perspective and how
To be really
Little people
Satellites
Also she like
Alex Smith
I believe
Scrap
Hillary isn't in charge because
It implies that he sings
Doesn't it
Terminix
Necessarily
All right there
Can see both sides
I like the camper love go out there
Get my hands dirty
I love it
Disgusting
Sometime
So it is next clip
Complain
This because I just want to get it at 17
Because it's so crazy
Leanne is complaining
About the idea that stories about Alex Jones
And there's the story but people are just going to read the headlines of the stories about Alex
Things about Alec
Which is crazy
Control
Alex Jones
Evolve to the point where they don't even read the articles they just read the headline
They read the headlines and they read
150 characters that might be in a Facebook post
Your boss
Who you're sitting next to is
The king of just reading headline
And has already said on this episode that Facebook
About it
Because most likely
He was operating entirely office about a headline
This is Dawn
Bring back the stock
I want people throwing lettuce at their face 424
Southland
Without
E-coli
90%
You can put
One quarter of a bug
Quarter of a quarter of a bug
It turns out that Alex is banned for being at peace
And all that stuff
Major pieces
He was a real.
So he didn't even know that Paul had been back
Along with
20 characters of the tweets
I'm a little bit earlier.
For Alex to get around part because he has a dedicated staff
You keep making
Whenever one of his
As I said in the past when they called off one of my testicle three more grow back
Which is definitely
Sound like the hero of this story
The right to be more effective
Wired
Facebook and Instagram
All their personal and professional ikaw
Organization
Are no longer permitted on either platform
Account
To represent them part
Is going to be
Kralik I believe
Yeah
0 basic social media Outlets to protect their users
We'll see what happens
But it's a little more than this
Today's our number
It might be another matter for a couple other people
Involved
Namely Milo and Laura Loomer
Alex Paul Joseph Watson
Infowars
The Griff and really the reason becomes clear it circumstances like this
Their only skills are agitate
Is there really a journalist
Social media ban wouldn't be there work since they could write it devastated
Peace on the road website or blog
Source
Picked up by at least
A number of independent
Places
You could get something in the intercept
If you were actually doing
Some sort of good work
About this
If they were concerned about the
Might have wizards
Actually blacklisted writer
Their supporters
McCarthy era
I like the idea of life
People like lubar have nothing
I empathize with her freaking out nearby
Thought of her
Spoiler alert we are going to talk a little bit about that
Episode
I don't want to make a mockery of someone who may very well be having a mental health episode
But make no mistake
The Freak Out
Globalist
It's Ono my scam doesn't really work without
Periscope
Comes from the recognition
This is the end of the road
Freddy
Concerned that we as a podcast
Have no fear
Facebook said videos radio Clips articles and other content for
From the site are explicitly condemning the material
I think our conversation has been pretty explicit
Who's wired article includes
We hope that this could be in effect
To ban against
Quotes books Thursday bank closes a loophole
The one where Alex could just
Usually reserved for terrorist organization
Excel
Claim papers are still reserved for terrorists
I would say that fits well within the bill right it's not an automated algorithm
People who
Appear to be
Taking down
Taking care of it
This is good
Alex is running an organization that motivated by inspiring white Western terrorism in apologizing for
For when it does happen
Excuses for it
And also deceptively selling fish oil
Company is deciding
Incorrect
This isn't the free-speech issue in the
And ultimately the irony of the situation is the only way that Alex
Decision is to try and get Trump to help it with executive orders
For years he screamed bloody murder about overpowered executive branch in
Evils of the federal government
And now
To stay afloat
Is the advocate for the federal government to step in dictate what
Speech is or is not allowed by a private business
Basically have to argue against
Free speech in order to save his
Suppose right to be on Facebook
Which should be fun to see him been himself into a pretzel
We all get angry enough
Enough that we don't have to
Free speech that were like okay Trump give it back now
To kill her for a minute
To put it briefly
Because I think
Things that I said there might
Sound
Victory or a little bit
Play soda still at this 8
I think
Alex has the resources
Disposal currently
UB employees
The built-in infrastructure of being able to have people
I think he has those things
Incredibly difficult
To stick
However the fact that they're saying
That they're going to
Treat this like
Knock down these dummy accounts
I think that's inspiring in someone
We'll see what happens
Not Super Optimus
I think Milo and Laura Arkham
Completely fuk
John with whatever hussle's they've been on
Cuz Milo relied entirely on
Yeah
He got that kicked off of
Ineffective
Infrastructure
He was only being able to publish it
His books and disseminate
Because of that Bond
Yeah
Instagram
I don't see what kind of hustle he can pull off
Laura Loomer has no towel
She's only good
Brouhaha
Without access to
Streaming materials and
Like that she has nothing
I think that's where she's
Going to go next
I wish you the best
Going to be a road that's open
We'll see what you think
For May 2nd
Alex is found
Kicked off
Social media
It starts
Maybe
Maybe he's.
You have really great people on the team would be able to
The time to recharge and warriors
Figurative
Would like
He wants to leave earlier
He gets high when he
Gardening
Some plants
Scratch but I do enjoy it
Go to that you'll be seeing Santa Claus in
Nothing it's really interesting
And then also understand that like
You think of a plant is like I've been on the same
You can interact with
Over the play
Because you just come and you see
It's right here
You don't see them over the course of a day yeah it's really interesting
Move a lot more than you think
From the experience of
Sir Alex go f****** be a gardener
You might think that was just a
Estrella Falls
I'm just saying
Just picking corn
You know what corner
The reason why
There's a reason why a lot of us are
The basics of what is real
Money-power
So he's telling his audience angel
Is pretty f***** up
Really
Maybe
To do that
F*** it up
I'm having dreams of sweeping
Uchealth
Fall asleep
Hillary face at all take a bunch of krill oil and I trip balls taking about
Shores
Piece of corn
Looks like Hillary
Expiration date
I mean
Is really important as a
Alex is so unhinged
As a person
I'm so on board
From like
Any kind of bearing
Keeping him
In place
Over the course of the show you do hear him screaming about decapitating his enemies
My games appear
Eva
F*** it I want a garden
I want get out of here
Music
Because there are
He has no sense
He has no ability
B2
Sad
There's a lot more
You have a lot of employees here you could
She doesn't know that
He does not but
It is it is a
It's interesting because this episode
Heavily and come again
Kind of giving
Assemblance of
Empathy
To Alex
Care for himself at least a little bit
Alex
Yeah it's also the inverse of what's going to be
The May 3rd at
Keep on keep that in mind
Laura Loomer
Nobu
The third here with Alex
Having
Talk to his lawyer
The night before
He's on a much better footing
She is a little bit of a manic energy
He's going to prove that everyone is wrong
He's going to lay it all out episode
It's going to be
Comparison
An old-fashioned
F****** cash register every time
He does show up on the
Smoking Gun
Rosebud
Crucify him
Oh man
He's got proof
Dunham dirty
I couldn't stop you're probably right
Factually inaccurate Alex
Is too fat
To crucify
Come on man
Lesbian
Clip
Because it was the most important thing he's ever covers
Because this is officially the most important
Alex's ever cover
24 a
The most important
Information
The fog
You see the sunrise
I'm coming up
Aurelio's Magic Moment
I was blown away by that term that looks really thought
I see everything the fog is lifted I see the globalist plan
Nothing is laid out in front of me instead it's actually beautiful
Not good that was very weird I really enjoyed that though it was a ride
Visual metaphor he's making out like outside
Experience before the fog break
You see a beautiful landscaping front of you absolutely
I was along for the ride
Just
Neck-breaking
Twist
Yeah especially
Important
So
Tunupa
Pieces that he's trying to add to the
The band narrative
The first
Is Mastercard
Make sure
If you give any money to people they don't like
They're going to erase your account
Doesn't sound legal
Built
MasterCard
Spokes
Blueprint
4 something
I won't say a word because
Antichrist works
Like there's a room in MasterCard where they're all sitting around with the Book of Revelations going like alright
How are we going to get the second one
We are over budget
The revelation
Alright alright
As I understand it is it MasterCard is putting these
Are there any type of conversation
Human rights
Emissions as part of their board
Yeah turn off your account
Breathing
Transaction
Places
Specifically but you know what I mean
They would just cancel that transaction
You can't use our service
To give that money
Right not the same thing is you need to
You give money to your account
Yeah that's really going to limit Putin's ability to unrefined
Because he uses MasterCard
American
American Express commercial
He was with Trump at the time
I started learning Russian but I don't know how to say what's in your wallet
This point I cannot I only know that woman is
Jenna should know that
I like it
For process
Apple
So is the MasterCard
Is going to take away all your money
If you're a bad boy
Rebel Without a card
Haha
He's putting for
Is that now if you're on this bad boy lip
They're also trying to make
You can't use phone
Anymore
Sing off of Oliver.
Being interviewed on CNN
About his
Alex's
Monster song
Instagram
Facebook
Scrutiny from people who are saying hey
You know you guys bad why are you allowing them to the present
Tony Banning Alex Jones
Infowars
Facebook from Instagram
WhatsApp
What the heck
Unclear
WhatsApp app
Water from Facebook
Water off
That we only oxygen now
Would you be regulated like
I think he is back on
He doesn't care about that in
Intel personal
Important
Place where there are people on both sides calling for the same thing
Perspective
The idea of
F****** break up Facebook
But yes
Elizabeth Warren
Still much comes down to like why
Is it because your hustle is being interrupted
I will take you
I will side with honest
Similar issue
Alex is trying to
Oliver Darcy is coming here on spaghetti
B Alex
To have his abilities
Taken away
Facebook owns WhatsApp
You don't know
WhatsApp
To text
You don't need it to call people
It's just an applications that you can
Use or not
There's a hundred different ways you can text and call people
It's absurd to think like I'm being kicked off WhatsApp
Because it's owned by the same company that kicked me off stuff
Now I
Text ever
It's silly
It's clear
I don't know
It's not clear
Calling WhatsApp
Breaking the terms
Of WhatsApp
Allowed to stay on Instagram for the time that he was
Kicked off Facebook
Broke
Community guidelines
WhatsApp
A bunch of regulations
Propaganda
Burnt
WhatsApp
Email threads
Control
I've never used it I've never talked to anybody
A couple
Stories Longo's
Larger point for our show.
Increase
The scope of what this
Because he needs
Look apocalyptic
Because it's
Well I still have some faith
Dukes of Hazzard
Generally over the
He realizes
He's in a bit of
Because
From what Facebook is saying
Seems to be born
Comprehensive it looks like it's going to be
A bigger thing
Hit the employee
Infowars
His contact as if it were just
Infowars account
So
Is rightfully worried
He needs to Double Down
This is just happening
Because they say
Somatic and
Directions
Yes I do
Is really sick
Be weird
It's not
Also you can be pro-israel
Just based on a couple years back
Ikea
It's
He's trying to present their and the reason that he's trying
To use
Taken down
Because
Create that as
Distraught
Version of
The big reason is because about a month ago he got in trouble for
Systemic pose
He's trying to complete that's it
Situation with the prison
Which are completely different things
We also know that he
Messenger
Precipitate
This is the reality
Did you just joined us
Discussion
March
Piece of art on Instagram that played on medic Protocols of the Elders of Zion
Throat with a hashtag wake up America
The email chain that was disgusting article on Business Insider
And the way it was being present
Posted on Alex's
Infowars
And the discussion was whether or not
Itself broke their Community standard
What member of the policy team clearly pointed out quotes
This image is widely acknowledged
380 Smith
It is a famous the public controversy
Mercy around it
Commented on it and then got a lot of blowback
Not look closely that
Bucked up
Was taken down
Current issue Alex
Because I'm
Episode
How from May 2nd Alex at the Facebook
That were the problem
This has nothing to do with it is very realized
Muddy the waters about very
Issue
Is so much easier for him to manipulate
Then the very idea
And I refuse to acknowledge
That I was wrong and correct my behavior
He was also playing on anti-muslim
And he can easily rely on yelling about Elon Omar and how she hates his real daddy loves
Somatic
Play Vanessa
The intentionally lied about news article noted
About hatred
And that's what he wants to do cuz it's easier
What others do you have
That really you
Please forward
You can't defense if the truth is
I got a warning about a dishonest
Clearly
F*****-up story that I was pushing
Trying to demonize
Micro population
Representative
The story I got a really gracious
Offer to
Correct what I was putting into the world
Icicle f*** yourself and then they kick me off
It's really hard to Garner any kind of
Support from
The president
From
Mainstream
Conservatives those sorts of folks
It's really tough it's much
Easier to say I'm
Semitism
And I'm not they don't even give any proof of it
It's all just because I'm a conservative and I
I support Trump
Do-it-yourself free speech
It's so much easier to play that game
Accidentally slipped
On this episode
This exact same thing happening
Behind the said that I probably would have no idea
That would just make you was a liar without a specific
Yep
Every time
There's a warning
Yep single f****** time
It's something bad happens to him
I'm certain that someone is giving him the opportunity
To do the right thing
There is
Undoubtedly
Some sort of a
Please stop
We know it in the case of the Sandy Hook case
They're absolutely
A please stop
But he just didn't give a s*** about an ignored
I'm certain
And how do you unlock I even though those lawsuits
Vague
Still give him a
He has been given every opportunity to do the right thing
He never does
These are just consequences
Why
Are like 18 Sprint
Warnings in like
We're going to do something
Bars like go f*** yourself
It was just the same situation Alex
I was trying to call
Really what's going on
Is the
Conspiracy
I don't remember exactly how it work
Convoluted
Title for this clip
This is not
Flagpole
Why about
Alex has a month ago he had this
Weather
Instagram because of
Very
He posted
With the caption wake up America
And then there were
Conversations
Violated
Blue
And the middle management was like
Now they're like
To provide cover to make it look like they're not just
Trump
Whatever by the throat Louis Farrakhan
Conspiracy.
This is pretty much
Of the Third
He said he is
Total proof
That's
That's better article about an Instagram post from a month ago and then he say
Pacifica
Produces them
He's never quoted from them never said what they say
Oakridge from
Means I don't exist
So it seems shocking
Politico
First
So first
Came for the Nazi
Everything was fine
They came for the slave minorities and I said nothing
Because I wasn't at my door.
The paper you weren't.
Silly in reverse
So I feel that so weird
Itsfunneh
Is super like whatever Trump wants to do I trust him
Because that's before the bay
How we doing
King Soopers
You were someone like Trump
Why would you ever trust Alex
Everybody has shown himself to be completely unreliable
12 sec separation
I think he's got a lot of what you wanted out of
Shifting the public discourse more acceptable
Those are absolutely
Are the Galaxy
But if you are the person in power
You got to know this person like Alex
Don't give a f*** about him
Things are going good for him on May 2nd
He thinks that you should start a dictatorship
On May 3rd
F****** done your dictatorship
He's going to pieces
Suspicious
Kind of
Consistency
Self-centeredness
Victor Alex operator
Yeah that's a wide spectrum in a very short. Of time
You really was just fantasizing about
She's mental state
Jeff
You should quit
Pull the trigger
You should definitely
Equip
Doing
Is a
It's almost like the audience or a group of investors
His show
Okay just
Indiegogo
Alright with the next
We are going to ship
Interpersonal
Do you want this
F******
All the people you don't like
Give me a lot of money
That's just
I find
Narratives
Points like a progression
I think there's going to be way too much
Lawsuit
That was
Is the pitch
That kept us from getting a second
Season of Firefly
In there and he was like all right here's what I got
I'm just going to do a bunch of people that I don't like Malcolm is going to be on the sides
Nope will give you a movie about years later
Alright
Billions got to go
Alright fight
So it is excellent I just kept this in largely to reinforce how willing Alex's to use his key
Kids Jewish heritage
Because it's convenient
For as before
He pretended
Clear that I do not care at all about his kids
Jewish order
Like that is that means nothing to me
I am not interested in it
He uses it
That is the only thing I just want to be
It could be
Not easily but it could be misconstrued that I think it matters
In some way because we're talkin
Think about it and I do not at all care
Deserve every ounce of privacy
About who they are
The children deserve
I am only interested in
Duwe Alex
Uses
Of their identity
And who they are when it's convenient
And lies about it
Laura Loomer
Showing up
And I want to be clear about this
I've no interest in making fun of someone who's going
Through a mental break
I do not believe that
Did she is having AC
Experimental brakes
If I miss
I empathize with what she's going
Through and I apologize
For making fun of it
But based on what
I think
She makes it a little bit
Clear
Is just making money anymore
Like in this first clip
I really think
But she's being too overt
This is about money
Rush
This thing is
Lawsuits
Baking soda performative aspects of hiring
50 lawyers
In order to make it look like they're going
This is a hustle in and of itself the lawsuit Hustle
Is something worth
Hey give me a ton of money
I will pretend to fight
The people you don't like
$2,000 I can
Can pay my lawyer
$5,000 to write a brief
And that'll take a while to be dismissed
Time.
Can you give me
Most likely intervening time
To Garner at
Towards whatever I do through periscopes where I
Help myself to the door or Twitter or
Go to the Facebook
Demand someone see me
Glass clips
Suing chair
Calphalon American
Nobody here that sort of statement the obvious first question anyway
Thinking person should ask is
In November 2014
Designated a terrorist organization by the United Arab Emirates
Uae's former their foreign minister Abdullah bin Zayed Al nahyan
Admitted
Explained when asked about it they are threshold is quite low when we talk about it
Extremism
Go ahead and just designate just about anybody other pair organization
And you know why
Because of accusations that UAE was wrapped up in the financing of 9/11
And allegations that they were trying to open it
Back in 2013
The UAE has been incredibly gun-shy about the idea of being a social
Group
Terragroup designation
The world
Nation of care as the terrorists
Organization
Multiple times
Laura Loomer
Need to know about her
First thing
Without pointing out that it was in 2014 by the United Arab Emirates
Context around
She doesn't give a f*** she just wants
Association with Lamar
To know the details
Last Laura Loomer be allowed
Co-founder co-founder Awad
Except
Voiced support for Hamas
Is 19
Which predates massa's designation is group
After that point
Condemned
We consistently with
I don't support him off today
We condemn suicide
Speaking out against
Where are they
The co-founder supported
94 ization hasnat
Information
As for the Muslim Brotherhood stuff
Conservative attack
Whatever their someone arriving propagandist doesn't like
Please vaguely Middle Eastern
With the Muslim Brotherhood
I seen this play out over and over again salad
And I can't find any credible sources that Lake Kerr in the Muslim Brotherhood
So I just got to assume that loomer's soft bulshit
Is more of the same
Yeah you can
Trump is moving to get them at
The ideas that
The connection with Hamas
So deep in the past
And something that's very
Understandable
And
Not
Really
To make them look like a terrorist organization
If you have to do them in the United States
Recognized as a terrorist organization
The facts
Chino's
UA
Designated that way
She knows that that lawsuit is used
Your honor
The UAE has designated care as a
A terrorist organization
Legal system
To use the uae's legal definition
Now
You're using a lot of words
Sure and I get where they're coming
But
Come on
Just this once
You have to understand
Steve her
Having a tough time
Building this up too much
But she doesn't
Okay little bit
In the same interview that this is like
I need people to fund my lawsuit money because I'm suing
Is a terrorist designated organization
She knows damn well
It's never going to work
Workout
Scam
It's a lawsuit Hustle
And I want to make this abundantly clear
Continues to go on
Give her money
Seems right I probably don't want to be involved with your gross publicity stunt
Like when she went in there
She doesn't understand that maybe some of the people not supporting her
Part of its Subs
And part of its Style
It's a little bit of something that like
You don't want to be involved with the girl who
Trust yourself to one door instead of two
Like by Yo whatever just give us a call
Employees could still get in and out the door
Embarrassing
Really it
Steven Universe
Doesn't
The hustle was busy
It doesn't she's not very good at this
It was still pretty profitable
But now without the ability to use periscope
Instagram
Like this
It's tough for her
Going to work
So at this point she complains that everyone has ruined
Remind
Conservative
And part of the party
Personal
How much are
You might have answered your own question
Kicked out
But regardless of the dream Oliver Darcy
She said
I chase
And then for some reason they kicked me out of CPAC I chased someone and then confronted them angrily about
Something unacceptable
For a conference
Yeah I don't
I think that means reasonable
Strange world
Road
What's acceptable
Is that not okay
Gralia G6
Conversation about what
Send someone in a costume
And then being kicked out
Alright
And from
It's about how like her like
Everyone's ruined her life
Jedi I mean
From from an external perspective
Real shity to her online
I definitely believe she deserves any sort of
Anyone deserves
Targeted harassment of any believe that she's probably been the recipient
Alex
Have been the target of
Eunice.
I would argue that a large portion
Did she get probably get
They come from
But
Larger
And much more
Important
Do ruined life portion of it
Comes from her work
How dare you consequences
Disenfranchised communities for a long time
It dishonest duplicitous
This is the end result of a hustle gone bad
Speaks for itself
And the word that its peak
For itself
We did a great job.
Keep on
Have you ever seen your own videos
Like there was a time when the
Could come too
Or you can grow a mustache
Now in the days of
Add social media
You are screwed
In a lot of ways because she is 25
If we go back to the first time we ever talked about her on the podcast
I remember you saying
Young
She doesn't know the cot like the end result
So what she's doing
I think I also said that I don't
Pictures very good at this
I still empathize with her because she does have a long life ahead of her
And it is
It's gotta suck
To have your con blow up
Like this got to be terrible
And I emphasize
Entirely
But I would be bored
Empathetic
If she took some ownership of how what she has done
Has caused
Suzanne
It really feels like she's blaming everybody else for
For the situation
She's in
And it makes it a lot harder for me
To feel bad all of this focus on
When I was over at Jack's house
It makes it hard for me
This is an anyway
An actual breakdown of mint
As it is
I'm at the end
Is this rope
This end the end of the scam
Edit
The Comedown isn't good
And I'm really fun for a bit right now
The next morning I haven't slept
F*** my bones
And she's not famous enough to have
Redemption
Stories recently option Story by the time she would have hurt
Lexcorp
Even further.
Complaining about how everyone
Has ruined her life
Go away with me
We're standing up
Yeah I bet you didn't know that
So your face and ice
Listen to
It's uncomfortable to listen
Someone
This is uncomfortable
Experiencing a Tesla
Important
Still discomfort
Is the scam
Fizzling out
When someone is at the end of their rope what they do is yell about how the people within the movement
And everybody else isn't supporting them and they need to send the money
Instead of run
I guess I'm going to lay low for a year
And then come back as Lauren Luna something like that
It's the bitter this
The anger of
Recognizing without accepting
That you are at the end of the
The con
And I think there's something interesting
I meant
It's super interesting
To see how little Alex give the
Empathic way is not recognizing
That what she
She's expressing is on sublevel rejection
It's her feeling like
Like Alex are rejecting her
You're not on Twitter
What she's expressing also or maybe mostly
Is the Betrayal of
What she thought were the people
Ulta
Something along the
I have to be in there because
Was because of all the support positive feedback
Young reporters out there you're getting the truth
We Believe
I don't know if Alex is
These days
What
He comes to Alex
Alex
You get here
A complete lack of care
President
I don't like
Find it interesting that it isn't
With the day before Whitley and was on it being like
How to build up this thing
Can take care of you
Distance
Response
Alex's bulshit
It's by Alex's Lac
Laura
Some kind of
Like we're going to get through this
You know hey
I know it feels dark
Are you giving a little bit
And that is
Suck it up
Nightcore
Alex brings up that the president is tweeted
To feel great about that
As a soldier
Qatar
That was that almost sounds like
He caught her
Audio off
So we could finish things
I don't know
She's embody there is
What you were talking about
And I started my reputation
Agree I deserve
Your own principles
RV
Very very contradicting
Your
What you feel you're entitled to
These folks
My friend Lord
Soul
I know you have degrees
She might
Laura Loomer graduated from Barry University
If you check bear University's website you'll find that they don't offer a journalism program
She could have received a degree in advertise
In broadcast
In communication and media
Orem Public Relation
But the best
The best
She could have received in terms of an actual journalism education
Is it have a minor in journalism
Which Berry does offer
The only three times that the word journalism
Barry University
These Pages available undergraduate is in the description
Locations program
Are kind of related to journal
She apparently I might have also attended Mount Holyoke College
At some point I'm not sure I've seen that on a couple website but I don't know if that's a hundred percent true
What school does have a journalism program journalism program that they run is an in
Independent study program
If you did or not she didn't graduate
Grandpa her to be at the top of her classes
Did you graduate
Trump
Also wasn't college she was already working with project veritas
Which I studied journalism probably would be adverse to
To doing
Proaxis group
She went around
And talked
Two professors at the school
Because of that stunt she was suspended from the school and one of the professors
Sushi filled without permission filed a criminal complaint
It should never taking any real journalism
Classes
But you didn't
I wonder why they she's not getting
Offers of like others
Writing a Blog
Salmon on
Periscope
Seems like she has
Like my entire conviction
Is
The immediate
He is so important
Vehicle
In the same way is it
After
Tragic events around the world it's so important
Places like Infowars
These Outlets
To get their spin out
Because
Concrete is still drying
Once it dries
It's
The scams
These people the immediacy is important
Laura Loomer is infowars.com
This sort of already established
Place where they can
Publish news
So her version of immediacy
Please live stream
Could do that being taken away is
It's devastating to her being able to run this hustle
That's all I hear is a recognition that without
These tools
I can't
Do I can't distract people
I can't trick them the way that I could
And
As the sun sets on that scam
The recognized
Careers that I
And do one
You said the Atlanta
Pictures of magic
Well
Pill
Friedersdorf
Doesn't have as a saleable a career
Laura Loomer
Access point
I don't know
The other thing with Laura so is she selfish
Forgettable
In the way
Tell that
Hey
Pro-immigration Isis or whatever it is
Exhausting
Forgettable
Completely forgotten what
Immediate requirements
Always reminding you
Empathize
With
The consequences
Your career catching up with
The freak out that you're seeing is
Is there
Kind of real
Something that I
I don't want
To belittle
But so much of it is
I don't have a money stream anymore cuz my spam is ruined
You know she's basically being
From her position as
Yeah it's a little different
The functional
Little different
I get Wyatt
You're not meet me halfway
Text web
Laura says Summit Fair Lakes
Disgusting
Really f****** hard
To feel bad for anybody after that it's much like she's talked about how
Worth living without social media before we
Pretty scary I just use my friend
Yeah I would definitely be
Much more like
Hey Laura
We need to talk about this you need to go talk to
She should learn how to garden
Sure Alex should be recommended
In terms of what I want
Text Bono's in what I wanted
Point out like
She's clearly lying
This is all just about her scam blowing up
It's difficult as an external Observer to really know exactly what's going on
You know like
I recognize that there's a decent chance
She does feel like her life's not worth living
Without the
Notoriety
Celebrity
Cash flow
The social media offers her
Because it's much easier than doing real work
I recognize that there's a possibility
He does feel that way and it is
A real Mensch
Philhealth issue
At the same time
I also recognize
That she
You suck
She's terrible
She says really f***** up things
It is
Equally possible that she
Saying that
To make people
Think that this is an extreme situation and they should rush to her Aid
I don't
I don't know
If it's sincere than
I hope she gets help
And I would not balk
Someone actually
We struggling with
When you hear someone appear on Infowars
And make it so much about how like no one supporting me everybody needs
Give me money so I can do this b*******
Lawsuit against demonized
Because they're Muslims in
Decided that they're terrorists
And then she ends with like I don't want to live
After my life because I have to work
I find it hard to label it
Maybe that's
This is coming in
And I'm not able to empathize with her
The way that I would be
Actually
Time and effort
Truly empathizing in
Figure out
Performance
But yeah
All signs of Alzheimer's
Got off the phone
And
Chip Pierce Morgan and said we did a great job today
Sure
No
Is there is a mental illness
Text to do what
How much
Should we
Calculate that into our system
I do think it appropriate to empathize with the
Struggles that people go through
Even if their mans
You know you shouldn't mock somebody
For human struggle
Even if like
If there's someone that you
Does bad thing
But
Mental illnesses
Who's leading Alex Laura Loomer to go down these roads
Evicted
Unapologetically
And don't seem to give a
How much
Are we required
Yeah I struggle with that
Good job of not making
Fun of this breakdown that you
She's had a kind of discussing it
Maybe we've gone too far
Too much credit
But I don't think
Feel ugly
If we
I don't know
It doesn't
Mentally ill so much as
Somewhat reasonable
What's actually going on
It's probably how I feel
That myself if I were on
Infowars
Like
Kind of does
Cuz yeah yeah
Help my scam
It's a Hail Mary
It could be a Hail Mary
Situation
Just say you will see
Hello Birds
I guess
I had to put a button on those I would say
Don't care that
Fair care more about is
Job
Caring about someone who is
Coworker
More.
The fight
Atopica
And ended with some old dude
Who's telling you the story about house
Oh yeah I lost my job and then my wife
My daughter she's got
Some health issues right now I got to
Help her with some bags
And it's all because of the Jews and you like
All right with the Jews did that part I wouldn't have cared
So in this last collect from the Raiders
I just think Alex is a really bad job
Supposed to be like
Keep your chin up
Which is just
It's just also
Such a bad job
We got
Conscience
It's always for the dawn Laura
Bless you
Glamour.com
So you heard her say something
Steamrolling through the
We got to go to Commercial Sound boilerplate
Yeah future up
You're brave.
Send it will read it
Has been banned
We'll see
How effective is
Could not be
Shut up.
How to spell he's been kicked off in
Next clip I think he recognizes that
He's Cried Wolf
Way to
Superman Cam
He's a real quick
Superbad
He's talking about Saudi
Today
Superman Cam
Squishy Mash'Ems
Godzilla
Flopping around
Gut
Yeah
Cuz Alex
She's also invented
This is still on the same as Broad
Which probably made Alex want to get rid of her sooner
Express that Rodger was taking up too much of a donation
Summer coming on your show and just being the like percent of my income is gone
8 degrees
Person
To be six
Spillane
Journalism
He doesn't want that come again cuz that could slice an awesome
Little pissed off about that
More fundraising
Whenever I tell people that we cuz we're
We're not seeing that all probably because I've said this repeatedly
A seriously I never disappear and none of the things I say are going to happen to end up happening
Diminishing returns
As we talked about so much
People get into him then naturally leave
Some people stay a lot of people lie
What's been disrupted is in
Flow that replaces
The outflow
As that happens of course
People hoard sticking around
Can only be squeezed so much
So if he doesn't see
Spy kits
Because the people who
There's left
Flow coming in
There aren't enough people to do
It's just
The natural reality
So
If that's the effect of these bands
Then I think it's good because it will end up
Cutting off that
Flow
American Pie
That'll do it
Anything else
Getting getting rid of the people who
Find him
It will be
So much better
Getting up getting rid of the recruitment
Indoctrination
Part of the pipeline is very
I know enough for listened to enough of this dude
He talks all the time about like
The money goes away I'll be in the garage doing this
He absolutely won't
Part of like I have millions
Dollars I will just go have a ranch
That's with my family
The idea of like I'm going to get
Continue fighting the globalist in a bucket
Garage
No you're not
So like
Cash flow from new Folk
I think it's crucially
Important
Because
It does
Seem like
Shmoney
Need you to support me
Needs it now
Needs our money
Eclipse
I have one more clip
Alex's lawyer is on
For a large portion
Everybody Barnes
Alright
This is Barnes
Alex has a Gaston who's bringing back the publication human event
Oh
I started the world
Alex says
When he was in high school you read publication
Human events
I believe it started
Publishing and
Disappeared
Not too long ago
Brought back by
This guy who's a part of UK
His lawyer saying
Reasons why
Publication headache
It seemed to at least
Provision
Position it was started in 1944 with decidedly
We should have I don't know exactly but I think
Pretend you're naive about the Vichy French
It's a little weird
I also
Supportive of apartheid in South Africa
Calling pro-western bulwark
Everybody
Rewards
Here's some of the winners that Alex
Probably have some issues
Use with the getting
Some kind of an award
Long list
2000w bush
2002 John Ashcroft
Paul Ryan
The guy who recorded
It's just stupid I don't understand why his lawyer is
Involved with that was the part that's very weird
They were at least supportive
The Vichy French
So we come to the end and
The thing is
Also
Good work
Great work
I think the important
Is
You know
Simplistic
Sick of you on it
Galaxy kicked off
These things
That's fine
You know I think if people want to just have the perception that he got kicked off for
That's pretty accurate
To look at these
Because Alex
What's the what's going on
He accidentally reveals
Pretty much
Most of the
The stop
And when you look at this it's clear
Given a chance
Abandon
Because it reinforces that message
With it the same
Campbell Boomers run
With her pretending the
She's going to sue Care
Alex could do the same thing with businessinsider
Aldi's
These fake lost
You bring in tons of money
People by pretending
But you'll be there
And fight therefore
But in reality you're probably just pocketing it or using it
Fight the lawsuits
About
I don't know
Yoda bulshit
Kick-off whatever platform
Decide tu
I would stop short of calling on a
Anybody to Kik
Choice
And I think history will show
It's the right to fish
Steve the towing the line
McLendon
Like outright violence
See the Wild Wings
Express tan advocated for towards
Lgbtq
Community Focus
Like
We have a potential things going really badly
Turn out to be a really bad luck to have not made a decision
You could being allowed to play any
Platformers
He's not a very fun blanks
That would be a delight.
You see here just people trying to do the best I can
Situation
That's all it is
Is Alex and Laura Loomer just trying to get by
Tough times
Title Montano refusal to accept any responsibility for your actions
Intergenerational
Do you know Laura Loomer over
It's grown adult
Peace of the grave
It must be
Right
Website.com
We do are we on social media
Condemnation about
To share icon
No probably not
What was correct on iTunes and also places where podcast
Can be found wherever they are
I'm looking over this
Robert Barn
Probably
Is a lawyer events
3 years ago
Cuz he actually does have a degree
2:30 bar
Real name is Barney
Someone else
Does ident I'm sure not positive
About that but I'm going to go
He's never killed anybody
His client
Alex Jones
You probably
Alex