Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages and talk a little bit
About Alex
Joan
Have you ever played a stripper
Board game
Amazing love this episode
Vigo County Stratego strategy in the day
Are you almost here
Play Pandora
Catan like
I know I don't think I've ever played settlers
Boys I heard a lot about it about it
Cooperative
Board game doesn't involve strategy
I really think about it
Play Candyland a couple years back then go be funny
It was boring
You if it isn't even that I don't think it's just
Buffets. Lord licorice
Which is very
Too scary for kids
I don't know man I mean I played I played a bit of risk
My day but
The games like that that I
Chicago comedian he'll have people over to play games
I played a number of games that I
I can't remember the name of that I've enjoyed with him
Like what
I've enjoyed that that was a fun game
I don't know
2/3
I'd like to get more into board games
I would too Alright
Hey if you have any recommendations for us know cuz this is a lot about Alex Jones but not a lot about
Cool new games
That is great
I will be going over
To find out how
Short version to get you up to speed
So far weirdly in our last episode covering
He did get mad at a caller
Who wanted to say that Robbie Parker one of the parents of one of
The children who died
Sandy Hook
And responded I'm not going
You talk about the parents of dead children
Which was a huge plot twist
Bewhy where it goes
Say thank you
People who have joined up and are supporting the show
First of all
Thank you so much
Next Nicole
I'm a policy wonk
Next Thomas
Text Nathan
Yarnell policy walk
I guess so much Abaddon the despoiler
Thank you so much you are now
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean black cake
So much
These guys
Click the button
Also I don't want to disturb
Turn into two extended
You can buy
Shirts up at the top
I only bring this up
People who are posting pictures of themselves
In the shirts it blows my mind people in foreign countries
Walking around
A shirt for our delmastro blows my mind and it really at
I don't know
It's amazing
What's that
Let's listen to an out-of-context drop from Today Show
A little bit a little bit narcissistic Alex
Has a very narrow
What are you going to eat
January 15th 23rd
A little bit of a
Return
His rhetoric
That's it will probably take on
I wish
Who discovered list
Dangerous
He always says he never tells his writers what to do so that's great
I sent a lot of
What do you mean by that going to get a lot of reasons
To impeach a president
That will
Echo Park
Situation
Would you believe
That I didn't even
Don't care about that
He's written his own articles
But for Obama and then posted them on his website
And now
Other
Media things are reporting on report has a link
To Alex's story
Eva link
Articles
The idea of that headline is a bit like Grassroots people are like
Infowars
Writing an article
That becomes how Alex reports
The story
But he has created
Citizens call for Obama's
Kicking out office
When I report on the story that I stopped
This is
It is amazing
Believes that the media and everybody is
So against
The founding fathers
I hate George Washington
Grapes
But it's never been
This then
Okay what do we got here
Programma
Paul Revere
Foreign occupation Force.
If that were true
Yeah we hate Paul Revere wouldn't have sailed as a pilot
It didn't get picked up at all
What is The Chew
Had no idea what he's talking
Mad about
Read the trades
Is helping
I got this
To the comedy game a little bit
But it should tell you like The Depths that he means
To go to to get out
Television
Michelle it was a pilot it was getting shots around
Wasn't that a beautiful
Remember when we all used to get mad about
Chose
Brownstone
And now we're mad about
Crimes
Is the emoluments clause
Right-wing terrorism
Is it fair to say it's creepy.
Sliding along
Yeah that was a
More innocent time
What time is that on this January 5th
Episode Alex has introduced articles of him
Barackobama
And then spend
Most of the rest of the beginning of the show
Doing
A supplement
Infomercial
So
That's weird
Where do they usually go
What are you going to do if you don't have a gun to defend your supplements
I will take them
I thought that was a really weird way to open up for this
Next cut they're coming for you and the supplements
Probably true
Not the order of it but like this
Illegal gun sales
The first one regulated supplement Market
In terms of like okay let's get rid of dangerous things
Welcome artist
Because
Issue
In the MoMA
Goodwill regulate the supplemented
Yeah that's
That I doubt it
You probably not so
Run
In the more recent
Daisies
Which was Private labeling a lot of products that were created by dr. group in the global Healing Center
No he's not here
He is a chiropractor
And Connor
But before Alex got involved with doctor
He had another sponsor that is this dr. Wallach
Who also is not a.
After he has Veterinary
Beyond
Promote
He plugs
I've made the point for sat on a boat
Too much but
He's not human doctor
He's a veterinarian
From my alma mater University of Missouri
So I'm pretty sure that means that he's cool enough to give humans
Medical advice
Known as laetrile
Wichita
Doctors who
Clearance not be used
There's a considerable risk of serious adverse effects
From cyanide
Atrial especially after oral ingestion
Balance of late Riyal is there for unambitious Lee negative
The drug is most memorable is one of the things
Steve McQueen tried and is unsuccessful fight against terminal cancer
Only $40,000 a month for laetrile treatments that didn't
Just a little more
It doesn't cure
Along with you sure
Yeah goodnight Nobel Prize which is impossible
Nobel committee keeps nominees
Confidential
Unless
Mr Abbott says it out loud only other legitimate
Conclusion
You can come to is that he nominated himself for a Nobel Prize
In 1995 it was reported
Chelation therapy
To treat Harkins
Which is absolutely not an appropriate medical treatment
A heart condition that's very happy
No that is
He got into a little bit of trouble when a family member of one of his patients
Has complained that their relative died after Wallach told him not to go see a normal doctor
Is chelation detox
Proceed with effective
Chelation therapy for heart disease treatment has been
Condemned by the NIH and quote every scientific medical organization that has reviewed
A few years prior Bahamut kept on
15 million dollars in Damages
The family of a patient
Who died in his care is very similar
Dances with chelation being used to treat heartburn
It's unclear why while it didn't end up in a
Similar situation affected wallets victims
Wife never pressed charges and quote is also a disciple of
And Healthcare and had the body cream
Just hated that
Helps
Let's do this
Need to do a quack therapy
I love it I love it
3 weeks later
Entire thing
Deficient
And they don't know it
So he's mineral-rich supplements are all manner of illness natural lifespan
They should be living which is 120 to 140 years of age
Unfortunately quote
The Centers for Disease Control and prevention in Atlanta Georgia reported the results
13 year study
10758 American
Which failed to find any mortality benefits from vitamin and mineral supplements
The study found that even though supplement users smoke and drink less than non-users eat more fruits and vegetables and non-users
Live any longer than
So
You can't trust
Remember how every zombie movie starts with them going down I don't try
Why we have a point
Claims that even though there are these
Stop the show that these are full of crap
Cultures that have lights
Between 128
40 years
I don't remember the exact ones but I know the one of them
Quesarito
People live long because they drink when he calls quote glacier milk
Which
Which is
Water that's filled of colloidal minerals
People have looked into these ideas have speculated that he
Address to make
Making this stuff up
What is a dangerous lunatic
It is appeal to people is still in line with the Alex Jones at
Khalid suncity
Is early sponsor the show
Well explained things to sell his product and they're very similar to what Alex
Hope and resentment
Wala Conference of simplistic
Completely unproven next
Explanation for everything that ails you
Everything that's wrong with
Your health isn't heaven
It's all just mineral
You just gotta buy his pills and you'll be good as new
False
Hope
Alex does the same thing with Paulette
Distilling very complicated situations
Different
Perspectives and
Interest he turns that all into a battle between good guy Patriots
And evil overpowered globalist
Each of them hijacked
The part of your brain that
Wella koleston harnesses resentment
The fellas where
Most people
Brookfield
Love the medical field
Almost everyone's heads
Some sort of a bad experience with a doctor or at a clinic or have a loved one who had some sort of a medical copper
Acacia Energy
Suggest your batiks
Periods
Coincidence
It was actually the medical establishment
2 Dumbarton
Even care about treating you
Sounds right
If only
Listen to dr. Wallach
And giving you his medals then you wouldn't have had that bad experience
Uses that
Happened to People's resent
For their bags
In order to convince the
Decide
Alex does the same thing with the
We all have some
Complaints about the governor
Very natural
Government does a lot of shity things
The problem is that Alex takes those feelings
Uses them
The push people towards his own goal
As opposed to allowing them to fuel their disappointment and resentment towards the government
I let that grow into whatever form of Civic action they feel is appropriate
Again is a hijacking of normal fairly Universal feeling
For exploitative purpose
So
It makes total sense it easier on Alex's show doing this
It's weird that it takes up so much of the show though
Scituate
Where you have
One guy what does Checkmate Wonka's direct Mario
American flag
Dr. Mario guy is dr. Robotnik with his mean
Okay love it
Thanks to me that's your we've had this
This progression over
OurTime
Interjet
Gunn extremism
Wall-to-wall
Piers Morgan
Michelle
Navel gazing festival.of I'm so awesome
Nobody can stop talking about how great I am on the
The biggest store in the world
I don't know where that
This huge info
Verystream
Hello
Capitalizing on that
Absolutely
Also I study this
Company youngevity
Is a multi-level marketing operation
Yeah
It's multi-level marketing operation but Alex is helping him recruit people into specifically
Gazelle
I tell you what
I.
Theo Ratliff
NBA
What time All-Star Joe Ratliff
Someone else
Expect
Longevity
Top 20 blockers of all time at this point the NBA history
Tuesday skills
Anything like that
Vig
You can play 10 years longer than normal because of it
He played for
Isn't just 5c
You know
And then the rest
Are part of the practice
So if you're
Not
Moving along in your
Career you wind up
Only play
But a lot of it doesn't come down to like physical deterioration
Select amount of spots
It's Bora Talent Gap than it is a like everyone's body breaks down
From listening to this interview which were not going to
Stuff because I don't
But also because
His main point
It may be that he got surgery and then also started
Wallach's
Whatever benefits he gain from having a
Successful hip surgery
Correlation
Absolutely
I also found this
Which made me not want to
Nope
Have a great
And I thank you for all that
Theo Ratliff made for
It is
Play multi-level marketing company had a conference in Las Vegas
Any recorded message
People who got
EasyPay representative of
Is basically just like
Here's one of our celebrity
Yeah exactly
Is this is just a shameful display
Whatever
It's probably
A little bit less ethical than just like whatever
Just because he's luring people into a multi-level marketing
Disclose that
Associated
Youngevity
Just that he loves the product
Into the indication
Representative
I told you earlier
Our friend dr. Joel Wallach
It's not at so much a human doctor
Is he is a veterinarian
And that could be a problem
For most people
Well they're not supposed to have practice or give medical advice
People lose their licenses
Alex
Knows that if you look into him too much you'll find out that he's a veterinarian
So he has a rebuttal for that yeah
Termite.
You get better doctoring
From veterinarian
If you let me see if you followed this
You got the gears turning
Looking into this right
I've written down a little bit
So if I understand correctly
No better medals
Because their job
To get beef
From one place to another
Because of that
They won't mess with
Industry
I think yeah I made on a simplistic level yes but doctors don't care if they kill you because
Cuz you can't
Bear Market isn't predicated upon
Beef
Yes
Do cows die that is
Negative
To the beef Market
No
No I don't
I think he was working at a
Zoo at some point
Serta telling of his life
Every time that he was at
Just like
Cease on animals
12-year span he claimed
Thousand.
Wow you was working a real crave
Play making it up
Smite update
To do it that uses that is like soda
Defense
For his argument
Cause it's really just a mineral deficiency
1820 he's a mess
Man stealing
Stealing bodies
Did you watch
Dr. Wallach
Is Bucking
Crazy
But
There's
That is
Alex has been taking the
Beyond Tangy Tangerine
Other ones whose names I can't remember
Is catchy
What's that stuff that you sprinkle into water and it becomes Crystal Light Crystal Light
Crystal Light the bunch of rocks
Delicious give me some mineral supplement getting really Agro
To ask dr. Wallach
Why is it that I take your supplements
And I'll be getting aggressive
I've been turning into like I've been angry
And turn it into this world
Detox a couple times
Here is Wallach
Turn that question
Because
Your testicles Alex
Essential nutrients to make testosterone
Enough testosterone make an elephant happy
Give your body what it means
Can you make a note
Is becoming a man's man
Because
His balls are working
I don't like
Definition of
I think it's bad
I don't like it at all
I don't answer that's not a good
None of that was good
All of the things that
He said we're back
426 eggs
Maybe two
What did you see they did a Fox News
In front of
Just like a dive
And in front of every
Is apparently put
10 eggs
Just every single one they just rotated 10 did not every once and I don't know I don't understand what the point was
What's the point
Nobody could
Oh
Is it just sloppy
Okay
He's in front of
Everybody while you're interviewing a very weird
It's entirely possible
Dee's wolf
House of headaches
It's entirely possible
Is that a restaurant doesn't
I wanted to say and that is
Pitstop fresh
George on our first episode we ever did
Tell us that it's a takeout Netanyahu
It's all over.
In the intervening
Two-and-a-half years almost now
We've never heard him explicitly tell us another time
Depressed
That's the sound I feel like I should make just
He was a little bit more confident this time then end up going into a prayer
That we weren't satisfied.
I want to hear that prayer
The guns
Guns going to be taken with it's time to pray
Because the largely boss of the show is that dr. Wallach
Song for his
Vertical
Going on here
The story doesn't evolve far past
I have decided
That I'm going to put In Articles of impeachment
Well he crows a whole lot about the idea that the founding fathers set up the government
In such a way that citizens
Write the articles of impeachment that the
Politicians can pick them up and run with them
I don't want to look into that if you want to believe that
I wouldn't want it not to work that way
Barack Obama has brexit
Where are you
Around him
He discusses
Common Sense gun
Reform
That you would like to push
Through
Like to work on
Alex plays better the press conference
She kept stopping
Did you can't even hear it over him
Being combative and yellow
Seems like there's some
Coded language
Urban
Pause
The speech to get a little bit of yellow
Whatever
Very thrilled
During that press
And I think this to Alex
Hardly stop smiling
Fine
Characterization
People in the real
Yeah that was what you would want to
Part right
I question whether when you think the real talking about like maybe Drudge
Fox News in that
I don't even think he likes Fox News
To pick this up at like 8 and PR New York Times
Whatever
His analysis of this is largely just Obama and Biden
Can't wait to get their hands on the gun
Are using these kids as a human shield
And
Pretty gross
Really cover a whole lot of it
Because it's happening
As he's doing the show
Deposits
I think maybe the producers stepped in and already huge
You just realize themselves
We could have cut Clips I can talk about this later let's not do this as a tactic yarn
Battle against the globalist
Richard said I didn't have anything planned other than
This is a pretty crazy thought
Around
Yes I want that
No one's making you
Greenlight that was terrible
I guess
Alex
Thinking about that day Alex
Alex's Sunday shows are such trash
Why not just do that they're Alex runs operation
K*** he has
Literally own limits
You can do whatever you want
It would be pretty amazing cuz even try to be Johnny Carson and then he would go
Here's how we're going to tie this knot right now and start a fire only f****** comedian who would come on his show is f******
Nick DiPaolo
Roanoke Regular Show Monday through Friday
He's never going to get that up that's the cash cow
Alex Jones as Johnny Carson
What that show now
If we could turn this country around
You got to look forward to
Country rap
Yeah
Rambling and talking freely
Expressing something that I find variance
To live in a polite Society
Good
SunTrust
We should all aspire
In peace
Happiness
Why his version of it is really problematic
To this clip its follow his train of thought
And how politeness is achieved
You're going to call you
Okay
Text
Is
Using camo
Expressing their reason ideas politeness is really only achieved by the
Threat of mortal violence
I don't want to live in that world
Compton
Everything you do is predicated on your fear of somebody
You might have to
Yeah I would rather live in a world
Where
People recognize that it's a much more pleasant
Be nice to people
And you enjoy your life a lot more when people are nice
Can you can
Just sort of I don't know externalize that and
Apply that to other people's feelings and realized
If it makes you feel good probably makes them feel good
Why not
In a very polite
Happy place
I can hear a happy elephant amount of testosterone
Yes lot of eggs
I don't know
Accidentally
Express
Describing is
Hopie and state that I would
Never one
Using to justify it has
Zero resemblance to what he thinks it
Is what he said
No
Nothing to do with
Polite
Lake Society
Medieval Times
Nope
Feelings
Text Johnny Carson watch
Globalist taken care of
Magnanimous
Coming up Alex
Some people
Hardcore
I'm talking about
I could even argue right now that's
I don't think clothing dictates your fascism level
I think this is so fascinating
The idea that he he's like
High School
It makes me think that Glenn Beck has
Something
Two decent set
Ludacris monster
But the idea that he would never respond to Alex's overtures with
Working it is breaking up
I know better
I know better than to accept an overture from this man
Wants to be
Separate from Alec
The same way
Alex
The same way Alex
You know where the
People who criticize him
Call Hera
Is Alex
Crazy fight back
Going back to business model doesn't work out if they get along
Otherwise
Clear
Alex starts rambling
About
Athenian democracy I guess
Arab Tire racer
Opportunity to learn about
Mythical figure
Democracy
Black Ops
So it wasn't
Is the plant manager that Muhammad transitive property
Well I know it's not the visit
We have no idea
The power relation of the hammer to the
Or the stores
Perfect DPS rating
For each of the
I have no idea
Did a vacuum that's a good
Version of The Grecian
Atlantic
Democracy
Little bit I don't care to give you a lecture about the difference between various
City-states
In-depth into that right now but
The blame for the situation
Indians are primarily concerned with her being blasphemy
People in the Public Square
I put him on trial for it
But he's found guilty is given the chance
Choose his own punishment should be given free meals for life
Going to kill you
Even after being sent
It was very clear that they didn't really want to kill him
Totally cool if you just left
Issues
He believed so strongly in the rule of law
Fuse to save his own life by leaving
Since his death was what the law decided was his own
Yeah he was a
He was just the real a****** bothering Everybody by asking a question
Everybody
Prevalence conceptions
So
Assholes
Tubi
4 people
Try not to
Kill you
Still have to go through
It's pretty bad is a real level of
You know
Grandiosity
Alright we find you guilty of last
What should your punishment be
Feed me for life
Testicles God bless
Answer ASAP. The only things anyone even knows about his life come from Fairly unreliable sources the Border online
Existing most likely entirely as oral tradition for about six hundred years before they were ever written down
It's thrown off a cliff
Haven't been accused of stealing a cup from a temp
Other sources say that the reason he was killed is because he got really mad at the crowd in Delta Edison she was given
I wouldn't give him any money
Calling the delphian quote slaves of Olga
Because of his great offense to the Dignity of
The city of Delphi
He would bring great to the reputation by Taco
S*** about them wherever you want
Someone suggested
Priest
We plan to the cup in his baggage
Cassette ASAP
When did Elsa
Took a stop to the cliff
From what you was to be
I called on the music
And then threw himself off
Yeah
I mean tonight you're going to be in Rockford
You got time
Yep yep
The religious traditions of Delphi
Calling the ritual sacrifices which
Amanda's body
Didn't have much
Herbalife
It's not entirely clear if any of them are actually literally true
His doll past announcers
600 years of oral tradition
Whatever the case there's some sort of the mythical reality
To the stories but no real reality
A large piece of how this story was used
Was to create an explanation
A subsequent violence
Against
Adelphi
Within the oral tradition these events were not just bad luck or an isolated War they were the consequences of Delphi
Immorally killing Aesop
The entire Affair takes on a cosmic importance
When you study oral tradition
You find a lot of assorted
Stories transform to fit stereotypes anarchist
Are you seated in the story of Aesop's death is
It becomes the story of a scapegoat that it
Blaine's
These
Incendies Wars
He became
His own face
But it's really funny
To see this little boy
See that he believes that lure is true throughout all of me
It's so Waurika truth
Get out of this little this framework
You know of of just thinking
Oldtimers
Kind of fascinating
In the way that
Because we know he can't read
Fatty fatty
Anything that said
The old whiskey bar
Patriots of old
Boy
Joel Wallach
Theo Ratliff come in
Can I just
Confirm
Glacial milk
Glacier milk
Okay
That does not sound like something
I do actually I think
If you just went to a glacier and
Belk have had great batting ever
Strawberry chocolate milk strawberry milk milk milk
Almond milk is okay
It's probably the only one I've had that's terrible
Didn't looking at banana milk and not
Kicking it out of my
Nesquik
It wasn't good flavors
Sky Zone show
Infomercial
He has another guy
Is so weird
He's completely transformed his narrative
The course of a few weeks
So now what
Context and understanding which were able to
Because we've spent the time
Forget it
Bez to not even recognize what he's
He's done
After Sandy Hook Alex Russell for a little while without the shooter was probably staged by the globalist
Even Tiffany's 2012 they were a actors there
Kind of water
You need to be a vent tube
Be suspect
Because it's a globalist are behind the shooting that goes a long way
Navigation to take his gun
Narrative pivots
Becomes nothing short of a Gunn paranoid do p*** kind of thing for weeks
With every person who comes on the show being people like Larry Pratt Stewart Road
They show up concert
Credibility to Alex's screaming about how the big one is coming
Dwayne The Rock
This Patrick Coleman
Starting a petition to get Piers Morgan deported over
Of course
Vale because Pierce played along
The real combination is Alex going on a mortgage
B-36
That narrative play.
Exactly as it was supposed to
Alex's penetrated the mainstream news
Everyone
Is just more proof
He's actually right
That is now fully implanted
So the narrative has to Pivot again
Instead of water in the gun paranoia
Alex is able to build further upon the block
That he's
Created in order to get to his
This is a classic game of what I would describe as if this is true what month
If the globalist
Sage Sandy Hook it must also be true that they're doing that to come
If they're coming for Alex
Two guns what else must be
It must also be true that the only thing that week
You can do is okay
Impeach Obama
This sure feels completely
In these couple of days
And you see it with these completely different gas
Focus on Obama and getting him out of office
Is Bang the Drum of the impeachment
Screaming over his Prescott
Gun paranoia he can call Pratt or
What do you need to push Financial collapse narrative
Call Gerald Celente
Peter Schiff
And now that the theme of the show is change to wheel of God from Wheel of guns get ready to use your gun
To we should impeach the president
He has a disgusting attempt at a publicity
Stop with the Obama Phone Lady
He's called in the most Obama
Reverend
James David Manning
He is using this passage
This is very interesting the way that these narrative build upon each other
Knows well enough to jump off a pivot before it becomes stagnant
It's very urgent
I've been waiting for Manning to come back up on me
The show because that's the last time we talked about him
He's found himself
A little bit of trouble
I'm sexually harassing a former student
Is Outlaw School
Someone who is conservative beliefs
2 years younger than
She was 18 when the tape was recorded but sat in it manager
Discusses how we started having sexual feeling
When she was 14
He talks about wanting to pull up her skirt
Incredible body
Editing a portion of our episode out
Because I couldn't find any sources that I would
Consider credible that were reported
So I thought they were
Smallest possibility
There was someone doing a really really good Reverend Manning
Impression
The post didn't
Expensive
Location of Manning's Outlaw Church
And the verdict is
And the picture of it is much darker than it
Even as dark as a 70 year old man with one of his former students absolutely is
That's very dark
Manning
Real tile
Idaho
Attendees of Manning School
Church
A picture firmly forms
Because of his position wielded unbelievable level of power
Which is more than happy to have
The first thing to consider is that parents would put their
Kids in the school are almost certainly members
His church
Almost
Manning is the most Godly person in the world
And Humanity's only
He's created Messianic thing about himself
Demonstrative pretty clearly Eclipse that we played where you yell
From the pulpit
You have a distorted view of
This guy
F*****-up situation
Use abusive punishments
Like you're in the case of a student you locked in the church basement in the dark for 3.
Yeah
What does wasn't allowed to eat
On the first day
The minutes drag.
In the dark
Alone in the
F***** up
Punishment
Because they believed he was infallible
Great great
Is the Arpaio of God
Incidentally what that stood was being punished
That girl didn't get punished
Coincidence
F***** up f***** up
Slept with underage girl
Just leave
It doesn't guy put them in a bucket
3 days
Jesus Christ
Yeah
F***
The number to read about this HuffPost article
Are terrifying
Whether it's through the kinds of
Biblical punishment
The employees
And the kids can't lie
Because their parents believe that the school's Headmaster is infallible
And he's made a practice of convincing parents to
Disown their children when they question
Just think about the situation that puts me
They can either put up with literally whatever Manning wants to do to them
Or they can risk be disowned and expelled
Becoming homeless and high school dropout
And that's not hypothetical either
That's literally what happened to multiple students who believed
The tape of Manning sexually harassing his former student was real
Joshua
Who Manning baselessly accused of being gay
Kicked out of the school and became a high school dropout
And then later I also to that guy's brother Isaiah
Then Derek Mills was kicked out for refusing to end his friendship with the Isaiah
Debussy in Flex on these people their own fault
After he kicked the students who believed that that was
Is real he said this from the pulpit
Tarifa song that's the guy
Friends I've been LED down a path
Destruction by following him
Many of you tonight do not have your children with you because of the LIE perpetrated
False doctor tape perpetrated by Hassan
From the pulpit
Yap
You say many of you have lost
Because
Your kids are liars
He goes on to call the students in theater
Expelled
The Huff Post article includes this endlessly
Flea terrify
Quote. The former students watched on their computers and phones horrified at the idea of their parents
Siblings
Intermittently participating in Clapton
Eggman calls their children
Terrifying
Also one article I read I can't confirm
Another article
They said that they spoke to
Church members
Who said that
Ask them to
Do s*** in bags
And leave them at Galen business
In retaliation
He has himself to spread poop
I would question whether that's or if it was him protecting about what he was
So
This is gross
Cult leadership
Positive HuffPost covered it and hopefully word
Dangerous lunatic who's abusing his congregation
A Zone in Richmond
Four former congregants told HuffPost
Decided a few years ago
To the church
That's when he started imploring followers to give him access to their Bank
He told them they didn't know how to manage their money and that he would take better care of it
Which is something that cool pastors do
What makes all this extra scary is it in 26
What the hell man in my tree
Respond if his grip on his flock was ever truly threatened
He owned about an old about a million dollars and utility bills
The back taxes
A church was in danger of being
Foreclosed on
Desperation man made a video threatening to barricade himself inside the
Search with kids from
Community
He said the standoff could turn violent quote worse than Wounded Knee
It's unclear if he was imagining
Himself
Lakota in that analogy
It's clear that you was sending a message
But if anyone tries to come take his building was perfectly fine using the children of this congregation
Is human shield
Particular importance of today's episode
Alex Jones spends a lot of time talking about children
What he's talking about gun regular
It's a gross way for Alex to attack the idea that there are used to affected by gun violence
What's an orange favor of gun can
Control Elisa
The guy Alex called demon eyes Obama
Guy who was literally threatening
To use her children
Shield
Just a few years later and at the time of this interview this recording
He was actively traumatizing students at his b*******
It's a
Massive level of inappropriate that Alex
This guy doesn't like
What's a super inches
Did right now to demonize Obama
Who can help me with that
We just listened to
Meet a lot of
Really bad thing
About rubber matting
Which
That's terrible
God bless you sir
Alex
You shouldn't feel a connection with this guy
Stop the show
Who you've never heard of
Unconstitutional Federal
Cool earlier Alex on the show it said that these people
Steve
He's rapping
Texas you look into people who really fight
Dyed-in-the-wool
These are people that lived in Texas
He was born in
New York grew up in upstate
Rochester
I hate every
Things about Steve that I want to tell you about
Well that's number one
Number two
He won his seat in the State House of Representative
Texas election with no Democrat running
He only was up against the candidate from the libertarian party and I truly want either
In 2014 he decided to give up his
District 15 in speaker
16th District
But lost ultimately showing at the support he was received most of which came from
Party
Wasn't enough to get him back into a
Possibly more important
Elevated ALT
House of
In 2018
Then ran once again for the
Giving up back in 2014
He Texas
House district 50
He wants ended up right where you left off
Just considering how high
House of Representatives
How they don't have Turbo
He literally just wasted everyone's time and money because of misguided ambition
Government
Don't know if he is
He is not interested in
Unlike the nuts and bolts of writing good
Whynotbi
An office now because of this
Significant donations
Supportive multiple far-right political action
Heeded their former speaker
Joe Straus
If you was to close
To the center
Course Hardline anti-immigrant
Islam
I need a lot of money
To make sure the conservatives once eaten that election work not
The types
Would be against Trump
Muslim ban the bills flying around to dictate who could use what
These political action committees wanted Warriors
And Steve Tok was willing
To be that to get back in office
In 2018
Great job.
What is groups
Texas right to life
Which gave toast 17,000
$500 for
Incycle Texas right to life received
China criticism
For turning on anti-choice
They supported for a long time
My favorite new options
Who were crazy far-right
Text support
His kind of lost their way
That's unfortunate.
To do
That's a quote from Paul Workman
Former representative of Texas's 47th District
Workman literally Champion legislation that would require women to get a sonogram before receiving an abortion in hopes of making her
Her experience that would change your mind
He supported every choice bill ever introduced including one that would increase the license
Requirements
Providers the goal of which was pretty explicitly
Play the first time to clinics
Close
The political action
Committee that donated seven
1500 dollars
Steve Toth
Thought work
Middle-of-the-road on abortion
Well I mean if you take a look at the Alabama just pass
I guess anything but aside from the death penalty right
Performing an abortion price
I'm trying to give you a sense of what kind of politics
These people who are funding him we're looking
Alabama Que
Interstate agreement for whatever
In 2014 the Texas Freedom Network wrote piece about huskies tofu
Was too extreme
A Texas Republican
A completely fabricated
Crusade against the Texas school district
Curriculum management tools
Complaining that their life
Comes workload anti-American anti-christian
Also the article includes this
Also tells a ridiculous story
To promote his opposition
Sex education that includes information about birthday
During the 2013 legislative session
So hot and bothered Parenthood sex education
Glass
Perception that the girl in the car later
Legislative budget cuts
The quote
Does women's health program
Electrical tens of thousands of low-income women
Family Planning
Shouldn't
Mean that
That they should have stayed in the sex extrication class
No I don't think
Finish the part of the class
I don't think anyone is getting real horny during Planned Parenthood sex education talks
Education talk
Boulder City super hard right
Sex education
Teacher told me that having
Sex without a condom
Put in your hair
Into a vat
Nuclear waste
Condom with
Putting I
Glove on your hand when you put it into a
F****** thing
Vaginas are nuclear White
Exactly
Steve Toth was too extreme for the Texas Republican party in 2014
Not anymore
We're not going to listen
I like to play a new game called
The GOP or icy
Pic quotes
It's really just a case of Alex Jones bring in a lunatic State politician
Auto Show do dog and pony show them agree with his ideas to let some kind of governmental credibility
The things he's putting out
It's mostly just Alex yelling about how they should arm teachers
Steve agreeing
Woodstock
Do anything about that Italy Texas House of Representatives
Steve
Toth Assange
Just sort of like Alex has a government representative on because
You know
Impeachment starts in the house
There is Oki Carolyn state government
Gotcha interview
But then
Cybersecurity
Thankful for that
And very sophisticated
You got fish
University computers
Really takes
Narcissistic swing-for-the-fences
Bulshit
This is
He been complaining other days about the website
He's very specific about because they're trying to upgrade
Text cuz they're trying to update
A new version like Infowars 2.0
They don't have that great of an IT staff sucks
Denial-of-service attack
Help
Create the idea that
Obama's afraid of Alex putting out articles of impeachment
Got on stage for the press conference
Because they couldn't handle the idea of being able to respond
To his at whatever I was saying
Sofa
Exact same thing
Imagine
Denial-of-service attacks
And hackings and stuff like that just
B his narrative
That's what he's doing
A hundred percent
Crazy
Alex loves
To talk movies
To be fair to say that
You generally misses the point
I mean
Let's
Asia mandamus
Is the good guy
Oftentimes
In stories of heroes and villains
Discerning
Which is which
Movie theater
Comic books are bad but it turns out comedies are also bad for now
So Alex is expressing he feels like he's in
In Groundhog Day
Because you just keep seeing the globalist
Metal whenever Wonderlic
Here's what I would say the point of that movie is that
Bill Murray
Yes and the only thing that gets him out of the time Loop is
Not being an ass
Realizing he's been living his life completely wrong
For others is
Actually a much better way to live
And then he gets to go to the next day finally wants
Grows through the Despair and
Utility of killing himself
Elvis is Alex really feels
Like he's living Groundhog Day
Consider the message
YouTube that movie
Maybe
You're an a******
Bill Murray
No no
Interview that
Bill Murray
Play trapped in that time Loop for like Millions
Yeah yeah
It doesn't give me much hope for Alex
To the other side
But it would be immediate for us
Any other day
Fascinating
Along with his inability to differentiate truth
Fiction
He also has no idea how to engage with the message
Do not
Like anybody who
Groundhog Day would get
It's the only way it's her purse Improvement
He leaves the timer
Stephen tobolowsky
Great
Love it
Sew-ins next clip Alex Goes to call
Just because I think we might have found
Somebody from Africa Alex
Happy that's right Alex
The good part
Yeah I know that's bad that's bad start
Back
Afrikaner is
Starting
You can tell is probably
Believe what you might describe as a racist stuff at Montreal
But what's interesting is it called isn't about that
The extent of his
Just
Flippant
Actually wants to talk about
You mentioned your web service have been going down well
You're not the only one so to speak I am a web developer and researcher and I'm here to tell you that the Illuminati is
Back online
Breaking news
Now what do I mean by that
Goodguys member of the Illuminati card game
Okay interesting thing is this card Game Spot It Out
Online game
Okay
Illuminati
GameStop
Steve Jackson's games
What's rated R
And the dates are that was on that server
The game was never supposed to get out according to Steven
Don't do that
You look
Very
How are
People
Give me Miss South Africa
I don't know how
This is
And I don't need to card game is one of the most
Perfect conspiracy things
In the world I'm so glad that this dumb race is South Africa
I need the card game itself is
Illuminati plans
Use lesser Magic on the bus
It is our people this.
It's amazing
The short version is how's it goes
Illuminati is a card game that was created
Games of 1982
The goals game is take on the role of the speaker
Society which goes on to take over the world
There's a very successful game of the circles that played massively complicated
In the early 80s
And it spawned expansion packs have been released over the years the most recent
Coming out 20
The concept of the game started out with Steve Jackson
Considering creating an adaptation
Robert Anton Wilson
Illuminati
Trilogy
But that would be
B2 convoluted
Confusing so I'm not even going to get that shot
Mostly convoluted
It's not as confusing
Play that bud
I'd love it really hard to find
The main one
I'd like to shop
Jackson realized
To do
Adapt
The illuminatus trilogy
He could take the basic
She's like the notion of Grant
Conspiracies being Bhai
Everything
And use that as the
Concept
His game
Approved
Be a viable jump-off boy
Conspiracy theory worlds together something
Details
He created quite a bit of a client
The Nerds loved it but have such high praise
I felt like his work was
Just enough so he couldn't
He was very mad about
Yeah
Illuminatus Trilogy as a work of satire
It's bent
To try to make fun of and mock
The patterns of reason
Chrissy Theory
And Jackson's card game
Extension of that
The cards are over-the-top by Design
Naturally cuz it's parody
That means
When you
As as always
Face when you make a
Satire
Conspiracy theory
1994 expansion
Impact that's called New World Order
They're pretty wild in Heinz
One of them is the terrorists
The Duke car
The visual on that card is a nuke being shot at
The Twin Towers
Pretty similar to what
CIO with 9/11
The game was made right after the first World Trade Center bombing in 1993
Free
It might not be as crazy as I am
Just on 1st
Glance right
Nearest used that card and a couple others
Steve Jackson new was coming into this game is proof
It's lesser Magic
Tricks
The World Trade Center
Trade Center bombed the first time
That would be bombed
Nobody's better than the first world trade
Play fast and loose with
The original that came out 1980
Car came out in 94
So when conspiracy theorists
Talk about these cards
Usually talk about it having a hit came out in 82 and predicted 9/11 when that car came out
The First World Trade Center bombing
It's all these cheap gameplay
Also
Conspiracy theorist
Are less prone to use the following cards
To make their argument
About predictive programming
What does Godzilla
Bigfoot
Count Dracula
Potato
Yeah yeah that one probably would do the job
Flying saucers
Literal Gremlins
The hammer of Thor
Crabland
Hitler's book
Love it
Set
Robot monster
Choose to play as
Your secret society
Your Illuminati are the Servants of Cthulhu I ever lost it
But now I know who your plan
The game is a parody of conspiracy
Some extent even take shots at itself
One of the cards in the deck is
Trading Card Game
And features a suspicious man opening his trench coat to reveal cards
Inside that he's selling
I've never played it but all the reviews I've read make it
You seem like a really fun game that uses interesting strategy
The elements
And it's one
For Origins Awards
The first of which was being the
The best science fiction
Board game award in 1982
So it's not like this is
Some kind of accident
We got out like I is
The race of South Africa
That idea is f******
I want this game so bad
I would love to track it down
Also Alex should know better than to say that this car game is in
Anyway a real Illuminati
The game
You think there's a card in the deck
The agent in place card
I was just the games version of an infiltrator or spy for your Illuminati group
The picture on that card there's a
Striking resemblance
To Alex Jones notice
Coincidence
It could be a winking joke on Steve Jackson
Apart cuz
The card it came out 1994
And that point Alex was on Austin local access
In Jackson does operate out of Boston
So it's possible that he would have been aware of Alex and Olivia wink
But my problem is that the car looks a lot like a later day Alex
Not a lot like 94
He looks like he's chubby present
More than
Pat
So I don't know I think it's probably just a coincidence
That take conspiracy people have built a new wrinkle 12
There is no like
Conspiracy theory that easy predict
He did predict that Alex
Was going to be fat with a
Eddie's talking into a mustard the phone
I just received Jackson games getting nothing to do with the
Illuminati card game
Board game
Award
82 and the raid didn't happen until March 1st
The decks involving all the cards
Conspiracy theorist
We're still four years away
From being made when the raid went down
Itself
Direct on called Illuminati
What are the operators of that board was a hacker named blue blanket
The track down stolen document
Information about BellSouth
Dude that bulletin board at another one run by Blankenship
The court documents reflect the agent-based a search warrant on
On the fact that
BellSouth computer system
Something 9/11 BellSouth document was a sensitive
Arabic
Computer hackers were tempting
Utilize the decryption
Procedure
Computer programs included the defense department
And these hackers were soliciting password
So that the decryption procedure could become operator
Misunderstanding that happened in the investigation however
Blankenship Ram this message
Message board for Steve Jackson games
Up and also called
Investigate
However
Message board for
He saw this greeting and got the wrong idea about
Greetings mortal
All right of course this is this is
Drag the FBI agent reading this just like
People
You've entered the secret computer system of the Illuminati the online home of the world's oldest and largest secret
Steve Jackson games Incorporated
Call God cuz he didn't understand the humor of the site
Foley thought that was an indication that this message board run for
Was wrapped up in the 9/11 documenting malicious hacking with the game company being a fake front business
Such a farce
The fact Blankenship was an employee
Steve Jackson games didn't help the game company got included in the raid and their computers and materials were
From there
Everything went to s***
The investigators have created a mess
Because they failed to do their homework
They have the ability to learn that the
The seizure of the Illuminati bullet
Board included
Private and public electronic communications
The seizure of which was not within the scope of their warrant was a breach of the Privacy protection
By the next day after the raids
His stuff back
Which experts estimated should have been able to been copied if needed
And Richard H and no more than within 8 days
He would not get his things back
Until late June 1990
Approximately 3 1/2 months later which was a huge problem for him
Cuz They confiscated all this s***
Yeah
Steve Jackson ended up suing the Secret Service and women
I got $50,000 in statutory damages and $250,000 in lawyer
The judge did find that the rated ultimately not cause financial hardship
However
The reasoning was that the company has been in
Bad financial shape
The time did actually raise their profile
Considerably
Plus Steve created a game based on the radar was selling quite well
So they just decided it was a wash
Knockout Prophets
Catastrophic
50000 statutory damages is
Not enough
Guilty as charged with a crime
For nothing
Maybe but I also kind of suspect that Nom charging might have had some
Nothing to do with how bungled this raid was
The objective was it stolen 911 document even if they were able to establish the blank
Stolen
Which I'm not sure they ever did
Taking this to trial Beyond
F****** night
Yeah so there's like wash your hands
And how the rate
It has nothing to do with the Illuminati card game or the government trying to stop him
From getting their seats
In reality the court documents make it clear that agent.
No investigation about Steve Jackson games
Incorporated although a reasonable address
Only several hours
Mr. Jackson would have cooperated in the investigation
They f*** this up top-to-bottom they do nothing
Yeah
Very clear that they didn't even know they made games
Let alone different Illuminati game free
Also just ask your honor in my client's defense
They're really bad
The defense
Also just to be totally clear about this
The color is a time like
At the time of the raids
Games was working on it about to release a rope called
Cyberpunk
Northrup's is an acronym for a generic Universal
Play RPGs on bulletin boards with this guidebook
McGruff cyberpunk
Dragon Ball Z
There is
Is this message board that I went to on an
Angelfire
Complicated role-playing
These groups the generic Universal role-playing system was a response to the idea that a lot of these games are really fun but they do
You played in certain
Like D&D could only be played as this fantasy
You know that other ones were generic Universal
Developed by Steve
For all
So different types
Of role-playing
What cyberpunk role-playing
Adventures
Straight up
Office culture
You're just
You're rolling
If you bake small
You could do that this is a cyberpunk horatian of this that was being worked on
Interfere with a release
Confusing with the Illuminati card
The card game came out 8 years earlier
But ultimately
Satirist
For sure conspiracy isn't that juicy when it's just a guidebook for a
Punk roleplay
Yeah that probably does
No
Spinosaurus
Like whenever there's these sorts of
Turtles of
I guess you'd call it
Conspiracy lower
The better story behind
To in order to make their fake store
Yeah cuz that's a good
Government
Totally
It's a comical level of ineptitude from the agents
Or some s*** like
Enough material for a movie
But the scene is
Yes
Completely
Screwing it up
But that doesn't stop Alex from
Atomic bomb
Probably let's go
Atomic monster
Like this card
That shows the one of the Twin Towers getting hit
That's all
Proved
What is at the border for entry
Conspiracy
Solo
Alex
From someone
Via the Bebe
DC the British Broadcasting Company
40 times a day
So this is also part of that Darcy
Statistic aggrandizement
It goes along with the you know the government's targeting me as soon as I put out this Obama in
Impeachment thing
It's kind of a way of focusing that save energy
Of the navel-gazing I was on Piers Morgan and using it
Facilitate
The anti-obama narrative
Each man narratives it is
Recurrent theme of the
The show
Backhoe
Didn't
But it sure does make him look
Good when he take
Julian the Collies like
I could have just
15 minutes
Ordering any commercial break
There's no reason to do except demonstrate your audience
I'm in demand
Is the BBC
But they still work
So far just b i TV
Right
Remember how I told you to
Women's Health
Texas
Because of his book
Story about
People f****** yeah after health class
Be like you know sex education
I think that's a stupid thing for him to
To think
Yes
And it blew my mind
That Alex
Later in the same episodes
That's insane
What
That's a nut
Looking at
I'd like the bisexual
I mean I remember it
Spare Laguna
Universal
Yeah
It's a teacher's are uncomfortable
Questions
Piece of paper and then handing it to are like putting it in a bucket so nobody knows who is at
It's not a horny making experience
F***** up Alex is looking at it
That class is deeply uncomfortable
Be completely bizarre
Interpretation
Sex education
Existing with
These two people on the same show
We're like
Toast with expressing this analysis
Very weird
Exact
He's in Texas
Rochester
Maybe it's just
Must be
Different there
Discomfort about sex education
That means that almost every Coming of Age movies
Except in the Midwest
This is where I
In this episode
Alex
Goes from there is
Really weird
And I like down for this
Adam Lanza
Control
Record now
Try to buy gun five times
Shop
What is mental illness was in the health record
Private dealers
That's a weird train of thought
Yeah
First of all
There's a lot is a lot in a couple seconds there
Gun shows where they don't sell to you if you look like an illegal immigrant
Does Adam Lanza look like an illegal immigrant do that what he seems
I don't know what he's expressing
Conversation
The very weird and Felons are innocent
Are you going to talk about Criminal Justice Reform
I'm here for that
Criminal Justice Reform
Starts
Giving felons guns after they get out
Esorts
In the day if you got prison while you were holding the shotgun when you got out of prison
That seems like a bad policy.
She got that from
I think that's from like old western tv shows
Baby yeah that's like that's like a story of somebody
Sleeping one off and then they still get their shot got back from the f****** local sheriff
The prison in the first place
A little baby that is a casein like in
I don't know
I don't I don't like
What he's probably saying with the most
Cuz I don't
Ross 280
Felony drug possession
They shouldn't be stripped of the right town
Brett there's
There's not room for conversation there but
Alex saying they don't sell
Like illegal immigrants
Bonkers unacceptable
Very weird that he doesn't elaborate or illegal immigrants
About saying look like
Like a hahaha
He was going over
Obama's
Talking about this
You're seeing a little bit of code here
Liberty talks about his gun issue
Weird
Little bit of coded language
It keeps coming up
It is strange
Almost like
The guns are there
Boy I can't
Responsible for
So is this next clip Alex has a
The plaintiff
Stop school shooting
Of course we know it's armed teachers
Why not
It's armed teachers
Idea of who the arm
The teachers
You just explained
Imagine the nightmare scenario of a teacher shooting up a school
Hand
Teacher accidentally shooting
Brandishing a
Terrible
Just the idea of you
And then a guns on the table
F*** you
Also the idea of arming the
Knox
Discuss that other than to say
Dave daubenmire
By my height
Every football coaches
Teachers who are weirdos
Maybe it's the same
He's a f****** Luna
Bluetick
Is this narcissistic
Trend
Fracture
He's doing this fake
Denial of service
In this next clip
You finally gets around to playing some of the clips
Of Obama's
Speech
And Alex becomes convinced that Obama is talking about
What's 47
Assault by tyrants on Liberty
This will be difficult
Probably covestro
But because
They want to Jennifer
Or higher ratings
Or revenue for themselves
I'll do everything I can
The block any Common Sense refer
Make sure nothing changes whatsoever
The only way we will be able change is it
Nevermind
Ba bar
Bob
That is that is a lunatic level grandiosity
I mean
Yeah probably I don't know is Larry Pratt
Is necessarily on Obama's radar
You probably not the president
Please talk about ratings he's probably talking about Rush Limbaugh
Yep probably not talking about Alex Jones Glenn back
In terms of relevant at this point 2013
Alex doesn't rank with those other people that he's
Just because
Obama is describing behavior that is similar to what Alex does
Exactly what Alex's
Does not mean
You thinking of
I think I think
Obama
Has probably never cared about Alex
He's not
How awesome would it be
Get high with Obama and watch Dreams of My real father.
About Obama's dad being frank Marshall Davis
That would be amazing
Observe
Think it's important to point out here
Completely narcissistic
And making everything about himself
Intentionally
It works for the
He makes it very clear that
He hasn't watched
Any of these clips
Isn't know what
Is happening on whatever the staff place
I'm sorry I didn't mean to
Does that start
You know what I find
Does
Correct
Picks out
Going to
Do what
I mean Obama said other people
Yeah
He knows that's what he
Please do it
Right
Like he
Possibly
Because of the only way we're going to make progress
Constituents
Understand the issue
It's like
If you weren't doing that
Stuff
If the people your listing work
Doing that
They wouldn't be the first
Names are out of your mouth
Do you know what I mean I think you could probably rub but that by saying
Like the reason that I thought of those people is
Cuz they're the people who are demonized in the enemies
The globalist
Or something but even though flying back is generally
Globalist shill
I know what you mean
I think
I think it's actually
Correct
It would be a nail in the coffin
I see what you said
Variax
Alex is getting really defensive
About being on Piers Morgan and yelling at them
Express
Because it wasn't a good space
Kind of debate
Because
Deserved it knows
I wasn't there that conversation
Now
Healthy Start
King
About it
He decides that he's got
Come up with an example of a
Conversation negotiations debate
Where where is mine goes
How are you doing today
First of all his neighbors
Don't do it
F*** it it's Jessie
The debate
No
This is actually conversation I've had
Specific means
Absolutely
I want to make notes
Considering converting is land to agricultural use to skirt property taxes
He's got to be talkin about acres of land
He's working with cuz otherwise
Secondly
He's absolutely talking about a conversation
You definitely had with his neighbor Jesse about committing tax fraud
According to Texas Comptroller's office in order to qualify
The land must be
Currently devoted principally to agricultural use
Agricultural land must be devoted to production data level of intensity that is generally accepted in the local area
That seems unlikely again
Bee plant but local
A little bit honey
Tiny bit
The land must have been devoted to agriculture production for Italy
7:05
Unless
Funny business to plug
For the last half
He's over 30 the criteria required for an Agricultural tax
Alex seems like he's just talkingshit here together enough
To actually get this plan in motion with his neighbor
But if he did that is
Definitely a text
Actually follow through with it I'm just going to leave this here is an example of Alex being
Very
Very stupid
But I do want to point out that when
To come up with an example of a straight-up good-faith negotiation
His mind goes to conspiring with his neighbor to get the IRS
Yep
No
No it's
Conversation
Probably
Call Tino
Yeah sure
That's his idea of what a debate
I guess
The only people who really
Get hurt by agricultural exemption
Open fraud
Because tax dollars go away that need to be made up somewhere else
Be passed down to
All other consumers
I've been also other people who rely on agricultural
So I was really only hurting
People he pretends to
To support
I don't know if he actually followed through with it and I don't know how I would ever find that out
Short of leaving a blind item
Anonymous tip
With the Texas comptroller and I don't think that's worth our time
How about
We put out some
On the Craigslist
Connections
I don't know I saw you you lived next door
We were going to wear Alex about emergency
Just gets lost
In a hole thinking about how exciting
Is that Obama is talking about him
But you notice
Really really
Really
Rearranged
I didn't even want to be the most
Popular really Alex real homecoming
Yeah I need a Wonder
That wasn't that was
Entirely wrong
I'll just get through this next one cuz it's
Making the argument
He's the main person that Obama was
Respond
Syracuse the main
Center of the group of people
Is responding
Intuit afraid of
Partially undoubtedly believe all of these things
Together it's because Alex has entered impeachment articles
Attacked as soon as
The press conference
Press conference where in
Ski specifically is talking to Alex
Reminder reminder Obama had to address
Alex because
Alex's
Move on
Petition got over 100,000
Yeah
It was real proud
Another consideration
And
We would like to
Officially tell you to go fuc
Yeah yeah yeah
This
He's one of those things
Coming from someone who stands to gain a lot of money
By creating the perception that the president was
Responding to him
And all this
If that wasn't
I would
See this as a mental break
I would see this with a as a break with reality because it's all building
Blocks of something
It's very profitable to Alex
It really kind of just feels like artificially could
Instructed
Things that would be scary if they were sincere
I don't think those
You know it
Listen to his voice
Sounds
Giddy
A President Who
Talked about
No longer sounds good
When
Trump a president who likes
Talks about it
Do you know what I mean
I don't think that
Diddy thinking about Obama talking about him I think he's
Giddy
Think about all the publicity
Yeah the Optics required
You met that Obama is talking about
Obama's accidentally
Given Alex all the ammo that he
You need to do
Years of shows quite frankly
But the best thing
For him would have been
Hillary Clinton
Saying stuff like what Obama just said right there
Hillary said they got a dark heart
A really long time
Reflection
Actually sincerely believing
Did Obama is direct
We talkin to him through the
That's a line that I think
Is kind of important because otherwise
I do think that we could be
Like looking at something
It's kind of scary
Either way but it's
I mean scary on lyca
As opposed to a scary what
Into the world
Rhetoric
Earlier I scolded
You were suggesting that it
Possible
That Alex really
Kind of just want his gun
To fight off a
I don't know some
Be mirrored in lot of coded language
Did he uses
Falcons
And I was just
That is
Pretty
Also I love the beginning of that being like what
Isn't that the premise of your career
What is that a new revelation your head
Also why are you creating this bizarre nonsense about him
Impeaching a president
Keenly aware that he's just a front man for the f****** globalist going to do
Come on have a good time
Bulshit
You know what maybe lose
Maybe lose the complex maybe the
Which is a totally thing
You know what
If you're going to go down you might as well go down with
He's president
You know
I guess
It does feel that way
A lot of those feeling
Behind
Unacceptable code
I'm at now
I could be generalizing with
But when somebody
The right
Is welfare
They are
Yeah totally
No totally
Let's call it 9
Clip Alex
Call from a guy
South African
Mickey's a bad dude
Consequences
Cover to cover
Email my copy to Barry Hussein
Highlighted
Yourself
He might get killed
For sending Obama a copy of this book unintended
The callers nuts
But the longer answer is that course he wouldn't be killed for that sort of a gesture
But
He knows
Implied death threat that you'd be making to Obama
Book written by a guy named John Ross
The book is pretty hard to get a copy of it
Super expensive
Certified online
Able to read it
Just a discus
The colors
Comic book
Militia p***
Pure and simple
All you really need to know about this book is it the consequences that are unintended are they
Civil War or unhappy with the government's meddling
Was what I was
Thinking
Book have threatened 100% Alex Jones Jackman
The novel tells the story of Henry Bowman
I'm Shady ATF agent
He does this by pulling a gun on an FBI informant at a gun show
To get revenge on Henry
The ETF somehow gets convinced to set Henry up but because Henry very smart
He gets the jump on them when they're coming
His house
Everybody I've read the book is
Very graphic
But how he tortures and then kills the ATF agent
Who are specifically described his quote
Cultural
Really one African-American female cop who shows up at his house is named gonorrhea
Ross is all about
As well as what kind of person would think this is annex
Flint book
Like Alex's describing
Wow
That
Henry force is one of the agents
A recorded confession video which is definitely a false confession in reality
Probably
To be Enrique
How wrong he was
Henry precedes to decapitate
I want to play this game
Burns rats van and shoot some helicopters out of
Guy before meeting up with his buddy
Start a war against
The feds
Leaderless resistance model
Like
What people
Thought red.
Was
When in reality Red Dawn was
The opposite of that like Red Dawn was supposed to put you inside of
Snow people
You would do and why it's
If you think
This is reasonable absolutely reasonable for 8
America
Kenter doing it to other than empathy
Gross
White people what if we just started being terrorists
It is kind of bad
They post a false confession video
If people begin doxinate
Henry makes a declaration that all 80s members cops or elected officials
Those were against their interpretation of the Second Amendment is guilty of treason and subjective
Multiple Congress members are murdered
Henry's friend
Cindy was a victim of sex trafficking
Henryettan AA meeting
Decided to start prostituting yourself
For Henry every very likely
We killed her pimp
Murders happened before his running with the ATF
Some kind of a peace-loving
This is bulshit
Ouch that hurts
He was a good man with push too far
Already a mass murderer
The Chiefs
He's the bad guy
Yes
The rest of the Patriots
Ultimately concluded with the Patriots with the presidential
Negotiate
Hey which point they force him at gunpoint to read
Executive order getting rid of all cop laws
Plot is grossly childish. Just
Grubs
A lot of the reviews I've read
It seems
Like he really
Sickly
Describes the murdering of the
Cops
Seems to relish it quite a bit
Here are a couple of Interest
Pieces of the book that I think are worth
Discussing
Outside of Justice
Simplistic childish
Militia p***
Over the course of the story being his friends live through some real-world events like Ruby Ridge and Waco
In the text these events happen is there in the
Communities not actually happened
So there's a weird historical revisionism
It blurs the entire narrative structure
The story happens in our world clearly
Play because there are events that happened in our world
But the Patriot Funhouse
Mirror of reality
Is the only point of reference
In many ways it's kinda like his book exist in the reality that Alex Jones
Creates on his program
Yeah distorted Twisted version of historical
Revision wear these
A pro-gun people have always been the heroes in every single way
This book literally and by name calls out
Support for gun owners for America and Jews for the preservation of firearm
2 gun groups Farber extreme than NRA who were both early sponsors of the Alex Jones Show
AR-15
Awkward
The president
Baby would be a rat
I don't think you would but it is
I'm a thread on that an AR-15 Message Board as two people I didn't recommendation
A books similar to
Pretty much all the responses are to read enemies foreign and domestic
A Trilogy of books written by regular Alex
Matt Bracken
Who predicts a race war
The writer of this book fictionalized characters
Support the same organizations that support Alex
I didn't join communities the most similar book people can come up with was written by one of Alex's regular associate
Notice small overlap that we're seeing
A lot of the rhetoric and a lot of ideas
In this book are very similar to things
Alex
Fields
Wrapped
LARP
Like this
It really feels like all of the
Are living
Role playing
Because
The real life
Doesn't do it for them
You know it's
Two people who've left
This
Andre.
They tell the same
Feel like I was important
Feel like
Personal
Control over all of the
Dr. Wallach selling
That's
But a lot of what is preyed upon
Resentment is a motivator and hope of a simple explanation
As the drive-in
Yeah
What do other things
Wind up getting them is missing that video games do and roleplay
That is Starbucks peaches
Well no not
Is the idea of like
Leveling up
Known for aggression
Adele knowing the way that the few
A linear path
There's no
There's no chaos
Exactly how they
Borders
Which is actually
You know
I would say that is
Incredibly
Authoritarian
You know what it is
Piece of the story.
They presented as his idea where the Patriots
America
There's no part of me that really believes that they're actually doing what people want
Draft any Ledger
Debate over it now they held the president a small group of people who are enforcing their
It's
Not some
Even the fantasy of it is convoluted
It's
It's very strange
The day they are
Pizza miracle
Inspired to go through
Is Attack on the Murrah building by reading the Turner Diaries
Well while waiting at his trial he got a copy of unintended consequences
This is what he said about
Quotes
If people say the Turner diaries with my Bible
Unintended consequences would be by Newton
I think unintended consequences is a better book
It might have changed my whole plan of operation if I read that one
You're a bad terrorist
Hey it's great
Eighth grade
Really
Really what it was
Look the content is bad but
W
Do you love
The pros
The pros is
Disgusted by and really kind of scared about in the present
With Alex Jones
It's always been there
It's just that the climate was
I think about it a lot is kind of being crafty
Yeah boys you know like
Cthulhu's always around
Until the stars are right
He has to sleep in really a
Unless the time is right
For him to come
Teach people
New ways of enjoying and terrorizing
And in the same way like Alex
Is always been like this
But the Stars weren't right
The social climate wasn't broken down
To the point where
These conversations
You'd be much more
More overt much borax
Accepted
As public
Speech
It does feel like
Novo
Coming up in my mind never comes up on the show because
The absence
Do something in his rhetoric
You haven't talked about Muslims
Really at all
In 2013
He hates them so much now
I don't hear him complaining about Muslims at all
The only times I've really heard it come up where I gasp
Calling Obama
Double R Ranch
He doesn't
As overtly islamophobic
Check back then
Weird and I don't know what train is special
Literally made a bunch of race
Is been almost entirely absent from this
Because in those rates
Clips
Add Muslims
Time
Just like even if he doesn't say it
Probably
On sublevel
Dino from contacts
Clues what are you talkin about
America
Call Emma Grimm
So anyway
Just do something more interesting Lee in the past
Cuz I don't want to end the show on that
Kind of
I would prefer as Alex
A Starship Troopers joke
And then getting really self-conscious
I'm not going crazy.
No further word
The very fastest book
New York Times
Plugging
Jesus Christ
Stupid
I think that's one of the things I touched on earlier I thank you
Sandy Hook is a meme
To an end at this
I'm not a already
This move. Progress the narrative
To the gun extremism
To overthrow the president
Impeach Obama
He's taking it on the path that it needed to go on
Which is probably the goal
And then also make a lot of money selling to come and take it shirts
Stream gun paranoia
So I don't
I do wonder how it's going
Progressed from here
It seems really
Possible
But he never needed to
Do anything more
I know he does
Never talked about
The hook again and I probably would have gone away
I don't know why he needs
Go back to the well
Destructive personality
Literally talk about
Very weird
Another episode where y'all
It's knowledge.
That's correct the Illuminati
Nope
Amazing seller
Bike
Bundles on Facebook
What if you wanted to actually listen to
We are on iTune
Other places
If your listen
NBA Grace
Theo Ratliff is blocked a lot of shots and killed a lot of Dreams
I don't think
Duxbury
Never killed anybody
Technically probably
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work