Alex
Have you ever done backyard
No I haven't no but
Your talk about like organized
But he might back in like fourth and fifth grade bags
She is never organized credibility
Friend of the show and in goodbye
He actually did do backyard wrestling when he was younger man
He has a credibility I don't have Powerball
Georgia
Nothing about probably not the owner name
Got it
I want to record a little bit of your TuneIn
Knowledge fight and you're different episode thrilled to do a crossover
Bit of an episode with the guys from qanon anonymous
And we are pumped
2% that for you
I thought it would be nice to jump in here at the beginning give everybody an update on my plants
Doing well
It's hard to grow herbs Tumblr
Everybody from our last episode on Friday
Nothing we've talked about has ever been this galvanizing of the audience
Multiple multiple people is offered to send me copies of it
And I appreciate everybody's that generosity and interest
It's so it's really cool
Obscure
Card based
Intricate game
And people respond so aggressive
Very cool
That resonate with people and they respond
I'm glad that there are people
I like it.
Peace talks
I'm a policy wonk
Welcome listeners to the 40th chapter of the
The qanon Anonymous podcast
And a 1776 episode of knowledge fight
The Alex Jones
Allow me to introduce the delegation of
Qanon represented by
Travis view Jake rockatansky enjoy and field
Hello
LOL
That's over here for the meeting
So across the table from us the delegation of Alex Jones represented by
Jordan Holmes
In honor of
Very
I protest this very much not like gentlemen
There Will Be Blood as both sides State solution
With no border between Alex Jones and qanon
A harmonious world of peace
Love
And shared cognitive dissonance
Main issues on the docket today are as follows
Number one will be done
Number two will be immigration
And number three will be the podesta
Definitely all categories that match
Each other after
Expository arguments by both delegations we will enter what UNESCO cause
Discussion time
During which we basically power outage shoot the s***
Catch up on recipes and subtly undermine Jake
I just want to say
That this is our most requested
Crossover episode
And so just want to thank you fellas
Buffer for joining us on it
I'd like to point out that
We join them
In wanting to subtly undermine Jake which is what's important
I figured that we would be using the Conch system of talking to each other but
That's fine
Yes yes well until inevitably one of us feels like the others had the Conch for too long and then
We start murdering each other and I eating our Flash
Ward
Behalf of the Alex Jones table
Before I get into my remarks
I'd like to point out that ground established we can build upon to her
Malt
Both are ranked
Alex Jones has had him on as a guest for many years but now it is later career incredibly long to videos
Rambling about Q Clues
I'm referring of course
As the child of the rationalization to unite the parties of this broken home
Conspiracy
Let it be known that today but
Horrible destruction in their lives
But if you dig for the truth you'll find people who are afraid of how aggressively Alex Telles
The truth
Particularly about God's greatest creation
The gun
Some people will tell you that the Chinese invented
It was God
Is the single most important exist
And now it's his right to own as many as he wants and whatever he wants with no
Is literally the only thing that is standing between pure beautiful freedom and dystopian globalist
Which I should point out
So is this why Alex actually looks like a Gun Locker
The dog
Is Guns n and Gun Locker
You see this country only exist because of guns
That's right
America was invented because the British tried to take
The colonists guns away we're going to start a revolution
Now sure the British tried to confiscate guns April 17th 75
A good four years after North Carolina Regulators letter armed Rebellion over unfair tax
Years after the Boston Tea Party protesting
And months after the British had declared Massachusetts
The Suffolk resolves largely directed
Itself a retaliation for the Boston Tea Party
Forget all that stuff it doesn't matter
The truth is that right before Lexington and Concord the British tried to take the weapons of colonists
Already pretty much a rebellion over taxes
And that proves conclusively that this country would not exist without gun
And if I expect
You guessed it
Gone
Reason you get up in the morning
Guns
A hundred percent because of guns usually that
By 8 that is going to fire
I feel like a Rube Goldberg machine with a name of an M16 at the endpoint that your head
YouTube video
Where they have all the dominoes taking forever to go off and then it's
Just hit the got a dildo but I could see that being apart of like a cutscene from an Ernest Motors
Absolutely
I didn't say anything about vaping
The globalist Menace that we face today
Coach we conquered back in 1776
And they have never stopped wanting to take Americans guns away
Revolution
The Rothschild George Soros
And noted anglophiles like h.g. Wells
They've been plotting for centuries to take down the Great American experiment
They play all sorts of dirty tricks that may appear to be hurting the economy or creating greater public
But make no mistake
Behind every single one of their plan
Is the obsessive desire to take away Alex's gun
Specifically Alex's gun
All roads lead back to attempt a gun grab
Literally everything
Take fluoride
You know why they put fluoride in the water
Scientist will tell you it's for your teeth
And the peer-reviewed studies the show
But you should know better than to listen to mainstream scientists
These are globalist scientists who don't want you to know that there's fluoride in the water to make you dumb and wheat
Resist when they come and try and take your guns
Strong in the teeth weak on the draw quote Thomas Jefferson
The real Thomas Jefferson quote by the way
Hundred percent very real
Make teeth Victorian again
Literally everything is secretly about gun control policy made by the Federal Reserve is an effort to devalue
Galaxy gun
Every mass shooting is a carefully orchestrated globalist false flag
Publix Heartstrings
Taking Alex's gun
Feminism is real version of female empowerment empowerment
Comes from gun
And that's half the population will be armed to help Alex
Not have his guns taken away
Money and politics aside unspoken issue behind every conversation about policy
Economy going to take a long sober look at the fact
It becomes playing that every bill every house concurrent resolution every executive order
Has an unspoken Clause regarding whether or not Alex Jones can keep his gun
Historians in the 2100 will undoubtedly look back at this issue as the defining political question of this Jenner
Duration and as long as we can find some common ground.
There may be hope
Of us reaching a true and Lasting conspiracy
Thank you our delegation thanks you for your words
A great comfort
I can already see that we are going to be friends
And that we're going to find a lot of Middle Ground
That's comforting
First of all I'd like to state that we are above these two
You never stoop to directly mentioning the second amend
In fact across all Q drops
The only amendment directly mentioned is
Is the 25th
Now let's be clear
25th amendment is ADT or playable character
Nobody in their right mind would use competitively its
It's just not that powerful in the current meta game
In fact it was created in the wake of
JFK's murder to make sure they would be clear next steps
In case of president
Resigns dies or is incapacitated a removed from office
For some reason
And really just mostly insurers at the vice president would take over when
Exact
Play the reason Q Frets more about this amendment than me recently buffed Str juggernauts the first and second and
Amendment is it he fears the president
Will be pushed into a McDonald's ball pit by the CIA and disappear forever
So I'm sorry I know I'm not representing my delegation with dignity here
My wife
Left me this morning and
I mistook my dish soap for coffee
What are you talking about
But your wife leaving you
Huron actually seems divided on
On one side they believe guns are good
Here's a q drop from February 23rd 2000
18 y school shooting
What is more precious than our children
Emotional
Event
Congrats event
What would locals go along with such a sick
Organized
Must control local police
Kelly officials Etc to work
Why
Many dollar sign
Federal aid plus donation
These people are sick
Now here Q links to a 2014 article for current by Dave altimari entitled
Sandy Hook two years later where is the aid going
In it he details all the different initiatives setup
To help the community in the aftermath
The shooting
The author reports positively on these
But also shines a light on the bureaucracy and inefficiency
Some families unsupported or unclear on where they can
Find help
Askew continues
Follow the money
It's always about the money
Jew
Why is he doing old article examining an event for the late
Well it turns out that the Parkland
School shooting had occurred less than
10 days before
If you needed to make it clear that Parkland was a false flag
And even if it weren't a false flag
And it would still be a way for the Deep state to grab your guns
And even if it wasn't that that it at least shows how local officials are controlled by the deep sea
But hate that might also not be true in which case let's examine how the money raised after the
This kind of tragedy is going
Pocket
This q-drop is the definition of a Gish gallop
Overwhelming your opponent with more arguments than they can feasibly address
In a response
Q thinks his audiences Rock dumb
He made another drop on the 10th of March
Guns are safe
Stop falling
Fake news
Doubt still not at Q
What if he hadn't been clear enough
What if his followers were more stupid than he thought
Well on March 27th
He finally addressed his anxieties with this drop
Parkland is a distraction
Parkland What specifically organized at his side to distract
What's the news
Actors are acting
Justice will be served at those playing the game
Guns are safe
Trustpoint
Q
Sadly this did little to save cues hunger for Revenge
Still he slept like s***
Still his dumbass followers believe the Earth was flat JFK jr. was alive
Still they regularly mistook mayonnaise for yogurt
So in early April
She decided to take action
This time with a more productive
It's been on Gunn
He posited a new type of gun mighty
A bad guy
What I'm sorry guys but you'll see
You understand why very
Very soon
Here's a drop he made on the
The Border
Black Ops
Call cloud in like night-vision.
So although
Referring to clowns America or the CIA
Performance
Raised owl
Supporter to what
13 / 0
Sex traffic
Drugs roadblock
Gordon's roadblock
China / Russia
Intel pool roadblock
May we don't say blah
Easy Roblox
Terminate
More than you know
Fight for the Wallace
So much for
Is he saying that Voldemort made is the Voldemort
Say his name
That's cute
Yeah they also said authorities
His brain cancer was a fake
And that he didn't actually die executed instead of instead of die
He was here
Secretly as as
Yeah because yeah because all the
Coerced
Wake up to
2 Q is by X
Executions that are completely hidden from the public
So you're not sure if they even took
C4 us the name that we don't say Arizona is Joe Arpaio
I took that a little differently
So the wall then as far as cute as concerned is an effective way to stop the bad gums from
Coming into the country
I mean can you imagine if America were flooded with weapons
Like when that stock
Anyways one of his fan to ask him whether the wall was about more than just you know stopping drugs assassins and child traffickers
Perhaps if and positive
Mexico was going to be used as a quote
Vector in the event of War
Soak you responded
What you would say to Country whereby a
Good portion of its citizens are armed
Ultimate deterrent
This does not answer the question about Mexico nor does it have anything to do with the wall it's just a boilerplate reaffirming of the
Second Amendment
At this point
Furious
Why won't
Pigs eat the slop provided and shut up with the questions
What if you could write a very long
Totally sane
Mostly all caps drop that answered all possible questions you could ever have
Sleeves
P***
Gun control
Wars
Fake
Election rigging
Drool
Your voice does not matter
Water
Typical sports for home use cleaning
Cancer
Receipt
Germany
Choice is yours
With a given your children cancer through cleaning products
Yeah cuz they crawl on the floor
Ureter is
Is this a baby on floor hands and mouse the Stark
What's the best route home
He was like
I better mention the paces baby on floor
Under my boot
Totally dominating it
The middle
Flossing
If I if you still have any questions after that drop it is
The delegations belief that you should
She typed them up into a word doc
In place that doctor reckley in the digital trash Patriot because you're too f****** stupid even for
Inclusion at the delegation representing keeping on I-90 closed my expository argument by stating a
A simple fact
One that does not care about your
Feelings
There are two types of guns
The ones owned by Americans
And that guns the ones owned by everyone else
We need to protect the border from the bad guns and continue to stockpile the good
We can find some good common ground in that position
I think if you're if you're if you at
So that would have been
Animated coffee a tasso
Urinal cake out of my baby's mouth
Guns that other people have could become good gun
Given to Americans
I think that we could probably move forward as long as we don't demonize the guns just because people don't like
Actually that's a really good plant to have it wrong
All just wanted to take
The bad guns away they're forgetting a key element
You take the bad guns
And then give them to people who will use them
For good you put them in the Calvin and Hobbes
Transmogrifier and then take him out
And you can use it on brown people now
Yeah well and yeah you know self-defense ghetto you can stand your ground with it
All of these
Things are good for guns need along kind of M16 shaped object
Stand your ground cuz it'll serve as a came
Right right
There is one insistence that
Guns are safe
And it was acute drop and so sure of the followers
Even though the
Keepsake
To take the Gods
There's no real risk of that happen
If I understand
The aljo delegation position
They believe that there is a very real possibility that any moment
That the government's can't descend upon the Alex Jones specifically
Sprite Corrections
If you open your door right now waiting for the signal to grab
Ruth is little
Trying to f****** yet from what I understand is there constantly standing outside of everybody's
Apartment or are they just have cloaking technology
So you know the moment you know the moment the orders given
Pomodoro to take your goddamn crap I would like to say one thing that I believe can build a bridge between us it's the belief that I think
Both cute out share that there that guns don't kill people
Bad people do
And so I would say that we meet in the middle there
In that
If for example MS-13 had a gun
It wouldn't make the gun technically bad
Just
Dad got until it's dropped by the MS
13%
Neutral is good
So have we negotiated enough
Do do we feel like we can live together
I think so and I was
Pieces of information
Nobody
No I think he means like if
For example your teacher
Patagon that would make you as schoolchildren safer
Or even that gun just in general are safe and if you get killed by one
I mean that's your f****** fault buddy Bridge built
To get killed by about people on is that there's a general theme like everything's under control in like all of yours
Surah conspiratorial dreams will come true and so
This paradise of the paradise
Everybody gets bored with the birth certificate
But so so I
A sort of up to interpretation whether or not they
That's our guns are safe music guns
Or not
Inherently threatening or that
Or that guns are no risk of actually being grabbed by everyone
But I think that I think that if it if it is saying that guns aren't
Dimecuba
Everything's going to be okay
That's true that that may be the only thing that we will have to deal with is half half a bar in a new state
Will be very alarmed that
People going to come in
And the other half will be like yes
You should be alone but also
Everything's okay
Control
Control your living room
Definitely don't turn off daytime TV
More like guns are safe and structure is very unsafe
Grammar is under heavy attack
BBQ
As the delegate
Knowledge fight I would like to
Give you a very quick rundown of Alex's
Dispositional
Immigration
Bad
Real bad
Very bad
Nobody should be allowed to
There are
Good immigrants
And then there are
Not good immigrant
Which means there are no
You can tell the difference
Between immigrants and non
By sight
Wink
Obviously the left is flooding the United States with him
Most of whom vote Democrat
Mind you they vote Democrat
Because they want
Handouts
Not because the
The fascist terrorist organization known as the Republican Party
Thinks it's hilarious to respond to the question
What should we do with immigrants
With
Shoot them
It's because of her
Handouts
When the Democrats
Consolidate their elected
Replacing the good
God-fearing
Patriots who clutch their guns like pearls
They will institute there one thousand year Reich
Wipeout
Read that is why
Immigrant
Are Central to the globalist plans
For reducing the world's population
Conservative
By 90%
Immigrants control elections for the Deaf
Step 2
The Dems take away our guns
Step 3
Eradicate the population
Could not be simpler
It also goes higher up still than the Democrat
Because they're not just going for a Merica they're going for the world
It is the UN
And George Soros
That no
From wherever it is
Into the Western world
Read White
And start a civil war
By destroying the West
You take the world
Because obviously other parts of the world
Never contributed
Technology or culture
Not a problem
Just bringing in immigrants from outside the web
Is enough to destroy the country
Now I know you're thinking this is about race
Because I've said it multiple times but it's not
This view is shared by many of his
Frequent gas
Prominent
Non-racist thinkers
For example Canadian would be politician Faith Goldy
British milkshake milkshake
Canvas Tommy Robinson
Rhodesia loving apartheid-era carpetbagger Bob Chapman
And
Whiny snowflake himself
Ted Nugent
What a collection of totally not racist luminaries like
Please agree on something
We can be sure it is very much not
In fact
You thinking they're racist at all
Is Reverse Racism
After all Alex has said again and again that he is not racist for citing his love of live
Latinx women
And
It is all flavors of immigrants that want fries
It's all immigrants who wants
Destabilize the mark
Take our guns
Kill poor innocent White
People without
Knowing full well that the live
Wilton
Call you rate
The worst
The elite know this
And they set up the whole sequence of a
When immigrants come to America
Patriots
Have no choice but to
Protect themselves
And their culture
Take up their guns
What's wrong with that
Thank you
Beautiful
Powerful
Very coherent
Toscana Lake
My favorite slam poetry you know
Yeah I'm feeling I'm feeling a little
If you will
A little bit till Dawn
I had to resist the urge
Map
Alex Jones's
Argument
You can't be racist cuz foreigners they can both horny and hungry.
I think it's rock-solid of not a racist
May or may not like Mexican music
As well so I mean like the evidence is there on the table
School love
Equivalent Sharon talking migration
What's in a week into
Existence
November 4th 2007
13 to drop
Cool fonts
Why did Barack Obama
Instruct Beach
Police MS-13 captures at the border
What agency after wreck
What is 80 session / POTUS
Immigration
Coogi wire for a hit
Eliminated
The job is complete
Seth rich
Shortly after his murder
What affiliation did they have
Classify
You
So yeah you've you have found
Somebody
Thinks that Their audience
Stupider
Then Alex
That's amazing
So the kids you know they
Cambridge
Now they know more about Seth rich
A murdered DNC staffer
We recently dedicated
Discourse Tysons
Immigration because
If we don't build a wall
MS-13 gang members coming to
The country
The country than the Democrats will hire them as Hitman
Hitman MS-13 well-off people like Seth rich
Busting Hillary Clinton for what she did to Bernie
Send off the Hitman that they brought into the country
Country to begin with
Because their lives mean nothing and no one will ask him
Questions
Big complicated
You should never give a mouse a cookie
Never given MS-13 member Mouse in this case has MS-13
And cookie is assassination
Complete
The book in the first place
You just have to remember to blame Obama for quote release
MS-13
Capture
At the border
Something which of course death
We happened
Because we have multiple agents with
With kind of
Giant Nets
Trying to throw them over MS-13 people as they
But either way Obama was like Naga
Catch-and-release make sure the hook doesn't lie
Mike hurt their mouths
And
Healthy drop
Subsistence
Exact
Yeah it's particularly angry about how much the deeps
Love's immigration
In June of 2018 Q made this
If you are smart
Stupid
Parentheses
You know what you eating in Russia
Attempts to free Russia / Clovis
Optics
Feeling
To keep POTUS away from
Enemies or Allies
America
Age of taxing our citizen
Across the world market
Over
World
Gvea
Rvw
Read the Bible
Claude Williams
Shoe
I took a turn
You should have said spoilers
Like it's kind of a dick thing to do.
Spoiler alert the Godwin is it coming in the form of telegrams what do we do
Read the Bible
Admittedly
Super aware of qanon stuff
Religious
Fundamentalist big aspect
You guys who have the 3 stars next to them and that stands for is the Holy Trinity
Hellboy smoothie if your if your blender doesn't work so you just shut up
Layered in there and never becomes a coherent
Slurry
General Flynn
3-star General
It was like the Holy Ghost
I don't know that s*** but
One of the Stars I think my
The second one is also the Star of David & David
You are allowed to hunt people like myself
A reading of this is the general Flynn is the Holy Ghost
I mean
Yes part of the trinity
The Holy Ghost
There's
Religion into like the ball as literal devil worship
They argue with Satan
And so
They're the white hats all the good people there on God's
Trump and Trump is like a soldier of God
The God has
Chosen this
This
Saggy grave of a man
You know I deliver us
From the onslaught of demonic entities
Maybe was little unaware of but this is a
Heavy overlap
Pizza place
Easily
Good good good
Cuz the idea here is
It's pretty simple
If you listen
That Q drop
Or Testament
Reloading immigrants
Just want to taste
Sweet nectar of American freedom
But they're evil
That's why American citizens get tax so much when
Traveling abroad
Logically in response to this heavy taxation of American tourists
Totally exist
We must close the American markets
That's because the country is not just
The country is also a mark
We're going to create a virtual wall to keep out the market
And 200 ft electric fence
The fire turrets
To keep out the other car
This is a question
Right vs wrong
And good
Obviously we have to stop
DeForest immigration
Because if you read the Bible God is a huge winner
You really think God would p**** out and not fight the immigrants
Get real
Friggin sleigh
The first testament
Is just God sitting on the border with Mexico
Double-tapping brown people until they all Rage Quit
It makes sense if
If you think about it
Either smart or an idiot if you don't get it
Anyway not getting it
But you also
Sometimes checks out
Dirtbag left Twitter bios
And he's not happy that they want to abolish ice
That's why in July 2018
He made this draw
Sorry she was too busy looking at
Videos of his
His own.
Execute its mission to the enforcement of more than 400 federal statute
Sportsman
Prophetic Terror
Https
Ice
Goodbye Democrats
You
Who knows that the best source of information about ice
Is there own website
Conspiracy theorist God
You can just link to the regular website
Obviously only morons would trust the
Dmsm
Sexual abuse
Manslaughter and murder occurring with a nice
And X official speaking out about corruption
Festering there
Give this delegation a break
Crisis actor
Everyone knows that when you resign from Ice
Mossad and it's President George Soros to offer you a cushy 18 figure jobs
A lot of those Parkland kids for example use
Used to be ice age
It's a Benjamin Button kind of tradition we can't let these X Ice Age
Children
Yeah abolish ice
More like no more mister nice
Guy
Goodbye Democrats
Unless
Of course Obama and most
The Democrats turned a blind eye
And oryx
Expanded ice
But not cool
Cuz they're Democrat
The point is immigrants bad Democrats bad ice good
It makes no sense to Boston agency
She founded in 2003
During the reaction a receiver of post 9/11 America
We need to give these guys more guns and pay for their 14 word ankle
And that's our delegations
Official
Except for one more thing
Antifa is involved here
They want to abolish ice
You probably don't know is that they're also not fans of white supremacy
Punching pitos and Mike cernovich
If you think I'm having a stroke
I'm not
In July 2018
Q posts today
A photo of a protest at Columbia University where epic gorilla mindset
Who's going to speed
But the intelligent counter-protesters
Have to do
They printed a giant protest
Bigger and more powerful than all the other protests
They took boilerplate
Key Staffing
What's next
Like the claim that the left
A few protesters
Are all members of
To the North American man-boy love associate
And they hate Mike sanovich so much because he
Anti pedo superhero
So they planted
And they got my turnovers to post
Photo of it
And finally they made sure Donald Trump jr. saw these turnovers post
Which will make him
Epic drops
Like this July
2018 July
Welcome to the new borders
Through keto destroyed
Antifa
The Democrat Party
Dark
To life
Q
I don't think this delegation needs
House
Stupid
Gullible
Our followers
They never check to see if
The sign and Bean
Stage-right information office another smear by the Mockingbird media even if they did
It's all one big family
Corporate media the
Antifa
They're all just layers of the deep sea
Structure
Event on November of 2018
Beast mode
He posted a New York Times article
Call showing a map
Of the electorate during the
Election
Crossword
Areas with illegal immigrant
You might be shocked
About white tees
Why they care more about
Did you
Specs matter
The reason the Democrats love immigrants
Immigrants
Haven't been thoroughly in
By Fox News
For several days
That means they refused to vote Republican which
Of course the huge sign that they're having their mind hijacked by the
State brain drawings in their all-bran
Or a 2%
OSU Patriots
So
Encourages researching
Research little self on the ice website cuz people really follow up
But those commands
From what I've experienced
Like listening to
Good stuff
So you're probably asking where their other posts
Maybe cleaning the judicial and or an anti-immigration movement
Or the open borders and a dislike of ice is a war on sovereignty
Or just did nationalism is good
Absolutely there are
Will the delegation P dressing goes
Absolutely not
Almost
The god that is all for whatever it is they're doing at any point
I know about the Bible Old Testament
Yeah
I'm shocked
The between what Alex believes
Professing
Yeah I mean it turns out that
Underneath It All
It's just brown people bad
Yep yep
The base we can build
You think so this could be that The Rock
This is like
Thing that certify
Underneath everything
Something's by
But Brown
Today
Alex Jones and having a nice dinner together
Possibly
Touching feet under
The table
This is our tomorrow
We can live happily ever after screaming about antifa
Fairy tales.
Yeah it's it's also important
He adds in there like the antifa is evil because another underpinning
Alex is that
All Democrats
Basically race-traitor
In other people if you're not supporting
Getting rid of
Illegal immigrants are you say that make me uncomfortable
Yeah race
Traitor is a tough
Phrased
Say out loud
And put our conversations honestly and put out a public podcast
Your parents may or may not listen
When I almost every morning
When I almost finish a marathon I always turn to the guy my right he's going to make it in
Throws up
What's the stick
Bicycle
The bad guys in breaking away
Speaking of a stick
The wheel of a bicycle
Easter Brothers
When we talked about the podesta brothers
Of course we're opening up the door to talking about pizza
And ultimately that means we're going to have to touch on the very important matter of
Literal demon
Pizzagate Alex was all about investigating globalist
Most likely abusing kids there
Employee
Rainbow
Took Aleve
It sorry but it's this delegations belief that you are making this personal
I wish it was
He doesn't always go by Rambo Joe big but I'll be damned if I'm not going to always call Matt Matt
Your weirdo with a periscope account
What's a Comet Ping Pong
Kicked out for the staff
Who's been dealing with frequent death threats recently by acting suspicious and live streaming forgetting to
Close to the truth
Dependent
Interviewed on Infowars about how he got such a creepy vibe there
How suspicious it was today
How he saw kids running all over the place possibly in and out of secret room
Because I hate myself I did watch that entire Periscope with him going to, to eat and I did not see
The things that he was describing
Which I didn't think was that
I just f****** love like this guy reinvented himself
As one of these like
Like stocks and logic
Journalism guys
And he's the guy who was just live streaming from inside a pizza joint going on
I'm pretty sure it smells like pedo in here
Yeah it's real impressive
Career art
We should all be so lucky shrink
American American life has so many chapter
Completely changed
Text podesta emails are real
But the globalist
20 people to the pizza place as a diversion so they wouldn't sign
He was pretty insistent at the time also that you would never into pizzagate
And even went so far as
To take down about pizzagate from his YouTube channel
No one really knows what caused the
The ship
Some really far-out conspiracy theorist to pointed out that just before he changed his story
Vegeta Comet Ping Pong owner
In order to avoid defamation lawsuit
I think we can all agree that do sound like coincidence
Whatever the case is here one is very consistent is that Alex thinks
Podesta brothers are Crypt
And most likely engaged in child trafficking and possibly the ritual sacrifice and in
Of human children
Industry with pretty much the entire Democratic Party
Are George soros's son Alexander
Robotics age
Alex is not ready had podesta emails that were at the core of the whole pizzagate thing
Due diligence
Enough about the topic on weird blocks to be able to rip about it
In one of the emails Marina Abramovic invites
Spirit cooking dinner at my place
She said she's looking forward to it
In the business
This is what's known as a smoking
Gun
The globalist Marina Abramovic
Performance art
Known internationally for decades
For creating provocative pieces
He'll tell you that the right-wing media intentionally conflated various vaguely occultic
Installation she's made
Over the course of her career with a dinner party she threw for people who donate to Kickstarter
Including
Stop showing up to
Dinner party
Adidas has conflated these they are these two things
In service of creating a style conspiracy
To attack Hillary Clinton
When they tell you
But the right-wing can play these two things together
I want to try that
Yeah I want to try that didn't show up because you probably just ate
Too much at home
Before you know
I think I think you probably didn't go because there were no bread I think probably email
Are you going to be serving
I like they do a Panera
And they said no I don't we don't have any bread bowls just regular
No thanks
I'm trying to do the opposite of cutting down
Reality these dinner guest
Gorged on food made of blood in semen
Making a mockery of God as well as traditional flavor profile
I know this sounds crazy cuz you got to think that food not tasted good but you think it's not
It's about ritual
These people like Marina Abramovic
Hillary Clinton
George Soros is one song that Alex knows about
Commence
Literal demon
Serious jumping around with pitchforks demon
This is not a metaphor
Think of it a killer Bob from Twin Peaks
They're like that except they can
Keep your s*** together long enough to legislate
Which is scarier than killer Bop
Killer Bob could never round up the votes needed to pass a gun control bill
You see
It's all comes back to adrenochrome
These demons puppets to destroy the world
Able to communicate with their puppet
Problem
Really high
They've got to be high on a specific called adrenochrome
These demons Commander puppets
The kidnapped children and torture them
In order to frighten their pituitary glands into releasing enough adrenaline
So their blood is full of address
End up being able to commune with their demonic shift
Managers basically Monsters Inc
Someone
Monsters Inc
Literally used as a meme in the qanon community
Describe exactly
Afraid of court
Are they secretly f****** with
The child can I possibly create enough adrenaline to turn its blood into a drug
You can easily buy synthetic adrenaline completely legal
Good high remember
They are mostly globalist
So to sum up Alex's position
Drug
Who give them marching orders that tell them to destroy the world
Mostly by meddling with a free market and trying to take Alex's gun
Also Alex is not thrilled with Tony podesta choice in paintings and sculptures
This is really
A place where we are going
Feel
The bonds of
The Brotherhood
Worries me as a human outside of doing this podcast
A boy but yes
I did not go very deeply with adrenochrome and now that
Torture
Occurs but
You're completely correct
Across the line
Contestation
R-pod
Our delegation
Call sit adrenochrome
And yours
Adrenochrome but I think that's the
Just the British
First American
Podesta Bros
Earlier
Episode of ours that we did
Discovered that there is a text startup company
That does sell the blood
Of a young human
Two older humans
I think I got shut off for a while though
Subscription Service where child shows up in a box up for a subscription fee once a month
18 to 25 year old to do to the economy being so shity are pushed into literally emptying themselves
Is there blood
Live longer it's not at all
First year that we did our podcast I needed to sell my blood in order
So I'm
Very familiar on being on the business end of that
The whole podcasting industry only is able to exist
Because we all sell our blood
Plasma center
I feel cold
Official sponsors of strangers
Play that on the podcast until we reach 4000 a month
Well I'm on our side
And representing this delegation
I'd like to see a lot
To say about the
Podesta Brothers
Mailman
Very earliest days
There are more good
The Wizards and warlocks
Inside
More of a sentence
This sort of
Q had to like try different kind of like
Yazoo promotes
Some of these dry I mean it's a little first-draft E I mean in my honest opinion could have could have done another
Maybe some notes from the studio
But
Warlocks inside
Not allow another
You're welcome
Trailer country
Realize Soros
Clinton's
Obama
Etcetera
Old control B
Worth
Which removed post Trump speech
Open up
Podesta indicted
11:6
Metaphor
Wasted the Trump's camp
As well as other
Otherwise 70% of elected politicians
We're seeing it already begin
Defense
Speak never thought they were going to lose control of the presidency
Do Tuesdays
Mistakes
Reagan
Yes
Closest Target
Worried
Your archetype of Norcross are
Engagement
Is with JFK and Reagan being the mistakes was the mistake actually killing JFK and not wreck
They shot Reagan and it scared him away from fighting the Deep state
And the mistake is that they let these to.jfk and Reagan
Become president not knowing that they were going to try to
John podesta to put things in perspective
Was indicted on the 3rd of November.
This was followed by his arrest the next
As mentioned in this November 1st
2017 drop
Q clearance Patriot
My fellow Americans
Over the course of the next several days
You will undoubtedly realize that we are
Back
Country
The land of the free
For the evil tyrant
Initiated
Digital safe going to public
Fallout
Mr. podesta
Actionable 11:4
Confirmation
To the public
What is the current
Will that be revealed
Will not be openly accepted
Really
Actually deaf
Credible stuff
Truly POTUS is good
And Q is good
Also who can forget the shockwaves
The podesta's arrest
I was
Stunned that I ever doubted you when those early early days it was incredible
We all remember where we were
Marched out of Comet Ping Pong and play through the squad car
They still had the blood of their latest meal tomato sauce
On their on their shirts
On their finely pressed
Shirts
Yeah that was
They should have let him clean up first
Publix
This is water
Reaction
Carried out
United States
Special operator
Worcestershire
Everyman
A child
This country
Being exhausted
Beautiful
Suddenly Tony podesta is involved
Key West
Later in the same drop
The podesta's try to run
They tried to hide but they are
Remain semi-public figures
In December 2017 Q drop the photo of human Aberdeen and John podesta strolling down to dance
Street
That's a monkey blame podesta for
The Steele dossier
Danny Riggs for the podesta emails
Podesta
It's too wearing a cupcake
Before the bandits masks
Then on the 15th
August
2018 Q2 drops
Computer pool with painting of kids
Red shoes
He of course means the Vanderbilts
Biltmore Hotel
Cool and biljana djurdjevic
Kids in pool painting
Obviously
Stay with us
The red shoes are made of human leather
Wake up Patriots
Second drop
Cross against podesta
Travel to Rome
View 2015 2016 pics
Inside home
You
Depodesta
The pool filled with Walnut sauce
And all the children do the backstroke
Cuz he stands poolside with a
Civil War musket
Trained on their little heads
You knew he was onto something
So he continued posting links to
Delete podesta emails
Pushing for that
Pizzagate without the pizza narrative
The podesta's running fast child trafficking Network
Satanic human leather to make red shoes
They run stuff like quote
An evening of cooking with John podesta
Which they claim is a Mid-Atlantic Finance event
What were they cook
Who made
The sauce
Are those spare ribs
Is the size of a non-human
Pig
Doubtful
But it's been a year now and
You did have to address the non imprisonment
And not indictment of John and Tony podesta
Ascend said this
Exploded all over
Ladder that Skippy podesta
Suicide law
Diggy FurReal Sade
Soak you responded on November 8th
What
Appendix
Pending
Yes
Indictments are
Are trans dimensional objects
There are several entry and exit point
It can be pending but also have happened in the past
They can be in jail but also walking down the streets in DC with total impunity bad Chicago deep dish
Pizza because they refuse to
Comet Ping Pong
Not enough cheese
On their Pizza there
A cool Photoshop was retweeted by Donald Trump and Decemberists
A bunch of people behind bars including Clinton holder Obama Mueller Rosenstein
AOC
And John
Friggin podesta
That day John podesta responded
Jail
AKA his local Olive Garden
And said this
Let the fortune lunatics
Qanon crazies commence
Wild s***
Cue f*** with it though reposting it with the jail photo and saying
Define projection
Departure
What is scheduled to happen this week
Coincidence
This is as real as
No Escape
No Deal
Update
View
The wait wait
He's like I love your graphic
Can you please add bread into Photoshop
I said payment
I have one more quick notes
Enough enough
Jail
One more
Maybe
Talk with the color scheme a little bit
Lower the contract up the gamma make sure that you were non-destructive
In March of 2019 when John podesta Zealand from jail
He was interviewed by the local press and said
The rumors were the HP and I were running a child
Horn ring which had no basis
Send anything
But a guy showed up with a gun and ended up shooting up a pizza parlor
It is the police this delegation that where there's smoke
There's fire
That's why his followers under
Understood that when Q posted a Twitter thread by a guy called
Birds 534
About podesta's New Zealand tour
Anons immediately notice
A wild coincidence
The thread
Was posted
Exactly eight days before the New Zealand Christchurch
And everyone remembers
The guy had podesta emails painted on it
What's gun
I think the case
Has been made
John and Tony podesta are pedophiles who are both in
And out of jail
Running a vast child trafficking Network
Hidden behind
Innocuous food-related word
Yum
Allegedly
But you have none the less
Good sirs
Back to you Fred
I expected there to be bombs to pick but
Very little
Shades of green
Yeah this one is I think our biggest overlap yet
Alex tries to not talk about
These sorts of IB
Adrenochrome
Hidden behind other
Other top
Other things we talked about
He only brings those up when he wants
Impress someone like Eddie Bravo
A big trump card
Where is it
Is much more into like
Throwing this out pretty regularly
Yeah I think that
You know because Alex Jones is somewhat of a public figure and he has a
The face to put in a face to go with
You know I think you're right that he sort of holds back I'm a super crazy s*** just cuz he knows
It's already kind of
What the public perception is it in
Second before we insult
The people are delegation
Our representative
I would like us to
To read something
Inclusion in the formation of the
One state solution
That we discuss
Of course it will be a period of
Time during which we
Have kind of offline
Discussions which might
Accidentally be recorded before now I recommend
We move towards
Single-state solution
Do I have
The okay for our first
Topic guns
It does it seem
Like keeping all the guns in the country making sure they're in American hands
Stockpiling damn
And then using them on anybody who isn't American and also confiscating any
Non-american guns
What's coming in
Putting them in the transmogrifier
Making them American
And generally staying
Incredibly alert
I'm thinking that everyone's trying to steal your guns while also ignoring
School shootings
It does that
Is there anything you see wrong
As long as absolute ism
I think we could reach agreement there
Absolutely
Acceptable
As long as you guys also promise not to
In the use of the 20
5th Amendment
To remove our God
Okay well then I think we found Common Ground there
We can move on to
Our second issue
Immigration
Pretty simple one really
Immigrants
Bad
Legal or not
Illegal eyes
Dreamers
Stop.
Go home
White wall
Biggest wolves
Armed guards at wall malicious
Growing
Morgan's
Snipers
Scopes
F****** night vision
Mine
Tripwire's
Drones
IR sensor
As long as it is only applied to
Exactly
Okay no United States
Okay well as long as you're saying Democrats are
You know
Immigrants from here on in and they get that status
Foreign usurper from hell
Pinterest app
Thirsty
Dying Democratic family
As they attempt
To cross the border
Hold them at gunpoint then shove them under a bridge and make them sleep in
Security blanket
Until you know they die
Then we're fine
Fantastic
To Arthur
Probably even less
Just point
Which is
John and Tony podesta
Have you guys
Seen the spinoff
Podesta conspiracy theory
That the lead singer of Linkin Park
Chester Bedingfield
Killed him say that he's really the illegitimate son of
John podesta
And that he was working on a documentary about to expose human trafficking and child abuse
And that is why
He was killed
Late and associations we have a delegate on the Cuban on side
Throwing some
Sticks into the wheels trying to slow down the process
I have it I'm just to try to derail these talks
I'm going to put this cash in my wallet
Look on your take your mobile telephone device
Right now
Chester Bedingfield
John podesta and tell me what you see
Chester Bennington
This delegate is not a huge Linkin Park Fan.
Lean heavily more to the Weezer side of the table
This a delegation would like to point out that
Attempting to broker but you cannot discuss a John podesta
Without also disgusting his illegitimate son
Subsequent murder suicide
Well well if not heard Alex bring up this particular illegitimate son conspiracy
It is arson
Not if you would not be opposed to it
Absolutely
Sebono
Well then you know without further Ado I would like to offer and put on a table
A one-state solution one country under God
Qanon Alex Jones
Council members
That rule over us
In dialogue with
A congress
That is filled with
You know citizens but only American
Course only white American
Patriots
And they can vote
Find
So yes can we agree to this single-state solution
With what
If that is the qanon please stop
Talking bad about Alex
We will need that confession from you
Qanon does not seem to like it but
It's it's been a long
And
Stupid War
Do you know yes sometimes missiles are fired from our side
Into your side Q's Alex Jones
But we would love it if we weren't you know housing open-air prison
And
You know cut off from
Supplies
Both Medical
Elementary is that okay
We can I think we can agree on I think we can agree to these terms
Will even accept the grammar issue
Alright I'm sliding it across the table to the
I've been on the air for 25 minutes
Information
The most important information I've ever covered the truth
Who they really represent V
Your folks
Tricon
Right in the
Blueprint what they're fine
You ever been in your kitchen
You open up
Richard Fox gone
Sun-rising you look down the valleys
Never had one of those magic moments
What is the opposite of antifa
President
Smoking
I hereby declare
Nothing
So close
Believe in God
Garbage juice
Isabel
I'm seeing Santa Claus
Your brain is made
I can't I just can't
Dammit
And now some coverage of a sale 2019
Knowledge
I can't believe that broke down at the end
That's the true disappointment lot of progress there
My life
I just hate to be called
A little shity
Teddy baby
How you know it wasn't meant to be you know I thought that you know what I think it would really sealed it was
Was that your culon calling Alex Jones
The Patriot
Pay3x
F****** headphones were taken off of me
I mean
Well
Talks broke down you're concerned about what
Well Alyssa Lies
Wouldn't even notice you were gone
Okay anyways
A lot of fun fellows
You know like I said at the beginning
We've had requests to do
Crossover it's it's a bizarre one because our topic
Pixar so similar
In many ways
Because Alex has to get up there every single day Q lazily rights
Like two drops every week or so
And
So you know your guy is way more
Public facing he's going to get
Dude you know he can have people sue him for what he's saying
Where is qanon
Way more of a coward
Hiding
Anonymize
Kaiser posting on 8th
Chan
But I am glad that recently we heard Alex kind of reneging
There are some things that are true some things that aren't
Accu is good and that he
He's he has to eat
Eat crow by the way
Has he eaten any Crow since you mention that during his like collar that
Who loves q and wanted to kill
No not really he's
I think after he said that he was expecting a Q and The Q followers to be like
Isn't this great we got Alex on our side now and
Overtures
And so he got mad and said that most of them were full of s***
Like a week later it was like
Seems like a tiny footnote and I did not notice anybody in the
Qanon Community even reacting to it
Probably just cuz they don't really listen to Alex and if they do they like great
But they don't
I not going to go online and discuss
I said Travis did you notice any Alex Jones talk after that.
Seem to want to renege on his
No no
Just dropped after
I've always thought of Alex's kind of like a gateway drug for these sorts of
Mental processes
And I think getting into Q requires a lot more investment no give you got a like
You use pretend critical-thinking skills you have to
Read
Ostensibly
You have to hunt down these things
Where's Alex
Cuz you're served to you on a screaming silver platter
So
I don't I feel like anybody
Actually
Getting into
The Q research
Quote it past the point where they
Really
Have any interest
If he doesn't recognize that if he does realize that he's angry about it but he also probably
Doesn't realize that that market is not open to
It's true that we might be looking at the
The kind of
The Wayne of non-interactive non gamified you know system of cancer
Alex is definitely
Play the king of at least
In America
And then you know the need for something to do
Due to not just sit there
And get screamed at because you're obviously boiling with rage and
Fear at the end of it all
And you'd love to turn that into
2 something where
Are you feel involved in
Maybe that's why she went on came in
I mean yeah it
It provides the like the illusion of activity
Right Alex
Alice Eve
Kind of dedicated to make
I'm sure his audience remains
Except for paying him for supper
So everything is already being done
M4u
As long as you give him money
Then he will fight the fight for you
You know that kind
Where is it seems like with qanon
People are active
Participant
In creating the mythology
Unearthing I guess I can't remember the last time that Alex advocated anyone
Somebody
He doesn't Advocate anybody go to a protest
Never said
But anybody should vote I don't think he's ever said
Did somebody should go vote
In order changed
Call baby for truck but not
People in Mobile but also just looking online at stuff I think
The shift and and how conspiracies are becoming more gamified I need
Start a little part of Infowars it was called like the dick or something and I'm sorry.
Spell cuz like trouble for a lot of people on his message boards talking about
Stuff like that
I think he got kind of burnt didn't want that much engaged
Is Vans
Like whenever
See videos from time to time if I'm running into his fans
Doing everything to get away from you
He's about use a dinosaur insensitive like
He's old school and he doesn't want
I do agree that I think it probably would be
For him to turn his business model into something at work moving forward but
I think it is just
You can't do it
PS4 something like almost like
Russian bass Super PAC
Does not know
According quote does not coordinate
With Alex Jones
What is doing its own thing on the side
How balikesir you know
Conspiracy
You have no proof the Rambo Joe Biggs didn't leave in order to do exactly that startup
Discussion
For doing this
A huge leak
Avicii went on Great Awakening Discord
Give me run by Dustin Nemo's
Who's quite a big
Your figure
In in the Acura. Industry
Right yeah
It it's it is very much
Understandable that Alex would want to kind of
Endorse
Discount discussion
Because
The amount of insane
Anti-Semitism stuff stuff is just like literally
The Jew
The Jewish
Cartoon caricatures
Rubbing his hands
Together
There was
There was one that was just
You know what would you rather this or that and like one side was
Like the Nazis and the other side was like
Tifara something
That's it that's a more direct
Hey, like we loved Nazis
He's then usually that like antifa is the real not
Cease but
Jeffy's this discussion areas get in
Incredibly talks
To break quickly
Understandable that will
Be hard to
Do anything about it
Yeah yeah I think it takes
Controller
The control that he has
His narrative
Be too attached
That over anti-semitism
Over Nazi apologia
Where at
You can control however he presented self even though presentable poorly
Show
But he's not going to get burned by a Discord leave
The whole the whole thing
Is that is that you know what
Like you don't need to rely upon any particular media Source anymore
You can you say do your own Reese
You can confirm your own personal biases
The idea is that you don't have to rely upon
CNN or even like
Alex Jones cuz they're they're doing the same thing in their kind of
Skyview Weather Service
Just tell you what's going on
And they're kind of tell you what
Directions
But yeah it. Yeah they that the vision of like how people surf understand
Edit people discover the truth for themselves
It's a difference in tone like
Hear que se investigated
Yourself it does seem like he's actually saying you should go invest
Alex will say
I'm up
Question
Format is like
Please don't actually go look at
Basically
These peace talks were funded by the
The knowledge fight
Qanon Anonymous Park
You can find both of them
Your favorite podcast app
You can follow him on Twitter
At knowledge underscore fight at
Qanon anonymous
We like to think both of these
Generous emotional labor
We can neither confirm nor deny that Alex Jones was
Shorting these peace talks
Thank you so much guys for 4
Agreeing to do this with us
Alex