Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Jordan Jordan
How was your first experiment experience with
Pandemic
Play the other night you just got a grill
Delightful burgers
Equitably was very widely recommended by our listeners
Jay-Z and
I don't know why we lost
I think that was part of
The learning curve though
We are just taking it out of the box figuring out how to play
You're going to lose
I got to
Self-conscious
Not feel like you're kind of dumb
Yeah you know
I lost you
We lost because of the timer
And the built-in
We could have won if we had more time
That's how the world is going to climate change kills us all
I know a lot about Alex Jones
Indeed we got episode 2
Dudes from qanon anonymous
And perhaps
Thank you to everybody who was all the positive
Departure from our format worried about the idea of how it was
Receive
Baltimore
I was very positive nice things
Jordans
The present-day that Monday was that
Present present
Take that rule this week
What present-day episodes one of the things I strive to do is be close to current as possible
Going to cover things that are
I want it
Do that
Because I started covering Wednesday May 8th
Yeah and I realized
It's all episode
But there was
Much going on on it
I couldn't leave this uncovered
Sounds good
Signed up and are supported to show
First of all
I'm a policy wonk
Text Kevin
Extant
I'm a policy wonk
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk Ruku
Thank you
Somebody donated an elevated level
You are now technocrat
Natalya brilliant someone sodomites
Has a career
Jesus Christ
Wednesday
I forgot what
Jose
Inconsiderate
So maybe this is the best present you can possibly ask
What was the first
Half hour 40 minutes
Very depressed
Clinical depression level symptoms
Just heard of a cross-section
Embodies
Depressed vibe
Here's what's happening
Yeah Michelle right now
Because things are so bad this country I think talking about it is he's almost a way of just making it a four-wheeler chain
I really really really do.
We have to do some really really drastic things
Did you see in person
I wouldn't got to run about a restaurant that wouldn't try to do what the Democrats
I would I would definitely let them know
I thought you were aware of their criminal activity
You can do anything
If you can do anything to let these criminals
Because they're consolidating power
Worse by the day
Fatalistic Elementary
I'm not doing it
Like whatever
Well it's kind of him showing his cards
Coming around to the position of like whatever I'm doing isn't
Do get sued a lot right now
Is this Justice
Super weird vibe I don't think that clip fully bodies
Those parts were there just like
Frequent
4-second pauses
Where he's just like
Are you going to see you again
I don't know what
It's sucked out of him
Is going on here I don't even know what I
I need any more do I want guns
I had
So many theories
Could possibly be going on
You don't need to have Siri
He will just tell you
Opening 20 minutes
You did watch something
You know I got the vibe that he was really depressed and it's something must be up
Good friend
About 40 minutes and he let us know exactly what's going on
And what has caused
Will to live
What time
Last night it was exactly what I thought it would be
At this point I thought it was Avengers endgame
Thought like
Pizza Avengers and it's the only thing
I thought that was for sure it
It's a little more
And worse
So incredibly boring show incredible today
So pathetic
Eclipse
I thought for sure
It is not engaging all right what it is
The people so weak
And so soulless
I thought
Following in the real world
Forsaken ism
Nasm CPT
You can get around something about Loki or
Actual devil worshippers
And that they see themselves as their food
I just thank God I'm out those people
Chicken around me
Watching their enjoyment
Was
Soul-sucking
The wash
And
Is the movie hail Satan
Waited just called hail Satan documentary about the satanic temple
Farcical a little bit
Are you going to get into it later in the episode
We'll talk about it but
Hail Satan
Documentary
Wheatley destroyed the beginning of his broadcast
That was my first question what are you go
From this
I don't think he allowed his kids to go put on a false nose and glasses
Mustache incognito
You seen the movie you probably drinking well
The baby this depression that is manifesting it's just a hangover
Mister put in a good light
Call dependent
The possibilities are there like you saw Satanist
Senna documentary
Ergo
Losing the will to live
Listen to documentary 323
A little sloppy the next morning all there
Long pauses between words
Equally
He sees this documentary and he goes on
About how's the Satanist
There are Lowdown
Brokeback
Soul sucked
Is normal satanic imagery
That's all the people in the audience
Penney's
Specifically take
A lot of those ideas
Putting on to
To the Satanist
And you'll see very clearly in this
40 dozen
He takes little characterization
And applies them
The Democrats
In order to conflates miss the Democratic
Somebody's doing that
I can tell you're not just here but in many other areas
The actual operating system
Like a computer program like Windows
Party
I remember
Air Force generals tell him that 2017
Dallas wealthy area
Reborn
White trash 84 message
Wait a second I got to pause there for a second
Alex
Like his whole brand proposition is
Defense of attacks on white people
And white trashes one of the
Most derisively
About poor white people
Completely in congruous with someone
With the market share that Alex does
Would be okay with like
Throwing that around to insult some other white people
Depressed you know your filters are away at their lowest
Directions
What do they have left
But even though I was surrounded I still
Couldn't believe that it was his lamp
I meant to write some notes last night when I got my number today
Washing
Hail Satan mystery movie
That's the Democrats
First 5 minutes
Oh my gosh
Operating system
There shall be Democrats
Images
So
Very strong
Siri is 2y
He sees
The Satanist
Send the documentary and he says oh my God it's the Democrat
I have
I want to say like the depression that he was manifesting
Episode
Kind of made me feel a little bit gross and sad
And that's what's causing
The previous night for this episode he gone to the old Cinema
18 the documentary hail Satan
Which
I mean the first question you had is the first question anyone has
Which is why the f*** would you go and do that
What if what if
Exactly what
It's gratifying in Subway
You can't just get that same charge
From Reading like a book by my uncle who wrote books
Uncle would be more than enough for him to
Wrote a number of books about multiple personality disorder and how it's caused by
Luminary
See this movie this documentary that Alex
Really pretty interesting and I would be
The story of the movie
Documentary follows a group of people who advocate for marginalized groups
And particularly against
Depression that comes
Disguised
Christian principle
Protecting
Separation
And they formed this satanic temple in order
The force the issue
Right there be like you're going to erect the Ten Commandments
Documentary follows is called the satanic temple
Explicitly don't believe in the Supernatural
Is just a metaphor that uses a powerful symbol that they will to get free press and demonstrate how much Christianity
In ways that most people just
Except as the default
For instance in 2013 they held a rally
Does Port Florida Governor Rick Scott's Bill 98 which allow children to pray at school
They specifically to illustrate that the film
The school would have to let them
They were using tulip people
Response to Satan
As a way of highlighting
You know you're probably not cool with the idea of satanic prayer in school and possibly
Maybe someone else might have
Be cool with any prayer in school
They're using that as a lightning rod
To get you to understand what your ex
Appear like
Bright
They've used the church to launch a number of purely social advocate
Started protect children project
What's the sign up on the website if their child goes to
Two schools that uses corporal punishment
Or prolonged isolation as
Fractions
After the parents Reggie
Destroyed the temple contacts
School
Using her violation
Religious principles
And post a challenge to the practice
As a way
The religious principle deer
That you are a yourquote body is inviolable
And subject only to one's own will
We just hope they can also be used for
Provide religious
Is exemption
You purely religiously-based abortion laws
Buzz Missouri
The Advocate
There were little
Little bit
PR stunt
Like when they married a gay and lesbian couple on top of Fred Phelps mother's grave
Pretty fun
The little bit
Tasteless
Make a little hilarious
It's it's on the
More
PR focused and of it
Teabagging
And maybe I'm more important.
Confrontational
I'm not on that side of things
The satanic temple
Who after Oklahoma State Representative
Planter
Ten Commandments
Insisted that that method
They didn't
State Capitol
They only wanted to illustrate why
And it work
The case Prescott vs. Oklahoma Capitol preservation
Ended up getting rid of the Ten Commandments
When Arkansas plan to put up
Misty brought back
Statue in the process of
What you got 12
The point they were driving at is very clear
It's basically high-concept social Progressive
Trolling under the guise of using Satan
Hakeem
Liberal
Members of the group don't even really have to be Satanist
To join the church as one of their New York members explained
You don't even have to be a Satanist
You couldn't be a strong Ally who believes in the political and secular actions without being super stoked about all the aphetic
So
I get what they're doing
Does f*** with ripe
Write using a lot of their tools again
Pretty much everything the satanic temple doesn't specifically about protecting
The division of church and state
Vulnerable communities
Community
Immigrant Planned Parenthood employees orchids
Get hit in school
Don't know everything about the group but from everything I can tell while my personal taste
Over some of them
It seems like you're doing important work
And are pretty effective
Well I'm inconsiderate
Almost certainly
Unconstitutional Georgia abortion
If you're going to have a religion
Exemption law
Hospital nurse refusing to treat
Is there such a religious
For that
Then almost certainly you can argue in court
That there would be a relief
Looking for a Porsche if you were safe
Logic tracks religious exemption
You could very easily
Mi religion
Specifically
Dictates that I have control over my own body
That night we were federally recognized
Religion
Exempt
I seem like a lot of what they're doing again I'm not going to bat for the organization
I don't know enough about their various chapters and there could be
Or whatever the higher-profile biggerstaff that I'm able to
Stuff that I tip my hat to
Just shorted me becoming a
But Alex
F****** hate
And he likes to pretend that he hates them because they're low down dirty fools following a little
Persona 5 Lucifer
It's pretty clear if you look into what this group does
And if you watch the trailer for the documentary
It's clear
Mostly about their social activist
Escape the
Hates about them is their social
He hates the rent providing
Pretty tough resistance
Pretty into
He hate to pay accept people of all sexual orientations of all identities
And they don't
Anybody is
Is weird
He hates take the protection
His religion is a
Exploited forever and turn them around on
Because he knows that the only argument you could really use against them
Is an argument that also erodes his religion
Hegemony
It's they have got him trapped
Is he
Use against
Whatever they're doing on a religious ground
Kia Rhodes
Is power
Advocating for an outing
That is
Going to crush all other religion
If it's it's not forcing his hand
Is that their evil work
Pretty lame and absolutely again
Their own
Stated
Position
Anytime
Recognize the people do believe in
A literal
Really are we sure about that I'm not sure that I'm at positive
There are some folk who
I've never met
This is pretty fun
In hating this
Which is a group of the documentaries about
Does an unlikely Ally
And that is
A representative of the Church of Satan who said that quote
Troll Quest for attention. Real statement
Enemy of my enemy is my friend Alex
They can agree on some
About them
Gilmore
The current high priest of the Church of Satan
Alex feels that the Baphomet statue
Get rid of religious encroachment on State Property
Is a monument
Pedophilia
Since they were children on each side of
Goatman
Gilmore quotes
Pedophilic
Fellows
Alex Jones
Church of Satan
You know it's
It's nice to see that
They can put aside all of their married
Agree to
You call a lot of
You would think that the people who were
The Church of Satan
Would be bored Center
About things that leads
You really do
Yeah
I don't know
We should be prosecuted
I'm sure nobody else will Mystic the two of us
The poor ones who were trapped
Seems to show.
True colors
So I am
Disease
Very strong scent
Triggered by watching this documentary
Lunch because they are literal
Because they are worshipping a literal Satan
He's more triggered by the idea that they make
Vulnerable
Any populations that Alex
These eyes
Non desirable
Can you imagine Alex Musk
Gone through
Listening to his arguments shot back at him whenever he
Whenever the cognitive dissonance in his brain
Exploded
That's where we are
Cuz he's like s***
They're saying the same stuff I'm saying
My only move forward is
Heavily demonize
Nnn basically manifested satanic
Exactly
And that's what he died
It's all about killing babies after they're born
And they talk about
Pedestal
And I was in the theater with all the Austin liberals
Squirming
Norfolk
The weakest of the weak the ugliest please are Satan's minions
These are Satan's servants
Death
We have to bring God back into America
Have to do it now
So I mean you see right there you have the
Desire to push a satanic panic
This desire to bring
To control
It's a good idea.
Right now is the
Perfect time for the theocracy
Sharia law
Centre-right completely different
We need to react
I don't know what that is
I just I just mentally transported to like a Mad TV writers room
Got a crack this
This out
We won't
Someone else
Sat there and Alex
Continues doing this
Throughout
Getting more extreme
Really just
Irritability
To deal with
This Titanic Temple as an actual
Intelligent
Group that is intentionally doing this
These things for political reasons
Exactly until he just turned it into even more
Nor fear
Coming for your children
Children location
Anime
Is highly funded or not
I try to make it easy to support Ash
My activity
The Great
Yes
Extreme already have your kids
The Alamo Drafthouse
So buy some f****** secret 12 so I can
Make it up
It's
So annoyed hate that now they are killing babies after they're born
Bulshit
People have already used
Is all of their other s***
Because we're in the situation that we are where you can just say any untruth in everybody's go
Going to buy it or the people you like her
You can just say either killing babies
I wonder I wonder
Like a
We've had
Progression of argument abs
Jay
I wonder how much it is and how much it is
I wonder how much of it is
Is just like
Escalation always 52
Staff
You know what else is killing baby
Birth control
Is there mom had birth
Control when they were
Things were
Stupid ideas
20 years ago when I was listening to Loveline
And they're still
Do condoms cost
These statements have your kids
Give Alex money
In most situations
The movie Ranch
You like some sort of good guy
Work for money
So
Uglier
Uglier uglier because they're ugly
A spiritual level
Michelle's onto you
Outrageous
Get caught them
I want you to stop
Alex
And we are
Listen to
Because God
He does eat does ramble a little bit after this
It's about
Some sort of like
God lyrics
It doesn't make it better cuz
What are you stopping into there is you can hurt him
Yeah
The water beer
They're trying to get you
To stop them
Glide beating up
Now wants to be he's in the stage of his career was like
Facebook
I'm losing so much money
I need to be stopped
Maybe
Maybe that mean it's an interesting
Satisfying
People
Be who you disagree
Cuz you know it's a little
Sturtevant body adjust
Application of hurting you
Your political enemies Express
F*** it out of control
Atopic
Next thing
I'm a bunch of issues next hour
Trump
Tax returns
Trump's Nobel moment
Ever done
So first thing East Bellport
On talking about Trump
And I don't really particularly care to
To talk about it because I
He knows what he's talking about
Lot of money when your
Investing in
I don't
I don't know enough
Talk to coherently about it
I'll drop off the billion.
Executive privilege
Alex is directly lion
He sang the Trump waived executive privilege about the Mueller report and that is 100% not
There was an article in the Hill from that morning
Claire's executive privilege over Mueller report
The issue was the Congress wants Leon redacted reports they can invest
Attendance
Chances that mother laid out about possible obstruction
Possible
Interesting Lee attorney general and cover-up veteran William Barr his
To provide them with the document
Just let the house
Dictionary committee
To schedule vote
Congress
Trump's Administration executive privilege
Basically
Even if you do that
You're not going to
Get your report
It also kind of feels like threatening to hurt a hostage to get your Co kidnapper out of
Not a great metaphor
This threat didn't work bar was held in contempt
Bottagra switch for something
It sounds so serious
Anythink
Destructive
Investigation
Whether or not
Previously
Obstructive jaundice
Nothing matters anymore in the government is a circus
That's important is it Alex's literally
Really saying that Trump waive his right to executive privilege
Opposite is true
This isn't over explicit example of him telling his two plus two equals five
The very same thing
Accuses his opponents in the video doing all the
The time
Alex is directly lying to his audience
Necessarily
This is
Something is demonstrable
Actually
You can find out what the truth is about that exact opposite
Right
This one if he is
Like maliciously lying or wrong
Stupidly
Because what he
Is that
The simple fact that we have the Mueller report
Because he
Could have possibly
It's possible that it is the result of
Profoundly
Poor thinking
Yeah
Except that on almost any other day on May 8th it was in the news the discussion
Executive privilege Visa V the Mueller report
It seems difficult for me to think it was like him
Dumbly
Miss asserting something or misunderstanding
The actual report
Redact
Kind of think it has to be
I don't know why though
Give me back to your stupidity
Possibility
Him a certain executive privilege over this isn't tougher Alex
He could do that.
It's not a hard line to walk for no collusion
Tough to figure out what the motive
Lying
Specifically about this
I don't know whatever the case
Reality
So
Par for the course
Big
Story bigger than Satan
Pretty f****** b****
Satanism
I'm shocked that we got through all that
I'm stuff this quickly I thought that was going to take
Maybe a week
Alex has another story here that I honestly think
Is perfect
It's dehumanizing
Norteno what's going on internally
I happen to have
Until here
As fast as they can
To have
Guess what I have
Meme
You guys remind me
When he said Dan Lyman was coming up I was like
Thank God
Cakewalk
Never been more wrong in my life
Shadowing for later
From your horse, imagine what was there
I'm going to cover this
At the start of the next hour
That you're not going to
To the people that have to censor the show imagine
Salsa music
Sjw
Upwards of half of them
Are becoming program and brainwashed
And I'm totally freaking out
And then quote
Be
Good teachable moment
I believe
And ourselves
Explicitly what's going on
Alex's pretending videos internal intelligence
What's going on in Facebook
But all he really has something
Already found on PBS
That's all he ever has
He has no inside information
Get no high-level sources
He has publicly published articles that he covers and
Pretends matches intelligence that he's already received
Literally
Public information
On the show and we don't often stopped
Of what he's doing
So one of the other things that's important to point out we already
Is BBs
The matches intelligence that we already have
And that is a referee
Prince to the fact
The PBS article is just
The transcript of an interview
With this guy named Casey
Newton
And it's just a conversation about an article Casey
About content moderator February
The information that Alex said it matched up with
Is the article that Casey wrote In The Verge
In February which is the
Previous Intel that Alex had the pit BBS article matches up with because it's an interview with the writer of that article
Nefarious
I'm so much
Explain
The process of how
He pretends their sources
Things match up with Intel
That is exactly what's going on here
The PBS article
Right about the conversation
About the art
York
The trauma that social media job
Horrifying picture of the working conditions at cognizant
A company subcontracted by Facebook to battery contact
It's not the same company
OKC in the interview does make
Make a good point I think it's
Pretty fair
Facebook employees
In everything but name
Probably legal distinction
Will the government like FEI does security contract right
Work in the same
Acura
The orders that Facebook gives them
Workers
Racist content
And all manner of other.
Deeply disturbing things that people post on Facebook
The author of this piece
Experience
From the work
Gun
Even while sleeping due to threats for people whose content would be
Or at least fears of reprisal people whose content
Sensor
It sounds
Leica an abusive fact
That doesn't
Korean animation
Intent micro management of employees time
What they can and can't do with their break
Ineffectual Council
Towing services
Being provided in harsh productivity and accuracy
Spectations all add up to
Hostile environment
Even if these people weren't being made to experience Horrors
As a part of their job
Employees describe the experience of talking to a co-worker is trauma bonding
Do quotes go hang out on the roof
Code for wanting to jump off it
One employee describes how you always loved cooking but now is afraid to be around knives
Because every time he's reminded of a video where a man is stabbed
The death and cries out for his mother is
He dies
And now he also believes autonomy
Terrorist attacks were false Flags
And wakes up every morning with a gun in hand and performs in arms
Take this home
He was recently diagnosed with PTSD and began
I'm f***** up man
I don't think it's possible to do the job and not come out of it with some acute stress disorder
PTSD
This is the closest
Anything
This article comes
What else is basa
Thing is almost gleeful reporting
The quote basically has with the moderators
Brainwashed
Freaking out
And they're sending them
The Mentalist
They didn't
Send this guy to Ventolin
Tiffany Scott help
Because
Death awfulness
Experience
They broadcast
Because people do exactly every single day
More nuanced
I got
Interviews
About this
Does they generally do make a point that
The bulk of what they deal with is maybe a slur or bullying
The most of it is that sort of thing
But I would respond
Yeah I could never
Even come close
Watching Christ
I could never even come close to people want
Affect you
Yeah
It doesn't matter
It doesn't matter how much of a snowflake Alex might call you for that response
It's a response
To your Humanity
The article is about the human that comes from running content moderation in
The same way companies run cost
Sporcle
It's a brutal job where people expected
The awful thing
Exposed
That make an impact on them
And the greatest indictment of this article is not on the people
Posting f*****-up
It's a Facebook
And it's subconscious
Better job of take
Care of their employees
But you talk about heavy ideas
You can have these
Horrible reaction
To the work that you're made to do
But because the work is
Really awful and
The place is run poorly most people end up working there for like 8 months
Yeah and then you leave
Is liquor
And a place where you worked for 8 months
Isn't going to pay for you to go get help
So these are the issues
Coming up in this article that
Pretty much
Middle finger at these companies in the
Very Alex only exist
First of all not at all
Specifically it's mostly about like
Murder videos
He only exists as a phantom as a
Byproduct of doing business
Like they don't even give a s*** about the idea that
Of him as
Monster Run
Anything like that
It's the it's about the
Yeah I know they're there
Basically predators
And then they
F****** throw them away
Life
I get tortured all day
And then I go home
Maybe.
Articles about news
Important conversation
Engage that conversation
You be able to score points against Facebook
Actually looking at what was being discussed.
They're exhibiting weakness
Rather attack the people who
Maybe but I don't think he's even doing that
I think he's a monster
Not an opportunity for him to make everything about his
Light
It's korachi
Cheap self-serving
Trying to make this argument
Victor
I think he's going to get into it more
Later
He's using the story is kind of rational but he's right
About
The wrong way to look at
I would say
The interview Casey Newton did on TBS literally had nothing
Alex Jones
The conversation was
Discussion of this
Investigator
Honda moderation fact
The very
Interview
When introducing the
Mention that a bunch of people recently kicked off Facebook app
Instagram and that's why there's a renewed conversation about case
February
Basically just
Explain why it makes sense for them to have the
This conversation
Yeah that's
The platform
So if its next flip
I just want to play
To understand
This is what like we now
Understand
The article in the source
Material that you talkin about
And here is how he talks
Facebook
That when they tell him and then they go watch years of my show these people absolutely
Is the angle and the narrative that he's using
These people who are suffering
Horrible consequences
Being exposed videos
Inshot
Into that
Some racist
For content in
Written form
Amb a lot of people there
Towards
I'll bring your not examining things
If you're secure
There is a
Towards
Automatic
When
When you're exposed
A conspiracy
C content audit
Which this is set up to
Because their workload has an expectation
You will just
Be exposed to these ideas for a
Cuz you got to get on to your next
Piece of contact you after moderate overrides
Critical thinking skills irritability
Two bit like looking to acquainted
You'll just be
Muslims want to kill everybody
And if you're not careful
Your default
You could let your guard down
Eventually
True
So Alex is using
That reality as
They're supposed to my content and then they realize that I'm right about everything and then they're getting
Baker acted in sentimental
Because she
Going
The sjw globalist
Some sort of an evil force but everybody
Steve's
Do you know that they are wrong and I'm right
Everyday
Crazy necessarily
Social
The moments moments early on
But because I have the time to look into
Claims
To deal with what
Is actually
It look into historical context
Listen to
More of the show that anybody probably
Come Away With It with
No
He's right about any
Yeah so I'm living proof
But that argument
Yeah cuz
Droog living in
Clockwork Orange
I mean if I had to
Do
300 of these episodes
If I if I had
The sword of time could
Strength of
For someone who works in a place
Office
I couldn't do the show
The way that you are
I think I probably would have
Head must have any larger context and it was just
Short little clips of him saying some
Something very confidently that done
Just bombarding concert
Play over and over and over again
The short clips
And you're just
Eventually it's going to inspect your brain
Yeah
There's money behind it the propaganda
Has
Craft
It's that
What we were starting to understand we didn't
People really knew
Would be a byproduct of
Attempts to moderate
Without those people
Who
This work
You have unusable
Destroyed
Fire
Everywhere
It's a post-apocalyptic
The fair assessment
Is it what's a actually this guy was arguing for is
Suggesting one
Protrude
Treat these people who work in the
The same way that you do
EMT
Give them
Give them higher
But because
Have an in-house
Counselor for
I'm not available lot of the time
Whatever Mental Health
Resource would be very important
Treat them like they're doing the service
For society
Because in many ways they are
I don't think there's much room to argue against
I know I absolutely agree with you
Gets a lot of mileage out of turning it into being about himself
As opposed to it being about beheading videos
Shooting
Well I mean I mean sink every time you go on Facebook
It's because of a moderator that I'm
Maybe not seeing a murder rate crying
Exactly the article
The argument
Excuse me is
Alex can make an argument
He makes it about him
They're doing all this to attack me
Nose on some level that the argument as it released
About
Horror
Jackie can't make that
That argument if he wants this to be
Be compelling and successful
So it makes it about himself
He might as well come out in
Like I used to watch faces of death before I went to sleep every night you know for sure
What kind of realize that was a dead end
But he didn't really want to
Get into it
He does get back into it a little bit later like shorts episode
Alex talks about have a Satanist
And that is that God wants
Welding montesini lowest of low Satanist
The work is Hollywood and the real shaking us to produce
Healthy
Garage
And their film Shan
That is God
The does The Killing
God
Vengeance
Is weird
There is a
He says a little bit later
Traffic may be trying to
Wiggle out
A mile or never know about real satanism
That was continued
Alright next flight
I think that's weird
The temple of
The actual sick
Right
Can you sing that they're not real luciferian
People in the documentary
AR
The
They're working for a literal Satan
And worship literal Satan
But they're also the sucked dry minions
Of true Satanist
Who are rich people takes a long time to get through his ideas
It does
Well I think he gets to talkin about
What's the version of real satanism
Sexual beautiful voluptuous woman
Businessman
This is meant to be
Because
To be soulless
This doesn't make
Why I really need
What did he say
Listen to becoming Satan
Write what what
Jamaican honey traps for businessmen because I
How did she do
Call Dad I know how the devil works
Exactly
It's nonsense
He expresses
More the idea that I was putting forth
What he is responding
You in these
People in the
Hail Satan documentary
?
Even the title there's a little bit of ambivalence
I believe it would he's responding
Two of them
Is
Resentment
Opposition
Did them because of their interest
Inequality
Look at the people in this film you can see
Gone
There's no one left there
Lowest of the low
Louis
Level
Generation
And it's a celebration death of children
Music inspirational music
Overlaid with what Alex
More
Hear that is like
Good Bad and The Ugly
Alex drawing the devil
Do the Twenty Paces and turn
That's what I
Now I want to do a hail Satan
With a. And it's just about a cab driver named
People around
I was trying to figure out a way to make that
Meat substitute
Work
Sherp
So what is really trying to
Drum up a satanic
It's pretty gross
It's really
Maybe the satanic panic
Everybody was
And everybody was still coming off the hives
You know the whole thing
What is 2019
50 years later come on
We understand
Actual demon okay and the devil
What
But here's the thing
Dude
With real
Satan demons
Omit
Does one piece of evidence
He's going to presenting the next clip
Amenaces by David
Dungeons & Dragons
Federer Aldo Rivera MO
Living
And one of the wealthiest areas
Whenever you get around well you find Satanist
National TV show
When a member of Motley Crue
Dot's Market
Show Bosch
Well
Jesus Christ
What you doing
Worship Lucifer
One-hundred-percent message
I didn't have
If your story
About
Real
Is the Mark Dice told you a story
F*** out of here
It must be so good to work for Alex when you
You can tell him stories like that really happened get the job
But you can't
A big part
Your brand as a con man
Is
Not really having
Lawson
Background contextualized
You don't get this job
Really talented
And not get something
So yeah I mean Mark Dice have to turn that around cuz it's a sign of weakness
He feels that the
Projection of I'm not good enough
You've gotten this show so in reality situation
Show
And I said no cuz I have principles
Bulshit
When was the you don't want to do
I don't know
Used to run like a memory
Improve your memory
He also used to be a pick-up artist
Scam guy yeah before he really landed on the
Getting on Ancient Aliens
Codename John Connor hotline for a while
The pile shoes
I'd like to know when this happened endocrinology
Because I would
Probably
Worth noting
Justin service of his
Later career defense
Yeah don't worry
Flying with a satanic panic
Was real
Here you go
Hyperspeed
Is anti Alex Jones
A lot of people are mad that they might overturn Roe v Wade
But we we should really be scared I was going to overturn
Christianity
Such b*******
Fingerprint
Demon
Amazing
Keanu Reeves movie Constantine Keanu Reeves movie Devil's Advocate
I could do this all day
Movies about devil
Gabriel Byrne
You might wonder about the
I literally found this to be one of the more troubling Clips I've ever heard
Alex
This is part one of
Play things that I find really disturbing the first one and then the next
Later in the episode
This is more just insane
This okay
Patrick Silicon Valley came from
Devil is a fallen angel
God did not say that
God has built
And she'll the devil doesn't really want to do it all
Tells this what been done before
What is the big
Deep stuff
Is that the devil trapped on Earth by God we got to
He knows a lot about
And there's been a lot of ancient civilizations that happen
Highly technological Jaguar
So he knows about those Technologies but he doesn't know how to build anything
So you can
Seduce people to Silicon Valley to create Silicon Valley with Promises of
Ancient technology
It is actually futurista
Speak to us
Rick
Okay this is not
This is nuts
I realize that the ultimate playing in the universe make perfect
When Alex says you're getting big
Really upsetting
Because that means that on some level
You presenting this is information that he believes
Has held back
Give you all of it
F***** up
Well
Look you don't want to do
Look if you come out on a first date
And say that you believe we're locked into a struggle of good and
Evil and that the devil is somewhere in trapped underneath
Earth
Is God dead
For whatever reason
Although that means
He's not a k a
Oso
Then
Is really get that
Give me a calculator
Now I must build
Alright
Alex
Democratic events
Or more accurately the people who are democratic
It depends on how you entirely.
I think I think
If you really listen
There's a better way to understand
The people look
They look like they're lost and that's the high-end
Apple's Immortal Oceanside
Weather for the enemy that they could simply
Finally
Have power
Empower
They found the Dead Space
And now they're only wish
Is it
Deposit
That I think that Zach
Clip
Perfectly
If you look
Through
As a defensive whites
Okay
Because what he's talkin about is people at liberal rally
They are gone
The devil has taken over them because they're on a quest
The power of black lives matter rally that I was
Or the woman's March
Diversions of
How are that they're trying
To take
More liberation
Scrum
Societal oppression
It's more about making things
Equitable
Empower overweight
Straight male
Right
The contextualisation of
For equality
Trying to take
Power over us
Yeah
If it's purely a defense of
Unit system wearing
Straight white male Christian
Are seen as the de-facto
Default
Swore and where the power lies
Just criticizing Danny
Turn
I've seen it but I don't know if the audience has
Sorry if you were waiting
Ryu would be but
Leanne Elizabeth Warren
I'm so I don't know I don't think
To staying but underneath what
You saying
The effect
Of what
Communicate to his audience
The people
He's trying to get them
Do not like
And the reason he's trying
To get them to not like them
8tracks
If you understand the code
Using SBA
The defense
Of of white
Default
Or whatever
Straight white male Christian
Absolute
I mean
There's room for semantic debate
I'm going to leave
So he gets done talking about Satan
For now
Comes back up
But he's mad about Facebook
Instagram
Initially that was what was really making him depressed at the beginning of the episode
And it might have been it might have been a part of it
He complains about how we need to break up
Social media
Teddy Roosevelt broke up the railroad
Cuz there was Monopoly
And I can't tell you how excited I am but how this clip goes
Roosevelt
He said
The railroads competition pay
The ship their own fruit
Underground
Pacifica
Promise to have your ass arrested
Commerce
A thousand miles
The kids
Oh boy
I can't tell you how much I f****** love that
What I say was a Gunsmoke
All the time
Haha
We're just trying to figure out how to make
TV shows in this era tell programs ever to air
Gunsmoke
20 seasons
It ended its run when Alex was one-year-old
A 14in was done before Alex was ever born
Somehow I
Unspoken Bonanza
It was ended long before I was coming
The s*** out of you
Gunsmoke was mostly show by Lawman being forced to make hard choices
Curiously High incidence
Applause of episode circle surrounding
Children Native American
Something that must have been a Hot Topic
As much as I'd love to talk about
Episode
YouTube
Topix up a little
1 years ago
I'm going to be the first openly admits he really liked it
Be very open
Clear
Even when my
This is one of those cases
Actually in the next
Squidward
Here Alex is going to make clear that he's talking about that episode 407
But before I started trying to solve the mystery
Of what episode
I came across an episode from season
For called Monopoly
In the end it wasn't the right episode and I accept that
However I did watch an episode of Gunsmoke in preparation for this episode
Not tell you about it
The episode was originally aired on October 4th
It's called
Monopoly
Course I did this is important even though this isn't the right episode 2 walkthrough hauben
Gunsmoke plot
About what they're about
If that makes sense
Okay
Sheriff Matt Dillon comes to work one day to find a lovable local character
Sleeping off of wicked drinking binge
Holding cell
The drunk wakes up and says he's leaving Dillon
Which is almost as referencing when he recently claimed
50 the cops will give you your guns back when you got out of prison
Holyshit
Small clarification. It was made in the 1950s but it's Dodge City Kansas
70s what racism was there
Lots
All the time
Real hard swing Asian
Asian-American
Particularly
It makes me pretty
And so it pretty much all the other wagon cargo people
Allentown
The mysterious mr. Ivy it comes to town from St Louis
Everything and he's buying up everyone's business
So Dylan goes to meet with Ivy as lodging he finds out that he's hired Camp Spiegel as his bodyguard
Dylan and Spiegel have a history in the back years ago in Wichita
Got away with it because Dylan
Didn't have the evidence to
Victim
Spiegel's come to Dodge City and he's working for IV
This doesn't look good
Her doll
How do you leave the hotel room
He becomes a problem it might be too late
The last Freight Runner who hasn't sold out
He comes to Dylan
Received a note from ivy
Turns out he's a literate
I need Dylan
Oh no
Ivy wants to buy his company for $1,000
Which even with inflation considered would only be a little bit less than $20,000 a day
If you're running a business that sustains
It's not like that's going to be some kind of luxurious all be set for life money
Probably because that's not that much
Shmoney
Ivy leader tells him that he's going to double his rates
Apple needs to as well because
Call the flood
But he can't handle
But it doesn't matter
Cuz I have to stress
Is not a huge part of the episode
It's only there to be window dressing
For the feud between
Sheriff
Okay
V story short
Saloon girl $300 to be his alibi
Roadhouse
It scraped throat
Even with this craziness
This is still
Super Bowl
Saloon girl $300
Girl can't go around these parts
Love the trembles
Although I am
The actor who plays Tim from the characters of Gunsmoke
Gunsmoke was the Law & Order of a dick
Are they wouldn't even allowed appearances
Either way this little girl tells Dylan about the bribe
Confront
When you get to news.
It's beagle the SHOT show tremble at the local Saloon
Shot
Dylan goes to check things out
Spiegel claim self-defense
Drawing
Who killed his wife
Because he has an alibi Dylan tells him no
He knows about the bribe
Dylan
Spiegel starts to draw and Dylan and feeling shoot them dead
Who's there
In court which is a fuk
That was such a crazy person
Well
Probably would have been fine anyways
You would have gotten away with it
After all this drama IV claims he knew nothing about Spiegel's action
Dylan
Get the f*** out of town
The citizens of that China will kill him on sight
Because they love the trimbles who I repeat
Have not appeared in the previous episode
Noranda 480 episodes of its 11-year run is a radio drama
Is about a small town
Terrified
NeverBeast
Explicitly leaving behind the company that he had bought
Obviously the first issue is that care about the Monopoly
The closest he comes to it is commenting that
Is very proper
He doesn't care about that stuff
He only cares about Camp Spiegel and righting the wrongs of Wichita
It seems like
He's just
He's missing the point of Monopoly
So he's calling the guy stupid right
Subtext of the episode
He doesn't care at all
Now the natural problem with the ending of this episode
Go from an attempted literally no one in the city having transportation
Back from IV before you run
So if they take them
In the old west
It's mostly just about duels and people being found guilty by insinuation and ran out of town
Sebastian from
That's not the episode that Alex
But I didn't want my time to be wasted
Anyone is very entertaining
Roosevelt directed The Jump
Department sued in Northern security
Please company would you become a railroad Monopoly
Credit for Basta
Monopoly
Discography
As well
It's inappropriate to look at that
Executive it's always a good idea to look at the executive as being Prime
Mover behind
All positive or negative
Executive branch
Should be the business
Decided what
Whatever also also it's true that the Roosevelt was involved in this truck
Ignore that it wasn't present
Progressive Era
Sender in office
So
Askreddit
About the Gunsmoke episode
What
Royal Farms
The big local corrupt guy wanted to take
The thousand-mile so he can make the money to save his farm
Takes him a month or so to get there
But they get stopped and then when he gets there he thinks all the pictures or dad
Under the first layer all the peaches are alive
What
Bistro
Still not
Bathurst
Okay
Gunsmoke and Bonanza
Right the wrongs of my battery
But it's not available online anywhere that I can
I can find but I did read
Eminent domain
Doesn't really have to do with monopolies in the idea of
Breaking up
Ranger technology
That was where I was
This is troubling
This next clip
I legitimately think
Is one of the more
Disturbed things I've ever heard
This cup is f*****
Trivia
Can release the biome
God has to remove his protection
The devil would nucleus planet in 10 seconds
Did not remove his protection
But for 1 hour
I want to know what's going to happen next
Boom commercial
He doesn't get back to us
That's upsetting upsetting
Yeah they're going to Nuke the planet release race specific bioweapons
I can't because of God's protection is going to remove an hour
.
Your s*** about time
Omniscient and omnipotent
Just outside of
The consequences of that are going to last
Way longer than ours as
Arbitrary
Also
Deeply implied by that cut off by commercial is that he knows when that's going to happen
Preparing preparing for protection
An hour Devil's attack
Alex prepared
Totally cool
That's Disturbed
That is very f*****-up way of thinking
It's a level
Untethered
You hear that
A lot of crazy stuff before but
Get to that level
That definitely isn't
Foreign to us
Him coming out and saying gato released
Protection for an hour and that's when we're going to
Hit
That is
Pretty
Creative
Also also
Protection is the only thing keeping us from being nuked
And hit by biome
Yes which implies that God can protect
But isn't that our
Yeah and also
Doesn't for the rest of the horrible things that go up
Implied
Everything weapons
I foreshadowed earlier
Through it unfortunately I can't
Because his appearance
Very harsh
Resonances
To Alex Jones
The present day
Dip his toe into a story that I started looking at
Very interesting requires
Unpacking
Bus schedule
Did you switch
You're borgia.com, exclusively there
Russell's Buster suspension Sunoco station
In the United States
Ono immigrants bring disease
The window dressing
North Station
Brussels
Close
Stopped a serving
Another bus stop because of
In order to understand the story that Alex
Understand
Surrounding context
I'm going to
Truth there is a story he's covering in a Belgian news Outlet
It does discuss the plan to not have buses stop at the North State
Patient the garden
Rumors
Hilarious brick
But as is always the case
There's more to the story
He cares to understand
There's a large population of itinerant immigrants or is there called transmigrant
Who are for lack of a better word stuck
Even flight from various countries of turmoil ultimately arriving in Europe
North to Belgium
Many of them finding it almost impossible to make
Where they feel they would have less of it
Sent back to where they originated
For many of them it's as simple as
Improper
Application to make the trip
Awesome because
Fled
Mosey on out
Some others wish to stay in Belgium butter afraid to apply for Asylum
Apply only government
Specifically rule called the
Supposed to deport Asylum Seekers back to their home country
But under the right circumstance
They're allowed
To send them back
First EU country they arrived
For many of these immigrants in picture of that would be Italy
And there's a reason they didn't just say
Dakota twenty-five-year-old Sudanese man
Financial Times
Conditions are bad
You stay in the camp and there is no
They don't want to risk applying for Asylum only to be sent back to Italy where they'll be putting a
And they can't make
The trip cross the English Channel
Weird in-between
States
Human rights Charities work with people
Established
From the Dublin rule cuz many are
The process and apply for Asylum
Which give the positive indication about a Direction
Forward there could be
First Progress
Yeah
But they're even greater risk
Because even though they're not
Supposed to do so generally
Sometimes refugees are deported back to the country
Left
Edit 2017
The flare up
After their allegations that people who
Snapbacks
Hibbett tortured when they return
These people were sent despite warnings from international human rights groups
The government indicated that they were aware that some of the people who were sent back
We're from the regents
Refer
Blue Nile and South kordofan
Which at made them automatic recipients
It's status
The government's motivation
Quote cleaning up
Public areas where immigrants
We're congregate
Places
Gardener
Maximilian
It's probably on clear off the
The back here why there would be large populations
Coming to this Garden
Just think it's where the train just
Barks so they get off the train
That's not true
Immigrants come to Garden North specifically because it's an
Established humanitarian
Several non-governmental organization
Together to provide essential
Emigrate
Start a new life
Doctors Without Borders Oxfam the Red Cross
And some more local
Established Center within the garden Nord
As a place where
Help help
That no one else is providing
This ranges
Psychological Services Medical Care legal assist
Distance food clothing Wi-Fi
Electrical outlets
To charge the phone
Walden
The psychological service
Aspect of this is really crucial
According to psychologist who works
But the humanitarian hub
Kisima trend of immigrants developing depression based on harsh dissolute
Perfumed right
They're completely disillusion
They never imagined that they'd be sleeping outside and
With a rule of law
So that's a little bit of a bummer
Yeah
It's a bummer but it's also part and parcel of a reality that there are these people
Providing the scalp and that's why there are large groups
Of immigrants congregate
Lifesaver
This
This life-saving
I'm in there other good things
Mansion positive
I volunteer organization called bxl Refuge
Just launched in September 27th
Urgent people to open their home
The refugees
Who found themselves in the impossible situation
When they began they were only able to find 10 families
House of strangers
3000 families
Opening up their spare room
What family
The gillis's
Refugees in
One of them speaking
Euronews
Quotes this family in Brussels is very very good
People in Belgium are very kind
They love everyone and we return that feeling
These people have welcomed us I don't have any problem in submitting
For Asylum
Their many good-hearted people were going out of their way
Something to help mitigate the problem and that is a very inspiring
Time there something
Inspiring there's something equally depressing
Any kind of optimism
Nationalism
The political situation in Belgium
Pretty rough fart
The Flemish nationalist party the new Flemish Alliance
They became the largest party in the chamber of Representatives
And in the Senate
The new Flemish Alliance
Sucks and their leader Bart do ever
Clear
Towards
Proposing Prosecuting them
And seizing their cell phones to send the message
The quote Belgium is not
The place to be
In a good news bad news situation
That they were part of which included the prime minister
The bad news is that they left the route
Because prime minister Charles Michel
Refused the new Farmers alliances demand that he
His plan just you and migration
Member states other than the US
And because Michelle just
In Flemish
Pulled out of his government
This is
Because there's still the largest political representative
The phobic
It push further hard right
It's concern
A what are the reason
It's a hold on to their far-right face
Which is starting to be eroded more f***** up
70s party
Blom's belong
Heart rate for a nationalist parties are starting from an unfair advantage
Visit their movement traces its roots to the
Movie post-world War World
It's called the front part
Well the party may have been started with Flemish representation is a front
Are we going to
Call boy
They started with an interest in Flemish representation
Is being a primary
Concerned by the early 1930s
Pretty far right
Activate absorbed by the Flemish National Union
An explicitly authoritarian party that were over collaborators with
The Nazis in World War II
Because Hitler had promised them greater Flemish right
It deserves mention
Did VNV that's there
Initials
Fiat
The Flemish Nation
Union pob l
I was collaborating with the Nazis
Before they invaded Belgium
With the hopes that they could help him
Which led directly to his party organized
The deportation of Jews
So you can see how that history gives people a little bit
Hard right nationalist
Flemish National
Sparty's
After the liberation of Belgium by the Allied Powers the VNV was outlawed as a political party for Fairly obvious
This led to the rise of
The Christian Flemish people
Wageworks
To make sure that they were nationalist
But also didn't put anyone in office would collaborated
That was nice of them
It's an interesting proposition
Do you know what
Oliver North
Oliver didn't hire him
The grouping nationalist in nature but also fairly moderate left in Polish
So a lot of folks jumpship which would eventually be merged
Block
The block was a very specifically anti-immigrant far hard right National
Party
Their slogan in the 1987 election was quote
Which sounds really bad one Splendid the word
Our own Drake.
The Party founded
Success with focusing on immigration issues as opposed
Stop harping too hard on Flemish
In the same way that our right-wing May profess an interest in small confirm it
More effective as an electoral strategy
And it worked well for The Lawns block
Growing from relative obscurity political party by the late night
Then the year 2000
A complaint was filed against the party broke Belgium
Platform
We hate everyone that bite based on race
For an entirely separate educational system
A foreign children
New taxes for businesses that hired non-european foreigners
And restrict
Benefits for non-european
Foreigner
The case of bounced around courts until 2004
The court of cassation
Ruled that their party platform was
Racist
Are effectively disbanded the Party by
Put their tails
Between their legs
You can just move.
Television
The state funding of Elections if they aren't
Access to that money
Groundhog
F****** they reorganized in 2004 Islam's belong
Which is now the party
Is challenging the new Flemish Alliance from the right
So you can kind of see how this all fits together a little bit better now
The situation
You are not going far enough we want to kill him
Interesting conversation
What are the members of the new Flemish Alliance
Government was their migration Minister Theo Franken
Who incidentally was the one responsible for Sunday
Protected record
Bee Gees back to the sedan
To be tortured
Michelle government Franklin
Play in baking
I'm sure that the issue of gardener.
In Brussels was not
Taken care of
His new Flemish Alliance
To the hard right position on immigration wishes
The Punisher deporte
People not
To help them
Another reason groups like logs belong
Happy to make out to be even further right
To make sure that he's not evil
Forgiven
Does
They start attacking them from the right
The terrible situation
The party with the most members in Brussels parlor
The local
Brussels
Is the Socialist
A large majority of the members of body are not hard right now
Most of them
Members of the brothels Parliament
Alleviate what is prices for these
But it'd be pretty vocal that they can't solve any problems without federal government
Cooperation
There's just that there's collaboration that
To be done
To that
Complaints
And request
New Flemish Alliance migration Minister c.l. Franklin
0 euros
I've always been against this migration
Can hubs
If Brussels wants to be for illegal transfer they should go ahead but not at
Sixpence of the federal government
He doesn't give a s***
Folks like this only care about you
Escalate to the point where they feel that they can rationalize dealing with their problem
So the problem has been allowed
So I know this is been bomb
But I think it's important to understand the forces
Does a play when we see
Situations be lied about
Said our country
We live in a place where most of us are incredibly unaware About Belgium
And the day today
Easy to manipulate
Forum events are often the most fertile soil for local propaganda
Because the disconnect
Involved and almost guaranteed ignorance of the topic
And your listener
This is why Alex loves to try to
Statistics from the UK
Knowing his audience won't look.
Contact behind the data
And the same is true
Situation here at the Garden.
A Brussels
All all the situation is
The forces at play
Time from what I've been able to sort out from the reporting ivory
The fact that buses are saying that they are going to stop
Station
Does
Appear to be
Actually accurate
However it should be pointed out that it's not the
Government
On the bus
The union that represents Transportation employees decided that they weren't going to be stopping at the underground bus terminal there
Instead rerooting to nearby
In an article in the Brussels time
Concerns about scabies and
And there's literally no
Either disease
And I did
The group that runs the bus
Federal Public Health Ministry
Just an unfounded rumor
The real issue
Comes down to complaints
It's from customers
About the smell the litter and being hit up by train
There's a climate where people don't steal
These rumors appeared
It was enough Justice
Navigation for the train
Unfortunately I placed at the buses to Rhode gear S2
Who's mayor in New York year is not happy
Mobility problems
Traffic has brought with it
Stop the buses for
I'm stopping at a city
Compressor
Quotes comprehensible in unacceptable
The federal government to abandon place as important as a gardener
I call on all parties involved to find a sustainable and worthy solution for everyone
So I'm not entirely sure
Exactly what's going on
Kind of like a good strategy
Might be effective in getting the local or federal
The idea of a queef ruriiro to these buses here and I know you're not
I'm not entirely sure but time will tell
The reality of the situation of brothels
Incredibly complicated
Helped immensely by a government that was
To do what it needed
To do to help
Crisis
A huge step forward to be removing the fear that many of these refugees
Have applying for Belgian Asylum
If they knew that it wouldn't result in them being sent back to a country where they might face
Torture
Or Bachelorette
It could go a long way to getting them up back
Removal of that threat could be a big step forward
He'll be nice if a steak
Could help with getting those who wanted to apply for Asylum
UK
For instance like a lot of them
It would be decried by
Read politicians
It doesn't you're already already losing their minds
It doesn't seem realistic
Belgium
If only for that
So that was
Is a complex story
Oh sorry also adding to the complex
Itinerary immigrant
It's better there at the station
It's also homeless Belgian citizen
Likes it there's a larger issue
I'm here than just a migration
Alex refuses to look at NE
You really look at what's going on
The hard-right Nationalist
Are not the good guys
He says he hits the point
That are convenient to his married
He pulls out that there's a disease go in an immigrant
Push the immigrants are called
Narrative in recent weeks
And that's only really cares about
Stories
Just fit with his narrative
He's a month
Push Broderick it will serve to demonize population
There's literally no excuse
For someone
The people were routinely kept for months
Ellis Island
A little bit about Ellis Island from their medical screening
Specifically
German article in the American Medical Association
Journal of epic
The diagnostic protocol emphasized
Gave
Demonstrating the conviction that disease was written on the body
Dr. Albert Newt argued that quote almost No Grave organic
Disease can have hold on an individual without Staffing
Some evidence of its presence upon the appearance of a patient
Observer
They've basically relied almost entirely on looking at people
You get on his various camp
Typically 15 to 20% of the arrivals
Physical or mental examination
Of all the people were found to be sick this is.
Which is just a small percentage
Percent
And sometimes years
In the isolation units in the southernmost wing of Ellis Island
4 years
Very few very small
A lot of it was under metal
Chronic
Or severe condition
Right
Berries
A number
Less severe conditions
Might be held for a week
Will there be held in these cells
Apply for Hospital treat
Mexico
To pay for it themselves
And ultimately most of the people who were treated for disease
Ellis Island
Were deported
Not because they were sick but because they
They couldn't pay for their own hop
Fertilization
So a lot of the people that I was referring to the very small numbers
We were held for possibly books
We're just poor
Because they were poor they ended up because they applied for hospitalization
And then couldn't pay for it once they were
Fine
I find this past
It's particularly important to remember
Most were certified not with the load some more dangerous contagious
Capacity
Perform unskilled labor
Senility old-age varicose veins hernias poor vision and deformities of limbs or spine were among the primary
Causes for exclusion
It's so few of the more than 25 million arriving immigrants
Inspected by the p.m.
Were excluded setting to Baldwin
Countries almost insatiable industrial demand for
Cheap labor
Of course even though this was the case at Ellis Island wear a vast majority of people arriving were European it should be noted
The quote
Space more considerable medical obstacles to entry
Mexican border immigration
A Texas border station
Jessup
Shower disinfected
Search for lice large groups
All second and third class Asian immigrants arriving
Francisco endured physical exam
In addition to routine Laboratory Testing
A parasitic infection
Which required attention on Angel Island for water today
Health officials
Inscrutable Asian
Particularly the Chinese
Do you see a little bit of a
It's always a little bit of racism the real organ
You guys were not
Racist
But in such a ridiculously ignorant
Just like
4 million
No idea what that looks
You're sick or you're fine I don't know
My magical medical Vision can't read
Your agency
F***** up
24 things start
We set up a Visa system where American Consular Office
Before
This was specifically
Need to cut off the flow of immigrants
From undesirable Sutherland
Eastern European
Weird lay under the system between 1926
Almost 5% of immigrants
Where is during the days of Alice
The race has been around 1% turned away for medical reasons
Approximately 2
Percent turned away
The immigration system is always been a backbone
Medical rules of all
Exclusion
Before 24 of those who would
Be good cheap
And after 9224 of people
Concern for public health is Ludacris
He is merely a more overtly racist grandchild of this same
So that's my point about this
You think
All of these hard right guys right now if we didn't
System of automation
Would be like
Come on
We need you to do the factory
Totally different conversation
Cuz I need it
So
You may have forgotten
But we're talkin about
Train station
Sure we are.
So
Train station in
I think we are Alex's specifically
She's trying to apply it
His negatives about immigrants
Safeway
And then prayer
I agree
Getting the sense
This is why
I could only cover
We wanted
You start the episode Alex's
Depressed and then he starts yelling about
Before you know it
Pages and pages about
Belgium
Political parties
And here we are
Alignment brings up a new story
About this at Garden Nord
Just publish that story
For a variety of different
Diseases including a variety of hepatitis
Strains and so
They're also damn playing this one insane
But I think that this ties into the larger situation we had this measles outbreak that's just explode
Just believe
Do that can't you just do that
Oh that's very smart
I'm covering this
Crystal
Listen to USB
It's very clear that this is only in service
Upholstery
Look the belgians are doing that we should get rid of him to this is what the story is about to these people
Like Alex and Dad
Suck the beat
Goddamn
Is using as a source
It doesn't involve local officials
Involves news organization
Current public health organizations that are on the ground actually know the fact
The meat of the matter
Nation among personnel
That's playing reporting of the
The fact
Is he trying to insinuate
Stop snowing
It's just the default position of
It doesn't fit the narrative must
Secretly be a cover-up
His mentality is incredibly dangerous
Dehumanization narrative
Because it's
Based on nothing
Idiot
Thursday
Completely misrepresented
Primary source
Espresso X
If you read it it clearly says around 10 workers are concerned and will be vaccinated against hepatitis A and B
It's just a few and got together and they were like
Smart
If your God I hate everybody
The French paper at a belt
Where you learned that around
It could be a risk to clean and cruise
Call my God I hate everyone important to point out
Scott is at the hole that isn't getting
Vaccine
It's done 512 employees request
To themselves
This is crucially important
I am rooting for
These people
Alex and Lyman
These people like them to propaganda
Cherry-pick their information in an abusive fashion
Because they are not journalists
Whose current primary objective is implanted
Solidifying their audiences mine the people who are from where from where you are
From should be suspected
Being transmitters of infectious disease
They're basically biological
Used by the Democrats you want them to get in
Is repulsive stuff
Engaged
Kind of talk
So flippantly
Is legitimately terrifying
Yes how do they not understand that this is
I don't I don't understand
So much like
Creation of the border between
Where is almost like
This propaganda
Just built up and then
Overnight
Your neighbor now became
Your
You know just like
The next day you're like a
Just not even
Not even realizing that you're
One step away from
It would be like
Eradication
Describe
Some more about
Just trying to make you afraid of him
Because that's the game
Anime
Immediately
Trying to prove that they don't exist
Accidentally
Cheyenne no go zones everywhere
Ozoner
Yeah I've been in them myself
Logos
Exactly
Nothing
Here's a little bit of a
It was a it was a Denny's
Is little conversation
About
No go Zone
Just to give that people in a tidy I mean
How to go into them
The police are up going in Paris
I've been in that minute
Send
Darius where the police won't go where they're afraid to go or they're just in frayed afraid to enforce the law
At this point there are areas of places like Portland Oregon
Which are also becoming
Who are I just basically they're running the show there
For making religion
Say that
The idea of
Portland
If you look into the
Situation
Just go do some Northwest has a long and wonderful history of being
It's a problem
Too big for now
Vincent van Gogh
Play Define what it mean
Just vague enough
Terms
Really
Interested in going
FIFA which suggests
If there is still alive
Edited still being
Skiers don't talk about it
This is one of the first time
The first time
Alex's show
Perhaps
Antifa area
They operate under Sharia law Muslims aren't welcome at all because the Muslims
More powerful
In reality what these f****** a****** right-wing piles of s*** or describing
Is predominantly minority neighborhoods where they feel uncomfortable
No it's a no-go zones telling me that I can't go there
I feel like I'm
Subdominant
You'll notice the damn Lyman is not being so
Specific about these areas he's been through it all
This is very intentional
Because the West Pacific you are the more
If you take away
Specificity your nailed to the wall whenever seems like you're f****** full of s***
Paris
Mini documentaries on YouTube that I found where she set out to do to invest
Checking out all the alleged Muslim no-go zones
Along with her camera
Specifically pointing out that
She's a woman alone
Watch eyes
Bad
Yeah that's not a neighborhood everywhere that meant
In Muslim
Neighborhoods where Sharia law wasn't
I don't
Pretty well-documented
Has about
Paul Joseph Watson definitely not a Nazi but seems to hang out with
Quite a bit
$2,000
To go explore the alleged no go zones in Malmo
And even he had to admit that he
Even in the areas that everyone said was the worst
That hasn't stopped
He's documentary as being used as evidence of
And it has 2.1 million views on you
China Sea
CID has been flying around for quite a while but I've talked to them as really ramped up some
Since 2015
Because that's what about a million refugees
Mostly from Syria at the
I can't be any more explicit than
These people who push these narratives are not doing it
Because they're concerned about and imagined ink
Whatever high-minded reason
Prince Temple the idea of no go zones exist is
Preemptive conditioning
To desensitize people against the idea of violence against minority neighborhood
It's a rationalization for looking the other way if
Police Crackdown on of course they had to send the National Guard
Regular police just couldn't with a hundred
It turns out that
Really we just need to send in a few
Few special ops people
Military guys
Maybe maybe send a
23rd
Hundred this is the implication behind no-go Zone propagate
We're going to have to suck it up and send the military
Is it deeply Insidious narrative Matt only to further stigmatize immigrant
And make sure that there is no chance
Integration
And here's the thing
In order to reinforce these
Motherfukers who pushed this
When Temple went to Sweden
Any footage of any
To make it look like a trip wasn't a total waste of time for right-wing.
He claims It quotes
Several men started masking up and following
To leave and had to escort us to our car
This is when he was in freaking be
Which is just outside Stockholm
He went on to later say quote they got in their car to escort us out and we had to walk alongside their vehicle and followed us to
Our car
As we're walking there were people just following
Just yelling thing
You suck you racist piece of s***
F*** you
Good story in your mouth
These stories of no-go zones are true
And maybe
It's just a reality a little bit
Kristen Tim pool
The skills to dick
It's precisely the sort of thing that someone
Nothing
Sports
Might be inclined to lie about in order to make sure that the documentary that he makes
Still work to reinforce no go Zone narrative
It's important performing any kind of science
Experimental or invest
To figure out what out
You want to have first
And then
Get yourself to that
Concluded
Whatever reality
You don't want the Koch brothers to tell you that your climates
So I'm suggesting
Look like a maybe there is something
But let me guess a question
Do you know who else
B b c
Pitbull
When the local Swedish news Outlet contacted the police
A press officer said that did not receive
Frida Nordhoff North law
When it started filming a group of young people
And shouted at him to stop filming
The officers in the middle of the square
Keep filming
Completely misrepresented
Being followed
Somehow
F****** b*******
Could you could you quit being an a******
Alright
Literally no evidence involved
Or things that could just be seeing his
The normal sort of thing
Some parts of cities have higher crime than other parts of the city
Had a lot of that could be explained really easily by economic realities that don't really have anything to do with Islam or immigration
Keep on pushing your narratives
That's cool
So This Is the End
The damn lineman
Play My Life
Alex let them go
They've done what they need to do
Alex wants
To talk about his personal aggrievement
And how
Compare themselves
This is an unfair cover
About 1,000 articles
A conservative judge
Have no respect
Collage
Kicks you off your butt
You get treated like you're a juvenile that's a good
I hate you so much
That's pretty crazy
On days like this
Really tossed your that kind of comparison
Like it's real brash
I guess I just found that out by saying no
You're more like an is
Supports Netanyahu
After his self agreement
Complaining
Holocaust
Alex gets to
Claimed was his main story which is the
The Facebook sensors
Who are coming down with
Chair
To spending it as
Sjw snowflake
Globalist
What students because if they watches
And show years ago I began computer
Which more more they're doing
Humans that have to listen to shows
Add Facebook and Twitter in Google in PlayStation
Well they get radicalized
We have the Shay
Versus what mainstream media
Is saying about us
So you can see that this is just trying to
A little bit this is
People are starting to
To find a mental health problem
Listening to you interpret that
Listening to me
That's not healthy
That's really
F***** up the actual article in the verge
It's very hard to come away from that article without
Decent amount of apathy
And concern for the people who
Have to make
Social media spaces livable for us
Take on it
So
Indeed
Wicked
Yeah I'm self into the most
Powerful man you could ever
Because
They can watch Fox News all day on their own
Wednesday watch even a little
Clip of my show their radicalized
Imagine
These people watch like half-hour videos
Three 400 things a day
Open Infowars logo they like to get it out of
Probably more about
Memes
And stuff like that
I convey appointment quicker
Yeah
Appealingly to
But anyway
Insidesource
In Facebook moderation
Seems weird
I don't believe them
But also he just gets real gross
Crew at the end
CBS put out a report
Chicago
Multifaceted
Snuff films
You see the articles about Facebook employees at the moderate conspiracy
Talk about why
Watch what they're doing
They spy on them
Sometimes
Because you know if you decide hey we shouldn't be
Highest turnover
That's the group that got a Target that's a group say that a watch
Is it
Moderation
College
And then
They get into my document last year
So now he read an article the moderators themselves
Our compatriots
Because of their
Experience
Weekend
True
He's referencing an article
Like a year ago
Publicly available information
To some sort of a
A noble Crusade that these people were being
Are are engaged
Not there people who are hurting
And so I don't know
Sexual
The child molestation
And then later on he says
They're getting teeth
Messi from
So he's
They're brainwashed to think
That the child molester
It's totally fine
It's only well maybe College
I don't know I mean the broader point
He's trying to make
Candlelight
Really understand a lot of
The finer details
Batman
I only play some of that stuff again
I don't really care I think we talked about it enough at the beginning that because it leads
What good birthday present
No support our
Alex
Loses
Okay
And you know what he loses it about
He's trying to cover the story
If you want on screen for the
Thesaurus
Of the article referencing
He wanted to be an Infowars
But it's a different sites article
And this pisses him off
To no end
And because he ends up storming off the set of
Facebook calls me dangerous imagine my shock no really
Infowars
Dot-com
Just go to the old infowars.com
Can I move to Canada
Like I want you
I heard him leave the studio
Gruffly that I can hear footsteps
But you can hear it wasn't video I be like that's total
Clump clump
Jesus so what happened a lot more build-up for him to just walked out the show that's like
I can actually I can explain
My very strong
Alright happened is
He's covering this Facebook story and I have pulled up
An article for Cuban events
Which is where is involved in erotic
Maybe so
Article
I'll pull it up on my phone I'll pull up article
To cover the story
Realizes
Or maybe
It's like I was going to take longer more dead air than I want there to be
I'm going off air
To find the article doesn't know what the article
Doesn't know how to search for it
Maybe
The reason that he storms off and the reason that if the build-up is so short
Is it
Chance
Is driving traffic
Aggressively
Hey the only place
But he has control over
IP address
State
Where is Aldi
These other platforms
Clearly go away
Yeah I know YouTube's kick them off now Facebook Instagram he's gone the only thing
He can really
Controlled
Flow 2
And what
You do with the flow 2
Monetizing the amount of traffic
Call he's got
Steven B like human events
The ideological he has an interesting by virtue of his lawyer
Being involved in it
He doesn't want to drive traffic to them because that is a zero-sum game
That article isn't going to him
Covering the same story
So he knows
It is really mad at his staff
For doing that you could always be an Infowars article that is always.
And I think that's what facilitated his freak out
And
I know about him
Especially the current
Please be like that's the only conclusion
We
Crazy
So now we have one last
Okay
Alex has come there playing video
Show up PBS interview
This is literally how the show at
Another Mike down
Because it is
F***** up
He is still mad about the music a different article
This is this is
Happy birthday
34 like Olivia Lodge
That's how they do it
New war started World War
Want to die
Has officially turns heel on Humanity
Whatever they say I'm taking my ball and going home
Just walking out the door just like
Everybody
But I don't like
And everybody
Because so much of Alex is early career was predicated on this idea that good
He's powerful and we can we can
PowerBack for these globalist fit of enslaved us
Now just because the plug didn't work right
Controller.com
CNN's website
Because of the petty squabble there and that
They're stupid and they want to die
Okay
Just escalate to the world exploding
Ultimate the website
Your pump
Because people
W
They want to die and they're f******
Website Veiled Threat
Employee who put the wrong one up
Doubt that people looking at you
Guessing you're fired already
So this episode
Blows my mind
From a from a narrative Arc
Showing up super depressed
Because you watch a movie about Satanism yesterday
Weird
I can Road
Belgium
Gunsmoke being factually
What
Do this
Dehumanizing talk about Facebook moderator is it don't even
Technically work for Facebook
Just self-serving exploitation of their pain
Awful
And then you reach the end it just because he didn't get plug for his own website on his own show
He throws a tantrum
I didn't close the narrative Circle they're pretty well
It's amazing that are like.
Because of the farcical nature
It really wasn't so bad
But it was a lot of
Stop
I could handle this
As much as I hate
The present day
I never
Look forward to listening to it
This I relish
This was kind of like a
You got a lot of meat on the bone
There's a lot of stuff for me to learn about
You're acting like a real f******
So
In 3 hours
Tripping my chicken 5-0
Real real possibility
Well you know
Episode on Monday of fun but
I miss doing this
Actually covering his stuff
I'm glad this
My well
We're technically still
Finishing
Run time for me to go to therapy
I think we have a website.com
Twitter
So many other places I might bite the bullet get on Spotify
Let's do it
Has to be a month-long conversation
But basically how we start
A butt
I don't know this is
I don't think we have a hero here
Gyros
Alright
That's an interesting one for this week
People
Fire
Okay and also not talking about the fictional portrayals
A literal has never killed anybody
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color