Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody look like
Alex
Best meal you've ever
I've made some stir fries that were pretty good
I think that's about it
I'm not really
Not very
Broad in my like a food
The other night I famously have said many times that if it were an option I would just
I probably would rather just not eat
I don't
I like some dishes and all that and I get the pleasure of eating but it's not a big deal for me
I would take food replacement
Now f****** heartbeat
Woodforest
Thomas Jefferson
Exactly
Absolutely
When you get those papers up and running you're going to have to
Don't see a show where I probably but maybe learn how to cook in the future
We will see there's a lot of meat on the table
Pretty intense
We're going to be going over
Ruby going over January 7th 2013
Couple of days
And reasons you have no idea
Idea about
Is there a reason that I couldn't ever
Possibly comprehend
Well the reasons you would expect our because we're going back to look over his coverage in the aftermath
Sandy Hook narrative that there is
Okay
Something else
It's crazy
Kind of exploration pop
Katherine thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Juvenile policy walk
Elevated
I appreciate that.
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites Italy
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much Laura
Hilarious
Laura Loomer
Go to our website
Sports show
One more shout-out special shout-out
Joseph
Illuminati card game
Some dick
Of the Illuminati New World Order set
And we got those in the mail I've been looking through these
The world
Took a look at it
The art style is amazing
Melt
Absolutely makes spark Joy
We really appreciate it and
I can think of no other way
To formally repay you in
Express our gratitude
Other than to declare you sir
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
I don't want
How to read
I am out of control
I bet you money are few living black people
Abused
Joseph Stalin
Photos
Thank you so much Joseph we really appreciate it
Our highest honor is also
I might
I am very seriously considering
And have put minimal effort
Put some effort into a couple of
To make new sound bite
For the the drop
Will happen eventually
Apps that I make
Move forward
From by 1
Do your shows
Father
What
Alright
Actual episode on 17th January 17th
Here is where Alex's head
He's covering a little bit of a new story
That he finds
Very excited
This is also a cam
Temptations
Coastal area
ASAP
How you feeling
Amer is
Warning everyone
That there will be
Mathway codes
Stand-off United States
When the gun grab that isn't coming
That might be what your perception is based on what
I'm not sure that's what
Was the mayor of Gloversville New York
It's the middle of the state which
Cuz once a hug
Its name
From the 1880s 90%
Through the weather in tanning Industries in Gloversville
There were over 100 leather and glove companies in
Season 70s
As foreign suppliers became a
And the New York State pure water program
When the federal much more expensive
For leather tanneries to do their business
Missouri super polluting business
Chemical process
Has a
Contaminate Water Supplies
If not disposed of properly
Which is something to add
Gloversville lost a third of its population
600 residence
To about 15,000
All in all it's a tragic
Example of a City built on a single industry
Which we discovered
Was killing the planet
Tree by-products
Douglas Adams
Shingletown
Confused
That was
Is it
But sometimes a little walk
Kind of fruitions Gloversville
Dayton King was mayor of Gloversville from
2010's
The end of King time as mayor is a
Completely sucked up story
King was elected
First time
He decided to run again in 2018
I want the vote
Lost local firefighter
Junior
Was really close
A recount it was found that they were missed
And they were enough to give King to win by a margin
28 votes
Robeck took the news
Congratulate everybody move forward
Understory
End of story We there's nothing further to report here where do
Gloversville is a Wonder
You don't notice the weirdness that his term ended in 2018 are you want that electric
Situation
After he was arrested
What was he arrested for you at
Well you got caught sneaking into government property after hours and stealing
Falsified records to cover his tracks
Use charged with a felony but in a plea deal
Who's allowed Justice
The $473 he stolen stamps
Even I will admit that's a little bit lamp
Maybe $473 in postage
Send it
437 dollars worth of a man who knows
Maybe it's Unbecoming for a mayor to falsify records
The cover-up is fastest
This applies only think about dating King that was sketchy I might say whatever
Yeah a little bit
However the first time the mayor King
Arrested while in office
Imperial
If only
Why did you say that it was fairly Reese
This guy is a dick
The previous time happened during the 2018 Mayoral race
Official misconduct
The results of the personnel file
Fitzwilliam brobeck Junior
From his time as a firefighter
Are releasing that information on air during the
Mind-blowing
After that
With polls showing the election
Okay
Degree harassment
Write a letter of apology to row back in
Gloversville firefighters
For violating a state
Civil rights law
He was out there violating people's Civil Right
And then just be like okay cool
Great when it was stamped
What's the temperature
Bank of America in
Seems like a real piece of s***
In 2013 he was interviewed on the local news
Second clip
But there's some people who predicted Waco's situation that won't end well
It's not really clear that he's voicing opposition to
Justice
DC some possible negative,
Some crazies
I'm not sure if he's even speaking of them negative
I don't know
Paul Joseph Watson Road an article on Infowars the claim that the Clippers
And a whole lot of the right-wing media picked up on that which is what Alex
Is doing here
Alex doesn't know what he's talking about and it's per usual
The guy is building up as a good guy in government
Guns is actually a local election mix
Naturally
Good Times
Together they're always
Together all the comments
Actually even shows up I know that
To get him on
But it's just because
He said something about Gunn
God I hate
For the people
The people
Struggle
Start people struggles
It's something
Normal to have
2019 FX
You might struggle
The Gap theory on the 70
Interesting to learn more about this guy
He is a sheriff
Oh no I'm already out
We will not
Surprise
Sheriff
First sheriff
Okay so Danny payment
Is this guy
The sheriff of Jackson County
In Kentucky when we go back
Dishonorable action story
These people that Alex has on his
Killers in
An exemption
Close
Like he had
Little over a year left
For years before he was
Right on the cusp of being sent to prison
Four years as Sheriff Denny payment received warnings
He was running
Pictures of Jackson County Sheriff's Department
Did the mismanagement
These were generally soft
Supposed to
The audit of the department
Have concluded
Head knot
Was not keeping appropriate risk
He was not tracking
New salary limits
According to the County's approved budget
Department of over $112,000
And the Fiscal Court
Well
And that the Fiscal Court had already loaned his Department 277 thousand dollars pay salaries would not reimburse
These numbers are completely insane
Particularly when you learn
Kentucky.gov
The Jackson County Kentucky Sheriff's department has exactly seven officers
That number may have been
There's very small
It's unclear
I don't know
I'm not I wouldn't make that allegation
Mismanagement to action
That's sad that is a papa
Course
William Osman
County Office
Any audit report there's a section where payment could
Responded
Just being real.
Things like there be
Being taken care of and that he didn't know where these were happening or that these things were prompt
Flash Forward about a year
He's not taking care of the sheriff's
Problem
So again
Raise and controls
Department of Finance
Take it away
And given to the Fiscal Court
And they also start another
Police Department really think that should have been the
The first time
What you doing
To fix the problems are 100,000
Missing that.
Highway
The number was
The county couldn't afford to allow it to
Well
Didn't take kindly to
All January 2014
You showed up to a meeting with the County Fiscal Court and arrest bet Sally and judge William Smith
Who happened to be in the middle of conductors of medic
Naturally this life this life to the meeting having to be adjourned with some interesting responses from
Article in the Lexington Herald-Leader
County attorney George Hayes
George Smith
But we had to adjourn cuz there's no one running
County Clerk Donald Duck Moore said with a laugh
You still in The Blues Brothers
I know it's not funny but still
A number of people at the meeting were pretty
Concerned they just Witness
Missed an overt example of authority
His only motivation is to clean up local government
There's nothing political about doing what's right
Smith with tampering with public records
Publix
Are engaging in organized crime through extortion
You started writing in
No it's just him
Easy it's just head out
Did he did he write everything
Hangout with a pen
Maybe
Unilaterally arrested judge County Treasurer because
The sheriff
Years apart
There's no Sheriff movement called
Be a sheriff and part of the Constitution
Sheriff moving
Self-serving
That's that's a bad idea
These constitutional Sheriff
Do not hold up
Reality
Is that what he did was against the law
Smith were dropped on February 6th
Fallout
Wildly
Stupid
Federal court and eventually reach the settlement
$2,500
Quite frankly
Election
In 2040
And then get zero punishment for it there
You know like
40 / 437
Stamp doesn't Trump
Civil rights
Sprite
You know what's f***** up
Judge Smith
Was Queen
Yeah
But
Play the 50/50
You try to arrest her for your prior
It's one of those situations where the cops try to frame someone who also happens to be guilty
Haitian and his charges work
Complete s*** but it turns out
Go to jail
Tarasco
You didn't face criminal charges for that
But
He wasn't arrested and charged with drug trafficking
Set up a hemp Farm
Permission to grow
Actually decide to start growing straight up and was involved in trafficking
Actually I think we should be legal and I don't think that someone is clearly an a******
I do think there's some extenuating circumstances here
To bring up to judge him
Infarct
The first is that when police showed up they didn't just find weed
They also found eight vials of steroids
But you didn't have a legal reason to have which is an amount that law enforcement
Considers indicative of traffic
Reloaded gun
Typically placed in the house today
Defend payments marijuana-growing operation
He might of a bit more than just some cool weed growing
The profit off locking people up
For drug-related crime
According to the 2016 date
Kentucky.gov of the 207 arrest
County Sheriff's
I almost
Halfway photography
Part of a system that works for drug charges
Deaconess whatever sympathy is left after exhaust arrested while
Yeah
So
Those charges on
Yeah
It does seem that way we haven't realized
If we just started locking
White men who do weird s*** like this
Play better off
Present
I'm saying you should go to jail and in 2013 he was awarded the high noon award
We literally playing Cowboys
Indians right now
Larry Pratt
Sponsors
The award is given to those who quotes
Stanford has run
Tell the truth even though a politically incorrect
Can't help but think that payment to feel like
If you could just unilaterally erect a judge later
Interesting Lee payment was one of the high noon Awards
Can 2013
The other was none other than captain
Sheriff David
I don't know
It's pretty strange
Butts
Show me cuz I care.
The whole thing
To comprehend
Silver spring summer concerts
Right
You're not the highest Authority in
Because we're not
Bright
No it's not
Alex talks about how Obama took
Took everything
Everything from
The good
He has a lot of
Personal aggrievement complaints
I really f***** up take on
Unsurprising
I don't like that at all I don't like any I don't like anything about that
Alex was taken aback for a second
Damn man is weird things a man
Settling
As unsettling just from Layla
A discernment perspective
Zane hearing
Describe the tea party like
This is weird
Maybe they are
Yeah maybe baby
Means that they're obviously
That's one way of looking
And Alex has Lou Rockwell as a guest libertarian
Sure
That's an oxy
It's a really really boring
Interview
I don't care
We don't have time
For goddamn Lew Rockwell
We'll get to him another day will come back
And say something interesting
I will get to him then
Because Alex
And it got me ears
The point is
Information
We got a really interesting position that Alex
Expressing
Which is
Really again really wanting
To call it a false flag
Someone's going to hit
Before kind of idea
The factory
He's resisting at all
Confusing in
In the present
Aware that it's a line that
You can't
I think he understands
Consequences
Yeah a little bit better
Is this time frame
We're going to get into it tomorrow
Get back
F*** off Lube
About
Paul Joseph Watson
His feelings
Tamara
So I think we can take away from that
Is that Alex
Who's responding to audience
In the present day
The audience
Made a lot of requests
Recover Sandy Hook
No I think you're I think it's very clear that there's Market pressure
Pretty resistant to cover it up till this
Giving him some
Allegedly
Some pushback
Because he has to respond to
You want the audience
Wants him to do
You can see it clearly their ardor
In terms of the lawsuit
Is profiting off
At least Deacon Frost
Whether or not
I don't know how much that illegal
But whatever
Episode Alex
Call from a guy
About another gun grab
I just hope
Because it's going to be used
Reimburse
People for weapons that are taking one of their voluntarily or not
This Monday is HR 226
IRS
For complicated
So I get information from my real
Repeat
226 is a house resolution was designed to alter the IRS $2,000 of a text
Credit to people who elected
Surrender their assault weapons
Do the federal state or local
Is completely voluntary it specifies that it was about creating an incentive people
To get the number of weapons laying around down
Yeah it's super pointless to debate the fine points
Because as it literally always
Case Malik Springs up a gun bill
This was already dead in committee by the time the caller is telling Alex City
3 days before this episode the bill was sent to the house and literally nowak's
Was ever taken on it and
Is there it died
Didn't know about it exist
He doesn't keep up with the news
You going to keep up with his
Premier table top
All he's about his gun rights
There is a f******
Bill in the house
The fairy isn't evil
Never know about
This is pathetic
The main struggle
To the 17th
Process
For now because
Alex took off on the 8th
Okay and generally covering a day when Alex
The general wouldn't unprecedented would never do that
But this is too important for us to 300 plus
And here we are
Talk about
Shuffle David nights
Earlier
Paul Joseph Watson
And I honestly think it was a strategic decision on Alex's part
A vacation that he actually wanted
I don't think that
Wanted to be anywhere near
This
Justin
Right
Because Paul Joseph Watson has a little bit of a gas
With
You're getting a little too excited
Nothing's over
Alex doesn't want to be directly tied to
Behind the Sun
Is perfect perfect
So James
The professor from Florida Atlantic
University
Is Paul Joseph Watson
Tracy was already pitching crisis actor
Conspiracies
The sort of thing if you're going to have him
You are responsible for pushing back on
Andalous
Especially for someone who the day before Alex said Paul Joseph Watson is critical of these theories
Do you expect
Prepare to protect
Conspiracy world that he is involved in
From someone who's dangerous ideas
The purity of the turf
I thought I thought
JW was giving him
Push back
It was
The same way that his listeners
You should go and papa soon
Opposite
Paul Joseph Watson is a voice of reason Alex's
Conception
Paul Joseph Watson
Paul's going to try
Pay lip service to that position as interviews
Professor James
Tracy
Pictures
Kikiwaka wafer
Is that he's
He's trying to mainstream
As a
Questioner legitimate
Or or something
The feeling that I had that this wasn't going to be a great interview
Started almost immediate
Absolutely
360 last Friday
25 minutes
Bicycle
That's an exaggeration
For sure
Your picture
I've just about every
Every time you call
I thought this was really crazy cuz
Literally a minute
Deep Sad Piano
Montague Island
Talking about somebody
Everybody
So I don't know
But your ear
Victim
Characterization
Are you being pilloried by the media
Questions
Mainstream narrative everybody wants to believe the same
Nothing but we got to have those sticker
Turns out there
So
Expresses
Sets forth
His position
And that is what he doesn't believe these theories
In fairness to him
I will
Hear this
We're going to go over some of the questions that he and others have raised
The Sandy Hook massacre
I think there's an appropriate way to do this
For Paul to live in that space
I don't believe any of this.
Yeah require pushback
It requires
Knowing and presenting accurately
What this guy is saying
Not misrepresent what he saying to paint him as a victim of the mainstream media's bully
I think that's important
We already know he's not going to do that
This is going to be
So you think
You think he
Keep playing a game on
Using Paul Joseph is
But actually does believe it
Acting is
Is the
Residence
It's going to be over at
I don't think it's the second
I think it's smart and you understand
This is
A Sticky Wicket
This is going this is a trap
Yeah if I if I get involved
I will be in League with whatever the consequences are
I think he's smart enough to be aware of that
Gotcha but at the same time
A dyed-in-the-wool
Instinctual propaganda
That he knows the people with the
Extreme opinions
It's good for business
Allows them
The theories are very
Popular like as reference
What's the last day Alex
Dina people are knocking down their door
To talk about how they were actors
Seahawk
All that stuff so poor kind of knows what it's good for business
To not be like
F*** you professor
Tracy what you're doing
Is shameful I don't believe it
You have no evidence yet
Because then you're going to alienate knocking down your door and demanding you have this conversation
Just alienate
Could alienate
Maybe
His listeners who would
His home
Yeah
Call is smart enough and is done this long enough to be
He's smart enough to understand like
There is no proof of this
Is
Shity
The airs on the side of what's good for business
So Alex is gone but that doesn't stop him from
Calling to the court for like 10 minutes to the show
Here's a little bit of that
My son so boring
College
Infowars.com to call in here
Don't care anymore
Because we know we're listening to people on the phone
Well
Alex's on the phone from camp
On the phone from floor
Yeah
This is
Visually
But is an audio.
Interesting because what's going on is Alex's taking the day off
Office in the middle of the days I suck it I got to check in with
Bucolic
My own website we were inaccurate
Plug for his own coverage
In a weird way
But
Talking about
Of course about
I am Department of Homeland
Security they put out some training videos
Yeah it's terrorist in the video are not Arabs
Middle Eastern
What is the terrorist
Does complaintive
Kind of
Where are the terrorists
So
You can get a sense
Your son wants to go fishing off the f******
Phone
Nothing nothing like camping you know you remember camping is
The kids you go out
The middle of the Forest right
Your fire and you
Call into your
Home show
Blame
I can take a day off you're not breaking news with Napolitano
Like White House
Rejected must your kids feel
I would feel
Real not great
Also I don't believe you static
What kind of leaves
My radar
Call baby
Interview with the crazy dude alright
We get to it
Deer Park
Described as a very friendly introduction
Interview
Conspiracy
So I don't believe you're having an interview with someone like this you necessarily need to
First of all
F*** off
It's okay to have some pleasant
There's nothing I would condemn
Yet
You can only call him
Professor
Well because
And even then like not if you're interviewing him now anyway
All of that stuff is there to burnish him as a
Credulous
Subject
Somebody who has information he's a priest
He's he's well-read and well-educated
He runs his own blog
He even does
Has classes on
Conspiracy so of course
Endive
Point out is that
Is
In Florida
Has never been
And should shut
The f****** about
That seems like
Spell
What you're describing him in this fashion
Goes a little bit even further
In this
This is a question
I don't actually think they get to a real
Conspiracy
Self-victimization
Aggrandizement
Because
Close
Do it all this is to do is this the first question
How do I request
It is to establish immediately in the interview
Is the victim
Of a harsh assault
By the mainstream media
So if you hear something for the mainstream media that super negative about
Text
I want to talk about
Bicycle
Week
Profession
Doing the same thing
Professor position
So
So you see there in the framing
The point comes the question
Frieza question like that unless you were wanting to paint this person is the unfair Target
Of some sort of
Vitriol from the mainstream establishment
It's like when they write
Students if you wrote that question on a pool
You're not going to get an accurate read
You're going to snow
Set up for a spike
James Tracy knows how to f****** answer a question about his own oppression
It's it's ridiculous
If your intention show through
When you ask a question like that regardless of how many times
You say you don't believe the things you say
Which Paul doesn't
In this next clip
When in this clip I believe
It lays out pretty clearly
What I was describing
What is motivation
The desire to personally be above it while at the
The same time doing what's best for business
Because everyone wants them
To cover this
Is a video on YouTube
Call the Sandy Hook shooting
Shows you how
I'm coming out
What's the question
Parents Day
Family members
Some people inflamed
So
6 million people or whatever watch this video in 10 days
Credibly huge Market
We hope to siphon some interviewing you
Unsatisfying
I can't
I can't be
Personal
It's so perfectly clear here
Fuel to the herd
Burdensome
Deserve like
If you're listening to this while this guy huh
Has a video that
That has over 10
Chameleon video
I don't think it's his video
Informed is Paul about who's interviewing
Because like
If he knew things
Tracy was
He wouldn't
Be able to walk this line
Presented at
If you are a person
Who believes that this was a real tragedy
You don't believe the people who are
Putting out things
Respectful
To the people who lost loved ones or died
There
Why would you
Put up with
And
Help the person who's making those theories
Bios
Questions that are designed
To play right into the
The things that they're able to
To make them look good and reasonable
Why would you do that it doesn't make sense
Even if your fault
Paul has more incentive to not behave that way
Because he has
A conspiracy business to protect
Like this make any sense
With a well-run show
Unbelievable that you would not
No
Who is coming on you
We believe he did zero preparation and he's just having a grand ol time because
But if so it
Is weird that he keeps saying I don't believe this stuff he doesn't believe
I don't know I just
There's a real
Nefarious intent
Be back here in this next question
That he asked
I'll because if you follow the framing of the quest
Again and
Incredibly manipulative.
It's trying to
See where he needs
To go in order to
Mysterious
Self-professed
Evenness
AR-15
Images
That's a f******
Awful Quest
That is
Giving a fiery and then being like you want to talk about that
That is not
That's crazy
What are you doing
Setting up that question is
Dishonest
The framing implies has proven that Obama is trying to take people's guns
Manipulative
Sandy Hook to do that because of an
The entire premise of the quest
Heavily on that bias position
And deemed fact within the framing
Question
Secondly a trick that class
The Conspiracy Theory full shade artist
Do we see the play out over and over
They set the standard of
Deem as acceptable proof of something then when they get that proof they move goal post
Provided isn't it
Itself fake
Cuz actually approved
The conspiracy
That they were pitching
In the first place
The idea of surveillance
Give us a surveillance footage
That's why we are
It's all just b******* long form birth
Nothing Obama could have ever released or provided would have satisfied the people who are invested in making the argument
The US citizen
You wrote that down.
Position to argue from
Attacktix like this Bellator intense
Once again
Images of Paul Joseph Watson
Specific question there's a number series problems
One is a yes no idea
Different School
Pics of different budgets
The policies listing of other schools where shootings happen
But doesn't really stand up to scrutiny
Have a good
That's what evidence should exist
The case of the shooting
Point of order
The fact that you are referencing
School shooting
Things that you think
Wow
So basically do they don't
Snow
Christ even though they get the standard weapon problem
These people
So much all those other examples
Virginia Tech are high school and college
Respectively
Obviously have different security protocols Elementary School
It's not worthwhile comparison for him to be making his like we had
Pictures and videos of their why not here
The most important Point here is that even if the police or FBI released footage or images of Adam Lanza committing the shooting
It will become the new Grist for the mill of conspiracy
Conceded his eyes turned the wrong direction
So either he's got a lazy
Somebody
Airbrush right
Zoom in on it
It's exactly what they would do they look
For any irregularities could possibly be there
Be the new proof of
Conspiracy is blah blah blah
This question is a horrible way to lead off the interview unless
The intention is to
A professor
Completely reasonable person is just ask
Questions as opposed to someone who's actively making slanderous claims about the family members of murder chill
I think that's what
Yeah so Paul asked about the security system
The Sandy Hook School District
Nevada
Gear with regard to what is actually going on
We can safely conclude is nonsense you're totally right totally
Playwright
There were articles about that that were available
The system isn't cut
High-tech surveillance
For the whole school
Running back towards system gear
Strategy
The doors of the school be locked after 9:30 a.m.
Order to get in
Boss R&B record
Nice by someone in the office
Where are you can see them through security monitor
That's the only definite camera to school at the door
As Adam Lanza
There's no reason to even be certain
That camera would have caught images
I'm coming in at 9 everybody
Conclude that there were cameras in every single one of those windows up
Play they didn't
Skimp on the bus
Get for their new security right
So let's start from the position
Cameras everywhere in this
I think maybe asking
For something that doesn't exist
End
Insisting that
It not being released
Proof
We're living in this dystopian Society
Security cameras
In 2012
Hallmark
Sandy Hook conspiracy
Exaggerating the scale of the new security
The school had put in a few months prior
Is allowed on this show to just
That's what their systems were
When is estimation
The money people in town
It is a sumption that their wealth must be the best everything available
This is based on nothing but speculation
Nothing
Nothing to push back
Pushed back
Publicly
Funded building
Design corner
I think that's the really rich the game or taxes
Property taxes
School
Going to making black people go to prison
Explains that if only there was evidence
Surveillance footage
So
Acting from a dishonest
Position
He knows fully well that releasing the footage would not put anyone
Aquarius to rest
Here's how I know that
And Paul Joseph Watson
As an example of
School shooting
Hey guess what
Uber X
All the releasing the footage does it take away the argument that it never
It's so easy for the
Conspiracy to survive by
Can you talk
Professor whose claim to study
Conspiracies
Knows damn well this is how the game is played
On sublevel conspiracy theorists know that the
Kindling
Keep their fires alive
Naturally deplete
Grows old after awhile
Engaged
Route to firefresh New novelty
This strategy
If only we got X then our questions will be answered and we stop this s***
Is it true as a two-pronged strategy
Provide to that new novel
On the water
Grandiose
Grandiosity
To get people to release the thing that you want them to
So you can calm through it
Renew Novelties or after
That generally doesn't
Sent the police don't make the decisions based on whether or not something shuts up
But he does
Matter
Because that's really more of a Hail Mary and they're not really expecting that to happen
This strategy automatically
Because it allows people
We've made it clear that we would shut up if they just released this
We have our question and they won't they won't provide the
Evidence
That would make it all go away and that that
It becomes itself pornography
Did they need to keep the fire alive
It's a manipulative strategy
And is loads of both
Are you
Stevie sorts of techniques being used
Hibbetts contacts without being like
Come on man
You know what you're doing
So
Here we get
Into the next
Piece of
Sandy Hook
Secrecy the James
To pitch
Unquestioning
Paul doesn't
Doesn't push back really at all
Say that s*** on air
But of course as you know there's also the CVS footage of a bystander
In the front seat
Optical
Initially from December 14th
First of all
I'm never saying who actually was
Suspicious
All death of that particular medium
SunTrust
Explanation
In the woods were
Because that's all been cleaned up my mess
Trust them because of
Retraction
Made which end
Their coverage is
If any if any news Outlet
Ever makes
You know you can never
I think that's how it works
The shooting storywood
Sprung
But they couldn't have gotten a quote from her because she was one of people killed at
The be retracted quote and apologized in early online reports from the scene of the December 14th shootings at
Sandy Hook Elementary
Preschool identify herself to our reporter is the principle of
The school that woman is not the schools
Principal Dawn hochsprung
Who was killed in the Friday morning at
Apologize for
Confusion may have caused
Bad sucker
The simplest explanation is
Severely Rush
Journalist
Stories out before 8
Fact checker
Or if you need a bad person to blame maybe it was a bison
Who is in shock
Who misrepresented herself.
To be involved in the story
Possible
Free online
Receive it's being sold
I would even accept that it's entirely possible that it was
Another administrator
The school
Communication of the reporter assumed it was
Principal
To become a Target
Might not want
To bring someone else into this
Easier
Retraction
The person writing
The story was
Thinking about her wealth
Thinking about the clip-ins
Just wrote it down
Mixing up their notes
Especially under the immediacy
The time crunch Express
Andy was a
Tragedy
Ultimately
It's very weird
Kind of
It has the vibe of a mistake made under intense
Tracy isn't saying you just
Distrust them as a source
Skizzy domanski
Consistency
Thorough
Checking from the media
I know that because he's on f****** Infowars
He says that because this
Which direction does one of the big early pieces of evidence
Conspiracy theorists
Is the poster there claims
No one died
So that's what he's doing
Lisa Veterinary
Because they got a quote
From somebody who is dead
Ripley dead nobody Acts
God you guys
Here's another piece of his stupid
Suspicions
I would say that you should
Critical
This is dumb
Also questions with regards to the
The alleged photograph
Students that were being evacuated
National and international news
Associate
And yet only two photographs emerged from that series of
Is this the best you've got like you're on a national platform and this is what you've got
Like do you not understand that maybe she didn't
Get clearance to publish pictures of people
Like
There are exclamation
That are simple or
She just thought these were the best
Does a bunch
If you get headshots
They take a lot more
Then to
Let's true but they only give you
Exactly what do they do with all those
Maybe like my
First rebuttal might be a little bit
It's a week
I don't know
Public
You don't have to get there
Information I think I do believe it
That's the case in most States
But if it's
You chose to
Couple
Who gives a f***
Yeah you got to do better
That's not suspicious at all
For a photo essay later maybe you saved the rest for coffee table book
Deeply disturbing
Any of these things are possible
Maybe they only had room for two in the copy
Not unlimited space endeavor
Stripers
This is 2012 is it before Squarespace man
Dragon drop
X
So in his next clip he brings up
Completely absurd
Conspiracy about Sandy Hook
And then says something
They broke this
Wide open
In a wave that I think Alex
Deep trouble I love
Did you hear about that report
The first time that it's an emergency really Ama
Avenue
Really
Explicitly
The Alex Jones Show
I might not have breath
Recall but I do not remember Alex covering fleeing danzo
But
Nuns were comforting survivors and people on the scene and they were wearing
Shoes that people online
Think look right for none
Too comfortable for none
A bunch people started posting they were like police
Okay alright alright
Them are interested in that narrative
What's more important
First heard this on the Alex Jones Show
I because I decided to look around a little bit
I thought a really strange overlook
Of James Tracy's coverage of Sandy Hook
One thing that I find particularly in
Is it the first time the Tracy covered Sandy Hook on his blog was December 20th 2012
6 days after the shooting
Hello
From the section where he's discussing
Contradiction
The official report
Bob story
Several independent researchers and most recently infowars.com reporter Rob to have over the pass
When did the evidence
Sandy Hook shooting suspects were apprehended by police
In that same post
He includes a quote about how journalists
Dictate how people
Experience
They set the stage
They conveyed to the public to meeting and atmosphere at essence of the whole event
For anything
Intrude on this
From John Rappaport
Frequent Infowars guest
And forth our house
Every single citation that isn't
Straight coverage
From AP or
CBS ABC or Fox
In the notes section
Of this post
The first time that he covered Sandy Hook on his blog
Is a direct link to an Infowars contributor
Jon rappoport in my catoms are listed as sources to James Tracey
First article
What are you started questioning Sandy Hook
I hate you
You beautiful
That's f***** up stuff
That you found that at all is a
Fired Pizza
There's no information that you
Makes me angry on such
Go home
And just like
Press myself in between two walls
Make sure that I'm okay
I think it starts
Explain why Rob lawsuit
Yeah
To be an open question before
So there's a little bit more here
December 24th traits
This was supposed that included the suggestion that
Enquirer weather
Sandy Hook
That's okay quotes
Sister
Just to take us back real quick
Anybody who uses
Is the word Sapulpa
Call Jon Rappaport
December 24th
Posted
Inquire
Weather is
No Diggity
Statement by saying
With the exception of an unusual and apparently
Contrived appearance by Emily Parker's alleged
Father
Family members have been most
From public scrutiny
Because of course that's his child
Just murdered about a week ago name
A bunch of
Scrutiny
My friend is
Is it healthy
It's worth noting that
First mention of Robbie Parker on James Tracey
Alex it suggested that he seems to be investigated on his own show on December 9th
Days prior
To Tracy ever bring him up
Interesting Lee this post Tracy made again
Herbalist
Radioman911 and Idaho picker
Just people who have YouTube
Alright by January 4th Tracy was a
Explicitly discussing crisis actor
Quote
After such a heroine event
Would be family members and students
It's lingering in the area and repeated of the offering themselves for interview
Possible reasons there
Is working under the direction of federal authorities
Incoordination
Cable and broadcast networks Allen
That realistically drives home the event stretch
In the post
Tracy goes on to
Is it possible that such actors were utilized
Effective public opinion
With the exception of police and government officials
Coshocton
Restrictions
Family members and pedestrians captured and photos from the shooting's aftermath her almost
Entirely anonymous
That is where he would fall back on the
Defense of Iowa
Questions
When you put forth
Do you like that
But this is also where that argument
If you're just asking
The question
With justification
Super Why the answer
That question is
Use
Is it possible that such actor for utilized in
Newtown
Control the event
Blah blah
Defend
The affirmative
Do you know
We do provide a Counterpoint to balances out life possible
The question is
No they didn't
Then you question is just a rhetorical device
Using to make your point while hiding behind a question
Tracy doesn't
Provide the side
But he does go on to say of a child who survived
Shooting
The frequent hazardous
Hesitancy with words in the child's delivery
Adjust they coached
Present memorized
I'm not being clear enough of the James Tracy 100
Recite was not in
Just asking a question
January 4th
Here is his
Conclusion
In the post
Quote
To declare that the shooting never took place
Is cause for intense opprobrium
In fashion
Historicizing
Will believe Maine
Terrible writing
Furious at all of the sentences and words people are using
Stanford
Trance will maintain
Silverlake
Similar operation in Oklahoma City
Osama Bin Laden was not responsible for the events of 9/11 in the World Trade Center towers
Vigorously
Condemned For Thought crimes against the state
Such are the immense
Dimensions of mass manipulation
Spit the motive
Design
Buck Barger apparatus of social NGO political control
Okay
Like
That's a rant
Let me describe that
As best I can
What you just read
Was
A
Used
Stock
That was just
That was
Tremendously
If you express
Get the idea that
He's accusing people who think it happened to being under orwellian mind
Control asking questions
Consistency
Was posted 2 weeks
Before this interview with Paul Joseph Watson
This is the sort of thing that he's putting out into the world
So f*** him
So not only
Timeline his very first article
Infowars
Repeatedly
Yep
Then
He is
Used as a
Source
All info
Infowars
Maybe not as extensively as at the beginning it was mostly in Fort Worth
It seemed to be informing
More people pick up on it
He has more Lakes
Veterans today Global Research
Organization
Is Infowars putting out an air
One of their listeners
Running as far as fast
They came with that.
Then Infowars graciously pulling them back in
The fold
We run as far with you
Also allows them to be the shield
Does a tenured professor
The credibility with these dumb.
You also had some people who were coming to his defense
On February 24th he posted an open letter supporting his indefensible coverage of Sandy Hook
From a very likely source
Tracy's defense
Which ekspresno literal Holocaust denier and would go on to write the book no one died
By December 2013 Don fully off the deep end it was posting articles about how many of the children killed at
The shooting with Jennifer Hudson
It's Super Bowl
XLVII
I don't know how to read roman numerals quickly
Good
He didn't get saying
It's not a great use of my time to read every little thing Tracy
He is ever written on his blog leave it there
The timeline of his b*******
However it's interesting to note that is earliest coverage of the tragedy used Infowars Rob do in Mike Adams
Explicitly
When Alex is getting sued for his coverage in the present day
His doctor phone says that he was just reporting on what Wolfgang halbig
A professor Tracy recover
Wolfgang halbig isn't even in play yet
If you look at
The fact
He was covering
Was inspired by what Alex
Alex by pointing the finger at crazy
Is it many ways actually pointed the finger at themselves
But most people don't realize that
So
Interesting wrinkle to the story that
We're not ignored but not realized
I think was going to have
Put out a video
10.6
Million views
Things like totally
Six million views
Crazy conspiracy
You only get a few people who listen
It's not right
I think I think
Your dynamic
It does open up a whole lot of
Doors and windows in terms of
Alex
Urea
Yeah
Before
Crazy made it clear by saying I heard that on Infowars
Which
Just for posterity
Before they got to that they were talking about
With Nixon during these tapes alfredo
Next clip
F****** hilarious
Police office
Definitely
So you see the dichotomy questions
That you have been
Presenting
Those are 100%
That we should consider.
Let's talk about some of the Wilder.
D
You have to
Is that when is interviews happen
They know who James Tracey is they know what he's been putting out to the world
There's no real interview without bringing up the idea
If that is why Paul keeps
I don't believe in
Mini series
Inoculating cell from any blowback
Doesn't this next
The way he said
Catsup
The question
Daddy's going to
Introduce
The conversation
Is the question in such a strong
Fashion
But I don't believe
You would do
Unless you were trying to get people
To think
But he was much more rational than you
Hey Becky I mean
I think that there is definitely a program
Misinformation
Supreme information in order to
The waters
Discredit
Research
Media
Because
If you can just
So is Watson setting up that question
The perfect way to allow someone to misrepresent their position
He doesn't want to directly ask him at this point if he believes that some of the victims were actors
Because that would require a follow-up
He doesn't want
Specifically what the
UT Direct
Stand on the show unchallenged
Like a f****** a******
Like what victim
Are actors
What evidence do you have to say something like that
The strawman
Play thing is actually Tony Hawk
That allows the
Middle Ground
It's his way of mainstreaming
Professor Tracy's completely insane argument
Did you form that's way more acceptable to the broader Infowars audio
It really seems to me like a
Lithium is a credible
If you're not following what I mean
This is what it is
He doesn't ask Tracy about the beliefs
But he has a spouse
He asked him about the eve
Even crazier things
Is the people on YouTuber saying
Because he frames the question by asking about other
Crazy
Question this way that provides
Paul Joseph Watson allows trade
Beside himself
Apart from those p
Sirius online
I have a hard time believing that this is an
Particularly coming from someone who like Paul history
He doesn't believe in the crisis actor theories
Which Tracy has a
Explicitly been pushing at this
Do you know
What
More than any
Victory Brewing
This is not our
Normal in
Infowars
Scary Terry
Calls trying
A little
A little while he's at least say
Crying so hard
There is a part of it comes from
Personal preservation
To an extent
But Paul doesn't have to repeatedly say I don't believe this
Lease to his credit
Yeah but that's
She's talking about
Dumb f*** who she doesn't like anymore
Information
Discrediting all of us out here explained
There are similarities
Please I would say to this
It's more
Because
Like for the company
It's from It app
It feels
Like an interview that would go differently if it was being done
Sincerely
I don't believe this
I think that it
You know these people actually are victims of this
It's awful
I don't think this conversation
Person who sang things Tracy is posting on his blog
I don't think it would go
I don't drink it
I don't think if you was operating from a sincere place would be like
Now there's a lot of people who say that he's crazy
Real journalism research Lake
Yeah cuz it allows him to present
I don't
That
The intent comes out
These questions
Will base their conclusion
Seems like the average
Income in this county is
Is pretty high so
The security system must be
Top-of-the-line
Journalist
They just really like to reasonable
Conclude payouts
Text Cliff
Admire
Just bought them
He's talking to
We need to trade
I agree with that but unfortunately
Literally personally harassed
She hasn't reached the point that he would eventually get to
Literally suggesting
Exact same strategy
Discussed with the surveillance
Brewvies or no
Yo I'm going to use the fact
You won't give me
A crazy person
I'm going to use the factory
He isn't your son
Tracy wouldn't reach that level of crazy and abusive
But that doesn't mean he wasn't doing some
Real damage to Victor
Call Joseph
Yeah
Melania trying to End online
Really
Your f******
Just a few months after this appearance he was reprimanded by Florida Atlantic University
Sufficiently disassociating his personal blog from the University
Reasons for his eventual firing
Heather
Blog on your personal time
You must stop dragging
Florida Atlantic University
Personal endeavors
Position as a credit
Infowars interview
Exactly the sort of thing that the school wasn't
Because
Planes quotes
Your actions could
Adversely affected legitimate interest
To the university
And constitute
He was so deeply on the this s*** is fake thing
From early on
Like he definitely was
In December 2012 he wrote quote
Outrageous claim Hook shooting ever took place
Dash Dash
At least in the way law enforcement authorities
As I
That's the slimiest possible to play this game
First
He couches the point in the languages
Suggestion
One is left
Inquire
It's such b*******
It's equivalent to that dumb joke I'm asking for a friend
Or how about sometime present the question by saying inquiring-minds-want-to-know
I'm doing it as a joke
He's doing
It's a way of saying something inflammatory without having to own the
The second thing it would erode their with that that's
That is a mess
Is the placement of a Double Dash
He knows that his readers will disregard
Comes after the part where you at
They're just going to run with the primary assertion he's driving
People towards which is this
Never happened
He sings What is love
Inquire whether or not
AP saying that in the weeks after
After the tragedy
Easy is it to jump
From there to one is left to inquire claim
Affected by this all are liars
It's a super easy pivot for
Conspiracy theorist
And a whole lot of his listeners
Unfollowers did exactly
Before he began directly harassing victims families
You didn't stop
He wrote an article on his website on October 15th
Entitled
Fraudster Lenny Posner Target
Mhbs memory hole blog
Is website
Of course this was after Tracy it aggressively targeted
Posner
Who wrote December
In the Orlando
Tracy is among those who
We sought to cause our family pain and anguish
Publicly demonizing art
Ski party
Photos of our slaves
From falling into the hands of
Tracy even sent as a certified letter demanding proof that Noah wants live
Where is parents and then we were the rightful owner of these photographic images
We found this outrageous
Police report for harassment
Once Tracy realize we would not respond
He subjected us to ridicule and contempt on his blog
Boasting to his readers that the unfulfilled request was
Because we use the copyright claim
To support continued Research into the
Sandy Hook massacre of
It means nothing
Paul Joseph Watson
Pretend to take The High Ground to be against people harassing the victim
What is offering a large be friendly and non-confrontational platform
Play song the seed
But inspired many of his followers
And would go on to be one of the most disgraceful harassers
Himself
Intellectual coward
On full display
Who would see that coming
Step from these
These
Pillar
Encourage
Desire to fight back against the powers-that-be
I mean if
You hear their bumpers coming in and out of
Commercials
You know that they stand up for truth
R-Truth
I can't imagine
Shrink
Legal
So earlier Paul ask a question about Christ
Didn't want to have any follow-up
He didn't know what he was going to
Now a little bit later in the interview
You directly.
About crisis
And Tracy's beliefs about that
And I think I can explain why he decided
Which of all people
Crisis
Surrounding
This is why we probably
Based out of
Denver Colorado
Department of Homeland Security
Alvin playing the roles of bystanders
RV
Social media
In creating an environment
Drill
School
For disabled children in Harlem
It's not known whether or not
By the crisis actors
Cumbiamba in the mainstream media radar
And quote
Qualify
From his organization in Colorado
To conclude no it's not that
Crisis actors
Ergo
Everything
Actors were there
What made him think
I think this shoot is so weak
I bet this is going to be slam dunk
Evidence it's so insane to hear people like
Even in a friendly environment
Try and explain what made them
These things
Cuz it's like if you just listen to it it's always so much more disappointing than you kind of
What you hope it's a better story than
Event
So a drill
We know that they were actors belongings
It's just how we talk
Okay
Maybe what you say is correct
Interview
But that's one of the reasons that I actually put that for
Of their being
Crisis actor
The most controversial
That's a super lame explanation for why you believe they were
Boron
F*** you
That's it
Yeah starting with
Is your explanation
I mean whenever I look at pics
Pictures and I'm always like
Call Matt if this was a crisis there be more people there
Reasonable aim for convince
You see here that's all just bought a did end up asking him about that
From earlier still staying
Aftermath
Albertino's
Furious at the topic doesn't
Who's the best strategy
He asked Tracy about the crisis actors idea but
Before hard out to a commercial
Knowing that Tracy's answer is going to be at least long enough
To get to the commercial break
Is Don in the middle of
And say that they needed to go to break no need for a difficult follow-up
He buys himself minutes of time during the commercial breaks come up with a way to respond that preserves
The possibility of Crisis actors being used
While also preserving the aloof
Between himself
And someone who would say something like that
He said himself a perfect
Play prick
I believe this plays out
Because when they come back
From commercial Paul at has realized
Swingrail
And gives out
Professor
We have people
On the ground
Into the official story so I guess
Talking about
Yes that's correct
Medias
Want it was merely a question
Actually
F****** right
Tons of people
Jerk off onto a typewriter
Because they're they're just
Because they already
You know what it is they
And they're so excited
To say that
We heard that defense
Alex
Bucking guy who you're pointing finger right now
He's asking
Mean question
And that's why I'm
Sending letters demanding DNA
The interview is pretty boring stuff and a lot of the stuff that
He's covered already so if
Be kind of laborious to go through it
Like you talked about how the story changed when the conference
Or were there an accurate early reports from
Immediate information like there isn't any of these situations
He says that he doesn't trust
The medical examiner because he had a bad press conference
And that's why you started to doubt
This is so weak
Bulshit
I can't believe
This person
Is this
Everything
Best he can in order to make him
Not look like a
He rehabbed the ideas
You're saying that they were there to massage the narrator
F*************** died
Albion Act
Yeah it seems like
That is made my mood very
Sapulpa
Where's the jovial
Here's the jovial and theranos
Okay we really appreciate your time and questions
Thankful
Raising questions about the Sunday
Even surprise me
Crazy inside
Call Michelle
Good luck
Punzel videos
Cuz he's not going to be able to walk that much better job
Performance
Did it
Good
The worst thing possible
Could not have gone worse if
Present
She probably just want to talk all about gun
That's also true
The first two hours
Of the shower
For the show
Mike Adams takes over the second
Health Ranger Mike
Yes boy the reason
Is because he also had a big
Guest
Cam filling in for Alex today
Joining me now for the rest
No no no
I told you
I told you what
I told you this terrible
Completely
Because you have that power over all of her
This is so bizarre
Because I'm looking through these four
And Alex's
Harrison weirdos
Is going on in the middle of it he says tomorrow we're going to get into Sandy Hook
ITune in the next day Paul Joseph Watson interview
Pretty f***** up this is a whole episode
As it goes on
F****** Mike Adams shows up with Andrew Wakefield
We cannot talk about this.
It's crazy
Yeah pretty weird started this show and we were like literally
Crazy
I barely remember
Seduction
Do this pile of s***
Skin wars
Thailicious
Garbage motherfuker
Viewed as an expert on
With the possible exception of him being an excellent subject
About the subjective experience of having
And countless
In February 1998 Wakefield Rhode a research paper was published in the medical journal
Journal Lancet
Artemis Children's Hospital between July 96
In February 1997 presenting with bowel issue
Let's remember the sample size is 12
Is paper alleged the two-thirds of the children experienced
Which is to say for example language skills that were there
Before we're actually lost
Send the child
Asserted that many of these symptoms were seen within 40
Has mumps and rubella shot
With the average being
Point three days after the
Cosby severe immediate backlash against vaccines
Impossible to put into words
Public trust was eroded the anti-vaccination movement previously
Completely Fringe phenomenon
Became more mainstream and embolden and Safeguard the Public Public
Help were Jeopardy
His claims began to take hold in the UK where he was
But
States in the year to
MMR vaccine
With an alleged quote epidemic of autism
The anti-vax crowd in the United
It states started
Some serious move
It would be want to study
I need actually found evidence
Vaccine
With his bowels
Condition that quote
But
Come out his work was not above board
I want to study only involve 12 chilled
Which is absurdly small sample size
Subsequent attempts to reproduce the results of
The study of all failed to arrive same
Conclusion
As more and more information about the study and how it was conducted the game to come
The surface
Lancet began retract
At first retracting the entire
The study
Completely retract
The study authors
With ethical violations as well as scientific
Misinterpretation
So it was all done
Never got back on
Three years later on Infowars
We'll get to that
I hate him he's so much worse than people think
Cloned human
The embryo not really knock knock.
Coca-Cola
That kind of thing
Like I'm not I don't want to
Claude the Chinese
Disappeared
Consequences
You think this is Extreme
Hold on.
According to an investigation done by British journalist Brian
Deer reported in the British Journal of Medicine
Wakefield failed to disclose
20 embarked on this
Put on the payroll of a solicitor Richard bar
Wakefield 435000
643 lb
Plus expense
Why
Why would a trial lawyer
According to Dear as part of a scheme whereby Richard bar would be able to begin a massively profitable class action lawsuit against back
But in order to
To do that he would need a study to illustrate that there was a causal connection
Between the onset of this condition
And receiving the vaccine
Close examination of medical record
The children included in the study
Turned up some really really damning
Stop
Perhaps the biggest red flag with regarding child
Whose father spoke with Brian beer
In the study tribe 11 is listed as one of the children whose symptoms happened after getting the MMR shot
But according to his actual medical records father that is not true
The symptoms preceded the shot by at least a month
This information is the results
Inclusion
Child's 11th Father's Day quote
Please let me know if Andrew Wakefield has his doctor's life
Revoked
His misinterpretation of my son and his research paper is
Probably go to jail
Another child child to develop symptoms 2 weeks after getting the vaccine but his mother is gone on record
He said it was 6 months
In the case of child ate her general practitioner wrote this a note to wake
Ignored and included this girl to study anyway
Simply reiterate that both the hospital and members of the primary care team involved
Had
Concerns about developments
Before she had her MMR shot
I have to study was scrutinized more problems
Coming up
I like the fact that one of the children's mothers was a member of a group that campaigned against the MMR
Are the parents of two of the other children
People that
New
Or that another of the parents
I was looking for answers about her child which led to beating someone who connected her with bar
And resulted in her child's inclusion in the study
The sample of 12 children with highly selective
As opposed to being an anyway science
Tif example
Lancet study
To get into all of the
But if you'd like to
Is a whole shitload of research
You can find that lays out almost every element
This study has the appearance of either being the most
Incompetent
Piece of work ever or outright.
Well that's good that we've got that cleared up
Sure
Wake me up in have his medical
He said he was completely discredited
Subsequent studies which eventually
Get 1,000 or whatever
We follow the protocols of science have consistently
Right there's no causal relationship between vaccines and autism spectrum
From sorters but it doesn't matter
People
He started
Unimaginable
Experian
It's amazing that in 2013 he's on Infowars instead of in a prison
It's presented as a credible voice
3 years after his daddy had been denounced and retracted
Fully years after the questions about his undisclosed funding work
Completely public
Well after the assessments of the methodology
Science
More of a farce is that Alex
He's being interviewed by the f******
My cat
Is just embarrassed
Chevy
Also far up is
Frites
Gadsden flag
Push back on that before you get too far
The interview
We have on
Disgraced science
That mean wonderful man
Scammer nope nope
In the end
Fitness First
Of the fact that these
These things about Wakefield or beings
But it turns out that those
The British medical journal still has not returned
There's slanderous statements about you and your research
Is the key
How did that go
Episode in August 2012 Travis County district judge
Bible action against British medical journal straight out of court
This case was thrown out because of course the Texas Court doesn't have jurisdiction for this case
But if you want to know the truth that's exactly why
Put this case in a Texas Court
Because I get rejected on a technicality
He would prove these monsters have wronged him so badly
You know how f****** know that
Well though because it's 2500 the high court of London
But withdrew that lawsuit voluntarily
He probably did that because the judge Justice
ET I was kind of onto his ruse
Same quote
Extract whatever advantage
She could from the existence of these proceedings
Progressed them
Or to give the defendants and opportunity of meeting the clay
She really didn't know her s*** Wakefield agree to pay
Wakefield agreed to pay beers legal
Fees when discontinuing the action
Probably to avoid getting
So he already tried to do this in London Court
Where you did have jurisdiction now
Wakefield to go on to appeal the jurisdiction
This court
Texas
Disclaims
Even threatened to take it to the text
Supreme Court
These are real
Their PR stunts to create the appearance that look like they're heading towards him is actual
Study habits be reviewed in court
He's quick to Rich
His unethical medical behavior is only rivaled by his cowardice
This is Allah
Helping him
Laura Loomer needs her money so she can file a lawsuit
Right
Courtyards cancer
It's been that way for a little while.
What's more popular of the hustle
To file a lawsuit
And really expand
Go through
Costly to lose a frivolous
Which all of these people are doing
Super Lube
Explain
Increasing
That patience
And there is a Relentless assault on
For me
Wakefield's claims is Attack on Titan
That one is
Infuriating
Considering he's a walking every moment he draws breath isn't it
Concepts
You know everyone will be afraid to do controversial research because they lose
Willing to do on the
Connection between Autism and
The nation
You're wrong and we're lying all of their work
Prove that you're wrong
Follow the scientific
Experiment
No one cares
Yeah I mean in 2019
Arkansas love 657
461 children
To gauge whether or not there wasn't
Increased autism risk among children who received
I'm sorry I thought I heard you say
What was the conclusion that study
The study strongly supports that MMR vaccination does not
The restaurant
Trigger autism
Susceptible children
The clustering of autism cases
After vaccination
Also there's
Another study published in the New England Journal medicine
530 7303 children
And concluded
Hypothesis
That MMR vaccination
Or if you prefer American studies there was a 25th
Study published in the Journal of the American Medical Association
We're researchers followed 90 5700
27 children
Including 15,000 unvaccinated
The children observe
Observe
No association between MMR vaccination
Increase ASD risk
Even among children with
Siblings with a F
Cuz William Barr came out after
Said that
Oh no
So we know
Brett Bar
Again
I could go on and on but this is the point
Conclusion
Which repeatability
An important feature of the scientific method
Wakefield results have never been
Repeated explicitly
Contradictory result
He's not a brave scientist under attack
He's a frog who got caught
Realize his only chance for a future career
Hard into the medical conspiracy theory car man world
Completely
So might as well might as well go hang out with
Elf Ranger
Court
It is next about
Breaking news
Article published at HuffPost
Children with autism
It has made the determination that there is a causal link
Between vaccinations
And the development of autism
Characteristics
Gastrointestinal symptoms and Steph
Dysfunction
!
HuffPost article that they're talking about
With the headline quotes
Vaccination
Two children with autism
Was not published by the
Post
It was published as part of their
Contributor platform
Whoever replied
Control their own work
And post freely on our site
It was blog post to the regular wedding
Now closed area of a
Second of all kind of crazy people in association with us that's awesome
Second headlines
The children who also had autism
Spectrum disorders
The court has been consistent in its position
3 - c in back
Autism
Award people money who claimed damages from vaccines causing it
However
That doesn't mean that a child who also has ASD could possibly also have another condition
It may be covered by the vaccine
To misinterpret
2nd battalion case that Wakefield to talk about is a bit of a
British
In July 2012
A Provincial Court in Rimini Italy
This case is the prime example
The Backs people
Their claims
The argument
An Italian Court hold up in an American court if they're brave enough to hear the case they say
As it turns out the only evidence presented by the families
And the testimony of an expert witness was relying on the Lancet study for his testimony
In 2012
Court of appeals and bolonia overturned
Decision in February 2015
Specifically because the evidence introduced was
Also really shity friend to point out that the Italian case made it so people didn't have to
Get the MMR vaccine
Italy because part of that appeal in 2015
She noted that after the case
Vaccination rates drop local
Clear round ribbon
2015 they had an
85% vaccination rate percent
Is a real-world consequence
For things like this b******* that microwave
Dangerous
But they're they're playing with
And they don't
Don't care about the cops
Because there is a point at which like if you drop down is vaccination rate too far
They could be
Real real
I can't imagine
Empathic nature
He's still lying he's perfectly why
Purposefully
The monster of leelai cleats
Entirely on his discredited study
Basically
Departs through whenever it takes a little bit of time to
Disentangled
It's not really all that hard to not wear the manipulation
Like
Cities next clip he cites a study
And I have some
Confidence in vaccines
In a recent study from University of Michigan
Found
So
I can't find the study that matches up with what wakefield's describing but I imagined
Close study.
But if it does I'll bet anything
Interpreting what parental
Concern me
Concerned about vaccine
If I would believe that's true but not the interpretation
He's giving
Regardless I was able to find the University of
Michigan study from 2011 so it's just
But before this came out or this episode happen
That involve Trust
Vaccine
Close
Do you talk
The problem is
He doesn't even come
Close
Conclusion
Is that weird
The study was a result of 2500
21 online surveys
Looking for determine
Incredible
Providers about vaccine
Jenny McCarthy
High level of trust for their child
Percent for other doctors
15%
Celebrities
Only 2% reported not trusting The Physician at all
According to the the American Medical Association Journal of Ethics another 2000
Study of 1420 household
Carried out by the national Center
Number for immunization in
86.5% of 4
Respondents reported that they usually followed their clinicians
And 84% reported that they Trust
I'm not sure where we was getting his data from but I can definitely find a to the team
Contradicting
I don't know what this the University of
You can study wise but I I'm just going to
As default
Interesting
Relies on it
Couple of months ago to his employees
Pediatrician
The next morning lights are out the child autistic
That's gross but also
Mike Adams is part of that 2% believe celebrities
As a reliable Taxi
Be part of the 2%
I would rather be
No one
Why are you dressed
It's wild
Yeah
Damn anymore
Fair
Calls now
All that good
Testing organization
Victim of a
Regulation
I just I wanted
I wanted to look into it a little more so I included
This clip just because I
Yeah they attacked their first amendment rights and then if they were to say anything about this anymore
They're basically an appointment prison so there
They ended their radio programming and we need the support of the people that's the problem
Is there attack
Killing the messenger
How's it going after the messenger
Federal Trade Commission
It's who went after I'm not doing nothing
CDC
Cancer
They should have
Yeah that's the risk
This is really interesting
Said that they took away their radio show
Not true at all
Outside thing could never type things
Misleadingly and that was how they were funding
The radio show radio show fraud
2009 the courts found against the group known as Daniel chapter 1
Because
Specifically broken
Commission
ABC was the fact their marketing Health product by making two monster be false claims about them
And making a real nice profit doing so
Reminder products
Including
The clock there of the Lord there is a truck
True
Christian
Products
The seven herb formula
Touch of God
And my favorite
BioShock
BioShock 2
I prefer Bioshock rap
Preference for nobody
Specifically able to inhibit
Tumor growth
What are the products
The prosecution address D complaint
Just wright
F*** off
Completely when their advertisements were in
Introduced into court as evidence
Which four more towards
Healthcare supplement vibe that I know religion
The courts determine that nothing about the case
Infringed on the religious freedom but their actions
Absolutely violated
Super protection statutes
Regarding
False medical claims about the thing
Things are selling
Ultimately Daniel chapter 1 was forced to pay millions of dollars in restitution to customers they defraud it
And a bunch of fine
You can read the court documents about the case there's a lot of discussion about their first amendment concern
Previous score
Every concern you might have it it's all pretty well laid out in the court documents
This is a case about a medical
Corsets
Haley should turn it into it called celeb
Because they're just
What is guilty of paddling
Is Daniel chapter 1
They're just more careful about not making
Medically unfit
Claims about the things
Bodies of water because
It's getting a little close to home
Goddamn
I hate
This is been such an inch
Furiated
Triplet YouTube
I know it would be angry at everybody
If it's the only possible way this
Could be worse is if your likes and surprised they did two hours of overdrive
God dammit
Climate change deniers
Exist I know it was a shock to your system to Gary New York
Bioshock intercept
Andrew Wakefield show up out of nowhere but I promise you there's no more
Surprise
Just a couple of weird collars
This first color is describing his experience
Dealing with
I think he's presenting it as
Indication
He's not mentally
But I would describe the story he's telling
Pretty indicative that his behavior
Evidence
My my parents made me go see a therapist
Basically started making things up
Besan
I was reading his diagnosis actually read
Michael Crichton Terminal Man
Basically just
Completely
Psychiatrist
Gave me some medication and then
By the time it was all said and done
I was on it first came out
Depakote
Also
Reminder
So you can hear their bike Adams
To talk about guns and mine are all those records
Steven B Adams attempt
Of course
Concern
I'll join the Army no one really cares
Like a pathology
Takashi
But I don't know what
I don't know because he has a game
The sort of person
He's going to say you lie to a doctor that automatically means something
To which he was doing it
Seem to be indicative of
As for you you wouldn't.
Hospital
Supposed to do
You're reporting
Subjective experience
Of your own mental state
It would be
Negligent
To put you in a hospital perhaps if you
Word describing hearing voices
That you were disturbed by
Like
I don't know how he
He characterized the voices too
Doctors
Musical really
Same
Response
What what you just described
A lot of
Situation
Appropriate
And he was the one who
It seems like from The Limited information we have it does
Yeah you are the one who's messed up
Maybe you didn't have
Depression
You're describing to the doctor
But your actions belie the
But you had something going off
So
It was like
Well
This wasn't
I think I I think I won
So I'm going to cut off the last clip cuz it's really goodbye
Expressing
Credentials
No One Colt
No one asks for an explanation
Credentials
Doctor Wakefield I just want to say it's really a pleasure sir
To be talkin to you
I myself actually on one of America's few remaining Pioneer research scientist
He's super Pioneer research is one of the last remaining American Tire your research
American Pioneer research
There's no there's no like what does that mean
Who are you
You are what you're saying
Grand
Confirmation for my f****** pioneer
Researcher really are something that we're not
About enough
You know everybody that everybody talked about how the bees
These are dying and
The climate is changing
Changing but were missing
Is the real human cost of
Of so few
Pioneer pioneer
That is a
It is a big blow American
Switzerland
Yeah
Pioneer of what
Is he also a imagine
Is on an episode of Gunsmoke
Any played
The day before got a call from this guy
Who's talking about this gun Bill the HR 2
Colorization
Makino's about Civic structure and
Recent like an expert that recycles that information as his spirit is
Mike Adams is exact same thing
Pioneer Trucking research scientist
What are you talkin
Just Dutch
Consist
Thread
These two episodes
That were completely f***** up and
So wide-ranging
Gotten through it in just over two hours
Thread is just
Ability
Unwillingness
You call anyone out on the ship
Yeah
You have this
Denny payment
Who is a corrupt
F****** a****** Sheriff
Cousin
Likes the gun stuff you saying
Refuse any kind of real
Oh my God you're a megalomaniac
You're at your a nut
All you have
Paul Joseph Watson
Because it's good for business
Viral video
Siphoning off some of that audience
More
Important to him then actually
Standing up for his
Professed principal
Yeah yeah
Is just allowed to run roughshod
And because he is also a medical weirdo and he makes
Ton of money off medical wound always bulshit
Allows that to happen
And you take this call that he's a f****** Pioneer science
It's just
Whatever you say you are is what you are
As long as you're not there
Children are pure
Because if we're not paying
Crisis actors
You're bringing me what I need
You define yourself board
Sad
Add
Ieg
Together after
Do you think they ever have meetups where they're all just
Man this
Or do you think they all just hide
To talk about it almost more like a
Like Gunslingers if we're going to continue this metaphor
Where they're just going into it and they've all got their
Their hand on their web
I know what you do
I know what you do I do it too
I think it probably be
Ghost to talk about it
I don't think that they would
Arrow be embarrassing
Like Paul Joseph Watson
Yeah
Sam Smith going through
Sensitivity training
Or whatever okay now here we are all running
I think it's something
You instinctually know what to do
Yeah
Them knowing about this anything
Bother anybody
I don't know if the people who have left
Said Alex
Said this is a scam
They just know it is from lived
Experience
Scamp
Evidence
Especially these days
Yeah no kids only getting worse
It's
Moved from any notion of
Subjective reality in
Purely sup
It's terrified
It is terrific
So this episode of terrific
Expose
I was really I knew that
Is it James Tracey
He was coming up
Eventually
But I knew that that would probably be at least in some ways
A big moment
Investigation
Yeah and I'm glad
I'm glad that we are on the other side of it
Because now I think I have a strong
Suspicion that this is where Alex
I'm going to change
Because
Paul Joseph Watson and Alex
When they were on the show Alex on the 17th
The Paul on the 8th
Both Express
Did they know that this video was as popular as it was
Review video
Sandy Hook crisis actors
False flag
I think that's going to have aliens
Inform things moving forward
Which is very interesting
Because
Had we not spent the time and gone through all of it
We wouldn't
Know that
Didn't care that much
Wake up till this
Point
He didn't even care that much
It makes a lot of sense
Assume
One of his motivations might be
Recognizing the market
Moving forward
Pivot towards
Covering sand
Hook and talkin about
Sandy Hook
You know damn well that's why
That's probably unfair to say
With certainty
Like that
Probably
Right
Unlike
People
SafeLink
However
It sure does look like all the oven
Pointing towards
Question even become
What's fun about going through this
We could have much more robot
Alex
Just saying
He said that they were after that
Conclusion
Is so weird
It's always weird we learned along the way
How we learned about lovemaking
In the early 1900s
Welearn
We learned about
To talk about
Comments I'm glad
Organically came up within the investigation
Rhino
Sorry
Is the worst
So we come to the end of this and we will be back on Monday and we will we will see you then
Until then we have website
Knowledge fight.
Realtor
The podcast
In podcast
Many places
Through
Podcast app
The Prestige
Or maybe we'll go
It's whatever
I mean I don't know
Raven Fringe daughter guy who's running against
Wednesday premieres civil rights
Tell anybody though it's
Just fine
Probably did
Is that boy alex
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work