Alex
Talk about our creator
Don't know
Georgia
Organize
Are you played basketball
Middle School
And I was not good
Fake an injury
Look at my
Or something
Blotter acid
If you don't
Most of the time that resolves itself
But I use that as an excuse not to play football
I was told that I would be on the line
Not going to run into
Does somebody over and over again
Part of the game I was interested player
I'm so high
Stop
Did you ever comedians have had
Meet up where they play softball or something
As bad as real bad
I never bowled in bowling alley with them
Because we would just get picture
And get really f***** up rulers rule
Close your frame
Scream
Team sports
Especially
Maybe I don't think we were as good a friend
Yeah that's playing with boys
Altos volleyball
After Chasing Sunsets
Playing with The Boys lyrics
Rebecca D login so
Skip
Powerball number January 20th
Your 23rd 2013
Because I was
I just don't want to do it
I didn't I am not leaving
State of mind that is like
Can't do it
And I'm too
Curious
About what's going on with the
2013 investigation looking at
Dialysis coverage
Sandy Hook
Especially after
Paul Joseph Watson
Send interviewed Professor James
On the last episode I was very
To see what would happen
Confirm that my curiosity
Do you want current date
Play where we talk
Talked about how all abortion should be
Yeah.
Oh I'm sure Alex is talking about that
I think there is some value to us covering that which is why
Present day
Decide
I did not
I watched a couple episodes
I don't think
I don't think it's a good
If not
Clear where we stand
Maybe we've done
Enough
Especially
Not sure get involved in social media
Pushing pushing
Publicly our support opposition
Absolutely
When we get back to the present day
It's not what is
Bother
Let's not worry about
So
Somebody
We had to get into thank you
People have signed up and are supporting the show
So first of all
I'm a policy wonk
Text Jake
Thank you so much
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Donation bumped it up a little bit
But I have a new drop
This is the whole reason.
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
The first
New drop
We got to go.
Heroin
Richardson bars
I'm not sure if that is as good as our old technocrat drop
Reviews come in
That's true
Respond to terrorists
But I do take
Website
Sports show we would appreciate it I don't want talk about the present day
Alex
Something on the episode
That made me think that we're having an effect on his world
I'm not sure
But I think that we are responsible for this clip
This is one of the first times that I've heard Alex
Say something on the show
I don't think
Can have anything to do with anybody but off
If it's that this is a blue my mind
Jones
Imprison Weaver in
Alma Street
People walk
Prison for murder
Might be assertive strong version
Which I've never heard anybody but us
Not like a criticism comes up
I don't know right wing watch
I don't know if this has anything to do with us but it was one of the things
Seems very strange
The 20th
Is the 23rd of January
It happens in the
Track
Big narrative
Big things
We got to get into
I'm excited to do that
Here is an out-of-context drop
From Today Show
Rural America
Mostly right off the top
That is a Sunday
And so he just died
21st ounces out of Studio
Mike Adams
You just talked to that sheriff Danny payment
I got arrested the first time
So Mike Adams has him an interview
I talked to an author whose name is
Is Max velocity
Tell me what
Gun to my head I don't remember I couldn't tell you anything that he did
Videos about what is the max velocity of most
Vanara our boy Jon rappoport
Excuse.
January 21st
2013 was the day of Obama's second
Second inauguration
First inauguration
Alex left
Show to go get interviewed on Ark
For a little while
Second inauguration
For someone who's so committed
The fight against
The globalist and Obama
Ever be around on Tuesdays
Or be totally fine to just
The ship probably calculator
So he doesn't work
Himself up in
Too much of
My friends
Coincidence
You couldn't have known in advance like the popo
Wood step down
The 22nd
Here is the
Clip Alex is getting a little bit
About people saying
But he doesn't know what he's talking about
Super smart
Coverage of Alex's documentary
Is really fun
Alex
Bibliography
Citations to Encarta page
Just for things that don't act
Sports
Links to Infowars articles he wrote himself
Citation
You never felt the need to finish
A lot of those and
Insert a citation
Never completed
Presuming to provide a citation
Exist often completely manufactured
His bibliography for endgame
High School teacher wouldn't even let it fly as acceptable
Paper documentary presuming to prove a grand conspiracy
Event on Cloverland
Global enslavement and depopulation
Even people who believe Alex
Should really see this bibliography
Damning proof
He's talking about
What is the end game.com with website that Alex used to redirect
Endgame the movie.com
Is in 2013
Recording snapshots from the machine
The URL what is the end game.com
Has not worked as a redirect
At least 2,000
It's been 5 years has been appropriate Place directions listeners
So even even him
Giving you the link to the bibliography that doesn't actually exist
Next Level and had
5 years
Proving his business
Control
You always is
Came out
Some people on the cover who were working
Regulation
Time Magazine
Gunfighters
Scootering
What
You can't do that before she got
Chapman
I don't we don't have time
Right now cover all of the details of the Gabrielle Giffords
Shooting
Just her
Block
9 year old girls
At some point I promise everybody
I know that we've gotten some requests
Cover that
I'm sure Alex
Terrible the way he flippantly said I'd let her whatever
I would point out about this
Wanted to draw
Attention to is the difference
How Alex is
Reading this
The idea that
Turn
The shooting into
Proof of
Tifa democrat-republican
Mocking
Gabrielle Gifford
It just
People don't let it be a people on the right really don't like
They are the results of Their Own
You know
And so they have
Undercut any other
Possible
Result of their
Scream bloody murder about when Republicans are attacked
They have to minimize whenever anybody else has it
I don't
Florida political
Do you want to do like I still think it's fine
Piece of s***
The same time it's not okay to
It's not okay to mark
Gabrielle Giffords being the victim of
It's not okay
Position
He's doing imagine he was talking about shooting victim
President Reagan
Might have done that
If you was on the air
Consistent
History January 2013
Alex was
Pretty
Focus
On
Piers Morgan
Gone on Piers Morgan show
Call over the flu all over the entire set
All of the staff offered to work for Alex
Text now just to not go on there now
Agents in the hallway
He bested peers about every way
And
Used lightly let this drop a little bit here by the 22nd
He's kind of
He's moved on a little bit towards
Maybe you'll get invited Obamacare
Piers Morgan
What is fire
The Piers Morgan wants
The kill all the gun owners
And here's how Alex
Automatic
That was the clip that I was already played that but husband
Condemned to that
Stupidest thing
Anybody could have done
Listening to it again I do think she thought that
He meant like hitting him in the face with the
I don't know I I can't pretend to understand
Or know what someone is
Feel like she's responding to someone saying
Who killed X
No matter
How much I disagree with him about everything
He's right
Except someone talk
Think about him like that especially on National Television
Unfortunately
Trinity
What I do is I replace the saucers of the machine gun
I'm just leaving the place to publish
I'm just typing
Text Alex
New clip of Piers Morgan talking about shooting people and
Play
Over and over and over again
And he says that it's about shooting gun owners Michigan
So in this next clip he plays the clip again just says it a little bit more
I am because he played it so many times
Care but
Because he played it so many times has started
To notice what was actually being talked about pick out the names that are disgusting
The situation the interviewer is acting explain it all to you
And it has nothing to do with it
Trinity
Greene Prudential
Replace deposit
I'm just playing
I'm just
Just replace the Buzzard with the machine gun
Always fantasizing about shooting
Alright so are you
Get what's going on here
Clarkson on
Britain's Got Talent
Some of the important details but Alex is praying his audience
Can't make out
Thing that everybody would say
Misrepresenting
I'm just at
Barely listening to the coil it's obvious
The first indication of that is that the interviews a bus
People imagine what he would rate them
Contestants on Britain's Got Talent the show the Piers Morgan was one of the judges on for the first four seasons
Which is why it's relevant to ask that question
Clarkson which as you were able to stop doubting the reference
Tucson journalist Jeremy Clark
Person who's possibly best known as
One of the host of Top Gear
Spring 1988 1998
2012 225
Aaliyah reference Jeremy
Piers Morgan have a well-documented long-standing
Refute
Some of this dates back to
A is the editor of the daily
Mirror
Corks And wasn't happy about some of the photos that were published
The Tabloid
Sort of Heaven
Comstock to dig up dirt on him
Being a Clarkson with a direct competitor in the mirror was
Bad shape financially
Unhappy about that treatment Clarkson portal
Glass of water on Piers when he ran into
What's
Reminder but there's no hero in this story
2004 British ceremony
We're a fairly drunk Clarkson
An approach that you're in my world I can tell you your
The guardian reports
Reports about what happened next
Apparently Clarkston
Quote claims Morgan slighted his wife
Which is a very British way to phrase
Carson started
Apparently connecting at least
Go to shop
Put his keys in a bowl
Skidmore
Here's unfazed gal is that all you got
It turned out it wasn't
Tears would tell the guardian quote
Let me present my nose by about an inch
Later. Would say quote I frankly taken worst beatings from my three-year-old son
Now that's a better life
Stryker
Is just one in a long line
We'll have to kiss and make-up
However later he was spotted in Windows on the world
The bar telling people that he did it all for Britain
In 2015 with Piers announcing the
Quotes
Clarkson
Quote
I'm going through a difficult
I'm going through a difficult divorce
My first ex-wife is also come out of the woodwork to give me how
I'm smoking too much drinking too much my back hurts
I'm all over the papers with this n words
Scandal I'm at war with the BBC bosses and my mother has just died I simply don't have the energy for you anymore
On an episode of Top Gear
Two cars Clarkson did the old
Eenie meenie miney mo
Expect
I got a little bit of water about that
The desire to shoot that Jeremy Clarkson has nothing to do with gun
Forgot
Anything like that
The second person that was listed by the interviewer
The contested does hypothetical episode of Britain's Got Talent is
Which is a referee
Prince2
Trini appeared as a contestant on The
2007 season of comic relief does The Apprentice
The UK version
Comic relief charity
UK version of Vape through the celebrity of run
A gun to a bit of a famous fight
On the show
On the episode each team was supposed to get a chef assigned
To them that would help
Complete their mission for the episode
The chef for the girls team accidentally showed up at the boys
Who decided instead of sending him where he's supposed to go they would lock him up in their bathroom
Do you want to try and sort this out but an argument broke out and things
A little bit
If you watch the actual video to show the whole thing
Began as a
Obviously
Contrived in manufacturer
The drama but it appears
A and Trinity
Who was quite a bit in the media about how she ended up crying
This sort of fight went a long way toward solidifying
A is reputation
Is being a complete
Later on was what part of is Brandel
This escalated
He cry
It said into that ugly
So I'm sure he doesn't look back
At that interaction with
Him joking about shooting her head nothing
Things to do with her supporting guns either
The interviewers ask hypothetical question about the
Two people doing an act on Britain's Got
He suggests Clarkson would be going on about his green card
Because Clarkson was a big enemy of the green movement
Cnv lesbian
Treaty would talk about what everyone is wearing because she was the host of whatnot
To wear for its first five season
The clip has nothing to do with gun
Morgan's high-profile to YouTube
UK
I grant that the joke that he's making
Incredibly poor taste
No probably
Critiquing for that
Brazen
Active intellectual dishonesty
Alex's Thompson
You can pass it off because his audience
Carefully listen to that and they'll just assume Clarkson and Trini are gun lovers in the UK or so
It's our operating from a sin
See your position
You would never try to pass off this kind of manipulation
His audience
This is
Deeply
Intention
You know it
Weird because it is
Contacts
Not necessarily taking it out of context
But because you don't know because the average American has no idea what the
Like no British celebrities
You know
It doesn't
The X-Men
It will be a problem
Delta Spirit be like
He does say that he wants
To shoot people on Britain's Got Talent
That must be what at least
Also he got the quote
Said he love you
Like whenever he plays it again I see it almost on one of
Documentaries
Got the full body shot of him saying
Zooms in and crops out
Step total
It's a classic Alex
For sure
We can still go fly a kite
Give me all of that tricks probably the only one who's probably I don't know enough about her I have no idea
She is like as a person or even as a celebrity I just know that Piers Morgan made her cry
Jeremy Clarkson a Morgan
Groza
I'm more sympathetic but also with the caveat that
She might have
Terrible skeleton Arrow
Go watch your girlfriend
Discusses how Soviet Russian Nazi
Germany mix
Is coming
Depression that represent
Santa's coming
And then we get to see what it looked like
German
Incredible
I do I do
T-shirts
Fine
Normal
That's what you would expect unlike NPR's
Sort of
Sophia depression is coming please for the sponsors
Evocative thing and then add
Character
But he's not
Getting people whipped into a frenzy
The same way he does
Differences
What similarities Bulbasaur
Whatever the Pokemon evolution figure
Charizard
Sears art actually whatever
Did you ever
It was
Obviously he is still doing his whip people up into a frenzy
But it was
In regards
News stories
Soffer NPR
Sing along the lines
Is Alabama's abortion law is the most
Draconian
History
This
Channel is the 49er with
Separate them
With a bed of music
They would probably throw in some weird folk songs
MP3 world music
Two comes in
It's our boy Max Keiser
Couch to Max Queens
The Great
He doesn't have that interests
But out of his own volition
Let's
Something happens
Becoming very
He's just pictured around
Because of that
Probably really interested in playing
Cancel predictions
Between now and April as I predicted
I might be wrong but I won't be wrong
Taken
So
You think about their prediction
Pennywise
He's not entirely wrong
Bond market collapse
There was a very large cell
May 2013 which is close enough
Forgiving him kind of partial credit for that predict
Yeah I would take that a couple weeks
The sell-off was the result of the Federal Reserve chairman Ben Bernanke
To taper off quantitative easing
Slow down
It's worth noting that Alex in his gas
Constantly call on the feds and quantitative
Exactly what they do a downturn in the market
Market by the falls
Ultimately I fail to believe that Alex or Mac really care too much about the health of the bond market
Considering it immediately after Trump won the 2016 election
The bond market crash to the tune of the loss of $1000000
That situation
This prediction by Max Keiser is not really a psychic predicts
I was going to make this move around that time or 2013
Probably could have guessed that there were significant
He's being a little bit more
Sensational that he needs to be possibly but he's
Not as
He's not being as irresponsible as a lot of viruses
Yeah and the financials
I'm talking about the common market trouble and services that second part
The gold is going to go up
And let me tell you Jordan
It did not
Max
It is explicit prediction that it was going
To go up because of
The downturn in the market
The bond market
Did go down
More or less as he predicted
$3.75
4 oz
Hannah Davis episode was up to
82 + 30
2 cents per ounce
Market sell-off
The price was down to 1470 dollars in $0.44
And if we continue dropping for the rest of the day
You're ending on New Year's Eve
205 dollars in 40
Great representing and approximately 27
Set drop in value
Gourmet the slight uptick in 2014 but it never reached 40
Gear down at 1181.
Gold spec 2015 barely above $1,000 an ounce
60 dollars in 80s
So for the next
2 years
After the school did not
Go up very high
And it's spelled
What may be a little bit more
Give or take it out
That's not good
Max's prediction about the bond market Services strength
Their appeals for Their audience to bike
Speculative advice
If this weren't a show being syndicated by a gold sales company
These sorts of conversation
They would be a bit more suspicious
If they weren't immediately followed by a commercial for Midas resources
Which it is as soon as they go to break
Anderson has a commercial for Midas resources
So all of this
Has to be
Proceed with M that
Larger context than that
Intentional model
Simple
Call the action in the book
Next thing you know
Guess who's selling gold
But the thing that I find more interesting about it is
Terms of
The financial
People that I've seen on our to the show
The closest to having
Not
Crazy
Set up
The other people have pretty insane
Yeah
First stages that get to the gold kind of like
Post Harbour
Close
It's all around
Because something happens breaking news
Well
In the middle of interviewing Mac
Will not stop interrupting my
I don't know
Irrelevant
Compared to a lot of
What's up with the word
Kind of funny
Decently clever of him to me for me to get that kind of
Depression because they're also kind of boring
Cleverness is
Contextually fairly boring whenever I hear him coming up on it
Fat guys are coming up
Poopy doopy
Realized
Yeah that's what
I only get excited when a monster
Of course
News
Here's what it is
Lone Star College in Houston
So Alex has eggs
No I predicted
That
After Alex recognized the popularity of these
YouTube
Videos about
10.6
Million views
Days on this YouTube video
We got to get into this business
Paul Joseph Watson interviews James
I had a strong
Suspicion that there was going
Tubi
And I believe that the way Alex of covering the shooting at the Lone Star College
In Texas
Is
Pretty strong example of
So is he going to go straight
Crisis actor
Initiative
Shift that there's something
Covering the shooting not broadcasting everything live
For the world to see
Because there's a cover-up going on
Urns are lessened because
The people on the
So Alex
Insists that he is going to
Play the
Stream
From the local news
Channel
So here is covering this
I will get into
What's going on
It's busy
Recorded
So Alex is basically pitching The Narrative that this is covering it out by
To do the work
They refuse to do
The Houston
KHOU
Feed
Infuriated
It doesn't matter super transparent
Sandy Hook
Video call to go through
Video
Is so popular that there's a huge market for it
The claim that space early with this next
Business is the next one after he
Realizes that market share
So that's the most
Capitalistic thing
Like he's already
Plotting it advanced
How he's going to make money off of
The next school shooting
That his rhetoric makes
Renders
Inevitable
He would probably call it
Coverage
Sure you would call it making money
Potato potahto
The next
Kia is going to live coverage
CNN Warriors
Students are not right
YES Prep
Basically
And
Fart
Disposition is pretty clear
Where he's coming from
Is very irrelevant apparently because we are not listening
We're just hearing
By Design
All the way down back here on the other side
That's pretty gross
Wow
So on January 22nd 2013 there was a shooting on the Campus of Lone Star College
Community College in Harris County
Incorporated area outside
The shooting was the result of an argument between Foster and another student
People were hospitalized
Including
Someone who is
There's a second person
The name Carlton Berry
Later because he wasn't
However after the police press charges he admitted that he was there
The police defended arresting Barry and charging
Because quote Barry Foster might not have been arrested
Recover
The police were real insistent they done.
Wrong with a sheriff
French
Did nothing wrong
It's a red front
The sheriff went to a forest
To demand an apology from the local news channel
Recovering his own press conference where he showed off Barry's mugshot
And said quote if we can make an example out of anyone we will
I hope he gets what he deserves
To putting others in harm
Basically the apology from school
The distinction that this happened at a college
And also that it was a shooting
It happened at a school
Not a school shooting
Yoda meme
That distinction it's still a terrible
Disaster
But I do think that technical difference
Between an argument escalated into a shooting
It's the one setting out to
The shoe people at a college or any other school
Our differences
Okay so this was
Because it God I wish
I wish I didn't
I have to say that I don't remember
But we live in a world where they all
Yeah this one was a
Person to person
I've got guns and I'm taking about the
The school day
Information
And he's barely listen
These Witnesses
They're being covered by cage
Show you his intentions
From the first second
He's talking about this story
He's convinced that with Sandy Hook the globalist
Slipped up and accidentally
The gunmen were in the woods and all that s***
Alex is saying that they're not going to be
So sloppy this time
Which is why he's making a big deal out of the Tiger
CNN live streaming coverage of the school
The fact without knowing any of the details he covers this breaking story this way is all the proof you need to know
Motivation
Proof shooting
Did Sandy Hook was fake
This story is a prop to him
From the job to help justify his own coverage
Eventually
Of Sandy Hook
Right and so unresponsive
And they were like
We're going to do responsible reporting
F****** up his evidence of a
Conspiracy
Responsible reporting is evidence of a
Thing you can do
Also I need to mention this
In researching the story I couldn't help but notice
Trend
But the shooter in the victim in this case were both black
Generally when I read about one of these shootings
The criminal past of the shooter is discussed
Wasn't
Really weird
Also
Interested in covering the criminal past of the victim Jody
To Houston quotes
Bo also has a criminal history he was convicted of unauthorized use of a motor vehicle in 2004 in possession of a switchblade
Knuckles
Assaulted
Fake news I don't have to care about him anymore because
Record
It's really wild this is only part of the story because he was shot but the media felt it some
Help flush out the story to discuss his arrest
I cannot think of another time when I've been reading media coverage of other shootings
Where this sort of coverage is applied
And I've read a lot of stories about you
Preparations
The only other times I can think of her of course other hope high profile
The police
It's
Not
It's not an illusion how many times do we have to see a white shoe
Fuk up
30 goddamn people and then the news shows a picture of him playing f****** football in his backyard
And a black
Get these f****** mugshot put up f*** off a 2018 study out of Ohio State University founded
White Mass Shooters are 95
More likely to be described as mentally ill as opposed to
Media coverage of 219 attack
Text to reach this conclusion
Quotes much of the media coverage of white Shooters frame them as sympathetic characters who were suffering
From extreme life circle
Shooters were usually made
To seem dangerous animatics
Society
It's pretty awful that this bias is so Stark one discuss
Just got the perpetrator
What is completely insane
Defeatist directed towards victim
And I find it very hard to ignore that racial element
Considering
Countless stories
About white victims Bash
Over the course of
Sofa
This is not an isolated case
In a 2017 article on the Huffington
Composed which is an updating original
Publisher 2014
Headlines regarding stories of white Shooters and black
And he is very
Highlights media often response
Dwight Shooters around of
If it's good person could do some
Something so bad
Meanwhile headlines cover in Black
Victims
Of murder
Highlight how the guy wasn't really that good of a guy and probably a crimp
Shouldn't worry too much about that got shot
To begin with
In high school but let me tell you something
GPS
Who's the real victim super f***** up and I don't know what else to say about it other than that
Alex
Do a better job of covering
Click2Houston
Over it anymore after this at all
Father's not going to help them
Alex has a story
About young girl
Pennsylvania
You got suspended for
For having a bubble gun
Little Hello Kitty
Kitty bubblegum
Big deal
Sorta
Subway
Where are we
Apples to Apples
Paris
He's coming from I supposed newest connection
But yeah
This is the kind of
Big stories that Alex
Who's been going on about it this time frame I haven't really touched it yet cuz I
Kind of thought it was
To be a flash in the pan
Going to go away
Is Aristotle
Stupid
Child in Mount Carmel Pennsylvania
But the issue wasn't that she had a Hello Kitty bubble gum
Not really she was threatening to shoot others
What's the school that was in violation of their zero-tolerance policy
I'll probably say that this is a little
I understand the reason but I think the sort of situation
Who won the probably calls for some
Creative thinking
Probably the best response would be to not make the
Child's your other door
Excluded like
But to provide them with some kind of a setting where the parents can
Disgusted is really inappropriate
Yeah whatever my feelings on the matter are I'm not a school administrator and I've never really talked to a five-year-old so my opinion
Is useless take it with a grain of salt
Doesn't matter
On January 30th the school district overturn the suspension
Charles record
It makes it easier for the mother to get the
Suspension overturned
Since she was a former cop and had multiple lawyers with her at a closed-door meeting where they discussed
The suspension to get over there and under a staff
Undertale
Somebody trying
The meeting was closed to the Press so we may never know exactly what happened within it but
Kind of feels like it was about suing the school.
Since it's her lawyer announced after the suspension
It was erased that there would be no loss
Surprise
It also is worth noting that the child's mother when interviewed after
The suspension was overturned
Email the school administration
This is almost certainly result of media like Alex covering a case
Because otherwise why would someone outside
Care about a five-year-old getting it possibly slightly too
Punishments in her
Kindergarten class
Who cares
Multiple stories
Infowars.com
And it's come up a bunch of times on the radio show that I've been listen
Does any story pointing out that this
Suspension was overturned
Another stories with no clarification that
Or any charges of terroristic threatening
If you're a journalism Outlet that's pretty important
As clarification
Yeah I would see
You know what I was
Cowboys and Indians
Young Generation that's off babies is right
A journalism outlet with post clarification
Something
Come on
We've learned over and over
Hey Dad how do I
Compare coverage
Of similar circumstances where the person they're talking about
What are the clearest examples of in for double standard as it relates to cover the case of Ahmed Mohamed
He built a clock
Showcase there's teachers. Receptive
Infowars
Distantly refers to Ahmed as quote clock boy or clock kid
Variation
Yeah
I don't know
Quotev
Jesus and all the coverage
To take his proven
That Ahmed was engaged in the house
Right
On September 22nd 2015
Watson Road in article with the headline quote
Judge
Klockit family could be charged with fraud
Purposeful hoax
Implied
The case about the child
Fox News hosts
The sub headline to the story is
Quotes on false premise
The problem here is that the full quote from Napolitano
If the parents were involved in a hoax now you have a fraud going because money has been collected on.
Pretenses
Is eating of itself
A frog
It removes the conditional aspect of beginning of the Santa
Which depended
Go to
Urban the same
Infowars went out of its way to post
The story the packing Ahmed framing the situation is an elaborate hoax to make it look like
Islamophobia is an actual problem.
Of course he'll tell you that the population
It is more than 10% Muslim
Bible Hub
That's Islam a reasonable
If you're keeping score
Suspended for threatening
Classmates
The fake on it
Huge deal
We need to take
Is very serious
A child named Mohammed gets taken into custody for bringing the
The clock people thought was a bomb to school without ever
It's an elaborate ruse to defraud people and caused racism against white people
Perfect sense
You see how this works yeah a lot of fourteen-year-olds thinking on the third dimension
Situation
Important
Keep in mind as the coverage of
Hours of Moraine 2 Guns
Alex gets back to covering this
Texas shooting
He's almost salivating
To get this coverage
Wilshire
False flag
Or at least yourself
It was a friend
And
Class
What happened was that
Calculus
Computers
And causing just in case
And we was at 4
And of course we start here in the
Helicopter
So we found out FedEx
Somebody else
So because someone came in your classroom
That was all
I think I've ever heard
You can tell
Is a little disappointed I'm not sure if he came out in that clip you listen to the entire thing
There's a sense of deflation
Anna comes over at 10
He keeps going back
To the yeah
Next clip I think
He finally reaches
The end of his rope
Got to find out what the latest and greatest information
Far as the official for a walk over here
Believe we do know at this point
Is that
Before she was pulled away to get the latest information I did learn that the person that they do have in custody
Sure if that person is actually a shooter
Texas realize that all of the people that are being interviewed or black
I think that there is a
I get a strong sense
That he pivots the narratives
The people that are being
Interview
Well it could be a false
You cannot care about it and push this to the side
Cuz he doesn't talk about it anymore for the rest of the show he goes to overdrive does an extra half-hour he doesn't go back
Back to the feed
On the 23rd of January which doesn't talk about the shooting anymore
Eagerness to be like
The next
And I'm going to be on the ground
Getting the information that others will
To make the super
Popular profitable
Videos
And it's not that and as it goes along he realizes
Suck it
And he just found it's disgraceful I think it's
If you conceived
What's
Interested
You know it's
Nothing
And this is one of the times we're here
The screeching brakes
Extendo crash
Overdrive here on the 22nd
Eclipse
But you're back Kaiser
Glenn Beck is trying to buy a bunch of property and create a libertarian
Disneyland in the middle of Texas
In the middle of a conversation Alex conveniently remember
He had with a real-estate
What is Newtown
It's ludicrous Alex's is making shut off
Let's catch up with beckville how's that going
I wanted to include clips of this but it's so long
Just decided to tell you about it
It's absurd and
Max Keiser swinging for the fences.
Yeah he goes he goes pretty hard on it
Me to tell you about it for about 45 seconds
Or so
The 23rd
We get into
Something that I've been waiting for for
For quite a while
And that is for Alex to get specific
About why he thinks Aurora was
A psychiatrist
National Security
Who I am
So
I've been waiting for a while like I said for Alex to bring up
Specific complaints about the Aurora shooting over the course of a bunch of episodes
That's unsatisfying for me to respond
Conspiracy theories are
Details because
Tire 128-page psychiatric
I'm so much more about this case
I was just reaching for Alex Pappas dumb head above the ground so I could
Ahead
I've seen people remember on the night of July 20th
2012 James Knight Dark Knight Rises
Theater in Aurora Colorado
He preceded set off tear gas
Something similar to tear gas before opening fire ultimately killing 12 people and injuring 70 others
After that he exited the theater and waited for the police to come and arrest as you told the authorities
Are you done some calculations and realized he wouldn't survive the attack
He absolutely committed this horrific Act of terrorism
And in the next however long distance
I will deconstruct
And approve each one of Alex's reason
Thanks for believing this is a false flag
Or as he calls it cartoonishly
Free fake
Do you in advance
Do you have the same last name
Call Jessica
He's not going to like this
Freezing I probably wouldn't be thrilled
Baby that one I'm fine with
Chicago
Doesn't matter if it's a Murder Castle or not you got a rep
Yeah I was going to say something about his creativity
Somali pirates
About the DARPA funding
Control stuff
Better Alex bring
I'm just going to go in order of the complaints
He brought up in
What's a good student
High School ended with a GPA of 3.77
Graduated
82nd in the class
You want to do is undergrad at UC Riverside initially setting out to get a Bachelor of Arts
Sendero sign
Bachelor of Science
Still in neuroscience
A few years in college
Career
Graduated college with a GPA of 3.949
Good student
Psychological evaluation that was done to try and determine whether he was compass
Trial GRE scores but they're literally impossible to be accurate as their numbers way higher than the
GRE test scoring range
There must have been a mistyping
I found said that he was in the 98th percentile for the
Of the GRE and 94th
Percentile for the quantitative score
Dinosaurs that put you well on your way towards scholarship
He's eventually at the most guide
But some of the most top-tier schools
Particularly ones with very specific requirements
My dad is involved in the process of grad school application
For the religious studies Department UT Austin
No smoke at him in the past about the process
It's very complicated
It's put the concrete terms
Go to school doesn't want to offer one of their limited slots in their grad program
Just somebody that they don't feel will succeed
It could be that they feel like the student would do better in a different program
They're aware of the different programs in different
Angry better ex-wife
Jersey school
So that that's one possibility
Could be as simple as the student
Isn't it good
Say 6 other people that are a better fit apply than you
You may still not get into the program that you apply for
And this is what appears to have happened with home
Neuroscience schools in the country but was rejected by all of them
These were the elite program
So you probably against ahead just as good a test scores
Probably better X
Extracurricular records and almost certainly better interview
Because he was
Socially
Weird course
Tell most people would describe him
Sure
After getting rejected from the school his parents reported it home sell into a depression
Where you sleep most of the day and watch television
They encouraged him to apply to schools that had a better shot of getting
What are the schools you apply to is the University of Iowa
Is there admission
Process office
Gives a glimpse
Into how the application
The person interviewing him noted that Holmes record was a quote slam dunk
But the interview that he gave
Because Brazil
Disconnected in a loop
With a global lack of
A sack
Administrator went on to tell the admissions
At least five schools and was
Accepted 22
Ultimately choosing University of Colorado at Denver over the University of illinois-urbana
His first year they're his performance was not up to what the high school and undergrad
A careers
Atwood Ave
Let It Go
It is lab rotation
He was making me uncomfortable with his social awkwardness
His habit of quote uncomfortable
About as far as I could get
Details of that but you got it was too
I've met that guy
He entered the program in June 2011
Any year later he had to undergo his preliminary or Alexa
And on June 7th
12 that was when they were
Take place
The results
We're not good
Pass
The preliminary oral exam
Professors report that James was unable to
A2g
In a timely manner
Organized matter in his answer
They stated that they were concerned that he might not have more than a superficial knowledge of the material
Or that he simply knew the words
To use without understanding the concept
They stated that he performed poorly uniformly
Not just in one particular portion or topic
He felt these exams book Rascals don't kick out student slightly
They told him that he could take a different
The program
Alex believes that he received
Starbucks
The reason for this theory is that Holmes was the recipient of a grant awarded by the national
Idiom out of 26,000.
Grant work
Every year there about 6
New Neuroscience grad student
Sweater the program
I'm at University
Colorado.
From the NIH is given to the school
Another director of the neuroscience
Diego Restrepo along with a group of faculty member
First decide what to do
Didn't choose Jamestown
And they probably actually had no idea
Even was
Each year three of the six new grad student
Get this grant
At 3 second-year students get it as well
50%
Through the school
Especially considering
You look like a super promise
You have to understand that element
He was overqualified on paper for a school like University
Colorado Denver
But unable to pass the more nebulous aspect of the application
Process for a
Your school
This isn't meant to insult people
Colorado Denver
Or anybody involved with the school
But they were probably super excited to have a student like him in their program
Total
I also that Grant is
DARPA funding was involved
At homes
He had mind control worker he was doing b*******
It doesn't take into account
Schools work or any of the facts of the case really
From there the assertions get even Wilder
Article on Infowars about
These connections are super
The first is that Holmes was a researcher
The Salk Institute
San Diego
Instituted work
Starfall
Peak Soldier performance
What's program
Hubble
There there
This is going to be so cute
I'm not take the long road around but a little bit
Is Grandma
Sorry
First problem with his.
Soldier perform
What's program
Scary that program wasn't about mind control or any
Creating cool new things gloves as well as warm
A soldier's hands
Save-A-Lot innovative ways for like wounded soldiers lost limbs being able to
Them have mobility and arm you again
All over the god
That doesn't mean anything definitive
All you have here's a super flimsy connection
That you could use the vents
Majestic relieved that there's way more going on here than you know mean you-4
2015 Janelle
The Salk Institute
The same place that you know
To pursue her Research into quote bolstering a person's microbiomes overcoming infection
Anything suspicious there
That's what they would want you to do they were home from getting all messed up
Super public
And open that every year
The form of their young
Sia War
Junior research
Who became more interesting as maybe James Holmes a gotten one of those
Or they were disproportionately
To the schools that he was at
So conspiracy theories
Conveniently just
Ignore that part with DARPA splashes
Research money all over the
Making it super
Them
Through webs of
Exaggerated which is all that's going on
What
80% of Grants can be six degrees of separation
So I don't know what
Globalist would choose to
Controlled
Eclipse
Both
So
So it's sort of Mystery Science Theater with like Joel.
I meant Joe Liz doctor Forrester as well
A very ask
To have it all
The conspiracy at least
This piece of it was largely the result of quote-unquote reporting or speculating
Infowars employee
New if you recall is the guy who are making
Photo with our call Larry Nichols
As you can see again
Super interest
Alex has deep connect
And who has it
Relapsed for Infowars
This point is coming up with the b*******
Crazy Theory propagating
The pattern
Incredibly consist
Work
Alex Presley
Embedded
No problem
Anytime we medicine comes up a responsibility to remind people that it was p.m.
Said that Hillary Clinton got murdered in a piece of paper
Makes no sense
Navigate to the claim of the top Air Force psychiatrist
Working over whole operation
Antonio woodworking
With home
I know
Less interested than the Air Force
So one of the things that's important to point out your evaluation
Uniforms at determine if you would say nothing
The Colorado mental health in
Conducted interviews with 12 mental health clinician
Checklist before and after
During the relevant period between March 21st and June 11th 2012
Home to seeing a therapist
Through the University of Colorado student health
This therapist was dr.lin
Fenton
Her name was made public very early in the investigation
Because before carrying out the shooting HomeSense
The Notebook that I was lying
Think it's a workbook
They worked on together
He sent her package
They can take that notebook
And because
Let her name got released
Possibly unintentionally
When reports came out about the
Yeah
Okay
It is evaluation
Explain the fear of consequences for his actions
Well working with doctor
When asked about it he says that he didn't tell Fenton about it because he knew that she would lock him up
And quote I would not be able to kill
Not be able to get out of this depression
My worth
More here in a little bit
Probably a good idea
Yeah
It doesn't matter if you told her
Because she got the
It is trial
Testified that there last
He left early
She was so concerned at home
The public in the months before the Aurora theater shooting
That you contacted
Mother
Violation of healthcare private
She breached confidentiality but she decided
Further
Specific enough in their sessions
For him to reach the legal criteria for Hospital
Psychological evaluation
Fenton specifically
So she couldn't hospitalized
He said he couldn't tell her that he was buying weapon
Any details with
The specific plan
Or that he wanted to be locked up
Because if you did
She would hospitalize him
I bet he couldn't carry out his plan which he thought would cure
Depression
There are plenty of people who have questions about whether or not
She did enough
Therapist who broke protocol
To try and stop this guy from hurting
Definitely not someone who is his mom
Control Handler
Sure sounds like she was trying to save
Probably more than yours but obviously more than you're supposed to
Like she went
Beyond words
Consider I guess I guess okay
The Conspiracy Theory hinges about her
Mind control doctor from the Air Force
I do hinges on one sentence
X41 CNN article about
She worked as a physician in private practice in Denver
From 1994 to 2000
Physical Medicine for the u.s. Air Force in
San Antonio Texas in the early 90s
According to her resume
That was a
From their speculation ran rampant
Conspiracy chef resume said that she was the
The chief of Physical Medicine
Psychiatrist
For the u.s. Air Force
Antonio from 90
Which is absolutely no proof of anything
Other than that she's a doctor and she had a job
Nowhere does anyone prove that
Physical Medicine or mind control
Nowhere does anyone establish that staff psychiatrist
This is just complete assumption and embellished
These people are carrying off
Cross reference
Though with all the other Air Force had
Physical Medicine
Then we can
Conclude of course
Every mass shooting
Has been in Bradley
Has been traced back to
Air Force
Maybe maybe
Prescribing herself and a few other people.
She knew drugs
Sure
She's not supposed to do that
Closer examination of what she actually makes me infraction look super minor
Although she was reprimanded in 2005 the incident happened
Between 1997 and 1999
And they were a Claritin and Ambien for her husband
Who cares
It's crazy
She got three tabs of Xanax
Herself not to take while her mother was in the process of dying
4 Xanax is for a friend who is afraid of
I don't care about any of
Nope not at all 0
Kind of Miss prescribing that I would call a moral
Between
Miss prescribing and then abusing
Stop music
I'm not a part of the medical ethics board
And it's not
Getting tons of Vicodin spell on the street
Stealing is bad but if you're starving and you stole a loaf of bread over there at 6 months
Either way she was reprimanded for it and I have to take class on property
That's the fitting punishment for what you did
I don't see
Problem
Claritin but it was enough to make a conspiracy
All of a sudden
She turned into an unethical
People started to write blog posts that started with the word
A lot of people are asking
One has to wonder is it possible that
Thrown against the wall
She got her undergrad from UC Davis
Apparently some people believe that they have a monkey called
Control
Force bases
She did 40
Years prior
So she must have to do the same
MKUltra work
These are some of them born on insane. They get thrown around
Playing or are tell you about
So there's literally zero evidence that dr. Fenton
Is anything other than a school psychiatrist
Who also worked at an Air Force Base 13
Beatrice Prior
There's no evidence that she was a quote top Air Force psychiatrist
Psychologist
Especially considering that you only work for them
3 gears and Lackland Air Force Base
Isn't even close to being the biggest
That was damaged
That was that was that quote is what
Talking about
Being a top Air Force psychologist Overholt
San Antonio
True he's just taking tiny details of her life and exaggerating them into what
To help him castration
I know where the seven million episodes but somehow they're still a part of me that is like
Alex
You're cheating this is not
To make it worse
Exactly what you're saying
Much of the primary source in for the
She's about Lynn Fenton traced directly back to
Who again is a very frequent contributor to our relationship with
The fourth our host of Alex's show many of the blog the painter is an unethical therapist
Speculate about her being up to no good with home link back to articles on Rappaport blog
No more as well as articles with his byline on Infowars
Again we can see this
Alex's Associates
Lindsay bolshit
He spreads it presented as well research
So let's talk about this notebook
Workbook
Alright so we're working together
What's your favorite
They were they awful
This is a different notebook
More upset I would say I guarantee I've looked through the notebook
Morissette
Forsythe National
Security and they don't want to release that up
So
May 2012 homes began planning issue
What do you hope to do
It's important to note very specifically that he wasn't working on this with any Mental Health
Curricular activities
On Infowars anonymously written article claims without proof that the notebook quote is a notch
We arrange a backstory on home
It portrayed him as a murderess
Psychopath
Keep it expressing his desire to kill since March
Miss Bee
As much in a group
He said he wanted to kill people
To which she replies that it's too much effort and he just end up in jail
Holmes replies quote that's why you kill many
In these g chat logs as well as his notebook home
Expressed ideas
It's basically a twisted version of believing that an hour of skilled Labour is intrinsically more valuable than an hour ago
And his consent
The human capital of a lice
Priceless
So quote you take away life and your human capital is
Is Limitless
You seem to believe that his wife was low on human capital and thereby killing a large number of people
He would get the capital that he was missing
Yes
You felt that raising
Is worth in this way
Human capital level
Was the only way that he could read himself
This terrible depression
Energy chat sessions
Energy chat sessions he expresses that he's not all Eva
And that killing people is
He claims that he found a good path that you would rather try
It is described
In the interviews
Subsequently with him
Is the plan that he had was quote Living a good life
Budget
Okay
Cuz he did go for
Yeah
Holmes Road
Specifically because he knew it wouldn't arrive until after the shooting
He sent it hours
Before he would go off to do
So he wanted to torture
He doesn't
Know why
Mental evaluation
Santa tour
And whether he saw her response would be
And he seemed unable to
Say why he did it
Sea-Monkey want
Torture her
Seems like it was just
I've been working with her
Almost Yelp from reading it like his response was
She might want to know
But yeah
Know if that was his motive
Think about it it didn't seem like it was a
If you were writing it up as some kind of unrequited
Maybe if you're making another version of the notebook notebook
Disturbed thoughts
Send descriptions what he was going through in the months leading up to the shooting
He discusses deceiving doctor Fenton
How is playing with the coke building
Sense of rapport
Truthfully
Incriminating question
So he was intentionally withholding information for a drummer in order to be able to follow through with
The plant
Throughout the notebook homes presented himself as having a lifelong struggle about the
The question of the meaning of life
As well as the meaning
It's a question you can't solve
And it seems to give him
The solution he arrives at
Is that quote if you destroy all life then there is no question
So you believe that
Which is really Brandy
Who discusses having these grandiose thoughts
Since the age of 10
Imagine
Do something
Everyone in the world
Yeah
Bipolar
I've had delusions of grandeur groups
Like it's like a
Disconcerting number of times where I'm surprised
I'm still allowed
So it is
Totally understand
How that can
Twisted Warp
In ways that you
Like
It's impossible to really kind of
Explain to somebody who's never
Experience that none of this is to say that what he did was open.
Provide an explanation
Is is not to minimize his actions are excused
No
Explain
Conspiracy that Alex's picture
This is something
This notebook
Created on his own
Who knows maybe it helped him
Feel like he was doing something
From the fact that you was going
2 KB
Intellectualize
Work through these issues
And it had nothing to do with Doctor Fenton
You sent it to her
Before you at did the crime
Knowing that it would arrive later
Yeah very clear from the available information
Not as
By empathizer or this is the explanation
That's a terrifying reality is
Minimize it there's so many other factors but like
There but for the grace of God go I that kind of situation
You know it's a it's a nightmarish thing to
So
Buck
Multiple shooters
There's always reports of multiple shooters
That's not enough evidence
Conspiracy everything that's ever happened probably
I've looked the conspiracies about the idea of multiple Shooters being involved in the shooting
It's all pretty standard stuff about police dispatcher saying maybe multiple shooters
And Witnesses reporting
Someone said someone was shooting in the lobby
So although all that sort of stuff is
Exactly what you see at every situation
There is only one shooter with so little
So the question is jailhouse confession
If not knowing who he is and he
He's drugged up
Psychological evaluation
To alter his appearance
That's for the shooting
Decided
The part of himself
He bought black contact lenses
Shooting quote as a way to differentiate myself from my normal self
Jesus's Red Dragon
He said that you liked the look because it looked like he was
In the initial police report
The first officers made contact with him pointed out that his eyes were very dilated
But this was before they knew that he had black contacts
This is where the misconceptions come from Dorothy was whacked out on drugs
Complete explanation explanation
So you taking one Vicodin an hour prior to going to the theater just in case he got injured while doing the shooting but other than that
Completely clean
Of alcohol
Street drugs
So he wasn't medications but by that time
Possibility
He rejected the idea
DIY was working with doctor
Because
Failed out of school
His insurance
The program wouldn't cover
Into the Joker
Again it was an attempt to differentiate who he was going to be from the part of himself
Betty felt was good
Disappearance because I would not my normal
Good that's another part of it is that like
Text because my insurance
Might be what
Eve used as a
Particular
Isn't it simply because
Look it's good teachable moments
So that was about protecting the part of himself that he thought was
Good all these changes of his
Alter his physical appearance
Himself anymore and that quote the other me did everything
Therefore it is pretty clear that though this is psychologically relevant it doesn't present with the same symptoms
Disassociation
Turn off
Compartmentalize
Largely willful
Through all of it
After you put in custody Homestuck a predictable turn for the worse
The ideas about being able to erase
Does human capital and free himself from his depression by killing
Hadn't worked
He was still depressed
He descended into a full-on psychotic break
Requiring staff to restrain him for his own safety
He was banging his head on walls and apparently trying to fall from his bed
In a manner so as to fall on his head
Dr. Fraser reported that he
You did not know where he was
And that is think it was completely disorganized
And talked a lot about being a quote shadow box
And the need to hide from Shadows
But this is absurd
He was put on Risperidone
And responded very well
He became able to organize his thoughts enough to understand
Is auditory and visual hallucinations
Subsided as well
They also found that he was in a
Starvation delirium
Due to not eating cuz you was paranoid about the food provided at the hospital
Improve dramatically
During that time he was also put on the right medication
He was before
S***
Doctors would have heard him saying
The stories about the things
Imprison all come from
What's the time
Steve Unruh
Claimed it while they were both
Sal's here 24-hour talk with talked about committing suicide
Evil therapist
What we do know for sure is that Unruh was at the Arapahoe Sheriff's Detention
Facility
The hours before the shooting
Haven't been arrested
Dragon set
Although
Prisoners are
Communicate through gaps in cell door
Multiple officers at the Sheriff's Department
And said the communication
Like Unruh is depriving is
Impossible
Due to the layout of the whole thing
So
That's one
Problem with historic perhaps
Plane on the idea that we have for movies of the jails being bars
And you can
Still like
Even if it's a solid wall
Between
Through the bars
A big person
Gave him and told him to call
That number goes to a bereavement counselor
North Devon
He claims that Holmes tried to send a letter in prison but that it was intercepted but no official record of an interception
Our letter x
Shark movie
Given the unlikely nature of their communication be possible
I see this with a little bit of skepticism
Probably one important thing to consider is that true just been released
From 6 years in prison
Admitted been re-arrested
Was looking to
From an article in Westworld
Quotes
He's going public with us
Account of the encounter with the Arapahoe County District
Attorney's office in a story
He's currently facing habitual criminal charges and it helped
Mental health treatment
Rather than a 12-year prison
Although investigator
The DEA hasn't been working with
He sighs
Occam's razor
And it unroe was spending it to cut DeLand somehow turn
A coincidence that he was in the holding at the
Appositive
The DEA didn't believe his stories
To the public
See if you can find any
It's also probably worth noting that in 2014 Steve on roof self-published book called the truth
Massacre at Cinema 16
And here is the description of that
Addiction relapse
And also in a mass murderers life
Just hours after the man kills 12 people and injured 70
The killer wants to
Commit suicide and the author is used as a power
Dupree with the killer convinced him to repent
I talked him out of his Suicidal Thoughts
I think all this is pretty simple pretty simple explanation
That is true is not a good source of
Information and we should not believe
About the jailhouse confession
It seems kind of
Likee
Inopportune
Oh man
Is it any good did you read I didn't cuz it's I couldn't find a PDF of it or anything but
And a lot of
Indications that
The people who published it the house that published is on a lot of people
A lot of warning
Gotcha
Big things about don't
Work with
It may not be one of the more credible publishers
Of books
Which
Surprise
It's one of those games where he wound up paying a lot
Did not he did not recoup
Future future
This is
A complete rundown of all of the conspiracies
Is the people spin about the Aurora shooting
But
There's no way that you possibly
Could I do what I want specific claims position
Parachuting with cartoonist
And obviously a false flag
None of them stand up
The scrutiny even in the least
And easily cast aside but as
Completely manufactured or misrepresented B
Information
Speaking of predetermined conclusion
Namely that the shoe
Is evidence that the shooting is
Cartoonishly fake is
Cartoonish Lee awful
At least series I can trace back
Specifically to Infowars contributors as either being the root of
The theory or being the largest propagators
Once they got robbed
Seems important ultimately what's going on here is Alex's aggressively arguing with the Aurora shooting
Was fake to justify his position
Claims about Aurora you can clearly see that there's
No-spa
Here for a Sandy Hook
And in fact
Behavior look worse
Very stupid
Do we ever referee somewhere to be like not know you're cheating Jordan unfortunately you've just described what
What we are becoming
NBA referees
So let's move on to the next clip where Alex has
She is going to win
Oh no
Contacted
On the
Another
Ford.com
Oh no
Skateboard company at least it's big enough that I ate. Skateboarder
It's real f*****-up
That's f***** up they released decks in collaboration with
Infowars
January 23rd
But it also does speak to something that I've learned from doing a lot of skaters over the course of my life
And some of them are pretty clever but they're not the best
General
Is that the time Alien Workshop was owned by Rob Dyrdek
Star of the delightful TV shows Robin big and Rob Dyrdek's Fantasy Factory
Really sad for me to realize that he put out an Infowars deck
Between the 5th and 6th
Seasons of fantasy factory
Rob
Makes me look a little differently enjoy those shows
Show Android Robin big quite a bit
And most the responses
Confined or not positive
Ranging from a red, that just says pluck out
To a message board threat accusing Alien Workshop of being a state
Company their boards and clothes
Alright are they also accused of selling out for working
Which is pretty funny to imagine the cobra
The point of which someone would accuse our two
The radar
This is nothing
Neither of them. They wanted out of people attacking Alien Workshop and Alex
Perfect synthesis of the bad parts of your heart.
Sorry Rob I'm out
Alright
All right I told you earlier
I told you earlier
We were going to meet
A real crazy
A real bad purse
Real monster
Yeah really excited about the opportunity to talk about the Aurora shooting
Because Alex brings it up all the time
Could be safe
To do that
Probably like
20 minutes half an hour of this episode
I'm sorry it's not for anybody but it's essential that we cover that as we go through
It's a big piece of the ship
Fight
Thought that was going to be
Okay
And then crazy
Alright
I was like
More interesting, Moto Moto
Asia
I'm going to just go ahead and play this clip and then I'll explain why this is super exciting
FM 92.1
Incredible
Long time I've heard Alex make
The following are key
Which is what he's talking about
Jim Garrow
Talk about
Obama
Bloodthirsty Patriot haters
The highest offices of the military the police
In order to achieve this goal these put it a litmus test in for advance
Central Canada
Sometimes this couch days shooting people
Dinosaur wouldn't go along with martial law
Alex wants to push
The point is the same
Obama selectively promoting Patriot haters so they can have a top-down control
Over Law Enforcement which will then press Alex and his friends
I've literally never once thought to look at it
That's because it sounds like complete
And just dumped paranoid
But one of the other reasons I never looked into it and I never wanted to dig into it
Was it Alex never gives a citation
3999 4420
You never talk about where you got this information from
So I'm happy to look into all sorts of obviously not true things
Better use of my
My time not much better
Slightly.
Silver platter Alex tells me that he got this information from
Even makes it seem a little bit too
Clear that clip that goes claims are all he has.
And he's taking his word for it because he thinks Garrow is credible
Who is
If the debate is based on Cairo
Darrow's credibility
I can look into
And then it says
Welcome to Infowars
You're not a trustworthy so
I don't care
Lizzo flute
Here are some of the completely unfounded claims
But he has made over the
He was a radio show where he claimed that he knew Breitbart
Hastings were all killed
Under direct orders by Barack Obama
Because they leave the key wasn't actually in America
President
Did Tom Clancy
Specifically know this
Sources man you think he does write a book
I don't because he doesn't like
4 books
On the Tea Party podcast
He claimed that Obama was in touch with
Or some group that would
It's kind of Uncle
Either way Obama was planning to unveil the contact with these aliens
Which is dangerously close to the plot of childhood
On November and November 2013 you went on another right-wing show and alleged that Obama and George Soros working fire
American
Newk's on Tuesdays
Obama Soros and Valerie June
Quantitative easing
Ninety percent of the population
So he goes on
To argue that Obama almost carried out this plan
But he was stopped at the last minute military map
Misfits
He said that Obama and Soros
There's literally no evidence that any of this ever happened in Nuuk
For his part in this imaginary place
Okay
I don't think that's how we
Seems dangerous
He claimed it Obama tried
The Killing by sabotaging
God protect
More likely decided to
Publix
He's claimed
And is also accused Obama of being a secret
Operative along with Saudi Arabia
Anybody else
Probably
He's not working with
Against being serious
They are working against the United States Obama
By definition work with that
I suppose
It was part of his original.
He began claiming that he was a former CIA officer
Overtime
Is the Dutchman 2013 by Obama and Valerie Jarrett
Oh great was this before or after they tried to bother
A few problems this story
MCI at 8
You also have to have a bachelor's degree
Reply
It's not unheard of to have a bachelor's at the age of 18
Super unlikely
Especially if
Another one
Another requirement is that you have to have experience in a relevant field
Like being in the military or law enforcement
My which I don't Euro story
Static required
Both of you have to be a citizen of the US
CIA
I should point out
His bio is written by an alternate route
Alright alright
He was born in
And it lived most of his life in Canada
30s
Yazbek Canadian
Aboot
Sort of vowel pronunciation
Canada
Furlong.
Oh boy
He has a profile on IMD
Bbsi mentioned because in 2050
Started
Appearing in nothing you've ever heard of
Girl did two episodes of a show called Shadowland
Performance
Fly fishing
He called himself doctor Jim Garrow because
Doctorate degree from North Carolina College of theology
It's cool
Any case anyone wants to go back and look through the records and
Pull up his coursework
Don't worry about it because
Degree of Honor
So he didn't actually even
A place where you could probably buy an honorary non-accredited
Geology in North Carolina
Like many weirdos Alex
Girl claims for a Nobel Prize
Lost
Specifically to Obama
That's only further igniting the Rivalry
Now I will say this
I too agree that Obama did not deserve that
Peace Prize
I'm also going to say that
Hero does not deserve it either or situation
United States
He will say
Like Obama
Personal grudges
He's a user by the name of Jim Garrow also
The claim of his lost Lowdown nomination
In 2001 Garrow tried to run a flight school at the Region of Waterloo International Airport in Canada
He got a little bit of trouble in transit
Leading to a $2,850
After quote
Intentionally
Steve instructors
2850 dollars is beat
Alma School
Alright open today that I don't know if I
Jim garrels very crowded
Will stores
Based on all this other b*******
A former eighteen-year-old
You're going to you're going to Texas
All other available sources over this man
Well maybe I'm being a little bit
Too quick to judge
Because there's other things
Is the Jim Garrow.
Almost
No one of these
Children from China
So
He's a hero
Also
That's Alex's portraying David adoption
What
Save them from being eliminated
Yes it's sticking a little
Alex
Next BART
Source from a grape
Macro lens
Guelph Mercury
Investigative
On
Jim Garrow
Might blow your mind
Really don't think so
Alex
Describe 45,000
It's one of the reasons
This organization called
Pagoda
Raclaims to alternatively the number varies
Sometimes it's 34,000
Children
Abandoned or killed them
One child policy
Question
Right it's called pink pagoda
To your question Chinese
Don't worry about it
Okay
Really feel like as a
If he's really doing this
Good on him
However some Blu-ray some questions about whether or not Garrow is just me
Making all this stuff
Who adopted
Three children from China
Facilitator for people who want to adopt children
From China
Them to learn more
Jim Garrow a lot about the program
Communicated areas in China where he works
I've made contact with orphanages in those areas and has been unable to substantiate
Anything you said
Surprise
Carol reply
International
Because
He's doing this s*** without the proper Authority on a very real and Technical level
The flip
Children out of China has quote in the buying and selling of babies
Nobody knows who you are
What
Properly registered as a charitable organization
Not supposed to take in philanthropic donations
But that doesn't stop him from
Listening donations
He's claimed to pick Pagoda his
Encourage
Dollars in Spanish
Pictures over the
And that the money came from running an importing
Particularly of Tim Horton's Coffee
Alexandra cycle
Quotes girl has no affiliation with the company
He's definitely not authorized and not licensed
To sell our products
So I guess we can add smuggling to his resume
30 adopted Chinese children
Hey come on board with Pagoda as their legal advice
Weather report
Never been involved
Pink Bogota and I have no idea
Malaysian I'm really mad at this guy
That's a little bit of an understatement
Jim Carroll going to write a book about his work with Agoda
One of the people who wrote
For him included in the book
It's part of the book
What is endorsement
One is none other than our old friend
Cuz I put the helfrich fingers at everybody
This one interesting
Division published Gyros book
It is
I read a review this book that I can only
Only describe
There was posted on the research China vlog
Run by helping
The stories of the
So as to help them create a folder
Themselves as they grow up
The book is described as a
Stereotypes about Chinese culture which
Quotes
He was watching a predictable movie
Darrow's view of China
Describe this quote
Simplify
Familiar
The book is devoid of any
Discussion of the specifics of how adoption
It seems like that's not a stylistic choice
It appears that Garrow does not even know the forms that are required to complete the process of bring the child into the country
You want some candy
It's only made worse by four
Protracted action
The book where where Gyros Chinese intelligence operative friend who he calls Yoda
Commits a bunch of murders to protect Garrow and his mission to save children
The whole thing
Is ridiculous now I want to read this book
Because
Tom Clancy
There's a really good girls never been arrested for child trafficking
Operate
Because you just make me
As we like
About us laughing about this
Yeah I think he's just lying about all day
That doesn't there's there's not a
There's not a
Goodchild
Journalist who tried to contact any of the school's orphanages and claims associate
Unable to find any proof
And end up just dialing phone numbers that lead
Daryl did get arrest
A light 2014 us
We all assumed we were getting to an arrest record
Could sooner or later
In late 2014 was arrested in quote
Is charges of unauthorized possession of a firearm possession of a firearm possession of
Storage of a firearm
As is the case with everyone who Alex hangs out with Gary
Immediately claimed you would set up
Is probably Obama Bhai
I can't find out
Nation about the outcome
Severe
And afterwards he'd spill all over right-wing media
So this is
Anybody
About
Other culture
Would probably look at him be like
What the f***
Because if he doesn't do any
It's work
Then
Because it's illegal you're not actually
To get a child
Super busy
If someone comes to you and says you took my child you know that you didn't
Yeah it's kind of a really great skin
They tried to scam the scammer
$40,000
I don't I don't know
Like a pretty good
I mean it's a terrible
If you're someone like
Kim
It seems pretty women
Yeah if you are of great
Humanitarianism
Get a lot of people
I think a lot of people are
He seems
I can story is full of holes
His careers
Full of bulls
Fraud
Also I didn't even get into
This stuff
He is like an educator
In his backstory
Mercury
Article in the number of incidents
Running the school or the teacher to school and then people in the area
They remember him leaving
Seems like there's
Kind of vibe go Motown
Problem
He starts
Inflamed feel children
Prequel
Show for every episode of kung fu there's a prequel episode
F****** s*** out
He's Wild Oats
In 29
Alex is so upset
Child traffic
June 23rd
He has
He runs a child trafficking
YouTube
You got to give it up
A very similar thing for me
Anyway look can have two edges
On one Edge is child trafficking
For good
It doesn't matter if you can't
Falsify a births
Certificate for one of these stolen Chinese
Needs children
So
Donkey
The kids out of China it's awesome
Interested
Is this
Play magaro is made
Okay and
Describe
Litmus test
Information
And keep in mind
Describing
His
Before yesterday in the morning
From this officer of former officer he's retired
But that he was quite upset that said one of the people eating in the military
Was being squeezed out that he was forced to resign his Commission
And it was because
A question was asked of him
Now I called it Alyssa
See what it is
Where the military was called upon to go
And confirm
People who were armed
American citizens who would not relinquish
In spite of the Second Amendment right to hold arm
Atwood you
Fire on American citizens
Related to me that the officer was total video
He would be asked
Question
And he said that his answer was no I would not fire on America
That is amazing
The hero
In the military
Situation here
He's trying to imply
It's most important story
Is related
Ruag a metallic
Telling you the story that I heard from a former officer
From a guy he encouraged
To join the military
Gato it's
It's real thin
So far
Get into it because
The household name
And he will not
Becoming popcorn popper
This man is a legend yes you would know his name every American with no
And no he will not be coming
He thought that the best thing he could do is
I was honored that he called me
But you didn't call you
General Mad Dog Mattis
A command
What if Obama tried to get mad
Civilians
And he being a Mad Dog
You said no sir
Was drummed out of the service
Case closed
The problem is
Jim Mattis announced his resignation in April
Neither Obama told Madison needed to shoot on civilians
Known Obama said okay
Keep you around for 11 months while we try to find a replacement
Meanwhile Battleship serving the president
You do is try to
Kill paper
Or
4 Mattis resign
And then Obama
I'm not sure exactly
Removing mobile.
Mic drop
This is the only high-profile military resignation around
Comply
Is the person who stalked
He knows better than to be
Pacific
Madison
Nation was because he
See eye-to-eye on Madison
Also matters join the Marines the 19
Madison
The oldest ship
Madden 16
Retired
Hey wife
This is just another fraud being carried out by this frog guy
It's right
But he's not going
So Alex knows
It's Boykin
Sheboygan
Which is stupid
Because retirement
Even took office
So we wouldn't
Also in 2013
Was employed at
Executive Vice President of the family research
F****** God
Information
Real piece of s***
Unfortunately we don't have time to get into him today but I'm sure he'll show up as a gas
Alex
ProSource
Into some sort of us
Yeah
This interview goes
Alex
Love's
I don't think the two of them has ever spoken before and they are fast friends
Mostly because
Garrow is reinforcing
Sing all the things that Alex
Yeah that's about
He does the steeper
Move
Really over flattering
I need to talk to you today
You know
You are right on about all this
Hitler Youth
Ready
Replace these old generals
Okay
Excited
This guy is on the same
The right answer to this
They got a whole Army of young kids who don't know any better
Ready-to-move-in
And keep in mind
Who are the people who get away with
In the despotic times who were the ones that they rely on Indiana
Exactly where here's the Hitler Youth
Resurrected
Now
Under this name of Obamacare that's
If you think it's William Boyd
Amanda
Excitement
It was not.
Hello tushy
No more frequently
And maybe go get coffee
New friendship developed that part is me
So you didn't actually say that
Friendship is
Solidified
And he leave
And then Alex goes into overdrive
Has Melissa Melton
I'm sorry
Eclipse it is but it does
Comes in as a guest
It's absurd
Spectate
Kind of unsatisfied
Just saying
How much control
Over and over
Aunt
Thoughts keep bringing up
Alex
Even if I had a thousand guns and I was in the woods
Fortified position
If those drones
Oh, the military is going to be able to
Really going to make that much of a difference
I don't
I thought like
When Alex said where can I be on parking garage and it's going to be alright have a comment
This is
It's ultimately not that crazy
Never boring interview
Reject right this is more complicated
And then finding points
Agreement and I drank
Find Alex that
What do you believe
It's stupid
You can go find it on YouTube if you want to listen to that interview
I just didn't think there was much
Worthwhile there
Merrilee Rush
Appearing on the showing
Trying to appeal to Alex on a
Not yelling at each other level
That doesn't make for good clips
Check that out if you
Alex Goes to Overdrive
Yes Melissa Melton
Who is one of his employees
Who has
XVideos
Yeah well
Yeah because
In college
+ 5
And they're trying
To argue
Do that
Violent crime
Flooring
But there's a causal connection
Bring up with Jen
There are other factors.
Consider that might be
Attributable it's not necessarily
That gun ownership
Pause that
Probably refutation to your argument
Concentrate
Is not falling
That's compared to
Concealed carry
Head come out of
Alex's just taking
Some raw data from the app
And create
Conclusion
Which people on the right never twist
Statistics in order to make a bulge
Also talking about UK
Since they took
But
Call Brittany
Or higher
I believe Australia South Africa here
Britain
The violent crime compared to Northern Ireland
How do you say
Scotland
United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland
South Africa in the United States
North America part of the UK of Great Britain
The United States
Canada
South Africa and New Zealand
Could be a slip
You don't think so
And also of course it is
It's London
I don't think that's what you
Britain is the violent crime capital of
You
That could be
Except that as a possibility
Specious
Poorly set
Melissa
Talkingshit on Joe Biden
Which is
I guess whatever
Auto Care
I'm not going back to bed for Joe Biden
Disgraceful
Ambrose
The Press
Yeah
He talked about how these are kids that were just killed
They were riddled with bullet
And so Alex
Playing
Supercut of
Him saying riddled with bullet
What's aha
What about the bullets
God
But
He doesn't weird Biden
Feed the trolls
You know I got to do in these wagons
Trolls cover it
Can you really get
Matter
About
Supposed trolls
And he wants
This clip is our
Gun statistics
If you ever want
Is trolls
I'll be damned to hell
It's weird
Fillmore
I think part of it is probably just muscle
Daddy started down that road
Field madder than you probably
Personal
She was kind of non-committal
Welsh
Aggressively so
Must you go to how many more
Frozen lake in the knights
Absolute
We come to the end of this stretch
Because
That I expected are coming
Pass
The prediction that after Alex
Had
Paul Joseph Watson work correctly
And they recognized
Value
Sandy Hook conspiracy
More aggressive
Market
His behavior
In the aftermath
They literally
Of the Lone Star College shooting
Indicates
A few days after
All the talk about how popular videos
See that is kind of
Pretty strong indication that
Wanting to get into that market
Whenever there's any kind of a shooting brake
Alex try to behave
I think
He's going to lose her
His mine
That constant
Chase for the
Proof of the Earth
The fakeness
And you know what I got that's a sentence that is so
People outside of our world
He's looking for constant
Proof of this
What are you
Called working yourself
Where at
You're faking
But sometimes people get
It's so aggressively that it becomes real
Kind of doing that now
Process of
Capitalize
On this
The profitability of
He's going to end up in a shoe
I think
Siri right now
I think he accidentally
Too far in
We got into that territory where those comp
He just kept going like
So much of my time
I get so much more excited and it's so much more.
Reinforced
Audience
Many people say
You got to tell the
Hello
Really
Trouble
I can't get over how fascinated I have but how
How badly this is going to go
I mean
The prediction that I had on the last episode
Ickey Woods
Start getting in
Into this business
A bit more before I listen to that episode with Lonestar
College shooting
Text David he's back in after his vacation
That's the angle he take
It
Suggested
Very very rare production
But if we got to get
It worries
I might I might be at
Real hard.
You know it
Relatives
Because he was so far under the radar
Back in 2003
Even more damning
Eva
He did say that
The Wreckers
Provide the
Preceded that light him down that road
It makes it
Even worse
Being there
He recognized 10 points
6 million V
Reviews on this video and everyone is demanding
Psychological evaluation
Is mentally fit
To stand trial for
For this statue
Their premeditated
Modern-day episode
You can find the audio
Recordings of thing
What is it called
We're on the
Cast applique
You can go to any one of those
Mysterious places
This is a literal Murderers Row
I mean
Gyros
Be lying about everything
Catchy f****** passed though
Which
Well he was in the CIA you probably have to kill somebody just to get into
Positive
Forbade
Max Keiser
Technically eyes and
Is being called out about Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color