Alexandra Thurston color
Sit around Alex Jones
Cosplay 2019
Before but I might as well fill the good people
Tomatoes
He's flowering
Trinidad scorpion
Chocolate
Hot peppers
In the soil soil to are in soil
Serrano peppers Thai chilies
Coming along quite well
How would you know
Because I cut the right there
Doing exactly how I would expect them to be doing at this point they're growing large
So they're all so mysterious
Red flower that I plant it is growing quite well not powered yet
But
I'm excited to see
If it comes about
I do not understand what a mysterious red flowers and it looks really weird
The seeds from a hardware store ways down the road
The person who is running it
I wanted to grow these but I don't have enough room in my windowsill
Rosie's take a picture and bring them and I want to see what they come to life
I was like I'll just bring you in I'll bring you back are you kidding
You just got seeds from
Eraser
You got a magic flower and I just wanted a picture of this flower to see how it came in
I offered to bring her in for
If I had said.
I thought I was making a very nice offer
Not interested didn't think what I was doing with the light I have no idea
That is that is a boy
Ask him which action right there but I don't know I don't know
The pollen will perhaps
Evergreen song
Excited about it
Games for a serrano plant to be doing well
We're going to be going over some present-day abs
Ups and downs
This show isn't good
It's B. Good it's too inconsistent
Like there was that the last present-day episode there was at least
Stuff that I could be entertained by engaging with
Sing about
This is a No Man's Land Rover May 7th
20th
Okay
Last Friday through Monday
And I don't know I mean
I'll just tell you off the bat Saturday Sundays
Owen Shroyer
Like you said
Blow register not even fair just
Want to do it
The first
Take me to the show the first Lakes
Minutes or whatever
Bee Gees
CM on Sundays
Also broadcast
Actual news
From a straightener
Have narratives that are kind of counter to Infowars Narrative of course
Countries reading of Associated Press
Stop
By professionals
And for the first segment of the show
Over
The news feed
They have the both feed
Running simultaneously
And it was
Jarring is s***
Great Clips
Just like it was too jumbled
Even really be working
And then when he finally took over for himself it was
Just like
There's no energy
Beulah a lack of
Desire to be there
He just got the the figures on whether or not his contract
Is going to be renewed at
Murphy's a temp now
Turn on Alex employees
You got to be thinking about
How do I brand for myself
How do I
Shield myself from
Whatever Fallout is almost
Certainly coming
Change my name
Legitimate news source so maybe a field Laura Loomer for a lot
Them
Deceive themselves a little bit at that like I've ruined my life.
Attention to me really like City or versions of her
Haraf I-25
I don't I don't
Free.
You seem that
Cautionary example
Come on out
A couple
Make fun of Laura
They make fun of her arm
Insult to being a
Isn't just coming from the laughter commentators
It's coming from within the house
I don't know I'm not going to psychoanalyze but I wouldn't be surprised if there wasn't
Put making that video was the conservative rights version of a Vietnamese
Mug lighting himself on fire like everybody goes emulation
Start a revolution or something
Starting Revolution
And supporting the show so first of all
Daniel not
Appreciate your support now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk I swear to God we have every Andrew.
Andrew's clearly they would be
Cheryl thank you so much
I'm a policy that Cheryl that Cheryl was the name of my lunch lady
Middle School
She was the ship
What's the lunch lady
Control person in the lunchroom
Finger on the pulse of your career ever since
Shout out.
Got it all the same
I'm a policy wonk
Somebody who's donated on an elevated level
Appreciated
Soul is thank you so much
Business heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you very much
Feedback on that drop
Everybody's
Yep
I don't know
Petitions to have you rewrite the 8th season of Game of Thrones and add Daddy
What if that was the end of Game of Thrones
Yara Greyjoy concerts at daddy shark Island
Rabbit shark attack spoilers
Dollartree.com
Please do
To the 20th but also the 19th doesn't matter cuz don't Roy who
There's an interesting
I don't know if I would call it
The Narrative Arc
But there's something going on
Watch that play out
If you have the same feel
I do
Is about to be real shity at the border
I don't understand how that's a
Since he was
I guess born
Covering
His new moves
Videos making
You forgot about that while back
Violation of the emoluments
Sure anyways continue
So
Whatever moves
She's going to make it
I cuz he seems to be disappointed that it's not Cruller
Declare a national emergency
As commander-in-chief
And then he can direct the defense department money ICICI
Under that emergency
Law enforcement emergency on Sunday
Congress that's not
Dwight Eisenhower
Declare this emergency
Familia 4 coming out
And deported the
So he didn't do that in the lights
If he doesn't
Before but
Get the sense
Cuz we're not seeing
Cruelty all-around
Alex
Seem like he's disappointed about how he wishes
Trump's National Emergency with more overtly a power grab or a display of Cruelty
Is wild in the Sun
We live in the real world
Face on Alec
Express
It really goes to show how little his
310 principles that really matter to
His fears of an overpowered executive or images of
Release date we're always just
You never really meant a word of it
Just tell by
The way you sweat
Around
However it would I find particularly upsetting about this clip is it Alex's evoking Eisenhower's deportations
Cuz if they were a good thing
Alex's referring to what's known as operation wet back
Which to put it simply was not a good
That's why we owe used all the time
Actually probably article
Operational not simply the enforcement of immigration
Beer against
Its goal was to draw line
Between who was and who was not American
54 which was just on the heels of the 1952 immigration and nationality Act
Also known as the McCarran Walter Act
Import named after senator Pat McCarran
Who won
Protect our country
From communism and quote to Jewish interest
Which ones
Not sure exactly
Would you believe he didn't spend it but
Much interest in there is a vibe
The bill passed both houses of Congress but was president
Truman
The veto was overturned by Congress and the bill was
What the bill were not good byproduct of abolishing the part of the 70
Naturalization Act
Specified that only quote
Free white person
Good become naturalized
That's opening the door to non-white in the
Citizens
This created the need for a new way to exclude people
People and the way that happened
Was a new mentality that operations like the one in
Namely that non-white immigrants were probably cheating and not you're legally
Isn't it ridiculous that single
Moments there is a lack of exclusion
Everybody's like sleepy
Racism towards the vacuum
They're already writing
Tooxclusive
Illegal until proven otherwise
And operation wet back when a long way toward solidifying
Mentality
Everybody loved it which is why we use that word all the time I believe it's the Washington again
The farms and factories
Suzy azzam
Support for
Professionalism
Meanwhile the reality was quite different
Repeating had their head shaved
For identification purposes
Added one in
Code 88
Detainees died of exposure in the
12 degrees
Just passed the California border
Many detainees weren't given the opportunity to gather their belongings often without
Due process
There is a
Customer support is Justified their actions by
To secure the southern border
Enticed
Fears of an invasion
What was the goal or not this operation
The appearance of criminality
To just be
Being an immigrant from Latin
In America
Alex is excited
We're bored here
Not me imagine
Solution to his imagine
Immigration
So does make sense
Pics of Eisenhower's action
Composite
This late article was written in 20
Pretty prescient
If the mass deportation
Beginning Trump is product
Ship of Latinos will always be questioned
Latinos along with people who look Latino Toulon Forest
Mike will be forced to produce their
Documents
To avoid deportation
Delivering a poisonous atmosphere
Suspicion
Enforcement and other law enforcement will inevitably make
Tragic mistake
Children will not be
On Monday child died while being held in custody by immigration authorities
He was the fifth child to die in such circumstances
So I think
Prediction
Accurate
Alex
Hearkening
To the Legacy
Power to jump
What do you want to try
He's a really f***** up thing
If it's not
Somehow
Horrific act of violence against an entire people
Is the
Well the good news is that
Inevitably
Play war with Iran or Venezuela
Absolutely have learned our lesson from WWII in Venezuela
F****** camps that would be crazy
Tell me we would never go back to
I don't know because
Alex talks about what to do
It's a bad sign
What an incredible
Alive
Publications like the recall
Whoops
That I reporters inside
And the president has floated the idea and it says he's getting ready to do it
President Trump Insurrection Act
A really good
Chin of his National Emergency
B******* you know imagine
Giving Trump this King like power
In the Insurrection Act
I don't like I don't like to hear this sort of
Sting
Is really thinking about using the Insurrection Act of course somebody else is right
It's almost
Useless
Speculate about whether or not this is based on a real
Gossip
From the kingdom
The palace
But I don't like to hear Alex
Excited about it
Cuz
Misconception
The Immigrant
The refugees and the people who are
Them and support
Immigration
People who are in open Rebellion against
Country
In Alex
His conception of the insurrection
National bird
You literally
Enacted martial law to put down this Rebellion
Alex is saying
You think doesn't seem like his use my multiple movies about martial law
Primary brand
Mr. Anti martial law
I f****** love that this executive is going to use the Insurrection Act
Barcelo is f****** weird
Yeah it's not but it is
It's not when you understand Alex Moore.
Really f***** up
Borlette
But I think that Alex understands that
But it's f***** up counter
To everything
But he's warned people about
For his entire career
And so he tries to
Explain why this martial law isn't
Bad martial law
And I think you can tell just
From this clip
Reconcile
What he's doing
Spurtle martial law
I made four films on martial law
Because Bill Clinton and others were planning martial law to take our gun
Using people
Is
Emergency martial law
To counter the emergency
Emergency
Define race war
Martial law Nationwide
Fake antifa Soros documents contract in order to
To justify and reinforce this
It's exactly what you're saying Revolution
Tempted
Never cruelty
Justifying SBA
Yeah
We can't because you made us
What you want to do to lock
People up
These immigrants and refugees you want to send them back
To there
Probable death
You want
Dental service with no rights whatsoever in fear
For their lives if they
Trying
Stand up for themselves
I'm sort of better working conditions
That's what you want
Assistant that you wish to see and play
Don't hide behind imagine
Revolution that you're the counter-revolution
It's it's pathetic
I almost see this as like
Years or whatever he's been saying that the government is going to cost FEMA camps in all this stuff
President
And all of that stuff and none of them
So
He's supporting the guy who will do it
In order to prove it
Man that's an interesting way to look at it
Retconning
Narrative
My prophecies have gone unfulfilled and now I must make my prophecies come through or else
Legacy movie
That's an interesting way to look at it I don't know if that
School job literary criticism
I think it's more than that
We talked about it a hundred times
There has always been
Write the movies about martial law aren't about martial law there about something being done to wipe
He feels his team is safe
Everything was conditional
Very queer
Albany
Literally talking about martial law
And he's talking about it
Watches old f****** movies about martial law
If you imagine him saying something like this
The first emergency was just going to Congressional
Oversee DeShields funding and
Law enforcement
Emergency
Martial law
Call the jungle
Marshal meaning military
Okay so I'm excited again
Ambrosia
Your Town's going to be put under the emergency by the governor a form of Martial law stop loading for a week
Border has not the only reason but also I think we could probably come up with
Examples of natural disasters where there has been a inklings of martial law
Agency
Different kind of martial law
Of which there are apparently
That's because of an emergency that wasn't man made
You're the one who broke the Border
You did this
You made me do this
The stereotypical
It's gross this is for your own good
Against your will but it's for everybody else
View of the world that he's lied about and created with his rhetoric
In order to justify the idea
If you believe
The rhetoric in the world
For his listeners
It's not real
Compared to the real world people are helping each other
Not going crazy and burning everything
What happens in a creek
WhatsApp in 3 days people will
Eat themselves in
That's not my bad
I don't know
My bad news is
Reviews episodes
Do I'll know in Alex's show
Milkshakes do come up once but I don't have a clip of it but Nigel farage as we know is running
UCare part he's really being investigated
Is clearly illegal and corrupt
Surprise
I don't know enough about that too, but it's not going to come out
Nigel farage is the word
He's a piece of s***
He's not going to be
European
And that is tommyrot
He's a piece of s*** he's a disaster
He is running
For the northwest
You know the European Parliament
And
He's on Alex's Show 2
To discuss his
Champagne
Man it's just a
Trap it's just a it's a PR trap yes that's all
Talk more about it on the 20
Recovering
But you're on the 7th
He comes on as a guest
I think that
If you listen to the way he describes
Political campaign
Kind of understand what he's doing
Diamond select toys
Out of the northwest
And I'm trying to tell
Till we get
All communities in Austell
Background
Our backgrounds
Free speech
Tommy Robinson's primary brand much like Alex's used to be anti martial law
Is a Muslim agitation
Get people out to vote is a noble intention in terms of a representative democracy and a republic
You do want higher
Numbers of people going to
Hiding behind the pretensive
Forward
Our backgrounds
Our daughter
You need to hear and then you know OU ragip
The moment you have that appeal to look at what they're doing to our daughters like you
Robinson is this
The system it's mobile
You can't see it without
The contact
But
I don't
Care much
Because he doesn't have a snowball's
Some hell of
Selection
I don't think
Season
Absurdity
And awful
Shuffle playlist
But what
Is
Sort of logical conclusion of the
Payment processors
That not want to work with him he's been kicked off all the social media Networks
Best political campaign
I think he's doing it
Specifically
Keep agitating
Against
And doing things
Does
But now be able to be like
You guys not letting me on is disrupting the political process
So what you're saying is he's trying to do because
By running for a political office
He forces the mainstream press to cover his bulge
Or at least admit it's an attempt
X2
To make the argument that these processors
Are not allowed
Donation
And turn it into some issues its much larger than it is when it really
Crusade against Islam
Is personal
About
Being
Forced
On to everybody
Yeah
It's a mess
And we'll get
On it when we talk about the 20th
But for now he's just on the show he's like
Help help help me out I need anything out anywhere
Cuz everybody knows I'm a dick
I am so that's all we're
Alex gets back in
Into his own bulshit
Talking about martial law
Making it
Pretty clear
Vets
He thinks that his audiences are sources
Intelligent
45 minutes
Quickly
Call Zack
Did you want
Focus Martial law
We're already under Anarchy way
So like a couple couple weeks
Trump made me turn on Trump
All over the f******
Play It's So conditional it's so day today
Anybody who
Tens that likes
I've read hundreds of books and that's what I'm basing my assessment of the globalist
My lifelong Crusade against them
Anybody who tries to pretend to have that rock-solid of a foundation about what they're doing
I can't imagine how embarrassing it would be for them
To know that they're recording themselves
Constantly contradicting themselves
I disagree
Short-term stocks Trader
Every time the market goes up
He's Chasin whatever High short-term news
And whether it's Pro or anti
Even his hero
Right
It's a sickle
A legitimate support
20 year-long mental degradation
As his attention
Has gradually dwindled
He's unable to remember the 10 seconds
It's I think it's also a manifestation of like
What we talked about
So he doesn't even remember it
I hope for his own sake I hope he doesn't
Yeah for sure
How much like
This show
Send it
Psychiatry
Sleeping breathing
Studying
Researching is narrative
And I hate it
The worst
Firmly convinced
That I know he's a liar
I know that he doesn't know what he's talking
I'm about I can't imagine
What it would feel like
In 20 years if we keep doing the show that long
To be like
I can imagine the show for 2 years
Believing the opposite
Continuing to believe the opposite
So or supporting someone who is going to bring
Yeah and then you everyday you wake up with a the burning
Tell Tale Heart
Maybe breaking beneath your floor
If you feel
And we're the only punishment
On top of that
Ancestral memory
Kind of bad from our position
In terms of his ID
Videos about martial law
And I will say even after the clip they won't
Look good
But
You tries to
Explain the difference
The martial law
Fart again
Martial law
Encouraging beyond our expectations
Try
Dissociate with failure
It's associated with ism
Could The clintons Wanted at that martial law
The same martial law
Border
Federal judges
That would be the same way
A hundred thousand a month for across
Clark's child trafficking
And I
Politically use the term martial law
This is a form of martial law
It's just marshall law means
Abnormal
Your wall because it's failed
Not what it means
Because the government collapsed
Nope
Martial law meaning Marshall
The Marshal of the band
It's not
Troubling
Equivocate
Do you know
A shocking
It's hard to differentiate
When I say shocking
Figured like I'm not shocked to hear Alex
Expressing
Martial law for gun can
Controlled
Martial law for f
Cleansing
Good exactly what you said there is it's a form of Martial law and the form of Martial law is weird
Marshalls
Seems that way
For it to be something that's
Is just a
Terrifying
Look at someone who's
Cruel
Don't mind hurting people
It's awful awful
Space is just
Is it terrifying
Glimpse
How people can
Each other really would have hated being
Are like he really loved being a dictator but he would have hated living underneath a dick
Most dictators do not want to be
It's almost right
To even
Talk about
But it's
Necessary to look at
This is Alex now
Hey Patriots come get your boy
He's wildin out over here talk about martial law
He is off
Lost it
Yes
Tarpley article that you wrote back in
16 warning about the idea
The
Superficiality and the emptiness
Libertarianism
In terms of the Ron Paul movement
Edsby
The Buell wherein we will all be led to
The fascism
Authoritarian
So mad at Tarpley for making a good point it's fascinating that insight
And how
It really does track
Maybe not the entire world and certainly not necessarily all people who have lived
Quotations
But f****** Alex it is
On the head
Hit met mail
So
I don't know
Alex's
Makes me sad
What's interesting to
Expected
You hear a lot more about these abortion pills
Jack doesn't come up
Does it come up
To say that they're protecting
Children
Like you got to give it up to the Somali pirates
Couple episodes that I didn't listen to
Not a f****** mention of it except for
Dismissive
8 bills are great
Protecting children
Cherish
Analysis
Yeah I like it but
That doesn't mean that he doesn't
Some of my old favorite
Like lying about Ellis Island
On average quarantine
No one's being checked
Diseases are pouring in
Can you imagine how
Huge
Ellis Island would have had to have been
How cumbersome
I help you
3 months on average
That's
Absurd how many people would come through a day like thousand
The jet backlog
For 3 months
Gradually
Ridiculous I would be about 30 million people by the end of 90 days
I would say
Estimate it would
Be larger than the city of Chicago at
Are you given time for sure
100-percent
With with a far smaller
It's a laughable
Thing for Alex
Text to be trying to prevent that
I know that we talked about Ellis Island probably too much
Impasse episode
To bring it up because it's
This is what
He believes
Used to happen
He's facing a lot of his
Understanding
Recommendation
About immigration
Stuff that never his exact
Listed
I just completed storical revision
Probably I would say more astonishing achievement
Ellis Island admission of so many
Immigrants
Sylvia
Was
What America was supposed to be here through the entire world
There's still some cultural and social problems with the history of Ellis Island
From a bureaucratic perspective it's almost
Simply Amazing
That it works
So those calls
Put out the call for military
Police people's call in
Actually the military
You just call it a call and say that you are
Ridiculous
I'm willing to stipulate just for the sake of like I don't even want to get into it that they all are
The point out that Alex has no way of knowing
If they are or are not
So we're going to take
The least likely scenario
That all of you
Just because who cares because if
They're not
This next call is really f***** up where caller tells Alex he's arrested
A couple of undocumented immigrant
Anyway here's this caller
Big listener regular collar for shiitake products and action else I won't waste anymore of your time served
In the last week I'm in North Texas
I have a I have arrested three illegals myself
Metric Hunter panel as well as other things on them
I'm nowhere near the border
Uncle to the Oklahoman I am Mexico
I have invaded us on every level as
Well-known
Their influence from MS-13 to the Vista
Drug pushers
Everything else have gotten everywhere and
Trump must shut this place down now
On an emergency and it must be done
I'm telling you Alex
So I just play that clip to illustrate the kind of
Consensus opinion of the
You're calling it today
People are still listening
So
With a grain of salt that it may not represent that large
It's what it's what Alex is audien
Is all on board with
Possibly
Identical lamorak
Take on it
That's not good specially
Not if those are people who are
Yeah that's usually a bad sign for civil rights
In general
It's almost a worst sign if they like 24
What all those border militias aren't really held in check by
Like basically allowed to get away scot-free and they even look at them as allies more often
Running around
Does being a bad looks at the future
Alex
Is it between calls
He realizes that like
He needs to let people know that
S*** is getting
Real for him
And he is
Trouble
I don't want it
I don't like
But
Inordinate amounts of Time funny operation
10 years ago back
Stupid
Because
Have a helicopter to go cover news
Wish I knew what I knew now when I was young
Just just to let all of my listeners
The money is
F*** the radar
People
Into what he was saying
Yeah if you have a reasonably sized radio audience
You can make
Quite a bit of money monetizing that audience
Especially if you're going with these sort of weirdo advertisers that have really nice
Survivalist
You have a market that's very unique
CNN's not going to be advertised people who has more
Maine
Incredible
We're only going to advertise for avatar The Last Airbender
Will advertise Jordan 4
Dude
Driver toys for Frank Herbert's estate
Yeah
Express
Is real
Money used to be no big deal
Because I am
Fuk right now is consequences
Of the things that I did when he was flushed
Tell all my listeners there's a story about a grasshopper
And that's how they say
Exaggerating
But he says this
A little bit later and
Like
How bad it might
The money
But we've got some shirts
Sports person in Spanish
Lawson
So Alex doesn't have the money to sue the splc
Weekend the proud boys
Conceivably Alex has less money than the sucking
Proud boys
Well I mean okay
Southern Poverty Law
Where is Alex wants to
Punish
The Southern Poverty Law
Center
Not a regular similar place because Alex
Run by Bosch or Banks and globalist
And they've designated him as a hate speech
Crippling is ability to use PayPal or something
So are we just complaints are very similar to those
Proud boys
Makes me think that I was may have less money to Gavin McInnes
And I don't think Gavin is saved from his bike bike
Some s*** about Jon Ronson
Really care
Move past that
Cuz it gets to another caller who I think is a little
Okay if I had to guess
Other end
A list of four things that he needs to do
He needs to stop
These chemtrails
Get the Air Force
Sons of pitches out of the
I'm sick of it
Everybody sick this is why people are delusional
Well it's true it's true
Reinforcement
Probably don't even know
Goodyear
This is a plan
The president has to take
Complain more about the Border cuz he needed to get off the topic a little bit cuz she just said Shoop Lane
Calling wild-eyed insane person Debbie I hope you enjoy Minnesota
So has been talking about rambling
He's been talking a bit about chemtrails
There's been some coverage
Which leads me to believe that maybe she's a Lionel fan
I don't know
Also those list
I realized
She's representing could be one of the scariest
F****** things
Send the ID in the world
Because
Let's say Trump does want to shoot up
Playing out of the sky
Right Hillary's completely
Medical situation
To throw nuclear warheads around whatever want to shoot
I'm obviously being
It would be in
Circumstance that is far past where we are now
It's a nightmarish scenario where
We are
Tacoma day where he
To use this as a cover
Poisoning your families with their barium salt in the sky
Beat me realize how much these
Conspiracy theories
Incredibly powerful
As a cover tool
Used
An excuse for any
Kind of extra
Judicial killing they wanted to
Empower there's always going to be
Thinly veiled excuse to remove
Your situation I understand that trend
And I guess I just didn't realize
How useful some of the
I think about very often
But hearing her articulated that way baby realized
So many of the prong
Right of the world that Alex has built up could very easily
Be used
To justify
Some really f***** up stuff
Well let me know
Go back to Jason's for any number of
F****** calling their genocide there whatever you like
And go deep
Further down and you find a ridiculous conspiracy theories it doesn't really make any goddamn sense
A large part of what I'm saying is
Suck me first
For having that experience of listening to
Thought about
Useful for that
Alex one more call
He's in the middle of
Plug for his product
And then he goes to the call
And let's see how that plays
It should be fun
Operation
For your support we couldn't do it without you
Arizona
Hello sir
Forgot what I was going to say if you can keep calling me I just want to plug your products real quick
The other day I bought six
T-shirt
My son is currently wearing the 50 caliber
1776 coming take a shirt to school today
Get me some of that D12.
She forgets what she's even
Talk about your Vamp by plugging Alex's product
She's got a well-trained dog or they're fake
I can't decide which weather
Sounds to remember
It sounds too insane plausible that you would have your son
2 caliber the teacher almost what you would do called
Reality
Is blurring debris and when she finally does remember what she's going to talk about it
Just a bland call about how the border is
I don't know I don't know
I don't know about intention but what I do know is
The fact and ineffective
What you see is
Take a call I forgot I was going to say help me plug
Yeah
Just a f****** everything
Is a bad show
Because if you are a longtime listener Valley
And you got a hold of Alex on the air
And you forgot what you were going to say you know to buy yourself time by just plugging in
Some favors
Is you have bought that time
So
Sunday
We are Sunday
No big deal
About to be fired
It seemed like a money is good right now
So we get to Monday
The 20th
And I think
Interesting
It's not a choice
But there's a vibe
That I'm really worried about
I think
You should be very worried about this
Time
Deceased
Some signs that it might be a good
Okay
I will ask no further free Quest
It's very complicated
Hear from the toy
That is the essence of what is globalist
Are establishing
Because the Bible says
Will come up
Are there
But one hour
Most of the Earth's population will be exterminated
2000 years ago that was written plush
2000 plus years ago
And then noticed
The world government wants to depopulate the Earth today
Revelations
Old Testament
In black and white
That's what I want
Because it's all there
So
First I want to I want to point out that Alex
He's going full-on
Christian doomsday /
For propaganda
The reflection of his diminished
His Radio present
Pretends it is
He's not allowed on any normal social media platform
Any more exist
Populated by other people who've been kicked off Facebook and Twitter for their white identity
Anti algae
SECU an anti-islam adjective
I have a strong suspicion that a lot of the audience
Still able to reach me also have some inclination
Towards absurd Christian
Which would understand
Taylor recovery
He's losing his mind and going towards
Intuit
Cuz Alex himself
Crass
It is
There's usually something behind you always look for a motivation that makes
Follow Occam's razor
Guide it'll be your Northstar without
Bit of religious
Different
The version of that
Another period covered in his career as a religion
Posted this level of Doomsday Prophecy
Videos
The Beast system
Mosquito with upon us
Beyond that it's nice to see Alex explaining that idea that he had about the devil taking over for God for an hour which we've heard him in Urdu
Commercial break I didn't know that
Scripture God is going to let the be
Pieces to be place for an hour which
Which makes
Year in God hours is that
Sewing hours
I can say categorically in with no hesitation
This is not what motivated him to resist the globalist earlier and
Back in the early 2000s is worried was about the globalist
Creating a One World Government which would rule forever
With no hope of a revolution
I'm against it 60
He imagined they would create a prison planet hence the name of his website
They were going to take over for a year
Initially the thought that he had and he was
Expressing scared me
But when I reflected on it more
Intuit
Because know what I want to say
I think it many ways it represent
2D escalation of his rhetoric
If this system is prophesied to only be in power for a year then it stands to reason that you could wait it out
It may be the best plan of action is doomsday prepping Behavior
As opposed to attacking your perceived enemy
I'm not sure that Alex is audience having been whipped up into a frenzy as they have already been will notice that's
Opportunity
But it's interesting
Train to Ski Resort
Has a built-in end
That kind of
He's at
A trapdoor
For his audience 2/2
Some sort of a hoe
It doesn't make any sense
If you believe in God
No I mean
No idea that
Going against God's will
Look I don't care about any of that
Pizzaville
It's not what I'm talkin about
Before
Alex
Almost everyone.
Exterminator
Lake
You're not going to be able to stop whatever this is
Thronecoming
You're not going to stop that from happening
Not in this is expressing here
If it's there for an hour
F****** get underground something
Underground
Go to the
Biotech on it might be generous
I think it's probably generous
That I have is that he's at least
Something's it allows
A healthier
Approach to be
Azadi
In the central
Prepping
The little paranoid and
May be misguided by it in a lot of cases
You know that the ideas like
Storing can
Food and haven't water been drunk
Stuff like that
It's not that unhealthy energy that Alex
Scares you into
Into doing that
As opposed
I don't know
Trying to
Parentheses parentheses
Yeah
Yelling about locking up Hillary
Political item
I'd rather have him take a proactive stance
It's two words preparation and
Yeah far too into it then
Probably
Deserves to be there
Listening to Alex
For quite a while I've never heard this
The Bible
It's just
Potential
Point it is aspiration
What what
Biblical Pizza
Revelation 13
Discusses the beat
And verse 5 specifically lay that how long the Beast will be given
Empower and guess what it's not an hour
There was given unto him a mouse
Speaking great things and blasphemies
And power was given unto him to
Continue 40 +
What's 42 months
Or 3
Were they still on the Gregorian calendar whatever
So who knows later in Revelation
17 vs 11
The Beast who was and now he's not is an 18
He belongs to the seven and is go at is going
To his destruction
Who have not yet received the kingdom but who for 1 hour will receive authority of Kings along with
I just want to say
Great job
John
Let's read
Really loved it make
Clear present
I think you did a great job
Just retroactively just want to let you know that big ol thumbs up
There is that our in the Bible
Is something
Word
From it
Cuz obviously Alex is trying to appeal to
His interpretation of the Bible
There's nothing I can really do with it
To prove that he's wrong
It is Imagine
Code isn't the right way
Text
So I'm
I kind of came to an impasse was like well that's what you think
Disgust
A little bit more
Explore what
He's doing
Revelation is one of the highest-profile examples ever of a genre known as apocalypse
Dick literature
Early Jewish writings
Send the text I primarily to
Two functions of
The first was to explain why
The second was to make
The awful condition
When presumably God is good and all-powerful
Pre Exile prophets issue prophecies
Like for instance the Jewish people returned from Exile in Babylon
But
True other parts.
Visitors
Problem
To be sorted out so the prophet
It's reinterpreted these older prophecies to show that quote promised Glory
Where you at
Come
The older Prophets
An invasion of Judah by enemies from the court which never came
Thus Ezekiel assault
By God upon Jerusalem
Which from that point onward has
Futurama
Literature
God
And my dog earlier
Prophecies by like Jeremiah
It never ended up happening
Interpreted as
The end of times that we're still yet
In order to make sense
Came through and the other part
Version of the guy who did math and he was like I figured out
Cyberpunk
Probably less manipulative
Crassly the modern-day
People buy
There was a bourse
There's a
Entire social purpose that they were probably work
Georgia
Maya prophesied that the Messianic Kingdom would return with
Years to min
Which was almost at its end
The Apocalypse of Baruch
Fourth
Again
When the span of time had passed
Didn't arrive
So this is a
Thread that goes throughout the tradition
Yep somebody make something up
The next person is like
So to the second
I think it's pretty self-explanatory
Conditions for the common person in the 500
We're not very great
Especially compared to what they would have
Expected
The prophecies about the lavish
Kingdom that was to come
Many people suffered which felt out of line with previous prophecies
Stone explanation was needed to show people that the prosperity and good luck
Was still on the Verizon
This tradition of liturgy
Literature evolved over the years until the right
Considered to be the first fully mature apocalypse
Send text
Because the question
Turn of authorship
It described 22 as being written by Daniel
But Scholars don't believe that
Possible
Somewhere in there
One of the chief reasons for this is that there's a weird thing that happens
Israelites
To the accuracy
Prophecy
Everything to Daniel predict
At the beginning of the book matches up with
Historical event
But at the point of the book where he predicts the circum
Answers of the death of Antiochus the fourth everything falls apart
Set a timer for parallel
No spoilers it is
Interesting
He gets the death of Antiochus wrong and they predict the war that never happened
General the predictions past that point Booker Market
Detached from what we know from the historical in Stark opposition to the beginning of the book
Scholars believe the book was written during the
Miss. It should be understood in this
Contacts
At the time Antiochus representative
Existential threat to
The Jewish community
So the prophecy of his death in the coming Kingdom served
Dark time
It reinforced The credibility this
The author of Daniel used
Which allow them to use
From history
Predictions Daniel what is made
Of the hundreds of years that it happen
It's like one of our psychic
Well we don't have any evidence of you predicting that before the
Right we only have evidence of you sing predicted
Revelation doesn't exist in a vacuum
It has to be approached and understood Within
Apocalyptic literature
Mostly because the book entirely relies on the
The references to it
Revelation is held up by the final battle ideas
Reinterpreting prophecies
The beat it has a prophecy uses prophecies as a tool of political speech
In the same vein
It's an insanely complicated thing that many people spend lifetime studying scholarships
Wise to look at any of these books
It's containing literal coded message
Just that we should use to predict
That is
A silly things
At this point I was going to list off all the people who have tried to use Revelation in there
I write the list is too long
And all of them have been
Equally and completely wrong
Consider that
In the history
That we have
That's hubris pretty brazen
For anybody with the recorded history that we have
Even if just
You could get it
History
Have the balls
To try and make Revelation base predictions about the future
It just seems like you have to be
I mean you're pissing in the Wind
I mean okay
It's it's like
It's like sucking Eldorado you know
For Eldorado you're probably going to die and you're never going to find it
What
What is my alarm
Personal Achievement there's no wind except for us
Like it really
From these people who abused revelation
To predict the end times
Supreme Douglas Adams
Apocalypse
Who accidentally gets it
You know like the guy who's scamming everybody
And Alex will be wrong as well
Because
It doesn't lead
To anything other than having to revise
Your prediction
Wants it doesn't come true I do admire on some level that he's resisted the urge to say a specific date
Show some restraint is still there
I admire you more if you pick a certain date then if you just give me a
No it's over it's not the world
What other related to Alex Jones and all these people who try to weaponize revelation
And for the road and I would like to quote to them
Deuteronomy 8
21 + 20
How shall we know the word which the Lord have not spoken
When a prophet speaketh in the name of the Lord is the things follow not nor come to pass
But the prophet has
Spoken a prism
Thou shalt not be afraid of him
You heard it first in the Bible
Don't be afraid of Alex Jones
Very wrong
Very wrong Deuteronomy is telling us that the
Mark of someone who is a false prophet is he says things that don't come to pass
Alex
You sir are biblically
A false prophet
But the Bible is wrong
You should be afraid of false prophets
It's because they will f*** your s*** up maybe not on a otherworldly level but on a
On this world
I'm through Alex
We kind of understand Apocalypto
Take literature and how Revelations
Use to make future predict
Alex
Still is
Is on that
Tip
Bible prophecy is
World Government clone humans
And all of us here
There's a master behind
There is a literal devil and that also there is a literal guy that Alex is working
He's not
Some guy
Is doing the radio show
He's a tool of divinity
It's not
Easy to forget that you think
Are we sure the music isn't
Because having like
Oregon directly behind him while he
He's giving these
Apocalyptic predictions
It's like
Are you self-aware you know he's f****** with us
I feel like a staff is doing
Habitat now
Like the people he could get to employ
I don't know if any of them were that clever
Like slight Rebellion
Talk
Literature 2
And now we're going to get really into the standard model
Woodstock
Science
That the global is there going to be in charge of for an hour
Google Steve already been in charge for a long time according to Alex
Know the time
Pennywise
Stockings
Traitor
Music
Dude
Going to kill you
Steely Dan
I wasn't feeling it still
You might notice there those little aggressive
Donuts break
To notice the characterizes almost Alex
In this episode
It's something I've seen a lot of presents
With shocking regularity goes that's breaking the globalist want to kill you and your family
Ramping up the fear these trying
How to create newsletter
Mirraw when he returns her break
He generally doesn't have that same intense
Comes back from break bragging about it
Like this segment right here that it began
Within playing Supercut of people on the
The street being nice to him
Wally talked over the video saying stuff like
Employees just too popular everyone loves in the globalist had to silence
Congratulatory thing coming in
The brakes
You saw through the b******* you know
When you're heading into a commercial break your number one job is to
To keep people
Turning the dial
This is why new shows do that embarrassing
Clickbait type story thing where they're always
Trying to kill your child come back at 5
We will get you after the break will tell you about the threat to your child
Trend
Exist
In poorly done exploitative media
Happening a lot more in Alec
I know that we had a lot of laughs over the years
About Alex
Yelling out to break
And of course
But please trust me
Someone who's Listen to More Infowars than anyone ever should it's noticeable
30s doing it a lot more lately
If I had to Hazard a guess I would say that because his numbers are really down
I have to use whatever tricky
To keep people around
I'm no expert and I've no hard data to support this although if you look on Alexa is
Is traffic
Going downward
But it's hard not to read this is anything other than pure desperation
On display
The only thing Alex has left
To offer his audience
Bortles
He's having a f****** Easter sale on
Is trying to terrify people
To the science question
Omniscience
The question of where Alex
Fear has landed
Scale of crazy versus reasonable
I can't deny that there are
Express concern about
Exposure to radio
How they could have unintended help concert
So don't seem like it's something that Alex is making up out of thin air
Spider-Man
With radio waves
The problem with taking the Alex might be out of sort of reasonable appears when you get into
The reason
Concerned about the increased health risk I asked to do with the increase
If the number of transmitters
What you think about their specific
Is the not just talkin about 5
Is what they're concerned about
The scientist or talk about this stuff pretty regularly
That it would be just as bad
G4g or Wi-Fi
The problem for them is all wireless communication
To accurately Champion the closet
Using a thesaurus
You'd have to take it to that level
He got rid of
You wouldn't be able to use that
Peace
The uses for staff to talk to him
I am going to ask this question
So very simple and base
They know what
5G
What do you mean Alex
Yeah I mean any of these like 5G
Cruisers or whatever
I'm probably that
So
But it doesn't matter
They don't still care about
He's just a
The fifth generation of the same
Context conceptual radio
Top of the Rock
No
Could you could make a decent argument based on
The factory
She is
Using
Parts of the
Spectrum Spectrum
That don't travel as far
So they do need to put up a bunch more transmitter
In order to
Coverage
For the 5
That works okay
Radio freq
Based on
Intrinsic misunderstanding
It doesn't require the
Piggybacking it
They're just haters up everyone would have
More of this
Radio freq
Bombarding them and that
Is benefit
Right I suppose
Okay so there is the
Turtle of
I would need to read up a lot more before reporting
If it's a new story at all
He posted an article on Infowars over the weekend
Hundreds of respected scientist sound the alarm about health
Affect
Has 5G networks go up Nationwide
Wichita
Scientists are currently sounding the alarm
Which is not the case
Back on September 13th
When 180 scientist
Doctor's appeal to
The European Union about 5G
Asking them to put a moratorium on rolling out the technology until there were appropriate
They were appealing to the EU because the EU
Tone of money
Making preparations and researching
45 G
So it seemed like a good place to go
In response to their petition
You clarified the quote the responsibility
For protecting the public from the potential harmful effects of electromagnetic fields remains
Including the choice of measures adopted
So if you understand that response
Have the Sovereign decision of whether or not to adopt
5G it's a states rights
No one is forcing anyone other than I guess the sovereign
To implement
Maybe like it's the federal government saying that is it is after the states
Horse that's being a sovereign country is about
Of those countries who don't
Discussion but whatever
Do you clearly has a firm in their position
And that's really something that Alex doesn't wanted to stop
To his idea of
The EU taking away States
Ultimately the more I look into 5G question of it the less concerned about it in the more I feel like as the manufacturer
Freakout narratives it Alex's basics
Small turtles
Bayan and used
Jumping from therein
Too irresponsible
Scientist
At the Advent of the fuc
Kingradio that weren't like
I'm positive
Concerns about the potential health effects
And they're not
Messerli lunatics or doctors who aren't doctor
Alex or manifest
What quackery would be based on
Some scientist
That raise
What are the big things
Anti 5G
2 as evidence
Is that the international agency
For research on cancer Has Lifted radio frequency electromagnetic field
Possibly carcinogenic
Well it's rarely pointed out the
But the iarc
His only five categories
These were things
There's carcinogenic
Probably carcinogenic
Possibly carcinogenic
Probably not person agenda
And not classifiable
Strongly agree with
You disagree with that or do you
Disagree with that are strongly disagree with
Things like aluminum production
Or the Epstein-Barr virus
Anabolic steroids
Or working as a hairdresser or Barber
Are listed as possibly probably carcinogenic
As is
Eating red
Or drink beverages hotter than sick
65 degrees Celsius
Those are probably
Is there a hairdresser who likes
Drinking really hot things
Included in the
Possibly carcinogenic category
The radio frequency
MC radiation
Here's some of the things that are in that category
Being a firefighter
On Wednesday
Dry cleaning
Exposure to gasoline
Car exhaust
Pickled vegetable right and aloe vera
The definition for inclusion in that group is quote
There's some evidence
Vera can cause cancer in humans but it present it is far from conclusive
This is this context is really important
Since it explains what researchers mean when they say certain things
The technical meaning of
Possibly to the iarc
Is different than what it mean
Conversationally and Alex and his cohorts are taking advantage
Of that difference of definition
Manipulating
Is almost like
Chronicle of
Modern inventions
If you want to exist in a relatively modern
In space you're probably going to
With possibly carcinogenic
Partially true partially
Not quite
Because a lot of them end up in the NOC category category risible
Area
Yeah because there aren't studies
Category
He's some kind of a study that
Is indicated if possible but nothing
I need a smaller list
Aloe vera and pickles
It's because those are things that are there
Not regularly eating platypus
That were study
Catholic Church
Oh I didn't know that
You can't eat red meat on Fridays or whatever for whatever reasons was probably person
Beavers
Fish
Cuz they live in water
Catholic trivia
So the LA Times article Alex is talking about there also
It's from August 8th
And talks about
Study that was done with
Found quotes
Small increase
Preseason tumors in male rats
And makes it clear that quote
Extrapolating the results to humans
It's complicated
The article comes from a quote
Include
I don't think it's clear that there are helpers
There are no help
Says Lee Kaku
Epidemiology professor at UCLA
School of public
Who is study the effects of cell phone
Yeah that's such a responsible thing to say it
Yuri atr8 so call back later
The point
That's the point of the article but it doesn't make a good headline
And so you make a more Sensational headline
Science
Results inconclusive should be the headline of just about every
I'm not too worried about this 5G stuff
And I don't think Alex is on good footing
If I can get some
First footing
Okay little bit later
Cuz he starts talking about Islam
You remember how he was getting really revelatory
Revelation
Stuff earlier Revelation to Muslims
Smell that shitt I don't want
It's not good
Wow unfortunately we live in this world
Alex
World
Is Express in the world
Wishes to see
Oh that's not
This is Joe
That's why they're bringing in
Muslims
That's why
Don't talk about what Muslim
Ascertain
Just pee
People
Have
A reticent
Except
U-save-it certain
Religion
Compatible
With
Good Society
I think that that is
Like it's not no one saying don't talk about is
Don't think don't talk about Muslim
They're saying
Yeah
Don't do what you just did in that quick
Boils down to about a seventh of the entire population of the
The human race
Is fundamentally in
Compatible with the other sick
Which leads to extermination
Mission is immoral
Complete isolation
There's no other resolutions
Restrained
Benevolent solution to whatever
Do you know what
Do all Muslims go to Australia
And you stay there and we barricaded it around
That's insane
So
Eva's next clip Alex
Explain
Is feeling
On
Islam
Himself
Is
This is troubling
Disturbing
But
I also think
Trim the video
We're early in the episode you was talking
About how
She doesn't want martial law but the globalists are making them do it
Course
It's sort of the same thing
How to get rid of all the Muslims
But they're making me
He's being
Forced into this position or at least that
It's exactly that
It's
Pathetic way to be
Little monster
And I want to explain something
Personally
Joel McHale
Open the middle
I personally don't want to be at war with Muslim
Cuz you're a coward
Globalist plan
For Clash of civilizations
But if your daughter gets kicked out of subway
Stairs
Byram islamicize cuz they
You know that she's a profane
Dog creature cuz she's a Christian or whatever
The police the media try to cover it up and that's long
On the coastline
The defense of the Muslims that's War
And that's wrong
We already know from covering
Stuff that I don't know what's
Stories talking about or if there even is one
Kick downstairs
But I know that that cross storyline
That doesn't give
Give me much hope that the other stories
Are being accurately reported here
Application for why Islam is at
You're at you're starting off on a bad foot know I was I was listening to that and I was thinking maybe our solution
City propaganda and how awful our media is
The hole is not deplatforming
What it is is putting a referee
In every live
What he's like when your daughter gets emotional manipulation
I suggested that is the punishment for episode
That was years ago
I just wanted to point out that that is
Cross story
You're stupid
It's a manipulated Collision
I understand it's a manipulating Clash
But it doesn't
The fact if you're
On the receiving end.
There is a class of civilizations happening
The globalist program
We must be honest about the cancer
That has become Islam in this current
And the fact
Systems cancer
Mainline churches
Epitome cancer
It's not
Good
Here
Because I mean
It's not good
Because
Globalist and the last girl can't
Throwing in the main
Christian churches is also
Kind of
Terrifying
Because
Would you sing the mainstream Christian
Churches are cancer those are the ones that are going to be more tolerant
So if you are not in a lake
Christian Church
That believes in his belief
Then they are a Cancer as well that you should get out of that church they're misrepresenting God.
See what he say
Right just like just like that thought that the tea party was a leftist group
Like that kind of scam
Like the glitterbug
I don't know if he does specifically
Keywords
Exactly I don't know I am not positive I've heard him
Come down on her either either way but
I.
I think that it's more the churches that
Church
So you talkin about this and I was
Hearing it
I thought like well
On brand
For now for president
But at the same time it is
In the context
They're talking about
Apocalyptic Santa
WWE
You get this
There's something really f***** up that
Communicating
Understand exactly what he was
Other than just
Killing time
Even people and saying it's not our fault that we're demonizing you you made a threat
Understand
Practice was being laid until
He starts playing a video the Tommy Robin
Well
I'll just explain
I imagine him
In whatever video you're about to play
I imagine him as Dick Van Dyke
Doing a shity cockney accent wearing a Nazi uniform
And that's not right.
That's how I'm imagine
Inaccurate
Of his event
Tommy Robinson
I thought about it long
In hard and there's only one thing I really want
Before but I'd like to double and triple down
And that is suck Tommy Roberts
Tell me he's running for office
It is video he specifies that he's going to work in class
West Townsend
From everything in this video
Yeah and everything of the video I've seen I'd be hard-pressed to find to non-white people in the footage
He specifically even says that he's avoiding places with Muslim population
People
Given Tommy's career
Is believes his lifelong pattern of criminality is lifelong Association
With Nazi white supremacist
This group's is document
History resorting to violence
Tire brands
Funny flavored islamophobia
It's not hard
See what he's doing
He knows God damn well that he doesn't have a chance of winning the f****** dog catcher election
And this political campaign
Rules to carry out his anti-muslim
Anti-islam agitate
Particularly now that he's
Kicked off social media
Didn't go to predominantly white working-class areas and give campaign
Is what you knows will be disrupted eventually
Which will then give him the perfect Optics
Continue with b*******
For another cycle
And get more
Tommy was giving a speech in Oldham on
Saturday May 8th
And there's a large faction the folks
Who showed up
Some through eggs in Brick
Those
Might not have been Brixton vitamin rocks
I'm not entirely sure
Tommy could not have been happier
You can kind of see it in the video
You smirking while you talked about the event
Everything purple
A group of white families
Just trying to support the political process
Attacked by a group of unruly Muslim
He got all the footage of children being put in cars where yells in the bullhorn
About
How you need to be concerned for their safety
Children being attacked
Obviously I worry for those kids safety
Absolutely
But I also worry about their parents choices bring them to a f****** Tommy Robin
Before he even got involved in politics
He been arrested
3 x 4 violin
Including one-time in 2005 when he assaulted an off-duty
Cop who tried to break up an altercation
Between him and his girlfriend who was issued a citation
For being in possession of cocaine
Every Behavior has gotten less safe for kids to be around since then
I'm not blaming those parents fully but it's
To not know what you're getting
To going to a
Tommy Robinson
Has a particular character
You know what's going to happen
Yeah
I do not endorse
The people throwing rocks at Tommy
I strongly disapprove of non milkshake now
No Rock
I disapprove of non milkshake related violence
And even more than that
This is exactly the outcome Tommy
He gets to be the victim
Use these videos as a
Powerful recruitment tool ticket Vince white people that they're under attack from
No.2
It applies this for me
I don't support what these people did but I wholeheartedly support the political message
Which boils down to f*** you Tommy Robinson
Which is something that you could hear every day they would be nearly enough never
Big deal out of Tommy's very manipulative video about what happened to him and how Islam
Eagle
I'm not interested
Deconstructing what he's all about I think we all pretty much seasons game for what it is
There are a couple points
They'll wear Alex's commentary on the video drift
Did the territory work
Become relevant for us
To discuss
So they receive those clips in here
A little bit of tommy's video under Alex
Which is mostly just a
Explain District
Here is
Alex play the video again
Vicki said something
It's very telling
Is pretty explicitly expressing
Nationalist
There's no Homeland for the white man
Is Christian
Christian like there are no Christians in Africa come out
Is very explicitly the language
Uses
Instead of
People's Christian
You know what he's doing
What is edit
Pathetically
Transparent
It's really bad
That's so
God I'm just bummed
You did
Just use the word
Use the word
They are
As jay-dub
Alex's something
You said
Episode
Firenze apartment
England
Top
So when we did that crossover episode with qanon anonymous
Made a point about that
Traitors
That's what Alex
Do you think those cops
Are mad because he's not a traitor to his people
Hoo-boy
You know it sure seems like it would
I don't know if I was exaggerating
A lot of that I used to describe these people has been
Lesson lesson
Extreme in regards to
Exaggeration
Yeah as we gathered more information
You've gotten
Less
Extreme with your rhetoric
Because we realized it
Or at least is your description
So what are things it's important to point out is that Alex is playing this video that highlights this
It's conflagration that happened at a time.
You know Tommy's history if you
You know what he's all about this
Exactly what he
Tinder and gasoline for somebody else
Is there fake or anything like that but it's exactly the sort of Optics
Tommy bags
Score cuz it's the
Kindling for the fire
That he knows how to build
Exactly
And it's important to point out that this video that Alex
Displaying is specifically
Materials
For Tommy's Run for the parliament
This is literally from a procedure
Never
Play the Muslim
Go
Paradise
So it's just a camp
Traders
Parliament
This family-friendly event
Black
Man
God he should not even be
You should not even be
Physically allowed to
Just say the words family
Censorship
Pro First Amendment
I also think we should take some words out people's
There's no first
UK
In a general sense
Alex
I'm all for free speech rights
He's not allowed to say Martin Luther King Junior 410
Or Huber
I just really think
Think that it's
Evokes
Exactly what it's supposed to
Which is
This idea of a race war more or less
Milan news
If you will
It's a real bad luck
It's a baby when I was saying that
Apocalypse
Fix stuff with me 1 hour
Is maybe at the escalation
Go ahead and ignore all outside
I just was a stray thought
Anyway your little bit of Mark Dice
You've got a special report that Alex plays twice during the show
The marks
Syracuse
Apparently
Taken to making fun of Beto
Which I don't know why
I don't know how relevant
In the primary race
Less unless the time goes
I already think he's down in the lower tier
Of candidates who are running
But Mark Dice makes a meal out of making fun of him
In this clip
And then Alex said something really funny
What the Patriots game
Does pouring rain
Kimberly Goins
But it's a public place and you know what I mean
This made me want to mark.
The best videos ever
Wow.
Text Mark.
A boy taking out Beto and the Blasio
Emily timely Beavis and Butt-head reference pieces of information
About this
Looked into it
This first one I just listen
The clip that Mark Dice played person who complain
To the Blasio
Is this a good place
Get your message out cuz it's
Trump Tower
They're not mad at him for being a bad Trump Tower so
It doesn't really work for his argument
Into his marked Isis 41 f****** years old
That is a
Parasite
Embarrassing behavior for Asurion
Impression
Hawk
Call man
Happy birthday to forty-year-old Matt dreski friend
He's not making videos like that that's why I
Signified in Loctite
Holyshit
You got it
That would be bad if I saw that Caitlin
Making it would be embarrassed
Anyone over
That kind that kind of behavior is
I would look down on anyone under 16 knowing a Beavis and Butt-head reference would be
Improve my estimation of
Possibly
I just need more style list
Less specific reference
Absolutely terrible
Squaw Valley
Described as hell
Climate
Spirit
He spells out a little bit of it
Government overreach
30 uses of the referee
Like a little
Specific real-world example
Necessarily
Offensive off the bat
It doesn't work for
He knows that no one listens
Make nose so
But do you see the total is
It's because everybody's underwater
And the world ending
In 12 years unless you do
Exactly what damasio
50% unemployment
25% unemployment General
The country
Has fallen apart it's been destroyed
This is an economic missile
To destroy economy
So Alex knows that his audience doesn't know any
Think about Spanish
Employment rate
Yeah
AP reported that Spain's unemployment rate currently
14.45
Percent good looking
But whatever Alex
Discusses to testicle
Crucially important
Consider the context
What issues with Spain's economy is historically been characterized by high on a
Employment even in the best
When their economy was doing 1007
Unemployment
High Country
Similar circumstances
Like three to five percent yet what is recommended by the vet
13% of Spain's
Employment isn't
Construction and housing
So the 2000s bubble was
From nearly a decade later
30% of the housing
Frey Construction
You isn't
It's a very large
Jesus people of criticize
Economy was largely
Possibly
Yeah
A country with
Best protection
Employees
In the world
Until 2012 was the law that if you fired a permanent employee you had to pay them 45 days worth of wages for every year they were
Naturally this made businesses look for ways to
To get around have decreed
Which they did
Fire hydrant
Who don't qualify
For the protection
An estimate from LTE says that 25% of the workforce is made up of the
These temporary employees
Who are not included as employed
Statistics unemployment rate
13 or 15
Percent
The 10% of that fourteen or fifteen percent is constantly cycling
Sick because of their temporary status
Entire month
X-Pac which explains why
Play higher
From this visually look
Three out of every hundred job contract
When this article
That's not good
Unemployment rate appears to be so high
Under ideal conditions
Already and always pretty much consistently higher than you
Expect
But now the number is inflated by putting workers into
Abusive
It's like Joe with receipt here with the
Gig economy
And on a personal level I can attest
But I was at
2 years before I go
Complained enough
But Heather exploiting me that I got high with Max
Obviously there are other factors.
Consider but these are a couple of the really big one that Alex
Conveniently not bringing up what he brings up these flames
Because if he did they would undercut the idea that the globalist implemented
Technology plan to take over the economy
Country because
That's not
True
That isn't what happened
It just
Is a wave
He can interpret
Statistics
Even out date
Yeah but you can interpret these statistics
And in such a way as to make his argument that it has something to do
With
Interpret is almost
Too bad it like obfuscate
Statistical fanfiction
Sorry one last clip year
It's interesting
Because on the one hand
So there is
But it also
There's two things that
They're going on one is Alex's arguing
Volcanoes are great for play
True
Sure you might be making a bigger deal out of it
Possible
Second
He's doing
Is he seems to be making an argument
The place is like Venezuela in Africa
To be based on natural resources
They should be the countries that are the best
And the reason that they're not is because they haven't
Superior culture
So
And then stay with the
Experience or how he's making this argue
Very much is
Based in
Position in a boat
That there is relative value of cultures
And
Central American South American afro
Working cultures
Inferior
2 European
White culture
Bright
Venezuela in Northern
South America
The world
They have
Incredible Wildlife incredible fish
Play more resources
It's joke
Level
But just like
And the government and assistant
Call Trish
How many resources
Sub-Saharan particularly
The only continent that has
I want a dinosaur bone
Summaries
Lithium
Every gym
Farm
Venezuela
Volcanic soil
We sell coffee
From southern Mexico
They grow on the sides of volcanoes
Why did Greece have such good food
Volcanic soil
Gary's middle
Volcano
The best coffee in the world comes from places you can get really expensive as well
They've got everything
Coffee
From the Continental us because
We don't have the soil to grow it
You can grow it it just doesn't taste
Storybook
Weird
Losing the thread
That's indicative of how his brain works that's really troubling
Nonpoint
Sandpoint
I resist
Just just like
For Note 4 no like positive
Reason
Crocheting
Miss generation
I resisted Mima sighing
Sure
But God dammit if that wasn't
Galaxy brain level s*** right there
Ice-T it
All laid out in front of me and none of you guys are all playing on it
Completely different chest
I know it all
Mount Saint Helens
Is in America
Campground
Because
It erupts
Unlike some of the ones in Hawaii or active volcanoes of the grow
Coffee
They have a nice
Sexually active
I mean
On the one hand I'm not going to
To deny that volcanic soil is very fertile and good soil not going to argue with that
But
I am going to
Alex got distracted of what was
A very
Rerulili racist.
Ignore the
Tradition of colonialism
And especially sub-Saharan Africa
Really seems to take
1 elements out of the equation
And that's
Bye
Beyond adjustable Isaac
Ratably
Amanda is another word for it
Shoota lyrics
I mean undeniably
If you saying that all these places that's all these resources
You'll because their cultures they can't get their s*** together
Wow
View
Coming to
Covington native
Is coming to North America
The Savage
By themselves
You hear clip like that where he's talking about
These
Other
Africa
They're mineral-rich
Cultures
That's why there's a nefarious element to when he's talking about Africa for the Africans
Is it that you don't mean retire
I want all of Africa's resources and I want all of you people
Yeah
It's the
It's a load of b*******
So what
I don't think
Episode is good or very interesting
It's because like a lot of these things
Just kind of
Explicit
Extensive
Of things that we've already heard
Revelation
We heard you want our thing on a past episode
Sometimes
We've already heard him say in the past that Muslims are incompatible with his version of what he wants in
Society pretty hard here
We've heard him
Certipay
Is ideas about martial law being bad even
Before
But he's now being
So bootlicker read and so enthusiastic about Trump
Doing that with the Insurrection act in
Yeah it really is just
What we
Do
Okay alright
Episode of a television
Preamble for an action
Do you know who this is
Another bottle episode but it's that episode of rising action kind of unsatisfying
Really a climax
Next to the building
In baking
Intentions were
I think that's
In this stretch
2 time from the 70
Service
Of a climax
Who's coming
And it worries me
Well it's
Repeat it over and over again is one of the
Isn't that I find Alex
To be a figure worth talking about
All
Is because he is that week
Glink
Right-wing propaganda that says
No he sings allowed part
The quiet part into the wild
Excessively
Done that Alchemy
I don't know
Fully if there's a lesson to be learned from this episode
The present sucks Robinson if
Fucium
Milkshake at boy
Yep
We are also on the iTune as well as other pods
Castroville application
I had a beard
A mime
Yes
The wrong episode 4
Or somebody
I don't know
What do you got
I mean we didn't talk about it really but
Jon Ronson hasn't killed anybody 100% looking good
The terms of what they may or may not have done
Not murderer
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work