Holding
Alexandra Thurston color to knowledge fight
Another installment where I
As a man who listens to
Too much Infowars
Explains what's going on in The Wonderful Wonderful World of Alex Jones who has absolutely no idea
Video what the f***
Is about to happen
I do you ever heard of it
You're right you haven't passed
Into the news
Your man was like
Yes yeah I was I would say I am globally where in the sense that I know about 40% of
The globe
I'm just trying to give you some Bona fides hear my expertise
University of Missouri
No no
Are you at the junior college you dropped out
I mean he did well for himself
He's very much like a like one of those Tech billionaire or like Eminem
Proud of it
Quote from Eminem 12 song
We got a lot of business to cover so you guys know if your Eagle listeners
You know that last week
Alex Jones
Was on vacation
He was on break
He wasn't in studio and we had tons
Have these been
Dingbat
F****** co-host we had the David Knights of the world
Filling in we had Rodger Stone doing a day
Did Paul Joseph Watson hosting I don't want it I don't want to cover those guys
So we're not we're not we don't have
Flash episodes
The cover right now
So to speak
But when it comes out it'll be Monday
Alex will be back into yo
Super excited about
But while Alex was off
He sent in
A lot of dispatches from the road
Okay he's in a lot of special reports
I think those are worth talking about a little bit that's going to be covering
I hear this episode before we do
I wanted to check in because
Our first episode
We listen to Alex
Explain
Was going to take some meeting
Yes
But you didn't want to explain to meeting
But the mainstream media could put two and two together
Was going to be with
I don't need to tell
Need to get kudos or a pat on the back
Lots of afraid to leave occupied
Texas
Call truck
A little blanket over a lipstick
But on this side when he called to give a special report
Music slightly different take on it he's his own in Spain color
Yep okay
Addresses
In this clip his co-host
Who's filling in David Knight
Explaining the situation
Regardless
Talking to meeting with people everybody I talked to basically against political correctness film almost everybody
Are you taking meetings with people and everyone hates political correct
Hooray
Here's and reveals in his own sentence Wyatt is
Nobody else is talking to him
If somebody likes political correctness
Instigating then run the f*** away
Probably
With someone giving a warning to break up a party
So he's been telling people it's a family vacation
Who's the conspiracy
His mind
Everybody cares where he's going
Sometimes you lie about things you don't have to
I think that's what he thinks he's doing in his head
Not realizing that he revealed on his show what he was doing
I'm going to go meet with Trump
Then reveals that
While he's been lying and saying he's going on family vacation what she hasn't been doing
Now say that he was on a family vacation I haven't heard
Patient has never been fed in the history of the world right
Even credit
This is working in a different place he's doing his work from the road and God bless
He is our true traveling Kung-Fu
Hero
Geico
Video that you put out right before he left
I feel like it's still the beginning of the year and I feel like
You know a lot of people is made resolution
You made a resolution
At a certain point here but he
Called
The Secret of 2017
And I feel like
He already knows the secret he knows the secret
Is this is a really I think it's probably like a 20 minute long video
I've cut out the parts that are superfluous
Like what
We're going to take a look at this this video today
This
The Secret of 2017
That I think
It's pretty indicative like if you look at this as
Just a microcosm
Of Alex Jones broadcast
Dial
Him to a f****** tea
So here we go we're going to kick it off
I remember
Over half a year ago
I was in
Cleveland Ohio
Covering
The RNC
I want to be clear I'm not putting in pauses
Tom Waits telling story right
Just a little bit
Pick it up part of me that thinks like from listening to this that Alex is itching to do
Foodarama
Really wants to start doing dramatic monologue
I don't like it
Wednesday
This video is that long I'm not playing 20 minutes
Went over to the Ritz-Carlton
For the main Republicans worst
Fox News
Official
Vice
Programming
Keep in mind I want to cut in here real quick to remind you that the name of this video
Is the secret of 2017
So just remember when he starts down this road
This is the first thought he had in his mind when he made a video called The Secret of 27th
You forgot to add the part where he's at
The way we learn about
Bethel Chris Christopherson there
Voice
I don't know if I have to go to you
And we talked about Megyn Kelly
And I said Megyn Kelly
Seems like
Just yesterday also watch out
Megyn Kelly is your bellwether
She can successfully
Convert your audience
Conservatism
Libertarianism
Buying into worshipping
Portable horse Hillary
Kelly
Destroy yourself
American people
We were racing ready slot
Chile top rated
Account
Adele
He's moved on
Peacock Network NBC
Bad son
Microsoft
This is true
But it shows how
She gets her hair done in Manhattan
Beautiful little elf woman
I still believe
You were laughing over him calling her solace
This again but I'm going to attractiveness
Disagree with her on her stance is Andres
Everyone is gorgeous
Absolutely
She's a b****
This clip is gone
Probably where else would she get her hair done in the Bronx yo b****
Harlem to get your hair done you a lefty
Easy but alright
Traffic
Elite
Show Megyn Kelly
The whole dinosaur media goes down
Is emblematic
The fall
Of the peacock globalists narcissistic brainwashing
That's really
The takeaway
So that this is the first clip and it's like it's a thesis statement
It seems like that's
The thesis
To go on this particular subject
Percent
Button
I believe they were
I don't know if she I don't know the statistics on that but I know that they did offer her a fat contract to stay at the church
Harassed by all
Numbers were slipping
A little bit but not like to a profound
Extent
Now
Has he ever criticized Megyn Kelly in the
I think so yeah she was the moderator of that debate and
Yeah absolutely shouldn't have gotten in the line of fire with a good man
I know he's a good man can I ask you question these elves are coming up on our Orange
Toes
Overarching narrative that they have that is like the
Media are bullies
And that like keeps coming up
And it's so like I do believe that Alex would think that like
Asking Trump hard questions
Is bullying
And it sets
Nuts
Spell completely. That control the Press everything he always says this
Everything that you accused of
Asif
Is what they're doing
Yep
If we don't do it
They're going to do at 2
Preemptive justification in the same way that China
Russia have reserved
The right to First Strike
Nuclear attack
I assume they didn't cancel that reservation right
I mean tables ready
Interesting Lee that is his
Opening volley of the secrets of 2017
Maybe that's the direction he's going to go
This might not be the case
Here's some more words about Megyn Kelly
Houston
And
Look at these parts
Megyn Kelly is a dumb blonde cheerleader
Looked okay
Fox
See that's
That's so unfair on a number of levels he's justifying
Sounds drunk who is
Like he's been on the road for a long time he's sitting next to
He's drunk
He's just
Rambling she's like what I thought about her appearance
The directions. He's the only one who seems intelligent at all
Like a dumb cheerleader archetype
Kind of archetype with her position but she does seem like a f****** whip-crack
Tracking smart lady and substantial
She seems like someone who has borne this out
In interviews
She's Not Just
Repeating things in the interview and questions based on what the people say
Which is why the haters because if you respond with an answer and then
That's hard
Skip over
Insinuates
Like a certain
Super the school might have a Gravely
For the second time in the Phantom 3 minutes women but this woman isn't ugly coups
Really went after why is he going
Appearance looks like a witch Bush League
But
You know when you really get down to it I don't know if he has many other tools
You know like other than Bush League
Stop in in Peru consult
We got more
Pixar soul
Ugly
Failed ship
Because she feels reject
After buying a lie
This is just her thinking oh my God I'm hated Fox
Let me go
NBC
Cuz those failures those vampires
Swindling
So that was just fanfiction
Assume what she was thinking
He thinks
She told her friends
But I'm ugly
Now he's absolve himself
He just repeated what she said never heard anybody telling us
Psychic
Cup me absolutely knows what she's dealing with
Okay
Alright
Is he everywhere at all times does he have everything bugs because it seems like everything's does is like
I know that
3 people
Yep
Small little camera setup wherever
Well I mean
Right now
He probably does
Let me think about it generally don't come out of people who don't have some sort of feeling
No outright hate is usually covering up some sort of
Conflict
You must have loved
At some point
Yeah you'll feel betrayed
Feels like he's been left behind
By the one she's the one that got away so now again I have to remind you and I'm going to constantly remind
This is the secret of 27
Describe the opening minutes
We're on 10 minutes
We have the focus abilities
Taking crack speed and Azan
Yeah
Taking up the beginning of the secret 2016
It personally attacked the appearance of Megyn Kelly over and over again and assume what she's thinking but
Really what it's all about
Also about how good a man
Alex Jones
I'm just an average person
Who has a will
Justice bound
Northrup
I don't want to go
Weird functions
Dinners
Fake
Charity event
Take photos of you just so you feel big
I'll tell
Luby's
Mountain
You might think that this is going to a I support local business
Redeeming factor in this
Log truck
Long and seemingly drunken
He is about to tell a story
That never happen
To illustrate why he's a great man
So we're back to the spaceship car
1000%
Champagne and enjoy some
Bulshit time
Already
When I grow up
It wasn't till about 6 years ago that I don't know
That your old ladies online would always been in line with stoves
Have the money
And a little purse bag
There weren't
And what's that
What is currently
This whole life
Here's why this didn't happen
I don't think of Alex Jones number of reasons isn't possibly a charitable
That's entirely possible
But this story didn't happen
Because no one goes to a restaurant and being
You stay home
One day out of
He's again this is Megyn Kelly's thoughts he's assuming you have no idea
So okay
Alright
So this is happened a few times
Apparently
Cmovies
If you know these peoples names
Can he give us any details about them other than their there old women cry
Xavier son
Do a news report
Feel better
It was at my whole life
My two years old
Never heard
Equality
Cheaper
License
Songs ever had
Relate the story to Obama
Also inflation
Food is worse Melville
It's cheaper but there's inflation
I don't understand
Is that is that is a
Twisted
That's a
Pretzel of a thought
Against like you're getting
This is the secret of 2017
Megyn Kelly is ugly and insecure so she ran away to NBC
Increasing inflation and it Alex Jones is a good man because he overheard some
Old women talk about
Paper food they ordered
Coin purses business supposed to be now
But he's still referencing coin purses from occupied Texas
Now he get I don't know when Texas is in the world
It's in the 50s
So now here's where he gets
A little bit
Off the chain
Obama
On a jumbo jet and playing golf
And sitting around delusional cuz he's black so it's okay to say
Black people got to be poor
He was chosen by the stick
Inbred corporate
Blue blood
The screw is over
We got a bunch of Narcissus
Who want to be on their news
Their shows their channels
Feel like we've arrived
So we'll sell our own family
Be part of them
Yeah
Okay
He's playing these clips on his phone and in lieu of actually having anything to look at
Just been staring at his phone so stupid paper cuz I don't understand
He went
That was a
What was the crazy triple Lindy triple axel
That was the Tony Hawk hitting a 720
Random
Because Obama's black he can tell black people there should be pores that's one thing
Understand you get off okay
I know he said he's not saying that
Literally saying that the world
Think that which is also not true
It's because Obama's already even more racist
Then me
Double Reverse Racism
Now the cars and microwaves thing
That's an old that's an old Chestnut of Alex's X
Obama telling third-world Nations
But they can't have cars
And air conditioning
Are you didn't really tell them that as much as it is
Uplifting
Conversation
Before we begin
No cars
For now on
What the f*** I think
I looked into this a while back because it was one of those that I was like
There's no way that's accurate
Azure modernizing we should find better way
To modernize than the ones we've used
Which is a very sensible thing to do
But you know it's easy to paint with a broad brush and say like nope
No cars
Really easy
Because he did it in
20 words
Yep
So now we get into the at the end he was talking about how
Everyone wants to get involved peacock Network
Yes he does
Which actually I come up a couple times
I believe
Yeah no a great-aunt
You know like
Do you think do you think anybody's offered him a job
No one bigger than he is
I don't think okay
I don't think maybe at some point in the past like Fox News might have
Or something like that I don't think
Michael Savage had a show
I don't even know who Michael
Of the Savage Nation no idea
Horrible
It's like Alex Jones but without right hate
From an old Jewish dude
Actual name is Michael weiner
But
He calls himself we did good change himself The Savage Nation
Listen to all the time when I was younger
A wiener
He's going to go to prison
In
A tweener nation in there
Michael Savage
Is an amazing storyteller
Do you tell these stories about his daily life that were in
Gauging
Full of detail
Unfortunately was a hateful big
Fox News gave him a show
Like around 9
I think they gave it to him before but then it was canceled
Pretty close
Was imagine his anti-muslim bigotry would have gone weight
Too far even for
For them he made a guy cry on air
Jesus blew his Muslim who was just like
Still trying to have it it's like
A debate about stuff
He also had a gay rights activist on the told me hope he died of AIDS
Yeah
Yeah it sounds like they gave him a show on Fox News and then had to cancel it cuz it was f****** like
And I don't think Alex is nearly as bad as
Michael Savage
But I think I take those Networks
I think those networks learned a lesson from that
That was like
Hog and even Rush Limbaugh can't have it
TV show
Will get sued
He does do the live broadcast
That's not Food Network
Senor fox hunting
What would
So easy if he did go if else
I assumed he would lose
Just about all of his
Listener bass like using now
I think
It depends if you went to like a cable network I think you might be able to pull off some of the bulshit but he says
Independent credibility
25 years of
Isabel news out
Okay
Be specific
The point of this was I do believe him when he says that he doesn't want to go to
He says he wants to do is what he's doing
Hundred percent
Now we have agreed with Alex Jones I just want to give him a
So now he goes on to talk about other
Stuff that
Is maybe more.
I've been on air 21 years
Almost
In April
Say this to say I'm sorry
Kickback
I say this to you realized
Wall Street
Madison Avenue
All of them an offer
I've been in major
I just realized early on
Don't you love that Mama
Set the drunk moments
The Gorge
Because I'm still agreeing with him that idea that Wall Street has nothing to offer you
Independent this is LP
Ford
So far the only thing and that's it
He's not saying this
To make him sound like
Like a badass
Exactly
Movies I want to I am I did a little research
Credits
Documentaries like loose change
Who directed those or store funded
The three movies he's been in as an actor
Well he was into Richard linklater movies
As the guy driving around in the car screaming in a bullhorn
About how humanity is too good to be taken over by opposing forces
F****** cast
Equator Boston
Alex Jones when Alex was like a public access host
So whenever you started make movies
He always had like this
Image of this guy in his head
And to also he was in A Scanner Darkly
Both characters who are crazy people screaming on the street and bullhorn
Then called amerigeddon
Amerigeddon
He plays a minor role as a politician
It was directed by Chuck Norris's son
Another movie also features Infowars as a media outlet that tells the truth in a sea of Lies
David Knight
Plays the broadcast
Infowars in the movie
Being in this movie
Kind of his PR
Like being in it isn't it's not a major movie also it's amerigeddon
I watch the trailer
And it's Wacky Tacky hours on IMDb
I don't know I don't want to watch the whole thing behind
Thank God it's that as LSD
Ride that out
Here's the plot
A fictional depiction of a future where in a globalist terrorist organization aligned with the United Nations
To disable the United States power grid in insta
Tatuta martial law
It will take a dedicated family of Patriots
And the remains of the Second Amendment to save America and reclaim its freedom
Plot point in the movie took from the trailer is that The Army Goes Around
Wow
Which is just basically the wet dreams open till 1
Obsessed with the power grid
Keeps coming that keeps showing up here is that
He thinks that the power grid is
Only thing between us
And granddaughter Zombie Chaos
I don't
Things I've read I don't know I'm not next
The power grid is fairly vulnerable
Okay that could be attacked
Inner wave at
Would leave us
I mean like
It is it is someone you don't think about all the implication
Comes of it
Lakers effect that would go through like
Internet going down markets would that would suffer from it
The ability to around
There would be
If you're going to choose a paranoid fantasy that's not a terrible one
It's much better than like bird flu
Like
Although he was scared of Berkeley
Okay
Alright
Elizabeth Blackwell
Communist Chinese
Play Russia
But but here's a what
Is that in
Like if the globalist
We'll destroy them
More so than anybody else
Get down like
What would you even consider like
If it drops
15000 because of a
Powergrid meltdown
The entire world falls apart
Is a lot of war room to drop
I think the A's argument that he would make
Put words in his mouth but he would say that the globalist
Something know that they're going to do what they've made preparations for they have underground bunkers
They have
Supplies and Munitions and stuff like that
They can hide it out while the rest of us kill each other off in the street
Because
Because hunger sets in and you become an animal
Do you know how this happens in small-scale situation
I don't know like how when Russia invaded the Ukraine
I can just call it you
The Ukraine extreme risk
Seinfeld
Vietnam
So this happened
Situations like
Got any number of the
What always happens
And is not
Everybody starts killing
What always happens if people actually go
The band We're All in This Together We are all trying to say
Yeah
Channels that are normal because
Explode optimism doesn't sell
Survival supplies
Paranoia and fear is really the only marketing force that works when your business model is set up to
Anyway Alex Jones
And like I need to do a way better job of
This one's just called Integrity Rambo
So
Android
You want a book deal every year for free
10 million dollars
You want $10 for your contractor
You will be
The next Rush Limbaugh
I told no they said
I am
President
Program
I don't
You're going to turn down three.
That didn't happen
No
How much does he make
I assume that he threw out
1.8
Do not use doing that as roleplay
He was being the head of another Network offering him a job
Head of a network isn't making $2000000 a year
Really small in that one might be like
Like QVC even with
Cops
Liquid
Net worth
Listen to this I used to work at a lab
I am the owner like not even the owner of the lab but like the head of one of the departments in the lab made
So like
But like the idea that the head of a broadcast network isn't making two million a year is b*******
Are we talkin programming head cuz that's probably what
So we will be looking at
Let's just throw out a wind
For the major motion picture
What is happening
But before we go any further
I couldn't possibly
I could not have to
It's it's very mysterious
Cuz I don't think
Actually done a bunch of research
In the last couple days about his advertising model
I don't understand where the money is coming from
Necessarily
Millions of people are buying these weird supplement
I don't
Like
On his show there aren't
What time is that
What is website there are
So I don't know what's going on exactly
And like shows like Glenn Beck
Sean Hannity
They actually had waist smaller audience
They were being propped up by billionaire republicanism
For the longest time
Like even if the show isn't profitable
It's to their advantage if they have a fear-mongering monster
Throwing everything at the wall to see who's going to do it's conceivably the I think they would look at it as
Like through the antidote to NPR
Or something like that
That has been the model for very long time I think it's entirely possible.
Speak quickly I think he might be getting some sort of money from somebody some like Angel
Or something like that
I don't know I would say that a lot more people are buying this up
Bloomington
The amount of money that it would take to run his operation
Big
Yeah how many people does he have on staff
If you talk about just in front of the camera personalities there's at least like 7
I know there's got to be so
Behind-the-scenes crew editors
Cuz he puts out likes
So much f****** material
Like
Operation
It makes me
F****** SoJO
Quit like a
4 hours of the Alex Jones Show on a daily basis
And that he has Infowars Nightly News
Would you like another 2-hour show usually
Hosted by likely Ann McAdoo or one of the other
I love her so much
The classic Outlaw day but she's got big old big old titties
And I hate to say that because we just got done critiquing Alex for his
That's more just a reference to the days of yore
Sure and I would never
I just had on I-25
Maybe from
Several
Well-known
People from that set era
Call myself
Whenever starting
You know we're doing it
Pretty harsh criticism job apply to myself as well
To a higher standard than drunken Alex
My
Integrity
It's like saying
Would you give up your eyeball
Probably.
Wine
Totally would have money
School hero
That's a normal move somebody that's
Wake Ally
It is a partisan
That's what I don't get
Is it it's so clear to me
The world
Trailblazing
Resist
Arkansas pathetic I told dirty
My half-assed attempt
Who I am
So this is where we Greenwood just kicks in
What do you say at the end of there that's really where I think he's itching for drama
Set like
Yeah take out tomorrow that would be Independence that's what that was
Independence Day speech
Taking out the eye for a billion dollars that he's just suggested himself is a literal offer that someone's made
I mean white and also what would they
They probably put them in with the fetuses if they harvested and pizzagate
Well what I would do is put them into an Alex Jones
The great that you could look into
To the truth already stolen
If you steal his eyes
That's true makes perfect sense
I think you look you first came in with the Alex Jones is drunk Theory which is amazing
And then you come in with the second
I think you're killing it
Who's another note you made
Has anybody ever described a rocket scientist
Demerol
Debatable
Rocket scientist
I can think of one season of Survivor
He was f****** hot as s*** and it was a rocket.
For people on Medicaid
Work on on the Manhattan Project
I can't remember his name
He was a Satanist
Rocket scientist who got mixed in with Aleister Crowley
Crowley is absolutely bananas
Manhattan Project
F****** gorgeous about this clip is in the same way earlier he was like
That was when they were trying to get me into the club
Maybe they weren't
Who's the same moment of insecurity here where he's like
He's like
I don't think that what we're doing is that great
That was my half-ass.
I'm worried the name of the rocket scientist is Jack Parson
Okay
But do you think you the flavor
I didn't probably
Because Alex has some bad thing
Okay
Totally unhappy
That managers about to kill him
Mafia
I don't have that
Big houses
Kardashian
Closet
Pupils small
See here's the thing
I totally agree with him on that one hundred percent agree with absolutely
Listen to drunken introspection
Jvna
Threesome the others
Tim Gunn like
I don't know what
My half
This world
He's like
Maybe half an hour of tape away from saying I'm not sure
I'm making this up
Things that are like
Celebrity worship is kind of a toxic idea
Instead of having a celebrity
Name of the celebrities for the situation they're in
I'm secondarily
It's wacky to be like
The fund the founder
The foundation of Alex Jones is understanding of celebrity culture is the everyone
Who's famous has gone through like MK Ultra conditioning
They're all
Ritualistic abused
Maybe that's not fully what he believes but there's colonel.
Anything of handlers that will kill him to get out of Houston died
Okay Marilyn Monroe
Of course absolutely she's the original right before that but she's
Couches big one
Anyway
Agreed on the celebrity worship stuff
This clip
Is not over
Get
Weird
Excellent it is further proof
Tickets might be dropped
It doesn't
Okay we get a glimpse into his psyche and what life he would like to be living and it's
Rain
You might have with my dad cuz I think you're going to blow glass
I don't care
Power Trip
I've been
The top
Top
Farmhouse
Fields around
Growing
Now keep in mind we have to finish the clip butts
His what I think is fake crying
Is what's going on
He's doing the hand over the face and they like
Kind of noises but yeah it
He's presenting crying
Coronavirus video
Final
Part of this.
A holster
Otherwise much like there I thought I thought there was more it's just a farmhouse
Filter supposed to be agrarian apparently
If that's your fantasy I mean to me the first thing I thought of was
He thinks of himself as Russell Crowe in the movie Gladiator
That's what's happening
Movies
Can you toss me my coat safely without knocking this over
Absolutely
This is
Dude Perfect
Okay so he's sounds
So f****** depressed
Can Alcoholics Anonymous meeting
The desk
He's like his the top
Rain being
Famous and in the system that's the bottom
Where he's at
At the top baby
Here's something that I want to propose
A potential
Amerigeddon
Three major motion picture
Suggestions of will give you a 3 million-dollar book deal every year
The bottom
Three-year contract for ten million they offered him a lot Alex
So I think
I think this assessment that he's pretty depressed
Might be right on and here's what I want to suggest in terms of if we look at the narrative
Before he left for break
Right before he left for break
This is
And I think
There was a piece in his head that he thought he was going to die
Really
I think that there's a chance that he thinks
This is his last message
Supply Maybe
Because I don't know I don't know still haven't established whether or not we believe he believes what
We're still in this Labyrinth
Is he is he playing us does he believe it does he believe some of it as we would like another communist
Bolivar like a just a
Propaganda onions
It's insane I want to know I want to know more about
I genuinely want to go to a bar with him
And just listen to him talk in a I'm not sure you do
Maybe that's a good point
Cuz he act like this when he's drunk
Wellbutrin
This is
This is fascinating
A bummer
Which is kind of why I have this little turtle of thought that maybe he thinks he's
Going to die
If you look at it through that prism
It's fascinating
It's fascinating because it's like
What would your last message be if you had a flock
And this is what he chooses to do
If you look at it through that lens
It's super bizzarri started by shiting on Megyn Kelly
But it makes sense why you wouldn't talk about Ruby's Diner
I wish I lived in a farmhouse in new my neighbors
Like this sort of thing kind of comes into focus a little bit
Bristol Moravian die
Why am I
Feeling sorry for Alex Jones
I think we have empathy within our hearts and
The others don't
You goes on from nothing out in between those two clips talks about how we should live in farmhouse
How's the newer Neighbors
Into this next thought
Which he liked the band
He would hate them
You would hate to have a good song
Highlights
One of their songs
I think you realize that he's forgotten that
He's doing the political show
He had to jump back to politics
And he says one of the things that I think is this
Rangers
I've even heard come out of his mouth
Get your butthole ready
Trump doesn't
Superhot
He does that
Because he knows.
And its whole life
Plan
Wow
Unpack that f****** settings
So this
The whole Trump thing
Has been age
Sleeper Cell
What's Bronx from
Baby
From her
From birds
Okay now is he is striving
Trump
Consciousness
From
More less
One of the front birth I'm being I'm being hyperbolic but when did he think this plan came up because
Trump has been Rich since
Yes
But he's not into it
Although every indication all of his behavior
I mean obviously he's really good because that's being rich
Because he knows it because he knows that we're trapped in materialism
And that that is what's going to
Empresa that's what's going to endear him to us
He's like
He's a good man
It's like it's bad
Yo that's a good point
That maybe Trump
Is not the man he thinks
I'm going to bed I'm just bending someone who's undefendable
To some extent I think I think there is that that that glimmer there
Also has to have started to figure out
That
All of the stuff that he
Thought Trump was going to
To do he's signaling that he's not going to do
I don't think he's starting to
Figure that out
So you don't think so
In much the same way that I do believe there are forces
Behind the scenes
That are a bit more nefarious
Fan are being presented
I think Alex might
Be
He might become a
He might also be compromised
Okay
I don't mean he was on Russian television
Being told American
What an americanism is over
So long and stupid
Don't go there
Don't give them any more twice
Definitely don't mind
I'm not saying for sure that he is and I don't want to speculate cuz
Obviously there's no evidence
Change so dramatically about Trump
That it does bring into question like what
What is going on
I was watching clip with him earlier today
He was talking about how Ted Cruz and Sarah Palin would be a perfect ticket
He literally was saying you was having wet dreams
About that being a ticket he was like
It's insane like to go from that head Cruise
Is so big a jump
Yeah let me that clip was in like a late 2015
So it's not like
That was
Decades ago
That it's bizarre
The the
Compromising this is from Trump himself
Or from Rodger Stone
Do you think Trump gives him a lot of problems
Oh yeah
Okay
No
Talk about this
For one of the ways you can compromise
Like without any threat due to butter up there you go
As Trump shown any inclination towards
Putin
Okay that's good compliments Putin all the goddamn time
I don't know
Trump was on Alex
So he appeared on the show when he was running
No thank you
Basically
You're going to be really excited
About me
I won't let you down
That kind of that was the center
Fajita
No but you also talks about how the good work that he's doing if you believe the things that Alex
Trump called him to thank him for his help after he wants okay
Bli
But that does seem like something that is plausible
Definitely
Put no
No I think you did way too far into the world of like speculation and it's
You're right we need a plan that Trump has had
Yeah it's to put together this entire persona
Well
In order to trick us into loving him
Isn't the whole
Supposed to be in like a benevolent
Decent person actually like you
The people who don't like him
Are the ones that
Are mostly like aren't they the ones who Heath
Thinkserver into celebrity culture
Yeah it's convoluted
Let It Go
It is like a weird
Ouroboros when you unpack the the logic
Well cuz there's no
He pretended
To be like that loving richness and all this to get in with the Insiders only two double
Across them
At this point now that he's president
That I think that's the underlying like if you want to put it in a sentence
Yes but it's for the Patriots
Do The Manchurian Candidate For the true American
Who art brainwashed by the globalist
Alex Wassabi
But has he
So-so
With no
Previous
Inclination that this is happening
Because all of Trumps tax
Up until this point have been
I love Trump
I'm a big fan of trump
And a lot of positions he's probably taken have been contradictory to
He has an hour to what
Goldman
But
They have golden confirmation bias
Behind the scenes
Whole everybody
Has been everybody has been working
Toward this exact
This is the most important moment in human history
Let's give him some credit
And say Trump didn't have this plan
Until he was
Maybe I go as far back as we can reasonably go
Trump has this plan
At the same time
All of these other people develop this exact same plan
They eventually get this plan
To bring us all to this point where they've successfully
Trick
Everyone into worshipping money
Yeah
And now
Now
They're going to go back on literally their entire life
Yep
To protect the Patriot
The true message of America
Yes
What is the truth Maybe
Maybe we already heard it
No other life
Okay the secret of 2017 that is that all of your Newsradio episode
The Secret of management yes it's kind of like that
With stupid it reminds me of that it cuz it's like okay
This is supposed to be about the secret of 2017 if we want to give a full breakdown
Is that Megyn Kelly is ugly
Ruby's Diner is where Alex Jones proves he's a good man
Obama criticized because he's black
And he doesn't want people to have cars
Alex has been in big movies he hasn't billion dollars to cut his eye
Celebrity worship sucks farm houses are cool
Amazon website
Yeah it's all the plan
But we're not done
More
I don't really remember with his foot all the label is
Hypocrisy so we'll see you there
Because I said we should be healthy
Because I say we shouldn't
It doesn't me
I don't do all the things
Experience
Okay that's
That is the most correct label
To do but I can't
I got
I'm turning down major movie Motion Pictures
I'm doing it what
Bhatiji Moses he ever
Where did GMOs come from
What do you mean he said I'm telling you not to eat GMOs
Those fake Foods
But where is robot from
He believes that like Monsanto
Poison
Next Level don't produce their own self-destructive happy
Which is maybe the most evil thing I can ever
Conceive of is like
Where were drug dealers birthday
We had the idea of
Making
Salmon more likely
Being real
Stingy with water
Those two things I think are fundamentally literally evil
Literally
You're literally tying lives now to money
No longer no longer any subsistence
At all it is
Purely
Oligarchical money stretch
Tying
Poverty that like morality of being like you're bad people cuz you're poor
Who's that came out was like if you can't afford birth control you shouldn't have sex
What the hell
That's an argument 30-40 years ago they would've been like
Have you tried the Rhythm method
Stood by a Catholic
Just stimulate the Rhythm
If you are legitimately against abortions
You are a f****** hypocrite
If you're against birth control
You are a massive
Massive hippo
Yeah morning after pills and stuff like that would eliminate 100% of
As we all learned
Jurassic Park
Life finds a way
Anyway this is not over yet not by a long shot
List
This biscuit
But the only setup you need
Ears on her demise
Of what is
In the potentiality of
Look at every
Weave.
I love doll
I love tigers I love Allison from Magic
They aren't one
But the problem is is that
An elephant
It doesn't have those Lowe's
We can go to the very bottom of her
Mahec legitimate
Also does not know how do
What do you mean, like dolphins
Spell outfit
They do love fish
Santa's a key thing in the animal world
Lincoln Center the weird thing for them
That is
Definitely Kenneth Branagh
Dramatic speech right there
I love dolphins
What the f***
Why can't I get his sort of like
Look animals are cool
But they are capable of what we are
We can be the devil
Or we can connect
It's like it's forced
Profundity
Weird
Such a weird
What supplements shedfat
Supports your
You know like this is his last missive
Before I death row
Spirit of evil
Laying
Very smart
These churches
She's talking about how this is something that I actually think
Is really dangerous
In the same way that
They try and demonize the Press
I like know where the real threat
Single
Today Trump started
Like to have this whole thing where he's trying to
Take out the Associated Press from literally saying that
You're the only voice aloud
Yeah Vivid that
Referencing specific churches
Probably Oliver
To that was he's more talkin about
Not literal churches but like the church
To know he's talking about literal churches
Because if he's talking about like the megachurch
Like those whole things you might actually be in
Really but don't
Evil
We know that cuz we've been to them as children
Do you love prosperity
That's true also Prosperity is
Maybe I don't know
F****** hard to unpack is this inherent contradictions everywhere
But here's the thing
When you talk about like these churches being evil
I'm stuff like that
I think there's a really
FairPoint you can make about like child abuse in the Catholic Church
I think there's
Fairly abusive things done to people in almost Church
In terms of brainwashing in terms of
No just sort of foundational problem
Organized religion
That's not what he's talking about he's talking about the message of Christ has been bastardize by these churches
But he understands the
True
Okay which is
But of course he gives zero bastardization
Example
But it's also like in the early church
They would do and that's why
People rebelled against
It was that
Back in the day there would be the priest who had the holy of holies
The center of the church where he could communicate with God everyone else
What God wanted
Them to know which is a great
Beautiful stamps
And that's sort of reformation happen
No I'm not saying that he's going to be like only I can talk to God
He's like
Only I have I have the right
View of it
And if you agree with my view of it then your right to
Situation going on here
Fitness hits
3 days before
Churches
Humble yourself
Destiny
That's a creepy f****** sense
Just said the enemy is basically everything
Everything all institutions
I've been corrupted
Yeah
By the new world order by the Illuminati by the globalist
By these evil forces
I may have
Twisted the messenger
They've twisted
The message of freedom
Which
I mean
It's not like that's a like that's not an insane thing
To stay in a
Smaller sense
Yeah cuz all of these things
Power corrupts absolute power corrupts absolutely
Absolute lambiyaan institutions are just collections of people if you have bad people
That is inherently good
The institution will turn back I mean you can have a single church with bad people in it now you got to bed
I want to get into the humble yourself before
Yeah boy
Utopia
Is if everybody
Just humble themselves as Alex understand
Is Alex does himself because
No never
Cheat yourself
What you're doing is just evil
You're just being mislead
It sounds like he's such an absolutist
Like there's no
Later he's David koresh
That's what's funny you should say that
No that's not the next next time I swear to God I would have killed myself right now
Incident
Call
Oh really
Really isn't Texas
Waco isn't super far from Austin
That was a serious overstep and
Really f***** up the cult was really f***** up what happened
Direct
Way too which is an even weirder and he has all kinds of ideas about how Clinton was
Personally involved and had to cover up cuz they were child sex Rings involved I like that
The conspiracy that he's dreamt up
Evolved over the years but that was like
Waco to him
Was
What year was Alec 92
I have no idea
That was when he was sort of like
Just starting
To get these ideas
That's probably when he was in junior college
The timeline correct
And that was when he was starting
To get
Read that book none dare call it conspiracy and all this stuff starts to Bubble Up in his head
It becomes the
Okay
After years of pressure cooking
This is where we find ourselves
Because to me like just going by our last episode whenever you talked about
The Y2K
He seems more like just a
Conspiracy theories
Yep just like
I am throwing all this stuff at the wall
To tell you
Survival
And gold angle
At that point
Instead now this is a
A full-on
Cult leader message
There's no
Because in this
Missive
As we all know is where Russia
Trucking radar blockers
Cuz I go down
There's no sales
There's no sales pitch
No do you hear any sales pitch
It's one of the longest stretches I've ever heard him talk without bringing up iodine or super male vitality
Fear
Loathing and
Depression
That might be a snapshot of his soul
Really sad
Feel really bad for him if he's in this headspace and it sounds like really is
It does seem that way the first time I've heard him and I thought this
Rings so genuine
I also believed every single thing
I also should say if you were watching the video you would see that the guy is a little fish
Maybe his body language doesn't
Support the
I'm not disagreeing with your conclusion but if you watch the like body language there is like a bit of Showmanship
After 22 years in April
But I think that what is important
That we can take away
Is that like
This is kind of what happened
When you go down these roads
These conspiracy Road
What ends up happening is it evolve
When you wear a mask long enough the mass becomes
Sure
It's more than that you also wear an outfit
It's not just the mask anymore
It becomes something different
In the movie of Alex Jones
Yeah
Who plays him
What does he wear
Cuz we're talking about somebody with a low
We're talking about I would say if it were me
Sir Anthony Hopkins
Rush it
To all no way Anthony have
Can play any age I would say let's Meryl Streep say we f*** around
Okay Alex always talks about how back-in-the-day he was a great athlete
And you could have gone pro
No I'm not leaving
We got to go younger I'm stuck
Table
Let's stroke Alex's eco
The guy from f****** Magic Mike's to play you you sign onto this.
You get him I think he can do voices
Channing Tatum if not
He just lip-synch that we get a domian to do it
That yeah that would work this voice Perfection probably already does
Equals
Anyway Alex has one last
I bet here
I don't want to be clear I cut up
Very little
I made sure to not cut out anything between these clips that has to do with Khan
Nothing
Was lost
In the shuffle if you watch the video it's a little bit longer
But I have not betrayed
The spirit of this
Anyway
Alright
All right I just have to say that because
Again if this hole like internalizing
Yeah I have to
This Waverly
Anyway
F****** hard to do
And it's so hard
Here's his Farewell to this
Clip
This whole video
By the end of it we'll see if we know the speaker
And in that experience
Everything
What's good
Wetransfer
And this whole world
I will always be
Spirit
Come to kill this
We are the garden
We could prove ourselves
Film
Modesto
And that's the end of the video
Okay
Welcome
I think he would do a great job there
His head shape is Right bald
How tall God
Okay
I think Chris Pratt's got to robust ahead
We're making Kelly and Chris Pratt
Will fantasy book this movie
So
That sounds
So much
Like the
Prayers that my
Dad
Has before like
The prayers of our fathers
Classic
If you were raised
Kind of
Rindge Church in the 80s
Clearly
I'm not sure about that he might have been
Yeah but he might have adopted it later so the Reformation
My dad still doing it
It's not like it's gone
No like you can pick it up in a lot of
At the same time
Trying to be humble while giving yourself all of the Power
It's it's like it's like
You
Need to Humble you
Set yourself before
And I already have
Is dependent on you
But God has nothing to do with it until your
Yeah
Turn your will over to God
But God doesn't have any control over that's such a weird way of thinking about it
Do you know your hard biblical Calvert Calvinism
Fascinating
Feces really bums
Cuz that is not
That's not what he's
Really
He doesn't understand what the species
Nope
He's not a scientist
Healing
Find to know
Which as we all know there are tons of
Assessment is not taking into account that he's again crying
At the a
And when he's when he's talking at the end here at ear does go down
Like the Italian play the Native American in the commercial likely like that member of our species
Species member
What do you is the secret of 2017
I need I need to know what you think you have a lot of scriptnotes
Listen to Amy rittenour twenty or so of breaking down this video I promise
I didn't edit out the actual Secret
This isn't some game show now we're in the match game
Butter pie crust
Without
Even throw in at the end like a support their Network or anything like that
Unified field theory of all the bachelorette things it's very disjointed
What is the connectivity
I feel like I'm the zodiac
Pictures up on the wall tying them together like Sherlock like-for-like
Eventually I'm going to have to buy like a weird chalkboard yesterday photo stuff up
Glenn Beck
So
The enemy is every
Government
He can't
To the things that he tells you to adhere to
Is unsalable
He knows the truth unfair
But he can't move it
He's really depressed
That's the secret
Because
It seems like
Here's here's what I'm putting all this together as I hope it's the same thought
It is that
He doesn't understand how to win
After winning
Yeah because the whole thing is actually building an opposition
Lost the opposition
He doesn't have any
So he's really depressed because
The government that he has been railing against
Is now what he wants you to believe in
Tell you that they are all an enemy are there Aldi
Global
I think my response perfect my response
I think he is
Bingo
That's really what I think the message is I don't know who I am now
Dana Goldberg about
Astronauts
If you gone to the Moon
Everything after that must be completely a letdown like her
Oh man I'm getting these
Double a batteries
I use these when I want
I think that's an unfair comparison to that pic because I don't really think
Achieve that much
I think to him
He ended anti-American
Well that's true
He's achieved a lot more than even if you believe literal Russian propaganda
Space command
I think
That
There's also a change of buyer's remorse
Thrown in there
Okay
There's a little bit of I didn't want it to go this way
I might be putting too much on him
Yeah right
I didn't want to win
Or something like that is just a like
We got play a different game now
Alright
The only way to do it is now changed the entire narrative to be like
Well
You know who's good at playing from the bottom
Globalist
That has to be the net like there's there's no other way to do it
What's the defense but it also turns into when you're this sort of
Becomes witch
Something that I think is particularly scary
It's it's
Tort jump
You don't remember McCarthyism fun
No I'm pretty sure that I read a book where is like
Who wrote that Rob do a
We'd like to would like to say you're welcome for explain to you guys the Seeker
Only 17 if you have any different interpretations of what the secret might be please reach out to us at Nala
Underscore fight on Twitter
Also you can send us an email directly at knowledge fight gmail.com
Absolutely I hope you guys enjoyed it
To discover the sea
We'll be back later this week so please get excited for that
I'm excited to hear what you got to say
Love you love to hear about your trip
I'd love to know if you're feeling better cuz
The ship
It was bleak
And even if we are kind of we don't see eye-to-eye
Still care about you as a person Alex
Gacha next time
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work