Alexandra Thurston color
We are a couple dudes you like to sit around and drink and have conversations about
Come upon Our Land
The plague that is
Popularization of Alex Jones
That was that was really defeatist I'm in I'm in a grim place
We will come to realize why throughout the course of this episode
Clearwater
There's problems
That's really problematic and terrifying
2/3
The inevitability of climate change
An infinite amount of
Gigi's smoke creeping nationalistic fervor and putting us
Nope that's not why
Like I said I don't want one
No it's because of what the trend
We're going to be looking at in this episode of the show
I watch Alex Jones
It is show everyday
Have you I do not
Particular
Do use a condom which is smarter
Exactly I'm in there Raw
Evan infowar Raw
Today we're going to be discussing
April 4th April 14th
But as is our tradition
Here is an out-of-context drop of Alex Jones
Songs from that show
We don't either
If no idea
This actually this this episode actually has like
Maybe
Candidates for out-of-context drop along the way
Tapestry
Situation
On Friday
April 14th
Yes I noticed a trend and that is the most
Of the week
Is boring as s***
Eman Alex Goes balls out at the end of the week
Like Thursday and Friday are generally like let's and actually get to work
Monday
Sunday is where he says things that you shouldn't say he said he like
You did that pizzagate apology on Sunday
He's got that's where he buries stuff is on Sunday casinos Bose wireless
Monday through Wednesday are just
Kind of like
Let's introduce the narrative
Hit the greatest hit
Absolutely
Send them to Abu Dhabi
How do you thicken rogerstone off the table
I don't know we're getting a Nixon tattoo on his back
Davis together
So
This week
It was pretty boring
No
Exciting
April 11th show from from Tuesday
So that was kind of
Interesting this week but that was just because I was having a little bit of a breakdown
Yeah and that was
Waco
It is just this boring stuff it's like
Siri
Syria's Ally
Dropping the Moab
Well apparently from a mile out it explodes
Don't get close to the mother of all Bob Butts
The most beef
So on Friday
On a MOAB
Jump right on there right it down like Slim Pickens
How come the Alex Jones hasn't done
A cover of
Purple
Okay what time
Used
Some country should 22 means he's in a weird place
Come out
So on Friday at the end
Of his show
Login
Deflecting a little bit from him having to carry too much of the weight
For most of the show yet Mike cernovich on
Okay who is Mike cernovich
Mike cernovich
That is a great question
Is grape okay alright that's the long and short of it
He's been a friend weirdo he does a lot of periscopes
He was really into the
The TV show
He is a journalist he loved the movie Down Periscope I'm putting journalists in heavy
Pierre quotes
Suspect
Contingent
In the White House is leaking information to
Suspiciously is he the one where Trump was like he should get a Pulitzer
Jeff broke broke the Susan Rice
Trump says you deserve
It's not super interesting but sticks around
That works great
I can't remember most beautiful
Fourth wall break
Slater's a real man
I would love by the alt right
Be a great housewife is all I'm
Alright at knowledge underscore
She's too uppity
She's out there talking about semitism
You took that to real I did as foreshadowing
Mike cernovich is on for quite a while and then the third hour they bringing Gavin or Nigel McGuinness
Oops Tavis
The rest of this episode as a show of disrespect
But his name is Gavin
Sound Advice
Iowa
They Trot around is like
Some sort of amazing
Credit Insurance
I mean
Come on now
I don't actually know anything about
I don't know anything about the inner workings of it but I've read a lot of articles
And it seems like
People who has an olive
What's their in-house editorial
I think it's
Like incompetent
Hana Restaurant
But kind of how I would describe a lot of their journalism
Okay I understand
Does he bumble around to shooting is gonzo
It's done on it but by and large it's like
Very young people who are much
It's Jack
A tripod
Bulshit
Oh s***
And
Dannon
Return
That is what we're going to be
Discussing when do you three men map
Alex Jones Show
Comes out of their mouth
They're all the same
We Human Centipede
We were starting to show I was telling you that I'm in a little bit of a weird state
Yes this is why
I think
That they're consolidate
Now
The vice people are going to absorb
We just f****** hilarious
More life
Born Gavin
Mike cernovich and Alex Jones
Thoroughly
Emerging in terms of their businesses merging
But it is sort of like
A rogue's gallery coming together to our Batman
Are Batman
Looks like a team coming together
And it's really f****** scary
Cuz this idea of the propaganda
Just working together
Create
Unlimited potential of audiences
Emerging
You know it's the same thing with Alec being on Joe Rogan and not being challenged
His ideas
It's that same sort of thing
Consolidated Echo chamber where they
Can each repeat back
The b*******
But not completely
Olive
Vanderbilt incredibility understand their audio
So they give Alex Jones by proxy credibility
Likes proxy credibility
It becomes a really dangerous
So
And I don't like what it's worth
Good news
No tunnels
These people are f****** released
So it will be easy for us to
To cut through a lot of their bulshit
But
It's still scary that they're amassing hordes
Follow them and combining
It's around in Skyrim
Now let's get
The first one
Is maybe the most delicious of them
I like calling clips
Tell me more
Delicious
Especially when they start
And
Look look at Czar Nicholas or
What was Edward the 8th father's name Gavin McGinnis you don't think he has a lemon chasing around 8
Every part of me
That happening
You know like that
I would totally be gay with you
As long as Irish Guinness has a novelty facial hair that would cause Alex Jones to
To scream for 20 minutes if it was on the CNN reporter
Beard and mustache that's a little too long for the length of beard
So you have a little bit of like prop mustache going on with his beard
To the point where the guy that he screamed
Mr. creepy mr. creepy over here on CNN
Not the same but
It's enough that if
He was someone who Alex was against kyuubi like probably does
Tax records
He's on his side
He wants to f***
So that means
Secretly wants to
Tupac the guy on
Perfect
Betrayed
Now we get to the beginning of this
Conversation that they're all having a
Again I'm doing this purpose
I know his name
Nigel McGuinness comes in
With
He's really on evolve to take
And hack
Comedy
About gay
Yeah
I remember the eighties to I remember Adam Carolla in 96
Verbatim that bit
If it weren't for the sex
It's just hanging out with you
Your friends like that's from
The Larry the Cable Guy
White Collar Comedy Blue Collar Comedy
Yeah yeah
Absolutely
Like Zacchaeus lamest things and Alex's are sponsored
Fake laugh
Glass that he does throughout this
It's crazy
But then also
It's
Productive in this idea that gay couples don't fight
It's really insulting the idea of a assuming that
Gay people art
Real people
Just some sort of magic
No
Get along all the time
Assuming that homosexual relationships
Are identical to platonic friendship
I think they are
Yeah and I think that's exactly what Alex
I know that he's
Knifeworks
I don't remember which is my whims
He is coming at I know that he's doing this for humor
Which is not doing a good job
One of the happiest if you want
Horribly reductive and insult
Yes
Cereal we're not just going to laugh at any bulshit
Yeah congratulations on failing
My man
My bro my bro
You failed us both Gavin and
Make some predictions about what's going to be happening over the weekend
In Berkeley
Lauren Southern
Home Depot
Bikers old keepers
English
Extinguish
How'd you do
Extinguisher
Minutes the softest area that's most attackable probably that would kill you
You're not going through the chest cavity with flagpole
I'm at the light of life
English
But he said there was nothing controversial going
So why would they get those life
That's crazy right
Celebrating free speech
In a way that I'm sure does not curtail the right
Nobody going to Home Depot
Torious Lee violent
Trust fund children
I every time I go outside I just see yet another trust fund child
Take this
This is McGinnis coming home
First of all
Reportage
You just never reporter at the Home Depot all or did you pick up migrant workers
Articles
I don't know
Can you
Keep us posted if any well-to-do kids are buying the weird things
To come to this conclusion over and over again that McGinnis is
I'm just popping up
And giving these anecdotal stories that I don't know how he
Could know anybody if he doesn't know don't mean anything but he uses it to prop up his stories
And it's b*******
This is why Rappaport
H
Home Depot bushes right now
Where do you think he knows all these Scoops you're making a really great argument here because I should say that John Rappaport wasn't on
On assignment
There's almost no doubt about it
Any definitely
Take that picture
Is going to be trouble
If it's Patriots
March on Saturday
What I understand a little bit
The afternoon
Everyone I understand there's a little bit of attention
Little bit uneasy
I imagine there are going to
B fight
The Breakout
Disagree with him at all there's going to be
In trouble
The okay
Hardcore
Keep off
But you know how this goes with that Milo situation there were agent provocateurs in the crowd
Who are largely working with alright organization
Some of them even employed
Directly
Buy them
Because
I don't want to use the same
Sort of argument that they use erroneous
I don't
Problem
But I don't
Exactly
They say is
Insanely
Ahead of us
Then anytime
A protest protest
Now it's a defensive
It's so
Angry
Seems like we're being outsmarted
Not super Proactiv
Like if we could do this show everyday
And really analyze things
Maybe we could
Do not get ahead of the 8-ball somewhat
We have job
We live our lives
Paid protesters
There you go there's a protest
We're just we're just outsmarted the argument
Who's there
Paid protesters
Just Gallimore
You know what it is
Pizza pair
Beats three-of-a-kind
Yelling the whole bunch beets
Game of Poker that we're playing
Anyway
Apparel
Yeah be nice
Anyway
Here's Mike cernovich coming in
Choose between
Berkeley
What episode
The choice to not do that
Thing that might hurt
I predict he actually asked Alex if he could come into Studio
Enable f****** up
Some guy in a black ski mask
Is going to come up punch the s*** out of me
Spencer all over again
But I am saying that every time I see
See the gif
Richard Spencer
I groped my heart grows
Three sizes
No it stops
I wish I could be there covering
Completely
But it's great to have that convenient
I could be there
The guy at the bar saying like holy back
And just grabbing onto his friends at the bar who's like
I could have made it I could have been in the show
You know just
Thumb something happened
I got fat
I got fat and turned out that didn't help I was trying to protect the woman in a bar fight otherwise I'll be playing probe
Ball but I'm a hero
No that's okay
Going in covering this place
Or I could go to Alex
And be treated like a hero in an air-conditioned Studio
I'm going to go with that one
Yeah that's
So pretty
That's pretty easy
Cernovich has take on it now Gavin has some some other thoughts that are a little bit
They're all rich kids are sons of professors
Losers With No Parental Guidance
Any forces are going out there and you can tell when you see
Funny thing they do is they putting women in the front line
Any guy
For the inauguration
When will Robert
This one
Just said that he started beating women having to push them off
Yeah I know that didn't happen for a number of reasons
Forest it didn't it didn't happen is that there's no video
Everything is out there
There's a video of him embarrassingly drunk
From that
The woman's March MP3
Also
They're putting the women out front it was in DC was the f****** women's March
All of those women together
Only with the permission of
The most feminists you might actually be pretty close to what McGinnis
Thanks
Of course it's what they say
Especially
Steve of a world where women are on
Especially McKenna
Menu
Evil masculine Force
And we're going to get to it
But like
I really
Really resent the idea that they're they're sort of
Presenting it as
What is a put
Front is human shield
Where I
The reality is
That
A lot of liberal causes women are leading
And we're comfortable
And we're super comfortable with that
I am supporting
Causes that women I'm not afraid of female leadership
Masculinity
You can't believe
Because that starts
If women
Can actually
Leave these March
Without
Other
Without the
Right even if
That they have to spend the narrative otherwise their brain
Like whoa
Riches
Decisions for themselves
Probably
That doesn't make any goddamn sense
Speaking of Gavin McGinnis his mind he has
Quote when they're talking about this idea
Cussing liberals attacking them having to fight them off
Which is going to take us down a very fun Road
What is the matter with you
Now
Jordan Jordan
Do you know what the proud boys are
No
I don't know I'm not sure those words next to each other
What metal band
It was a song from musical Aladdin
Be proud of your boy
That's what it comes from
I think that's what it comes come from
The proud boys
Masculine group of people that this guy knows
Name
From The Aladdin music
From what I understand
That's like how the KKK has
Dragon
What are you doing
Now
You can be this
Childish
Looking filled with delight and
And turn it into such
We're going to talk about a bunch about the proud boys now
The proud boys
Are an organization
I don't know I haven't listened
The proud boys are an organization
That is basically
From what I can tell
A really awful fraternity
Really
Awful man
How they put out a video
Is Matt
Just a regular
They put out a video
That I'm going to play part of
I want I want you to listen carefully
Gavin put this video out
Alright
Some of them are in their 40s
Summer the authorities
Alright if anyone ever says like that kids in his parents basement
40 year old boy
Playing at children
It's worse than you think
Of course it is now listen to this this is the beginning of their Sizzle reel
That they put on YouTube
They're probably looking to do that right I might watch it I mean I watch the Bad Girls Club
There's no end to what I would watching television everybody watch The Proud boys
Become consumed
And I'm confident
What no
How much you play time of your life
Giant pussies
F*** it
Price
You know
And the West is under siege
Shelter us from fry
Paying for it
This is a shity Zach Braff
From Scrubs
Overlays
Horrendous overlays
I'm playing with his baby
And stuff like that
Give it a break
So
Give it a rest
Just take a sip of the wine and just enjoy the rest of this important to show how much of an idiot this guy
Alright and what kind of
Crazy masculine Messiah complex
That's insane
Actual tenets where we have to
Restitution for our sins
I really want is for everyone to stop
Crying about the winners
Cologne
Quitting masturbating
And quitting p***
Call Ash Dad no way
Prison
Give everyone a gun
And Welfare close the borders
Recognize
Shutdown
We all want
We all want to get better
What's the name of our moon
I got
Call
F*** you
No
Like video dudes
Proud boys tattoos dark
Music video
Itsblitzzz
It's necessary
Imagine
Imagine a world
You know how much better my life with your life
Joyous
I mean yeah the world was going to end
Salvadoran rigano
Look at it
Look at the darkness Jordan
Don't deny the darkness
That are deal breakers
It's for me
Don't fuc
Quit my job
Don't f*** with my dog tootles
And don't fuc
My Little Pony app
VIP
The beginning about a week
I'm a proud boy
And I'm proud
What's My Little Pony
People who want to be left alone in the
Who won't leave them
How about the people who want f****** roads
How do you outlaw
Without some sort of authority
Government
Also how vague is venerate the housewife
Mother up on the goddamn abroad have a job
It's not that she doesn't have a job
I hate I hate
Condom
Is a complete and utter nonsense
F****** punch
In the face
A Milli
Hold on calm down we got to get to this next clip which sort of
Nigel McGuinness philosophy
What do you like to seeing as you've pointed out
There's there's no way for him to do the things that he wants to do I within his own
Don't have a sense of what these proud boys are
So now we got to take a look at that
I'm not going to use any of the words that I have
Proud boys
Would you like me no
Listen
Adjectives this video explains a little bit
Focusing on this game and having meet up
F****** secret handshakes
Yeah initiation game
No he's saying let's beat the
The s*** out of each other
He just wants a Fight Club he wants to jerk himself off of pilani
That's basically what's going on here
So not that point of the video it goes to show
It's
I looked into a bunch of
I like I looked into the poison I was like what's going on
I found a ton of videos
Of their initiation ceremony
I wish you would have
No
Pulling up
Here's the audio of one of them
It begins with the proud boys pledge
Because people need to hear this
I am a western chauvinist
Apologize for creating
Pottermore
So you heard that there was a modern
Western chauvinist
Who refuses to apologize
For having created the modern world
Which is f****** horrible
A proud boy
You're hearing some slaps
And that is their initiation ceremony which is everybody gets around the initiate and they all just pain
Pontius
Like really good
Are the guys just started laughing
Haha and here we got pulled up please
Cool.
You were so Furious
Reddit
So whenever they're getting potties
The only set of fox the only one Twitter
Everyone's afraid
The only bright
Who tickle each other and f******
What is what
F****** is that
The f*** is that
Rage
Watching angry about every single moment of my life is now
Pain forever
People who run the world
No
No let me go
This is my advice
To Every Woman
Kill all men
Put more money into genetic
And just f******
Move on without
You guys will be fine cuz there's a segment of the population that's in toothpaste
I feel like I need to fully explain what's going on
So there's this dude to explain what's going on
Punching him into the group they're all just punching
Jerking
The only the only way for it to
Then wait for the punching to stop
Is for the initiate
To name five things in a certain category that someone yells out
So in that instance it was cereal
Yeah and he was yelling out the names of cereals
Circle of Death
Play in college
Category time
Note to just recording from the movie
Ariel
Totally real video video
Do not act like this in real life
The video that I just played you were the guys listening all cereals and getting slapped
At the end of it there's a title card that says video produced by Gavin McInnes
This is directly from him
Here's the other thing
I found a bunch of other initiation videos
At one of them
It's so f****** funny
Cuz they're like
I can't remember what the five the category
But he's like naming them
And then some guy accidentally punches him in the face
Biodomes for these f******
How worthless pile of human garbage to masculinity
Punched in the face like that's the worst thing that could possibly happen
You don't know these body shops to prove that you're a man and one guy punches you in the face
Yes
It's not for your face so beautiful
I hate all these old men reclaiming their masculinity
Peppa
The theater of Western show
Yeah
Done
You know what
I dunno what the only way this makes sense
Is this
Is if white people were genetically engineered
It's totally possible
You understand
This is what
Nigel McGuinness is all about
This is his group
Pictures
Horrendous
It's somewhere
Somewhere between a drum a dumb drunk pussyfoot
Fraternity
And Fight Club
It's somewhere in the middle of an ambivalent Fight Club
4 dudes who filled dispossessed
I'm feel like they don't have any masculinity
Walking Among Us
The proud boys
If I find a proud boy tattoo
I am going to
BP on that tattoo
Ariel
A human being yourself
Or at our Gmail
Number of words
Like
I hate to seem like a lot of really repressed homosexuality to
They're always without shirts on and s***
There's nothing wrong with the
No not at all
As we all know
Doesn't get stronger than them know super homoerotic
I don't know wrestled or something but they were the f****** proud boys
They're so proud
Proud boys
What does even a specialized mean
Call yourself the f****** butter
Butterscotch or whatever the f***
But wouldn't it be better if I mean in terms of their brain
Did you listen to any of this ship
That is
Subconscious reality hitting
This is what
The Little Rascals
I mean they are prank Suresh
Certainly
Yeah
It's so f****** funny
But it isn't funny because
One of them is going to
Beat our asses
Murders people for whatever the f***
End result of This Is Us
But even if I do get my ass kicked by a proud boy I still think they're f****** hilarious
Pride proud
I have no doubt
Based on that
That they will feel very guilty and turn themselves
Because they are Jaya
Also I want to say that we're done talking about the proud boys for now
That we needed to discuss that just to give a sense of who's this McGinnis character is as
But as this develops as the rest of the season
Yeah
You don't have a full understanding of the sky
I have
This is that
Do you know what
Watching homoerotic
It seems like you thrilled by it
Another out-of-context drop from Alex
Machine
They call him to Mean Machine
The meme machine
God how is that even worse than what you just said
Toenail
Anyway
No
No one also calls him Maurice
Bora Bora
Where we left off in the episode was
McGinnis talk
Alex
Alex has some thoughts about how liberal
Onset arthritis
As we all know that.
That's how I punch also but that's cuz I have a mild related to
Oh really
So I mean
I'm sorry
I think it's mine
Gavin wants to
Discuss why people keep attacking him
Have you ever see why is
What
But you understand why I
Have you people ever seen an adult
And then I
Punch hard are you a f****** Cro-Magnon Arc adult that's what they
I think they are
They think they're the ones we're adults and we are children
That's awesome
That's amazing
Anyway
Gavin wants to talk a little bit
About why he thinks
And I
I got to say
He's kind of right
Axalta wrong
Nazis or whatever the hell we are
Killing a baby
Trump
Everyone in front of me
I mean that's kind of ferrets
I just have this
Cheyenne
Boehner fantasy
Punching somebody
And being Justice
More like all they want
Is to be justified in
Because they have so much
Repressed
Rage
Useful when I was in Middle School in junior high I wanted to be in a street fight
Really like a big
Like group
And I don't want
So it's interesting
You know I just have these sort of
You know benchmarks in our own lives that we've grown through the kind of relate to how the proud boys at now
Like Poor Boys weenie
I want it I want to talk to about this
I think he's right
Though about this idea that people saying that he's a Nazi
Allow them
To be able to attack him
I want to say this
When we talk about people like Sebastian
He's actually a Nazi
Your Napolis
He has
Flight attendant really a Nazi
Fraxel that's fine
When were talking about someone like Gavin McInnes
Mike cernovich
Or even Alex Jones
They're not Nazis
People make those comparisons
What they are
It's still someone that needs
Yes the whole point of that was push for the right
Is it everyone's comparing them to Nazis to make it okay to punch them and I agree that that stupid
Go ahead punch
You know what I feel like that's a good point
As opposed to
Bingo
And really get into usually like page 87
Exactly
So now
We're going to take a shifter
It's the three of them talking
I meant at the end cernovich disappears and it's just Alex
And
McGinnis
But for now
For now
Mike cernovich is going to pop back up and I'm going
To bust his bubble
Are you really working for
American traders he's useful
Kill you
What is going on with Trump
I get the missile attack
I just say I do
They caught before
Coming coming
No any very conveniently not asking sort of it
Who is sitting right
Very
Strong evidence it is now come out that at least as it relates
Do the Syrian hoax
Hashtag
Twitter
That was
No that was a Russian
Oh you think so they've traced back the earliest tweets that use the hashtags.
Trace back to the earliest ones were in Russia and bizarrely a very high incidence of people
About that in Somalia
Which could conceivably be bought for
Which is
It does support beep
There's a lady who
Fully documented.
Beginning of the
How the operation sort of went
Yeah
With the hashtag no more fake Wars
And with
A call to Arms
To a group
I am so about
Started retweeting
With a bunch of other hashtags
And immediately Syrian hope Scott
Involved in that spread the people
All of these appear to be
Aphakic
Concentrate
Attack
They use the bull
Yeah that's what they did over and over and over again
Until it found its way into the public
It's basically you have something that's bouncing back and forth on a really small area
You have a ball that's going back and forth between
Got two walls that are very close
Is there it comes in with momentum it'll keep going much further apart
Run by the same bot Farms
Start coordinating
On this thread and start putting memes on to it on to this thread
Along the way at all times
Buy these wars are Jew Wars
Meme
There is a Mean Machine yes
Most
Import
So that's how it started
People started
It started trending
People like Mike cernovich
Got involved
So it is
Is it is
Like a
A literal propaganda
Yes and it is
To believe all sorts of things as long as it fulfills their Global is deep State narrative
Yeah they push them really hard and then oh s***
The reality starts
Come out maybe a week later
That this was
Something that was started by Russian
You can never catch up to it
What you're going to
To reject any
That would make you look like if you want to go further than just this awesome article
Screenshots that documented the beginning of the hashtag
On the topic
Coincidence
Hamburger was a member of the International Center
Counterterrorism
I'm at The Hague
His job is to
The study propaganda
Call techniques
Hugo the same
The theory of
Clear example of Russian
Influence campaign
Designed to undermine The credibility of the US government
Appointment with campaign people involved otherwise be involved
A lot of people really characterize themselves as being pro-russian
But they're receiving influence from this campaign
Oh that's the f****** Hague
So they're dumb
Yeah
Sugarcoat
Seems more fair in like that
It like that way that
You go auntie
TV news and they don't say
The president is a liar
The president
False claims
Has has implied
Whereas the reality is this
I'm not going
That's not our job
These people
Are dumb
How many say
You might as well be an honorary proud boy
So weak mean
We have we have what I can
ABC and whatever all my research is
Has led me to believe that they are
Parroting Russian and pro-assad
But aren't necessarily based in true
Right
Now what the hell
How they're presenting it is the people are accusing them of being a Sade agent
Where that's what Alex
Yeah no one is accusing you of working with Assad
They're accusing you of having an agenda that matches up with his
And you're using his propaganda because you've been doing
Yeah exactly
And it's hard to admit when you're duped
Like I very early but right before we started this podcast
Me and Marty durosoke recorded an episode
Of podcast
We're talking about
We've been duped podcast might as well
We discussed
Conspiracy theories in Suffolk I bought into stuff for 4
And to make a conversation more fun
But there was a point
It went to its we really did buy into
For instance
The idea that Hillary Clinton was going to die
Like she was deeply sick
Now
We bought into that because
It did appear that there were videos
Good
No
The only real
Response that we had to that
Was afterwards but I know
We're dumb
We f***** up on that one we believe bad sources
We bought into whatever this
A Mike cernovich knocked on that
You never fought
That's not being a man
Well I would argue of course it's not being a man and so far
I'm done with man
Adult
Nebulous concept of what is it in adult
Being an adult
Being a f***
Big Mouth Maury
So now you get the glimpse of this round table that we're having in this team of superpowers cuz he's
Huge followings on the Rhone
Cowboys L over here
We've got the dummy who believes
Pro-russian propaganda and
And fully documented is a fragile broken human being
Somehow we have more
Poor heartbroken
Useless
Remember
Might as well be an intellect
Blah blah blah
Human remember
Never going to not
Be angry at you
For telling me about
Like
Personal level the fact that I now know that the
The proud boys exist
Is going to SLC
With you
For the rest
Turn my lights on the back of my head
I'm going to be thinking
Cowboys
Always there
Volibear
Always
I want you to remember that you're making an argument
You're making an argument that we should have empathy for anyone who
Bill's group called The Proud boys
Remember that later as this goes on let me let me go
Let me do this
Just because
I have a
Does not mean I also don't want
Every single person
On the entire planet
To hit them in the
The face
Punch them right that's silly mustache
In that dumb face
Yeah right in the dumb face
McGinnis
Was being asked
Alex
What's your response
To being called a Russian agent for Assad agent
No service
And here is his answer
That really goes bad
Yeah I was just talked to him on the phone right now from here
Via Skype
I don't care
I don't care if it was actors I don't care if they just had kids do like that
The big picture is that the world a bad thing
On the bad thing and now women respect him
It here
He's talking about the pictures of the Gap Kids
You should care if it's
A lot of people
Those people could totally not die but if it's real or fake
Kill people
If it's not real
Ghost
Phaeton Ally
Idea
15 goddamn years later maybe
We were
Speedway
You should
Not start a war based on a lie on Twitter also
That goes back to that
But do you like don't you love that boat
Real or not
What ends up happening is big man has to make Boom-Boom to impress woman
Feel like I'm
I bet you don't like
Just for the verges remotely like entertain what is it
Feel like I'm
These assholes
Hurtful it hurts probably
Probably very unpleasant
Like within
Go home
And they're watching to
And their brain is right
Yeah
Right I would assume
How to spell Mia
I think that's a pretty human thing
Really
And the depth of
Because I don't
Small and child
I feel
The world
And I feel that way
Cuz the world
Is ending
Right now
5 years ago or so we didn't have proud boys in the world
Beautiful weather in Revelation
Actually there are the four proud boys of the Apocalypse
Exactly so you actually goes on further and I think it actually gets even more
Cuz he said he would draw a line in the sand and he got caught
So that's awesome you killed as you say the Russian
Wiped out
Tears are absolute animals they dismembered our soldiers
Fingers are
Hear them with huge fireworks
Also
FedEx
No it's not
Women are actually against the patriarchy
That's our whole goal
You remember how they say that all the time.
Speak out against
Secretly wanted the rest of them are cool
Added space
That is the
Slightly
Aggressive
No she actually
That's exactly what that metaphor
You don't know what you think
It's absolutely on its face not true
It implies some sort of like secret knowledge of women
Fit like cookies talkin to Proud boys most of the time
They don't know
Whatever he says he seems cool he started Vice
Bus know what women think
No
We know a lot of women who are feminists
We know a lot of women who
Are on the fence about what they want identify themselves
I don't think that any of them are like
I really
Secretly wish man ruled everything
Every Woman
Told me
Captain on my Armand Moore's
Oh yeah yeah
Like to make as much as a man
Which is really saying
So cool
I make more than me
That sort of thing and I didn't know that I was actually in the proud girls
So when we did learn about that
Jesus the cookies are way better though beyond that he's
Trump's actions have destroyed the Russian narrative
The dropping of the
Mother of all bombs
On Afghanistan almost immediately after news broke that
Countries
Relayed information
United States intelligence
Community
Trump surrogate
We're directly meeting with Russian spy
The idea that this is going to stop that
No absolutely
Did the proliferation of information is
It's gone too far.
No probably not reflect
Why can't they
Because if they pull the trigger too early they bought the entire thing
This is how it goes with investigations
If it's not
If it if it's not Ironclad you're going to end up
Coming into early that's exactly what the
The CIA said
Delete
Lee Harvey Oswald
Jump too early
Stop this
It's clear
At least at the okay
Circumstantially it's clear that
The president
Committed
Yeah
It does not matter if he actually committed
Not ruin the entire world
The American
That guy committed tree
So let's not have that
Can we just not have that guy
Like if you're if you're in the GOP can you just
F****** balls
To just be like hey no
Can we have a do-over
Jewel
I'd like that
Information
Request
Made about the pool
And the states the Trump won
Boost stores
North Carolina's Michigan
Connect
90 reports
Malfunctioning machines
They're 90 reports about malfunctioning machines
Enso state
All that information is about to come out
I've no idea could this be like
Oh these poor counties had bad machine
Too far
Plastic
About
We were talking about presidency
Having deeply
Democratic
Counties
That are
Heavily
Disenfranchised population
Giving and refusing to
Didn't employ
The GOP
Is it couldn't win
Good at that like historically in America date
Always do that
Alright you guys got us this time
Where were bumble
Now
The proud boys are winning over
Can we get a music sting of that
Wildboyz
Anyway the next
Clipper going into
Is a little bit of discussion about that mother of all bombs
It was dropped
I mean
If it's about
Fair to college
Distraction because it's
Real Act of War
Yeah but it
The timing of it is very f****** weird
It's very f****** weird
Please works like that the only escalation past business is nuclear
Bombs in Lubbock
I realize that I totally cut you off nearest Starbucks
He said that was
His proudest
Not too
Because it demonstrates restraint
It does the whole thing because literally everybody in the government
Told him that he now has
Blow them up
He's the only voice
And now you look
Everybody who was in his government and they're all like
That's the most beautiful
Bomb the fuckout
Gorgeous
Also this leads into Gavin
Obama's mess
Kill Them All
To carry out his constitutional orders
I like the team
But they were saying that to Obama
The guy who
Ordered
And succeeded in killing
Thesamba
I don't know cuz Alex's mixing up his narrative
Alex
Alex is all over the feeling on this is
Bin Laden was killed
That was all it was all a cover-up and what have you
There's no winning if you're Obama did you see the
The the most amazing people I think I've ever seen
Democrats
Who supports
37% when Obama
37 /
That's great that's consistency
The GOP
Prior when it was Obama
10%
When is Trump
F****** believe a consistency
I don't know kind of ideology
The other than
We don't like
You really did just
Just explain it
Really f******
Stupid s*** that all explained at the end
I'll even crippled our guys over there I was talking to Terry schappert recently and I said how do we win this war and he goes let us do our
Our job
I mean right now they got RPG
He misunderstood in order to save our lives because they were shooting from the mosque and they got the don't shoot the mod Pizza
What we were trying to kill them
We got to let these are dogs loose
I want the Terrace be going
The Middle East
By the way
Track 10
Composition
These people are stupid
Something within set
But then also the Rules of Engagement
There's no authorization that's needed to respond
So the idea
Do you would have to call back and be like
You know I don't
I don't know I don't know
I'm not going to speculate on that there are any number of reasons
Even if it was
Is it symbolic situation
They're pretty regular
That argument is flimsy
Yeah it is a flimsy argument
Military history
There's a lot of dumb s*** that people do and say
I know Alex when he was sick
But
That's fair enough my position is the
Defensive
Things are very different than assault
I talked to a vet again
Anecdotal story
Is
Contestable
And furthermore we know that he has
Talk to
Blank and there is never actually
So I'm at work I just think that's that's pretty stupid
It's very steep
I don't
What are you
The solution is to kill more people obviously
How many p
Ludacris
It's ludicrous
Yeah yeah I did always do seem to be
Sort of
The poor
The author
It's so simple
Did the mother of all bombs
Cos 310 million
Biggest 314
Yeah something like that
Swampert firebomb yearly budget
Eddie number
It accomplished
Nothing
Regular other than to show that week
Can make a big
It killed 36 Isis members
And I'm at number was upgraded till like 90 something
Is dubious before people
That's not worth it
Anyway
But beyond that there's no estimate that I've been able to find
The amount of civilians that are killed by a bomb that has a blast radius of a mile
I can't imagine how many
People died
Yeah
This is this is why
Like
It is really important
To realize
That America is
Is not the good guy
Certainly not by default
F****** at this point
Russia's kind of a better guy than we are
If they just stay out of it for like 10 years ago
But
We're getting off track
This is this is not the let's discuss American foreign policy
More about Sebastian Gorka
Cuz now we're going to take a sharp Veer from this war
Culture
And this next
Clip explains is all about
You know like
If you really want to get into
The truth about the left
It's right here
I'm assuming that they know about the left hand
Sure I certainly died
More about the
That plays in
On Earth
What
The song about being in bed with
Microphone
They're so
That they will roll into the most nasty crap in the world
Quality culture
Assuage pain
Well I think it's because they hate the family and why do they have the family I don't know they have daddy issues
Maybe they're weak and they can't bear the idea of having kids and having a proposal
Green shape lies are overwhelmed by their own magic their own they're sentient being
Batman just don't have the balls to stop playing video games and actually put a ring on it
I saw they created this world for everything about them is anti-family more a wedding
Extremists who want to obliterate
Directions to
Hijab on my head
That's interesting.
I would embarrass me being sarcastic
I would posit that it's possible liberals
Are cool with Muslims because we're into
The diversity of opinion diversity of cultures
I would save it all liberals
But I've ever met
I already
Things like genital mutilation
Child child Brides
False flag
That are part of primitive culture that
In parts of the developing world
We are
Those things
And that
Not at all religious theocracy
It's not at all fair to point the finger at all Muslims
You cut clits off
You know that's not fair at all it's not fair to say that
I'm sort of sign of a pressure
I don't want to get it on a soapbox here and make an argument that
World that I'm totally outside of
Yeah but I do know a number of Muslim people in a lot of conversations that I've had
It's a choice
The choice you can make
It is
It's not really a big deal
It all comes back to
If you guys have never met
It's like I've never met people like 12 year old Christians were
Yeah
Yeah true to some extent never experienced any part of the actual world
These people have retreated inside of their fantasy
Cuz they're afraid to go out
Yet that y'all Liberals are in bubbles
Play video games and yet at the same time they're sitting in with
The f****** proud boys getting tapped on the shoulder
Oh no
Where was Bubba Smith
Goodbar the
First one you came up with the weird
I like bananas
Is there anything more you
You're going to have to put down the mic
A bunch
For the segment that's about to happen
Cuz it's so bad
So at this point I tweeted about this and I saw it really
Kind of bad about the tweet I made
Cuz
I felt like I might have been missile lining for conversation of tiny bit
Rage
My very nature to second-guess points
For experience I still second-guess and question
Like a cuck I treated that
Mike cernovich
Gavin McInnes and Alex Jones are having a rousing round table about how women secretly want to get hit by
I treated that man I fell really insecure cuz some guy tweeted at Mike cernovich
I was worried that they would edited out of the rebroadcast I wouldn't be able
Find the evidence
Here comes the avative
There we go
I want to say that I was a little bit wrong cuz they were
Simply talking about 7s
And
Your workout this is this is an act
A place that will come out in
At least two acts maybe three
Here is the first one of it and I sort of about
How families secretly want to be
Free slaves
In a family-friendly but a lot of feminists do have very dark desires Fifty Shades of Grey sold a lot of copies and
There might be a little bit
I want to say this is my son
We haven't really heard his voice all that much
Mike cernovich
We've mostly
Clip so far
Spouting his brand
Misogyny
I will stay
He comes he's a little bit more self-aware than the other two little play out
In a second
Want to get to sort of
In a family-friendly but a lot of feminists do have very dark desires Fifty Shades of Grey sold a lot of copies and
You know so there might be a little bit they maybe they like that Dominic component of Islam and maybe
Feminism
Respect
Exactly
These people really
Everybody really wants the strong alpha male figure
Smartpoints
Cuz you screamed over that clip
Cuz we're not being real man and we're just down beta cuck
I don't think that's really
They're saying
Take this unfairly out of contact this is the conversation
Coming out of their mouths
Don't me
F*****'-a
Any size
That because Fifty Shades of Grey
And these ideas about
Consensual BDSM kind of fantasies
Most
Middle-aged
Bulls Housewives
Read like an old romance novel
Similarly
Sort of aggressive fantasies
Contain
It wasn't all just like
Super romantic
Flower petal
Like there was there was that sort of thread throughout romance novels through Street the reason
But then Alex related to like Islam
Slave block
All this stuff for Mike cernovich f***** up
He said
About
This darker sexuality
Feminist
I think it's stupid but there's something you could unpack in there
Power dynamics
Consensually is
There's one thing I didn't really discuss it interesting thing that goes on tonight
Play describing all of these
Btsm things that feminist secretly want from there
Islamic managers
How much do you get paid to be an ace
Is it like an hour
Being submissive in your sexual life really has nothing to do with what you do
And if you really want to talk about how these women
Secretly want a big dick
All that stuff
Unfortunately
Rinaldi's
They told me stories
Leaving out people's names for privacy
Super powerful bankers and then people like that to them and want to get beat
Essentially they want to be punished
Diaper play comes with
It's a lot like if
If you are
Publicly
A heterosexual
You might
The club
You just have to write your name
Tell me more
What type of butter do you like
Is it the visit landolakes.com
Margarine spread
I think we could encapsulate
That they should have gotten
But can't buy saying sexuality is an incredibly complicated
It doesn't have anything to do with feminism
This idea that Alex
Seems to keep coming back to use it is
White women are going with Muslim men cuz they want to be oppressed
Because all these white men are not men their cocks
Ignoring it
Like you said it again
I just kind of slide through
My brain because
At like how do you even engaged
Makes so little
That's kind of our show
Good point
We just choose our spots so anyway this next Clipper going to get a little bit deeper into it
I'm going to play this play out throughout
This episode is
Please put that my time
You're the
The trends that I want you to
You keep an eye out for the things that that I think are the most in
First one
Is a generous use of the word metaphor
Haha
The 2nd
Is that Mike cernovich
Open burn
And he knows
What Media Matters is going to do with this
And so he jumps into save it
Okay and I actually think it's really smart as him
Like we've discussed
Media Matters is pretty manipulative
Sometimes with how they choose to cut
Eclipse in terms of where the start point is where the end point is
Now based on
Who bought I just said about his act
Westcliff is clearly on the wrong side of ideology in the sentence
In this particular case
He doesn't deserve
Hit by
He's just smart about how he gets
Exactly what when they call us
And that semester asking for a metaphorical now not little nothing for a metaphorical slap
Where you going
Don't you dare talk to me like that engine on the concrete sometimes a woman needs at the club.
Sometimes a woman needs to smack
This sacrilege
White women just for the dance floor
Dancing or asses off they love testosterone and they're only pretend
Beta male allies
Then a feminist man
Huh
So there we go
Fryer
I think they're I think baby one thing that makes them dryer is
Guys discussing the moisture level of their p****
That's
Also
Nothing makes my dick limper
In charge
Runaway
But to her profile
I'm looking for a woman who is
Involved in her own interests
So Gavin starts talking about how whenever women Gallatin white white mansion
From a man
Metaphorically
Hold on and then
Directly there the point is made from that is
Bring up
Sean Connery's quote
I'm I'm sort of it's jumping into being like metaphorically
Has slapped a woman
And it might have been buried in that a little bit and listen to it again
He said
Doesn't work
The men he mumbles
From what I've heard
I don't know if
He's had women
But that's a bad quote
You know what a better quote
Don't hit women
Can really stay
No not really
Wouldn't actually
Then they would never have thought
Don't hit women rightly is like
Coming to be like
Media Matters is going to cut this which he's right he's totally right and because he said those things
Now it's not really as usable the clip for them
Sweet kind of playing defense
Really smart light
How's that defends like if you put the whole clip on there
Then all you're really
Is that these guys
Legitimately
Believe that
What they're saying
Yeah
Has
The slightest amount of
Clever and
To say
Well look at them
Choosing to report our word
Guys
This territory is not
Waring Waring murky story
Really
The
Parents
Terrific
White women
Flood to the dam
The South
Stang
Miscegenation
Interracial dating and everything
That goes along with
Just the idea
I mean that is entirely
Let's party
Hannibal
He's white women
Gravitate towards them cuz I was white man event pussies for so long
What's nonsense
Sphere
Beer
And impotence
Justice
One of the most important pieces of it is a deep-seated
Yeah if I was Media Matters
That's the clip that I talk
Because
Your race
You could make about that not
Racist or them saying well
You know I love every race and I don't believe in any kind of race
Pure white
Man fear the most
Blackface with rubber
So I mean
Who is Nigel McGuinness
I agree with you
Anyway
Mike cernovich is kind of smart again which is like
I got to steal this in another Direction
And these guys are going off on
Hitting women tangent we can't do this so Mike cernovich
I got to be honest
I dislike him quite a bit from his
I think crnkovich is smarter
Ben Alex
You know what I can do I can shift this into talking about Alec Baldwin
Champa massage unit
Mel Gibson
Mel Gibson was yelling sugar tits and being anti-Semitic
Cop that pulled him over and he was wasted
Back the f******
Who gives a s***
There's not a false equivalency
No but I can't you can't be like well
He said all this s*** so immediately any
Trump is worthless
We don't even support him in that
Congratulations
On your comedy
Yeah course
Typing a domestic abuse or the way he talked on The View
Yeah we just got to make sure
Emotional abuse
I want to know why
Why we get taken out of context
On the answering machine and yet nobody's trying to advertise him
Why do you think that is
Donald Trump
It's known
I've never touched a woman
Aw and he's never hit a lady he's never raped his wife
She never wrote about it in a book
Please play he's ever
Buckley said that you should
Grab a Woman by the p****
Walked into underage
Dressing room
For his
Model shows
He's never
You know been the target of multiple multiple
Great Glam
Sexual harassment laws
Sure never never
It's
It's also of all the men
None are more virtuous
Also I want to say it's
It's kind of important
I think
Alex just committed
Slander
Because I don't know of any instant
Necessarily
I haven't
Fully researched Baldwin
But he hits women
It is
Reported
I don't know if that's reported but
Baldwin
These guys are f******
Monster
They only care about Alec Baldwin because he
Impersonates
That's the only reason
Shake it all the liberal like
So it doesn't matter how many
How many young women are leading the charge
Against this
Because Alec Baldwin has a
The dumbass
Clip where he does
Bacon
Compare it negative
To f****** whatever
What is a goddamn
Yep they never actually have to
Engage with the fact
Monstrous
What it is they're saying
2 take away agent
Horrific f****** b******* a perpetuating on this show and flip it
Is isn't
To be saying these sorts of things out of one side of their mouths and have the other side be like
He women
You don't understand the implied pieces of the things you're saying
Because you're racist
When you hate women
But we're off the charts for now and we're going to get into
Talking about how
The left is dumb
You don't do you know why it's good
Do you know what I really like it
Feeling self
Some sort of paragon of virtue
I think something we both we both know lives
High Road
This is
Truly monster
Who cares
Visit Warsaw
I promise you
But for now it's okay
We threw the most
Anger I've experienced
Many many
But for now the King of The Proud boys
Is going to come in and explain.
The left
Dumb
Right
Is all about
Alex
I'm going to stay some facts
Anime soon as the clip is done
I'm going to tell you the real fat
Alright enjoy this rollercoaster ride
You know they followed Obama through everything they followed Clinton through the cigar incident that 13
Dallas Cowboys I mean it's frustrating that were fractured
Are there
It America
So Alex Jones fake laugh there but also
One woman told him there were 70 billion
That's insane
A dump very dumb person
Who told him that
Who might not exist
It might that do it might just be a completely made-up thing
Also complete the numbers of illegal aliens
Not the right nomenclature
You don't want to call people illegal
Undocumented immigrants
Whatever
The Beatles number are people on the right
Someone saying there's
3 million
Illegal immigrants vote in the election
Statistically impossible number me that weirdo dude on Twitter who had like eight followers and then blown up
Exploded and he's been interviewed on the news is I got sources Avenida never has any of them
Quite literally Impala
That's one of my favorite things that is gone
Very unanalyzed
I think most of the population is
Where is that
Like sort of myth started
I might write something for the website about that
Just because of how stupid it is
DIY ideas
There's more
Immigrants undocumented then
Laugh
Is
Conservative
Right-wing idea 70 billion
It's probably a right-wing dum dum dum dum
Somebody who does not know that
There are only 7 billion people
That means
A lady told him
There are more illegal immigrants than the number of human beings
Who have ever
Can you talk about
The current population
Existence
It estimated at 50
Boulevard ghost
You always get
12 dimensional ghosts
So where we got the clip Alex was fake laughing and now he's going to get into his rant about facts
Is the number to throughout
And you realize this is all posturing to you
Culter35
1.5 billion China
25 in India
They don't know any of the stuff I don't know the population White America 600
6 million
Somebody tells me the population of a place
That's a conspiracy
Write this stupid
That's that's really stupid
No but also he's just rattling off fact
Turn off
Will you know if you know five things then that means everything
Let me walk you through each one of these
Alright
Population of the world is 7.5 billion
That is about
Is that one
We got one on the board for Alex Alex Jones Heather 35 million illegal immigrants in the country
Furtively conservative
So that would be roughly 10% of the entire United
Pew Research Center there's 11 million illegal immigrants
The trend has been moving downwards
Every year
Yes even according to the wacky ass website
The figure in 2016 is 10
10.5 ml
According to right-wing wingding site
It is a third of what he say
Yes and the actual number is probably right in there 10 million or so
5 million
Alex says
The actual number is 1 points
3 billion
Which seems small but it's billion
2.2 million
I am willing to
To give him the b******* Roundup
I'm going to give him the b******* I'm not I'm not
Alright cuz we were talking billions
Talk about when he talked about that is that it
The percentage of the world's population that that represent
Has been trending downward every year for
A great number of years
Oh yeah
They are growing slower than the rest of the World stroller
In that
Because culture
Right now women out now
Number Madden
Dating age nearly 10 21
Tell course their population is
Is it more
Significant that he's
.2% off because it's trending downward
So he can't even be like
India's population is 1.5 billion the actual number again is 1 Point
3 billion
Is there is there actual population growth
Has been trending downwards every single year since 1983
Is actually getting
Smaller
Percentage-wise every year
They're their growth has gone down
Let me know again he's off by 200
Million people
And the pictures of what's going to happen in the future
He says that the population of United States 335 million the truth is it 300
6 million
Again
Giving a temp
Like if you're in school and you're giving a test
That's pretty
Substantial
Reset the population of Latin America is 689 million
What is the included
The definition of Latin America
The definition of Latin America is a very nebulous thing
If you only consider South America and Central America than the total is 600
Scream
You have 177 million living in Central America and 426 million
Living in South
Now you add the Caribbean to it was you add like Haiti and Cuba
You come up to 600
And
26 million seventy million
Short of
What he is
I don't think you're going to be able to get that with weird
Unaffiliated
Did appear around you know they have populations of like
If you want to see the difference between 689 million and 626 million isn't
Special that's fine
For the fact that he
He's using it to show off how much
China 1.5 billion hundred percent correct because
Liberals they don't know what to say
Comeback
3 billion
200 million
Women
Right but it's more to the point I think the thing that's more important
He has these
Please memorize that are tacky
And it's like a middle schooler trying to pass
Cast of Hope
Freaky's close enough
Conspiracy theorist
What's going on here baby
It's not what's going on
Also you're wrong
Alex Jones
Come on.
You know you know
You know you just want to love
He's wrong
But in
That is
Not as bad as
Something wrong
Most of the so-called refugees going to Europe or actually not refugees
To investigate
Old people
Don't get fingerprinted in Denmark
You want to go to Europe and do you want to go to Germany or Austria for the big bucks the welfare I kid you not
It's admitted they have like hundreds of times increase birth defects
Villages
Marry your first cousin he was wrong Muhammad was wrong
Wrong sorry guys
So with a lot and I have a lot of fat
Wow
So Alex screamed
Of all Islamic men are on welfare
I did a little bit of research into
Conspiracy theorist Family Security matters. Org
By a gentleman named Dr Sami
Call Robbie
Kiara Timebomb
I found some other articles that were talking about
Percent figure of Muslim man in Europe on welfare
Now what it is
Germination
It appears that way
No I don't know there might be some other thing I'm missing but it appears that everything
All roads
Lead back to Rome as it were
This article has literally no citation
No links to study
It only has quotes from people that
Maybe
Telling the truth
Sightings
So this guy says that
Turkish immigrants
In Germany have a regular job by 20%
The other 80% live on the so-called hearts for
State social benefit
70% of their children have no education
Now the argument
That there's a scam going on
The come in and for every child that they have
They get a certain amount from the state
Very similar argument to one that was made about welfare Queens
How this pervasive lie would be used against any part
Or any parcel
Of immigrant population
Large group of ass
To vote against their own in
Interest or even support things that are just
Insane
Like any number of genocide
Set of occurred over the
Let's talk about the Turks which again
He is siding that
All Muslims
In all of Europe
And this article is only talk
Talking about Germany
And it doesn't really have anything
It has quotes from people
Like this
So amazing
Can afford to buy a house
Or department and drive luxurious cars
Like Mercedes or BMW
It's a first name
There's no way
I will trust
What about
I'm sorry
Call kinskey
Anyway
You get my point back they have just first name people who are anonymous
Random sources
Interesting story of the music Queen
Immigrants coming in
Shoddy journalism
I don't want to say this to this is on Family Security matters. Org
We looked at their Twitter feed
Their most recent tweet
I was a frustrated Israeli
Defense minister criticized the UN for ignoring the issue of Palestinians killing Palestinians
Yeah that's a really big
That's a really big issue right now
You definitely don't want to worry about the Israelis committing
Across that Palestinian
You don't know they're not talking about that
The killing people
We get thesaurus
That way
This is a website
Is really inside a
Especially seems to be
Again I can't say definitively that's where all of its coming from but it seems like most of the articles that I could find
Link back to this article
It again had no evidence
Outside of unattributed quotes
So I can't I can't go on
That 80% number
Can't
Can't do it
I just can't
So then
We get into
All of the deep
All the child
100% child 100% what number what magnificently
Pittzarella
That's what the
Jordan
Is rooted
Deep-seated White
Goddamn
Phucumol
Maybe
I have two things to purse this bubba
First thing is some statistics
From the March of Dimes
From communitarian organization
I don't know if you knew that
The instance of
Child is about 3%
United
Is about 6% around the world
Most of this has to
To do with malnutrition
A lot of it has to do with a lot of countries not having access to vaccines
I'm at one of the other things
When you talk about defect
Just because it's a really big umbrella term it can mean a cleft palate
Which is not like it's nothing
That's just bad
It's it's not as severe as some other birth
So all that gets lumped in together
The 6% can be a jarring number
But when you get down to it some of them are things that are easily treatable and some things are
It's not still not a
Still not a relative
Quality
Would call a ray
Not
Doesn't matter
It doesn't matter if the it doesn't matter if the birthday
Population of the world is
10%
If you are pointing to a
And calling
Them the group of
Most genetic
Never going to be Bass
And it's always going
F****** Venom
But I'm just a liberal
That's all I'm just trying to bring
These days
Conspiracy look like you secretly want to be dominated by an Islamic
Play Secret
And he's like Muhammad said you can marry your cousin
You talk about it
I know
As a liberal cuck
Just wants to be loved by the
Islam
Estate
I don't like to hear one more
Well here's the second prong of my busting of the
This bubble is it that Muhammad
Didn't say that
He did say you should marry your first cousin
Bingo Genesis
Genesis 4:17 cane
Heather wife
Though there's no account given where his wife comes from
Accepting direct creation from God
And that area contain groups of people not mentioned in the Bible
Possibilities for her that she is either a full sister of Cain
Or that you was Cain's Mother E
The later generation of
Descendants
Because time was really weird in the Bible and people dislike 900
And Elijah
Still isn't dead
Baby boo boo
Abraham's son Isaac married Rebecca his first cousin once removed
The granddaughter of his father's brother nahor in these
By the way right in there is brother
So there's another instance of cousins
Another
That was Abraham's brother nahor marry his niece
Malachi the daughter of his own brother hwoarang
Like if you took
Eat a religious text
I found a lot of dumbass Jacob married Leah and Rachel were both sisters
They were the daughters of liban
Devon was the brother of Jacob's mother Rebecca this would make Jacob cousins with Leah and Rachel
Do you know what's the weirdest thing
So my parents
The
The hardcore Chris
Christian variety
And they have sung the song it multiple
Wedding
That is about
Isaac
Burying his cousin
No point in time
Did they ever connected
He never quite figure that out
Lesbian like out
Or even Onward Christian Soldiers
News about killing Muslim
The fourth son of Jacob mistook his daughter-in-law.
You know what I'm saying daughters
Yeah the two daughters f*** their dad because there were no suitable men around him drunk
They got him drunk and onto Max they f***** in to get pregnant
But I mean you know what I'm going to tell you this right now
Muhammad was wrong when he said that lot should
The fact his daughter
I mean it is again that just goes to
Cuz I'm that goes is xenophobia
Because all of these
Since his existing religious text
Because again we talked about this
Before they were written
F****** long time ago
I think there's something to be gained from them if you
Approach them with a metaphorical understanding
If you don't get it
Who cares
This is actually what we should end the show with
Okay because it's not good
Cuz there's
You're giving yourself notes during the show that you're not paying attention I'm saying that we should I'm the show with this because it's how a lot of our shows
Independent
But there's so much worse
S*** after it that we have to keep discussing it
But this
Guys
Just now listen to me
This is how we would have ended the show
If it hadn't broken badass
I'm not you have another line hours to cover I
I've got like 20 incredible Cliphunter the stories are all insane
Amazing
But also when you saying that people want to get off the air
He has to be talkin about
3 hours
To drunkenly ramble Tuyo
You son of a b****
Even Rob do.
You would have lost robbed robbed who is the bellwether
Clear attack on South Korea Tokyo as well as the free
Ben call mirror
We online
Operation
Yeah whatever
American people
Christian Brothers
40% off water filtration systems
Your family your children
System
And God slept
That water is got to be run through that filtration
Open system
Yeah I mean I was like Leviticus 12:7
Clean my water
Listen
No rock badgers
By my filtration
North Korea shipping like super cheerful
It is very alarming
North Korea or threatening nuclear war
Really bad
Come out on Monday so who knows what will happen on Sunday but like
The more more I think about it the more I realize that is just two assholes
Kind of normal
These exercises what's up Korea
Or normal it doesn't happen every year
The different is we have a lunatic
That makes it scarier but at the same time it all could not end up going
It's possible both go back and forth on this
A week ago
Give me like
I'm afraid this North Korea is going to go down this is the one that does it
All the time
Freaking out and a week ago I was telling you the opposite
To get on the same page
Alarm
Internally I'm still freaking out a little bit but I just
I think we can make it out of
I think I should be okay but I don't know what's going to happen next week
It doesn't just
Become friends
No it doesn't work
That way
Like I'm
At this point
Just like
Guys
Pick one
We're going to have nuclear war
Don't do the Brinks
Dementia
Just be like hey either we're going to kill each other or not and then let's move on from stop it with the edge player
Not
This f****** blow
For not one of the two
Blow it in your mother of all bombs
Muhammad
Listen
I'm coming for all those birth defects probably wouldn't happen
Corvette just filter their water
30% off at infowarsstore.com
Thanks
I would give a
And this is nothing
Terrible if you look at that ideas like I'm way to come
Speaking to come
Government
To take all my money
Alex
Dick
Stop trying to get in the transition game
Who's next
Is really dumb
Another example of Gavin
Dennis
Not having a real story
Forgiving an anecdotal
Source about something
The point but doesn't
And then I want to get back on the other side of this
And I do so
School function
Information in America
Are the most red-tailed millennial
In three generations there 15%
Or white
Yep yep
That was near the Coca-Cola factory I think that's
Nothing Idaho I can't remember
But he said
Are about half conservative
The parents are like 80%
100% of the teachers are hyper hyper left-wing
If you
I wouldn't be allowed to write it like you have to
Write the assignment that you want
We have to show education that
The free market of ideas is more dominant than you are hysterical
Newspaper
The thing that
The true Injustice
Is that they won't publish
Proton particles
Truant
I said this about newspapers
And publish
Is a weird word for an assignment to school and whatever I mean like I don't believe you
Disagree with him like
If that's what you believe
Rite Aid
And get enough
Sure
To me that has
Has the ring
This is another example of a
Conclusions based on false premises premises wrong there's no way it is like
Oh yeah I know you want to talk about Trump being good you can't do that you know what I
All Things Are
More likely
Parameters
The fact that you
Can't wear American flag shirt
Is more to do with you and not because they possibly
Millennials
Do not skew more conservative
The numbers are actually down
I'm past all the cross
The board pastime
The republican-democrat party affiliation numbers hipoteca
Actually
As the
Dependence
I witches
I think that's hard
Do we
Fiddle back and forth more liberal than
Mainly we're not beholden to the Democrats
Many times I think I would I would say we're more Progressive
Angry
Very much as the difference
That is wrong I'm lying about that's just a lie
The Pew Research Center has a very in-depth polls about millennial
Party affiliation party leading
Those are two things
It's far more democratic and Independence
Could be libertarian like
Yeah
But
Now about Generation Z
What's Generation Z I haven't heard that was under millennial
Yeah and
The underboss
Is a population that is very difficult
Forget
Statistical information
Fright
They don't have
I've never voted before
There's not fully formed
Adulthood in
OMG
The six-year-old who feel like
It's incredibly difficult to get demographic information about them
In terms of their political
Of course however
There was one that was done
Just because it's the Hispanic heritage
I was going to say
Say that I'm just saying for the audience
Just in case
The word is a second
Study of 14 to 18 year old high schooler
Old 5000
Students
They found overall
34%
We're in favor of
20% were in favor of clay
31%
Said they would not choose to vote in this
So that's overall
Over
Obama's job approval rating
41% approve
25% disappear
No opinion 28
Cuz their
Direction of country
Positive
7%
Negative
Smart kids don't know
Smart kids
Can you get back
Alright big Gavin's argument
That Generation Z loves Trump
Nonsense
Then I would prefer
This
34% favorability 20% favorability for Clinton out of the overall
And say that means
There's an overwhelming
Conservative
Uprising what's going on they love Trump nationalism
Unfortunately
There would be
These are children
Greatly in
And your trampoline
Are going to be
Much more
Domineering
In regards to what it is
Can I do a better job than you explaining this
Read the rest
Can I borrow the rest
Daybreak Netflix
They break down the statistics even more
Among African-American respondents
7% Trump
47% Clinton
33 would not choose
Well
PetSmart the government
Not traditionally good to them disinfectant
Asians 18%
6% Clinton
Hispanic
Percent Trump 31% Clinton
Now we get down to
What
Do you think the numbers on white folk
Let's get
They specifically broke down
The difference between white male
And none else
White males
58%
Favorability for Trump 8% Clinton
Genetically engineered by
21%
I would not choose to vote
Obama approval rating
27% approve
45%
Non-white male
22% Trump
30% Clinton
34% I would not choose to vote in this election
Obama approval rating 59%
Approved
16% disapprove kill us all
That's a very big
Safari bags
Percent approval rating among white males
A percent
Do you know what's crazy about the show
What's up
For somebody who rails against white genocide so much he's the best reason
For Wyatt
But you know what he does he uses arguments and then doesn't engage with the rest of the fact
In that argument
Did prove that he's wrong of course it's insane
It is truly insane
Distance
Tire listen
Episode
Has been about him
That all of the
The people
Most damage
He believes
Secretly
Mulatto
Suggestive
They use
Evil s*** that they do is that
Secretly
Everyone Acts
Actually wants it
The fact that they
The system is
Is built around 2
Supporting this
Miserable
Is evident that
The miserable ideology
Should be what
What the actual study says and all the rest of the
Breakdown
You could say
The youth
Are super into Trump
And what the reality is it's most likely
And it is women are also
Fairly
It is white
People
Genetically engineered by youku pants
Race somehow Trump
Anyway
This next
Lieu of
Starting fluid there's this blue I think coming up
Veyron
Oh okay
Clips or so
Are all
Bigotry
They're all just bigotry straight
That they don't understand is dumb
They don't understand it the bigoted
We'll just take it as a come
Take a note
Even the liberal colleges high schools have giant we need more families
Why
Kids are 14
Walked into a group of fifth graders and said
I'm going to teach you how to have sex
We need more white family
They are gone so far left
I had a sex ed class in sixth grade that's one year off of his 5th grade assessment
Praising it
If some heterosexual just wandered in off the street
Do we need more
I think it's probably something like
Respect
That's the shirt
Christian holiday
Free water filtration
If this damn if you buy our
How do we clean up our beer numbers
But that's just like straw man
It's getting mad about nothing
And like you chose the wrong year to be like fifth grade cuz that is right around would help classes
They put a condom on a banana and s*** like that
Every school teach you how to have like they're like okay you want to be in missionary
Short. Of time
Now that's usually better but communicate
With your partner
Maybe she's into some BDSM s***
Like
They don't teach about like ass play
But you know that y'all have better lives if everybody was being
You know the reason they have to do that isn't about the age.
Puberty and sexual maturity
Chappelle kids
About that sir
Probably a good idea never speak about it at all
Somebody
Good morning
I'm sorry Jordan
Sorry that your birth was prophesied
Are are at risk
And gays are hiding in their home
Scared of being killed
They are horrible welcome
Welcome Nigel McGuinness to the season brings a cowboy
Will agree with it for the rest of the show
He's joined us
He's going to fight against Trump's America where gay people are huddling because they're afraid of what's going to happen
As many overtures against the gay community necessarily
In terms of
What is policies
Just a DLP being bold
Set the problem
But
He really f***** up by choosing disabilities
As one of them
Because of
Because of Betsy DeVos
Who is Betsy DeVos who's the Secretary of Education
What is
She's really into voucher
Program
Here's one of the things that people don't
Standby Voucher Program
I'm taking this from americanprogress.org
A very
In-depth very well site
Article about the
To participate many voucher
Programs parents must all of the protections and right
Under federal law
What's more some states are not transparent about the stipulation
For example Florida's McKay Scholarship
Choir students
Described above
And that condition is not clearly stated in the information available to parents
The state's website
No one they say the information cited above
They're talking about special needs
The talking about the Americans at
Disability Act
They're talkin about the need
Situation
To where somebody is dead
Thank God I forfeited my
No I am not off hand
Positive
Jesus
If I hadn't forfeited those rights that I have
School
Is the right to a free and appropriate public at
Would really have that right
Going to get an education
The free inappropriate part
Super bored
School
Entails
Schools must evaluate children who they suspect to have a disability classify their disability in developing individualized education
Program an IEP
Describing
The appropriate placement and services that will help the children meet grade level standard
Some IEPs prescribed minimal services or combination
Such as additional time
Complete assignments
Well others include
Such as this
Sports on 1A
Iep's must be re-evaluated on an annual basis
Sister determine if the students
A new Supportive Services are required
This is part of the Federal Protection
For disabled
This is one of the things that you waive away
In about 4 Pro
You shouldn't wave that
No because very important
It's superb
Because
The idea of what a Disabled Student is also really
It could be someone within mild
Behavioral problem
Or it could be someone with Down
It could be someone in a wheelchair
They're all sorts of things that fall under that category zacian
Now within the voucher programs also
Because
We know it makes it
Difficult to deal with these
Did you have to create these iup
Is individual education
Because the federal law demands that
Is public school or private school
Can just deny stood
New Bern to our school we can't handle this
Or whatever they can just say
We don't we don't want
We do we can just reject you as a student
Which is
Really scary
That's a really scary world we could be entering into
And it's exactly what
The person that Trump has made the Secretary of Education
Wants to do
It's his vision of education for the future
So
Nigel McGuinness
With your thing is like oh my God these people with disabilities are going to be screwed
What kind of car
They absolutely it's going to be
This isn't some weird
Spear this is based on facts
Is based on
Rejection of the federal
Standards that are made
She said that
Directions for disabled students
Answer be handled on a state-by-state basis
Not recognizing that these are federal mandates
The Americans with Disability Act
And the idea Act
Are both Federal Sanford
The fattest
Fetishize
State-by-state
What why would a
What one state wants to
To do with this
Disabled
Stay 302 gerrymander
Wouldn't you
Why would you why would you trade
Why would you want
Disabled kids tube
Retreated
Oh you don't actually want that
You want
Businesses to make as much money as possible and you want things
Do not cost that much
I know that I know the underlined
The reason
What is your possible like just
Human
Explanation for why
The state-by-state part is that states are much easier to control Legend
Slated leave than the Federal
Even on the Democratic side Illinois super your
Sinister
Because that's the reality
Communicate
With their proper
Where's the compassion
Possibly silver
What
What possible
Could you say that
Do you want disabled people also
2 Estates
Oroville
Free market
Situation where
If Illinois treat their disabled
Kids better more disabled
Move to Illinois
And that means that
What
Simple benefit could be
By making it
States
Right
Well because I have to speculate cuz I'm not really in that head and I think that is insane
I would save it possibly their argument would be that
If
Please disable kids
Stop getting such a fuk
Confirm
We'll have to work harder
And they will
Learn how to succeed
Doing coddling these disabled kids for too long
In the same way
Like that
I think that most
Like
I would not think it's too far bridge to cross
For us to save it
Possibly they don't believe a lot of these disabilities are real
Amateur people are forced to stop faking it
Perception
Then all this autism will go away August
So it's that kind of b******* like
Is the kid
You weren't called Ada
PhD
He recalled
Bright
That whole
Brett
If you just
If you just ignore this
Kind of
Situation
Then you'll be
Forester
Assimilated
Somewhat yeah
You are
You are what
Validating it you're supporting it
I don't know
Doesn't
It doesn't give now entered the area where
I can't further defend it with a hypothetical cuz I don't know I don't know
This is all
Business
Akon
Institutionalized
Separate
The federal government from the states
Is just a masquerade of
We should allow certain
People to be cruel because that's why
What they believe in
Did they can't then make that
At 1
Tiny f******
All of their
Against
There are all of their argument
Islamophobia
Like
Exactly what they're saying
Do Islamic people want to be treated differently based on their cultural ideology
And their beliefs
We you think that that's evil in everybody in America
Should be held to the same standardized American set of values
But at the same time
American set of values should be separated between the federal government and
The States government really what you're saying is that Alabama right
Should be different from
F****** Islamic
Different from f****** Illinois right2know a made-up
Nonsense
B******* way of saying
Don't
And act
Exactly like
Somewhat yeah
If you do not
F****** commit to that reality
Stepbet
Is literally saying
Every single day
Goddamn life I could
Give a f***
If you don't look exactly like me
Exact staff
YouTube
Deserved
Treated like
S***
You just you don't deserve the protection
430 other
Possible
Reasonable explanation
Now that's a fun thought that you just gave me through that ramp
No that was great
Google is taking away all of our money percent off of
We need to keep up the beer shoes
Feel like a
One of the fun thoughts that came to me during that rent was that like
Now let's say
Apropos of nothing
Arkansas decided they wanted Sharia law
States rights
Woodside
Are they now going to defend
Like it
That's a white people
Arkansas said I we want Sharia law
States rights
No
Wanted to put up
Satan
Right next to the
Commandments
All the people who are about religion
Just Freedom said
We absolutely support that we love this
They totally did
F******
Next clip
I don't want to we have to move along
You're right
We have to move along
And I
Dan
This snake has my mom kicked me off Ernie
This next clip
Legitimately might make you more mad
What I'm going to throw the microphone across this goddamn that's what's going to happen
Just have to hold the mic
This next clip is about liberals treating
No it's fine
What has an aneurysm
Booby liberals treating a populations as
They think they're tripling down
Yeah they're painted themselves into a corner they keep choosing stupider and stupider
Pawns in a chess game
Birthday shows Tran
And they said these are our new black
But black didn't get with their pro-gay stuff so they said Alright you're out we're going to go with trans and you don't
Start winning all these women
And that's not working out email MMA fighter
Accepting men and female sports when their men
And they're obviously cheating it's so Chris wanted to talk about the case of the word beginning
Are making
You know gay or whatever
Gay or what frogs are gay or whatever real scientific
Superseded
Do you know what my
Maintenance
But they're just mentally ill gay
If they're beating us
They're beating our
Regular web
I hate it
When
I'm watching
And I see a guy wearing a wig
Like that movie
Guy wear a wig
Alright
I want I want to make
One point
Crystal clear
I think that there is an interesting
Discussion that will have to come up
In terms of Trans Am
Because in terms of
Musculature and endosorb things it isn't interesting
You know the purity of the turf
Kind of argument
Very minor
That part I get I get where I was coming from but it's so
It's not even tertiary its way Beyonce
In the
Women should be represented
Their draw at professional softball game
Like men drama for baseball
This is all that we need to know about gender now let's let's take a step
And get into Nigel's argument where he's like
So the Liberals try black
But they weren't in on the gay agenda
Trans
And people are just mentally ill gay people
We don't want that
What are you talkin about what is he
That's not based on anything
I don't
I can't understand
Liberals still very much
Support African American
Yeah there's not abandoned
Anybody also black community as a whole isn't against gay people
Nope that's an absurd premise
The idea that trans people are now the New Black
Stupid and productive
The idea that trans people are mentally ill gays
Is offensive
Idiot
You're just a
F****** idiot Gavin
Grow up
It is
It is it is this
Boys love it
For us to engage with
Sure because then we have to
To that is now
We are
When would it really
Is
I don't give a
F***
If your
Crest
That's a big D
It doesn't matter if if there's
Like because what he's what he's trying to do is like
Conflate
The fact that there is a
Cause
Du jour
You know like
Right now
When you look at North
Carolina
Your first thought
We need to stop them from doing
Trans bathroom
Right
That does not mean that I have
Change my mind on whether or not
Go Cops
Black people
Port Orchard
Which is what
Under the umbrella
Of
Suppress
All of these
Because again
They don't look
And act
Well what it comes down to two is this idea that
Themes
Like sacrilege to
People like
Keep multiple thoughts in our heads
It's not really difficult to be
Worried about the oppression of trans people and black people
At the same time
And then throw Hispanics in there to throw everybody in there
The same
Yep it is it is tendrils
Fatima prayer
And the
Problem is
That it is very much
War that is
Multiple free
So no matter where it is that
Depression is hitting
And it just so happens that
Unfortunate
We're influenced by the
The media the news of the day and I don't mean like the
The news media so much as
Somebody
And it makes it on
And then there's
10 million
Who have to respond
Daily basis
Fortunate
We can't smoke
PS4
For a full year
Imagine if everyone liberals could do triage
Everyone's addicted to doing hot tape
Or here's my pain about this social ill or whatever you know yeah
If we could if we can
Like hey
The first thing we need to do
And all of these other play
Serious
Real
Devastate
But the first thing we need to do
Is
Kathy kuo
Cool pay for equal
Just focused on that
Just every single person
Every single day
The only thing we do the only thing we talked about
Is this until a
Then we go to the next
Then we go to the next thing
If we could do this triage
Because that's what the GOP does better than
Anybody out but certainly true
Focus
Fixate on one thing
And that's all they talk about
Anti-abortion
Fixate on
Restricting women's rights
To the point where
It's at the healthcare law
The f****** tax
Code the f****** military budget
Them trying
Can I make an argument for why it's
Kind of impossible for liberals to do that united front
I think it's impossible is most
Of the issues
That are being discussed
Or legitimately life-and-death
Different community
Especially trans women of color are getting murdered a ton
All of a lot of trans youth are committing suicide
It's not negotiable for them to be like
Oh yeah let's get the pay Gap get down
It's difficult for them
To be like this has to be our number one issue with life-and-death
I meant about the African-American Community were like
Cops keep killing
I'm beating the s*** out of us when we do nothing
Agreed and it's difficult to switch Focus for them off of that
That's what becomes very difficult there are five issues
Legitimately on the left for all of these communities
We focus on
You're absolutely right
Issue arbitrarily you didn't mean that specifically be the first one
No thank you
But like that's why it's difficult
Consensus and unified
There are a bunch of
Allied
Causes
That have like
Just
Death and of course the reason that the
The GOP can
Cuz it is
White people
And because they're fighting again
You know like you said text
Code
Elvis sing imaginary enemy block of the same
The left left is a block of
Everybody
And they're fighting
4 lives
Whereas most of the time
The right is fighting for
I don't want to make a cake for a gay dude for I want to save money
It's much easier to team up when those are your issues
It's harder when you have
Blocks of people
I mean I mean really what it comes down to
Is we have
The most corrupt government
In the history of the
Because some people
Yeah that's really what it comes down to
To be fair so we're not super easily attack of bulshit wasn't like it wasn't perfect under Obama
Either they're still
Immediately following the crisis
He didn't
F****** execute any number of different
Controls that we haven't seen much of the dogs attack of fever
If governments
Commit
F******
War crimes
Against countries that
That we have no pain
Without Congressional
So of course
Trump is going to abuse these very same
Things that Obama himself
Led to
I understand that
Yeah
Truly
So a lot of the mistakes
Obama has made
Comeback
Vitae
Sinoway
Because none of us ever expected
Trump president
Slim Chickens came home to roost
So we have it let's get through some of these clips
Let's just do it
They keep screaming at me you need to love me more you need to explain need to bake me a cake for my
He's talking about the game
Yeah
And I go
We're not homophobic you don't care when I get up there was Liberace dancing around with his ring then we had Paul
Call Linda
I got with men
Love me
Abject jellyfish they're all into their pity party
So they went black.
First of all that's involved understand today
Never that's a really fun like when I was younger
And now they want to be treated
Like humans
Unfuk in believable
That clip was called even understanding of the game
Unpause
Unbelievable
I don't know if it's called
Evolve understanding of supreme of supporting Muslim Muslim
And this is going to end with what I would call an ice cold take
Take that will not age well
Cringe they crawled into bed
With people who hate them
Human recipe for disaster you said I want to be weaker and weaker and weaker
Good luck with that by
Play I come crawling back on their needs to Trump and they learn to shut up because they don't know what they're talking about
Yeah that's probably have some
I'm shaking
No this is Gavin
I wish
I wish you went to a place where
Somebody
Totally clear welcome I would welcome
Either Mike cernovich
Or
Gavin McInnes
I talked to them
Yeah
I think I believe I want to believe is
A person who
Who wouldn't
To violence
But God listening to that makes
Violence
Like I like
Dixie House
Yeah it's not hard
Antenna
It makes me aware of my own
Masculinity
Where my first response to that
Is
Violence needs
Has to do with the fact that I was raised where if you
You got freaking hits
I mean by that
So it is
It is something bad
Just buy
Just like my
My
Response
Is part of the culture that
That's really what it is
But they're the
The unexamined version of
End up hitting him first
You still wouldn't hit him
I think I think
There could be a conversation
It would devolve into yellow
Undoubted
Play with me
But
If that's the difference
Between like
Really understanding
These negative impulses
Saying oh no
What makes me great
That's what makes me me
That's my masculine
I just don't know
I listen to this and I worry that my reaction
Exactly what
It's exactly what
Perpetuate this
Behavior that
That I'm doing all of this s*** like we're also laughing at them
This
Central idea of
I am not part of the school
Well that's that's really what
Whenever I
Whenever I hear their rhetoric
And I think that the way to respond to it
Is with what
It is
Whenever you have thoughts like that
Just take a second
If you started group
Call The Proud boys
Good point I just be like okay that takes the piss out of him a little bit
How parents would be you no like I tell you stories about the monster under your bed it's like will actually you know he
Yeah he's he's afraid of
Or whatever going to like you're absolutely right thing out of him
You started a
Well what
What defeated the KKK in the 50s really
Was the Superman radio show
Because
One of the writers
For the Superman radio show
I infiltrated
Did the Ku Klux Klan and that was
Enemy for a long
And what they did was because he infiltrated the
He could use their dumb
Oh this guy's the Grand Dragon
Until what
His people didn't join the Ku Klux
Because it was so silly
Yeah
Super
How would you
Why would you join the club Hillary
Call the guy
Group with the
Grand Dragon in the end
When Superman
So we have a couple more clips
If noted satirist
Doesn't this next clip
Virtue moir clips
The next cliff
I don't know what
Is about
I've completely lost
I titled it incredibly poorly
It just says
Definitely not stupid
I think
I level I think so
We don't have Title 9 crap reinitas legislation that supports their mythical view of America and they just throw
They just learned to shut their mouths when they get back into
Art music and fashion the other things are good at
Is coming
That doesn't cut into British soccer into football
You know it when you go problem
They started head-butting very long and
That's definitely not stupid
I would argue that is the antithesis of stupid
Donuts
I not mine his
What
Did he say
So you was talking about pennies
These beta cup losers
I don't understand
No you keep you keep thinking that losers who are trying to get
Leave it for the men. Go back to our
Back to Arts home decorating
That's clearly homophobic and Alex Jones correctly
It's actually straight white men who are
Preston those fields
Gavin
Mechanics make
These stupid analogy
10 year old girls
Going to a soccer hooligan match and trying to
Start a fight
British accent
Allama.
You know pricing football that's that's actually the most offense
The part of that clip
That was a very offensive British act
Not for me
So I mean okay so if you track what his analogy was it was that liberals
What
Liberals in the political sphere and in this
Protest
Year-old girls as opposed
To the soccer hooligan that are the proud boys
Okay okay so his point was that liberals were punching outside of their there
Wake lazareno they punch like we've talked about that earlier
So yeah that's basically what he saying
Endogenic kicked out of them and then eventually go back to home decor
And all of the
Eclipse that was Hertz
Eventually boiled down
Liberals
Cape
Fight
Yes and they mean that
Yeah they don't ever mean that in a like
Even when Alex junco even when Alex
Just trying to say that
Metaphorically hit women
Ivorian was talking about how they considered a conspiracy theorist cuz they don't
Engaging is ideas
Rattles off numbers
Correct
State record is coming back
Back to we need to be able to
Punch
Last week was that I'm coming to the conclusion
That Alex Jones thinks fact-checking is censorship
Yeah it is this
That might makes right
And if you are saying that he's wrong
And you have
Evidence to prove that you're bullying
He beat the s*** out of them
Answer that
Kind of is all that
If that bullies a dog
Oh man
Beginning
Pulled
You will go fuc
Yes absolutely it is it is
It's insane cuz it is that two sides of the mouth
My ideas
On the other side they come to beat the s*** out of
That's not an idea
Over the course of this episode good bit of stuff that
But I'm not doctor takes out contacts
Hour hour-and-a-half
Interview of all
You don't need to go into the repetitive stuff
We don't need to talk about Syria more than we need to write
Flying out of someone's mouth
We have facts we leave
Made arguments that completely deflate those Arkham
We've used even the things that they cite
Yeah
Now if you want to say is that like
Do
And I think about that
The Fight Club
The Chuck Palahniuk
Rule number one
It is
It is very much
Fantasy
To the point where I
Genuinely
Really haven't engaged with the text
Because even I read the book and
Like
There's a lot of like masculinity masturbation
But I think one of the bigger theme
Well that's what I do
I think one of the bigger themes is the disintegration of the
The self and becoming whole again
Yeah you know there is a part of it that is
That Tyler Durden personality was it
Negative manifestation of the the narrator's cell
It's your your basic
I like Wall Street
Was supposed to
Take down that idea
What are the same thing with Wolf of Wall Street
For the way that you look at
When is that
Is the hero
When in reality
He's the eve
He's being
Awesome Parody is not understood by
Which is why
I believe
Set the Irish
The truth is that
That part
Sing an outlandish
Proposal
Get some things up
And this is an argument that actually factually I can't
Super Disick
Agree with but I ain't guy
Down
So that's the one thing we can't really like
I can't get that
I can't really argue with that with research
I can vary
Well I mean
It's hard to deny that
The patriarchies back in style at least know if it isn't he was very popular this
Nebulous concept
I think that you could a lot of people could probably
You don't poke some holes in it
What have you and then the end show the patriarchy is a negative
But I understand it
Most people who support
The patriarchy coming back
What are motivated by is
The fear of women being
They don't think that women are capable of being in charge
They're scared of women being
Equivalent to them
Threatened by the idea of listening to women when they tell them to do things
Agreed and I think that is one of the other definitions of
Cowardice
I think it's
Not manly
I think it's not adult
And if you really are super into the patriarchy
I really don't understand
What argument you could possibly have
Yeah well I mean
Study this is the thing that I forgot
Just this is Burns
The pastor
During the wedding ceremony
1st Timothy 2:11 which
Isleta woman learn it all submissive
I permit no woman to have authority over
Man because Adam
That's not a great wedding
It was in the wedding
Yeah that's
What you if that's what you really believe
No reason other than
God picture
Yeah
You should net women should never be allowed to do
Unbelievable
Physical
Looks like you were talking about like
Sports being prevalent because forces existed longer
It's the same kind of thing is just
Back when we were caveman
Era of our evolution
Men
Physically dominated women Ergo we had to
Control
In most
Primitive civilization
They're a bunch of them that had matrilineal civilizations
Mother ones were weirder and heading
Like a bunk killer based
Civilization
What kind of swinging
You know there are a bunch of them they were a lot happier
Yeah
Studies have already shown that male-dominated
Society
Fragile
Even if they're still sort of male-dominated male-dominated
Secondary degrees
Civilizations where communities race
Your uncle would raise you and you sort of
Not really trade kids
But there would be a communal understanding of like
Your parents don't own you
Where is matrilineal is the mother is the head of the community patrilineal is the
The father
But unfortunately as our civilization
Grown
As men are the mighty ones
Physically and the ones were full of testosterone
Restaurant with each other the patrilineal society
And the ones that have
Exhausted
And destroyed
A lot of the other one
So we end up with all of our civilizations basically that exist nowadays are the
The Manor in charge
Does the ones that have their roots in the caveman days when men were physically able to.
The civilizations that are the best at destroying other civilization
Exactly where in the long game of Risk
Can we just have reached
Yeah get close
Year 2
You know what I've played a lot of Risk game that seemed like they were about to end
They were there for another seven hours
North Korea is going to roll Shady
God dammit Kim Jong-un
Kim Jong-il still has Oceania
Why does it always win goes to the
I know but you know what I'm saying like
That that's why
These male ideas exist
It's not because
Dick it's because of just
The problem
We know what the real solution
Which is all men need
Immediately
Different solution
What's your
I want to shave Gavin McGinnis
Does beard and make
That
I totally support you
But I was like
But I was like 22
We do not Advocate violence
We do however
Advocate shaving
Feeding it to him
Do you want to go with slowly or like big clumps
I don't care
When I was like that whatever 22-23 my brother sent me a news article
Was this guy
Who had been
Screwed over in
Anicow deal
You told about him over
Held him down
Set then I thought that was like one of the most degrading things possible
While not necessarily being applied equally
It sometimes
The best
Yeah so we're going to get out of here
Because this has been so
Toxic
I want to take
Trip back to the clip we played on the last episode
Is a gentle reminder
I hear you
Plants beautiful I love it
Just like I love my
Mommy when I was six years old
About 6 results you kick me off for lap
You don't get any more love.
That's what come down soon
And that's the man who is put on the show that we have just listened
Come to Alex
I would you just did
You just
Dropped
A hammer
That's the only way to describe that all of this
But yeah relates to this this is why Alex is totally fine
Having people like Gavin McGinnis on his show
Now we've had 24 hours a day
Doing it for 20 years and got drunk on Arrow
I imagine he might say something like a crazy week
Been pretty outside of our scope
In terms like he wasn't nearly as bad as those two
This is all about
This is what it's all about. You're mad at women
Congratulations
Now it's right
Tragic f****** tragedy of a human being
People who otherwise probably wouldn't
Like
Because eggs
And
Godzilla
Yep they exist
Tell him that we are at knowledge underscore fight on Twitter
And they can subscribe to us on iTunes
Gmail.com
Dot-com email address
Proud boys probably gmail.com email address
Gmail.com
For fun I hate most of the things
We talked about
What did you notice
I noticed
Double policy wonk
Holding
Alex