Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
A little bit about Alex
Do you have a p
Pop culture something that you re-watch her or realist
2 / Dover
Pop culture cuz I revisit the book Steppenwolf
Pop culture Maybe
I used to watch a lot
About every few years
I'm trying re-watch
The entire Bank
Love lost
I don't know I
For it like them so much busier now than I used to be
What we watching
8 seasons
Something will be at the
Disaster
No I don't know
No I don't think there's a lot there there many things
Things from the closest I can come is that I've read
Steppenwolf a number of times
Separate
Lovecraft
Not in the same way that I hear this from people that Game of Thrones is over I've heard a lot of people talking about like
Wait to get back to my yearly re-watch
We're all now have the final season
Present stuff like that don't have anything that's on that level
Repetition
No I have the lights
The universe and everything and so long and thanks for all the fish by Douglas Adams books that I read
Over and over and
And I have since I was like 14
My Canon
Growing up present day
Most of it memorized
Just reminding myself of who I once
That's great I was young and beautiful
Call Dad
What is the black history you know a lot about Douglas Adams
Schedule guys and
Maybe I'm a little bit about it
ND
Scattershot
Buckshot
It's going everywhere
The first Michelle thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Language IO
Next Lewis
Thank you so much you are now probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Hur nail polish
Katie Bar the Door
Somebody appreciate it very much
If I guess back then it wouldn't be a thank you
I don't know what I'm doing here but thank you so much Joe cecconi you are now a technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
You can do that by going to our website there's a button on there
It says the 4th
Appreciate
Jordan today I should let you know what the situation we all face in the
Okay
So we can talk
We did for Wednesday in episode about the present
To the 20th
. app
Do you want something
Is the present day whatever
Really you know a lot about the president
Present day
You're the only person who
Vicious like if you were leaving a review on our own show
Is bad about the present
Listening to his show at the present day is that it's a frustrating experience
Transmuted into something
Hopefully decent
As I was to put it out
I got some updates from
Who is the 21st
Was a crazy show
Kind of unfair of us
This this time
Crops were fallow and nothing was going on on the show
Just missed it by a day
Because of our timing we missed the good
So I decided he was going on in the 21st
Cuz I want to be overly fair to Alex
Okay well
The show that was worth covering
So today we're covering May 21st and 22nd 2019
Is that show was as good as policy wonk
Has
Saturday
I just wanted to know where am I putting this on him
Everybody right now
Milkshake
I'm not making this
I've just saying you know when people reach out and they have suggestions I listened then sometime
It's
Caltex dropped from Today Show
It means your body might have given up tonight being ready to die
Ultra commercial
It's upsetting
If you don't have allergies body might have given up and you are about to die
What is the best justification
Forever having allergies be a good thing I've ever heard in my entire life
So we start out today here on the 21st
Is Jonah in his vibe
What kind of stalgic for our old Studio going to go back and forth
Different days
So I decided to come into the Stitch Studio A B A
56 years
OpenTable
Sedation with back
Irregular
What is the news
Information
That would cover my friends
There's a real
Depressed Wreck of the Edmund Fitzgerald
That is that sounds like a diarrhea
Andre more than a
Preemptive conditioning
For his audience
Studio
Beacon already laid some groundwork of like
Nostalgic
Can sentimental for a
The studio
I wasn't broke
Right
We didn't have to downsize
Celtic result Studio on what he used to have
Is it legitimate
Considering how is life
Spiraled into whatever
Veracity is right now it does seem like something he could be feel like
Yeah I would be
The salad days
Just do whatever
Marginal celebrities would come hang out with me
Brenda naquin all my friends weren't getting milkshakes thrown on them
Milkshake
Is insisting
Strong take
It's not a take as much as it is
To really over
Exaggerate
Now that everyone is trying to just
Spy throwing
Nigel farage
Yeah tomorrow
Interesting real
Stupidly mispronounces
Is Nigel farage which leads me to believe
Maybe he's drunk
Or maybe
Just thanks
The name is fraud
Authorized
This individual
Just individual
Crazy Frog
Nomenclature equivalent of throwing a milkshake
Very unintentionally insulting
Twitter has authorized
Authority
Correction access
I believe I can't remember coming up
Narrative
YouTube stories
He's got a very important headline
Report
2 years ago
By black man
First thing it's important
Distinguish here is that no one
Covered up
There was a note that the shooter Emanuel Samson
Left on the dashboard of his car which is file as evidence and not release
The case is current
Korean trial
Previously the police
Existed but contents
A sealed until trial which
Which is not super on,
The note expressed a desire to get retribution
For the Charleston
Dylann roof is less than nothing
The blood that 10 of your kind will Sheridan
Detestable
And using route to justify shoot
Churchgoers is not acceptable on any level
Discussing this crime that is not my primary entry
I feel like other news outlets can
Handle that just fine
This is important for us covers
The disparities
It's coverage that we can Ferry
In this case the contrast
Stark
What else is covering Dylan roofs murder of 9 Congress
Of a black church
He joked about how is that guy really wanted to kill black people roof should have become an abortion.
Any catches coverage largely on that
Kind of territory
With regular insinuations
The black population
South Carolina riot
In the case of the Antioch
Shooting at
Pure and simple racist
Attack on white
People which the media is tried to
The cover-up
Alex does appear to be correct
Inasmuch as this
Antioch shooting
Attack against white people
If you were a normal media Outlet covering the story brought that
Detail up I wouldn't really see a problem with
Disgust
The problem is
Only covers
Because we're White
Our people are victim
Crime
Which is why it's impossible for
For me not to see
That kernel of truth about this attack
Be an expression of a ray
Disposition Whitaker
Comes out of Alex's
So here's what was going on
The Patriot
Okay
Gave this dude a bunch of drugs
He was on a lot of antidepressants that the Patriots
And this was entirely too
To the threat that you have
Deep intelligence or
Conveniently you can't bring up already
Beginning first clip that we heard here was Alex
Harkins
Back to his old Studio
Wistful
Sentimental
Give me to believe that the money
Good
As Alex's
Is literally sat on
Our last episode
And it also makes me
Fillmore
Picture of that
I hear him do this
Incredibly lazy address
For a new product
Now is the most important time to support the info warm
My friends there has never been a more critical time
Republic
Censorship and attacks are at all-time highs
He had his reading voice
Is so different in
Sellmore dispatch
Extemporaneous speaking
And so when you hear that you hear the the time the globalist
Part of the atom
Consistently what he says
Speaking shooting
Is written down for him to read
New your house
Lackadaisical you getting through the
An important distinction
Because
Funny reading about the product
Do
Board voice
The sephiroth
As bombast
Bright
A part of the ad
Yeah most of
His rhetoric there is no line
Demarcation
In between
Stanford shutdown Independence
Aleutians the family against Christians Armitage
We are
Watching game-changing specials
You're that breath
Almost Sy
Memorial Day
What's our system I haven't read this copies
The total health
And performance that has been
Design
Research and development
It's called
Power stack
Which combines all the most powerful Health supplements
Easy-to-use package
You laugh but I think that's a good name
I think we should just
Compared to what
All of his products together to create the appearance of a new product
Tonight we got that
Privacy
I'm at the bus garage
So the descriptions of all the element
Pack
Products that describe products
Quote
Kickstart formula
The quote nootropic brain formula
Literally
Is just a bunch of different words that mean Brave
Formula sounds
Knockout
Factor
One of them
Krill oil
Dollars and ninety-five cents
It's only 5995 is more than half off out the gate
Either
Hyper-inflated base price or we're in real trouble with the money
F*****-up thing
When I looks closer
Products
Okay
Likely sounds
Not the same thing okay that's weird
Website and check the ingredients
Existing product
Some of it
Kinda similar
Like for example probably just going to
I have a combat live at the same three or four ingredient
Product
For some of the products I was able to
The trace to existing things that Alex already
If you're that the new version
Amber just slightly worse for
Missing ingredient
Possibly to cut corners and cut
Car cost
I don't know those my butt
Some of them are just
Hey we took the lemon balm out of
Knockout now expect
The same thing
We got way more L-tryptophan it cuz it's super
I mean
This is business important
Two supplements he doesn't produce them
Explain Global Healing Center run by dr. group
Does he can put on his labels
Manufactured
On the products he doesn't produce in house by law
He has to put manufactured
For the
Center on his label
And every product Alex.
Sal's
Has manufactured for Infowars on
Subcontractor
Structure to actually produce supplement
On his own
To the product
I'm his 8-pack use a trademark
Ingredients
A company called natural remedies private Limited
Which is a good indication that they were the ones who met
Manufacturer is
Exact power
Fordham
Also I think it's a pack power stack or a
I can't remember now
8 pack I can't remember what it is now
Natural remedies
Is that are not primarily
Very natural remedy developer and manufacturer out of Bengaluru India
Market
Animal supplement
Beo magazine
Natural remedies private Limited
Address the unmet
Animal Health industry
The article describes the beginning of how the company came to be
Intrigued by the Alchemy of neem
Healing wounded animals in Mahabharata
Drew inspiration of what he wanted to contribute
To the world
Years later a rough patch came in Shriram laws life
When his beloved horse died who could have been helped by the herbs
This Bitter memory
Closely
Farmers in treating animals
Stimulated
Fill this Gap
Aqr the ale
The animal health
Volume
Infusing the knowledge
Which of aggravated
That's how the company
It wasn't
Religious
Natural healing
In Tradition
Elementary
If it's not strict
Flea religion
Cultural
In his defense
Penicillin
Dylan
What makes products or animal health
Like their product
Which is a topical spray for bovine
A few years back that dude started human side of the business
20%
Of their market share
Their business
Largely
It's just Alex Jones
Goop
There's no real problem with sourcing your products from an Indian veterinary medicine
Do heavy
I Wing to their business
Few questions mostly because this is Alex
We do know that the history of treating veterinarians like human doctors in selling a product that Alex did with doctor told
Like who Veterinary
Another issue that Alex
Displays made in America
For America
Can Industries
India to get different version
Many of the products
He already sells manufactured
Particularly from a business
Primarily Veterinary Health Market
He leads one to believe that maybe my other manufacturers wooden
Work with him
But that's just conjecture I'm not entirely sure what
What the situation is
Yeah well I mean 5995
His overhead
It's probably almost
Hayirli ship
Just to get it from India
I would imagine
It's like once
It can't be
You must be making a profit on 5995
Which makes you
Really question
How much
That's what I'm saying
3995 shipping
From India to have $0.01 for the product
UB gets even twenty bucks
Yeah that could be I don't know
Literally no idea but I find this very weird
I think the thing that lied to me
Down path of life
2D dynamic
What's the
It's so many of the elements
So the products are
Things that he already sells
Yeah
It just seems like
If you are
If you're selling this
And it extensively helps you with
Sleep and it gives you a nootropic
Why would anyone buy any of your other products if they can get them all in this pack
You're undercutting yourself
Are you under cutting yourself
Cutting
Exactly
Please Network my doctor group anymore any
Simulacra still from
I'm not sure that all of them are but
Clearly
Labels
I don't know his business
This is really weird I can't
Probably do something about that
21st
Alex
Very into
Shity
YouTube Somali
No longer giving it up to the Somali pirates know there is an irony they are for
Sure Somali pirates
She has some stories about Molly that he wants
Somali immigrants
To do that
Long time
Making fun of the idea that
People made that Bon Iver
We love long ago
Was a bad idea Alex's going
He's dangerous
Pizza
Propaganda
Do you offer him
For no reason
Are you understand
The thing about it is that he
Silk
Could never
Have the creativity necessary to make something like that
They like
He can
Continually
Use that because it is defective you know like
He would never have been able to make that
He could never it would never exist
I think we've made that point a little bit
It's just s***
He plays the music video
David
Dispersed with
Pieces of
News that
Misrepresented
Molly's being terrifying
And doing
The objects of eyebright haha
PriceRite
Talks about immigrants
Minneapolis
Start singing
Where is Minneapolis
Here
Chief of doublethink
Fall of the Republic flag
Gohan
Kia
Nobody called 911 immediately after hearing that in the studio we have a psychotic break
Occurring right now
Sincerely
I'm worried for your safety
And I'm worried help
I don't know but
What are you talkin about
Kids of hammers will get into later that's a news story that
He's covering
Quite aggressive
Lyrics to the parody song
A m
12th Street
Yeah so I refuse to watch whatever you
YouTube video Alex is talking about there at the beginning
Because we wasn't surprising to me at all
He just pretending
I generally refugees are people who are not leaving their home country cuz there looks
Looking for a change of scenery
They're fleeing would often represent
Mortal Danger
And their only hope
Survival is to get out
Are countless examples of this re-entry from the Tutsis in Rwanda
In the nineties for the people in Darfur in the
Be genocide
Existential
Without living through something like that it's very hard to assume what your mental state might be once you reach a country that represents
All the one-handed probably be thankful that the threat of the intercom way or the
But on the other hand
Good the country you end up in
Is not but even if it were it would never
It may never feel like your home
Parentheses they're not just leaving a
Piece of land in another
Regions where they and their families made that generations of memories and
Heather ham just separate from that place that was their home in a deeply traumatic way with no
Tunity to process the separate
It makes total sense that part of what makes me rent
Do Jeeps. So difficult
Is a feeling that may never go away of wanting to go back
To home that may no longer exist
It's not a longing to leave in a war-torn country cuz America sucks so much
It's a long to go back to
To home they loved before this
Circumstances arose that required
So when Alex points
Somali refugees in Minneapolis who said they want to go back to Somalia I don't feel like that's weird at all
Nor is it any sort of two nuns
Nation of America or display of ungrateful
Disrespect
It really feels like what being
Expressed fears more an example of Alex's inability to feel empathy or understanding
For other people
Because
Tamales
Is Betty hate
It's so much
Don't want to be in America
That
Would be expressing
America
Cuz I don't know if I
Kim
Articulate myself
Right
To be in the
And
In their penis
Why
He's trying to represent
Is it
These Somali immigrants
As well as Omar
To be back in
Bloodthirst
Rapacious
Violent
Come over here in order to
To create
Here at the behest
Of the globalist
To create
A clash of civilizations in order to bring down the West
What's behind
What you saying
Okay
Why they're here though they wished
To be there
That's the version that
The idea of
That is
Is their home country
Longs for
The better days
He's not thinking
Looking like oh how can we help them
Get back
I don't think so
Absent absent from
Be thrilled for
Deportations
Hey wife
Stop here in a minute
Cuz Alex
Hellboy
Very not true story
About David Knight and his wife going to an anti-abortion
Abortion
Baby
Yeah yeah
I know that didn't happen
The only people that I ever really
You're talkin about virtue-signaling or his friend
Alex
People who make accusations
At least that I can see I'm not saying the people on the left
Don't
Necessarily
Call something virtue-signaling but I would say it's a very small piece
The pie
It's sad
The people who say virtue-signaling are often the people who need you to be signaling as opposed to actually
Be virtuous in order to kind of feel better about them
It appears
Is Molly stuff a little bit quicker
Then you might have thought it
It was just a short little trip down
Side roads
To hear of fake story about David nightmares wife
So
Alex is on the warpath
As it were
Somali immigrants
A particularly representative all Barbie
Ringleader
Sure why not
Yet he's focused in on Mini Apple
Because there's a large
Somali population in Minneapolis
What Saint Paul
There is a reference
About him
The kids and
He touches on that
Terrifying
Of Affairs
Minneapolis
Population of fair
Where you have a tax
Little babies being thrown off balcony
Tried to cover it up
That story
He's telling about a baby
Being thrown off a balcony
He's lying with contacts
Your five-year-old boy was thrown off the third-floor balcony
Can you get the Mall of America
Responsible with 24 24 year old named Emmanuel Aranda
Rhonda was born in
Chicago
Is not relevant to Alex
Contacts
This clip existen on the show that's what that's what
Mogadishu
Sew-in 22
All right there's a good portmanteau
Darondo is
Convicted twice for assault that happened at that mall
Once water in one
On women who rejected his advances
These assaults lied to him being banned from the mall with fairly did
Arrived at the mall in April
Intending to kill an adult
That quote
Workout
He chose to throw the child off the balcony and kind of a win
When asked about it then
Defended indicated that he had been coming to the mall for several years and had made efforts
To talk to women in the mall
Caught them to lash out and be aggressive
Well obviously it's awful that anyone would throw child off a balcony
It's kind of clear that this story is not about immigrants
It's not about race
Violence
It's about a man
Entitled to women
And when he didn't get what he wanted he responded with violence
Salter more than enough
To establish a pattern here and is only explanation
For his action
Confirms that
I was just completely lying about the story and you can
By the way
He's willing to use whatever he can
Defend his whites are under attack narrative
Regardless of how the stories
Fit or don't fit into that
Meredith
Because he's white National
Insidious things
Almost
As an undercurrent
Through everything that he
Claims about any violin
It is always
Excuse for talks
Masculinity
If it is not a ritual
Thanks
It is always like it if it's if it's
Racism
Masculine
You know all that stuff
Yeah
Media coverage
Golf Course
To touch on this story but it's also hard
Back to
What do you think about earlier with
The kids of hammers
Sew in
Most of the coverage I can find about that story
About
A gang of Somali youth attacking people
Minneapolis
Pretty f*****-up
Editorial tone
I posted the American Thinker accuses the media and police
Lisa covering up the attack
But it does so kind of tips are handled little
Quote
Now that the Old 97
Percent plus Caucasian
Thursday's ultra-protective of its prized
Diversity in Dowling Somali I would like you to rewrite that from start to finish
And then go hide in a barrel of water
Call r.j.
The media is covering up the attack
Buy a piece of
The article
Representative ilhan Omar who represents Minneapolis most ungrateful people we've ever offered ref
How about we go to a barrel
Haha
Jump into it
And here's a milkshake
It's her responsibility now to behave exactly how
Call Ralph
Don't you remember on every white man it's written if anybody not white is not grateful
The guy who runs insta
The pond at the cries of the media wasn't putting
The teen's alleged
It describes nationality
Their headline
Instead they were small
Showing gratitude to the
There's a super consistent
Trendon all this coverage
Be centered around the idea that one
We shouldn't be accepting refugees to
They should live here as subservient
In order to show their appreciation to
Do the white people who let fear
And that's a really sucked up thing and it's more f***** up how consist
And it isn't that I've read about this story
We
Let the bright everyday I think to myself thank God that I let
Carol live
Thank God that I let
Don I like you
As far as I can tell this story May well be
Have a group of youths
Possibly Somalian
It's possible but also these commentators
Bitrode all these blog post that I've read
They're just working office
The police dispatch recording it was released that they were looking
For 11:50
Small
But that's just based on where people who called 911
That doesn't mean they're
Person who called 911 describe them that way
These people could be right
Describe people
Especially if you were in a Somali refugee
Population
There's an inn
A very good chance that literally
Anybody brown that you see anywhere you might just assume is tomorrow
We're not that is the case
Just a possibility
Eyewitness News
It's irresponsible for these
But these blogs
To be demonized
Somali community and all immigrants apparently
Based on
Non concrete reporting
So if it's accurate and it was a group
Smiley team threatening people at a bus station with pipes
Describing it hammer
They should be arrested
I don't know if it's Ruth justify demonized
Tire small earrings
But what's important is that these people like Alex and all these Publications
They don't care about this story
They care only so much as they can use it as a prop to
Nice immigrant
Attack Elon Omar
The bygone
Peaceful days when their cities were 97
That's what's going on here
Group that should
Speed Demon
In this story
Teams because there are roving bands of youth's everywhere.
Teens are underfoot
They're everywhere
M35 anti
Very protein
When I was 12 that ever since
So
We jump off these Smiley narratives here
Anything that he gets into
Especially because of how it ends up laying out
Alex
Is responding to a story it's right-wing blogs
Consider attacking Bernie Sanders
Because
He held up a chicken
Weighing or a drumstick
Take a picture with a man who happens
African American
This is why it's interesting
These right-wing blogs are talking about that as if it's
I'll look at this racism
But Alex's take on it is
Come on guys
What yeah
No
He's version of it
I hate Bernie
But you guys
You doing stuff like that
It's very
It's very weird I promise
It's super weird but how it ends up playing out on this episode
It gets you back to normal.
Even ask
He's defending
Bernie Sanders about there
It does seem that he
He gets a little racist on his own
It's 2
You'll see
Bernie Sanders
He's at a restaurant showing off
Somebody
My mouth water just thinking about drumstick
Also a little bit later I didn't try to clarify this but Alex is like
You talked about the story a little bit more and he's like guys
So I can go get some pasta
This app to another layer rate
Number one
Guns
Most important fact number two we thought was racism
Actually number two
Food trumps racism it does a little bit
See that you got that's all you need to know
About
Real racism when black people
I don't know that ended well but
Alright so that was that was a real I was a real Dan Harmon story Circle kind of situation
Feel like you're on good territory where you're saying everyone loves chicken then
Graduated
Just don't know
Introduction
Pieces
This is a pretty great
No
Delivery
Popeye's Chicken
But we'll get to that
Middlesex Corp no
Think there's a strategy
But in the next without starts talking about the
A little bit of a conspiracy
About weather
Chemtrail stop
Establishment wants me off the air
Is because we have a fighting spirit
And we believe we can change things
We've done that
Thanks to the audience the steak
Successful
When I was going to do really during this little 5 minutes
Or really make that point sailing Italy
And post it
Westside Players called action
Whatever happened to the environment
Almost everyone I know in Texas
Outside
Whatever Texas
Black screen
Real reason
Future
Please do new California
We are basically toilet bowl of China
So this is weird
I think he's just talking
Complete s***
Because here's the thing Jordan
The Texas commission on Environmental Quality
Stanley statistics about air pollution
Records that are easily available online
Obviously things very day today
Sources of air pollution work that way
But if you look at the data
Are getting worse
In the last year's
Because of China
Dumping things in the Jets
I know what you're saying
Standard reported in April of this year
Some cities is getting worse
It's getting better another
Uncle talks to Janice no
Can you put that the annual state of the air report looking at air pollution
Send levels in America
Insidious 2019
If there was one
Worsening air condition
It's climate
With warmer weather temperatures the more weather patterns that lead
To Drought which leads to wildfires which creates smoke
In fog
Just definitely affecting air quality in the
It's not even real
Houston has been pointed at as April
Particular hotspot of bad air but the recent years were hurricane Harvey
And that fire at in the Deer Park petrochemical plant
Insane amounts of fine particle pollution
Never shutting up
Also the Jets
Stream is not a stationary thing
It's not like
It's not like it's starts in China picks up some smog carries it over the
Pacifica just drops it down over Alex's house
I think he's almost a rainbow
You know like
Like the jet stream dips down whatever it is
Think that
If you had the right
He could just jump in China
Need to get home
Trying to find out
I don't know what do you think
To be representing
It's very childish version of how weather patterns
The jet stream
Studies that attract Chinese pollution
West Coast
The jet stream dips down in Texas
Just dropped off Johnny's Belushi
There's some indications of pollution
From the California wildfires definitely reach
But from what I can tell Alex is stretching a little bit
Cuz he's talks
Quite a bit about his allergies
Like this is like carries Bell's palsy
Definitely not that I
At the Palmer weather
Gaylord weather
We know that Alex has been very wishy-washy about
In the past
Month very very much turning on him and then saying I love him
For sure has landed I mean I'm sure within a month he'll say f*** this guy again tomorrow
Because Trump has made some in
Medications that he's going to
Try and force
Quotes on social media platform
And all that I think Alex has decided
We're going to move forward with a pro Trump
Opposition
And in order to reinforce that one of the things he has to do is he has to try and chip in
The people who have
Next clip
He is trying to make the argument
Support
Straub
He is turning on him
As is Fox
Obviously
I know for a fact
That there's a litmus test going on
On whether people will accept
The removal of president
Trump
Or not
So if Alex knows for sure that there's a
Litmus test going around Fox
Haven't gotten fired
Support
Very similar to ours they're clearly secretly behind the
Willing to
To turn on him
If the globalist to remove Trump from power so therefore
Even though they look like the most
Zephyrus Trump supporters around
Alex is the only real deal in town
Alex
The deuce is loose
He is
Denying The Patriot
The populist movement
God
Piro Jeanine Pirro clearly isn't even travel
I don't know if you still wanted to know who he is
Shepard Smith
I don't know man this is really stupid
Just trying to find some ways to differentiate him
Himself from
These places that are more profit
Lest you think that Alex is talk about revelation
On our last episode
Alex now gets into some religious
Just talk
Vet
Poorly
Interesting ways I would say
Understand
Printing traduce
Ocean of the Buy
Zip tie
Just a
You know what I mean I can't come up with a better way
Not if you talk about King James
Nothing is his Telltale
Ash what the Bible says
Not true
A couple times
Red
Testament that Christ shed
Gadgetry
I think from the estimate in red I think from that
He doesn't understand that
This is where they're always in
In most Editions
Yeah that's what tradition of of
The actual when it was originally written they specifically wrote it in Red by or that this was somehow
More important among the things Jesus said
It really feels to me like
You think that those are two
Two different things
Being in red and
Jesus said it
Which is not the case of every edition of the Bible
Majority of them
Allah Jesus
His words are in red
Maybe more
Evangelical world
Versions of the Bible
That's
Pretty strong
Then let's say
I don't know Eleuthera
Churches that I went to grown-up our Bibles were
Provided directly from
Alright
Yeah
So
Alex is getting into this
Mode where he's
Breeding
Which I would say
It's not a good sign
For a propagandist
It really does especially after that earlier the clip where he was talking about Fox News rigging debates and all that stuff
Whenever he was talking about the
Success story
This whole show and I put it up an hour to put it up
Call to Arms and you're like no
You just
You just wrote of eulogy
Your sentimental four-year-old
Cheap Studio cuz
You know you have to make
Subpoenaed
Good to hear just
Outright
Preaching
Yeah
The scripture
Finish next play
And then he
So weird OK was one of the things that made me like
Play the last episode we did about Revelation apocalypse
Literature
Well that's pretty normal that's just a normal
Doomsday
Interpretation of
Religion
I was like
This is
Interesting crazy
Orange men do not
Nor of a bramble bush
Gather the grapes
A good man out of
Good treasure
Of his heart brings forth
That was yours
This is the
Versus after the verse
About time
You know a tree by its fruit
And he just kept going
That which is evil
His mouth
Why everywhere
Exactly what I was watching
Why do they lost after creating crime
Why do they lost after attacking question
Because it's the abundance of their heart
Spiritual
It is an operating system
Call it a spell
What
Country
Go under
Mass psychosis
Pushing the psychosis
They degrade to the very lowest common denominator
Pyramids
What
Wavelength
Whatever you want to say
Every culture
Eating babies for every culture
So I was so fascinated by that cuz I like
Weird
Figure out what this light.
Good stuff
Literally a site in Egypt called The Black Pyramid
Is created by Eminem hot
I just got into my head with Eminem lyrics Eminem
I didn't go all that well
Another pyramid
That pyramid was built during the 12th Dynasty
In Egypt
After which point
Civilization
For a very long time
Also the Black Pyramid was never fully
Construct
Didn't happen at the end
Decline of that Civilization
Also according to Scholars the practice of human sacrifice outside of the possible
Instances of killing prisoners of
The war in the ritualize version
Capital punishment
Send it around the beginning of the second
Steve Farber up for the time of
Eminem hot the Third
Believe that the practice was far more prevalent
Actually was
It's really easy to convince people that
Easy like it
Really
Predisposed somehow
3 pyramid
Conspiracy theories about a secret Black Pyramid that was once there and no one wants you to know about
In 1737 Explorer Frederick Lewis Norton
Visited
Egypt
Called travels
Egypt and Nubia
Published in 7th
Conspiracy theorist of pieces of attacks to argue that there's a fourth pyramid that should be
Is not
And it was made of a black granite material unlike the other
3 pyramid
Is there
Is that was true
Of course not it's just a result of a mistranslation
From the original French Norton.
Describe the fourth pyramid As You Are
Which is to say more black or darker
Other places
Send a text to specified
They're made out of black
Not it is
He's clearly speak
Of this
Parative level of Blackness
Also scholars believe that he mistook
Satellite pyramid of one of the other three
Pyramids for being a great pyramid in another
Itself
So this Black Pyramid doesn't
I could ever exist
I don't want to put too fine a point on this
Other than these two examples I can find no evidence of any black pyramids anywhere in the world
Not in Central America and South America
Anywhere
But I did run into a few
Few possibilities of where Alex might become
Okay I think
Might be what he's talking about
I don't know if it'll be hard to say
So this is two truths and a lie
No I mean there's no guessing game
There's a book that was written by Joseph Bushnell a
It's called Curly in the Aztec gold published
Which features are Central American Black Pyramid
The pyramid is a Herald that the adventurer is
Location
The Treasure of the Aztec
The problem is this was the work of fiction published invoice
Specifically for the Boy Scout Democrat
It was part of a series of Boy Scout Adventures
It's a work of fiction
Pyramid was made up that were six Liquors The Legend of Korra I don't think so I think it's just
Coincidence
Okay
Here's the joke
Not too far back
Chris Brown did start a clothing
New event is called Black Pyramid
So if
Not outside the realm of possibility
Buzz Marketing for them
There's no but I don't know what you're talkin about
18 babies
Easy saying that every culture
It falls apart
Especially
Pyramid building cultures
Incur
Egyptians
This is absent
He's just making this up
That is built of Black Pyramid has eaten
When you eat all your babies that's what your civilization doesn't go anywhere
We know that none of our civilization
The Black Pyramid
Babies
Hypothetical
I don't think
Should be pitching this way then
I don't know I think the closest
If I had to guess
The closest thing
To explain
About is
Probably that Giza mistranslation
Popular
Conspiracy world
81 reference
1 mistranslation
One-flight
Idiom that is missed
Now we have a burgeoning
Conspiracy
Implied
Information
It should give you a sense
Of
How little he looks
You could just
That
Even start talking
And how they because this is Victor levels of like
Priest has a plus one
F****** Cana
So he's trying to justify his declaration
Let you know you got a little bit too far Black Pyramid
Course and this is how he chooses
To support his thesis
And it's not good
Equation of glass
That's the Titanic program
Interesting weird piece of
Implying a suicide
Because of what he
They were in the first class
Next
Captain offer to chance
Commit suicide
Any toast
Suicide
Did the way that he's suggesting
It's not even like
Committing suicide
It's like a
But you get to choose
Sia
Gordian was only a for 21 days and after his son was killed in battle he hung himself without knowing that his time was up
Since their rule
Contested as it was
Years old he's kind of f*** no matter what he did
Again it was a death sentence but you know
Yeah
That's not
His top General iberogast
He was the real power in the Empire
He was the one who found Valentine
You killed him or paid someone else
When he started building that black.
Killed himself to resolve a war he was undertaking poorly against by Tilia
Knowing that his forces were unlikely to win
Against this enemy
It's far more just to Parrish one4all than many 41
He then went to bed woke up the next morning and stab himself in the gut
Historians like tacitus of notice
Civil War
He was looked upon as a hero after
Quintilius is that Joe committed suicide but it's Oracle records are on
Unclear
Somebody was murdered
Suicide but the records are very great about
And if statement about that
Nero committed suicide after he was informed that he bent riding UPS
Dance to death by the Empire who would ultimately
YouTube down and bring him back
Believe it narrow it actually committed suicide
And that led to rumors going around
Eventually
Return to wage war against
It's a bit of an open question but there's some Scholars that believe that the prophecy
Seasoned Revelation are largely about this
The coming return of narrow
Who is a well-documented oppressor of Christian
Prominent
Interpretation of the Book of Revelation
Version but it's certainly not
Certain
There's some debate about
But there are there are some
Pretty strong indication
Is that a lot of the idea of the return
AR
In reference
DeNiro in the idea
Everybody of note kind of went along with that
Another very popular part of the interpretation
Choose that
Nero
Suicide
But the people claiming to be Nero with
Come back and try and use
Starpower
To pretend that they were near us
They they did not go from zero to Nero
No
I told you trying to do that was not good
Jordan jokes
Julie Rose
I apologize
So anyway the point here is that no Roman emperors committed suicide in the manner that Alex's
Describing
Might have been murdered two killed
Themselves to avoid certain Capital Pawn
Punishment one killed himself knowing that he was a Sitting Duck
Alex is full of s***
None of this justifies his argument that they killed themselves
Babies
Class blah blah blah black.
This is all just
Anybody who listens to
Pathetic
Think that anybody
Might
Knows what he saw
Yeah I know that was crazy
That was absolutely just
Pulled from thin air fun
I realize it would I kind of
Resonate within the present day
What makes it so difficult is a lot of
The stuff is really dangerous rhetoric
People getting hurt
Stuff your stocking
Fuckingawesome
Enjoy how wrong he
He is about stuff
Because it allows us to be
Education
Am Joy Bryant
To learn a little bit
Explore these things
And talk about what the truth
Wickaboag sure that you didn't know all of the Roman emperors who committed suicide
The show that I really enjoy
And that's why
Is more fun
Christmas pics
Fart
Awful about
Knowing that people are going to get hurt
Because of what he offers the opportunities to learn
When we are in the Pres
Because of the
Contacts
Where is
This stuff yeah yeah yeah course coming tomorrow
Where is if we look at 2013 we do know what happened the next day
Like that
Because he said stuff like this
Is just awful
And they're going to take
They're going to get you
She realized
AR
And what they are
Book
You're a God
Because they are gone there
Is your children
Before we go to watch face
So I mean like what you have there is just like all of your enemies the last
The globalist
See
Immigrants
The lgbtq
Atq folk all of them are just demonic project
Trying to stop us from going off-planet
Don't care about them
Don't even
Think about the ideas that they have all they want is you
Your children
So f***** up
Yeah
More difficult to deal with
Opportunity
The Roman emperors
Are impeded by
Anyone
Because if anyone believes
Roman emperors
Committed suicide because they were all like
That's a historical
Fiction that they're believing in
Inform the present day
Like you're not going to be able to lash out at the Roman Emperor
Bright
You know where the target of this
It's very hard
To hear what if we all just
Stop doing everything
Okay
And just really focused on making sure people like
Alex
Who are saying that what's going on
Is where all impeding their progress
What are we
Really focused on getting them off
I feel like we would probably not be able to
You do that and probably
It would waste time that we need to focus on other things I don't know
Maybe get rid of them
I think it's an interesting idea allow them their space colony
Islam maybe it's not
Christianity maybe it's just guys like Al
Incompatible
Deserve their own
And that Nation should be on the bucket I don't think there's anything
Incompatible about white
I think if there is something
Incompatible
People who believe groups
The people are incompatible
It is
Disqualifies the possibility
This allows the possibility of people living together
I don't know if you
To have a white nationalist
I feel like that might come back to bite us
The ass though because we stole it from them
The legends about being an exile
A good path to go down
You know
Feel like education
The best possibility
You probably don't have the time for it
That's the approach I'm going to stick with cuz I don't know if we
We can get them to Mars
Alex has a gecko
Stu's very proud
Dealing with some tough times Pauly Shore
Impasse on the show
Okay.
The weasel okay
Stephen Baldwin
It's
I heard that he was going to be
Guest on the show
Can punch on this
I do not care at all
But after listen
I realized
What year that we should get into
Here is
Bit of an introduction
Alright welcome back blazing gentlemen thank you so much for joining us on this live Tuesday May
21st
2019 Volvo transmission
As a joke
So we had count dankula yes of course
Of course it's count
You never suspect a Angela
Is not going to prison
020 in a joke
I refuse to accept your credit
Decide
Feel like I should read it again
Mark meechan so he's not going to prison 800-pound fine for posting
The video where he trained his dog to Heil
He's refused to pay that fine
Best way to appeal the verdict but I see no evidence
Other than possibly like a holding
Or that he's facing the possibility of jail
Not only is he not looking at jail time
You currently running for MP on the Q-tip ticket
Which is probably little more high-profile of thing that he should
Should be trying to get involved in
So you're saying that it was a joke
Got his dog to do the Heil Hitler
You can party
People who've rally to his
When you're making Chucky videos by dogs doing Hitler salute
People might think you're an a****** and you end up
Concurring a small fine
Review run for public office
People are going to start actually research
And that's bad for business
Discord server
There was a cesspool of racism and anti-semitism
Meeting himself posted tons of races
Around the n-word a bunch
But was more telling was
The stuff is members
Proposed is the question.
People were advocating
Tacos nuking Muslims went around
Free
Sport was expressed for the audible
Send division a Neo-Nazi group link 25 murders in
The US
People post
The group would quote actually do something
The BBC notes
Remember of Sonic
Pretty good reason
Recirculating material advocating
Prince Harry
For being a race traitor
Beecham's Discord server shutdown
Become part of the campaign rhetoric moving forward
I got to say that you kept is really knocking it out of the park in terms of letting s*** heads run for office and their name
Tommy Robinson all running under their Banner
This level of shitheadra may never be top
You kind of got to feel bad for count dankula
Third build
Discord server ship barely even registers as notable
Yeah that's said that's who do you want to die
Sargon
No
I don't know what do you mean
Also-ran
Exactly
Do all his bigotry and all his nonsense
Is good enough to make him a hero now with his eyes
And so he'll be coming up here in a little bit
On the show
But the interview.
Start immediately
Evolve
Into
Some weird
Thoughts
Okay Ru starts talking about how what he did with his dog
And
They would have
Looney Tunes
Cartoon
Or Donald Duck
Do they do satirist
Things about the
Alex says this nothing but I just think it's really funny
Donald Duck
The hall Hitler
B
You are looking
Like you're terrified
Call nine-one-one right now
Various
Terrifying
Even if
Even if count dankula
Hitler
Bennallack starts rambling about how he had a dog that is now past
Suspicious
Looks like it had a Hitler mustache because of the group
And he said that he got it to do a
Hitler salute
I think he's really just trying to get it on
Marc's
Just a bit also being Hitler dog guy yeah
Yeah it's
A little bit sad
To be Hitler dog got you got to give it a shot
Yeah it's a pretty
Pathetic display on Alex
Estes Park
Best thing on this episode
Apparently his children are into watching
Speed running videos
A video games on YouTube
I don't mind share one
I don't mind some of the
Take some long for me to watch
So Alex has his kids watching
Speed running videos
And I'm not sure he understands
I watch Like A nine-hour Final Fantasy
99 are Final Fantasy
Crazies
May I recommend building a ship in a bottle
Groupon
Alex yells about how great astronauts
Were and how great
They had
Being able
Control the shuttles
Switch joystick
As sort of an analog
How trivial
The speed Runners are
This is so weird so he's comparing speed Runners to astronauts
Alright
I feel like that's a little unfair
I'll let him
Pika pika
Did Nintendo joysticks that can do things that robots can't do
Robots can't do it
Sure
All the perfect moves to perfectly go through a game at the maximum speed
Business
A lot of them are married and a lot of them have made businesses out of speed running video game
More than Alex
Military
Sizing ocean man
What they do and how they spend their lives that's your life
Level of skill
Wash down the toilet
Over video game
Is sad
Oh man
You have preset
If LeBron James had funneled all of that going to war
Right
Play Child
F*** off
Yeah that's sort of mentality could be applied pretty capriciously across-the-board
What I would say is I really love
How that clip started
Against top robots robots robots
Who wrote the robot
Coordination
Talking about these
Competition
People are going
Robot
Quotes
Tool assisted speedrun
Yeah
Who is people who programmed the input
Controller in order to make
The most
Perfect run possible
Trying to talk about I believe so and I heard him say
Lego robot
I really think that's what he said
Is really about to assisted speedrun
And people racing that are sometimes able to
To beat these two little sister
Speedrun
Which is the most perfect way to go through it
Is because sometimes shortcuts are found
And it takes a long time to program a tool assisted speedrun
Sulfate before someone would be able to reprogram the computer run
Through the game
Someone could have discovered a glitch
To be able to do it
Situations where people are talking about
Frame perfect
Nearest
If you could program the 12 glitches
A human will not be able to do better than a robot
Because
It takes too long to program
Can do faster than robot
Anyway
Whatever else to talk about is if you watch a video with his kids don't understand what's going on
Which is kind of funny
It also said that he doesn't understand
AP understood how huge Market that is
Could tap into
Gamers
No they were making what was it there was just a recent report that it was
Looks like they're making
$30,000 in
An hour for
Twitch stream
Robot
Top robot
I'm not talking s***
Gamers
Turns it around a little bit
You have your speech I have mine I'm not trying to take your girlfriend
Your cell phone video game
Where you're comfortable I place your comp
Ultra reality
Someone else to control your life to make sure you never amount to anything
What's a snare
Human world that is now
For you
Shower if you don't
I'll tell you products
YouTube
Apocalyptica
Go f*** yourself and then buy my products while I mean it's a little bit apocalyptic
You look you guys enjoy your life
Now I have products
Bad
We will
Gamer
I bet
Get the 8-pack double stack
Replace the Ruby Red Mountain Dew with the Apex
Code Red Mountain Dew
Everyone wins
Killer interview
Thank you I'm sorry I forgot his honorific title
Desperate to let everyone know that he did Hitler dog
On top of that
Hitler mustache
Looking for someone to pay attention to you and anyway
This has raised a ton of money for his own like free-speech grip that he's on and I was running
A f****** MP in the UK
He's gone from
Nobody to
Someone who I would have on my show
Just because he didn't Hitler dog thing I have to anybody
No one cares
Text clip
Is making the argument
That are dead the last
Obviously
And his argument is that it went
From milkshake
To Brick
In a matter of days
He fails to recognize is that they're too
Group
Rocks at Tommy Robinson
Are not the same people who are milkshaking
People now
Not like that's a one-to-one escalation
So that's a problem
I meant seconds
At
It count dankula so you might feel better
I think so actually I'm not entirely sure if he's one of them
He said that if someone threw a milkshake on him
Share great good for you
Grow up
So he's trying
Make this argument that escalated so quickly and then now we're going to
Killed
He does something that I signed entirely disgraceful
Interim
Justifying
Ketamine and enema out of days it went from milkshake tubex
And Des
Ramada days and then you put people in the media.
Eden on I think it's that's only going to be a matter of time before someone you know
Not your father's Tommy Robinson you do me a solid going well we're going to get hit with a milkshake
We're going to be seriously assaulting someone is going to be in jail
Someone's going to get hotlist result
And a day
People that
One of the main things the switch was absolutely
Tragic horrendous thing and obviously measures should be taken to prevent such a thing from ever happening again
So
It's hard to hear what he said there cuz of that Scottish brogue but what are you saying is
Is that the murder of Joe Cocker
Logistic Lee measures
Have you taken to prevent a thing like a murder of Jo Cox ever happening again
That's something that I find really
F****** in
You don't know Joe Cox was a Labour MP who was murdered
Shot and stabbed multiple times
X back in 20
Listen to Someone Like Tommy Robinson or Alex Jones
Without you know they
Completely overrun Britain
Heroes like Tommy are the only ones with
That wasn't the case
52 year olds
Scottish thomas-alexandre mayor was the culprit
A little bit
Interesting to reflect on
The measures might be put in place that could help avoid something like that ever happen again
There was a big fan of one of the UK's big right-wing Terror
David Coppola
Coupled with a
Devotee of
Franklin Pierce
The author of the Turner Diaries
Any planted three nail bomb
Comes back in 1999
Specifically targeting
And a gay Pub
Respectively
Copeland was associated with the National Alliance
SanSai was Thomas
As they were both subscribers of their publication which almost
Glee It's called free
If there's one thing that is so clear from
History and so forgotten and not talked about enough
It's
Has long been a central piece of the Neo-Nazi strategy
Seeing what we now see
See from these right-wing s*** heads
Painfully predictable
Marisol Sosa
Subscribe
Call SA
Which was about to play
10 South Africa
He wasn't only a reader he also wrote the magazine
I still have faith
The white race will prevail
South
I fear that it's going to be a very long and very bloody
Struggle
You see
Tomas Maier with a dyed-in-the-wool white supremacy
No National
People of other races
His primary focus was on collaborators
From his letter
In my opinion the greatest enemy of the old apartheid
System was not the AMC
See you in the black masses
But the white liberals and
Traders
Overtime
These racially-based feelings
Who was a traitor and who was
Contemporary politics
Reflected Pookie salt with a traitor
And the days just
Before the attack
The Liberals the left and the media
Google flights
I don't understand
He felt an urgency apparel
Carry out his attack because he was confused
The white race
Spacing exercise
We're just coming in the form of refugees and immigrants
Holistic
Khalifa Tommy Robinson Alex Jones gal about constantly
Merit attended rallies run by the English
Defense League
How much of an introvert
We join up with group
I don't understand
In the days leading up to the murder of Jo Cox
Party were running camp
Specifically designed around
The immigrants were an invading horde that we're going to destroy the country
And leaving the
EU was the solution
Into that problem
Jo Cox was chosen as a Target
Because she was
Strongly anti brexit
But she was a traitor to the White
Because of that
All this is to say
Did the person who killed Joe Cocker
Believe all the same
Things that the people count dankula
What's up with you
He was motivated to action in some part by the rhetoric put out by you
The f****** party 2
Count dankula is running for office
All of the rhetoric put out by the guy who's interviewing
Is indistinguishable from the writings of Thomas
For this dumb dumb
Get on f****** are
The s*** about Joe Cocker
His murder is repug
If you would take a look in the mirror and realize that the
And profits from
Is the same one that mayor came out of
And here's the thing
I know
You can't blame the person who puts out the hateful rhetoric for the actions of the people who believe the exact
Bootcamp
Comedian your little snowflake Teddy baby cook soy boy
Comedy
Or not
Hi judge of the Queens
Court Nigel
To say
To carry out a terror
Inspired
Thomas Mair
To begin with
Just
The thought as a joke
But he couldn't get it out of his head
The thought became stronger
He woke up one day and decided he was going to do
Has been an inspirational Force
Winter risen in the UK
Started out with jokes
Jokes
Make jokes
I mean
Sing it started out as a joke
Expose reductive
I don't want
Characterized
By that
Or even by himself but I don't
Trust that
There there was a little malice
In there from the beginning
It wasn't it wasn't it
Joke
Define is a joke
Annette
That's between those shall not be together
I think the most important thing though is that
Hey there they're completely wrong
There
Sweetly wrong
The escalation is
Never going to
From milkshakes
Because bricks are far less
Effective than milkshake
When fighting against these guys look
Silly is infinitely more effective than hurting the milkshake will escalate
The bricks being thrown at people with milk
Because what
What is more effective at
Declawing a guy like Nigel farage than a headline reading
Nigel farage in bus hiding from milkshake
Absolutely
Giant p****
Thrown at him and all of a sudden
Smarter you are throwing milkshake
Understand
Jordan
Count dankula and everything
Dance for this pitiful free-speech Griff that he's on his bad enough but to descend
Was just f******
Sympathetic
You think measures should be taken to make sure that things like
Yeah we should Outlaw far-right party
Did you need to recognize that the ecosystems that create Foster and nurture people like
You need to recognize
You need to recognize the intentionally manipulative media strategies that I'm tagging Aizen played to the same
Paranoid race
That led him to murder
You need to recognize
The political figures that are
Spoiled nativist and races
Spears in order to make a name for them
Make money
Then when you're done with that
Recognize that you're immediately and intimately involved with all of that s*** you're on the wrong side of it
And the only measure thneed
Harford County
Goddamn 800-pound fine
Shut the fuk up
And tell his friends
To do the same
Will go a long way
Towards
For topping make sure
Smashers
In the world count dankula
Well
Nearest bucking fine
Want to
To say to him if you want if you want
Change
Contacts
Some immigrant being
Whatever whatever Boogeyman they want
And say what measures would you take
To stop this from happening today feel
How do we stop this
Well I mean
It would we were chatting too loud
Temperature
Committing acts of Terror
Okay
Done
It's f****** stupid their measures against terrorism
Does Keith even advocating that
F****** whiteness
He's not
Paying lip service to like
Measures should be taken to make sure
Is on the left dark killed but like
YouTube
Okay so you like
The only measures that would be actually helpful here are exactly the things that are counter to your stupid
Free-speech grip everything about your existence
And what you stand for in the only reason
Counter
2N
Fighting against
The idea of
Creating those measures
They could protect
Sogo
Fuckyourself you
Stupid
Scottish
Kind of like his accent a little bit
Yeah kind of Joya
That's good
Scottish Twitter and you will have a
With
Accents
Avis Mexico
The context
That you knew that
He's talking about
The left
You might think
Accuses Ally
Perfectly describe Ali
If you if you defend yourself against these attacks you
Sasha's races not save Safeway excetera
If anyone comes out me with a milkshake you know I woke them up and down the street
If someone told me I will defend myself and I've always had an example to make sure that nobody has to do it again
Said that I will defend myself
But people use the violin one boil
I'm not the one that's going out trying to insult people
I say to defend myself you're saying you're so people usually instigate
We always try and even though you just said there's okay
Bestow try and paying you as the bad guy even though they all the people instigating that there
They have an absolute complete lack of self-awareness boeglin that Decon
They kind of feed themselves for what baby Lianna
Wow you really want to experience
Envoy
Begin with an O my God
It looks like to me you know what they wanted
Dehumanized to the to the point
My God
Free because they made themselves convinced that you know
Demonizing immigrants Muslim lgbtq
Is he actually Banksy
Are we sure he's up
Performance art scam of like
Here's how I'm going to tear that everybody else
Do it
I'm going to say
No probably not
Because these are easy
Waze
You're going Keyser Soze on it
Because I can't believe otherwise
If it if there's no master plan behind this
Stan Houston
As dumb as some somebody we might elect Brett
Yeah I agree
Square Pizza
It's important to remember here
That
Made a meal out of
You're not paying lip service
Stupid ideas
Joe Cox's murder
When you look into the person
Who committed the murder a lot of things
Media spheres that
Existed in or exactly
Play the same thing
They're being open
On the Discord server run by yeah
And then if that's not bad
Alex expresses
I believe the fear that led
Marital murder
Next clip
Race-based groups
Read White
Tomorrow
George Soros
Nazi collaborator
Interpretation
Really the one with the Nazi past
Sure
Exact
Was it
Operational
Person acting out and killing
So I mean anytime
I don't know if all
The last of the UK's
Use the memory of Joe Cox are in good time
I'm not as fully aware of politics
So I'm not going to
To say that for what I am going to say
Is this
Absolute disgrace
Super care in anyway and exist on this platform
Is an indication that
You don't care where you don't know
And or your f****** with milk
So Alex Jones
Text Cliff he comes in
From break
With mother
As as a feather boy left
No he still there he's still there so Alex is just singing while the Scottish dude is on the
Okay
Alexandrite jewelry running
Count dankula
Jorge comedian
Years in the trenches doing open-mic some shows every night off of multiple night
I always get a little suspicious when I hear someone aggressively give themselves the title comedian or successful comedian and I can slide litter
Really no evidence
I'm doing comedy
Reminders work if you can confess all comedians
I came up empty on my
Search result that I could find was just a story about his Nazi dog video that credited him as a comedian
No real evidence
I came across a piece Byrider Mick cloherty
Comedians
Scotland
It turns out
Much of him
Here are some quotes from the article
For me personally the most offensive thing about the whole debacle is that the news media freak
Currently refer to Mark meechan throughout as a comedian
Muchin is lower-tier of lager
He has to stand up comedy what Rebecca Black is two hard-working band
Who played around
Material
Cereal with innuendo irony and real satire is quite frankly not the same
An improvised racial diatribe and Dorito crumbs Vape cloud
From your stupid mutton-chop face I told you this guy's have great insults
Robert Brown
Anyone
Can call themselves a comedian
He's not a peer
YouTube is created in the Democratic comedians who assumed you're not laughing because you're offended
Pull it back just a little bit dude I'm with you but pull it back a little bit we're getting a little close to Nick depalo here calm it down
Another comedian said quote
You my dog
You were saying that as a critique on people who think they're
Another comedian said quote
Comedians feel scared about this and I would ask
Shouldn't you be scared bigger materials just anti-semetic
There's no comparison
For well-thought-out research
Tire
This is just some
Country train a dog
Which is
That's a lot of effort to react
Most part of the article is that the comedians that are interviewed and the writer
You shouldn't be getting
Prosecute
That's just too
Too harsh but they also think he's a racist
Neo-Nazi hacked on the Free Speech Chris to make money
This is a conclusion that the article comes to
What that we should really do with Mark meechan is to leave him to make shity YouTube videos for America
Teenagers
I can pick up no harsher punishment
Tommy Robinson interview
Leave him with the realization that his most earnest
Defenders are the ones wearing Jack
That last line is so great
He is allowed to not wrestle with
Because of the position.
Is that like
The people
Who
You are surrounded with and the only people who support you
They happen to be.
Scout
Make of that what you will you would think that that
There's so many comedians in Chicago
Heavy scare quotes around
You've been to so many open mics where guy has been there
Yeah and you're like
Just not
Just don't be this isn't for you just go away and now imagine that guy was a f******
Popular YouTube
Gross running for UK
Into the line of like whether or not
You're allowed to call yourself
Comedian until
XYZ point
I don't want to do that
Yeah I like
So do I go f*** yourself count dankula
Because you call yourself
Successful
All behalf of all comedians you the f****** bird
No s***
Not as successful
So I told you earlier
His staff
On the task
Popeyes
And now middle of this interview
Alex
Get the Popeyes
I should tell you that I know exactly what's going on okay
Story where there are people who are accusing birdiebee rapist
A chicken
Check
Good face arguments all I assumed in the same way
Keeps bringing up Vicky is also done the Nazi dogs
He is eating his chicken on are in a
Desperate attempt
Everingham
Everpure stunts
But the way he does it is
Okay
The left says
Is photographs
What else
Northern projection
Wewatchit
It was wrong
And the right-wing jumped on it
Because
Really screwed up
Restaurants
Another food
Pizza Popeye's fried chicken
Which is really really good
Again
The idea
Everything is racist everything is bad they are
That was f******
This is not a sponsor
Pathetic attempt
To get some sort of run off press coverage of like
No one is going to do that
Bernie Sanders
Everybody knows
Do they have Spa
Jordan
I need to know that cuz if your Popeyes
Add a Scottish person
Who's never had Popeyes
That's just rude
That's rude
Deep irony that Alex Jones is doing this Fried Chicken racism
He's well he's interviewing a Scottish alleged
Comedian count dankula
You know why
Cuz the Scottish Inn
Invented fried
The Scottish invent Fried Chicken
American tradition not South America
American South tradition of Rights
Is the synthesis of the spices
Pan-frying techniques
It's from the Scottish combined
Slavery
Studies of migration patterns in the early America early American history
Reflected the Protestant Irish immigrants
Arrived early on settled largely
Virginia North Carolina
Tennessee
As opposed to
Catholic IRA
Cities along
East Coast
Much of this is theorize to be because the
The Scot Irish were generally poor and were pushed to the underdeveloped Border regions
The country
In many ways the Scottish
Built
Which would eventually tried to secede from the country because they couldn't
And in between those two
In between those two things
The Scottish Building 1000
Receipt over slavery
How does techniques
An African flavors combined
Create American
South style fried chicken
None of this is to damanhur anything kits
No idea about this
He's talking to a f****** Scottish
The pejorative Association of black people and fried chicken dates back to those days of slavery when slaves weren't allowed to own
After slavery ended the association lingered as a way to make fun of a
Mocking other
First and that it's really
Simple hits.
Manufactured fake outrage being peddled by the right-wing right
Calling Bernie races
For holding up a drumstick while being photographed with
The guy who's cooking said drums
I didn't know that I was
The right-wing
Is do that doing that
Imperative
The the lab
Yeah
But that's not accurate either
Because when you talk about the other instead
David is like
Bill Clinton
That was two years
I can only find right-wing media people talking about
That is racist thing
Oh and weirdly RT
It was the only places that were covering
Thinks that he doesn't like
I don't know why
I don't either but like a those the only places that I can
Confined for coverage
I did find an article on Fox
Randonautica
Fried Chicken in Louisiana
Restaurant but there is literally spelled out the article
To be honest we're surprised that we didn't see Morpho rage on Twitter over this
They're making fun of the idea that there would be fake outrage
The only people expressing outrage Roblox like the American mirror and Truth Revolt or message board threads on clock
He's pretending that the media covered it
Right-wing stuff the whole time
Because of what this really what amount do is Bernie Sanders is like a Curb Your Enthusiasm
We're all the sudden
He's been
Erases the whole time and then he's a
Accidentally getting
A photo op
Yeah
I just
Explicitly clear
Pretending that
Does the
And now the game
And that is
Default
Explanation
It's the right was doing that another rated
Discontinue into do that
Well I think he says that
He's he's referencing like all the time
The left is correctly pointed out that the
The people on the writer
Obama fried chicken restaurants
Understanding
He's
He's taking the wrong example
7 strong
Express
And I don't.
Very much
Alex
We'll see how he responds
Nazi salute and a Jewish man's face then yes I would understand if that caused a little
Do you understand
Hold on
You do know you you're saying you understand
Would offend
Would offend people and you would think that's Justified
Connie say that basically selling Fried Chicken on event that black people
Which everybody like fried chicken
Play everybody like fried chicken
What a pro
Contender for life's very fragile
This is a broadcaster here man for years on Aerotech
Drops God
No I think he's f****** with everybody
What is an anybody make any f****** sense
The only thing that makes sense
In a world where people are not in arguably
Is that they're all f****** with each other back in
Unable to understand
This kind of insanity leads me
To think that you might have been
Might have been having a
I meant also
First and on the 22nd he's almost
Half an hour late starting to show
He shows up 20-something minutes into the broadcast special reports
Tapes.
Alex Roldan
Bo
He is in a f****** mood that seems like how I would feel in a hangover
Our worst fears confirmed the worst
Congressman Larry McDonald
Water
Joseph McCarthy
Turn out exactly what we face
Everytime I try to go on air
I hate myself
I feel like a complete failure
Because I cannot summon
Oratory skills
Properly convey you
We're dealing with yourself
I bet you have a same feeling
Seems like he's waiting for the Alka-Seltzer to
Cricinfo
I hate myself when I try to start it shows that I'm not good enough
Convince you that the commies
They're coming in
I don't know it could just be that he was running late
Piano
Making such a big
Show of that Fried Chicken
Feel like a sober decision
Goodfair
Give me the Fried Chicken on Ayers
Man he feels it feels like
Keep packing it in
It really does feel like
Winding down like this is that
Class and all the sudden he has Popeyes delivered and everybody's looking at him like you
He's a hero Captain teacher hates
Six-month somebody back in my old
Studio
To this next
Business here on the
The 22nd
Like we know that he thinks
A gun
Civil War
If you
I mean
Think about lake house
Soldiers
Civil War
I guess if more people get kicked off Twitter
And it will cause a civil war
The equation
Time to get into
College means
You break the country
At least politically
It will turn into a Mindless Civil War
Everything leads to us
Sybil f****** Warfare
Yeah yeah that's
Breaking the Electoral College would really like the idea of the
The popular vote
Elect
Sing the president everyone would lose their ship
There will be a civil war.
If people didn't know exactly how many delegates
We're going to go
People would lose their s***
Civil War
I don't pretend to know what the intentions
Of the people the people who
Created the electoral college system work
It's very hard to argue against the
The conclusion that the real-world impact diminishment of minority vote
This is not a new thought
The globalist
They're just throwing out now it was discussing the paper put out by the gate
They almost certainly, previously
This isn't some kind of Crybaby thought that's a knee-jerk reaction
Did the Democrats lose in the 20s
16 election is Alex wants to
Losing the 2000 election
Or the 1876 election
There's a movement for the states
Opt out of the Electoral College this
What's going on
The candidate that wins
The national popular vote
This be done by States and governors
Probably shouldn't have
Problem with it
I don't understand where you draw the line
And here's the issue Defenders of the Electoral College
Sometimes unless you know why
Support it
This was the case with Paul LePage
Former governor of Maine radio show back whatever you wear
Brickheadz
Why don't we just adopt the constitution of Venezuela and be done with it
What type of dictator because that's what you really you're going to is going to boil down to
What would happen if they do what they say they're going to do white people not have anything to say minorities
Who would elect
The argument
The Electoral College is that it allows a small group of Voters
Exert a disproportionate power over the election
Leslie Paige makes clear at least
Support for me
System
They replied
Up with the argument of the system is important because it allows
Control
So that's a strong argument
It's kind of silly that we still use the electoral college system quite frankly and honestly
Even sillier that almost
America Civil War
These days according to Alex
Already passed at least like 10 years ago
I don't know I don't I don't pretend
I have
The fullest
Understand
Of the Arctic
Commence for and against the Electoral College
But the sense that I get
Is
Even
If you take away some of those new on Stark
It's f****** self
It's a ridiculous kratom
Silverado
That would be
More sense then everything would lead to a civil war
Get to Popeye's
My stomach
So this next clip involves Alex
About Hillary
Everybody
Blackwater Army
All good
What's the problem
So I don't know
Okay to respond to that other than
It's so funny
Think about
Lakeway the path
Like during the Iraq War
Alex
Imagining
Cdb bragging about talking
Me to Blackwater
It's really
Really weird
Good guys
Is good people in Blackwater the military and the CIA
Who would Alex reaching out to
So Alex has been here on the 22nd
Picture
Feather
What's a grievance
Certainly wouldn't apply to have even if it were true cuz it have to do with
College
Overwhelmingly
That there are massive amounts of colleges that are not black colleges
That have black only
Equation ceremonies
Not much. What that means
So I bet he could but I don't think he could actually cover the story he had that whole day
So what a shock
We stumble upon yet another case of right-wing
Misleading people about racial issue
What's going on here is it Alex's piggyback on reports out of the washing
Examiner
Which were heavily promoted by Charlie Kirk
Turning Point USA
The story here is about how lot of black
There are graduation ceremonies
According to this Legend
Investigation
But really the invented inspired all this coverage
Harvard had an alleged
Blacks only graduation ceremony
Does highlighting with propaganda
Deeply in League with white nationalist
Search sites called
Neo segregation
Of course Harvard ceremony
Only graduation ceremony
Explicitly been about how there were no whites allowed
This isn't true
The event was organized by the Harvard black Students Association
And was just about celebrating the achievements
Graduating
Students the literally everyone was welcome
Unimportant
No degrees work
Stanford during the
Because it wasn't an actual graduation
Rosa celebration
The water needs to be created like what that was being put forth by Alex and turning point because
What they really want
Do is eliminate all
Like a black student organization
Or lgbtq
But they can't really make that argument maintain their we're just
Pro free speech
Those Brits
Those two things have a very difficult time
Being
Varsity misrepresent events like this
In such a way as to make the point that they want to make
Well hiding behind manufactured outrage
This is a segregated
Graduation ceremony where no lights are allowed
A simple Google search could bring up Apple evidence of white people at the event celebrating along with their fellow students
Now is you immediately responded during the clip
I have very strong
Suspicion
Is it this is a way of responding to
The story of billionaire Robert Smith
When giving this year
Speech at Morehouse university
It is going to pay off the graduating class of students estimated 40 million dollars
Morehouse College is a historically black college at the alma mater of Martin Luther King
Important to point out that the student body of our house is overwhelmingly black or African American
But not entirely
More than welcome to apply
School
This is probably something that races
Sister not thrilled about
Cidl today
Very benevolent
They should be more grateful that they get two little boys
This high-profile sincerely philanthropic gestures be a billionaire
Support of a graduating class at an overwhelming
School
The predictable that on the
Heels of that story
What would it
Who is some kind of a propaganda narrative demonizing black people in college setting
So I don't
The return of Ali
In some sort of a propaganda
Yep it's just that
It's very it's very sad
Because
60 years ago
Killing people so they wouldn't have to go to school with
With black people
And now it's 60 years later the same white people who would have killed
To not go to school with a black person
Here--now like
Why won't Black people with his be there even though we don't want to be
You
Things that Alex's
About
If I had a little bit more time I Nevada Supercut of to make my point
Is there any
Misty's all about not.
Violet
He's all about defense just like I
No big deal it's not I'm not instigating
Right
Certainly
Of that mentality
Offense
FIFA
Politically
Here's what he had to say
They're committing all these crimes
It's just insane
I watched a family on the office
Or they destroy the country
They know that we're on our last legs that get rid of trump
Pushed on it you probably like
But I don't trust his audience
To be able to
To discern the nuance
Between them that likes
If we don't go on the offense
We
Lou's the country
Forget exist
Sort of language
Exist
The contact
In the body of the show it exists
Defensive violence
I do not explicitly encouraging violence but
Easy interpretation
I think that is someone
In the space that Alex
Existing
Has a responsibility to not be
That
That's your response
Speaking biersbach
Towards the end of this episode Alex has Millie Weaver
Studio 28
Graceful
Better Business
About
Her going to an abortion
Rally
Everyone there
3 years old
And I won't answer any questions
Think you're asking questions that imply an answer
Why do you want to kill baby
Cuz they're delicious
To fuk with you
Here to support killing babies
That's the way your framing the question is why you no matter how I answer
You're playing a game
Is left
What's going on with that
They're not even talking about those bills
They're covering abortion in the exact same way they always have
This Beast bills are almost like a non-issue.
It's just the logical 8
Conclusion like that build
Lay low
Yeah we don't want to f*** anything up
Exactly
Because he knows
Things are out
And he knows that that process works with or without any propaganda adjective
He can only screw things up
That's kind of the feeling that I get
The end inasmuch as he
We talk about those things
They would be
For someone like him
Part of his brand
Is Central piece of his bread
Pro-life
Yeah but the idea of actually following through with it
Because he had a pro-life country
The question to be settled
At least you wouldn't have had
Did too when he was younger
Now that he's older he might be fine
Applying those standards on people
He doesn't
Feel what they're going through
I said I kind of suspect that he's
I would say that he himself has got an abortion hotline
This is a red phone that's the only one
The button
The only reason I'm going to allow you to
You suggest that is
Because of his own
And I'm not going to say it
Rather live in pro-choice
World
Probably
It's it's an interesting question I don't know
Care I don't care about him and Millie's coverage
And manipulative
But there's one point though where they're talking about how loyal Trump is
And how important Alex
He's in the Trump World or whatever
Which is not at all
How is the reason
Interesting is B
Because
Not too far back
Alex was turning on Trump use only
We've been like a month or two
In the past but he's like
Turn on drop
This guy's a f****** a******
Because Trump is signaling that he's going to
Enact rules that might help out
Skip back on social media
Backup to a functioning
Position
Alex is
Fully on board with
Because on the other end of the stuff all explain what I think is
To any establishment
Rhino neocon
Blue Collar Americans
The people who live in white
They thought they could attack me in the name of trump
This works
And they cannot believe that they can't
Hey on your age
Do it
I'm not going to attack you for that as long as you stay true to the agenda of Americana and freedom in pro-life and God and Country
Free in the military
We're creating intelligent
I cannot stand it
Presenting it as I write reports that go straight
To the president because things are looking
Like trumps actions are more in line with what Alex
Is wanting him
To do
Ethos
Things weren't happening
Alex would be
Stuff like this
Because it's not true
Horse.
But here's why
What's going on
Trump is bacchanal
He's campaigning
These ideas
Pandering
To these people whooping kickoffs
They were the 12 agitated very important
16 election
Who helped
Create support for him and allowed
Camp Bow Wow
He is pandering in such a way because
The entire time
Since the election to
Pretty recently
There hasn't been
I mean outside of
Two things that a monster would do anyway like
Pardoning Joe Arpaio
Overtures that are things
That hasn't happened
But there have been things coupons
They're just constant disappointment
Not doing what I was wanting to do and how it's
Trying to rationalize staying on board or leaving
Should I go
This is campaign s***
Alex is falling for
S***
Because he's good he gets to feel
It gets the little f******
Scraps the Trump is throwing his be like hey I need you to
Beatles Don't
Get off the team
We're going to need you as this Camp ramps up
Here I'm going to pretend I'm going to
The next free speech rules that'll get you back on f****** self
Daddy read all my reports
I wonder how he felt about that report you wrote about Isis being up his dirty as well
Review with that report was
I think
Such a
Bootlicker on this because even in his own telling of this story
He gets
I'd like Trump even in his telling of the story goes like okay that sounds good I'll keep that in mind
Which is
Which is the classic brush off for it let's end this conversation
Alex is done that a million times to people
And I'm sure there's some reality
Me to that
So now Daddy's giving
Weibel
The story
It's just like come on man
Like when you talk about people who are obsessed
Put Hillary in
None of them act like this
Who's the sad
Replay what you want about Keith
A mess
Now that's
I mean they're both
Embarrassing in different ways
How much battery is
You want it you got it they keep showing me
Love it
I'm coming for you
I'm going to get you
God
You are going to be upon over by me
You're going to get it my hands are around your neck
Call Cheryl you heard from him
Today
Might have been a little more with Millie afterwards I don't really care
As someone who
Follows our
It's pretty closely
You are miserable Alex Jones
Macho political donkey wrestler
I mean
I would say that in terms of the recommendation that we cover it I think there is
There was some stuff that was the Popeyes
I think that there was more fun in here than the last
Stretch of present-day stuff
So as long as we're covering the present I do think we would have missed
Some good stuff
Hear Count Dracula say some f****** horrible things
Being someone who I'm aware of but I don't really give a s*** about you being like
No you suck go to worse than hatred
The start of transition that
Now I have a new person who I hate
That's good I would even upgrade him to some of the harder ice cream
Maybe some
Rum raisin or concrete
Frozen
Custer Street
With
Heestii louis-style Frozen Custard concrete
We got to go get fried chicken
Concrete write another episode
Suno in
Noteflight.com on Twitter what would we are
And I we don't need the president on it
You can find this on the iTune
You could download it you could
Subscribe libreview
Yep
Intel Annex
Back
That guy who made chicken for Bernie San
Definitely
We do not know that's true
Shows about 8
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color