Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
About Alex Jones
What was the last time you had
Cigarette
Maybe like a month ago or so
But otherwise
It wasn't
Successfully transitioned over to a vape
The ideas of like
Cigarette will be so much better if they're really not
So
Just an Illusion of a bygone past
It is
2 months since I
The regular
I just don't miss
It's weird how about you
I feel like
Cigarette but I don't really
Hashtag
Vapelife apparently
Cigarettes
I forgot to give a shout out to
People who signed up
So first of all
You are now policy walk
Melissa
I'm a policy wonk thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Thank you so much
Thank you
Very much
So taxable income you are now it's
Democrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much thank you very much
Hey I like this show.
Show
Jordans
Episode
It's rough
Because what I'm going to do is I'm going to
Play you a clip
When this is from
Appeal to you what's a timeframe we're talking about
Context clues
To figure out what era Alex Jones
This episode is from
So are we are we doing this is something Alex
Could be saying 10 years ago or is it just out of the blue
That's not fair
Chucky
Boxers
Fourth Amendment
Because they're criminals
Society
Proposition
So you got you got the globalist
Me to take power and their opponents
Which is very in line with the ideas of the present day
Qanon
Right I don't know what do you think
What is Kenly
Archetype
Globalist
2011 or 2013
24 through 28
The reason that I didn't go at all I hoped it would
But the reason I did
Was
Contacts
What you saying
Is almost identical
He's expressing at the Press
The Narrative never changes
The idea that the globalists are going to go to jail unless they do something
Is always there
It's consistently there
BECU in the present
Although I thought for sure you'd be able to tell
Glycol
I guess you didn't say in 2011
You could tell it wasn't present vocal patterns are
So f****** different
Just imagine
The present is Ludacris
No no that's not
Play reference
Just the way he
Organizing his
The way he's speaking
The mannerisms the delivery
The East luring
Or apps
Since their of obviously
I thought it might be a time travel episode anywhere like going to be like
I don't want the next request
Where you're coming
Over the 24th to the 28th
Wide span of time
Because
Some of it was a
Slog
Need to find things to talk about
You can listen to whole episodes
Doughboy
He's almost a college for people
I don't
Let me be let me be clear about this
Contacts
It doesn't help that quick
Don't know what
He was trying to express there because he doesn't truth
From where I'm sitting right
Yeah
It's not accredited
So in this first clip we're going to start here on January
24th and Alex
The racist
Because
British are the best of that they took over the world
Kind of
Little Elementary that that is like
Fun fun way to look back on our history
To talk about
. big
Is anytime at your herb maybe he should talk about it tells us about what he thinks
History was
It is a Fantastical ridiculous
Ridiculous
Doubt
K member
Context of Alex
Beginning this episode without describe is
The protracted rant about
His friends
Because they won't turn in their guns
He has this conception that's like I don't want to turn in my guns oh well you're a racist then
More about American history we're all Native American tribes basically have the same run
Fighting each other exactly
I don't believe anyone is actually making a
Accusation that Alex
To the races because he won't
Misunderstood
What they're saying
Just listen to really be a full demonstration
Alex
A huge monster astray
Discusses Native American tribes
How bigotry inform his worldview
The contacts that I clip is that
You say that the globalist
They're trying to trick us
Listen to fighting with each other
Heathside loves
Attracted to take him and his friends a racist
Does the globalist want to demonize them
The globalist of trying to play Alex and dollastic
Each other quote like
Native America
The first problem that jumps out of the Alex is trying to present the plight of the Native America
The drives in early American history is being the result of them being gullible and stupid
There's so many more of them than the whites
The fighting with each other
Or they were nice
The second problem where is real bigotry is on Full display
Yeah that's a problem problem
Because he gets most of his information about Native American
From F Troop
Christopher Columbus arrived
Easy call the people he encountered in
Urban Viola curator the Smithsonian
Intuition
National Museum of Natural History
A fundamental mistake that persists to this day.
To speak about quotes
The America
Can Indian
Despite their small numbers the Indian peoples of North America
In terms of languages clothes
Lifestyles militant
Religion
Different parts of North America have differed greatly from each other
Native American tribes
Look similar
Into him and knocked out
It's for someone to say that in the late 1700s a real site
Elsevier bigotry in the Bible
Express
F*****-up different forms
Government different languages
It's
France-info
The distance error like the size of
Indiana and Illinois
Completely
Languages Native Americans
Play larger than Europe
Monoculture
Dismissal
But you're smart enough to develop individualistic
Society6
Which is classic
Classic
Which come together
Like peanut butter and jelly
Oh yeah
And how great
Show and how it's been awesome
Getting real tired of him bragging about the
It's kind of like that, you know who gets a big gig and talks about it for five years
I'm getting with Alex
Insulting
Piers Morgan talking about how stupid
Idiot
Experiencing
The JFL audition process
Such bull
Since I got in the new faces
5 years ago
I just you know they won't allow me to do it I had a great time and I loved while we're on the subject
Alex talks about Piers Morgan
And how was the bigger
Was aired on
Thoughts
Different department
Neon
I would imagine that someone being polite trying to end the conversation
Places don't want to have
Alex on not because they don't want the ratings or they're afraid of him it's a
Pop you know it's it's it's a cheap way to get
Attention
The quality of what you're doing in the concept
What is like
Start booking
Yeah yeah
Play Alex's mind work
Which
With how much
Baby
A Morgan show was i j k
Quotes
Even his own telling of here
He didn't accomplish anything
Piers Morgan is still an a******
His precious guns are still in Peril of being grabbed by Dianne Feinstein discourse hasn't been
The way I was raised in this
Is correct
That was a media event
Netgear Donley at generating
Publicity
A PR stunt
That's all that was
And he knows it
I decided back on 2012 in January 2013
See if Alex is playing stood up to scrutiny
The Disappearance of a Morgan.
Cable ratings
All of the networks
The decided
I'm going to
Consider all media coverage
To be relevant to my calculator
So I'm not just
Considering overtly
Manufacturer
Manufactured although there may be some
Here's some of the things that happened in 2012 that people certainly remember way more than Alex yelling at Piers Morgan
CERN discovered the Higgs boson particle Summer Olympic Games in London for remembering
President minister
Murder of Trayvon Martin
The Curiosity Rover landed on Mars
Barack Obama
Gardner live stream jumping out of space
From that Red Bull balloon become a man to break
The sound barrier without a vehicle
The s*** out of that Madison Bumgarner won the World Series 2012
It was even your magic baby
Grumpy Cat
And of course we saw that your saw the deaths of
Houston Andrew Breitbart
Rodney King Ernest Borgnine Neil Armstrong and Michael Clarke
Aurora and Sandy Hook shooting
What do you do it I'm not I don't
Did Judge at all
Borgnine movie list
He's a big Superstar
They're probably other choices I could have made a list of celebrity deaths but
Relevant
Probably
Is the biggest f****** thing
There was an election
Yeah yeah it's whatever
Did narcissistic a******
Thinking it like we are the
I yelled at Piers Morgan and it changed the world
This is mad
Because
Feinstein
May or may not have meant
Been talking about gun
Control bill
Alex
And he said something
Tragic
Considering what we know
From where his career
A Muslim
Muhammad
Yes I can imagine that would happen
Stretch
Condescending impression that he did at the end
Literally
So much of his now he's screaming about how atheist secretly worship the devil
So what your bosses
Totally
Steven B
Even if she is a Christian you don't speak for me lady Christians all the times before everybody
Lorax guy
The middle of that clip which is the real tragic
It's funny to look back at this and maybe like wouldn't that be just
So awful of me
Not much
Like technically why he's kicked off all these social media platforms
But he could he could probably imagine that that
That's the
Even try that
Ultimate
Nothing
You have no consequences Alex
Except for if you add jatate long enough you'll go on Joe Rogan again
Throw us overboard
The Jordan
Piers Morgan
Wouldn't that be great
That would be a bold move
Gcn sponsor Piers Morgan
It's not that but this
Screaming commercial
Conspiracy
To discover exactly what it is
I'm not sure how long this video be online but go to weird device.com before it's gone forever
Again
That's weird device.com
Weird device.com
Hi level sponsorship coming in from weird device.com
God I want
Gevalia to redo that audio because that is
What are your first thoughts about your device
Well commercial
It's the first thing I thought is a banner ad like try this one weird trick to make your device
Or whatever it is
Like that kind of thing and then 280 million is really
It is a lot
What 8% of the population
It's 8% population
YouTube 280 million
Discounted whatever he was saying
Start
No longer function
So we may never know exactly what the weird device
The video down
I don't know it's not
I think it might have been something about you
He fears
Cuz I think it's probably some sort of a
Threat to the power grid
Sure
That makes the most if it's 280
Would be affected by knocking out of the power grid by nef
Maybe that's the rest of the
Broadcast
Another possibility is that I found another product at this dump
Pretty cells that is referred to as a weird device
But I don't think it's the same one because it's
Just a solar-powered kennel
It's very weird
Advertising it online
It's very strange
I don't know it looks like it was made for TV products
Oh here's to make a giant donut
The sun's rays
Take a tall cylinder
That's basically how I sell it
You know what else is a solar cattle
A really hot day
I don't think that's the commercials for
Open this late 2012 early 2013 time. I've been hearing that commercial for the weird device and every time
Suppress the urge to
Figure out what it is
Is I know from listening to Alex
They have this great thing that you
Come on come on look at it
It's always been satisfied
Marketing Traditions are really manipulative and emergencies in secrecy
Like that commercial
Decided I wouldn't even
So I can get into it trying to figure out what Frank
Mike Bates in a weird device are all about
But this time
Couldn't stop
I had to get to the bottom of this
And thankfully it wasn't too hard
Progress
The weird device
Is the advertising campaign put out by a company called for paper
The company that sell survival Foods
And all sorts of other statutes suspect Patriot Orient
It's a company
Stop Frank Bates has the face of
The company it is story is this
Downtrodden
Patriot Ledger
His family it's a dude is unfair termination by an evil business
Power cost
The driven him out of his home
The federal government wanted to put him in a FEMA camp
As Beauchamp
Bates testimony
Dependence
Three meat product
Is the Beating Heart of the 4patriots
Brand public m
Prevacid
These products that they sell are the things that allowed Frank Bates to break
Free of government oppression
High power cost
Then all the rest of the other b*******
Become a independent
Patriot
Yeah I'm starting to
Suspecting some issues
Well the first issue
There's literally no evidence the Frank
4patriots is a company that was started by a guy named Allen Baylor a Harvard graduate
Affiliate marketing
This is the sort of thing where person is aiming to drive to
Take to a seller's website
So they create their own website
As a resource on product
With links to the sellers website
The internet is littered with websites like this where page is like a write-up of the importance of
Humidifying air
They have a bunch of essays with
Talk at the right words keywords in it
Amazon link
I choose specific
Humidifier that is what
The goal is to get the website
SEO
Then the affiliate marketer get the card of all the purchases
Does it come from
Pics of that link
Around 2011 Balor
Be conservative
Community r-vi began Focus
Specific
He began a company called reboot marketing
The parent company of all the various
Initiative
And by all accounts
He created
To appeal to all the little things
To conservatives
Which all basically boils down to
Frank paranoia
In 2012
The company brought in
11.8
Million dollars
To quote Beauchamp
All Ballard does is drink someone else's stuff and paranoid anti-obama finery
And advertise it
Fictional life story
His his advertising
Brilliant
Earlier
He's not he's not creating any
Into the world
He's just manipulating you just recognize his and sending them to Amazon
He's just recognized how easy it is
2conv
At least this
Descend
Descended
Hey man
Advertising
TheBlaze
It was pretty endemic
Now I would like this
It's such an interesting
Justin question 2 of like the legality
You just make it up this guy as the picture
Defrauding people
Horrible that this guy is real
But where it does get into like a
AC laws
Being violated
Is
If Frank Bates
They faked character is giving a
Testimonial
That these products
All right you are entering the territory of
Defraud right
This weird I don't know if he's ever broken the law
Navigation
Is that
Weird Middle Ground
Are you still like you're stealing money from anybody.
He is because I think a lot of them have
Sirius Marco
Oh yeah I understand from that article
Progress there is some
Like buying a ton of stuff from
And then
Seriously Mark
Get up
It marketing
Is 1
Fireplace started
But it appears that the business may have grown to
He's also starting to sell his own self of other companies
Supply.com
Jesus Christ according to that thinkprogress article Yeti
Severe markup survival
Yeah
Is doing
It's weird an advert
Retirement
Basically for Alex's business model on his show
Deborah's almost like Alex
She's missing out on
If it's adolescent
You has very
If you
Outside hustles
Other than his own business
Right what other kind
Like whatever
Possibly
Secret funding
Just the advertiser.
Limerick soap guy
Is water filtration device
Is actually limericks out
It's entirely possible device
And
Before Patriots
Is
Specifically
Veto power of what sponsors they put on his show
So it's not like
Hey Alex we're going to put this ad on your show against your will
Either it's just either accepts it
Courted the sponsorship or
He doesn't care
Doesn't have I would go with has no idea
Based on
You know there's no way that Alex
Marketing
He would get very bored easily
And I've heard other one
Frank Bates before
Like I've heard him do others
Address
In other time.
For a while
It's like having bugs
So good
I love that he made it up that's
So funny
Where where does the
You got to respect
Where is the
Care about these
People even if they're gullible I still care about them
Consumers who does
Protection
Funny story is already
It's a 10 value in the first
You selling
Like guides
It's on how to build your own
Oh okay
Do you think progress article the guy talks to experts in the field
Is this something that you could do
No
Yeah
It would be
Much cheaper to
You just buy solar power
Time to try and build your own
The parts that you would need
Ridiculous
So anyways
I don't know
An advertisement analysis up to
No good
Real fun
No good and real
Alex
Hezekiah
On the show on the toy
It's the first time ever
Interesting
So he's been on the Nightly News
Infowars
The Infowars
He's been kicked he's been called up to
To the Major League
CS
It's kind of interesting of course
The guy who runs
Veritas
Has become a very big
Regularly
I can't speak to that in 2019
But up until 2018
He was definitely around pretty regularly
Alex would promote dumb scam
I did eat the part of being forward
Consistently
Flabbergasted anytime his name
Comes up
Atheism
Every time it comes up I'm like
The jail right now he's still making
Alex can really pull from memory that
Is John is going
2 Acorn Drive
Does a pimp
There's there's no reason
Positively
Seeing about what James O'Keefe did with acorn
Which is
The association
Community organizers for reform now
Yeah that's one of the most
F***** up your b*******
He should be and we'll get you another reason why I should be in a little bit
People do you forget about it cuz of all the other f*****-up Pikachu
So after those videos were released I became the biggest f****** thing in the conservative world
Obama had just won the 2008 election
To find ways to attack
And one of them was the accusation to Acorn had engaged in voter fraud
Which is just the GOP code for helping poor
Voter fraud which is what the GOP
The videos that O'Keefe made were not investigate
Received a plant carried out in
An edited specifically with the explicit purpose of smearing acorn
Set in stone
From the
Those videos were manipulative re-edited to such an absurd absurd
Alex remembers about the video isn't
Real
James O'Keefe didn't go to a court dress
Does a 70s pimp
With a girl dressed like
The prostitute
They showed up and talk to people what you might call business casual attire
But later
Frost
Institute in order to make if you were think that all the interviews as they were happening
Buy whip it when they were talking today
They want you to think
That they were drafted
As a pimp
Person was engaged with someone dressed like that
It's a false framing of the videos
It's the only detail that Alex remember
We know
Is an edited together the acorn employees answers
To make them look bad because I was forced
Release all the unedited footage in order to avoid being charged
Illegally recording people without their consent
Crime
I-10
This is clearly
You are leading them down roads
Glad to know that all of the video footage came out and he was discredited of course
Never paid attention
Everybody remembers acorn
Conservative lies
Investigations were launched
Acorn which consists
Show me found no wrongdoing on the part of the organization and its employees
Done just by the appearance created by these f****** Liars
And the GOP successfully pushed for defunding of acorn before the investigations are
Concluded
As the gop's used Acorn to attack Democrats
Themselves or failed
Stand up for the organizations which ultimately led to take
Close up shop
Close up shop because they were unable to
Insufficient funds
Together mission
Especially with it
In America the right mix it up and the left is libel
Call that normal people lose their f******
Care about possible human traffic
Navigating or voter fraud when he made this video
His goal was to make Acorn unable to do the work they did
Because it was a threat
To the right wing
His actions
Constitutive intentional militia
Attack on voting rights
But in the process he also managed
The shutter group that help people receive
Fair wages for work
Receive a quality at
Education
Consults for predatory loan
Ultimately the Legacy
Work is
Crippling a group that existed
To help the poor
Congratulation
The acorn videos were a big
Success is probably because of Andrew Breitbart
Who discovered okay
He's an amplified his work and put him on retainer
Basically for Breitbart
It's really hard to look at the sort of
Failed stunts that O'Keefe
For this
And how consistently you stink
Completely Fall Apart
To the point of breitbart's death
And not think that Andrew sensibilities
Really had a ton for the acorn camp
It was the tutelage
Mentorship
Of someone who was good at
Keith is coasting
On that one win
To the present day
Constantly has ship blow up
Like that Roy Moore thing that you tried to pull with the Washington Post
Completely
Everybody's discredit in forever and nobody's ever going to pay
Do we have it
It's fun now that we can
F****** bang on
What is that is named Delta work is Laura Loomer
I don't think either Breitbart likes Alex G
There was ample opportunity for him to be a guest on Alex's before he died and he never did come on
They're working for similar propaganda goals natural allies
Andrew Breitbart didn't want anything
To do without
Explain why
The 2009 Acorn videos
Keep watch Don Alex
To show either
His bread was buttered by Andrew Breitbart
Breitbart
And here is okay spreading his wings a little bit apeirogon Alex
All the people we run into
This show
I think I have the least
Respect for James
Is only for how much work he puts
Sent to doing absolutely
His goals are always destructive vulnerable
His plans almost always fall apart
Raymore
Someone like Alex does with his work
Tepeyac
Dealt there people who are evil
But somehow the fact
James O'Keefe
Singles him out in my mind
Particularly
I f****** hate
Wylie Coyote
The Roadrunner in just was punch
If he would presently
Coyote for quite a while coyotes backstory was one
Could someone else help
I don't know
Do it
You know this is a
A bad interview and it's mostly
Yeah because
Track what's going on in this
13.
Typically it's about trying to figure out
Cook stuff
Appearances
Really
It's just about Alex screaming
About
James O'Keefe
Being great and being a real journalist
Figure that
But there is one point that I thought was really into
That is
He got in trouble for
In the past
He's completely lying
About this situation
Camera
In Louisiana
Bass
We're going to have to
Prison
None of that is
Charger
Ridiculous
It is actually
He's got arrested for what he did to Mary Landrieu
Felony
He's damn lucky
Do hard time
Really mad about that prison for this guy's never go to it
These darn like that one time we tried to lure a reporter on his boat
For whatever
Seducer
Creepy as hell tonight
Wake me up maybe you should go to prison for that but this one for sure
You claim that a bunch of people have told him that they weren't able to
Slander you
U.s. Senator Louisiana
Land claims that people are having difficulty
Because the phone
Work quotes
There was a hot-button issue in terms of healthcare
Being discussed at that point back
Which would increase volume
O'Keefe decided to interpret this explanation of the phones being
Is actually
The problem with her phone Sis
Helium-3 friend
The dress up like telephone repairman
And why their way into her office
Which is super Elite
That's called entering a federal building under false pretenses
Once inside according to the FBI manipulated the telephone system
Which led some to believe that their true intention was to bug her phone
You can't do that
You can't
Even like
Like you couldn't come
Here and manipulate your phone device
Okay tonight that's what he was doing but
She said her phones were really busy
So they dress up like telephone employees
What the phone system to prove the phones aren't receiving
Don't really make a lot of sense
Text but it make a ton
Illegally Tapper phone
And here's the thing
Tap the phones it would have just been her phone
While they were there on there
They tried to access the
Entire buildings phone
Closet which would have given the max
Too many of the phone lines in the building
I remember this is the f****** Federal Building
Other officials government organizations and
Judges
Had their office is in that building
It's pretty f***** up to consider what
Could have possibly been up to
Ultimately O'Keefe plead guilty to entering a federal building under false
I'm kind of like SB
Rihanna's chart
Tapiz Senators phone
I'm pretty sure that's like
Borderline
Treason level
Love like
Nope
Situation where they were
Incompetent
To a level
Like the Mueller report says about Trump stupid
Erik Prince
Was talkin not too long ago about project
Yeah I couldn't
They were unteachable
That's 23 years probation
100 hours of
Community service and a $1,500
This is just one of the many in
In his career at emptying
The living embodiment
Of the white privilege
He insists.
Because anybody else
Caught
In the situation
And if he was caught in
Would not we wouldn't know about
What year did Guantanamo stop taking new people
When the next president
So
Hours earlier said that
You know the Piers Morgan thing was
Biggest media events of the last year
He's got a media guy on the show now a great
He's got to know
Thanks
About Alex's appearance
Morgan show
Morgan appearance
No I don't doubt
Translation
I would like some of that attention
California
Cool, right
Playwap
Wards.com
So we got there is basically Alex offering to pay James O'Keefe to harass Piers Morgan
I don't know what to do with that of Alex
Whatever he absolutely
Fixates on one thing
About what anybody else
Trying to interject
Nothing else seems like
He's like
He's not at the chicken back
Of course
So
Going over to
Two Piers Morgan's house
On the one hand he's a public figure
I think if there is a legitimate
Argument of it being
But I don't
I don't know how against did I am
As long as it's done with it like not you
You're not going to go on his private property
Cuz you're demonstrating outside his house isn't on the street
Appropriately
Applied to Piers Morgan
Any kind of feel like there's a little bit of a
The next one
Room or gray area code
Smart
School
You guys have done that so I guess you don't care that much by Prince book
I want to say
With or without going to the school
This conversation on the show does
All the deck
Which is put focus on this school
It's really f***** up to hear these dude say that sort of thing and act like
Some kind of acceptable gun-rights advocate
Isn't what they're
Even if
I'm confused but yeah
Even in school shootings were a very real issue
And even if there were an actual movement happening to take away people's guns
What they're joking about is making a public spectacle of a school where children
To learn
Sidwell school is not just a little house where Obama and Dick Gregory's children
Private instruction
It's a place where over 1,000 kids getting education
And with classes
From preschool through High School
Even if you don't cause someone to view the school as a target for an attack by these sorts of
Conversations supposed hypothetical
Buy single get out in
Creating a media storm
You are hurting children
Because here's the thing
That's cool is already at Target
And going through with this. Like what O'Keefe is
Describing is only playing into that and exacerbating the issue
October 18th 2012 Sidwell school was evacuated
October 2nd 2014
The school was evacuated after
Discovery of a suspicious package
Coming on the heels of the White House fence Arbor with a knife
Beginning in the 2008 primaries if not before
Deathreat
Do not limit themselves to just the present
And for James to protect
He's not aware of that is
Pathetic
Miramonte
Before this interview
And that will keep his on air
Casually joking about
Things that would obviously lie
To that happening
A bunch more
Irresponsible
It's just that
It's that I don't understand
Okay so
Here's their plan
They're going to go to this school
And just put an advertisement saying this event
So the idea being
When they are shot up
You'll get to go
See look at how smart we are we told you told you
But he's saying like hey I'm going to put this sign here saying there's no guns
But I'll probably be arrested by the Secret Service
Right there armed guards everywhere
Rhetoric like the stuff you put out into the world
Ultimate
Stunt
There
Desired outcome
To be there being guns
But
Be likely or outcome
If people
Seating at school
Jesus
Yeah
I find it tough to argue that that's not leave the functional out
What they're talking
If
Speak to intentions
But it does seem like that would be the logical
So
You know
We're going to jump off
From the 24th
Just have a long conversation about nothing
I don't care
So we get off the 24th and we jumping out of the 25th
To be about
Sandy Hook
Stuff where bad things happened
Analysis coverage where is
January 25th
Might be
A crucial Turning Point
Then Alex's career
Because he
He says that
So
Detect
But you can tell that there's some sort of a mastiff
And he doesn't say what it is on this show
Episode
News to try and figure out what you talk about
No
So we don't find out what that isn't a little bit late
On this episode
I watch the f****** episode of the Nightly News
So in this next clip Alex has a big
Is
I can't even tell you how
Game
Alex is running a contest
I said I would announce a few weeks ago I just been too busy
$15,000
Cash prize
A big drop box
Shrink from work
Charlie Sheen
I would rather
Do the Doritos. That dumbass
Alex Jones
I can confirm that Alex did actually named a winner in the contest
Surprised because I can
Can find out who this person is
Baby crying bloody murder
Valic
It July 2013 Alex name the short film called Purge the winner of the operation
Paul Revere contest
I watched it
And mad
I can't imagine how bad the other entries must have been
I bet the other
Silver for
It started to make me think of how much I would love to do one where I just breakdown
GTA V
Critical review of this film Purge
But I repeat I watched it's only like 18 minutes
I'm going to start with deposit
It appears that the film was shot with actual camera
That's about it
Bowser -
The acting is s***
The writing is laughable and Buddy
It kind of implies that people need to start killing government age
Sounded like from the name being purged
And if Alex
Chose this is the winner
Gunsmoke
But here goes
The short film begins at a meeting of the Homeland Security
Group of like eight people who have unspecified jobs
He's giving a description
Situations the dhs's spacing
Imagining what DHHS and their beatings would be like
Terrorist terrorist
Sure
Every time someone in the meeting Express
The disapproval of what's being said
Are the speaker Whispers in German to his assistant is it to imply that there Nazi
Gotcha
The people in the group grow Restless
They talk back there sent to the other
The other we go to the other room to finish their training with the American people are good
And another one is sent to the other room for reading and Infowars magazine in the middle of the meeting
When asked what he's doing he replies getting some real intelligence
It's a Shameless plug
That was my first I want to let you know that I love your product
It's
Embarrassing in the context of the short sale
But
Yeah you get Wyatt
Extremists in there
Sector to follow the given
People
What are the ages
Decides to
Call what-have-you
Extremist she has a file on
Extremist
Which is crazy
A call to him is
Laughably written is it a pile of
Quote
This is Agent
DHHS
I'm concerned about an operation but dhs's conductor and I wonder
If I can get some more information from you
Okay
Dresses up to something f***** up
Can I ask you some questions are you an evil person
You're not that was you saying no
Nami evil person
Meet up and buy him a beer
Skittish about it but they agree to meet up
Presumably for sale
Going to kill those kids
Seward idealized version of
I think they are
Veteran veteran
He's cool as a cucumber with a well-trimmed beard
Of course he's portrayed by the director of the
The town of Federal Reserve talking points Robin
Red pills the f*** out of her
Anyone not trapped in the Infowars delusion
Put in the film
He's a prophet
All his ramblings end up coming true and the rest of the movie plays out pretty much exactly like
Dramatization
The extremist was actually right about everything
You get the heads up message
They're coming
But you misspelled there I asked
Their
Come on
The short ends with agent Robbins following the age
Percent to rowley's house
She follows them there and killed
Another agent who spoke up at the meeting got sent to the other room
DHS office
And starts killing
Okay it's a really f***** up ending probably exactly what Alex was looking for
Ya-hey
I'm all for free speech and artistic
Expression and all that but I would be remiss
I didn't point out how f*****-up a fictional short film that is like this exist on a platform
This isn't Affliction to the Infowars audio
So when things reach their natural
Conclusion
People in the short start murdering the Department of Homeland Security people it's hard not to imagine that his audience
That is a happy resolution to the story
Unsurprisingly according to IMDb the director Michael Dorman
Corner of Show Business you might describe as
Infowars O'Jays
Self-produced short film
So
It's really sucked up the twist at the end of them murdering a bunch of
Kind of got a little bit of a flutter
Lycos anxiety
Because it came out of nowhere
Cuz I would be the
Courage would be of the DHHS employees
Stood up
The Patriot
Fulfilling the paranoia
As opposed
To the
Murdering government employees fan
It was weird
The paranoia didn't really make
No
Murdered
Patriots
Like in the
JS people didn't just go to Roland Vick man
Like his paranoid
Is did come true
He was only spared by the fact that agent Robbins calls in
Let you know
Like a bunch of people still got rolled up
Isn't that what you wish to avoid
Well the way to avoid before that
Seems like that's a
Pretty logical
Thing to take away from
My other logic
Clearly
These people
Think that they are some level of hero
And that Z100
Are capable of red
Other.
The first part of that strategy
Where they call up all these guys and go
Tell me more about yourself and what you want to do
I'm part of the team
And then they'll reveal themselves in the real world how it would play
Is the agent calls this guy meet up
The guy suck
Thinking it's a setup or something
I or
I don't know he gets seen with a DHS agent nose Patriot Buddies
Thank you that's nature
Should kill him
What's the plot of the story is
Defense
The Purge that happens isn't ever going to happen
So
What is going to happen though is somebody shooting up
Office
That's what they say
It does
It does seem like a
Impossible
Fallout company
Yeah
Be created by
I don't know free speech
The make whatever kind of art you want to make
But shame on you
What's guns being for
They always create these Fantastical scenarios where in
Now it's Justified
All my self-defense rules or are met so now I get to
Go out
90% of Alex
Cuz rhetoric boils down to when you just get
Deep enough for you when you follow the thread
To the end of it there
Justified viola
So
Gatsby comes in here on the
25th
In the present
Jerome corsi
All right and the two of them
Sit down
It is like a date
It is going well this is before he
Because I hate
They got great
Fantastic
Corsi is a yes
So Alex will say something chords he's like you
They have a momentum
BB Charter
Alex
Whereas Corsican ham have
Electric
And that makes this very hard to
To cut clips
Because they just go all over the place
Rainbow
Mostly about China
Okay
Going to go
Equity
Parts of United States
China wants his arm United States
Absolutely
Siri
Bankruptcy plan
Yeah if you ever heard that song Cuttin heads by the Riza nodb
Weather like trade in line
Really rolling with his energy
Yeah
I mean because of who they are
Just sounds like
Find me a little bit like he's got a cold
Eddie has this like a up and down whenever we talk
Pretty much
Let's discuss
It's not
Collateral for the day
They're going to take over and that's why
You take the guns away right
And then
The cloward and Piven
Stuff
Corsi talking a little bit more about the cloud
Am I talking about
With
Now
New York in the 70s with this idea
Socialism
Just being
True at all
First of all cloward and Piven ever been enacted
By anybody
And the cloward and Piven
We talked about this way back
Remind
Episodes
It was a plan that a couple of sociology
Suggested
And the motivation
For it was the realization
Who are living
Poverty level
That aren't
Taking
Which of social
Programs
I was probably eligible for
Take advantage of
That program
Suggesting was
People
Being made aware
Qualify for
So that they would sign up
I'm so it would become a very
Large prop
Was not to bankrupt
Estate
The country
What it was was to draw attention
To the idea that there are so many people who are living in abject poverty
It was an attempt
To make
The system
Make the government
Recognize
The tremendous
Size of
The problem by making it their problem
That's what it was
And it's never been
Enacted
It wasn't designed to
Bankrupt
Anybody it was designed
To make
Recognize
The problem that citizens were living at
The desperate
Straight
And the only way
To pay more money
I want to
Well at least that's what they say
I am so whatever
I know course he doesn't want
People
To survive
So great
Poor people suck haha
Jerome corsi
Like I said
Firework
It was way better listening to them
Because the more course he talked by himself
Opposite of vocal fry wherever
He will end the sentence
And he's going to talk to you all the way all the way
Boring
Dude
Nosebleed
So
Keeps going through the show
And it really upset me
Because
Is trying to screw
The law
What time advocate
Keep his audience stop taking
Which is
Credibly
Or over the horizon
Stop it
Psychologist
Is
Much of him saying get off your meds
Wildin
The awake doctors that we've talked to
Veterinarians
For the most part
Saudi
Is so f****** response
The medication then go off at cold turkey
But even
Unless you're under the care of a doctor
This kind of flipping houses
Super dangerous
Even their life
The person that he's talking
We'll talk to him
Talk about it
That would be wrong
It's a pharmacist
The name of Ben
Alex interview
Easy answer
Because board member of youngevity
The supplement company was one of Alex's main sponsor
Beautiful
Also been accused
I host a show called Brightside Communications Network
Talk about synergy
It's important to point out that has a license.
Don't have a doctor
Or any kind of advanced
Degree in the field or in any other
He has a Bachelor of Arts
In broadcast
Open pharmacies
I'm taking that information from his own bio on his own website
You should also know that
In 2011 the accreditation Council for the pharmacy education
The organization
Policy
Postgraduate degree
Quiet
For someone to be eligible to take
The North American pharmacist license
Ensure examination
Doesn't qualify
To try to
Because I a doctor at a pharmacy degree is required to
To become a pharmacist
Schools in the United States don't even offer a bachelor Pharmacy
As an accredited saying any
Degree in 1986
But doesn't exist anymore
It doesn't even qualify him to pursue a career in the field of being a farm
This man has zero qualifications
Dispensing medical advice
He has at least two conflicts of interest with doing so on Alex's show
But that's the thing
He's not here to give medical advice
He's here to sell youngevity
He doesn't give a f*** about the people who might be hurt
By Alex using him to Advocate that his listeners go off their meds
And most people throw it away I can possibly Express this
F*** you been few
That you can do that
And I really don't think okay like she can just go
Represented as an X
And then
Undoubtedly causing harm upon harm upon
Use less
Irresponsible about an hour
At least
Couches so much of it in like
You know what the great if you're depressed
Sunlight
Yeah
So yeah
What makes
Even worse
Is this is f******
Paid time
But you know how I know that
Because listen to this clip
Benfield
Pharmacist Ben
The question
This is just
Your show I've told you what I want you to ask
Mia's setups for me to go into whatever
It was next with Alex talks about his
Get off your meds
X his question about getting off your bed
Varies
The weather
Started off as a question
So he can introduce these ID
Cabana outdoor pharmacist been out a little bit like
With
What he saying
But doesn't give him any time tours
Respond
Supposed to
You got it
Let that happen again
Who's Mike was probably off
Becky realizes he's been ran
Little bit
Leave the studio so Ben can talk
Tryptophan
Who's who's
You don't want people getting tripped
Government
Actively
Eroding our Thanksgiving being against vegetarian war on Chris
I've Dan really not sure
Alex
Some folks
From his past
And also simultaneously
No Alex the crazy thought.
It's
So
Talking about youngevity
Product
It's just
You hear him
Ben say things like
Care to discuss
Is medical claim
You can hear
Dot-com
Polymers Plus
Well
Relaxation response
I also I do like the idea for that because
Anybody else
Stole
Because this girl
Because this guy is paying for his time on the show I was at the let him him
Funeral almost sounded like a little petulant when I was like
Who's going to get out of the studio
Because it's like this isn't my time.
It wasn't petulance but what you're saying is
Is
Like I don't know this time
Hot and bothered about telling people to stop taking their bed
I think that was
Do you like this
Broker program
But it wasn't
Like it wasn't him
Correctly God what I'm distinction
Sing that is
Is even while he sang like
They're going to tell you
Maybe you should stay on it
Also
Going there you know you're going to get the wrong answer
Right now Alex isn't telling you that it's the wrong
We're going to give you the wrong
Sounds right
Much like
Pharmacist
Psychologist
ISO
Psychiatrist
You should probably
Be more specific
There's a real Trend that's going on that Pharmacy
Trying to present
Himself
You Scientist
Perfect terms
Gives you the etymology of Serotonin
Not right about it
He's trying to
Scholarly
Real scientific and medical
Alex is getting weird
East close
Retaliation
Eastern religions is just to calm people down
You that are receptors for messages
I got to go I got to go Alex I don't know
That is not a corsi level
They got along well cuz youngevity pay the bills
Of course
That was the 25th that was Friday
And
Beginning of the 25th
He's on the Nightly News there's going to be big breaking news about Sandy Hook
And did not have
So because
We're doing this episode and I knew that Alex said
In from the Nightly News
Will be good that'll make the episode whatever
I watch the Nightly News
It's nothing on there like well now I got to listen to someday
Geo and says what the news
Is
Here is Alex
Coming in on
Yeah we got that right
So
That gave me a
We're in for something
Promising
Do that immediately because he's got others
Things to write about
Impeachment
If you had any kind of moral clarity
And intellectual
Wars
Dot-com
Area
So if you're going to
To complain about speaking fees and
That that's
Alex
Jimmy Carter sold his f****** small-time
Sheep farm just so you would be in violation of the emoluments clause
Also
Pretty sure that you have to be British
Benighted I think that there is a difference of the state
Still upon you like a friend or something like that
Right
You have to be British
Anyway
So we get now to the big news
About that
Nice Alex's
I thought that was an actual
I don't think that was intentional but it does
Speak to wear his
Yeah that sounds like he's speaking New York Post headlines now or it's just Sandy hoax
?
Confirm
Screen
That's the one
Conspiracy
I'll show you the rest.
So it's the CNN Anderson Cooper video
That is very well explained
And as shaken Alex
He wasn't going there with the actor stuff but now everything is changed
He has turned the corner here on January 27th
This is pathetic
Him
Having an egg
Exasperated
Tone
When he says
No Alex
No it doesn't everything have to be an opportunity for your tickets for the money
You're the reason it's hard also not to hear this
Only a couple days
James Tracy on recognize the profitability
A million views and also a few days after Alex did that
Durable display with the Lone Star College shooting
Like it
It's really hard not to
See this
Video
The CNN
Cooper video is being more of an excuse
It is actually
To Alex
It does it does feel a little artificial
So
Still a little bit
You can tell that something
The direction of iskcon
Towards
Actors
I show you the rest of stuff
What's going on
Sources
Which makes me think you're not real
Because we
So he's got he's got whatever pivot he's going towards
Because August 27th Alex get the collar
Towards
The show
And
This guy might be someone who Alex is a real source
Alex
It's very important I've asked
Freestyle
Eminem
Flag attack
Syria
Send it to you right now
It's not going to be here very long
Meet with your people
It's happening right now I haven't
Right now
You're in the army
I'm calling on
Behalf of
4chan.org
Oh
Interesting
Pictures in 2013
Calling in with
Proof of an imminent false flag attack in Syria
Betty's
Fortune
So this color is trying to
This
Fishing with Alex
Syria and the information
Nothing is really all that different back
Really it's weird
The more you look at it the more
It pretty similar it is
Even though somebody
External appearances a thing
Have change
Quite a bit
So the case of this information is actually really
The caller is saying with the documents
Come from a hack
To explain.
That they came from a hack
A group called Brittany
Defenses
And it is apparently true that for
So that you know there is
Some real world
Much of the information that was
They ended up getting put
However
Expert
Studied or certain
The document about a pending false-flag in Syria is
Steak was fabricated specifically to be put in this league
And we planted
Yeah in fact
Britton defenses
For posting a story about the
This document and one
Winning a settlement of 110,000 lb
For libel
Interesting Lee Alex posted an article about this
I wonder if that has no
Something to do with it
Man the fact that this fake document was planted into a legitimate
Malika haqq
The question who it was
To carry this out
It doesn't seem like it would be
Some random person or low-skilled
Britain was Operation
The only real motive for inserting the false
Which is the one that was publicized
Not using the other documents as
Support
It was this specifically fake
Thick got all of the media pushed its what this caller is calling in to try and sell a crime
The only motive is to make any chemical attacks
Immediately be suspected as false flag
And the only people who really have that kind of emoji
Would be pro-assad entities
The list
Is pretty short
So
Extremely powerful
Or at least
Sarah Elizabeth
Eating propaganda narrative
Community
Right
Just nobody I can think of not a single person
Putin frequently made arguments that chemical attacks list
False
Probably a coincidence coincidence that this happened
After Putin
Again
Coincidence
I don't know it's one thing to
To save it
Good
That's feels like Russia might have been
Entirely possible that
Wanted to f*** around
Jump to that conclusion
History pattern
But that doesn't prove anything
It hasn't been
Who necessarily was behind
But
Whatever the case is
This caller probably Unknowing
Is
Alex is getting this call and I don't
Respect
It is actually
This caller is
Trying to
Trick Outlet
Facts about something
Layers of b*******
More interest
Alex by Zeppelin hook line into here is Alex's respond
Why don't you
I understand that Alex look
I'm sending it to you at Chouteau
You look at it
You be the judge
I'm telling you
Damning
Right now
God help
Me I'm probably signing my own death
Send it to
Infowars.com
Demonstrative that Alex doesn't believe the bulshit he sells on his show
The way you so dismissive of this caller
Howard
What is this guy some sort of secret information that you could be killed for 278
No Alex is far more careful with his sources
Is Ben The Intern
It's an insane
Level of distrust
If its own audio
Which I think is healthy
But it doesn't match how Alex
I asked you this cuz I could go either way on this
At this point
Alex
Know that he
Has a show tip email
Yeah okay
Alex says okay
Posted to YouTube
He was just trying to be like yourself
Why don't you get this ball rolling then I'll cover your feet
Don't want to create more work for Paul
What I thought was interesting
Christine
I heard that
And Alex information to comes out of anonymous sources and
I heard
Immediately I don't know why
He's going to f****** report this as
There's a story
Like I just knew I have a hunch I had to listen to the 28th because I was like
Positive you can report this report
I was certain it was going to be the next day
Here's what happened
Alex is literally
Completely right
But everything that surrounds that caveat is to get people to not think that's the case
Paul Watson he knows a lot about this job he thinks it looks good
He scanned over to check that if it's a hoax elaborate
Which is super unlikely guys and you know what I think it's credible because it matches up with things that I've said
In the past which is
Support of Assad
Man
You just
You got tricked
He went to bed he woke up the next day and was like I'm f****** running with it
Siberian his defense
I don't I hate that but
A lot of other people
A lot of people got tricked
You know I don't have a scorecard of how people responded this early and all I'm interested
It's really a
Nice
For me
To have my instant
Clearly
Vindicator
Here we go
Amanda
Throws me a curveball by being like it's usually government sock puppets
Good I got to say
So sorry sorry dude
Fabricated document is not good
Because it is
Dropped on its face
Prettiest
Yeah
Part of it is
Email
About
Basically
So even if other people do get raped by it they wanted
Alex
It indicates that he looked at it was like we can work with this
So
Anyway
The rest of the 28th is mostly Alex just nothing
It's not worthless
To Death By ignoring airbox
Texas
Velo
It's it's pretty crazy episode
I mean there are moments that are kind of
Bordering on entertaining
Stretching it out
Bra sever
It's just
Such standards
And we are through the 28th
I hear and that's the
I think I think there's massive
Progress
Here in this
This time span
I also just like
I look back at this episode
No more episodes
The experience of listening to all these episodes
It's just a wallet
Yeah
You got f****** Jerome corsi and Alex
Hitting it off
Having a great time
Isaac trash
Yeah right I see pharmacist been coming in Alex using him
As up as a signpost
Get people to stop taking their medication
Isaac
I have at least get a call or who calls it with 4chan f****** document their clearly fabricated
I'm sorry
Trash Operation Paul Revere contest that ended
18 minute video that I had to watch that was trash
Crash
Yeah James O'Keefe showing up for the first time
Everything
Sucks
I disagree with you on one point
What's up I really did find a cute when he in Jerome corsi
Got into that little sitting there I was I would not
But I don't agree with you
Start something
There's something to that
You guys are having a great time Lex Luthor
Really well
Fart
Make a career out of tricking p
They might combine
There are ever
The Legion of Doom from the 60s Justice League cartoon
Yeah
Wow there is acumen
Lightning
It's ugly
All that is just
Crashed
If you look at that
24th
25th
27th 28th what is that
Like
15 hours of
It's worth it
Because
You scatter that trash
Kika decide clean your room by Jordan Peterson
After you clean your room
Is Alex
Rationalizing
And pivoting
On the twenty
And I think that is
Crucially
Important dates
We have the isolated
Does Alex learning about that ccnn
Video with a dress
Cooper's nose
Being to just
You say things
A fake
Interactor
Enso
That's going to be a real real fall off
Really big
Alex being a piece of s***
Thundercats coming real soon
Man
God I hate Jay
Everybody everybody so far in this
In our episode
That you've curated
Has provided
False
Evidence
Yeah they're all fraud
Yeah it is a point of like
Yeah I think I think a lot of these people in the world would not be free Jerome corsi
Pharmacist band James O'Keefe
Massively irresponsible
The public Trust
College of
Evil
Professors
At college
Way more sensitive
Can say is we'll be back on Wednesday but until then we got to website
We are on Facebook you could go there
Cast tablet
I don't want to
I don't want to say any
I need to go to bed
The show
None 0
There no positive
There no Heroes
There was one
I wasn't there
Definitely not oh yeah
Sam Elliott
For not doing the voiceover for that s***
Okay
Vice.com comfortable saying the same Elliott that never killed
Okay smle probably nobody
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color