Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages
Don't talk a little bit about Alex
In
Deed we are
Did you say in because you're subtly trying to buzz varkey or show tonight in Indiana the people who are listening to this tomorrow
Mishawaka
What time machine come check out Jordan in Indiana last night
Go to better Java plug-in yourself
I think it's probably a smart I probably enough show cover
Conversation
A little bit disappointing cuz they're called bomb
And all they do is Fizz a little bit
Find a display
What you mean I mean
Experience out of it
I want I want
Or something I don't know
Bath salts for me are very like
But it's a part of my
Brains
Still loved
New AG b*******
It's something I really value
Which store do I go to
There's
The one I bought was from
I know that there's no magic
But I'll be damned if I'm not going to go by
The Calgon brand
Even though I have
Calgon bath salts in my bathroom right now
Just people who make this possible
Maria
I'm a policy wonk
Jack you are now apology walk
Jackass so much
I'm a policy wonk very popular with Jack
We're trying to fill up our quota
I'm a policy wonk
So Rachel
Thank you so much
Democrat
What's the business
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Rachel
It's for these guys what they do you do that website says sports show
Now Jordan today we call a pickle Barrel
I do or I did yesterday when I was preparing myself.
We had it weird weird situation original coming up with episode to do and the time frame of the word
Really f****** in
European elections
All his boy faraj
Buckwild on food of course
Call Alex's other friends lost
All the people who will show up on Alex's show the Tommy Robinson
I guess the Sargon
I don't know if he's ever come on out
What's the show but he also lost
So I thought like for sure Mondays show is going to
Pretty Buckwild
Turned it on
It was was trash
I don't know why but Owen Shroyer was co-hosting the entire show
Tiger show
My theory was that they thought he alternated babysitter cuz it was Memorial Day
Okay that was kind of weird
Doesn't seem drunk
You just seems kind of
Present-day Alex there's nothing
On hand underneath his death
So the first half-hour was kind of just
Bacon
For money it was all just
Like seriously
Severe
Plug
Yeah
I'm not just saying it
Happening it was a
Attracted
Commercial
Based on the premise of the European elections
And how can over the world
Clothes of Alex
Entirely Infowars as Nigel farage is jeavons
Alex is responsible for UK
Becoming a viable party
That should be
Punishable by
I think 20 25 to life
But what
So Alex
Construction
Nationalism
Kind of rambling nonsense
Not really care all that much there's no real good analysis
There's no good point
It just sort of fatalistic in like
Trump is going to drive people for treason
Laps around
South Verde
Kind of talked about already
Alright it's
Where is Wednesday
Wacky Wednesday
Let's get into it
Someone over Project Camelot there's nothing there
Trash
Wall-to-wall discussion
Everybody lady I don't care get stop it
Contacts
Alright maybe Dave daubenmire
3 minutes into a video like
Get out I already understand you
This is
This is garbage you know what I just remembered
Larry Nichols has a YouTube channel where you started recording things
Larry Nichols has a YouTube channel
Cowboy
So maybe we should start covering Larry Nichols weird YouTube videos
Like 30 minutes
Dispatches
Information brakes sure
Are so boring
Not surprising cannot imagine how terrible it is to listen to
Half hour of Larry talking
Straight I can we talk to him
Without anybody else there Larry is
Listen to
Okay so what
Although I will tell you this
Because I went through his YouTube channel
I can tell you two things
Larry doesn't believe in qanon
Larry Nichols recorded an album
I just took a drink that was a very close
Song covers
This is not that terrible
Japan time
50/50 serviceable
Call Larry Nichols
That was long but me I needed us to get to Larry McCoy
That was very that was the cherry on top
You can go find B online
If you need more of that Larry
Fairly recently recently
Yeah
Kohl's
To question his voice
You know what I mean like
Red rose
I know the people speaking and singing voices can be pretty markedly different but I don't think
I think that's
Absurd
Dammit
To his vocal cords
You wouldn't be able to sing
Things like that I don't say
Very much like a
Disney cartoon from the 90s
It's the speaking voice in the singing voices all the sudden you're like a different person entirely
Exactly
Yeah Christina Aguilera is singing
I don't know how many points
Butts
I don't think that Larry has the right
Sal covers of the song
Like did you get the Eagles to let him sing Desperado of course
I certainly don't have the time or interest in doing this but
Glenn Frey if you're listening
Larry Thiessen
Larry
If he's not paying your royalties
Get down there take care of business
So we can't listen to Larry Nichols
What's a while we going to do I was really up against
I couldn't figure out what
What to do if
Alright
With Project Camelot stuff
It basically becomes
Like
Let's
It's always exciting when there's new information about Margaret
Never she goes back to the prison
It's always fun
Steward of morph
Because of Kevin Moore making this documentary
About Mark Richards
And him having this
Feud with Carrie
It became become more
We covered him
Because of his
Coverage
Psychic
Quote let's
And I found
Completely insane
Does involve Kerry Cassidy out-of-context drop from
Today Show
Splash
What we got going on today is
Kevin Borg
Guys making a documentary about Mark Richards
Kerry Cassidy believes
Is whistleblower
But it's actually a murderer
Yeah, con man and
Is on another show
He is on a show called freedom of Joyce
Who runs this show
It's a little
Answer sheet
Kevin Moore on as a guest
Discuss
He's documentary about Market
But over the course of it you might
Joyce
Doesn't like
Cassidy
It is excited about the idea
Maybe 3rd or 4th
Most important
In terms of the trends
Some sort of saying hello
Unpleasantries
On YouTube
Is Kevin Daniels
Welcome to the show today thank you thank you so much for having me on
Glad to see you in person
Yeah I know we've talked a little bit on the telephone
Person you'll notice that she says
You're listening on YouTube and hopefully literally just wrote hopefully it will
What is hopefully
Automatic
No
It indicates to me that the only place she knows this is going to be is on her YouTube
Challenge
So important to remember for later
As it is now I believe she met has an association with American Freedom radio
Which is better
Second network of
Chose
Shows of people who have like snowball bike talk about Liberty
So that's that's the sort of
Thought in the sex club
Kevin
Gets into some of the ideas of
The documentary
You know why
It's offensive
Carrie believes Margaret
Cuz he doesn't get it
36 years for the murder of his friends Richard Baldwin Wichita
Richard Alexandra Baldwin along with his crime partner Crossing river
Considered that carry doesn't that
Yeah the people that she has as longtime gas on her show I mean
Like yourself and myself maybe you know someone's coming on for an hour
What wedding are we going to do you know what I mean
Maybe we'll pick him up in the interview
Complete
You know where to get the airspace to the people weapon into talk about that was
Just remember that he's on his show before he's had Joanne
So many other f****** weirdos Paul Craig Roberts
Jerome corsi
Never heard of before their names
I just listed them off
Universe
Wow wow of the game is not wedding people because if you
Start a f****** game is busted
Kevin borseth the he runs a sex shop in Amsterdam
He runs a f****** psychic hotline are you kidding me
Let him the way that we can
Because the game is up then
I think they like to pretend that they are like with a Google search
It's it's nonsensical but everyone knows better than to
To poke
Each other in the
The places where the
They themselves are vulnerable
Because
Target glasses
Collaborative
It's like a Mexican standoff
Yeah you know it's just okay I'll blow up your business if you blow up mine
No one's going to do that
Stop self-destruction
Basically pointed at each other's heads at all times
Hey you f*** this up for any of us
You f*** it up
For all of us
Consider really
Almost universe
Parcel Within
Paranoid
Truth
Communities
Is attacking people who have left
Yeah you know
I was inside the
Toxic and awful
F****** flip by the CIA
Or they make a personal attack
That has nothing to do with their
Cam lights
He on the sex shop what is it which isn't a personal attack
But it is
Smear the guy
Heat interview
From primary school
He was thinking
Sing about
Setting up a sex toy shop
In Amsterdam
But then decided to go to university
Instead
So you never actually followed through
But there are like
That would lead one to believe it
Still an actual
Osoto
Show Business
No it'll
About his own life over Carey
Covering up a
Sex toy shop that you're admitting
We're going to start
There's no there's no strap
In this next clip I think we'd get what I'm going to
Described as
Kevin Moore
And he uses a buzzword that is
Tremendously
Important
And it gets thrown around
These worlds
What does Worlds
Pearl Harbor
No
The documentary to be at the surname documentary
I want to go to a community V Community the
All since 2008 when I first
Took out radio broadcasting at Glamorgan University in Wales
Discernment
Discernment is a buzzword with these
What is what do they use
I mean I think it means the same thing that you are you are I would think it means
The ability to tell
Truth from fiction
Yeah that's what you do Discerning the reality of like you bring something to me and I use my discernment
Tell if
I believe you are
Are incapable of even allowed to use their version of discernment
Based on subjectivity
What's true
That's your discernment as a really don't make sense
Information
Empirical evidence
Directors not caring for chocolate I know that
That doesn't resonate with me
It doesn't resume
Chocolate
Okay
I like that
Where are they doing this interview
What is going on
I don't know
It is
I think it might be
In a library
Library
Shushing people
I don't know
If you think anything goes in the library now
Everybody in the library's just stoked that libraries are still at
Yeah you'll put up with a lot more these days it'll
Library
I'm not sure
I couldn't tell from the video where it was taken
In place but it looks like a room
Corner of a public building
A hundred percent
Could be a library
Not a private
They couldn't
The studio space
Cuz Larry was
Regarding follow up
Next one
The Pendragon
Part of Mark Richards
Murder
Which if you are
You haven't listened to all of their apps
We've done it
Mark Ritchie
Plan to turn Marin County
Into his own kingdom
Styled after Camelot
Literally would have worked for those meddling kids
Murdering Kids Laser
Yeah there's a problem
So he learned about that
He's telling about his learning
And how's that was
The time
Recording a documentary on channeling to get to be released
Again not documentary movie
My journey and just sending out on this documentary
So I get that and he shows us things we were coding interview together and I technically to the way back to the UK
This is just not right on this guy
So he's talking about getting
Contacted by someone doing his interview with like a couple years after
Interview with Joanne
Guy gets in contact with him is like a man
This is f****** nonsense
Nation about the
The trial
Press clippings
What have you
Bet her very well
OU
Cousins
Almost almost
This is storico
Why isn't this a catfish Channel
So
Bipolar
We play about the the
Audio recording that we did was I now because
Austin mission to record a conversation
I don't release again if you want to put it in the show we can play it right now okay
So
What follows
The half-hour recorded conversations oh yes
What are calling Kerry Cassidy
And that is what we're going to look at 2
They played the whole thing
Can't be real
It is
It's far more interesting
Want to say before we get going
Up to a point
I'm totally on Carrie's side in this phone call
Totally right
About a number of
There's a social dynamic
Between her and Kevin Moore even about Market
That she's on the right side of
I think
And we'll get into that as it goes along
Here is from the call
This information
About
Camelot
Pendragon
Him but it's not new information to
Scary but he doesn't
You seem to know that
He doesn't realize that Carrie knows all this s*** just doesn't care so there's that there's a weird dynamic it play there
Emailed him out-of-the-blue contacting him
Being like hey
This guy is evil and
No one ever contacted
Larry Carey
Who is
Years of her life of course
Either thinks that or using the appearance of him
Thinking that as cover for trying
Cover
Either way it's sort of patronizing
Consulting
Yeah he's an ass
It does seem real assholes
We get watermelon to reach it for
Was
Just to let you know about
Chapel run into
When I was over in San Francisco so
I was over at contact in the desert
Which I just released my interview with yourself
When I was at contact the night then I would spend this this this chat that
This kept getting contact with a spine priority oh but by the phone I've been seeing once we swap numbers and everything else
The tell me a story about Mark this
This this this Chapman to speak to him ready
Because
I didn't want anything to do with 1800 Enderman I said I put my interview with you out
And it it really hot
You know it's really not
Not my business
But
Doing this
One thing is showing me is that
Showing
I've had to show the sermon to student in the bedroom
Reply to that then
Maybe I should apply to this other
This UFO Scott.
That raises the question
Why did you apply discernment in your career
Beforehand
Sloppy
We all grow and change get a word of day calendar and discernment is on I don't know May 27th
Everydays is remember
So
I thought about it and I thought look on in
I'll speak to him
It is
We have to say this this this guy
New nudes
Stung
I got kobold when the guy that was this guy that was murdered
In
Annnnd in the case of my riches
He knew the song
But anyway
Please tell me the story over the phone and he sends me a couple of links
It was interesting what was in the links had to say I never come across the meadow before I thought montrichard
Innocent
Did you know what I mean
From YouTube
As well
You thought it was what I was when I watched it
Expect a more passive aggressive speaker
What the f*** are you talking about you talked to a guy
To sum that up in like 5
Ya knows the victims
Information that I found really troubling would you like to hear more about it
Now that is red
I got in touch with the guy on the phone numbers and when I talk to him
Nobody talk to me
Pieces of paper that's passive-aggressive
Let's
Invader information
Sew-ins
Eclipse
He gets to the
Actual Dragon of it all
Sheridan care
At all
It's admire this response
It was
Because this guy was a complete nutcase Mark was in some respects
Brood
Set this
Disney in the Golden Gate area
I know it sounds crazy to you but
Again reading the court document
The case when I've done it a lot of invest
Navigation
Right
And he wasn't
But it's you know I understand that perspective out there and I understand the links in the things you read
So
What is the
You know I guess
Cut to the chase
I don't have a lot of time I'm packing
So if you could
What new information was this person trying to revive
I never knew about that if you knew about these links before I don't think
That's not
Like out there is those these things are out there and people can just find a most people go along with the
The story that you accept that that mutt reaches telling you
22 lynxville 23 links
I don't think most people doing the just take it a tattoo
That happens
With everything I got
Celtic.
Investigate what they take
To put it
Essential Google
I was one of those people that went
Cuz your f******
Stupid that's why I just don't look into them at all yet
View myself as a pillar of truth I don't know why
Responsibility tell every angle
Of course I got a hundred percent disagree with what Carrie believes
There's probably
Turtles about the social
Dick
That's not my job
I'm running
A f****** secret space program media operation
It's not in my interest
To try and debunked my own guess other people want to do that information is out
Why would I do wreck them to it
I know about all that stuff I've chosen not to believe it
F*** is wrong with you a******
Oh I'm just one of those people who would never put it into a cursory Google search
Is a dam
Anything to your Covington Mark Richards
Information without
Like when he had a joke
Press clippings available all over the internet
What I get from
I mean
At a certain point I think it goes bad for Carrie
Up to this point in the beginning of it
If she just hung up I would been like Kevin you shouldn't put that out
Has a space
And she's protecting her
Like
From the first question that's like the first question
Which
Can't believe that it took
7 minutes
He's a little bit of
I don't know how to describe it is just a bad talker
I mean
Passive aggressive question
That is clearly a question
That is an accusation
Hey
You don't know about this that your guys and Uncle that's the first knows that she doesn't
Covering this up
Will be covering it up but it's not like
She has the ability to
Actually coveranything
Google search
So
Little bit more
Contentious
Still on Carrie's side
He was still out there anyway
In the original court case
No he had to
Put this new
Agency operation
And that
Details a two-sided
What is that worth
The truth
Opposite was true have you considered that
Both sides
The story
You know but
What I'm saying I'm
Kevin I'm trying to
Cut to the chase here
Are you bringing me new information are you just saying go look at those links I've already done that so this
That would be the end of the
This conversation
If you have new information
If that guy has new information
Then what is the new information
Well I didn't know you knew about that so you know about those links right
Investigative reporter
You know I'm interviewing some guy eight times I go to the
I mean give me a little credit
You know
I do investigate my my soul
People in their source is excetera so you know I do I find necessary
And yes of course I've been missed
I think you and I would probably have a different definition of due diligence that's necessary
But whatever he's doing is just rude well what are you doing is also tested
Doesn't
Do any investigative
Like if he's if he's asked
Her that question
Assume
That she would know that's that
But she wouldn't have looked in
2m at all
Meaning that he assumes that
Because he does
Or he's trying to
To pass off
The responsibility
His guests
His own preparation
Like ideas
It's on her to have researched
Husband
So if she's coming on
When she's wrong that I'm not really wrong
Haha carry-on it whatever she's saying
She has the responsibility of figuring out with her cats are legitimate or not
If that's not good enough
So that's almost cowardly and compass
I would I would describe things I have
So I can try to get down to business
You got any new information
Because
This is old
Making a call to me York
Claiming this guy calls
To direct you
You could do on your own
That you know
Regular person can just do
No
Any of them
So it's me with new information
I do too
You're already know and care about
I'm really on
To be trying to
Conversation because it has run its course this guy called me he has this information that I found
Tubi
New
I thought it was interesting and added a layer to this story that you're
Not covering on your show
Bulshit
That's why I think Carrie get
Savely frustrated with it
Crosses into like
It sucks
I do feel like there's
Bienville
Poorly
But it comes from a frustration that is very understandable and she's not wrong
Social
F***** up a sphere reminds me so much of
The energy vampire from what we do in the shadows FX
The office just going in there just
And Iyaz solo
Have you ever
That
The show I can't
The name of
Show
It's the one that
Have you ever seen
TV show
The TV show that your breath
Or the character is
Okay well let me talk about it
Hang up
Chicago to Barcelona
Escape
Because Kevin Love
He carries has to get into Attack Mode
The first thing she does is suggest this guy contact
Is up to no good
I guess what you're doing is you're letting me know that
Dunning interview
With some guy
New the son of the guy that was murdered
Sakura
Exactly who it was
So he's not exactly
That clue
Forward years later
To set to suddenly
Try to contact you
Trusting that is trying to contact you and Joanne
So then you have to ask yourself is Disgaea paid in
Informant is he working for the CIA
Reasons a person comes forward in this way
To try to bring a journalist such as yourself
Into one direction or another you can believe him and it's fine if you did an interview
Thanks for letting me know if
Not that it matters
Too terribly much
But you know if you think I'm going to change my point of view because this guy suddenly
Coming forward to say absolutely 30 years
Absolutely
You cannot just tell the story just the one person to Angela
So I
Even though that's a little bit stupid
The CIA
It's a little bit overly paranoid
At the same time
Coming in with a position of like kind of Desire
To convince
Really of her
Correctness in the position
Barcelona
Yeah I find the only issue being that she called him a journal
That's problem
He's still
She's really wrong
Yeah but who cares she doesn't care if
If Kevin believes
This guy who contacted or I don't particularly care
She decides to believe
Mark Richard
Yeah this phone call should be over unless he unless he's got
Okay cool
Out-of-the-way
What exactly was Mark Richard
It's doing at this
Tell me about that later on
People that that okay
Click
So instead of that resolution
The call
Kevin
Sammer's
Kerry Getz
Kevin because of
Sky had nothing new to add
Have you ever done that
You know what I mean when I say a false flag
Okay have you ever tried to investigate
Will it let me ask you this
Would you put these links
In a new videos
Easy face
I'll check
But I do I've known
Investigate
Was Kevin Democritus
Stuff like you and
You knew about police before you knew about the 23
3 + linxonline anyway or what
Supposing that
No actually that's not that's not what my job is I mean everyone
Does what they want to do about these things
My job is
Discussions are not about
A murder for which he was framed over 30 years ago
I mean she's wrong
Obviously
But it isn't her job
Is b*******
That's what exactly it's it's it's
Such a hypocritical expectations of another conversation
I wish they would all get right with the
The story or whatever nice
If everybody had a
The more rigid
Intellectual honesty
I would love it if
The access but she has to Mark Richards
Actually took the story seriously
And
You're told the fullness
I don't know what her job actually it's entertaining
The only thing about it at all is people thinking it's real
There's going to be people who believe crazy
Baby stuff is real all the
She's just
You get one in the large family of people who are
I would prefer if every Infowars man who believed that
That weird bulshit
Go over this where we carry and believe that b******* I think I
Slightly less
Probably there's a lot of overlap
I would say Carrie is
Dangerous that I was not guns and more the Raptors
Auto Repair
Anime
Spyder leader
So what's what happened
Mark guilty
Of course
He was often
And also I think this clip
It's kind of where I turn the corner on
Find her anymore okay
I still think he's being rude to her but I lose all interest in defending her after the
Innocent
He was off
The planet when the f****** murder house if that's the truth if that's the truth
If you don't understand I mean I have so much evidence
Of of the way that this works
Do you have you ever looked at Obama's
Birth
Different way of looking
Reality
The false Flags
The reason I asked you about false Flags is
That if you invest
Westgate Falls Flash
I mean listen to my interviews with James Fetzer
Ask yourself why you
Doesn't want those interviews
Out there in the public
They've deleted them off my sight he's he's an ex-marine
He's at a tenured
Professor
He's written over 10 books
He's a heavy-duty investigator
Very respectable man
Empty investigation
In my noosha
Every
Flag that is
Just happened
In the United States
He's he's
Obsessed with
And so what you really have to do is
Is look at the false flag
Start
Manufacture
By the secret
Government by
Under orders from
Higher-ups Etc and disappeared
It's a
A fascinating Journey
And I take it
I don't have time right now to educate you as to all the steps
Encourage you to watch my James Fetzer
Interview which is no longer on YouTube
It is now on
And also on
What is this called
Bitchute
Bitchute is place where people get thrown off of other social
Videos
Even know that this was going to be
Played on another show
Yeah I do know what that's nobody else
This is being played on Kevin
Channel and on freedom of Joyce
And I'm certain we have more listeners than Beau
Which makes me feel a little bit awkward about this probably
I think now
Comparatively
With the continuation of a storyline
I feel bad punching down but
It escaped its kind of inevitable
Receive the difference between
Where
That
Defense goes away
The defensive Mark was a murderer
And is making all this up
She's telling a story out is like
And I can kind of see it there
I think I probably feel differently
If there was any chance Mark was going to get out of prison
You going to start a cult that actually
Could get some traction
Mannerable
Syfy
Novels
Internalizing
The flip side of that
Stray is James Fetzer
Jim Fetzer
Carrie does have a responsibility
Need to point out one of the things
This is a false flag
And that is
The Holocaust
She's talking about
He's a great scholar and
Alright
That is where you do have a responsibility
Little bit
Is really into
Just include like
As we already know now but it's a clue as to how bad care react
I think it's a Rosetta Stone
Videos
Okay that's
In the right
Interesting
Because in the early 2000s Fetzer was a popular conspiracy theory
He was an actual professor
And because of that state is arguments about 11
Credibility
His work was s***
And most of it was entirely debunked
And the rest of the stuff that isn't debunked
Just the stuff it's too absurd to eat
EvanTube Anki
11 was done with super powered lasers
Celebrity status
Conspiracy world
Is a holocaust denier hamamoto
Something happened
Any wet for Holocaust denier along the road
Yeah when he was putting out these theories about 9/11
He was coming at it from a perspective of
Entering the conspiracy world
Decided to go in the Holocaust denial directions
But someone suggested that it was a natural conclusion to the path he was on
Career was characterised by severely uncritical readings of primary sources
And it nearly pathological drive towards
Sensationalize
He never cared too much about academic rigor
Wisconsin
The Hive making claims that got him attention
It feels like it might have only been a matter of time until he realized that denying the Holocaust wood
The most sensational
And there was plenty of that information he could misread
To defend his claim
That's pretty much top of the list in terms of
Wild out there clams beds
Will get you
A lot of tension
But it's a lot what is it what else can you deny or call a false-flag that
Bigger than the holler
The book no one died at Sandy Hook also
On May 21st 2013
Wisconsin hosted by jazz music
Where you came out publicly as a holocaust
This makes sense because admin believes that the narrative the Holocaust that is a religion for socialist Jews who were trying to use the
Religion to create a new world order
History
The book is as been described by United Kingdom Jewish Watchdog group has quote quite possibly the most
Antisymmetric book published in this country in recent years
That's an accomplishment.
Sure you got to give it up give it up.
Like to hang out with that guy
Decided to argue publicly for the first time in his career that the Holocaust was a false
Play Never Happened alright we're going to play some Miles Davis over here
So in 2015 Saturn started publicly supporting the Paul McCartney Is Dead
Conspiracy theory
A book called
And I suppose we didn't go to the Muenster subtitled The Beatles the Holocaust
And other math illusions
Yikes
Man that is a title of the book
Poorly researched and badly edited
But I believe
You can turn a phrase
Yeah we get to learn something about Kerry Cassidy that changes my tune on
Pretty much all
After Fetzer started denying the Holocaust
He wasn't really as hot and item in conspiracy circles anymore
It really says a lot about someone if they're still interested in interviewing Jim Fetzer in the present day
Has been on Project as recently as October 19th 2018
Redid a two-part episode about how Christine blasey Ford was engaged in a
Psyop against Brett Kavanaugh
Which is suspiciously exactly with Alex Jones
So
I've been defending Carrie to a certain
610 and
Mostly because I picked Kevin Moore's addicts he's being a dick
But defending her for there is a bad version
Of the same behavior and I think it's important
To recognize that
You got to you got to look at things on a sliding scale with people like this
Mark Richards is a murderer
It's kind of funny
In terms of
Lack of Integrity telling people that the Holocaust denier
Is irresponsible and dangerous
In terms of
Akademiks
Intellectual dishonesty
We've always known she's got
Solid anti-semitism
Little little bit
Kind of races that up to a larger red
And also
They have not
Not addressing it
Yeah this is this is one of those you know I got no hero it's fun to let him slap
You both suck
Still
Even if I don't like either of them say you're being a dick I don't like
My largest issue is how
Awful he is at
Talking acrobat
Note so scary
Just outright tells
Mark
Bart
Outright tell Kevin
This information that you're coming so I know all about it it's b*******
It doesn't it's your choice
Choice
You know you have to rely on your
Investigate
If you think that I should be
Links on my website
But I'm not
Okay because I think
Like I don't
I do think that the motivation
Preservation
Play We destroyed if everyone believed
He was a murderer
I just making all this s*** up and tricking me
I'm not going to post this stuff I don't have
Yeah
I don't know I just
Yeah she's going to be able to
Even though I was
Wrong about him murdering somebody but
Still right about every
Everything else you know too much weight
He was off playing it on a secret space program mission
You know it's
Established that he's lying about that
Calls into question
His
Integrity about all others Place really a claim
Emma's next clip
Probably the worst offense
The marks you could deposit
As her friend happened right so who
And Quentin that I masterminded it
How can I how can I counter that
You're talking about a man who didn't come
Which any kind of instrument show up on the scene or anything
He was supposed to have Mastermind
That is a mental David koresh
Mastermind you know
Whatever that was called again
Are these
Responsible
It's it's.
Verbally get
Cordis voice
Did he actually write in the Bible those words but we don't know any of that but but we talkin about
This particular case talking about but think about it
You know you're talking about
It's basically when
Reduce it all down
It's f****** word-of-mouth
There's nothing
Improve it
That's a little bit
Stop Fair Word of Mouth
Is everything word-of-mouth
If your argument is David koresh didn't have any
Do with Waco and f******
Jesus wasn't real
Choosing the Jesus wasn't real I think
Persuade anybody event wasn't the bathroom
Take that
Stanford
Universal
Everything on her show is worth
Were you there on the moon
Are you going to Indiana tonight to do a show
Who knows
Get out of
Plans tonight you are a very Discerning color
So the claim is
Actually what's going on here is there's a strong
Inflight
And that is the carry his taking the Mastermind
Idea
Mark masterminded this murder
And turned it into
He was mine
Controlling
Do 17 year olds into
Because that's an easier thing to argue against then
You promised them a car
Yeah it takes on
Superhero
Kanye
To her
And because of that she
Attacks that Mastermind idea
Potential other people
Who might have mind control
Crossing Hoover
Jean Grey
Any number of these
You cannot prove that those 17 year olds
Brain control
By him
Who else brain control
And who's very likely
Well hello the Nazis
Well hello there
People that took over mine
Control technology
From the
Which is the secret government
Rich pretending to visual
Or is it the state
Your Allegiance with the state
In this conversation
And you know I'm saying
That's not my
WIC Way Beyond that and I've got
For so many years I mean
A little condescending
No I meant you to smoke me a little bit
You're just talk
My anti-establishment
Has been triggered
Spell manipulation works
I then
Called her out of the blue
I'm not judging the condescension because I think you deserve
She has no reason to call need to be like half an hour long it's absurd that it is
It just gets to her being rude to him
But what about is so f****** awesome
You put your mic down
The snakes clip
Kind of subtle
But in the middle of it carry complains about the lighting
In the interview that she
Did with Kevin Moore
Cuz you did that
She complains
About the visual
Of the interview
Kevin Motors
In self-defense but it's kind of
All I can tell you is look at Obama's birth certificate
And ask yourself
President of
United States
And allies are
Plant
Unbelievable
This is the reality we live in you know I didn't create it
But I can tell you
That if you want to believe the evidence
That this man is showing you that's already very much in the public domain and has been
30 God
God knows how
Do so
It's alright if you want to put on your website links
People which is not very nice because it was visually
Aside from
From that you know
My information was good
Clear people I don't
Courage people to think what I want
Think for themselves
On the other
I am not going to
To become a state
Post their bulshit
I'm not going on to mainstream news
And post their lives
I mean
Post what I feel is
The closest
Truth
Disciple
If it wasn't coming from her I think that's a good pic
Crispin's Day speech for bass
Do whatever mean if you knew nothing about Kerry Cassidy be like yeah
Amended if you got her channel it's like oh here's a holocaust denier oh hear somebody talking about
Beatles and have been a very different speech that Pat
If he started with an also the president's birth certificate is fake
Right
But man I think
It's so
Funny
How
It's so funny because Carrie like visually her videos are just like
Sturgis
Like kind of grainy Skype
Call
This is not this is not the
Kettle black
This is watching the pot in the kettle stare each other down
Like this is
Crazy
So this point
You get Kevin
Talking about
The Pendragon
The idea that Mark had intended
Set up
Anu Campbell
Hey Terri realizes
About it for a little while
The end
Of her yelling
She reveals
Something about her former partner
Project Camelot
Bill
No longer with the operator
Ecuador
I don't I don't I don't know what he's up to
He seems like he doesn't like what's going on
With that carry much
Hey Auntie
Exact going for
You got to be got
If you're not into my Gretchen
Negative
Heroes 2
Weird
You know he did talk about he wanted to isolate Marine County wooden Transformers
Intermodal of Camelot
I mean you know
I don't know that sounds kind of benign to me What's the total of Camelot I mean you know what
Kennedy and Jackie
Return to Camelot
Use me up
As far as you know people could say I'm f****** crazy
I think I'm The Reincarnation of Guinevere what do you do about that I found something crazy I can tell you that
The bill Ryan
Comes from the Arthur
Arthurian bloodline
According to the Illuminati
That we've got
Okay
You know he's oneg
What do you want to do with that if you want to say we're crazy cuz he really a descendant of the Arthurian
Been told by several psychic
Pixie is
You know that's my intuitive
He doesn't claim it
It sound
Outlander
It sounds like
And if you want to come to that conclusion you're very welcome
How to make a pretty good point
He hasn't murdered anybody
Which is kind of a conversation
I really love a good
What do you think about that huh
What do you think
Cool
Good arguments all around
Yeah
Brothers
What do you do about that
In this neck
Kevin is talking about
Going to the
Conference call contact in the desert
And
He's not talking about going there and realized
Mark is
Full of s***
Or anything like that
I went to this conference I got a little bit disillusioned with
The Uso
Community
His mind again
Mark Richard
Their contact in the desert
On contact in the desert
He'll turn to the ages
You know I think nothing is truth out that this is my take on it right now
Especially
Can of worms
A lot of this
They're not being honest
And I can tell I can go right down the
I was going to say to that
Going to least
There's about 20
80%
If I
Is that an ATM
Symbolic
20%
Truth
I think this so much disinformation in the UFO field
Belmont
Is it ripped apart by disinformation
Ripped apart
Yeah certainly is
I would say
You got to throw the baby out with the bathwater
From scratch
Hold yourself
Responsible
Then for creating
Spaces where it don't let the b******* 20% is so real
I know what I'm sure there are
Some ghost alien
Researchers who aren't
Nonsense
Maybe the person exists
I've yet to see them
University
Possible if that person does exist
To preserve that
Harshly excluding 80% of liars
You have to
Because if you don't
And you know what they do
They support each other
Each other's cons
The same thing but not wedding your guest
Is what those 80% due to make sure that they Remain the 80% in that space
It's pretty much a
It's pretty much
Yeah
And you know what else
Exactly what
Put also about yourself
Yeah that's the problem
It's the new Hustle
He's trying to
Create legitimacy for his discernment
About his channeling and his own
By putting a feather in his cap of taking out Mark Richards
Yeah it's
Disgraceful
Yeah it is
Cannibalistic
Yeah it's a hundred percent
He's willing to
Take the risk
Hope you know
Eating himself
How to try and get over her
No one other than
This b*******
The possibility that his documentary could be
Outside
Space interested Community world
It seems low
It's about a half-hour on net
I don't think that he has much to worry about in those
Communities
Like with him
Going after Mark Richards hotline
No one's going to the community
I already
And they already believe the others
Yeah there's not dark people
Externally
It's so subterranea
And it's not
It's so far outside of what most normal people pay it
For sure
Flourish
It's a it's a little bit of a
But it makes for more fun for us
I'm a little bit put off by this
Conversation now
Because now it's
Seems like Carrie is full on bullying him
Really like trying to
Steamroll over here putting up with this for like 20 minutes
Within the fur
If you don't have new information this conversation isn't really
Do we have anything else
Talk about
So I understand why she would steamroll
Bulshit
And she
Attack him in a way that would
Useful
And I also find him
Manipulating and godinger in
So I don't like
Like it was fun whenever I was doing just great
And now it's
He's here
He's putting these little needles in everywhere you can
He's trying to goad her
Into screaming
Batman
Of somebody who's like yeah
Itsy itsy
It seems like
Awareness
On his part of like
I do believe that there's a possibility that he's just
Wired in such a way that he doesn't think that Carrie knows all this stuff
I think
If you bring her new information
He doesn't know where to go with it and doesn't want to
Sounds like an idiot on the phone
He's trying to find different ways to bring up the
Flags Apple
Do you know about this stuff
Osher Project Camelot
Call you don't want to be on
Yeah
I get I get where you're coming from but I think it could all be
Him being
Poor communicator
Out of his depth in terms of
Communicating with someone who's like
Before
Purposeful
Satoshi
Oh she's recording
She brings up
Durant
So they're both recording
I think that's what makes it legal for him to
Play it
What are these people
I don't know probably smart for Carrie to have done that
Just as
Self-defense
Yeah for sure
Because this guy is a manipulative
She didn't know that back bringing up stuff about Mark Richards
It seems like it would have been a wise
Decision just in case
Edit
Have your own version
So
K2
Try to pretend
Joanne on the show
I think someone
I think when I interview John about years ago
Many moons ago like I did
Insofar facts
No that is not at all how he comported himself
He was helping her make the narrative
Established
On his own without at her helping at all that Mark was off-planet when the murder
Participate
And the Farfetch'd
The very first question I believe was like
Everything that you say is true tell me a little bit more
Basically
Purview
If you can call that
Phone call annoyance
Kevin just gives up on what he's trying to do because realizes I've hit a brick wall
There's no real point
Continue
Carrie's just like I don't really care what you
Small Potatoes
I think it's I think it's
I think it is at
Pureness
In her
Establish DeLucia
I knows it I know whatever information
You're going to throw at me I've decided what I believe
Let's live our lives
What you do
Flakka
Looking at this place
Interesting
You know
I mean you don't have to let me
Just do whatever you do to be honest
Iridescent
You're an independent agent and
If you want to let
Joanne know that you know
Journalist you're going to do something you know
Whatever
That's fine
Cat litter I'm sure if
If you don't if you need her email address I'll send it to you
You know I mean it
It's really neither here nor there what
You said to me
In this conversation
Because it's not
Anything I'm not aware of
And have dealt with
Not just to do
This case
But so many others
Alright
I would say outside of Defending a holocaust denier
Support
Pretty much our entire position
A little big except
Is
For me to get home
But in terms of social dynamics
Swear at him
Oh yeah absolutely planes on Terry juices show is Evelyn
By having that
Mastication
Hey call him a pedophile Adeline
I got no one's back
Exception of herpes
Totally
Rooting
And then I want her to be
By somebody
Government regulation on Tropicana
No Maybe.
To spiral out of control
Surprizamals
For all of them
To just have
Actual exposure of
What they
Put out to the portal
Are you rooting for some sort of ironic
Revere Kevin documentary not him
By someone
Isn't
Also a f******
Channel
Like someone who doesn't have to
Text the business
Someone who can actually be like
This is how the sausage is made
A bunch of dick
Someone who doesn't get
Channel 8
Ghost and then have that goes tell him how great
Write his own voice character
You are such a good boy
Bring up the
Portion
Because we get back to
Terry Joyce
His interview
They come back after playing
There's a lot of caffeine
Aspersion on
Carry course
Terry believes
Security might be working
Things for Michael Aquino
To Satan it's a bunch of
Not a problem in this world or alive
Terry brings up that Carrie is like
Seems to have a lot of people who are criminals
Switch
FairPoint Sean David Morton.
The
Mark Richards
Some others that I don't know
I'm not I'm not going to necessarily DoubleDown on cuz I haven't
I don't know
If they're actually criminals but
If not convicted
Still eligible to be a criminal
Fraud types
So clip from their interview they had that conversation
Can I get around to talk about Simon Park
Who is the
The former MP
From England
Who says
About once or twice.
Alien
Either
Defender
Of Marc rich
He is one of the ones
Carrie
Goes to all the times I
They've got marks back
The voucher all this
I remember liking him
SMS
I think I thought he was doing
Pretty good job
Better than Nigel farage
Perhaps
I will certainly
Pequa Park
And that he had intelligence
Contact
In the UK
Who
Vouch
For all of Mark's stuff
And could prove
Fitmark wasn't lying
About all this
Would have access
I don't think he is anymore so
Look I don't want you I don't sweat
He claimed that he had all this proof and then
Kevin contacted Emma's I'm more than happy to look at it
Obviously
Excitement
So
So Kevin is decided he's lying
Wouldn't allow that s*** out of
Home office
No thank you
Agree with Kevin
About this s***
Kevin take that
Is problematic
As we know that
Channel Azalea
When you
To lie
What are the b******* are you talkin about on your other parts of your information that you given out Friday
I hate him
No it's not allowed to say that
Literally not allowed to say that
I am now talkin from an alien
Yeah yeah yeah
Can't you can't be like okay
What about Mark Richards
When
F****** alien
If you're willing to
Aliens on your show
My God
But that's part of why ice I entirely believe
This is all part of
Intentional strategy
Who does Kevin wants to Corner the market
Community
Debunking
She wants to
To take the space of
Within the community who also
He wants that
Space really badly and I take that from
This
At the end here where
Is that some plans
To make more.
I wish that Sam
This just helps one person this information
Jokes on you know what I mean I will be walking away from at some point and start in another documentary
Tomahawks will be a documentary that I am going to be doing this well
Civil Corey Goode and David Wilcock okay but they're also fragile
You hear that at the end
But not from the same place of anger
Coming from a place of anger with Carrie which is
Unhealthy
New channel would want you to do
Will tell you not to do this
Don't do it
I think that he is a completely sucked up dude who's operating from
Composition of bad faith
A doing something
To be done
That's what's up
I can't trust his Mark Richards documentary
Robin
Somebody information probably you can
Do you verify it
I can't trust
Because it comes
From him I want a mark Richards documentary
So awesome
Tia Mann
Absolutely
Absolutely I think
Topics are grapes
4 documentary
Great for documentaries coming from a critical perspective
I don't want him doing
Service of him
Establishing a position of unassailable Leti
It looks like
Are you f******
Serious I'm skeptical
Because
That only increases my legitimacy
I am a skeptic towards this channeling I obviously have interrogated it
Google search on every ghost that I'm f******
Build a wall around himself
For him being full of
Right
I can't support
Well the same time trying
The siphon away
Carrie's
Audience
What is the real thick
Deal
I hate it
I really would be even more I'm going to be so mad if
Turns out the
Like it's Nails it everything I've seen some of the other stuff he's made
Not as professional you know like your vlogs
Spiratone Ocampo
His trailer
Zoe contain clips of interviews that I think
Bye.
The voice-over was terrible ending wasn't great
So if he's working
I think that it could be
Not that good
I really hope that actually
He never released
I feel like people are
To demand
We do an end
Documentary about
It's interesting that
Kevin Moore is on this show that
And he's going
On and on about
Discernment
We've heard him
Within the interview with
Terry and in the car with
Carrie
Say discernment
The buzz word of the day
This is what
It's all about
It's one thing to let someone
Something awful slide
Just coasting in life
Be able to Channel 8
Intelligences
We can probably easily told you
Mike Richards
But yet you can see how that might be a low priority for these days
Tell you about that
Yeah they got bigger
That's the difference of discern
Discernment is something you must
Tubac
Earlier he can make the argument I wasn't
Fixing this discernment about these topic
So Kevin says
In this interview with Terry
This is a fairy in Fort
Interview
This was an important interview at 2 I'll do with you
Right now I'm at wall
That's how I feel
This is a very important interview for him
The bearer of bad news
You go on the freedom of choice
It's
Just one in a long line of
Kevin Moore
Chose
Shity discernment
Cuz for what he's saying it's important interview like
This video has been up for a couple days now it has a
Couple hundred
Did did she make it
On the radio.
I don't know I don't think so and I don't think the audience is much more than that
Which is 80
Very small
Audience but he's speaking to not
An important
I wonder if she
Put in the
Comment to the Linq
In the comments of the YouTube video a lot of Link
Two showing how much of an
An a****** that
I would love that if that's okay
Interview
He's full of s*** right it's giving it seems unlikely cuz even though it be
Beginning of their interview they talked
About how Carrie doesn't
She does that
She's doing this interview right now
She's had Randy Cramer on as a guest who's the super soldier who carries
Also had one who told stories
Miraculously being returned into his bed
After years of fighting in space
Yeah but the
Space Ghost that Kevin channels
His story is no less or more credible than mark
It's just he didn't murder a guy
Yasso
I don't understand okay.
You do get points for having a guess who hasn't murdered again
You get a pass
It doesn't matter if you didn't murder a guy I guess
So
You have
The same
Guest
Shows that your discernment or whatever
Now
I have
Strong reason to believe
Her discernment is far worse than carries cuz there's a guy who's been on
I think one
Maybe twice on Project Camelot
Who has been on Terry show
Time
That's
Kelly
The guy who believes that there is a alien base Under The Getty Museum
Right
Okay
Now
In his defense
There is
She's a huge fan of Steve Kelly
Anybody with the tiniest amount of discernment would be able to watch a video of his and be like
Oh my God this guy is a f***
Freep
I think if you had any better
Wedding that you wanted to do
Did you get it
I think I did this within an hour 2 hours of just looking into it
Oh my God this guy seems like someone who steals
Looks like this guy is the weapon
Museum
And let me tell you
Play Museum
No aliens
Great music
I know this from going to Terry's
YouTube
She's also
Which
With Steve
Okay
No
The f****** outside music
Now you see this slope to slope of this wall is so they have a good shooting
Position from Up
For the Dozen
Unauthorized tour that he gave some bogetti
He wanders around outside
The outfit that he's wearing
Is
Ridiculous what does it look like long hair long hair
Rocking sunglasses has a button up shirt
Also
Unbutton
Not all the way
I would say three buttons
California
All the way up
It's real like this is how you decided to dress up
To give it to work of the alien space base Getty Museum
I think I might get the
The appearance
You don't care
There's a lack of professionalism here certainly
Different
Like I want to go to the the Tower of London be like
I see you know if you went down this
You would find
The first
So she has a bunch of b******* going on
On her website
Exercise
None of them will talk to each other
So
Anyway here
So here's the last clip
The cabin is a f******
Cancel
Is there anything else that you would like to add
As a button or something that you want to make sure that
Those who were listening to my Channel or
Radio
Get Terry Cassidy I hope this documentary
Your work and yourself
That's what I want
Awful
Is he recording a shoot promo like
So I just I can't walk away from without
Thinking you're
The total assholes
Cuz I want to support
The Dabangg king of these people
Playful debunking
Right
He's a malignant narcissist
Two took that phone call really person
He got bro
And he was like I'm not going to let somebody do that to me so I'm going to
Definitely
Yeah you're making this documentary
The last word
I hope that I destroy you
F*** you man it is all so hard not to the sample size is small but it's hard not to notice it
Set of the people
Matarese about
The one who
He's filled with anger
I think he might also have that anger towards Simon
Parks
I don't know it's hard to tell from the context to what he was saying
Brightest future documentary
I agree and if I had more
Actual evidence
To say that he
Anger towards believe me
I would bring it up
I think that Carrie probably
Call
And maybe he's responding
I asked
In a chauvinistic his anger comes from a place of
His masculinity being attacked
It's possible I don't know I don't have enough
But certainly would fit a pattern
Other people
Is Trey Smith
Play that
Phone call
Like it was his choice.
Play that song
Is he does not come off
Looking good
He doesn't
I listen to all this and I came away feeling a bit
A little bit
Because
On the one hand
I'm defending Carrie
It's qualified
It's not
Sounds like yeah she's right f*** this guy
I think f*** this guy but not because I'm
I'm just
Being fair the
But he's being rude
I'm also being fair
Her behaviors can go too far and when
Define holocaust denier
And so it's not it's not cutting it's not black and white
And I realized I was having
Of discern
Seems to be all about
Jordan what if I told you
That I found the perfect place to learn
About discern
Microsoft Encarta
No
What if I were to tell you that Kevin Moore has channeled aliens about the very issue
Of discernment
Really
We're doing this
Here is a video that Kevin Moore put out a couple years back
Where he channels
The one
Lucci
That's the people that he talks to might as well been
So here's where he channels
About what
It is a good question
We would say that too hot
22 sermon
One has to be
In complete control
Allstate roof
To begin with
One has to know
Xanax
In order
To take back your power
I know you'll truth
You must first
Learn to listen
Until very soul
I got Paws here really quick as we get through this
Concrete thing that he actually says open by reading the dictionary
No just really interested in Webster
What do you do I open with closing his eyes and making a scrunchy face
Choose not
Which your eyes look out
Which
Is inside
Audiobahn
To that what you came here with
And you shall leave with
The only thing
That will always be a come
Fuel cell
He smiles as if like
I pulled that one
Well almost
The improv lines
He was like ice
Surprise myself with how
Bullshittin that was exactly the vibe I got from the visual
The discernment is something comes from within you have to listen to your soul
Great
I feel like Stefan molyneux if enough people
Perhaps
Yeah
Honestly I hate
To say this
Christopher newest
Stupid
Stefan molyneux is way smarter than
Antelope
What it is
And how it says it
Your soul that is
Chihuahuas
Any
Current situation that you may be going through
It is your
Through
Alarm
You're one
Ruth
To yourself
Knowing or loving
All of you to you for you for others as well
Define this
You must go deep within
Instead
Justice situation
Feel-Rite
No
Really
Except
Sometimes it gets a bit
You could say
On the way that
Lost in the situation of
This is Phil Right
No no I'm not feeling right this is this this is not right I shouldn't be doing this
And you you
Get logic mixed in with a motion mixed in with a motion to extend with logic logic logic
Motion
And he's never coming from that
To place
Pure soul
I want to point out that it's strange
That these aliens that he's channeling verbal tics of him
Sorry I told you when I start back
It's so weird interview private folktale
Aliens speaking through him
I think they would probably still change
Word choices
Samurai
Customer is just looking for words
It's just
How the the Bible
It can just be a vocal tic by Asher
You cover
Your brain trying
To come up with the word you're looking
I do it all the time
If aliens were guiding the words coming out of your mouth
Unless
I don't know use your brain to come up with Words which I guess
Which just means are you
Anyway he's not done
Yes of course
New alarm
Hope you recognize
What's true north
Realself
But we are choking about here
Most important
Audible
Yeah come on
Start it over after that
Now these situations remembrance
Yes
Then there's nothing
Someone
It would be wise to
Stop straightaway
Cuz you have no rights
Do that
I think you doing
But how would you like that
We still talk about the sermon
House choice
Situation
Is one way
Define that place
No it is not
How discernment works
Factory
Another
It's true
Very still
Being
As much as you can be
That
The feeling of
This feels right
Is foolhardy
Now to be able to get to those
Actuation
Places
Shall we say the shall we say aliens often
The one thing I leaned often
Supermarket
Situation situation
The shall we say
Trying to pretend
I'm saying this is reasonable
Or something almost compulsively as a tick
You can edit
You can do it you can do takes
How do you watch yourself doing this go
Going through
Suntrust.com feeling
A number
And you feel not too sure
As we have said to you before the best way is
Little
Small decisions
That's very cool
Getting to that place
Feeling what they got saying
Feeding weather joyous
Feeling with the feeling
Situations with small decisions are to be taken
Small small
And then yourself undisable ones come alone
You may need to
Do I take this job do I not
Do I put this investment money here to Minot
Newspaper decision aliens are real
Used
Same
Apply the same
And you
Only come
Scheelhaase
Truth
Aliens are really into portfolio
Crab
If he's Twitter and I got burned
What he's talking about there is really Elementary basic self-help
Difficult time
It is very powerful is
Building the
It's from those smaller victories
It smaller
Regions where you did make a choice
Knowing that you made a choice and everything was okay
You know building up your confidence
It's this is 101 self-help tapes
Just repurposing
And regurgitate
Under the guise of speaking
For a f****** group of alien
This is interesting
Isn't
Because
101 stuff
Find if someone
Takes that game power over their ability
Controller
Don't also think it's that interesting
Because we've already kind of talked about that
Absurd
Especially
Smaller parts of it where it's
Came up with a word before you do it
Dammit
I'm trying to get to that I find really interesting
Realized
Can't really
Come up with it ahead of time
Because I think that was actually going on
Is
Almost as genre of performance
Like
If you want to take it from like an anthropological sociological level
Is
Expressing
A modern version of
Performance
Kind of an oral tradition
Like the way
Using these terms
Susan talking about
Comes from within
Those words
That he gives a s*** about closer
Those are signals
Open oral tradition
Comes down
From
People trying
To rip off
Eastern Traditions people who have channeled aliens in the past
All funnels down in this oral tradition
And he's just trying
To become a part of it
He's trying to
Thinking he's channeling alien
I don't think he is
A willing misconception
That was a
She's actually doing
Tapping into an oral tradition
These people have established
In the past
I don't know hundred years
All the way back to Edgar
Perkasie
All of the people who Channel bulshit
He's taking the
Terms and taking the ideas
From is that that's built up in his subconscious
So when he's very looking forward
Or feeling like something is
He's coming through him
He's
Willingly misleading is audience into thinking it's an alien group
In reality what it is is
Corpus
Of
Work
Existed from those
Spiritual Revival of the early nineteen
Interesting go on it is actually more interesting to me than just calling
Outright Charlotte
Because then you could kind of get in
To like how this
This
Tinuum of information
When you look at it as
Type of
Performance
I don't know I mean it's still misleading and dishonest and he's using it
You make money off people in psychic hotline
Becomes much more
I think
What I find in
Interesting about
Channel
Play song
All of his other
The wind chime
Is that
Channeling and more
Daily Affirmations
Like he seem like he's more talking to himself in almost
Like writing down
Here's what I'm going to do I'm going
And he's just packaging it in this
Way because
Some of them have to do with like Atlanta Roswell crash
And stuff like that but because
The word of the day
Discern babe that's what we get when you start
We get to the end of this and I would say that my discernment tells me
Kevin Moore is
First of all
Piece of s*** to Charlotte
Yep
This is an elaborate
And carries the victim
Ensure
Carrie sucks to
You know no winners
Yelled at me for saying that last time
So anyway
This is been our Wacky Wednesday
Stuff
I don't know why I'm interested
Has metastasized
Spread
Looking at
Mark Richards interviews
On Project Camelot
Has now spun out of control where
We were listening to
Kerry interviewed by
Kevin Moore
And now we're listening to Kevin Moore being interviewed by someone else
Stereo completely out of control everything is going crazy
Terry Joyce
Nothing good
Probably hanging out with
Steve Kelly talking about
Avenida storm the Getty
I believe Steven Kelly would bring a bomb
You have to blow up the outside to get inside
Human life would be lost
You got to get the bomb into the center in order to get rid of the whole thing
If you just blow up the outside that's cosmetic
But you can always rebuild the Getty
You're still talking about a bomb
I don't like it
So anyway
On Friday with
We're also on Twitter
We are at knowledge underscore
I'm at go to all sorts of other places are
Free to get Podcast
Around this year intern
For now as we come to the end of it
I don't think Kevin Morris killed
Anybody that's good for him
No he doesn't he's making that up
That's all bulshit
He's killed
My ability now he hasn't believed this stuff before him
The definition of discernment
Beat that into the ground
Is Alex gay
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color