Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Flash have you ever been on a bow
Dear friend Matt a little bit of a boat
Excursion into a lake
Where is deeply hungover
I was swimming around and
Declared that I belong in the water
I was built to swim. I love being in that water I think it was just a hangover it's relieved by that
Water
I don't know I'm not that I'm not generally on a boat
Go down to Belmont Harbor
Lake Michigan I don't have a yacht
Nope nope
I don't understand anybody who owns a boat
Chicago other than they are
Just people that idea of owning a boat in Chicago
Thought about it
Not terms
Actually thought about it
But I imagined what it would be like
If the docket during the winter
The reason
To hire somebody to handle all of the bones of a boat guy feels that way
We're not both
Tell me what the show is kinda about
We're back from our way of new folks
Into the show
Cuz I did get a number of messages
Expressing the
The f*** is this
Not even angry whale
Some confusion about why we were talking about
List
But I apologize for any
Confusion about that
We are
One of the reasons
That is I of course
Duda news broke in the middle of the week if you had his mother came out
The most non committal bulshit that obviously means please impeach the president
Committed
Novikoff
Before a lot of the sentence
A little bit of
We can't
Say that he
Alex
We're going to have a real unhinged response to this
Did the show we have to record
Put on Friday
Alex is back
Studio on Thursday
Prepare episode in order to get it out on Monday
Get back to it but also I have a really strong prediction
He already has a
Mueller is a f******
Game Trader for the
Narrative built into what it what is this going to change
It could just
Like make him more
Desperate
Or whatever
Lycopene about how awful Mueller is
Mueller
More be like
No he said a bunch of stuff to the report really basically means this you don't need to
Please if you are a Republican or a can
Conservative or
Do not actually read the report because they will tell you things that maybe you shouldn't outfits diversionary
What's his role
Yeah
It doesn't matter
Especially for Alex's coverage of it
Me either a more RAM
Version of it or
Exactly what he's been saying all along
It will do present-day episode on Monday
When we have more than
In front of us
Back in the past
Check out what Alex is doing
In the aftermath of
News coverage of it
Today we're going over January 29th
Through 31st
Yes the greatest
It's a good one
That's all I got to say about that
Devote
Entire month of February
History Month
He's really going to go to
Through a lot of
How's your tune after we left
The very first stand-up comedian
Black
Kate
Stand-up crap
People have signed up and are supporting the show
I'm a policy wonk
Think it's Mark Richard
Perhaps
You are now
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Alexandra
Sport Chevrolet
These guys do that
Show
Important to remember about this time. Right
January 29th
Specifically
Is that we've crossed a line of demarcation
First of all we've had Alex on the last episode
I haven't gotten into the
These people saying that they were actors
Now
Christian Anderson Cooper
100% proof
Committed to that
He has signaled that he is
Supportive
Of those things
Which is building upon him having
Professor James Tracy
On
By Paul Joseph Watson
It's immensely annoying how it's
Movies Littleton
Any babies
Just want him to like
Perhaps more importantly than any of the coverage
The point where
Has sent Alex
Some email telling him
Time to stop
The point where he has gotten in contact with Alex
Made
Infowars aware of the fact that
Their coverage
Having a negative impact
On their life
Yeah so everything after this point
Really take away any
Volusia but he doesn't know the effect
It only gets worse from here
Kind of
I mean
The Paynes
A bad picture
Further on the Spectrum
Stupid Flash
Email
Then you're responsible for everything
Episode
The first years and I work
No that's great
Buford piranhas piranhas of Liberty
I don't know what to tell you
Swimming up the urine stream of I make this promise
To our listeners
If I ever meet Alex Jones
Messenger
Ono Liberty piranha
All right. It here we are on the 29th
Never
Expect anything
Sing to delete
When I go back into the
The past or even a present look at Alex Jones
But here's something that I found delightful I will see if you can figure out why
Cinematic film
Why does this delight make
Well that none of his previous documentaries have been powerful
He's quoting Orson Welles
But he's not calling Orson Welles from a movie or a speech
He's quoting Orson Welles from
Paul Masson commercial commercial real
We will sell no wine before its time is the tagline of Paul Masson
Winery
If you guys
I would play this audio on the show but it's so visual go if you haven't watched
Go on YouTube and watch the outtakes
Of Orson Welles trying to
2 film
Commercial
It's a1421
Famously
Drunken commercial
It's not
To me that he's
He's passing off a quote of
That is actually just
Logan
Shiama commercial that he probably saw when he was
That's like that's the Orson Welles from Animaniacs
If I were quoting
Country goodness Siegfried penis
Alright just dance
For the road Maurice lamarche
Next week
Difference
Present-day Alec
And
Social media
They didn't this Mexico
Itsfunneh
These sorts of things
About Facebook for example
Cannot operate without Facebook
You Don't Know What You Got Till It's Gone
Facebook as a joke
System
Now certainly he still believes those sorts
Seem to have any concern about the idea of it
You're entitled to be on in 2013
Maybe because he got on it is business model shifted so heavily
Towards
A sensationalist
Promotion on social media
Quickbase without it
Things Fall Apart where is
It wasn't so dependent on that back guy whatever some still had a f****** gold
Can't put it somewhere where people
If that's a problem with
Make it better Cornerstone of your marketing
Social media
Can't even muster the energy deplete I just want to be in the water
Famously I just
Sit here and
So I can open up Twitter and
Try and type of promotional teams like
Battle Lake
You are The Hungover piranha of lakes in my little teeth
I got three tweets
Reading things where people talking s*** about Dave Brubeck that's all I want to do
From the 29th we get a really depressing caller
Me
Out
I feel very bad for him
I feel like Alex
Deeply explosion
Oh yeah I completely agree I just wanted to tell everybody
I live on a $900 a month
Spend as much money as I can on it
Wards.com
Rothman.
I bought every one of your hat
Anything I'm going to join the Paul Revere contest I'm going to do anything
I'm considering moving to Austin
Just to just to be closer to your operation
These disabled that part of the quest Washington disability dollars a month
Tons of Alex's merch
Response
Stop
You need to take care of yourself that's
You know you're out of fixed-income don't waste it on multiple shotgun shirts
Specifically people who make $900 a
Well what do you mean
Is given is going to say like that Alex is Paul Revere contest
That we know how it end
Maybe short film
He didn't I don't believe so but
Meowth
That is about
So we can have a caller
He bums me out for a different
Thousand dollars
Because of the content that he brings up but it also
Offers us a glimpse
I think is really interesting into another
We have
Didn't give a s*** about entitled to it now
Here is another one
This has to do with his rhetoric and worldview
I did have another point I wanted to ask you if you've ever heard of a man named Wally Chobot
Shoebat
He wrote a book called God's war on terror
And he's a former Muslim terrorist
And he would be a really good interview
Happy to have them on
Basically
The conversion that he had to Christianity was amazing
I mean because he was a full-blown I mean he was
No killing people
For Islam
But you really ought to read that book God's war on terror.
He doesn't care about islamophobia
He doesn't have that as a primary driver
Of his of what he
He feel
Call like that nowadays would be like
And not only that I'm going to yell for 10 minutes
Christianity because they are held by the
Yeah it is very different
Respond today
It was a guy who has started making the rounds and right-wing circles and
Early mid
As The Story Goes Showbox was a terrorist working for the Palestinian Liberation Organization
He claims that he was a terrorist
And he was responsible for firebombing and
Israeli bag
I called the bank
Okay can I
Interject 41
Yeah he told me that he was
The former terrorist who wrote a book called God's war on terror
Christianity
Suspicion is he is not
Real or not
He claims he was locked up by
He came to the United States and went to college here in Chicago
Ultimately becoming US citizen and converting to Christianity
Ocean career with a book called why I left
Terrorism in the return of radicalism
He began to get more active in this line of work around 9:11 because he saw the outcome of terrorist
Surrounded
Southwest
In 2009 he brought in over $500,000 on the election
Circuit
Interesting Lee one of his clients was
The US Department of Homeland Security to pay them
He said things like quote
All Islamic organizations in America should be the number one anime
All of them
But here's the problem
Showbox story involves specific
I know specifics
And when they are they turn out not to be true
Because
Specifics
If you do look into them and they're not
This is a huge credibility problem
There's no evidence
Robot was ever involved
On the record and said there was no Fireball could match the description
Time frame
The attack Shobha claims through carried out
The Israeli government is clear that they have no record of him ever being arrested or jail
His family members have said that his story
Just doesn't make
And of course the story doesn't
A guy firebombs and Israel
Especially
The story stretches
Credulity on it
Reflect reality at all
Now what I find interesting
Things that I do believe one part of Showbox
Block Story
Money like crazy as the war on terror ramped-up in the following years there was so much money on the table
Over former terrorist
Could give a glimpse into the mindset of this country
Supposed
When there are no records
Support the backstory of a cup
Claim that you know you're you're using
Luther
PLO terrorist
For the bounty on
When your family member say unequivocally that you are
The fake name
Sympathizers
I hate you for converting
The Christianity
There's always a way out of the quarter
As long as you're willing to be
Which seems to be what
Walid shoebat
It appears that way
He's spreading
B******* anti-muslim propaganda
Department of Homeland
Security
And of course this career Shobha trick to whole lot of people
Prophet office
In 2008 he was listening donations
Walid shoebat Foundation
She claimed is registered as a charity
Pennsylvania
Although the Pennsylvania State Attorney's office
Horse races pretty serious question
But the biggest questions need to be directed towards how it was so easy
For someone who is
Rhythm exporting counter-terror
For example
After the Pulse Nightclub shooting in Orlando he said quote
The only ones loading over 50
He gave slaughtered our liberals idiots and gay lover
I don't care about gays who are Muslim loving anti-gun liberal
Stupid people late life die stupid people who hate life always die
After the Charlie have no shooting plotted the terrorist attack because the magazine had quote insulted the Virgin Mary
Like this is ridiculous s***
He's a little bit all over the
He's a little bit all over the place
It should be no surprise that he's a big
Supporter of trump
Theodore has explicitly
We called for Trump to establish a quote Christians
Supremacist Society
Be creative
No freeway
For homosexuals
There's no liberation
For perversity
Weird mutant psychos walking around with clip liberal Dyke hair event dressing up as
Looks like OSHA
Stop
Society would be arrested
Put to death
In the present day will leave misunderstanding ship it sounds really similar to a lot of the stuff that comes out of Alex's mouth pretty regularly
But what interests
Sing to me
Should I clip with Alex
Interested in this
Even though what we do has been agitating against Islam for years
This point
Third book
Islamophobia is not a primary part of Alex's marketing strategy in 2013
Which I assume is largely because
You didn't realize something that will
New from day one
And that is the Pacific
Super lucrative business
He just hasn't gotten on board yet
That he's lying about being
Terror
Beginning
Later on
He becomes essentially at
Terrorist
Yeah
An apologist
That's a weave
Pretend we know we become what we pretend
Yeah the master that we were too long because
Yeah tunic
I think there's more just
If you don't have a real good through line
And you're just
Shut off eventually
The worst parts
Love yourself will
Will become appleside
Yeah I think
I think that's something
So Alex gets another caller British guy
Who Alex's
Is doing the fake ax
Yeah I don't
Okay
Because he does
A pretty good handle on
British Affairs let's play
Doubt he's just embarrassed
Sing Alex
Okay cuz Alex
Keep trying to bring up the
Things he think
About like the Royal Family
Or Britain
And every single time
Actually Alex
Here is a cliff
Here is a clip of Alex getting embarrassed by British guy
Who is doing the fake accent
No idea
About the Royal thing
Actually German
The name is pretty sure anyone else
200 years ago
I think that
Actually it's kind of more mixed
On the other hand I am defeated
Hooters the boaters glad
That's embarrassing
What are you talkin about
I was talking to this guy for a very long time
Is because
It gives Alex an opportunity to go
I think Alex is enjoying
But he's making good
Hubert you think so I think so cuz what I'm hearing is it from this
Is a long interview
Because it's
A fly guy, trying to get off stage
Hizi keeps
That
More than
He thinks what maybe but I would merge our two idea
But he also wants to come at the expense of making fun of
So if
It's sort of
But it reaches a point of
Intolerable
Seem like he wants to
Hang up on you
He does
He seems like he wants to
Going
The guys expressing
Idea of
About
He's defending royalty
Royal
And monarch
Alex is very dense that
You know being into the Royals is
Kind of okay cuz you're like you kept their nationalist
People leaving the royalty is a nationalist
Holyshit Alex
What's going on
I don't think it's the
His his arguments
When walk
Through
And ideas
So bad
He's like
Which is better
Does end up actually ending the conversation
It's
Jarring because very quick
Alex accuses him of letting his ax
Wichita
If you
Listen to what's being done
Disgust you realize that this
Is an intolerable thing
To have Alex
His narrative
This is 2 Central
What Alex believe
And this guy if allowed to keep talking
We'll end up pointing out how Alex is wrong
About the central point
Of his beliefs
Will actually what I really think
Most of
What you're seeing comes from h.g. Wells
Yep that's right
Thank you look at the history when I say progressed if I don't mean
The modern
America around the
19th century
Are there
Alex knows that he's out of his death
It will reveal that there is a larger political context to everything that he's
Trying to present to his audience that actually refutes a great deal of it and all Alex's doing is MIT purposing
F****** science fiction
Authors
And then
People like Bertrand Russell
Using
Stuff from their work
Selectively out of context and manipulative lie
In order to create this
Conception of the globalist
Pretty wild going from not knowing about him 2 and 3 months
Obviously debunking every stupid thing that Alex
I admire it in some way
Although I don't I don't know if I totally support
Some of the conclusions that
British guy was dry
Restraint ideas
Okay
He was one of the better callers
Of her.
If only because it becomes so clear how Alex
Have to protect himself
Like that your accents
Got to go
Not at all actually played it back at number of times
Text Cliff Alex
Or anything
The new idea
Alex
Excuses
White terrorism but I thought that this
Shorter clip
It's kind of a perfect encapsulation
Adjust
I thought it was worth it
As it is an art
It's just a perfect
Set up
If you have the idea that they want so desperately
Organs that are willing to
False flag terrorism
To blame on you
It ordered
Facilitate getting your gun
Do you have that in place
Anything can be faked
And the way you selectively use the accusations
Something's being fake
Becomes
Important
Because it's
Reply it's revealing
Absolutely
Clip is a perfect encapsulation of how you get
The groundwork laid
In order to excuse just about any
Alex talks about Bill Joy his article
Nita
We talked about this a hundred times
Alex claims always
Consistently
That
Bill Joyce article was about a meeting
Of high-level
Technocratic globalist
Who we're getting together today
Discuss what to do about human
Once they are taken over by me
And robots
That is not true at all
That is only true
Have a very short Passage
Where Bill Joy is literally quoting the Unabomber
Not discussing that as a
Technocratic
It is
Rumba
Unabomber Manifesto
Yeah
Yeah it was announced it was a pretty good man
I've heard that from
People I don't want to talk to at Target
Anita
Why
Discussed again
One reason
And one reason only
I believe in this clip
Alex makes it way to clear
That he knows
But he's misuse
Send that article
And he knows that what he's doing
He's quoting the Unabomber
That's not in the article at all in the article
Quotes the Unabomber
Not say that
This is crazy
He believes to be true about this article is just the Unabomber part of
F***** up cuz the Unabomber as part of the globe
Obelisk
Through it
Cut through the bull shakes
MKUltra program
I don't know but whatever it is
Read the rest of that article
Bwild zurita
Outfits
About Alex's
Beliefs about what the globalist
Plan to do
We're about to hear Alexei
Something
News radio's Jimmy James
Might be able
Donkey wrestler
That's literally me
What do you mean you're not going to take me into the bathroom with you I mean it makes sense that Alex would have his buddy Joe Rogan
On the show it was great
Very
The 29th
There's not a whole lot going on
LabCorp 30th there is not much going on at the show either
Alex has a guest cancel
And so he has his second
One of Ron Paul's
Yeah it's so weak in one of Ron Paul's Buddies
We have to second-guess
Need a good saying for like 2 hours
Who will never f****** lie
Questioning
The military brass
General
He's been talking about
Mr. gyro is talking about
Mario run
Fortunate
Get up
Marijuana recent episode and we went over how he's admitting to shut up about Obama giving soldiers
Iran US citizen
How is clams
To get female children out of China which
He's most likely making up entirely
Jim Garrow
On the show his fake leak from his high-level source is gone viral
Has become a huge talking point the right-wing militia Patriots
More days until Obama second-term it's being seen
Baby dum dum
As the best shot they have of getting Obama in
And
Bring a present
I guess
Which is their big goal
I don't think we learn too much
Tennis episode that we didn't know before but I find it slightly interested
Vaquero secret sources General
. despite the fact that literally none of the details agueroooo is given him buddy source
Match Boykin
Bicycle brain is fairly convinced that Alex knows aguero's just making this up it's kind of freedom
Makes it up to
Girls going to call Alex's Bluff by revealing his not exist
System source
So Alex has the green light to pretend he's solved the mystery
Make himself look super clever
A little about how Alex
Qanon early on when it started
He's really just messing with the whole thing but he also said he was behind
It's a smart Gamble
What someone else is running a con they can't really do anything about it if you decide to piggyback their con
Without risk
Blowing up their entire
That's just one element that this kind of thing their minds
We have a guy coming on the show and giving out Crypt
Verifiable information that it comes from a high-level military Source who is just
Get the word out and people about the evils of the left
There's less and it's a little easier to collab
Jim Garrow
Or when tons of pain
Patriotic ex-military officers don't start coming forward to back up his b*******
But the framework there is very similar
But
It's very it's very strange
I'm a hundred percent convinced
Both of them know that they're both full of s***
Just thought that I had
But I definitely think more about but there is
There's kernels of like
Similarity
In the skeleton
Yeah
I think you're probably a lot of eggs
Is Greer
It's kind of interesting to think about like
When Steve pieczenik would come on
In the lead-up to Alex decided you love Trump
Until about the counter counter coup against the Clinton
Yeah very similar
Lucas where's Steve
It might as well be you
Right only differences
Steve pieczenik as opposed to an anonymous message
Convey
So
There's something really interests
I need to think about it a lot more
But I'm a hundred percent
Hundred percent sure
That they both know that there are no steak
Call the other one out this like I'm f****** around around 2 cuz then Alex
I know it's General Boykin
I'm smart I figured this out
And then
Alex
To take control of the naira
Because now he has a narrative
About
General
Which is no longer
Jim Keras narrative
Jim Goetz
Keep playing his game over here
Alex has created an Oscar
Shoe business
For himself over here
And that's what he tried to do with qanon to with Zack
These days
It's it's the story of long-form improv and how Upright Citizens Brigade
Here
Know what it is
Anyway
Jim Garrow here
Before we do
Alex has a bit of breaking
News
Vex
Is disturbing January 30th 2013
What's happening in the
Okay that sounds good
10 +
Pretty messed up
You can't do that
I don't I don't know what you can and can't do I don't really know where the line of legality
In terms of making
Claims but that seems pretty close to it
Auto killing cancer cells with a homeopathic
Galaxy
Cuz you just reading a press release about one of the sponsors asserting that their product has a health benefits
The FDA hasn't evaluated
It hasn't been proven
How to cure your cancer
He's just reading a press release that heavily implies it
And that might be legal
I'm not sure
Yeah
Whataburger
Even if
Screw if a doctor prescribed
Tangy Tangerine Beyond Tangy Tangerine I would suck
Punch him
Is it Beyond
Tiny describing the Tangerine or is it Beyond a Tangy Tangerine
A good question
What's modifying what how far away is
Aransas Pass
Illegally is uncertain
Is a deeply
Deeply on app
To be doing and he rather
Reasons why
First youngevity is one of Alex's primary sponsor
Financial interest in over selling a product
Has been done this product
He's the last person who should be covering that story
Send a text
Two-story away from the context of beings
Mysterious
Analysis
Atlantic directly in paid advertisement
If you were youngevity
And you're serious about this study
You would never want Alex reporting on
You do not want him being the person to convey this message
Second
I think they don't care youngevity that is
Cuz I don't think they're serious about the study
The press release that Alex's reading is from ATL International
Which might sound like a scientific
Research group
Actually just youngevity parent
Thought
In June 2013 they just decided to change their name to youngevity International
National that's that's most of what they're busy
This is youngevity putting out a press release hyping her own products and having their pitchman Alex
Yeah
Next
Presenting
Clemson University
If legit
Really do that research
Search technically
It came out of the Clemson University in
Attitude of nutraceutical research
The kind of open
Open question
Even knows what it means
It's a little vague
Nutraceutical
Research
Covid-19 results on the first page of a Google Search for The Institute of nutraceutical research at Clemson University
You find a Facebook page for The Institute has no followers and no post
One amateur slideshow presentation about the Institute
7 links to stories about the youngevity story
Probability that
Straight up
It's it it's a red flag the fact that all of this is
It all seems to lead back to this
The Institute of Medical Research does definitely
As you can
The third page
Results
But the difference between the other ones
A review
It's slightly different
In 2016 Michelle Van Etten
Was announced to be a speaker at the Republican National
Conventions
This led to some people in the media taking notice and ask
If you question
One of which was about this study that youngevity
He's made a big part of their bark
Come out with her neck
So The Daily Beast reached out to Clemson spokesperson Robin
To get some sense of what was up with this year's what they had
3 eggs
Cheaper than dirt
Nutraceutical research
Preliminary laboratory research
For youngevity several years ago
No clinical trials
Performed the Clemson has endured endorsed any youngevity products nor authorized
Or data in conjunction with any claims
Efficacy
The insta
No longer
This is a real problem
Because the website
Infowars
Team Alex's multi-level marketing operation
They just reposted Al International press release in full and it literally says that they did quote
Research studies
Which they did.
This is a misrepresentation on its face
And it's probably illegal for that one feels pretty close to
In the post on Infowars TV claims
Study showed that Beyond Tangy Tangerine quote
Killed 60% of cancerous colon cells 65% of cancers liver and stomach cells
And 30% of cancerous breast
While their other product ultimate
Quote killed 95% of 5% of cancers
65% of cancerous
It's 30% of cancerous breast
And they didn't know trial
Weather clinical trials
Cuz that brings into
Which is very questionable
Cancer cells
One of those shooting targets
And they realize that they put holes
Yeah
And specifically didn't do any tests on human
Did that for a reason
Studies have been done on cells in test tubes at find that everything
Strawberries grapes Rosemary
This is true in test tubes
But has literally no application towards whether they have any
Similar effect
When taken by a person
One block I found describe the study if they put it this way
Bleach kills cancer cells in a
Beach
This is the sleight-of-hand of a study light
The Institute of nutraceutical research
There's knew before they started
What the outcome was likely to be
Get similar results with
Clinical trial
Which really makes the smell like research
For hire somebody Hallmarks
You paid for this study in order to get the thing you needed
Yeah this is climate
Paid for by
What are any number of b*******
Feels right
Did the Koch brothers pay for the study to
Dr. Wallach is not
Whatever the
Weather
She was paid to deliver a meaningless study for youngevity
Free to lie about it.
Matter to me
What Alex is doing on air regarding this study is
Deeply enough
He's selling false hope to his listener
As opposed to other
Lake Winnie
Some pills to give them virility
Free just a placebo effect
Casella dump
But with Beyond
It might kill your cancer cells
Level There's an actual underlying
Condition here
Superbad
If this isn't illegal
Man I think it should be
He's probably
And I know that the source of it is a l International and youngevity I'm keenly aware of that
But Alex is disseminating the best
And I think that that
I told the wrong side of the law
10 billion dollar
There's no way we would
So
That isn't that is messed up
I'm not
Duffy's happy
A piece of Alex's advertise
He has Jim Carroll they're talking about this
Does litmus test for soldiers
There's no real new information
The girl has to say is that
The guy
He spoke to
Talk to him again and the guy said thank you
Preston Ford
I think about that girls like
I admire him. Getting
Deeper into it
There's there's a part with these Khan's people
Seem to really
Really like overcomplicating
It isn't real impulse
Gilding the lily
I do not want to add layers
Any further action will just lead people to realize
I'm claiming to run a child traffic
I don't want I don't want the law enforcement
Volver
Apparently I accidentally claimed I was committing a
A very large International big clarification it wasn't
He brags about it
Yeah because he's not actually do
Subway
Maybe just didn't realize that what he was
Scribing was a
No one knows but you don't know what I'm doing like in the orphanages because
F****** illegal
He's very aware that what he claims to be doing
Deeply illegal
Only illegal in China
Sure
A special shout-out to Larry neck
Never going to get over that ever
They're having this interview and there's nothing really new common from it there's nothing that interesting
The end of the
Talk forever very long conversation
No really really kind of Alex
A buildup
Any kind of
More information training pull door
Threads out of him
Like trying to get
Trying to get Garrett
But he doesn't
Episode they start taking calls Alex wants to
To talk to military and police
Get the call from a Marine
And Alex asked
But he's been told to shoot on civilian
Oh
Yeah he was information
And this is
Not
I got a
Recent survey dropped in my email I haven't opened it yet but a couple my phone ringtone
They said there's some sketchy stuff in there about
I haven't opened it yet but
Eminem
Go home and open it
Mailman
Alright City High
Hey if it wasn't even if it wasn't even man
Email that you are optionally as to fill out
Going on there
Hugh doesn't want to disappoint
Yeah yeah yeah
And he doesn't want to be the person know
Is no butt
Then I heard it might have something to help you out
I really want there's there's a codependency
They don't realize it
Abusive
He's you gaslighting writ large
The 30th
Dogshit episode
Real boring
That really
Got me
Got me going
Here on the 31st
Finishing up
January
January fireworks
But they're not that great though the kind of fireworks are parents will allow you to
Sparklers
Maybe a Roman Candle
But it's at we start here with Alex
Talking to Paul Jones
Watson
And he's bringing up those
Tax
The color called a couple days ago and told him he found
And he was afraid for his life
Yeah it's a sin to Alex call Joseph
Over these
He's deemed them to be
Credible
Now
If you listen to this clip
Alex has fully whitewashed
Where he got
The emails
So it's no longer a caller told me about these things that you found on 4chan
Pjw put out a report by the world the World by storm
Information
If you had listened to the episode when that caller called in
You wouldn't know that's where Alex got this
Information
You might assume that it's
Some sort of intelligence stores
You might assume the Paul Joseph Watson is a great
Investigative reporter
You're wrong
You're wrong about all this
Food
Some dumb dumb who's hanging out on 410 told Alex about it now
Here we are
So it is in this next clip we hear Alex
Expressing something
Is very interesting
Given the present day
Kind of aware that
The document document
And in that leak or that hack
That talked about Volkswagen.
He seems to know that's fake
But where he goes from that
Wild
Responded
Thousands of documents
Passport
Where they're discussing a stage
Which is better
Qatar
Sounds like something the Russians would do Alex
Interesting
About president
Tune on the things that Russia might do
For political purposes
Sophisticated
Through certain channels
In 2013
I can't I can't think of any real-world parallel to that
That's interesting
Interest
About the the
There's not
Not a lot.
Other than Alex
Being aware
There are people who are saying the document was fake and it is
But if it's not
Still operating as if it is even though you saying
Sue The Daily Mail
Proposing
As we as we discussed
Alex gets to complaining about
Regulation
It's impossible to do business
Anymore
Probably one of the worst
Examples he could
You can operate
This isn't 2013.the two years later today
Don't have his gold and silver license
Revoked by the state of Minnesota
That a little bit later
But it's just funny to have that be like
Leica gold operation
Regular
So
Firework
February said there was fireworks
Sparklers one of our favorite thing
The show
Whatever
Someone who made an album in an album
Raptors
Personal favorite
Beyond esoteric Alex
Is fake story
Oh yeah I love a fake story
Coming up here in a little bit
First part about a park ranger
Big Bend National Park
Okay
Sapulpa
Does the Hulk work as a park ranger
It's closer to Hulk then Hulk Hogan brother
Say hello to you.
Do you take your vitamins
Sempre
Probably
So in this neck
Clip
Little fake story
Bright LOL
Alex Jones we all get
What were these other people think
I don't think they're real first of all
Raise a lot of question
Park ranger
Big Ben
Here is
Is the story about the next one
This story did
Not happen
Is there
Gorgeous
It sounds like you were drinking
Oh yeah
Universal
Your old guys out there
Girlfriends
Not permitted here
My dad Mother's Day
At the hot springs
Zithromax
The ranger trash recycler
Hundred
Nope I don't believe that story at all I believe that probably Alex was drinking in a hot tub
Hot spring Adventure cop
Yep
National Park is an amazing natural wonder
Unlike enter very romantic
Rob doing his dad to go to
It's unlike anything else in the country and I can totally understand why Alex loves it so much it makes it a vacation desk
There really is so much to appreciate their
Historical value of the Land Park once served as a home
Four members of the Comanche
And Mescalero scribe
And artifacts of that time could still be found around the park
The park is home to a bunch of really cool animals like roadrunners in Jackrabbit
As well as all manner of cactus
Wildflower
All protected by the status
Enjoyed
Is a national park
They're gorgeous rock formation
Kansas waterfalls
Canyon
Picturesque
Used enjoy sunset
It's a one-of-a-kind
Three complete ecosystems in the form of a river mountain
Desert
Each separate from one another
All-in-one National Park I sent the hammer drop
Thanks to the federal government that land has remained relatively protect
For hundreds of thousands of people year to visit
I think that maybe the trumpet
Ministration
Here's the thing
Big Bend in the Rio Grande River
Park is situated right at said Ben
You may be aware that the Rio Grande is the technical marker the boundary
Between the United States Amex
So on one side of the river it's the United States
Not
Because of the natural beauty and importance of the area to the ecosystem the land
Second side of the border is also National Park
Vanessa
Xperia a bit complicated from a political
Perspective
My feeling is that the only real way to crack down on immigration there would be
Militarize the National Park
Which requires development of what are we even really doing
Show me bring all this up because
Love's Big Bend National Park
He talks about it all the time
He has tons of stories of being in those hot spring
How much he enjoys going hiking in
That's why it should break his heart didn't 27
What Trump was trying to get his border wall
Big Bad Wolf
As many as the place you could
Easily build
The reasoning was that it was a stretch of land along the border that's already owned by the federal
So building a wall there wouldn't require using eminent domain
Which would inevitably lead
Two drawn-out court cases
In order to get any of this wall built
Pacifica cheap victory
To put up the platter
Hunza people
Words
It definitely wouldn't be a pyrrhic victory for the entire United States
F****** beautiful
Existence
The proposed border wall would by definition have to run through Big Bend
National Park delicate ecosystems
Protective
One example of this is the Mexican black bear whose population have been blind doing in the 90
50s. Because of the protected land of the park was able to fight off Extinction and repopulate
A border wall would completely disrupt the Bears migratory pattern
It could lead to them facing
And that's just one of hundreds
Hundreds of species that would be Rock
Disruption
Which
Building middle of wood apps
Marco's preparedness overtired Rangers that quote
Many many people who put their pool
Careers
I working out here
Preserving and protecting me
Azaria in one Fell Swoop we do all of that with the
Does border wall
It's hard to tell how much would it cost to build a wall or just meant to rile up native is paranoia
And up
Xenophobia
To keep Trump space engage
But let's leave that aside
Alex Jones
F****** loves Big Bend National Park
And yet he supports Trump building a wall
Something that would probably destroy the very hot springs
He loves to bathe him
He's a stupid racist
Monster who's willing to destroy something
Buggy bug
To satisfy his desire to
Immigrants and refugees
Or that desire has blinded
Dim to the fact the following
What destroys
Are you lost
I think it's a pretty good microcosm of Alex Jones's Life as a whole
He used to love his radio show but is blind hatred of the government
His Litem to slander murder victims
I am lawsuit about that
Become the proverbial
Disrupted the
The show
From an external perspective is very little in his public life it doesn't appear to have been
We we just destroyed as a result of him pursuing its
Petty hatred
Far past the point where
Any sane person would say
Destructive consequences,
So to put this morning
Succinctly
Alex Jones dachshund is a total idiot
And conversely National Park Rule and we need to do everything we can to protect
Yes
It was a little bit more poetic
Also small Point illegal border crossings in the Big Bend area are absolutely not
Concern for what
They're talking about building a wall
But in between
100 book
On either side
A2000
3 study by Department of Justice
Explicitly says that the
About people who cross the border in Brewster county
The county where Big Bend Park is low
Crossing through Big Bend National Park Austin die from lack of water
Or exposure to the elements
According to the County Sheriff's Office their bodies are not found until the remains of skeleton
In terms of any crime of its
Described in that report about the immigration patterns
What are the main things
Brewster county
Is Poke real burglary
That's a crime that they have to be concerned about there
A county official had this to say about that
People break into my house
Get something to eat when I'm not home wash the dishes and leave them by the sink with a few pesos
Better than when you found it
Break again
Food leaving the couple
By the way that's not in the 19
That was a 2003
That that report
Amanda another official had this to say in the report the she said
Stocked with food
And quote if people come needing food I filled my foreman to give it
There is a
Real strong sense that the people in this County
Don't see immigration
I'm coming through as a victim
There isn't a ton of it a lot of people who come through end up dying because of a desert
Cross through
And they are more interested in helping
People not die
Then they are with whatever Alex's
Concerns are criminalizing
Helping people
What how many you people have been arrested
Charged with
Only 1%
Enforcement budget
Brewster county
How do I to do with undocumented
So you're saying that they aren't using Brewster's Millions
The county had to pay four times as much for autopsies and burials of
Bodies of undocumented immigrants
They found in the
The county
So I think is loaded
Metallica spit
Also this is going to drift into a bit of trivia
County to Brewster county
Jeff Davis County
Confederacy
That's wonderful yeah parently guess what that's one of four counties
The country they're named after Jefferson Davis
All of them
In Georgia Tech
This Mississippi
And Jefferson Davis
Parish in Louisiana
Realize that was f***** up
Back in 18th
23 counties in Texas or proxy
10% of the County's
In the entire State Brewster county
Percy Brewster who was a colonel in the Confederate Army
It's not so easy to find counties named after abolitionist
Georgia likes
The claim that Douglas County was named after
Frederick Douglass
That's technically true
What it was named after him in eight
County with
Confederate Democrats
Power in the government change the name of the county
It's still called Douglas
But now it's spelled with one less f
In honor of Stephen Douglas
Illinois politician who ran against
Lincoln for president
And supported slavery is being protected by state
Right
Douglas literally believe that the Declaration of Independence only applied to White
People saying this government was made by our fathers on the
Made by white men for the benefit of white men and their posterity forever
So that's that
Just a little bit of
Pull back the curtain
Oh
Cool
That's not cool changing the name from
Frederick just removing an ass and then being like
Guess what
Instead of Frederick Douglass
Let's call it Strom Thurmond County for Christ
So we know
Accept
So anyway I started out with Alex telling a fake story about going to Big Bend
Run-in with imaginary police
And then we realized
Sports politician
That Park destroyed
If sex with Alex pretends
To cry about
This time it's Big Ben
Cuz the park later
Anymore
Okay
You forget you forget depaul's been on hold this whole time
Search up with Syria talking about those fake documents
Asad burning and murdering thousands upon thousands of his
I knew we were food let's get out of here
What year
Scribing
When you talkin about being food
Is
Getting a ticket
For drinking somewhere that drinking isn't allowed
Yeah that's an open container violation
That you're on Federal
That's Federal property it's the park
If they say there's no drinking
That's the rules
We could do you drink at the courthouse
Just a hangout
Do the 40
At the courthouse
It's not going to fly
No I did meet a guy who did some coconut court house one time
And that's
Is he ate well and that's during his trial for cocaine
But I bet it wasn't like
Make a show of it
Yeah
Implies something worse than
Or maybe a
Small citation
I mean if you were drinking a Coors
The hot spring
I'm sure someone will come over like a pour that out
The first time that a park ranger
And throw it away
Don't litter
More less
So or he also would have done
I've no sympathy for Alex
Overhyping
So does victimhood agree
Mentality
As it relates to
Then I would love to be in right now
I don't feel like a gift shops
Why would you want to be outdoors
I don't know what it is about parks that gets
No I know I get it I'm looking at me like I'm
I don't know I don't know
I do like going to a national park
Little Wok
Alright whatever
So it is next Quest
Larry Pratt
From God orders
Who is
If it's next clip though
It's clear that bragging about his appearance
But also Larry Pratt has been on
They got you a little bit of a fight
But apparently has been boosting
The membership rolls
Applications
For gun owners
America
Clip Larry Pratt
Piers Morgan
In a Morgan blessings pretty card
Did a little bit it is very here too
Increase our membership and we're very grateful
Piers Morgan
I think I'm
Grateful enough to form a fan club
He helped our membership and the NRA's membership
We may look back and say
What he started
During your truly about how the United States Auto operate
Supercilious
British accent of his
That just kind of
Kills most Americans right up to the gag
Highlights of very important things people need to realize
Correctly use the word supercilious
And confuse Alex
Conform
The thing that's important is that
These people
I'm going to go ahead and call Larry Pratt fashion
For a specific reason
I will get you in a moment
When you have people like this
Who have nefarious in
If you allow them access to your plants
If you don't
Be very careful with it
You help
Is expressing
We use Piers Morgan is it useful idiot
He didn't understand the game we were playing we played the game
You know there's a fight
We won
Is what happened
Where you don't push back
Is because
He was at the Rocky Mountain rendezvous
Advocate
All those folks back in
Larry OG
So
For whatever
Legitimate second
Defense
Arguments
Behind that that is far darker
Even if
Even if he doesn't
Express outright whites
Supremacy India
Very very very
Elbows
Recurring theme in America
Is that
The left
Piers Morgan
Gun movie
People do boat
More infuriating
But what's a common recurring theme is that
They're playing a different game and nobody
You think
You're playing one game
Playing that game
We were even really all that aware of that no
Spending this much time
Looking at deconstructing
The Alex
And his associates
Folks
I really I don't I don't think we would be aware of that
If it wasn't for deep
Immersion
And that's a lot of people
It's it's so much easier with social media
Easier
Capitalizing
Quick attention
Expand
Social media
Well that's just even more obvious
In the context of
McConnell
Supreme Court
That people calling him hip-hop hypocritical
He's always been
Is this is
Consistent fact he was full of s***
He's full of s***
He's playing better than
Autocracy
See play into his other team
It's a charge that won't get you where you need
To go
Because anybody
Vet
McConnell isn't bored
Isn't going to be convinced
Spy accusation
Apocracy
Because they see the autocracy
Lesbian
Affect
And people who were playing that other game understand what accusation
AR
Define impotent to hurt.
Not even just not impotent but almost a rallying cry as well
You criticize or you can wink
Hypocrite
Everybody was like hahaha of course you would
Because everybody knew of course he would
If somebody said to me
When McConnell was
Pulling that b******* with garlic
That
It was just like
Well you know what at least he'll be ideologic
Consistent and if I eat Supreme Court
She opens up and
Election year
I'm sure he'll do the same thing
I would have wanted to punch them
So heartbeat
Obviously
So
We get to finally something about Saint
How do you hook your on January 30th
Much talk about it further reinforces
My sorta feeling Metallica
Call are called
Alex
I really care about you
Emotional level doesn't really care
About Sandy Hook
He's interested in
The opportunism of the conspiracy theory Community that's growing around it but it doesn't really
Really care that much
So he doesn't talk about it
A lot
But he has this
Bit of news
But he's coming to
Wholesale
My response that is okay
Let's get those choirs
Yeah I don't deserve
Was that
I don't know it's very
It's strange
Just a way of trying to
Whataboutism
Yeah one from all-time and other countries and everywhere around the world
If you do one example
Real
Consequences
Does bulshit but everybody do the cloward-piven approach to publicize
Victims of gun violence
And I think Alex would have a new complaint
Did you get that witches like
It's somehow still not to address
The central issue
Interesting about this is that
Conspiracy
I don't know what Alex
Fight 1
Tracy was putting
Was that some of the children who have died
In the shooting were actually sing
At the Super Bowl
That becomes
Large
Conspiracies Alex
Mad about
Choir singing at the Super Bowl
His
Because that doesn't
Seem to be present what are you saying here
But we're still a little ways off
From the actual
Describing your level of
Stupidity to your end
Just sew on
Houses
Morphs
Like does Alex pick up on any of them
It's kind of tough
To find an angle on it other than what he's already said
Get those kids from
Schools in Mexico
Cuz I think mostly will be like you bet
Really terrible arrangement of Ave Maria
I think that's how he's going to
I mean if he wants to go for that then Larry Nichols album
Super Bowl
That's right next to your quickie survives will get him
I think it's also super weird that Larry Nichols hasn't
I'm showing up at all in this 2012
That's true hasn't shown up at all
I really expected
Show up
Psyop
A lot more in the last 3 or 4 days that I've been listening to
So you put around the corner
But it is a word
Associated
No it's really weird you'd expect a lot more of these like regular people
Back to business
A whole month in the week
I'm about to have almost that I've listened to
12 2013
Anza
Nothing
Not really
Just gun dudes
Just Larry Pratt
Stewart Roads from The Oath Keepers
Bulshit made-up bulshit
But we are
Tear that's very familiar to us
Alex is Scream
But Financial
And then
Most predictable thing ever
Okay
I wasn't drinking
You're drinking right that's what you're doing here
Yeah
Now you can just not said that
Cuz I was a bad news
Bob Chapman died in
2012 so he's already
The shortcut
Does Nepal Chapman
Straight shooter
I haven't really come up in this 2012.
I thought that it
It's only interesting
He showed up
A lot
So now for years later
I think it's also probably partially because
You taking on like
Thibiant
Doesn't have
As much
Central importance
Yeah
Anymore
ATL to Cortez crankbaits
Weird device
Right
You know
Know what to do
And tell so
And he's all out of
That's very old
Other gold companies
Running ads on Glenn Beck
And Rush Limbaugh
Negative
He's having Alex to it
That's for sure.
What
Lights on
Free
Butler
Differentiating
And and
Need to know two years later earlier
We talked about it on the show before but it's worth
Indicates out
Michonne is one of his biggest sponsors through Midas resources he's no longer legally allowed to sell precious metals
About to come out with the state of Minnesota and they revoked
Because he quote misappropriated customers money and misrepresented terms of sale to them
Resources quote route
Without prior agreement
To deliver with customers
And otherwise misrepresented to cost
Tomorrow's the terms of sale
He was kicked out the precious metals business and had to pay
Payback hundreds of thousands of dollars to customers
Andres tattoo
Ted Anderson is running
Shady as s*** gold company
Hard to swallow
Complain about some other gold company running ads on trust
Or Glenn Beck show with markups that offended
Grateful
He is doing this I don't know why you doing
It's just
Shading the competition you know
It's one of these things like if you're working with this like
Tammy f****** gold operation
Don't call other gold operations
Amy
That's going to draw attention to house
Amy you are
A dino that apparently in practice it doesn't work that way
The exact opposite of the way the world works if you're running a scam accuse everyone
That's weird literally to get elected president
It's so weird that the world works that way
It just seemed like that
Hillary
You're interested it is a gold
What is really about is
Condemn these other companies
For being shady
As a way of making
Sure that people
Trust Ted
Making them look bad is in service of building up Ted's credibility
As you can hear it
This resources
Resources
Tell me he's even saying it like this is a business
It's full of f****** shady
People but
5% markup
He just wants to get you the best deal
That's f****** used car salesman ship but for gold
Just see within a couple days spam
This kind of
Shilling for persons gold
The youngevity
Can cure cancer study
You just got like
Roast
Rose business model here
Even give a s***
So we have one more clip here
And
In terms of this clip it's wise to remember
That
After Alex had
James Trace
The guy who
After he had him on the show
There was a video that got 10 million views on YouTube about those
He started
To change the way
Covered thing
Particularly school shooting
We saw the Lone Star College shooting
Where he was
Was covering things up
Find a false-flag angle on it
Many realize that the school was pretty much decided it was
Right
Now on the 31st
Right at the end
The show there's another
Here is how I would
Middle School
14 year old
Drudgereport.com
Silver dollars for $70
Fat
Disgraceful
Many many levels
F******
Disgrace
That's pretty bad
So the story that I was covering hears about a shooting that took place at Price Middle School in Atlanta Georgia
A fifteen-year-old student
Was shot by a fourteen-year-old
A resource officer at the school was able to get the shooter to drop his weapon
He was taking it
That Alex was so quick to decide that this was a gang related
Well I'm sure it has nothing
To do with it Lana being black maca
So I could Price Middle School as a student population that's a 95
Percent black probably a coincidence
In February police would come out and say that they are investigating a gang and go to the shooting
Information wasn't
Mr. shooting is not even really being worth covering
I can find zero confirmation or details about the conclusion that it will
But even if the police are a hundred percent
Correct
Suggested that this could be
The result of two gangs fighting
Doesn't change
I don't particularly trust the flip it definition of the word gang when it's applied to the two black eats by police
Particularly when it's
Shoreline
The details are absent
And from the reporting of this story even in the articles that I can
The victim's mother was
Publicly very clear that our son wasn't involved
Banana gang
And don't want to Legend gang
Involvement at provided any concrete information
Plus and most importantly
Even if this was a gang-related shooting
It doesn't make Alex
He had zero reason to assume it was a gang shooting other than
He saw fit all the students
That's cool we're black
This
The only piece of information he's operating off of
Exactly definition
Cooperating
Entirely off of racial prejudice
Also parents couldn't pick up their kids
From the school
Because they've been evacuated to a nearby Church
Where they were before they got the whole situation sorted out
There's nothing
Nothing suspicious
Just about that at all
So we can have ears
Really care
About this
This would be suspicious
In a vacuum
Cliff would be suspicious
A b self
No other contact
You like
Dismiss that story
And then sell
TARDIS
Texting is Bond
It is
Desire to
Dismiss this story is gang related
Did shooting
But when you take it in the context
The larger world
The end of January 2013 Alex
Where
What's 2
Hook Market
He wants to find his own
The General
Narrative offshoot wants to make
So he's
Teresa
Through
Using his pan
Sadtu sister all of the school shooting
And whenever something
This is the school shooting I don't want so
Other than
Breaking news school shooting
Oh nevermind
Atlanta
Oh I'm positive what happened
Is the he got it from the producers
Big shot over an article to him
Yep in the photo
Context of this
Sandy Hook
Kids to do
B diss lives in
And the lone star shooting coverage
Is the more specific
When he was covering that
So excited that it was possibly a fall swag
Did he was going to get the information on
And when he started to realize
This isn't
And it's all black people
He's like immediately Oz's gang-related yep
In both of these instances
It what's the similarity
Predominantly black schools
That's how his brain work
This isn't worth
Attention is not worth feeling anything about
F*** it it's games
If somebody in a gang get shot
It's a gang shooting so
Hey he definitely does
Literally
Be right there
So
I don't know I mean
Seizure of this episode
Not a ton
Development
Truck stop
But a lot
Abrasive
Yep there is a lot of bigotry on here that is
It's the sort of bigotry that Alex
Private
Because it's
Isn't saying
I don't know
Or anything like that
But it's just as
Bad it's something profile
Oh that's that's one version of it absolutely
It's Justice
Is potent is bigger
Covert
Because it has that plausible deniability
So I don't like to see
See that
It's so interesting
Consistent
You know
The phobia is not
Yeah
That's very weird.
I think that's the regular progression
A lot of
These people that
At age they just get add more and more to the list of things they hate
Especially if they're bigots already or shirt or something
Things that most people
Like this
Wouldn't just by default
You do
Pennywise
Will be back
On Monday
I don't know I don't know who I was
Just made this episode
Rapist
There's nothing in it in terms of like what we're looking
Big giant
There's nothing looking for it
So much
Sounds like
Fraud
It's it's
Free
It's a bit of a holding pattern that he's in
In terms of
Conspiracy infinitives
But it's just
Full steam ahead
Demonize Obama demonize the last
Call Fran
Guns are under threat
For the
Chris's and then he'll really have a twin
Worries at the pounds is the boss
Boston bombing
You think so I'm worried about
I don't know if
Is it yeah
I'm worried that that's the why he responded so
Strongly to it
Immediate
Volkswagen everything on air
It's possible that this is all priming the
The pump for that
Something happen
Before then
Well there's a while
That's true there's
What I mean
In 2013
I bet I bet there's at least
Before the
Before April
I'm sure there is maybe not
We will find out what happened in the past
Spoiler alert
I believe website
You are on
Twitter
Underscore
We are on Facebook
You can download r-pod
Every website has a download button
Right every single one even
You can just go right by 4 if you're in a rural area a truck right up there and down
Download the show
I completely zoned out
I don't know why but I was like
My brain is like I am not accepting though
I will not accept the charges
For this collection
Call downloaded the podcast
I've already used
We can't
The park is done
Ron Paul's friend
Whose name I can't remember
Alexandra Thurston color