Alexandra Thurston color
Little bit
About Alex J
Who's your favorite
Potatoes do you put over where you at
Quest
Quite frankly there's a lot of prep potatoes presentation
I would say that I'm partial to mashed potatoes because
It's kind of a cumbersome
Process to make them
And so when they show up it's usually special
I would say
Top
Are up there
I always forget about
If you have to choose the best fry talk probably doesn't count so they waffle waffle fries probably tomorrow
Very underrated
With thanks
It's in there it's in the conversation
Ways to eat potatoes
Simplify
Lava Crunch
The most riveting conversation I am a little hungry
Thankfully our out-of-context drop which will here in a little bit has something to do with food
Potatoes
About the fight
We are in the present will be going over May 30th
31st
Is Thursday and Friday
Of the week that was
I really appreciate it
So Steven thank you so much
Strawberry
Text Sophia
Thank you
Jason thank you so much
Journal pollywog
I'm a policy wonk
Donations and pump it up a little bit
So first of all Kim thank you so much you are now
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
You are now watching
Heroin
Freakishly large
Absolutely
Interested in
Finding out that Alex is very predictable
Press conference
She does come up
Can't be real. In the context of the mother stuff but he has a
We'll discuss that today as it comes up
Seems like I got to
Spend a lot of time covering live stream the right-wing media
Alex's take on the
And a very small part of what makes
These two days about
What's the show
Super f***** up
They reach
Levels of astonishment
Haven't had in awhile in quite a while
Really
Really took me aback
Where are we
It's like out of left field Somali pirate territory or we out of a wound
With racism
More the latter than the price
Catch me as you got to give it up for this Miley Cyrus rarefied class
Alex Jones,
But before we get into any of the
I was around
Or somebody bought donuts and I just inhaled two of them
I love them so much
I love it so much
Little moments ever
Appreciate
So soft and deliver
God dammit
I'm so in this first clip we start on the 30th
And Alex
Has some information
And it's the explanation of why the globalist
Want to get him off
The air right which is
He's explained to us I don't know about billion f****** time
Little bit different
Explain
It was true
But this is the reason the globalist want to get him off the air
That may be a good thing
Establishment wants me author
And that list includes a long string of retired respected generals and other
Military
Because their people Robinson was singing on my phone calls in Fresno
Recalled affect me
Thursday
That was just a pat on the head sir
They're coming after you
You got people
I said you got people lying to you that are bringing these folks in
Here's this particular lady that they brought in
I can explain that
Off the air or whatever because
He was telling the president
Stuff like this
He's misleading the
And that would be fine
If the president wasn't a sundowning moron
That is an issue
Yeah yeah
How do you think I knew that
I realize well
See if I can figure out first of all what the f*** is talking
Somebody about context clues
Write about a woman
I was brought into trumps
Somehow
Reduces the
But he's actually Soros operative
What is it
Doobie quote over the Stanford
If it means being cheapest
Conspiracy Alex's warning Trump with autism
Because guess what
Under its original name
To the president
No woman has ever filled that role
So obviously the
Metallica
Weird because that's who does a lot of
The Oval Office
Mick Mulvaney
That's a fairly recent
People who were around under the Rings
John Kelly
The number to pin down who Alex's talk
Obama had no female Chief of Staff however there were
Deputy chief
So maybe this is
Obama Hillary a holdover
But unfortunately none of them stuck around it all alleged Trump
Administration
I wonder what the two are still around in 2017 both last on a dog
I wonder why
Kate Walsh was a deputy chief of staff working on schedule
For the trumpet
Menstration
She was on board from the jump and she was part of the transition
But you left ministration early in March 27th
Pro Trump dark money Super PAC
America First policy
Which was founded by Brad Parr scholly
Trump head of digital operations
Is the 2016
A lot of trump Administration folk found their way to America First Paula
So did
Some Nazis
I don't understand why are those two separate
Words in your car the two separate statements
I believe they are redundant and sound
Is there director of advocacy
After a bunch of old radio shows
Super islamophobic
Super anti algae
Navigator for being able to shoot
Kill anyone who came across the border on.
Whoa whoa whoa guys why are you getting rid of me I
I don't want the last one anymore this is called America first
Policies what have I done wrong
Everything's that guy is
I was probably the one
Surrounded America
The first policy
He's out there
The guy who was there
Juan Pablo Andrade
Previously been on Trump's National Hispanic advisory Council as well as
Before heading to the Super PAC America
The first policy
Newsmax
Put them on their 30 under 30 list
Justin 27
He was a real rising star in the dumb dumb
Unfortunately that you're his star exploded
What do you recorded himself in a hotel room at a turning point USA conference
Hotel room I should point out that
He wasn't just an attempt
He was there
Invitation
Right in the video he says quote the only thing the Nazis
He's didn't get right is that they didn't keep
Keep f****** going
I'm sure
Just joking but you look more into the circle
Natalie wasn't
Yeah I know I think at a certain point you guys we all got it
Just admit that
A few bad apples
Amounts
To actually they're creating
He's on purpose
That's what they want
Caught we all know that the whole thing is not
Weird
To be literally dripping with bigots and is run by Trump's the head of
Communications
Digital communication
Yeah unless she's a real
Guess what
She is who I was talking about
In the early days of the Trump campaign paranoia was it if
Fever pitch on all sides
Books on the West in the middle were rightfully very worried about what was coming
But the right was really worried
Slightly different issue
Particularly the more authoritarian
Does that was crushed within the Trump Administration
He wouldn't be able to enact the white supremacy
Supposition face supported
There's a real sense that the real progress towards an awful end
But the biggest thing that stood in the way with the people who were inside
Mike cernovich Jack pestova cats
Throughout the people who could possibly slow down the March towards their dystopia
Targeting unnamed
Collaborators and wolves and she
Sheep's clothing
Within the administration
You remember this from Alex Jones is show back then
There was so much talk about internal pallet entry
Every
Single f****** show was about
You know the things that I love the most about
How little reminds me of Stalin
Yeah that's my favorite part
Very very unsimilar
Correlate
The goal was
Threefold
Rhetoric this
People who are wolves
Keeps closing within the inner machinations
How you build a pre-emptive excuse for why Trump isn't getting anything
You maintain the climate of fear you
You needed your audience that should be diminished by their guy being
You make an example of people in government
Of how anyone who deceived
Deviating from the program will be treated
The chief propagandists rationalize their attacks on government
Easiest blanket accusation to throw it anyway
It wasn't to stop leaks
The root Outlet
It's to create a Perpetual feeling of a witch
We're purchase of government employees who fail
Is that the purging of them is
Should support
Is
An actual
If they if this were in the soul
Supporters of the
Castration crowdsourcing
This
Please the motivation of the rationals
For the birds
Directly from the
Right
It's kind of a situation I think all of these guys
All of the guys
Empower but for so long the people in power on the right
Have been stoking these
Horrible horrible impulses
In order to win election
Knowing full well that what they would if they were 2X
Rather be illegal
People would start getting murdered
Yeah
And
Abusing and end
Exploiting
Finally were like
What if we just killed everybody
Or we're not going to be controlled anymore by this kind of exploited of relationship
And then they
Do this
Yeah
If not kill then at least root out or metaphor
Send to
Re-education
Kept doing
It just kept happening
In those early days
Threats of purges
Suspected
Conformist
Do the program
This over and over again the previous loyalty
To get routed out which of course eventually became
Or the Kushner Loyola
Could morph it however you want
In order to
Maintain that climate of fear
And paranoia of
Excuse
You know impotence
Yeah that first year or two I think
Banks are worth
300 separate
Profiles
The adult in the room completely person
Then you're like you got to realize there are no more
And that's kind of a lot of the other
Sommore
Older
Meteor
Data
Disservice
Yeah.
Media
That was
Yeah
Is reporting that after the most read
Kim Jeong hoon and Donald Trump didn't go so great
And carried out a purge of government officials who were in charge of
Negotiate
For it
Control counterpart to Mike Pompeo in the
Was allegedly executed along with for foreign Ministry officials who stood accused
Of spying for the United
When the North Korean state
This alleged spying boiled down to
Quit poorly grasping us intentions
Give me to go station
There were reports that these people weren't executed but some of suggested they were just sent to a hard laborer
For re-education
Which I mean I guess it's better than killing p
Be bold by Dido
Watch better seriously
Not good
Curated
In Austin have
A results
So what people like Chucky
Kind of reference crowdsourcing
Authoritarianism into the
True democracy
Sure
Classical liberalism
We all f*** ourselves
My point is that it's very hard
To radio have
Like Stark
Reminders of this
Just happen to North Korea
It's really hard to look at that sort of behavior that was going on instinct
Dudes who are doing this which Auntie Behavior about to officials
To work on board
The f****** knew what they were doing
Oh yeah it's almost inconceivable realize
Yeah well that's ridiculous
Do these right-wing douchebag
Won't go that far
Look at what happened North Korea
They're going to go as far as
Get away with
They're going to go as far as I can feel come
Westerville getting away with
I'm not saying that there's North Korea
Probably further
I think it's true
Human impulses
Yeah
Alex
Has
A real serious problem on it
And that is that
The EU
This is a problem
Because Alex constantly says that the EU Parliament is
Is unelected
However
Because
Is his buddies in the brexit party won a bunch of seats
It's on display where Alex
10 seconds
Abusive
So it is a Templar at the end
That hurt me very much physically it's a whiplash
I am having
Brexit party
That is
Baseline problem
For Alex
Here's one of the constant arguments he's made was that it's governed by an unelected
Bureaucrats in the parliament
It's a constant drumbeat on his show
Is repeated over and over again
Is a compound noun
Unelected has become an epithet
In the same way that gentle was
Super Truck
That's all good and well except when there's an
New parliamentary election being held
Which there was this girl
Alex doesn't this clip its 5 years ago people didn't know that
You Parliament is unelected
Which is interesting
Because Alexa
Comparing every size
So you specifically
Parliament
See how this is freaking consisted internally really really frustrating me
Do you Parliament to begin isn't
Initially the MEP
Peers or members of European Parliament were appointed by each
Which countries elect
Did parliament so their National Parliament
Would elect
Choose the people who workout
He's in the Europe
Still a democratic route a little closer to legit and that's
It's like saying that the Secretary of State
Technically that's true but they're appointed by a directly
Elected president
And have to be confirmed by directly elect
Did members of Congress
In terms of the EU Parliament over Alex's claims really don't make
Because the night
They started holding Alexa
For the wrong number
With only a few rules in place about proportional representation that are universally required
Member states are free to run their elections
Their parliamentary representative however they choose
Which is a great celebration of national sovereignty
Which Alex doesn't want to talk about
Is very annoying
It is very annoying this information annoys me
Are you I am vexed
Fixed by the fact
He is holding both of these
Conflicting points of view at the same time it's like him saying that
3 people voted for the Federal Reserve
Really be talking about is the position of the president of the European Commission
He was an unelected
Deposition
The various political parties
Vote
What's will be the
But that post isn't the same as like being the
Europe
The position is described as being the first among equals in the European Commission
Members of the commissioners
Selected by elected governments of member
Country's interest
In the context of a collaborative body that balances the larger needs of
These examples of unelected folks within the hierarchy
You government are easy to point to as examples of undemocratic
Government run amok
But if you look at them closely you find that each of these appointed positions
Garfield directly by people who are elected by the people
And they could be ousted from their positions by electing
If Alex wants to be philosophically consistent attack
These positions for being indirectly elected requires a problem with every appointed position in our government
Every cabinet secretary should have to be directly elected
What about Krishna foxy doing
I almost
Every
For almost every foreign country that has a prime minister becomes a problem for him the list goes on and on and on
Officials who are just unelected
I ordered directly elected
Purely Technical Center
You can play
This European commission is unelected
What Alex
He's been stupid
Is not true
For years he's been able to just be free to lie about the EU Parliament cuz he knows that none of his listeners were going to look into it
But then like three months ago Nigel farage stuck at the brexit party
It became clear that the story election was going to be
Favorable
Smash monster taking over the world narrative
Immediately he had a huge problem
How do you maintain your b******* about the EU Parliament elected while simultaneously bragging about your Euros skeptic and fascist
Parliamentary
Put your
Finger up to your head and you
Tangled webs we weave when first we
Is to deceive
Event venues
Right
Particulars
Put on a little set piece
Pretty much
That's discuss
Well I mean it's it's one in a long line I think of Alex being screwed over by getting what he wants
EU Parliament positions
Destroy the EU I guess
But in order for that
They be elected
This Parliament
One of his chief complaint
About it
Succeeding in the goal
He's working towards
Undercuts and destroys
One of his big reasons for wanting it gone
National Health Service
Like so many people who voted as it was
Gina with Boris
Is money
And they voted specifically for that type of
Danzig
Of course if brexit actually follows through with the way that it
Play with the No Deal Services going to be privatized my American Insurance
Are all doing something that is active
Whatever it is
Seems like
A real strong current among the
Quote on quote International nationalist
Like 390 the only people
Play not know it's I think I think that might be the
They
That's what you don't want to say
Did that support they don't want that stuff
So
Text clip Alex
Has a list of complaints about him
About
People that he perceives
As being against
Comerica
I want to do things that I find really interesting about this
He's Furious
How many gigs does Liz
About his
No no no no
Somebody wants a debate Ronald Reagan wants that conversation
What are you guys want is
To list off things
So
Explain each of these and why they're not true
Chinese Express in why he doesn't like the other side that he proceeded
Every single thing he says is not true
Show
That we're trying to get our country back
Commence
Cauliflower
Toledo
So
Case study it's almost
Inconceivable
Knows that he's intentionally misleading
Volume
It's important to remember for the purposes of what's to come that he is a forty-five-year-old human who claims
Hebrew
He be able to do that on a nominal level
However
Literally everything about clip
Examples of things that are real
Let's look at that one by one
The red begins with stuff it's too vague to mean anything
Alex buddies or reclaim the country from them and that they hate America
Literally nothing to even respond to that's just him talking
So we can leave that aside
Little warm-up he's doing a couple of jumping jacks and now we're going to get into the bullshitz the word you have to get into an impression
I've never been never will be
This isn't intentional mischaracterization of comments made by New York Governor Andrew Cuomo
Trays make America great again
By expressing a very defensible position that for many people
The part of the quote that Alex's specifically using America
Great again it was never that great
But the quote
Relies on what Cuomo said amidi
Ali after that in order to give his
Context
He went on to say quotes
We have not reached great
We will reach greatness when every American is fully engaged
Will reach greatness when
Discrimination stereotyping of women 51% of our population
It's gone and every woman's full potential is realized and Unleashed
Every woman is making her.
Naturally it would have been nice if you would have expanded its going to include other groups but
Specifically the New York women's rights event
Map direction
What Cuomo was saying is
Not in any way an insult to America it's a wreck
Ignition dinner ideals are great believe
Historical
What he was doing when he said quote we are not going to make America great again
Was not saying f*** America
It was
Clear difference
Between Trump's catchphrase Cuomo's vision
Of what are greatness
Should strive for
This is a willing interpretation misinterpretation Metallica
Both version of
And paint them as Bank of America has always Comerica
That one
That one is the far-right reaction
Any kind of
Like if you are
Blunt
The far-right about America
They will do anything and everything please
Because I can't handle
So afraid
Call the races
Just doesn't want to
Feel bad
It does come down to their fathers were terrorists
Direction of course in Star Wars
The rebel good terrorist
He doesn't like it
12 years as a reference to an interview that Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Where to cut emissions by 50
Alex is turning this into some kind of Doomsday Prophecy that you was peddling which
It's kind of hilarious considering what you did
She pretty Horsley for that everything
But all she was doing was citing a report from the UN intergovernmental panel on climate change said exactly
They predicted there's probably 12 years left to keep Global temperature
Pictures from rising to a maximum of 1.5 degrees
Yeah I was amazed
Like I assumed that everybody would know that she was
Who is quoting something
Now that I think about it
Of course on the right had no idea what that reports
Is it wasn't carbon credit
Even this
Interview
12 years if we don't address climate
However
T.i. what sheets that just before that
The larger context that I quoted that
The younger generation
Millennials and gen Z
The older Generations
Before it destroys the world
Any older Generations
Responses how are we going to pay
Ending part of the quote was dry humor
There's a little bit of that that's clearly apparent
Just say the truth clearly
She isn't in that interview baking
Specific prophecy that we have 12 years left then it's all over
She's referencing the
Epic study in articulating diffusion
Concerns of a big cross section
No one is saying that the world will end in 12 years if we don't do anything
Amount of time we have before things will be completely out of our hands and no amount of emission
Got it. The Domino effects of climate change
Alex's misrepresenting decent
To create the image
Text trying to
Doomsday prophecies
In order to go
Get a carbon credit
I really
Like there should be a
Advice
Adjustment
For these
Just a tease
You know like how would they do polls Rasmus in has a rightward bias
All of these Studies have a optimist
Bias
Yeah because every time they updated everyone that's revises like
Hey if we don't do this by 2200 is it
It's going to wind up being the next reported like we have
6 years left
You what you'd look at that is like an optimism bias Alex would say that that's evidence
So
Cauliflower
This relates to a recent livestream that AOC was doing when she visited a community
Discuss issues about what
Environmental efforts
Community garden
One of them she pointed out was the difficulty of growing crops that are traditionally used in their quiz
A community garden
She singles out Yucca is being a plant
Difficult to grow in urban environments cauliflower
Which she just picked out asthma
Example of a vegetable
She wasn't even saying anything specifically about cauliflower cauliflower or something
It was a random example
Of course
Example at Sebago
Absolut Vodka
I think so
She said that it was of colonial
Call flowers
Cauliflower has
Colonial Lake
English introduced
22nd
T22
It wasn't
AOC choked all flowers an example of a crop
These communities
Involved with cultural
Soda popular is
The big city community garden
Where space is limited
I'm not entirely sure that's fully accurate of cauliflower
Right shows cauliflower as an example
Possibly just
Because she had seen it at a community garden that you can visit
That is such one of those blind spots that I would
Never have thought of because
Cuz it never even
Comes into my life
Plant
Community garden
Like why would you just play at some random ass 85th super difficult
Space is limited
An example of colonial approach to Environmental
Of course response to this other right
She's stupid and that she's calling cauliflower
But in reality what she's talking about is a pretty important
Real issue
As a paper published in 2009 by the sustainability Research Institute
Around the world colonialism became synonymous with the alienation of people from their land and resources
Colonize people became from their resources
Largely because the colonizing
Powers did not fix
We trusted to Stewart over the land themselves
This is basically what you
You talkin about
Environmental projects
Cultural context
Because if they don't
Colonialism
Being portrayed as Environmental
Yeah you can disagree with her point if you want but if you
Then you've got to wrestle with
Town of scholarship on the intersection
Conservationism
And Colonial
Especially when we're getting
Very similar
Here is what we should do to stop all of this
That can
Boiled down to
If everybody lived like this
If everybody lives like us which for some people is culturally
Absolutely
Make slime individual
Yeah there you go
You know so
And Alex could argue this if you wanted to rub
The points of environmental colonialism
Just to say that I am
It's because the goal isn't to tell the news
Analysis
The goal is to portray your enemy
Eager to call things race
But even vegetables aren't safe
And of course the goal event for Alex
Defend himself from very accurate accusation
So there you go
Three things but Alex's used to characterize as an amazing why you fight so hard it gets what they're all bulshit
He has his own show he runs everything unlimited time on air
And this is what he brings
The table
To explain
Our enemies
Just bought
You got nothing
Okay so
Toy
So these aren't
And
So if they're not true
He knows they're not
Then they can't be the reasons that hehe
What does imply there's got to be another reason
Perhaps
One that he would rather not put out
Instead obfuscate
These lies and bulshit
Wonder what those are
Alex is really pissed off
Cauliflower being called race
It makes a little
I just got to say
And the cauliflower comment
My favorite Judy Blume
Realized
Are the high priest over fighting racism
Smoke with racist
Bought milk with races
Sensitivity
It appears that they managed to trick the right person
And this guy
It began with legitimate not making videos
Richard Spencer in baked Alaska added milk
Push the hashtag Twitter
They were doing the same thing they've done a bunch
We saw it recently with a botched
The temperature for 10 to the actual hashtag
A symbol that was a white supremacist
Troll sent journalist tips
Trying to get them to cover the story but none took the bait except for Mikhail Phelan
Of the daily.
It distinctly Mikael Phelan was a writer for Infowars
But it's not rebranded
Is a tech writer it's a lie. And somehow is getting away with it it's crazy
Just obscure enough of an Infowars important you could still do this
So
That's a problem and that's why someone like me is important to exist in the world I guess
Probably not too worried about me
This is the part of a larger strategy nationalist attempt to create innocuous
Attached
Easley post office
Is there ever called on it
We saw this with the Okay Hand
It was simultaneously a legitimate symbol being used by these extremist community
To signal to each other
Are you serious it's just an okay sign
They could respond to any
No criticism
And then the
Ultimately it doesn't matter if the okay sign as a gesture of Because by it
It's usage
Thursday
Going on
The accusation that the left thing
Milk is racist
It was a manufacturer campaign took make the last
And accusations of racism look Baseline
Because at the
Creative spirits that races
Really just
That's the motivation behind it
The phucstyx
Seriously there's only one group
Yeah yeah
0 group
Anyone still peddling with narrative in 2019
Dudley trying to signal to their base of neo-nazis and white nationalists
In on the joke
Either way it doesn't look good that Alex is still on
Unfortunately those white supremacist or we're actually onto something with their stunts campaign
Hazard
Supposed
The attempts to make milk a racist meme or supposed to be
His article discusses a book called nature
Perfect food how milk became America's drink
Which does seem to argue that it's very
Is the early advertising campaigns for the national Dairy Council
Explicitly
In the early 1900s the national Dairy Council marketed milk by saying things like quote
People who have an appreciation
For art literature and music
Court Progressive and science at every activity
Are the people who have used liberal amounts of milk and its products
The book goes on to say quote by declaring milk perfect
White northern European
Announce their own perfection
In the 1930s
An agricultural history of New York's quote
A casual look at the races of people
Seems at to show that those using much milk
Are the strongest
Just physically and mentally
And the most of the people of the world
Of all Races to Aryan seem to have been the heavy
Drinkers of milk and the greatest users of butter in
Impark account for the quick and high development of this division of human being
Louis Pasteur is the patron saint of the White Castle
I believe
Is on the Rushmore this could be called
Is because the marketing was specifically designed around the idea that there was a
Association between drinking milk
Convene better people
By Andrea freemen of the University of Hawaii School of Law
Although
Statistics very 7% of African-American adults
45% of African-American children
74% of Mexico
Kingsborough Community
98% of Southeast Asian percent of Asian Americans
Cannot Digest
A large number of non-white communities are lactose
Intolerance Market something
Naturally better people
Name something that only white people can consistently what you doing is kind of racist
It's in there
Couple of steps
It's more than you're used to seeing with
Like you got to know
Is are lactose
Intolerant you got to have a
Beretta
Information order really
Milk for how races
And now that I do
Justin like liking milk isn't racist but that doesn't mean you can't look at the history of it
Lactose intolerant is even kind of messed up
Using that framing makes
Sima being intolerant to lactose
Option as opposed
Norm when in reality quotes
Percentage of individuals from all communities
With the exception of Scandinavian and northern European white did not retain the enzyme lactase
Northern Europeans and Scandinavians developed this enzyme as a response to living in climates hostile to creating something
Sustainable food source
Which compelled them to resort to
To drinking their herds milk
So it's something that is specific to communicate
Abundance of life
Sister somehow
Deficiency
How to change
A mutation
You guys lived in the dumbest f****** place to live and then you're making us feel bad for it
None of it's wrong but
Do you take that
Is even somehow making it
A negative
This is vexing.
Texting episodes
There is a reality
Racist history in the milking.
You being tricked by or
Any criticism of racism look suspicious
The goal here was to provide a response
The next time you are one of your races
You can pull out the oh yeah Grace it's like milk is racist
It's an attempt at building
Counter-narrative at 100% only exist
To defend
Accurate criticisms of race
This is what Alex does
It's what his show exist
To do
Search be all that surprising
Cauliflower we got
Metallica
I just got to say
Triggered by this conversation about food
Or something he starts yelling about corn if he will taking corn is ready
South America
So anyway
Who cares
It's easy to grow its nutritious
How do you say it's racist
Everything
Cauliflower
Is just
He's real mad
The problem with that presentation
The way you feel
Tell if he
Do you think that mockingly or if
He really means that everything hinges on fighting back against
What's this
Accusation the cauliflower is racist
Because
Either could be something I I could
See it being
Almost like a wave function
Through each word as
Saying it what he's
As he's going through
It all and I mean
Now that is actually a joke
In doing this podcast
We Are embodying The Observer paradox
If Alex just yells it simultaneously a joke and serious at the same time but once discuss
It no longer exists
Thing that he said of like
Even if it did come from Europe
Who cares
That is such that
Colonialist mindset
You should
Immense
William Porter
Because it is
Coming from a different phone
You have to be aware of because this
Glorious is just like
America
Like that concept is
If you
Like I
Someday
It might be starling
I can't remember
There was a guy who was so upset
Shakespeare
Can you believe that
Every bird mentioned
Shakespeare
Should be on
All the
So he brought starlings he ratted destroyed every
Competitor
A monstrous
Nightmares
Did the
Never bring up
Cassowaries
I do not believe he did
God
Murder murder
Alex
Complains about
The Daily Beast writing an article about it
Complains
About people who are
Suing him
Cutting me up
How to shut me down
Again
He almost admitted
In a deposition
He's playing
Your lawyer said it
You understand the level of organized defeat buddy
It's all formulaically written it's all put out
Lying
The Easter special will be back on though
Undoubtedly next week
So
Convenient that all of the people who are
Critiquing Alex
For the things of it
Are also just happened to be wanting to destroy this country and all of his
Listeners family
It seems
He's so lucky that the people who are personally going to
To jeopardize his
Money are also enemies of the Republic
You know it's
It's just
It's really
It really makes it so
Your content on the show
Really worked
Defend yourself from
Lawsuits
I like like the way
You are getting covered
And so
Conveniently it also happened that they were Adam
Criticize you know what it's like everybody win
You know what it is
Dance to hate anyone who criticizes
Yep that's number one
And then number two it makes
Too so much of the content of Ashokan
Sort of Loki be about him being sued without him having to say things
Yeah that will like end up
Another lawsuit if he attaches the idea of all of these globalists and all these anime
Needs of America they are the ones who are coming after him
It makes it very easy for his
To build up that hatred of
The people who are coming after him
Through his
Long rambling diatribes about the globalist
Translator
Speaking of sneaky
Alex has his lawyer back on the show
He has also Jim hoft from Gateway pundit
But it's kind of boring
He's back on the show
He is boring also
He does say
This should scare you to hear a lawyer say
Beautiful defense
Of tyranny anyways
Is not obstruction of justice
It is just
And that's what President Trump did
So
Slippery slope
Hoboy
That's travel
I mean
It does seem like that make
A certain kind
In this context
It means that
Anybody who
Criticize
Accountable for his actions
Instead it's a coup Ono crime can be committed
In defense of this nation
Jail the people
Who haven't got
Maybe you should hard labor camp
Lee's globalist 24-hours everybody who
All of these arguments
Sorry service
Of creating
And environment where power can be abused
Did Alex's pretended to be against result f******
Career
Is ridiculous
So not too long
Talk about how we can't
Sitting up with
Text Machinery terrible
Sleep apnea and his neck
Super thick
45% oxygen
Next clip
And then by the way guys we haven't resisted spoilers about Game of Thrones but now Alex
Spoil Game of Thrones
White supremacist
Whatever
I warn you ahead of time but it's not like we could ignore this
Because he has some analysis of it.
I think you might have missed the point
I am completely honest
Articles about
Successful will cause the Civil War
Doesn't just stop at
Turn around looking at you
Electrochemical
We're not just seeing with with the circle five senses
Inherently
Crossroads
Most popular shows
You really believe that they are ending the last couple of episodes were going to be very popular
The most unpopular ending of a series in invasive
Peanuts TV history
How did that happen
They presume that people would find a normal okay within the range of acceptable conduct
For someone to go kill a bunch of innocent women and children
Just because they were mad that day
Wait so
Is his
Contention that the writers
Thinking that everybody would be
Super stoked
That Danny
Honey kills everybody
Or is he saying that the people
The episode
Because they think it was actually a good idea
And didn't like
Seeing her retribution at
Yeah that's that's a great question
I'm not entirely sure
Barnes
Isn't
Really
All that clear
In his in his
Perspective
Alex themes
To think that it was
Predictive
Program
Conservative witches
A real snowflake
Just self victim
Yeah Status claiming
But
Interesting
Terms of how people
But more interesting to me is that both of them are apparently psychic
Alex is a twice
Alex literally said we talked about this off-air it's not mumbo jumbo
Got Alex
Tell the story about when he was younger
He is family had a land grant
And so they had like
Hundred Acre
Batwoman
Auntie be like shooting vermin
And now varmints
He had a
Something was watching
I looked over
I saw a deer
That wasn't what we
What's triggering my Spidey Sense
They looked over
And then he looked closer and he saw the eyes and once the eye is about Ryan ran away
Okay well then Table stores
I think he's right
Tried everything
Possible
It's within the realm of
Stories that could have happened
Alex did have a lot of laughs
It wouldn't be all that crazy
If you was walking around
It got real lucky
Well it's at memorability thing
There's hundreds and
That you had a sense that something was bad
You don't remember any of those times
You do remember when
It sticks out your mind because it's the Fulfillment of that
Betty White
Which is great I thought that was loose talk but in a little bit we're going to find out that Robert
Does Mankey look like
Yeah
Phuket jobs
Last scorpion from the 30
Alex
Compass point recently
To quit
That's red that's worth
Pointing out
Intuit again talking about how
Feels really want to do this anymore never really did wanted to be a farmer
25 years
That literally wants to stop
I'll be completely honest with the Western
There's a big part of me
That
I didn't get into this from some narcissistic perspective that would be on TV I didn't want to be on TV I want to be a farmer or Rancher
He wants to
That you got Trump elected say no this broadcast worldwide and you promoting it has spread
Nationalist populist
Capitalist ideas
You are
We need the lister's that haven't bought product
See how great they are
I want to be a farmer
Look we've had a lot of fun with
Add pivots in the past but that was one of us
Smoothest
I've heard in a long time slowed a little bit
Kind of
Probably not
Accurate I'm sure Alex is always been paranoid about guns
In other points in a career I'm positive you would have said that Waco
Overtly
Like to be involved
Get active
His campaign to help rebuild
The church
In Waco
That was much more foundational interested
Starting as media career
Then we're going to take 25 years ago
If you say Waco now people are going
React to different
Then if not his audience
That's fair.
I think it's more just that like everything is
Become so much about guns
That in order for it to make sense
Then that has
To be the root of why you're doing what
What you do
You know you can repackage Waco is being
About Gunslinger
What's that ostensibly
So in this next clip we get into the 31st
Man I got bad news about the gas line up on the show
Tiger house Alex Jones
4 hours
Robert Barnes shoes
Great lawyer and release
H and I will
Open the bomb shop on Alta Vista
He opens the phone
Like 10 minutes till he's done
Again
He's on all the time now
EasyBib
I had this thought
I don't know I can obviously can't prove that
Does paying him with a
Exposure or something like that.
Alex is like
Either that or he's like
He's gradually just like everybody else in his life is
Stepping away from him but it's possible.
Things that make sense
This would be a time when
Maybe on a bunch but also
Happen like
Robinul come in town for a weekend
It's it's strange cuz he doesn't
Really have that much
Bring the table Rogan's lawyer isn't showing up on rug
No
That's awesome
Yeah I think that the most
Likely
Exclamation
Static level
That is just
Hanging out on air with someone he literally pays to defend him
I don't think it's probably a bad sign
Just kind of this Hotshot lawyer
Do the ascended right-wing fast
Community
He was a lawyer for the Covent
Popping up on Alex's show was a guest on a recent episode of Dave Rubin
36B on Fox
Snooze a little bit pretty regularly
He has popped up on Fox News
Given all this
Maybe I should look into him a little bit more I kind of gave him the passes
Opportunistic lawyer brand
You think so I think so
So I read his bio on his website
What's further into this guy
Once established in a law and business advisory practice
California is keen understanding of persuasion patterns
It was lucrative side business
Sports and political betting
So okay we have a
Lawyer to set up a gambling
Which doesn't sound at all how you might politely describe the mob
They used a lot of persuasion their gambling winnings
Are political gambling
Turns out
He better win the election
Ended up winning
70 thousand Euros
That's right
Is prices in Euros because betting on presidential electric vehicle in the US
You would like a half million dollars. Elections
Like
The real weird thing
Now for him to be
Actively involved in political
Activities for Trump when he made half a billion dollars gambling on an election
Barnes and Barnes
His bio goes on to say quote Barnes is now working for the rights
Of the underdog
Fortune-telling strategy in Polish
The candidates
Of the populist persuasion
I think that that means
You literally
Mystical abilities
Which doesn't sound at all like something
Sorry 2004
Tax protest against the IRA
Joe Bannister here of Alex's for a really long time
I find it very difficult to imagine that Alex wouldn't have known
Cool Joe Bannister lawyer
There's possibility that he's known this dude for 15
Yeah for sure I don't know that to be
But the fact that he was
Mr. Bean
Yeah I'm sure
In 2008 Robert Barnes represented Girls Gone Wild Creator Joe Francis on tax evasion charges
Well you did for a little while but ultimately left this is cancelled which Francis that quote
The only reason they wanted me as a client was to mooch off me and open up an LA office
There's a Paris Hilton of lawyers
Just to be famous not to do any
Even when he's criticizing a monster that guy still a
Yeah
Cassandra Fairbanks
When she was trying to sue a reporter for
Profusion
Image of Fairbanks
Okay
Which the reporter caption does a white power
This is exactly why the trolls started doing that
Debate people into responding
It's a publicity trap and the lawyer Fairbanks. The representer was Robert f****** Barn
Fusion rightly responded
Complete quote is clearly frivolous
The suit is an obvious publicity stunt another attempt
Intimidate reporters who
Scrutinize the extreme-right
Which is correct barnes's into that
In June 2018 the lawsuit was thrown out because of course
In 28 Chuck Johnson hired Barnes to represent
Twitter forgot when they kicked him off
After he hit that threatened to
DeRay McKesson
I don't know why
They
So you got like a real interesting
Real thread through
Barnes's career
Outside
Interesting cases
Representative Ralph
Why do
He has other interests
History of some of those like
Celebrity client
Stuff of like
Licitly working
Right-wing figure
Little bit like Avon Barksdale
Like I like that whole guy they have on retainer of just like hey
If any of our guys goes to goes to prison you're the one represent
Go to the position he's trying to
Claim
Community
I think it's going to blow up in his face
Because of Alex
Wise enough
To avoid the pitfalls
I don't think he is going on this show a lot
Classic
It's like a shortcut that has a trapdoor you get there safe
Cut you're going to fall through too much
Especially too much bad
The f****** show 3 times in a week
You're right that's crazy
So Alex
Complain here in this neck
Text clip before Barnes shows up
About how blue City
Falling apart
Course
We know cuz we've listened out of the show before it says it all the f****** time
Every blue
In the country
It's not just collapsing into typhoid
And leprosy
Rogers music
And literally hundreds of other diseases
Hundred into homelessness
Drug abuse needles
With a cherry on top of men dress as women
Running around at public events with small children
Cherry on top
Sodom and Gomorrah in the Bible
Archaeologists think so
Okay but there
Butter
What's your point of order
People people
Referencing Sodom and Gomorrah
Just as
The place
Like there's a larger context around it
But it doesn't matter if the
The place is real
So
The store
The claim that they've been
Discovered the archeological sites were Sodom and Gomorrah
Each time they're claimed
Scrutinized and found to be
We flawed Ito also I would imagine
That a lot of those guys share one
They're looking for Sodom and Gomorrah
For a very specific
I strongly disagree cuz I think the archaeological
Curiosity
Is very strong
Heinrich schliemann
I don't think anyone's trying to prove anything by archaeology
No Hayward
Being the person
Take your name Moana
Imagine
Discover
Sodom
I suppose I was leaning towards the people who would then
Exploited immediately after
Proposed locations for Sodom
Which
Geographically possibly where was
Unfortunately
But if that site is accepted as. I'm finna completely rewriting invalidates except
Biblical dates for the
Similar problems pop up graphic location
Alex is kind of right as much as enterprising archaeology
Just looking to make a name for themselves
Scholarly community
Takes a more measured approach
Take me to position to take
Also
I don't think any archaeologist who believe the story of Sodom and Gomorrah literally
I would suspect most of them would say that if the
The place was real there's any truth to the story it's a metaphorical retelling of a natural disaster that happened it wiped out of town
It's an element of oral tradition
Scapegoating
We talked a little bit about this when I was brought up ASAP
America
You tell a story about two cities destroyed by a terrible earthquake or some
You need to have it make sense
So when oral tradition you introduce an element
Divine retribution
The kasbah
Instead of CityWalk
And that way you also enforce cultural norms and expectations
Through the telling of the story
Don't do any
Complete
Just don't agree that's out of my borrowed were real places based on
Available
Alex
Just doing that
I guess
Be a dick
Turn on Trump
And Kushner
This is because losses come out
The kushners going to Bilderberg
This is my problem
With your narrative
Yeah but Alex
It's cool unless Kushner
Circe
And
I don't think he had me Wildfire but
The thing is
With Alex
He's already done this
Yeah Trump went to Davos already
Worked out how to play this game
Of course it's a den of globalist
Yeah but it's cool and replace
He's responding to criticisms that a lot of people have been throwing at
The kushners going
Two
In order to
Say like hey this is
The problem
He makes it clear that is there every
Is a
Or if there was
He would f******
Turn on that
I would like to point out it happens
6 times already
This is me
Anything out of touch
Shoppers value
Turn on them
Pitbull
Flash
Everybody should just relax
You're conquering Bilderberg right now
Okay
Fair enough
What
Never assume the outcome
Before the
Is the experiment Kushner going to Bilderberg
An experiment that's just a dude going to a meeting
Not everything
The experiment is
What would it take for somebody to turn on Trump
So yeah it's not going to happen
Because you're not go
We've seen
Of course
Cool
Whatever man
So you remember earlier I was talking about the idea of
This
Purge
That people were pushing for in the beginning early days of trump
How all of these
These people in the right wing
Media including Alex
And people who are more associated with him than they are now who doesn't come around anymore
Images don't show up in their photograph
I compare that to
Specifically in intentionally
The idea of this recent Purge that Kim Jong-kook
Yeah
For Alex to bring back Robert
First episode enzyme talk about that Purge
Cool Whip
We know 60 years of this
Is there killing in prison everybody who he blamed for it
But what
The president of the
He said they taunt the president called
Absolutely
Is a really f***** up way to rationalize and be like later
Either killed or
It's definitely not the healthiest way to go about
Stupid
Oh boy
Look
If I had my druthers
It is kind of you got to give it to him
He wants to move forward
This is a real strategic move on his part
Support at
Was
One of the most
Disjointed
Like ideas
I've heard come out of the lawyers
Let alone
Against on Alex Jones
It's delusional
First of all
VI
Like what the North Korean
Press
Is that the idea
For The Purge
Was that
These people didn't
Understand us
Intentions
There was an expectation.
Complete denuclearization
It doesn't
I'm like The Purge
Was
Particularly
To get more
No
More
Away from
1 rum
That should have been pushing for
So it seems like this is a step backwards
Alex Jones are willing to go on
Did a purging of government officials
In the wake of a not going great
What is a good sign
You know a lot of people do meteors crashing into the Earth
To see all that fire first
It's great
That's what does a wild thought
There's a lot of times that I
Just think like
You guys are really going for it and that's one of them that's really going for it
Trying to reclaim
Kim Jeong Hoon
Persian people
Deposit paperwork for nationalism
In-N-Out f*****-up
Man
You don't
Barnes really
Define lawyer
It'll because bro
They're presented as being rational
Intelligent people
When was like the rest of us
Speaking of crazy
Robert Barnes
There's a story going around
About some
That are supposed to be released I believe
Of Martin Luther King
In a positive light
Probably I don't know enough about it and Reporting on it that I
I was looking at was secondhand
Seems I'm in the archives
Record this
But I do have a position on it in terms of like
I don't think that anyone is
Trying to get Martin Luther King
You know what I mean
Because they did
I mean the kids
You make a point
Nvs PW
Aren't trying to
Cancel Martin Luther King with
Is Taco
That seems to be what Alex believes though
And Alex Robert Barnes
Have a conversation
Can about the cancel
Of Martin Luther King
Write about why the left
Just turned on him
Alexander Barnes
I don't either
I don't recall turning on my lip
Either but I guess
Schnauzer Alexandra
To find out why
So this is what unique about Martin Luther King
Get your name
It was I'm an American
Absolutely
That actually unifying figure
Across classes across races and he was appealing to the deepest part of Americana
So
He said that
Is so mixed with
Corrected
In the right and wrong way
Simultaneously
Ferret
It's a little while
Episode
Beck's probably
Is openly trying to discredit Martin Luther King
Exactly
Crazy the left is God
Teen is probably the biggest threat
Message
Because because
They have to take him out because he was a uniter
Now if I were to make a complete
Hoover
Maybe describe right maybe there's not enough contact from Vuclip
These tapes there
About the bike
To cancel Martin Luther King
But I wanted to point out a few things
Alex and Barnes are intentionally Luther King jr.
Take me to hundred percent sure
That should Alex have been active in the sixties would have been on the side of those calling for King
In 1952 Martin Luther King Road quote
I'm much more socialistic in my economic theories and Capitol
Capitalism has outlived its usefulness
A 19-6
67 Martin Luther King literally gave a speech
At Riverside Church in positive
Private property rights were not a primary concern
Motives and property rights are considered
The giant Triplets of racism materialism and militarism are incapable of being calm
She's the only thing standing in between the left and Victory
In his final book where do we go from here
For guaranteed
All amendments regarding economic equality and increasing public housing
He expressed his support for job guarantees and Universal Health
He literally called for redistribution of wealth darling of the right
Because of his inclusive message
What Alex Robert Barnes are doing here is engaging in whitewashing of Martin Luther King's life and Legacy
He wasn't uniter absolutely
He was trying to unite people for a goal that these two Dum Dums would have fought tooth-and-nail against
You think Alex Jones would have heard him literally called for reparations
You think Alex Jones would have read the letter from the Birmingham Jail where he said that moderate whites maybe more of an impediment to civil rights than
Clan
All of Alex's guides and inspirations
Strictly opposed to Martin Luther King when he was actually alive
Alex's favorite book none dare call it conspiracy was written by Gary Allan
Who was I f****** segregation
Alex's favorite nontron politician of all time
Was explicitly against the Civil Rights Act
It's true
Number of libertarian
Yeah my point is this
You can say that Martin Luther King was a uniter all you want that's totally cool
What bars are doing here however is
Stealing Martin Luther King
King's Legacy from him
And imagining that the some possible world exist
Were they would have been in that very small percentage of the population
Martin Luther King when he was still alive
This is a pathetic and disgusting
Display just about ready to
Expecting these couple of dicks
Tire repair
Looking party
I mean it is one of
Better B
The idea that every year white people add another hundred
From the day
Yeah you know like that
Everyday Martin Luther King Jr's been dead we can't
Take a little bit away from what he was
To do and then just really oh he was a symbol of American
You forgot to
Pretends that like all the stuff he screams about the globalist about aren't like very aligned with stuff today
Go fuc yourself Alex globalist
You dumb
Prick
Take a note is because he was uniting a lot of people
In order to fight against people
People who are engaged
You are
So
From what I understand
That are to be released
Are they have to do with mistreatment of women
It's complicated
That is not playing today
Disgusted
It's something that you can't
You can't just ignore the
These bad parts
Important
And it doesn't mean that you have to
Say
You have to wrestle with those
And it's interesting that Alex wrestles with that
Specific element
Because I think he goes the
I think you get a glimpse into how his brain works here
Is that
Somehow
What county is Duvall in in
Perfect
Exactly
Martin Luther King was the Harvey Weinstein of History
That is ridiculous.
Because
What king said was true
Whether what they're saying about the throttle body
It just makes me want to anymore
First I believe your
Discussing
Which which wood is the proof
So they do have
Presumably
I'd also
What
No that's
No it's weird
Impulse
Is like
Alex
Your brain is weird
Barnes makes
Was all about but you still
To claim him
You trying to pay
The Legacy
Appealing to our constitutional history
Patriotic
I'm because I'm a man I should have the same rights as all men is All-American
It was not a reparations based
I would like I would like Barnes now to give me one
Martin Luther King
King Junior that you have read and remember to
None of that
Go ahead
Is a speech that Martin Luther King jr.
68 it was on his speaking tour leading up to the Poor People's March
Washington
America refused to give the Negro any land
An act of Congress are government was given
It was willing to undergird its white peasant
It's from Europe with an economic
Floor
But not only
They built land-grant colleges
Government money
Teach them how to farm
Not only that they provided County agents
The further.
What to use in farming
Not only that they provided low interest rates in order that they could mechanize their Farm
Not only that today many of these people
Are receiving billions of dollars in federal subsidies
Barb
And this is what we are faced
This is the reality
He finished his thoughts by saying quote
Washington in this campaign
We are coming to get our check
Illicitly
About Refrigeration
Barnes and Alex are not interested
Martin Luther King
Feeling him
And turning him into a prop
The further their agenda
It's very transparent
Really
Fox News should be
Band from
Actually saying Martin
Disgraceful
Stay at
Scott
Yeah
So remember how Alex responded to
Step Brothers
It would be just like a room talk.
I I would find that
F***** up
It's even weirder that
Not
Couple minutes later
He says this
About 14 years old
One of my dad's cousins was already she was good-looking hot blonde by like 30 years old
What
Slapped
What the f***
I don't know you are
Man
That's pretty
I wish we'd never started I think you just thinks he has attorney-client privilege cuz he started
So it's really weird to have a situation where yeah I mean there is the possibility that
Some of
Martin Luther King jr.
Personal history
Is going to change
The conversation
I'm surrounded
I think that's
That's something
That history allows for
Scholarship allows for that
Recording
It's something that'll be more complicated conversations
To have eventually
Alex is like the mirror
Furtive
Number 14
It's weird
Really weird
Kids four wheeler
Weird
What it is
Cousin
Weird
He's married with first cousin once removed
I don't appreciate
Nope
I thought
I suppose I thought everybody knew that
Jagger Hoover was trying to Black
Martin Luther
Because he was
End-of-summer VSCO pastor
I think so I don't know cuz
Not specific enough for me to really
Clean a ton of information about it
I don't know
Hey I'm not qualified to speak
Is
A kernel of it probably involves
Sprite
But I also assume that there's more information
Is known
Going back through with so many of those p
People of like
The heroes of the
Women's right
Right to vote movie
Also being
Virulently anti-gay
And all of this stuff
You look back at the
People who you think are
Pillars
Progressive
Thought you know
Go back inside
Oh you're actually
Like
Complicated
Does bring up something that really does
Scare me
Because it is
That
Done event
Emergency
Technologies
That we have that is
Completely
Rewrite their history by creating doctor videos
The new technologies that are emerging
There is the possibility of
I'm doing that I don't think that's what's going on here but
The f****** scary thought
And I assume the people who listen to Alex
Community will be
Be more likely to do that than anyone else
Tried
Really hard never to think about that
Yeah
The annihilation
Real
So I don't know man this is weird episode
Vexing as you said and I agree
It's
Crazy
I expect he's 20 good work day
Non
Obviously I thought it was going to be a lot of Mueller talk
Robert Barnes talks for a little while about how like
Okay that's what I said
Boring
There's just not much
Kind of its
Every time
Moon for murdering people
There's also
A lot of cauliflower
Which I am not here for
Don't care
I'm glad
Did we did this episode if only for Alex's
Got to drop about dona
Yeah that is so good it's only for that I do
Or somebody bought donuts and I just inhaled two of them
Stop
Appreciate
We'll be back with another episode
I'm at go to bed book you can download
Places scribe reviews go to Napster
Brunch restaurant
B. Can't remember any other download music
But
Then I mean Robert Barnes has had a lot of
Weird client
But
Ralph Nader's killed anybody
Probably true paid Robert Barnes
Probably never killed anybody
Ralph Nader
Maybe
We probably have
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work