Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
A little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
How do you feel about a good song
Who are you
I like a AAA concealed as a boxer
I like a True Skate
If I'm going for a cracker I'll probably get address
I absolutely have no use
The very boring cracker it reminds me of times that I would go to the
The nurse's office
XXX faking sick
Electric wire
Yep I have that Gatorade
Throughout
Electrolytes
Play Drake backup
Experienced a good salt
Yeah it's my position on it
I love the way
I don't think I've ever
Experience to good salt I like a Wheat Thin from time to
Time
How do you feel about for Keebler buttery Christmas is for you
That rounds out
Actors and not others
So Jordan today was good interesting episode back in the past in 2013
Who's doing the aftermath
Sandy Hook of course we are on February
First 23rd
Game today one day only
Weird f****** show okay I was so disoriented by it
Pleasurable experiences I've had
Preparing an episode
Just because I was so
All over the
Alex
Follower
It was a situation I felt so untethered
The 2013. Like it doesn't get sad
I'm feels different
It's just lunch
Completely all over the place
It will get the how and why what happened
But before we do I need to give a little bit of a correction from our episode
We talked about there being reports
Play Purge
Done by Kim Jeong Hoon
Some government officials in the aftermath of
Failed Summit with the Donald
And as it turns out those were erroneous report
I apologize to everybody that I got that wrong
At the time that we recorded the episode
That was what was being referred to
And I operated off
What was being reported
Now the more important piece of it was
I wasn't
Reporting's
As to stay
Here is what's happening in North Korea this is the news
I was discussing it in the context
Alex Jones believe this to be true
And his
Response to it is
Cool
More accurately I guess
Not the best way to send a signal it's all right
So the conversation of it being whether it is true or not
You know we dropped the ball a little bit
Bigger piece of it is
It's still stands alone
Weather the story that
Is true or not
You know Alex Jones
Response to that story
Under the assumption of it being true was fuked up
Yeah that's that's a little bit like
Look we we got the reporting wrong
But Alex did still see that guy that's a great
His take on it
Yeah I want the reasons why
I find the present a little bit less gratifying to cover
As much as
There there's a possibility
For the greater possibility
Things like that misunderstanding
Bad reporting that you read and then by the time the episode
Goes up
Has been corrected
24-hour news cycle
Absolutely think so
Definite downsides of it
These things
2013 February 1st
And are supporting the show
Next web
I'm a policy wonk
You're now policy walk
Text Lillian take you so much
Very much so
Taylor thank you so much
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Appreciate
So
Rottweiler verse
This first clip is only interesting
Central
Eastern
Very standard introduction to the show
Note of that before our show
Yes he's doing 3 hours
Another hour
Go to overdrive overdrive for like 5 minutes
For something
I'm only making note of this to show that like he often does not know what he's going to do
Or what his schedule is going to be like when he starts the show
I did an extra hour another extra hours
Think it's indicative that the spirit
Is Indian whatever you doing he wants to be doing because of
I don't like that
Well
You know is that clip he did say Lord willing
I'll be back on Sunday
Yes you could take that kind of religion
Office episode quite religious
But I should say that he always
Since you know that I got a little bit of
Big
Episode
Post-tribulation rapture
Which we know he's a big fan
Kinkos Bastrop
Yeah that's bulshit
He believes and we'll get into this a little bit later in the episode he believes that the idea of a pre-tribulation rapture
Concocted by the globalist
Because they were scared of the Christians
Ability to
To take them out
The the Christian
It's okay don't worry about raptured before all the trouble that we're going to cause
Okay
Is either.
Raptors
We're going to have to think about a little bit
But before we do Alex
To talk about
Play the Chris
Used to be
So
Against tyranny
But now they don't care
Because
Pre-trib rapture
That's today
Georgia
Laden
Sociology
Important psychology
If you've been listening along to these 2013 episodes in the aftermath
Gruas
This this focus on priem post-trib Rapture is very much like
What is happy
Sucking extended the gold commercial at the end of the previous episode
Parks
Security guard
What's the date before this
Grunts at you
You got to start thinking about the end
Perfect sense
You know first thing that happens
Then the very next
Daddy is just like I don't know what's going to happen next but I hope there's a
It's just it's very weird
In congruence from a narrative perspective like
So
Also I should say I've been hearing Alex no King but King
Jesus a b
Emmys 2013 episode
Some kind of phrasing
Paraphrasing tool
Scripture that I don't remember
So I just decided to leave it alone
But for some reason this time I don't know why
It hit my ears a little bit
And maybe it's because of that jarring
Shift from
What he was doing
This this religiosity
Different
If I can trace down
Where that phrase came from and what we can learn about Alex
From his repeated use of it to attack Obama
Turns out there's something
Too clearly right
As The Story Goes
Reverend
Clark on the night of April 8th
1970s
Clark was a pastor and said to be involved in the local militia
As the men gathered Paul Revere arrive in Warren that the Brits
British major Pitcairn showed up
He demanded that the men lay down their arms
Do it the Patriots were said to have replied
We recognize no Sovereign but God and no key
King Vegeta
There's a lot of problems
Historical perspective neither John Adams
Karen arrived historically
It was Samuel Adam
Attended the meeting
Clark's house.
Brewer and Patriot
Very detailed account of the question April 18th
Deep 1775 doesn't include
You can't trust but plenty of other dialogue
Mansion had it happen
It's unclear if this framing of the quote in this fashion actual
Exist anywhere prior to
John Ashe
Minecraft game
At the noted Evangelical Christian School Bob Jones University
Hey what she said quote
A slogan of the American Revolution which was so distressing to the emissaries of the kings that it was founded correspondences
Back to England
Was the line we have no key
King Vegeta
Tax Collectors came
And Colin it's frequently said we have no key
King budgies
Restaurant was George W Bush's Attorney General
Sobe certainly weird
If that was where I was
Take me to Crossroads
F****** hate
George W George W bush and all things related to him
That's weird
That one though
For my Morrison
Diversion
The story of that night
April 18th
That was told by Charles
Eugenics
King George
Version of the story
Almost every
Matches up with Alex's story
Mattress up also with Charles
Leader in the Christian identity movement
Which was a religious group that was very popular among
Extreme right in the
1880s for your first sentence
Right around that was popular with this that
Alex probably would have been right around the time he was coming of age
Sounds right
Christian identity members called for the liquidation of the UN
They didn't believe in paying taxes
Suzanne argued that the sheriff was the highest constitutional Authority
Is a heavy heavy overlap
Virion
Likely to call it a coincidence
This is important
Because
The first person to articulate
The fabricated
The quote Alex's
Heatedly saying comes
Seems to be
And Beyond
James is also a huge races
Biolage
From an article in St Louis posted
Dispatch from March 5th 2000 about Charles Jenkins
Christian identity conference
Being held in Branson Missouri
Children sit with their parents
The speaker Charles agent
Call Tim cell
And said he was pleased with the quality of our races in this room
What audience member who applauded Jennings
Beach was top Rob
The Grand Dragon
The Klu Klux Klan
American Revolution
For preachers who are leaders in
The Christian Movement
It implies a very foundational problem with his voice
Namely that he believes to be actually
Respect that's what I was generally means
He says lower
Strong races
Contacts at like this strong
Connected Force
Between neutrons and
Protons and then the week
I think it just means
Emphatically
This lady has very
Alex
Believe this
Articulation of
A story that absolutely didn't happen
Historically
What was used
Fairly
Propaganda
Weis
So
Episode from the 29th
Steve. Alex
Robert Barnes were talking about Heather psychic
Alex has long felt this way
How do you do this
Pappadeaux
You're never right I'm Amazed by that myself
The present
Completely identical
To be like
Relic between
I don't understand how that works I was waiting for and I was going to jump out my window
I was waiting for the simulation
So
Valex is literary love
Spell bored
Enjoy this
I couldn't cut this
Flip out
Despise
Fear is the mind-killer
Philosopher
Frank Herbert
Is the mind-killer
Google petite Mort
Hey
Frank Herbert comes up
Frank Herbert
Doolin
Yeah
Amazing novels
Leave the Brian Herbert
Theranos
Fair enough
This cliff
In the same way
For you as a dude lover
Thank you this one
Here's what I want explain
Infowars.com
Si.com
Dot-com
British royal Commission on population
It's
Congress of the United States
It is not I love you f****** bragging about geography
It makes me wonder if he's not aware of how poorly done it is
Like if he just gave
And they just turned in shity homework at he wasn't paying never check
Yeah that sounds pretty implausible on now he's just never checked in
I just assumed
For whatever
I told Rob do f****** get the bibliography together
And because Broadview
Can't
Because their makeup
Alex
Bibliography I can't put a meme
I found a patriot Message Board years ago doesn't
Play almost like a dove
It was it was a large percentage of them but I don't know what the gross
Number one
How do I do on our Wiki I do have a running
Completely made up quotes
I love it
I always love it
Geography
Terrifyingly plausible that he
Just have no idea
I consider that
He is terrible
Employees
You probably
Right
When is operation
Not a bug
It's protective
Yeah yeah
Next talks about Bill Gates
Speech
TED Talk
You might
You might start to notice a little bit of
At the beginning
Little bit religious
Yeah talking about you no no
King Kong
And then he start he got into the
The bibliography for
And he starts
Weaving
Kind of a lot
Endgame
Well no cuz then
This is Bill Gates talking about
Extermination
Bill Gates kubicek
TED Talk
That Alex is going to misrepresent
Beverly
Clip where he discusses
Alex thinks you talking about
Destroying all
Extender
Which means
Branches of government
Asian
So for long time
What Alex was there cuz I've heard that sort of thing
I thought that represent Bill Gates
Like Bill Gates made a dump
Joke and Alex
Like I thought
Was it Bill Gates
The ad made a joke about that
And then like
This number
A population could be zero that would suck
I went back and re-watch that TED Talk
Joke it's just the audience laughing at a poorly set-up slideshow
That's all that's going on laughing at him
Disastrous effect
We need to get carbon emissions down
Close to zero as we
He brings up his equation
Where carbon emissions equals
People X
Number of service
Services
X
CO2 produced
A unit of energy
This equation
He goes into
Variable one by one
It says that for the equation
2 equal zero one of the variables is going to have to get pretty close to zero
In the meantime
Has moved on to his life or the variable of people
Search shows a bunch of people on the
The screen Oso everybody Rigsby
People in everybody
Are the Bill Gates even realizes
Slide his chain
Or if he does
He doesn't seem to understand why people
Yeah that actually does
That sounds right on both counts
I believe that he does not understand why people laugh explicitly says that the population is going up
Provide appropriate Healthcare
Can slow the rate of that rise a little bit
Variable should go down go down
Argument is about how
The efficiency
CO2 per unit of energy
Are you actually have a
Chance of bacon
This Peach is very clear if you listen to all of it that has nothing
Population
Bring you that b*******
Has everything to do
With creating
I mean if you can't really argue with it
The people time Services times efficiency
3 * 302
A unit
That does make sense
What all those add up to 2
Be close to zero
Closest gyro drop all of them
They will all be dropped for us
That one could be the one that's closest to 0
Variables that you may have possibility
Nature will change
Is explicitly against
Depopulation
Rich's in Irish
Yes
Yeah that is
The reality of the
Situation is the result
Of the reality of Alex
It's from
Anything in that equation
Korean propaganda
It is very apocalypse
He's a depopulation agent
49 Royal Commission
I'm very excited to announce
I figured out how Alex Jones knows the word actuary
All the time context
Report
1049 report of the royal Commission on population
Was conducted by an actuary
The 1949 result was the result of the report was the result of a five-year study on population
What are the concern about that confirming the conventional accepted
2.33 repeating
2 1/3 children were required
Population
And this is one of the Benny primary Quest
The commission set out to
What they found more less boiled down to it being
Quote the size of the family has remained comparatively stable for 20 years at about two point
Two children per married couple
Percent deficient for population
Airport called
Itself out however for not being able to
You predict
From lowering ages of marriages which was it
Beginning to happen around the Sun
As well as
Decreased
Infant mortality
So that's 6% deficiency
Replacement
It might not even been Acura
An analysis of the report which is done two years after its release mirrors
Disconcern
It explicitly lays out how to use more data has made the 1949 after effect
The analysis goes on to say quote
It will course be argued the two years
For now projections
That is no doubt true enough
But skepticism should not be allowed to stifle all Creed.
So
There's a built
Trends that are happening
That make this in
Incomplete picture but it's worth doing anyway
To know if our future analysis
These mean anything
Let's see how wrong we are and why now and then later on
Recognition process
What are the chief findings of the report was that fertility rates
Decreasing at whatever rate they word
What's the result of people being
It was the result of people having a
Choice about having kids
For the first time it pretty much ever
The oral contraception would not be approved by the f
PA until 9
1946 Family Planning centers
Advising people in Britain about
Techniques
One level I suspect Alex probably
Reported
Because it was one of the
The first in Britain
Recommend the first control should be made available through Health Services
Which drew the Savoy
Buri are the religious community surprise
In an article in the Catholic Herald
There is not a spark of religion about it is purely pagan
Example
Of the way in which the mind of England
Is gone pagan
If we give women an inch over our lives
Make sure everything is under our control the more conservative
British taxes
Report primarily for that reason
It stands to reason that this is a groundbreaking report in terms of open
Disgusting family
What all Alex's
I sincerely wish that I could say with certainty with Alex
The talkin about
He talked about the 1949 Royal Commission on population
But it's pretty hard to find context
Clues
He just says
This report is at the at the
Prisonplanet the entire website
If you search them for any sort of irrigation two words 90
T49 Royal commission report
Literally nothing comes up
That can't be real
Forever and never song
To write
What is the point
Complaining about this report
That's crazy
I wonder if Alex maybe just
Fell down
Drunk
Front of a library and somebody was walking out with
That Commission
Somehow
His brain
I thought that's just what he referenced I strongly suspect what it is
He's heard other people in the
Patriot
Right wing
Communities
Complain about it but maybe on message boards and
And newsletters
You would read
5 these
Paranoid John Birch
Society of Jason sweaters that would go out
In the early days
They would make referee
Or W Cleon skousen
Might have brought it up in
One of his writings without
What's love
His main problem was with the
Dafont
Who is wing ding
What does a mistake
Wish they could go back in time
I think that it's possible that he's heard about it secondhand
Who was pissed off about it because
Birth control
And the cycle of stupidity and the Cat's in the Cradle and the silver spoon
To talk about it from a perspective of like
I'm against this because it advocated
For people being allowed
Contraception
Recognize
Treat you like that
I think you just doesn't want people
To know that that's his argument
It seems like that's the only thing you could possibly be
Yeah
It's very confusing
Figure out what year
What do you mean
Cookie Swirl of s*** is just about
Contraception
I think that he
Either
Of his own volition
Or based on something
He read somewhere else
It all traces back to just
Resistor
The idea of the
The freedom
That is offer
By having a choice
Giving birth
Yeah but Alex is talking
Hear about
This is this is why I
Cuz you still
Sorta talk
About
He's talking about
This is directly contradictory
Something to eat generally
Don't they have 20 kids
They want to do
Destroy the world and you can tell because they don't have
The globalist
It's just been
Because they've been
Eating so many of them I guess
Zion drum supplies
A lot of this stuff
Cut out a lot of clips
That's going back over everyday
Hun
Post office
Endgame last night and was like
I could see him rubbing one out to his own movie
Brilliant brain rub out
It's so we have this
Kind of religious
Friend going on
I have this app game
And I think it comes
Together in the
It's very strange.
When I told you the beginning
This episode
Very untether
Because of this vibe
I think that this clip really well in body
That sort of
What he
To the table
And it made me
Deeply on
Europe
Even my family
3 minutes
On the PowerPoint
Child of
Iowa score
Red pile of skulls
Standing ovation
So
I was very close to leaving the clip out of the theft
And just kind of
Trying to find
The new point
Alex brought him up game
Little bit
Ultimately I felt
Really represented this energy that Alex has
On the show
It's Super Why
His manner is entirely different.
The previous episodes
In 2013
He has the air of a
Creature to
More than he normally does
The repetition of it
The end of eclipse
Made me feel very unsettled
Simultaneously
He's doing a shitload of rehash
Is it like weed
We watched it the night before he was reminded what
I'll just remind you to do that
Sorry guys get back on track
Buckwild
Hits 2013
Contact Straight Outta 2008
Literally the day before this episode he was telling fake stories about grunting Park Rangers
Is today doing the preacher in
Literally nothing feels right about this episode
It makes me feel really
You f***** up
I don't know what to do with it
And we'll see how it
Hands up playing
Bisquick
Completely line
About dr. Eric.
Bianca is one of Alex's favorite go-to examples of members of the
The Intelligencer
Depopulation
Who is playing
Interesting Lee in pretty much
All the time
I was listening to Alex
The only thing
Brings up about Bianca
Is this one
Where people gave the standing ovation for rooting for airborne
Ebola
Interesting
Let's just saw headline 2006
He's been riffing on it ever
Back in April 2006 are kyanka was giving a speech
The Texas Academy of Science
It was a speech that he delivered
Or called The Vanishing book of
Is an evolutionary ecologist
The speech was about to
Tastrophe that was living in the ecos
Catastrophe that we have willed into existence through an axe
50 ride a new speech every year cuz you can't really tore on the same hour
I'm over and over and over again
Charlie sure how long he been doing these bit
Before this without into
Alright
But on that April day
Was named Forest meme
Horse anasshole is named for
He's not he's not to be confused with the rapper meme
Who did that song This Is Why I'm Hot
He was named Forest
Memes Dark Forest memes is an amateur scientist
Skeptical
About time comfortable saying he's not assigned
Of course it doesn't stop
The University of Nations
Kona Hawaii
Unfortunately the University of Nations
College ocfo Pablo Rivera was sentenced to prison life
3.1 million dollars from the school
He created fake invoices
Used to make up the money that the four left the school
What are the things he allegedly bought with the money was a gold mine in Sierra Leone
So that dude is real cool
That's like chicken all of the all of the boxes of evil
Gold mine in Sierra Leone of course I'm going to buy that I've already reached the state of Mont
Osterhoudt where
There's no recourse for me and help well there's actually one box left the check off
You stole from the school so I don't know
Nine-tenths of the law
Anyway that's
House is not in order
Is what I would say
Kind of amazing that the guys who describe themselves
The Skeptics are the ones most often
Been taken in by these kind of place that I actually
General in 1988 Mims alleged Scientific American
Views
This in combination with his disbelief
Climate change
The sharp Focus
Doctor
And it's an expression of them
Is being an a******
First Mims was there for this
Can you took it upon himself to write an article on his website that was covered
Gazette Enterprise
I believe it was just
I would say
Crying and cheering fans like a baby
No no
This article of the local papers at Washington
Sensationalize report Avianca
The speech was then picked up by The Drudge Report
Immediately
Come on
Analyze the quote
Provided
To The Gazette Enterprise
And compared them to
Transcript of Bianca
Speech
Add up
The quotes were taken entirely out of context
Text an offer from different parts
People who were there came forward and called Mims assessment a quote dishonest mischaracterization
And said quote doctor Pianka in no way advocated billions of deaths from Ebola or said anything that would lead a reason
I've read the speech and I 100
I concur with this
I find it very hard to believe that someone could reach
The conclusions that Mims did
Without doing so intense
The right would never ever use that
That doesn't sound
Information becomes pretty clear that men's would likely offended by Bianca
Phone doesn't care for creationist in climate denial position
It is speech Bianca said quote
The biggest enemy we face is anthropocentrism
Attitude that everything on Earth
It was put there for RJ
To be use anyway we want
Which is a direct opposition
Into the Bible which we know creation
Generally do
Is Bianca
Studio
Mims is a fellow of the discovery
Which exists specifically to
To quote make
Intelligent design the dominant
Perspective in science
Mirror prominent evolutionary
Ecologist
As an advocate of human extermination
In the Fallout Bianca receive
Rapunzel death
Even reported him to Homeland
Insecurities as a bioterror
This harassment campaign
Seriously out of hand
Will you take a closer look at
Absolutely based on a willful misrepresentation
The closest thing that you can
Come to m
I'm saying something
He's close to this
Is in the quote he does say
Something along the lines of
The world would be better off
If there were 10 to 24
Percent of us
People wear that he wants the world
Dude I just that
The natural is illogical systems
Call Rick better
So I don't know everything is just a wealth of
Mischaracterization
And this is the only thing that Alex knows is the smear
Oh yeah guy
The right-wing is so good at that
Getting some small dumb and nocuous life
From some idiot in the middle of f*** nowhere
And turning it into
The
Lake house
The middle of nowhere
Professor
No not him
Punishment
Because it is
He's someone who's
He does know a good bit
Self-taught
Electrical engineering
Electrical
Yeah from from other side
No right I agree but because of that he had a position within
Texas Academy
Appliances
Okay
Auspices that are appropriate
It's one of those interests
He got out of his Lane
And his creationist
Climate denial position
I think led him to
Great offense
It's like a veterinarian and we all know that
Also want everything is really important to remember is that Alex's
Completely lying about research
Slideshow
Descriptive speech and I mentioned Bianca includes
Is graphics
Alex's tacos
In about
Skulls
6 cartoon skulls
Next to a cartoon of Skeletor
It's a part of this
Talking about trying to find images to go along with this
It's clearly
How to know that if you looked into it at all
But he would know exactly what he knows
If he'd only read the account from Mims that was reposted on Drudge
Which says quote
Pionk event displayed a slideshow with rows of human skulls
Had red lights flashing from it
That one with red lights
Flashing
It was
Skeletor
From He-Man
Is the most
Annoying
It's saying that I have heard
Since our last
Goddamn episode Dan reality
Is where Alex is like we looked search the image
If you search
For the images
Human skulls
Is misrepresenting a description
It's only unfair
Technically accurate
If you want me to take
Because it's so highlights how little work out
Yeah but you do want to check into what
Yeah that makes it very very point of lies about his process
Lies about the work that he does
Because he needs to
So we get off there
Like I said
Religious vibe
Through
And the
Don't know
Why
So it's not 42
This one's more current
Although
Making him hold up newspaper is now it all of these
Def just to confirm when the date is
This one's current
Beatles
Homeland Security
License plate stand
Major cities
Talking about a specific veteran who got arrested
For a possession of a weapon
Full over anyone who's of that
Desperate plea
Join us
And you know what we're going to do
Find all of the homeless veterans because
What do you say
Commercial
The story that he's talking about the Pacifica
Haddad
Veteran who was arrested after he was found
Being possession
Illegal weapons accessories
In specific he had 30 round magazine
For an AR-15 and AR 7
Then which is really illegal
New York
As it turns out this may not be the case of overzealous cops
Just pulling over
It was likely the result of a sting operation
What are the things that makes me
That is at the edge article about his arrest
It clearly states
Doesn't seem like how you would describe someone at a check
Also the article says that he was parked because he had quote
Advertise the magazines for sale on Craigslist and was waiting to meet a potential buyer
Okay so you're you're thinking the cops may have found that Craig's
Really bad planning whatever you're trying to commit an illegal sale of goods
You don't want to
You don't want to advertise it like a lot of people do that on Craigslist
Nevermind this is a basic piece of primary reporting that all the Conservative Christian
To gloss over
They all say that he was arrested for possessing
Which
But he was
He was arrested for trying to sell them
Which they don't want to because it hurts their basic argument of
These magazines are safe and good in the hands of Ben
Upstanding veteran
Veteran really bad the moment hands them over in exchange for money
These magazines are specifically for military use only so obviously sneakily traffic trafficking
Isn't a good thing
Either way it doesn't matter because I just got a slap-on-the-wrist with a conditional discharge
Here to pay the $200 fine but consider
I became a cause celeb of the right-wing militia Patriot world
He raised over $50,000 and online campaign
It's very likely you made a profit
Items
Destined for math
Not
Sara Lee.
I don't know that yeah that's that's all I could find in the the article about the disposition
Navigate I don't know
Entirely
If you like reoffended
Because that conditional discharge is basically like
Suspended
Kind of thing
If you get arrested again
We can recharge
Okay
For a certain
Reminder time
Then you just have this Vine
I don't know
I don't know how I feel about it I think it's probably not
But whatever local cases
Someone else definitely say they would Alex is doing
I don't I don't know about
Skorts
So Alex
When I listen to this episode
Alex's vibe
Of the religiosity and endgame stuff
Really can't
The show went on
It started to make
This first guy
Fairly clear
Why he's endgame
Why is getting back to it
Because this gas
He's somebody who is an expert in endgame
Type
Narrative
Snow
Rosa koire
She wrote a book called behind the green mask
Agenda 21
Channel 21
Get her on the show now
Haha
So
She's on and they just talked about Jen
121 and Highway
Takeover plan
It's a lot of a griffin
And so I
Isolated Vista
Got clip because I think it's won the most specific thing
Recess
I think
To this
You can see what they're trying to attack
When they attack
AccuWeather
They make accusations of Agenda 21
You need to show up an occupied of government development
Let them know that you know what it is economy
Break that down
So the argument is essentially
This
Who is the u.s.
Is that are under the eye
Do you want to be local forces
Plan is ecology, me and social Equity time
Things are involved
Ecology equity
Anytime you have a local thing
And so you have to fight back against
Involved
The intersection of
Economy ecology and social equity
And if you do that what you do
Not good stuff
Automatically
Things that you're again
I proposed this Council that to we limit the ability of Coca-Cola to put pollution
Okay well then I guess we can
That's a perfect
That is the utility
This sort of argue
And that's what you
Please bring to the table
But I would spend a lot of time
You should about Agenda 21 with this
Rosa Corey
She's up a group called The Democratic
For a Democrat to hang out with a lot of right-wing
Sing us a bulk of her media appearances that I can
Can find her on Alex's show
Hanging out with Glenn Beck
And of course appearing on the overtly white nationalist show right Red Ice Radio
Their particular complaints about Agenda 21
Alex's in Roseville
Pretty boy
Ramble about how it's the governor
Let's plan to take over everybody
I want to tell you a little bit about what you
I need to know about
First things first we discuss this matter in overtime to the Past
Babadook
Chris called the Earth Summit
Held in Rio de Janeiro
June 3rd and 14
Would have been funnier if they held it on the moon
They would have
Certainly
Agrees implementation of
Parts of this
Suggested sustainability measures
Discussing the reporter entirely up to the
Individual um
There's no expectation to Country
Saturday
Based on this report
Is crucially important thing to understand
How about this
It was never
Secret it was made public during its
Into secretly
December 9th
And that's the State of Affairs in the world were markedly different
Cold War attended there's a sense of hope surround
In the future
Those poor dumb bastard
The world was still dealing with the Fallout from the energy
Covid-19
70s
Illustrated
Problem with energy
And that problem is going to be made worse
Developing
To the world
Strategies
It would be unacceptable
To say something like these countries aren't allowed to develop
Industries of the realm
They did they did it with the same Technologies
Used the pollution overall damage to the environment would be
Chesterfield
You can't have fridges
This was not an issue that
Could be solved with unilateral decision
A required everyone work
Was needed
And sustainable development became a topic of
Late 80s early 90s
Alternatives to fossil fuels became more widely can
A recycling
The public
It's in this setting that the Earth Summit was held
And Agenda 21
It's just a plan but the UN was encouraging smaller governmental bodies
Create their own sister
There were suggest
Alex
Some kind of evil States
Because
Treats private property rights as something
Be balanced with
Environmental issues
Rural development issues and concerns
Indigenous people
As opposed to how Alex
Seized property rights
As the most important thing other than gun
That Alex
Has
That problem
People who have property
Pretty I'm always interested to know what I would be like
More than
I don't even own two pairs of shoes
I don't have proper
No that's
The Shoe Right Market
This concern about the
Or at least
Conditional aspect of private property rights is a big part of Alex's problem with
The agenda 20
Proposal
Also the opposition
Involved
They're opposed to anything that involves climate
Explain why a
21 activist
Show me hard right
Nearest associated with roofs
American policy
City Center the Heritage Foundation
John Birch Society
Eagle Forum
But that doesn't
White rose
Corey
Ostensibly a Democrat
Is also opposed
To Agenda 21
She's good friends
Joe manchin
Private property rights and the paranoia surrounding them
Generally the exclusive territory of the right
So if I'm just very
Confusing
There's one other group
The super in the property rights
You know I real killers you know what Cory's career was before she became a public Champion for agenda
She was a quick commercial real estate appraiser
Specializing
Business of using eminent domain to dry for private use by commercial interest
Direct opposition
The government's parceling land
Republic
Which is an element of sustainable
In what Public Works
Excuse that she was involved in she said quote
I was able to put together the players
What was influencing restrictions
It was related directly to agenda
Sustainable development
So she'd crack
I wonder if the
She is receiving a
Further funding
People who are
I'm not entirely sure I couldn't find any strong
Indications of that so I would be remiss
Indication
All the players involved
Solved the problem
It seems
Mostly she did that by creating two
Deceptively named organizations
You two look like legitimate neighborhood group
But we're probably just
She's literally a Russian troll
Who started the Santa Rosa neighborhood coalition
Begin agitated which is definitely not the same thing
The very real Santa Rosa neighborhood alliance
Who's
You said you believed that roses group
Carafe
Inkay
KB and Roses partner who is a general contractor
Find work
Coincidentally aligned interest
Rosen K filed a frivolous lawsuit against
Santa Rosa gateways Redevelopment
Which cost the taxpayers
And delayed the plan for
For three years
Bentley achieve nothing
Other than that her strategies
To be just to show up at local government planning meeting
The disruptive
That is intense
Escoria said quote
These public meetings are truly designed to stop you
People from having an opportunity for input
The only way to block a thing is to really shut down
I really wish you hadn't gone
Pro with
Quit being a lunatic
Council meeting should be stopped by somebody
Screaming
Conspiracy theory
But not all
Probably doesn't agree with you
Probably inform Sarah.
Corey is an embodiment of how deep
Conspiracies are destructive in real life
Settings
Opposition to anything that involves climate change
Doesn't deify private property rights
Has happened to the k
Agenda 21
Is grow up around the planned or anything
Is your city putting in a new park
Agenda 21 is your city trying to put bike Lanes
Framework of the conspiracy is accepted
You saying that it's probably
But even these people know they're talkin bullsh
Outside of Infowars
Behind
Program
Agenda 21 vet
Convinces them to do so
Sure
County Alabama on November 6th
2012 all nine members of the planning and zoning
In protest
Weather comprehensive development plan
It wasn't killed over budgetary concerns or anything like that
It was a result of tons of people accusing their plan to be
Too close to Agenda 21
And protesting their meeting with
The county needed to develop
Cuz between 1990 and 2000
Increase in population
Percent
Quotes for popping up everywhere
Little consideration given
How many projects
Would fit with
Each other the environment
Future
These nights
Problem
And they were shouted conspirators
These people
AR
Exactly how do we coexist
With
Leggett there's got to be a way
For us too
Like you can still have your
Not allowing you to influence
Maverick
Do we test
Like
Dismantle Fox News
No I don't think so I think
I don't know
I'm obviously wrong but my answer always
Just comes back to Greater education
That's
So anyway I
Text clip
I would say that Corey
Is cuz her last name
Misspelled korir
I keep forgetting how to pronounce it as I look at it
Courrier
She's expressing in this club song
Expresses a lot
Real
Salacious way of thinking
It's the sort of idea that like
People are attacking me therefore I am
Is it dangerous
Dangerous mentality
We do have them on the run when you start
That's what I know I'm winning Twitter actually out there talking about
20 years you know you're winning
Again it wasn't a secret like it wasn't
Don't denied that it
Exist your interpretation of
And I will
So f****** Danger
Better give like I'm getting criticism that means I'm right
Criticism
You're terrible
You can get criticism
Or if you're getting criticism cuz you're creating
Fake groups of concerned citizens
I'm trying to bully
City Council
People say creating fake group
And lying to people
Disrupting canceled
People say those are
And that's how I
I believe
Probably the reason Alex's
In his
MD MedSpa
Possibility in order to prepare for her being there
Is homework on
He does his homework on him so I don't remember what it is
I don't want to read her book
I'll just I'll just watch endgame and assume she said the same stuff I did also Alex
Just trying to sell his
Infowars magazine
Something right
And then he have another guest
It comes in
Starts to give
Understanding of why
In the religion
Really into
To talkin about post
Trib rapture
Mr. t
Exactly
Intro
It's because the leadership.
The tribulation
I'm not particularly interested in talking about what the Bible does or doesn't say because I feel like that's just going to work
Send it to a
He's also not recommended
So
Alex has gas
Infowars.com
Obama
Steve Anderson
Aggressively
Remember
Doing some biblical praying for Obama
Brought down
Houses of carbon that is really an Oculus
People just pray for the president to be quote
Brought down Pat Robertson or Jim Bakker do that everyday
Probably
You could describe as like
You're not
Robertsons
Second Amendment people to take
Take care of Obama's a little bit too far
Steve Anderson
In 2009 the day before Obama was scheduled to make an appearance
Clear exclamation
Heated Obama
How do you spell that Obama could not be
Please save
So praying for it was point
Well then
Quote
I'm not going to pray for his good
I'm going to pray that he dies and goes to hell
When I go to bed tonight that's how I'm going to pray
The next day I Do by Christopher Brock
Showed up with a loaded
Obama's
Which ultimately was probably more of a CR
Anything else
Then a pastor
Be free of a government
Depressant
This isn't praying for Obama's death from the pulpit
One of the people who was
In the congregation
Speech showing up at Obama's speech the next day with a loaded weapon
The PR stunt is a
Threat
Exactly
They were
That's what they were doing
And they did a good job
I mean good job is
A weird way to put it but yeah
Incredibly homophobic
Well he's the one who used to go on Alex's show but now hates them
Boring
We got a deep well if people to fall from their right
A little fun update on Stevie
First person ever to be banned from Ireland
Good good for him I was just on the heels of a lens
The last Americans band
From the other ones were Richard Spencer and devout races
Taylor Swift company
These are just the 26 European countries that ban
I plan to visit on a tour and they're like no
Countries in South Africa
As countries where that piece of s***
Welcome
We can get rid of him right when you remove his citizenship
Within their borders
Open arms
YouTube
YouTube YouTube channel
Twitter Risa was a Twitter account
Twitter
Nuts
Little fake hair
Do not care
Set a reminder
Jason calixto
Talking going for it talking about post-trib rapture
Can you go back to this
Exactly
Yeah yeah yeah don't worry about it
Pre-trib rapture globalist
Faricy Theory
Barbarian
Badabun
That makes
The least sense of anything I can
No sense from a
Liquid like from a strategy standpoint
It makes no sense from a
A goal
He gets a call
Who wants to talk about
Carroll Quigley
The book tragedy and Hope
It whatever
He just talks about a passage that I'm positive we talked about
This before it's
Completely misrepresented
This caller is misrepresenting
Quickly is talking about historically
The difference between
Arrows that are characterized by
Complex and simple weather
Embarrassing
Web
Ease-of-use for people like
Spears
Or something along those lines
Then you have a situation where power is much more
Because people are able to fight with
Each other have the weapons
Together in
Have conflicts
A more specialized
Becomes
Power
Can tend to become much more
Concentrated
Alex
Read that and think
Well
That means I want to create specialized weapons in order to create
Consolidation
And authoritarian power
This is how history attended to go
Yeah so anyway I don't really care too much about that
But Alex do point out that he and his buddies
Completely stole the intellectual property of Carroll Quigley
Associated
There were
The caller from Australia called
What's on the page
Alex
Personal private property
Intellectual property
Pretty rights
So I mean Carol Quickly's book only printed so many copies
Scholarly texts
The copy
I wasn't
Demand for the
So
Alexandra Patriots
Started reprint
Is a direct violation of personal
Believe their own principles what it comes
Some sort of wave they can
Disseminate messages
So
Search for that wonderful
The basement psychedelics cells
Got tragedy and Hope
This is the fact that he thinks
Carroll Quigley has admitted the entire Global is playing
In this book
All the time
You might think that is red
Squid
He shows himself to be like a college sophomore
Talking about inter
Janet Jackson
Illusion of choice
Libertarianism
In what possible world does an Alex Jones exist
Hasn't read the entirety of a guy admitting
The global plan
Alex Jones
Can't possibly believe that this is
Sincerely
Admission to the global plan
Not make
That's unacceptable it is the way everybody
That's on except
Because it you or me.
Doesn't finish portrait of an Artist as a Young Man
Whatever
If you're a f****** person
And you haven't finished it
Go fuc yourself I'm like that undercuts
Scholarly credit the subject matter
Expert on it
You better Goddamn well it finished the book
Because how could you not
How could you not
YouTube
Do you remember Freddy multiple times 13
It's like I'm not really into
You know what I mean I'm glad I like I like James
Give me out on that
That's a completely different area scholarship totally fine with that I'm not finding that person 10%
Dollar Tree in the prescribed
F***** up moment
Obituary
How dare he on I-96
Yeah what are you going to do I had to go f******
Yeah I assumed he had hearing him say it out loud is such a b
I want you to lie to me quite
Yeah we we coming to this with an agreement that you pretend to at least believe the b*******
I know what other people have told me about it
And I can make all the conclusions in the world that I want that I've read
I know the people who are and I really don't think they've read it
Have you bring really long
I think he's probably read like six or seven
Yeah that makes sense
The relevant that are misrepresented
Yes
Which is a big frog
Yeah and the only person that we can guarantee is right it is skousen
Because that's the only way I'm not.
I'm not sure you read the whole thing
Well the whole thing is long 1307
Maybe that's it
So it is with Alex
Discusses like
Okay so this call or called in
He was talking about the
Fun stuff in tragedy and Hope
And Alex had a vague memory of
Of that
He says right here we don't want
These
Send stuff like a level of
Quick recovery
Of a memory
I guess that
Beginning of Wiz
Right brevity is the soul of wit and of vague memory is the basis of wisdom
Yeah that sounds right that's not good
Overdrive
The beginning of the show
Because this guy brings up Carol quickly
And Alex gets really excited
To try and remember what
What about
Yeah or at least gather his
No into this post-trib rapture
Souhegan
Steve just
It's not Jerome corsi level
It off quite well.
Play The pre-trib Rapture
Everybody of course
Of course
Episode
Alex's Pizza
You got to give it to all your pastor
A word comes up
Become
Sort of relevant to us recently
Discern
Black snakes
Actually understand the Bible
Well
That's the
Is discernment of coded word that we're not aware of
We got discernment somehow I think there is a religious connotation
Because I don't
Necessarily think
Use and when like Kevin Moore
Or carry
Sara Lee
Similarly but there is a religious code
For sure it is there is something something
But discernment very very important for liar
Really powerful and useful way to make
Make people distrust their own intuition
Because like you might have read the Bible and have your ideas
Discern things
Cred
For your discernment
Mcrad people to over
Override their own
Tuition Durham
Perspective
If I know better
They have good dessert
Eclipse
And they are
Jumped
Steve
Weird things about
Bible
The first
About weapons
He talks about every single
And then also even Jesus Christ
Alright everybody got swords
82nd Amendment
Cool
That
Religion
Government
Prescribed by the Bible
Romans 13 is really clear
About what the purpose of government is
Which is the punishment of
Exactly
Exactly right
Enforce the government
To regulate Our Lives
Here's the problem with it as a Libertarian
Based on principle
If that guy is stupid
Steven says God.
Didn't say that the government can regulate Our Lives
But how do you enforce the non-aggression principle without regulator
We talked about it when we made fun of
The idea of the non-aggression principle applied
Universal
Involved
Deep regulation of businesses
In terms of pollution
Because
You can't can't initiate you can initiate the second
Smoke on people
Because that is in the Gresham
You'd have to ask
Completely regulate solution.
So many aspects
People's life
You wouldn't be able to cars
So a government that operated off that
That God would be
Involved
Intense
Regulation
So that's kind of a little bit of vodka
Which is like
Apply to Thai
Post-trib rapture
A Rapture stop and personally I don't really care about those are
You know what I'm saying
Post-trib rapture
Comes from like
Suggest that to just because you're personally.
Rapture before the tribulation
It doesn't mean that the natural conclusion is
It's just not caring allowing evil system stakeholding heard everybody
No I'm pretty sure that's
What's morally cool with what God wants
People work to feed the poor whose hunger they can't person
Feel
So his idea that knowing the Rapture is coming means you shouldn't resist
Simplistic and self-centered on its face
I don't think that
It's a accurately depicts what a lot of Christian
Believe
Is what motivates
Experience
I believe there's a lot of people who
The Rapture be pre-tribulation
Would still alive
It wouldn't change their
Perspective Alex
Very much narcissist
It should just give you a sentence
Reading colors on
He talks about Australian guy
Who wanted to bring up Carol
But for the most part
It's more like this
For Alex to a call at the end of the show music is playing
I just wanted to shake you God bless you
Call Pastor Anderson
That is a solid way to get a collar off of whatever it is they wanted to say a right onto like
Yeah we'll see you next
Yep
This show is really upsetting to me
Because there is
Trend
Bo of the religiosity and the end
Stop
Each of these could be
Explained by one of these
Still doesn't make
F******
Different
From January
January 3rd
January 29th
It is
Varied
All the stuff you was talking about is been left aside there is no Piers Morgan talk
Barely any Obama's the devil
Maybe the devil
Impeachment talk in the
He's been focusing
There's very little event
They're going to take our guns
This is one of the
I think this has happened at least once maybe
Two or three time
Every
We've done where it's been like
Okay well this episode
For some reason
Parked in between this long string of b*******
Is Evergreen you have no idea what
Evergreen
Exist
Weirdly
Detached from the
This rounded contacts
Satisfying for me on many levels because
I want to understand
I think it just shows us
Has these ideas that have been
They are forever
Inspirations of his inability or unwillingness
To do any kind of research
Topix
Claims to be Expo
The no King
Claiming it comes from
The revolution
American Revolution John Adams
Absolutely not
He's just accepted quote-unquote
Patriot lure
About it
He has not read Carol quickly book by his own admission he's tried and failed to read
To be an expert
Dr. Eric
Pianca he claims he looked into his live show but it's f***
But he's talking about. A pile of Rwandan
This is b*******
Even if it is a bottle episode we get
Nothingness
Sara Lee in terms of
The grander picture of his Sandy Hook
It's still worth it
Memphis's of his ability
Yeah this is just been a long string
The hymn
Just really not knowing
Anyting
George Jefferson
Set timer
I do feel that way about
Website
Go to bed we are also on the iTunes
Which I guess will no longer be something that were on anymore
Since it won't exist very shortly
Apple podcast
I don't know dude
I don't know
Alright fine I'll get on Spotify
Just come to the end
And I would say
Eric Pianka
You killed anybody
AmeriPride
Little bit of
Sensational speaker
Prone to
Skeletor's ranking
Pretty cranky
I appreciate that
Probably has
Alex