Alex
Little bit about Alex Jones
Tallest
Highest you know like
What are my buddy
We are in the backyard
Which we would not be able to do prior
Could you could you
Drink yourself to passed out later so after just like
Is constantly smoking weed kind of got bored
That wasn't you asked me but
It is a story
I also feel like a week after that we were finding little chunks of
That we have just dropped
Cuz you kept rolling in
Weed
To the top of skyscraper
Chicago play on building
Sears Tower
Put on cliffs
Yeah you can Grease
When I was there
I don't know
OfficeMax
The Hawaii
This one wasn't a grease
Me and my brother were supposed to jump off of a check it out
Tell Sarah rocks down there anybody else
Yeah I was it was
The one who I was a bit smaller in knots
As the water looked
I'm not super afraid of heights
But I'm not into
That's not the highest parasailing
Oh really
Coronavirus
Probably building is hiring
I think so
A buddy of mine had a wedding
At the top of the Aon building
That's fun
The woman who is marrying is very rich
Aon building
Chicago me and my girlfriend
Chicago
For real for that wedding
So weird
Down to the bottom to smoke
For most people
I think there were enough of us that
Cisco smoke in the corner over there now
Weird every time I've ever been
The highest I've ever been high
Best Buy Casper in a lot about Heights
Alex Jones
Episode
Of the podcast the present day
It is
4th and 5th 2019
Some real weird stuff happens and I'm comfortable saying
Two episodes
I've heard in a very long time
Tired of myself making Proclamation
Like I would never
Oh it's real up there Alex is very weird
Yeah you do occasionally have a bit of a Carson like every night you have the greatest
Put myself in a certain pattern but like I like
Stuff made me gas
I've been doing this for a while
The kind generosity and support of our listeners and
First
Jordan
I'm a policy wonk Greg
I'm a policy wonk
Angry Bird
Text Petra
Somebody who donated on
So go black
Heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
So maybe just like municipal building
Calculate clovelly X
So much if you were at there listening or taking headlights for the show it like with these guys
Super buck.
We start off on the 4th
Alex
Begin the show talking about it's not really all that sucked up
We can tell that he's head is not right
It's getting real pervy kind of about a topic that is not f*****-up at all and is not pretty
You'll see what I mean
Veritas
We have been trying movers here on are the audience clapping
Parkers Lighthouse
And myself at law firms that I paid
To follow my own research ideas
That reflected the reality
I didn't just make it up the last 3 years
Control
I watch today
It's
USA Today
Presidential office
Turn the music up
I love that song.
Whatever
Can't not have the feeling
He's talking about is the houses
Opened up the
Possible
Investigations in
Facebook Amazon Google
Pretty much
People across the political aisle
Probably like
Anti-competitive practice
Says they're being
Turn out the competition
I hate to assume before an investigation
I don't think breaking up
Dances that are found to be acting
Monopolist
Yeah but what Alex is doing is he's complaining house investigation with
Campaign rhetoric
The trumps been putting a
Because I realize that he doesn't really have a
Into the 2020 election without the support of the agitators on
People who are like the Alex Jones's of the 2016 election
In order to maintain
Support
Thinks he needs to do is give lip-service
So a bunch of them feel like they're being unfairly censured for their kin
Conservative positions
On the social media platform
Does
His you know he gives that conservatives are being unfairly targeted
You can sleep this campaign rhetoric that Trump is putting out
With this house investigation
And you turn it into
These
Companies are being investigated for
The unfair treatment of
When in reality old Trump is doing is trying to create this season's version
End of lock her up
Jessie
Victory Alex
Anyway
It's weird cuz that issue is not something
They would make a normal people growl
You can tell like if he's covering this story that way
Lookout
We talked a little bit more about the Social Media stuff
Before he gets
Real real
F****** out there
He's talking about the social media
Stop
Contacts
In which
Scuffing it
Should lead you to believe that
Not right
Design for the global Chinese social score to control human behavior
Anyway you slice it
Where you'll get the US
Areas
Is the China
Helping build the architecture of this and that apple
Google
One year ago
No they didn't say that
The Chinese customers
Which is that we should
Soto
It was the entire world
More important
Beginning
In some way this social media is what was prophesied
I don't think he's wrong
I don't think you would talk that way at all if you still want it
What's the difference for you and I
Maybe this is the coming of the Beast
I still have a Facebook
I've got kicked off YouTube still recognized
Westerly wood
If you didn't have a business interest
So in this next clip
What we've got is Alex apologizing
He's not covering
Too much news
It is not forgiven
The world route
I would argue it's too difficult for him to
Emotionally difficult
Action News here
I wondered why I don't cover a lot of this everyone.
Get ready for hours at home and I get ready for
Hours
The reason he said for an hour here and
He's trying to say like 4 hours before
Is because recently there was a new story about how some of these depositions
Of other Infowars employees
There's an article about that for the
Alex gets the story before he goes on air
Claimed that here
Here I do it for an hour
Workout gear
You should be honest that he doesn't do that much work because it's so much worse than Magic
And this is the product more tolerable
No
Off and on
The left is so evil
And socrate just show into doing that
I want you to run away from that comes looking for you
Runaway inflation
They're going after the children
Here's an example
So
He's got I can't I can't cover these
News because
S*** is to
Difficulty
Just want to run away but
But you can't run away
Because the coming after the kids
Here's an example
McDonald's
This is got to be some
Next Level s***
That is
Completely f*****
His world.
Do you want to get to the story that you seemed like you had a thought
Let you know
Isn't his version of running away not
Talking about the news at all
So when he says he wants to run away but you can't
I mean he is
It's a constant active
Running away
Whose life is just a cop
I'm going to look over here
Is a complicated game of Escape
He does
Dictate sort of the ACT
Of pretending
Discover something is his way of Escape
He's just he's just an Escapist
Performance
Kind of
So here's a good way to
Text
Accidentally
Lobster here's the story that he's trying
Cover
Is ground shake
If this is a pretty big deal
Bubonic plague leprosy drug-resistant TV
It's spreading into children everywhere
California
Leprosy
Cisco
And places like that celebrated
Coming up next shower
San Francisco's watching
Restaurant where you eat was you at your table
She can enjoy the Ambiance of the rats and celebrate
Just kidding infestation
Don't worry
Cesar rescue rats
San Francisco dungeon
Launching
Do you want to be
Sunshine
Good read
Let's eat with rats
How to lower ourselves
Do you like that
God
This Force doesn't like that
Jealousy
Head
Human so they want us to eat with rats
Okay alright alright this is a little bit out of left field saying but I like that your I like the
Still brainstorming very creative
Crafty Old Scratch
Up to his tricks again a medieval times but with rapping
Whatever
Point very
Seriously
Before I get out of it
Alex Jones is so pathetic
In 2019
Ifucking restaurant where they got a bunch of rats running around it somehow celebration of a globalist
Are giving kids a leprosy or some s*** Next Level laser
This legitimately just alyx looking over a list of like 50 headlines and some kind of a weird news aggregator
Hey picking out the ones that he feels natural in his voice
Then just riffing on it
That's all
He's doing here
This is his workflow
And you know that because he knows literally nothing about the stories covering except the surface-level s*** that you get from a headline
Hero rats in a bar in San
Francisco
Woo
Is a pop-up installation to be open
From June 13th
Jeep 215
It's not it's not a bunch of restaurants it one
Pop up
A group called the San Francisco dungeon which is Alex it looked into it is basically a mini theme park at Fisher
Gwar
The big tourist destination in San Francisco
Includes
The bunch of
Barriers where actors portray characters to give customers the immersive Theatre Experience
Most of the rooms to pick famous aspects of San Francisco History
Like two of them are about the gold rush
But not necessarily about the glamorous
Recreation of Alcatraz
A1 dedicated to the outbreak
The plague in Chinatown
There's even one experience at the golfer called Shanghai Kelly's boat ride
Where you learned about the lives of people who were sold as slaves
So they're putting on the ramp bar as a supplemental thing to their other attractions
And it's meant to recreate the experience of being in a saloon back in the time
Before
And all that kind
Honestly it seems like a little bit of a PR stunt to me but who knows I could see haven't
I'm not so jaded that I couldn't
Agree to go along to an escape room or something like that and someone invited me I'll never come up with the idea
I would probably say yes
Same thing with rat bar
Also they did the same thing last year when they open something called the rat
The only review I can find it at said it was disappointing and there was not enough contact with the rat
Tuesday like you might not know what these people are up to
Search
If your head
Hello
Yeah
Animal cruelty
Storyworth covering
He's in a fight to the death
China
But he's going to spend any of the globalist
She tried to normalize leprosy by opening a novelty bar for 2 days where adults go play with rats
What the f*** is he doing is he forgotten
How intensely he decried attacks them
So stupid
It's crazy
Is Jesse have a trip coming up
Is there any reason why you might be phoning it in this early like as is he doing anything
I have no idea I know that he has
Like another Sandy Hook deposition coming up
Next month
Cases are proceeding
So maybe he has that Sword of Damocles hanging over his head but like
I don't know I mean
Intermittent vacation never know until Owen Shroyer just shows up so I'll be
I don't I don't know but like I was
The lead-up to that of like
It's so f****** awful to look at the news but you asked
Bar
Whiplash
I love it on something if he is
Local access new store
Like that's his version of being like
Example of
This is the dude
Terrible Eddie Musk
Avoid looking at
You know you know
College I got hired to write Ford like this
Weird
College
Upstart
Blog
There's like a collection of blogs a different University
It was horrible for long
And they never ended up
Universal experience with these sorts of things it was I would go
Play I just find some sort of right about that
Local paper for whatever headlines
This is going to be easy
That's what Alex is doing
He's using the workflow of a lazy f****** undergrad
These are 40 f******
5 year old man with a millions of dollars in a professional studio
Can't be bothered
He can't be bothered to know what the San Francisco dungeon
He thinks it's a dungeon
Yab
Man that sounds like a good place to be
He's doing his job poorly and making more money
Not be the most Pleasant
I'm surprised
Just started
Shipping stuff to some other country of Rihanna loud and that way that way you can just on a dime
Bolsonaro so much tired of freighters
So
In this next clip we get to another news story
It's not just Iraq cafes
But there are other stories
And here's one of them
And I
What is the latest news wars.com
Love has no filter
That's right
Video
Love has no age
Pepperidge Farm
30 years ago Howard Stern making jokes about November
Love has no age
North American man boy
The slogan
Pedophile organization
Cool
This is
Snapchat filter about love
Who makes statements the filter does it make
Pop up on the video on the screen
Including love has no gender love has no disability
Love has no sexuality
Love has no religion has no age
Wichita
Naturally this is taken as an endorsement of pedophilia and now Alex's beta deleting story
The article
Infowars was unable to reproduce the filter as of this writing on May Monday June 3rd
The filter was not available when search.
If possible Snapchat quiet
Birthing but I suspect
That's my guy
Did you download it
Right position I've always been tools
As long as Snapchat existed I have eight
I enjoy it 11
Yeah probably
If you search through Twitter you can find a couple
Examples of people who have screenshot
I guess it was a real thing
Distance going on today
Stories that reference this video all the news articles
Very heavy quotes news articles to talk about it
They all references video put on Twitter by Ashley sing
Claire
And she posted the video at 9
P.m. on June 2nd
Her video is tons of retweets and is without exception the one that is in all of the stories about the
Infowars natural
Hey Big League
People have been posting screenshots of themselves with this filter sets at least 12 hours
Before she made her video
But hers is the one that everyone
And I think there's a clear reason why
If you scroll through Ashley's timeline on Twitter you get a very strong indication that maybe she's a big old dumb dumb
But
Specifically
A very precise
Kind of dumb
Right next to her retweet about her expose like the article
She's retreated a picture that one is going around of Mario and Luigi making out
Dumb
Fake outrage
People on the right
And she retweeted that picture with the caption
Express disapproval
God no
There's constant pointless culture-war fake-out right rates camping
Outposts on her
Frequent trashing people like Lena Dunham
And retweets of s***
Overall it's exactly kind of account you would expect from someone who's trying to make their name in the exciting world of
The only sites that have articles about her bulshit are sites like
It's stupid right-wing Christian propaganda
So I really
Question with
Going on here
Even leaving aside how clearly this
Seems like an attempt for a budding young grifter to get her name on the map by stealing someone else's out there
I don't really see how this has anything to do with pedophilia
What are those
Scriptures of love
Listen protect
Two classes of
You can't discriminate against people based on disability or their gender a religion
For example
Like you
Pointed out
Immediately
You understand the f*** is going on
The discrimination against the elderly what's going on
I really can't find any evidence
Outside of right-wing media insisting
That proves that love has no age is actually a slogan of
Find proof that it's part of
Call swarthy who won the Nobel Prize for literature
There's a quote attributed to Pascal of Pascal's wager
There's classical examples of people who are not my knowledge
Passed out
There's also really popular book from 2011 about a Doppler
Dog
But not wanting
Just get puppies
Azusa
Who's older dogs
Need love too
Prefer if that was
It's just all about getting older.
Typically when you find the words love has no age you're finding them in stories about elderly people getting married
Like the 2015 CBS article about George Kirby
Who got hitched at the ages of 191 respect
Via headline is
Story is Dory they found from the website Texas FM
Exactly
Being about
Who got married at 87
4 years ago
With very few exceptions
Depression
Lopez
Discuss the elderly finding love
And we can all agree that that's some heartwarming
What's up with R.Kelly song AJ number
Which is very
That's quite
Downward looking perspective
A little different
I looked around I can't find any official slogan
What is the official multiple slogan I don't know
Being their official site
Group it was a predecessor of Nampa called Dee Renee
And they had a slogan that was
Quote sex by gear 8 or else it's too late
Snapchat use that on a filter
And Alex could find a little more of a middle craft
It's not your slogan
Really
In the way that Alex
If you was talking about this in the mid-70s
It's hard to even say that it's a real group
A lot of this is thanks to lgbtq
Excluded from their work
Which effectively crippled man blows ability to present themselves as
Because they try to latch onto right ascend
Okay I like young boys I'm a man this is a game
Is lgbtq
Exclusion for
So they should be applauded for that
By associating them
With
NAMBLA
I'm selves into that associate
Coming from both
Aggressively
Tips
Straight people verse
Creative login
To use the opportunity of
People take
More seriously as an opportunity
Opportunistically using
Kajol to hit the lgbtq community
Using
Things as props
Newport
Unusual
Over the years the FBI infiltrated the group Nablus fairly easily in
Sting operation
Read out that effectively made the group irrelevant as an organization
People who would have joined we're now too afraid to do so
Just lurk in sucked up corners of
Internet
Groups of mailing list which can be hacked easily
In 2016 device didn't investigation that found that does pretty much nothing
Even a representative for an a
Anti pedophile group called perverted-justice
Express having no real interest
Send them anymore
Because the face of the real threat
The children is not an organized
Group like NAMBLA
Elsewhere
I think this is another example of Alex's being super lazy and relying on him
Information from
Like 30 years ago
The craft is correct
Conspiracies
Is very dumb
Very bad it's job
And I can't imagine anybody
Not recognizing what that filter was
Unless they were trying
Make a fake out
Like if those other ones weren't there you got an
That's weird they just had
Because of religion disability
Like
Lyrics about protector
Two classes
Ashley
Claire is doing
Is
We're going around
12 hours before she made her video
And to make sure video
Falsely
Characterizing this
Is a pedophile sympathetic
And if you look at your timeline it's really clear that the motivation is probably too
Space
Enloe
World that she swims in
And the story does kind of have a happy ending
Yeah because of this manufactured outrage
Ashley Stewart
And she was allowed to write her first call them with a byline for human events
Alex's lawyer Robert Barnes is involved in
That's not good work
So I think you can kind of see what's going on here you have an enterprising grifter
Who is made her first
Dent in the world
It's exciting I'm thrilled to see her
Publicly that'll be great
It's about how our life is ruined
Get to play the cycle all over again congratulations
Yeah she really should have watched the Laura Loomer stuff
Maybe I should
Change my life in
There's a cautionary Tale 2
All of this stuff
So in the middle of show Alex
Play the report
From John bowne
But this this
F****** Special Report was really
Big 4
Because I think it put into focus a lot of the feelings that I have about Alex
Watershed couple minutes
Yeah I really did and I think it's
Accidental and negative
For Infowars surprise
This
Special Report
He's mostly just
Old clips of Ali
From back when he was on
Turn on his early radio.
Almost like this is your life
To take him off
Second part of it
Where Alex is talking about
Military
And listen to this compared to him yelling about a rat Cafe
That
Complicated
Position is really important
We're now here in Southern California
A little town called Victorville located
Acquire the Air Force Base
More Middleman
For the Chinese military industrial
This again is the first
Facility to be built
Pretty restrained
On-site
He's doing a Fieldpiece
Yeah man got it sure seems like that's the guy you want to go back in time and talk to and be like hey
Hey I'm going to show you this video
And he's going to break down
I listen to this special report
Special Report
Honestly I thought it was the best worker John pounds done
Primarily
Edited all together
Reaction to this was astonishment
It's so insane for Alex to play clips
Deteriorated
You can hear it completely
Different person
His voice is different his manner is different his
Ability to present ideas
Mpq them juxtaposed with his current state is a severe bummer
If I were Alex watching I would probably start crying
Yeah but even more importantly I really think
Exact opposite
Point that they're trying to
It's being presented as a collection of insta
Power over the entire course of his career
He wasn't afraid to talk about black helicopters
He's calling out the Rockefellers and the Rothschilds before it was cool
This is being presented as an explanation for now why he's being kicked on social media
But all it really doesn't prove he's expressing in that video or categorical
He would have been banned long ago
Everybody was totally fine with it for years
David Rockefeller had no idea who Alex was
You didn't give a s*** about it
Oz full of s*** in a little bit crazy
Except for people who have way more important things
To do with their time than sue him or pay him any attention
And that status quo is
Maintainable
Then
Conspiracies
The conspiracy theories about fluoride about Waco about 9/11
Those are all directed at the Powerstroke
They may be misguided and wrong but on a fundamental level security
In the bush
Inspiration
In the conspiracy world is the equivalent of punching up
I'm certain that it wasn't the first example of it but what
Behaviorist related
Sandy Hook
And his inability to accept responsibility
Is because it's such an example of him taking his skills
Power structure
Hey coming down hard on victim
Whose loved ones have been murdered
It's an ugly thing to see you watching the report
Is what fuels differ
About the Alex likes we started doing this show
In the end of 26
You watching this
Why I felt different
For one I used to watch him
Like it just after college
It's that differ
Everything is done
General experience the earlier Alex Jones is way easier to listen to because victimizes people in power
He's super unfair to them
About what he's doing
Easier to stomach
At some point he stopped giving
He started victimizing powerless people and that's his stock-in-trade
Whether it's random members of the lgbtq
Q community
Whether it's Muslim
Victims of gun violence
How is it they were David Rockefeller themselves
And that's what's gotten him into trouble
That's what this John bowne report accidentally makes total
Clear
Alex's imagined enemies
Punches at them
And make a living off his body
Doesn't like bullies
And that's what he's
I know that no one's paying as close attention
Created a damning indictment of our
His b******* about the Chinese and the globalist need to get him off the air because he's critical of them
Is undercut biased
Compilation including clips of him shiting on China
Way back in the VHS days
He's b******* about the EU and you and being a
Afraid of him
And always criticism is undercut by prove them always criticize
He even includes footage of him exposing the truth Globus false flags at a point where he was left alone and allowed to grow as big
For 15 more years
What I'm getting at
Report but it really
Made so clear to me
Is the crystalline differ
Of why it's so much more palatable
Go back
Wayback
It's so clear
Keep punching up
Yeah and I don't know Sandy Hook is the exact Line in the Sand
When everything changed
He started punch
I think that's why I'm so interested in that
As a Time
. and why I'm sticking with it
Victor 2009
Invicta rise of the tea party stuff
Became such a
Warm-baths
2B hair
Harsh differences present
Even from what we've seen
In the 23rd
Investigation
Sandy Hook
Changing point
He had that caller on one of those Monday episode
Who was trying to get him
To talk about Robbie Parker being an actor
Responded
I'm not talking about someone whose family died
Kid got murdered
The fact
Is such a marked difference
I don't know they don't take John to those thoughts
To that was
It was a ride
He had bounced
Seems to have created a
Clip
An edited video of all the reason
That Alex wasn't kicked off
You know where you could have saw those when they were made
Suspicious
I appreciate his voice
Not really being in it
Double hats
That is
Because
If you weren't kicked off social media right now and that same clip show work
To be made
I'm like if you weren't being sued by
Sandy Hook or or anything
He would almost certainly have all of the false
Because that's part of why the 11th
America
We talked for a long time
Have any of that stuff
It's clear
It's so clear
So clear
Respect
Define
When I jumped in on this episode
Cuz it certainly wasn't
The Noir was there at Cafe
Alex
Jumps a new narrative
Should Wild
He remembers something
He read
The past shouldn't be allowed to remember things
The last 45 minutes since I saw these two articles videos
Defy
There's just so much
It was a vice piece
T-shirt
It was about 2 years ago
Better. She was an actress but she really did it
Something like five shares piece of woman saying abortion feels good in
And she's doing a fake orgasm
Wilder killing a baby going
So this
Is an interesting memory that Alex has
Of source material
Doesn't formed a bit of his rhetoric about abortion
I think we can agree that this isn't too far afield from some of the stuff you normally says
Coming out
With this
I would really want to know exactly what I was referencing I would not want to come out with
Some b******* like
This lady is having an orgasm while getting an abortion and say I think I remember something
From all of my abilities
Stop looking at
Use conflating
Get into that but here Alex
Released
Figure out what
What he's thinking about
What am I thinking of you got to find that
Abortion table
How wonderful it was not right one
Hoping the system
Woodland Caster in bigger roles
So
Memories are weird
Certainly
Sacrifice
Both equally satanic things to do with the red doesn't
You're just
You can hang your not where the
Price of baby
Turns out
So Alex
He has this vague memory of something we're like women are orgasmically enjoying abortion
And he finds
The article
Betty's
Forum
Is one of the crazier thing
But I think I've ever heard
Abortion
It's not just because I'm killing a baby
So he's going to read this article
But also
You heard that
There it is
Yeah there is a sense of familiarity and I think that's incredibly important
There's actually nerve centers in the back of the uterus
I can be stimulated to regular intercourse
Wow they're fetishizing killing babies
To visit a clinic
Have my vagina
Speculated scooped out like the bottom of a big cherry pie
On
Pictures of satanic panic
I'm a stupid baby
Do you found it
Let's go back
So
That article is
That's that
ReadWorks
It's like that
I will get you to Alex start talking about these demons
Because he has to wait for his remember what
I would prefer it if I never heard him say the word coming again
Cuz that really don't want to do that could you cut that out
I can't
Which does exist
As an article
We find out
The demons
How to do a certain
Something that Alex
Talk about a whole lot
Alex seems to know what happens
If you do what
These demons say
This makes me really convinced Alex killed his dog
Getaround
Satanist are in trailer park still under dog
So I can see demons
Which bottle I do
What
Helicopters
For not very long
Are they just wanted to know
That's like they gone to the Rock Cafe
I don't know how you know that when you kill your dog to evens pop up until you to do really bad thing
And not only that but you just threw it
Demons do pop up from
The problem
He specifically pointing out
It's not the lsbpie accidentally killing
He's just
Hey by the way
It also seems weird because
Man that's no good
So convince
Kill dogs
Like it just it does kind of occupations
I just started out as a joke
When I asked
And now I think we all know where no
D.
Investigation
Michael Vick of the right-wing media
I don't know
The bortion
Derisively because when I tell you what's going on here
Not something that needs to be taken seriously
But Alex
Is taking this
Quite series
Having orgasm
Lindsey Cooper 2
Came out of my plane
Come really hard when I get an abortion
Please stop that
Especially the bottom of injury
Deliberating
Adrenaline rush
Jumping
Snapchatting
Opportunity to go to his other narrative
Final equation
They give their children the fires of Molech and Baal
He even changed his tone of voice dimensional transmission control system
They're falling like why are they doing this
Because their spirit
That might be true for you
Hunter's Pandora heartbreak
This article that Alex's reading on are as evidence that women are sexualized
Is it supposed to snow today
Starting in July 2013 and started posting articles that are clearly satire
On this Thought Catalog page
His first article headline is quote
Gay stuff homophobic is disrespectful to people with phobias
The articles are so clearly trolling literally zero investigation
Here are some of his other head
Tell Chinese people that new years was a month ago
Quote is anyone else man poop is brown
You know who didn't complain about minimum wage
But slaves
Better one
Shows racists are more likely to reput bake
Anything on this blog are complete
But their purported evidence for the dumb f*** point is actually parody of people who are
Really really turned on by that
Justify
Allenport subgroup excited
I know it's a lot of effort to just click
The block
I can't expect someone who professes to be an expert very smart and able to read
Before he reports
I think so I'm not going to
Is unnecessary
That's f****** article itself is so clearly satire
He just jumps
The page
Hear some parts
If I actually read that you're going to have to read it like
You fellows are you fellows in our little secret
Women's mammograms to prevent breast cancer
We get them because it feels good to have RTD
If you read that text
Liberal Liberal
Getting abortions orgasms during the procedure
Let me ask you this if it was wrong and unnatural why am I squirting
There's a whole part about doctors who would molest women it to treat hysteria back in the day
Anyways
It's really funny to see Alec be this
Huge
An idiot you know like
He clearly reinforces what's become like
Kasim on the show lately
He doesn't know anything
But I think there's something really scary that this
Suggest
This article by Nicole Mullen was posted on February 12th 2014
To be unfamiliar with
It seems to know of this article 23 years ago by Vice except
Show a really sounds like he's read this article years ago
There's an outside possibility
In some way
Portion
Are based on this very clearly troll
Call for a couple of
One question what level of prank or satire could be could be behind some of his other beliefs
But more importantly to
It demonstrates how far Through the Looking-Glass
Yes we are evil and f***** up thing someone who missing
Understand satire can do with that satire
I got a lot of messages from people asking me to cover this respected listeners wishes
I was happy to oblige
Story
How embarrassing
For Alex if you gave a s*** about anything
Is one of the most important aspects of these two days shows
It's fun to laugh at Alex and I fucken love doing
I've been listening to that clip of him yelling about Donuts
Repeatedly
Something recorded that episode
McKay's
. like that is missing the forest for the trees
I believe I expressed at the beginning this episode but that this show even without Alex
Clearpro blog post
Is one of the most
F*****-up detestable displays
But I've seen the last two-and-a-half years of doing this
Are clear indications that Alex
Actively trying to
He does not give a
And he uses
Some of this stuff
To reinforce the
About Alex getting
Going to get orgasm
Because it sexually pleasurable
It's funny to laugh and how bad of a job he's doing
It's important for us to listen to the rest
See where it goes
See how
What's the dangerous things
He builds on
Yeah you know maybe we shouldn't have taught some people how to read
You know what
It's an interesting thought
Rising the Irish because they ate so many babies
Like they didn't blow up Irish
The smattering of it
Sure they were just
The they didn't use them actually eating babies as a as an excuse they already hate him which is why
The satire whistle effect
Is because he was
Playing out with that
Unfortunately
Very close
Narrative
People who know about Nicole Mullen
Like they know that this is
Alex being f****** idiot never want to dance all over it
Dote
And there's no reason why Alex has
Any initiative or any reason to come on air
Hey guys
Really
Screwed up I feel right that was a troll blog
I got tricked
Sorry women are going to get abortions
Sorry guys
The correct itself
Not just continue
As if that's real
So before we get to what I was talking about how this is
This takes a turn toward
Pest duties
Videos about to slander Steve which never ends up doing
Representative
Also not
It's the author Steve King
Stephen King
I'm so confused
Oz
Never gets around to actually following
Through with this
In case you eventually does
So we know that it's very premeditated
Mist
I'm getting ready to come out
Tomorrow
In the stuff
Piece of crap
If you just talkin about Maine
Call piece of crap
Are all slaves the devil
So yeah sounds like he's talking about me information about Stephen
Stephen King's books that you'd only know if you were on the inside which
Comes off so f****** Halo after he reported on it
Your reading of Stephen King's books
I don't trust
I no longer Trust
He doesn't care either
He doesn't care what you say
I was on cocaine I was deeply it's cocaine
Maximum Overdrive
I am crazy
There's no reason why I go whatever accusations
Next
So we now
Almost immediately get to
This part where
Super duper
Chinese women come during abortion
And he's talking about how a lot of
People particularly Anderson
Cooper art
Possessed
And
It's all good
In his
Ballpark
The Anderson Cooper is
Yeah
How far have we gone off my back like water off a duck
Oh yeah
What are you talking about
Insane that should be
So interesting
Someone with the radio show called Gators and Cooper is even
That should be
Escalation vanilla and then all the sudden
DSM it takes two seconds
Escalating with the b******* millennials
Anderson Cooper's wrong two seconds later what are you going to do
It goes to this
Is
Man
This clip is 4 minutes long
The point but like
I kept I listen to this a couple times
Because I was trying to track like
Of his
Cuz they're so deeply Disturbed
Can I also was like well I could cut it to your return this
Eclipse
But I couldn't find place
Sister cut it
It's so deeply
He's booked up
If you trace his thoughts
I don't
I don't think this is legal
I really think that this is illegal
He's calling for the assassination of the person who's leaving Donuts in the office
Know you appreciate
No
Trace thought
If you agree with my assessment
That he
Is sort of
Telling his audience
That God will reward them
Anderson
Feels like it
Ambiano grass Mill
The children are
That's why these demons come after our children
Girl just pray against Anderson Cooper
Play against the enemy
God will break them out of vengeance
Milam's
God
Communications are
The dagger which.
Vengeance is mine saith the Lord
God
Doesn't use vehicles
Is there a loan debt
Because your God vehicle you're probably
Enacting God's will because
So I mean metaphorical daggers
God
God is a god of free will
God doesn't give you jobs you can complete
I might do everyday
Dollar Shave
How much you can handle let's put this much weight on you
Jesus said that Don and Aunt
Piles on
High pressure
So he's keep challenging
To the
Challenges that are put in front of you by God
Now you're at urinated a free-will cuz
Is Godzilla freeway
So if you
Become
Reagents of Gods
Vengeance
Because he needs it
If you do become that you must do it by free will
And God won't give you a time
So you do little things can work your way up to killing someone for God
Outside of the part before it that part about God not
Rising difficult
The task comes after his
Vengeance is God's vehicle for God's
Like
I can't say strongly enough
Key
Without gokil Anderson Cooper is heavily implying that someone should
Jesus's parable of the talents
Was not about becoming
God's instrument of murder is just about like stewardship incompetence
Your part
It's alright
Also he did it with his Alex did it like he was a drug dealers like
That'll give you some weight and if you can move pretty good maybe he'll give you a little bit more work that's all I'm saying
Keep raising your profile
He was using wait in that
To be like
So this goes on
Fred
Really starts
To be unclear what metaphors
I think that there is a
Piece where he realize like I've gone
Too far down
This particular path
Because the spirits feeling pretty good
On this
Tip I'll take a left onto maybe harm Anderson Cooper Plaza
I got to control myself
Let's see if I can
Figure out a way to do it
I don't think he sticks The Landing
Does it stops making sense
Really fast
You ever try to go back to the surface
You no longer a person of that
I think he's talking about the bends
Come back from where you are
Metaphor that he can jump off
You know
Go down so deep you can't come back to the surface without being change
Contextualize it is looking into the abyss
Is the metaphor for looking at evil
You look at the abyss of the Abyss looks back at you
Beautified by God's divine
You are corrupted
Directly
I can respond that all right this is where I'm going to go
I'm going to take a left
When you stare into them as a conscious being
You don't become Fallen like these.
Like
Otamatone like these Avatar
Clutch bags
What happened to the NPC meme
The richest man on earth
He's not there
Ever come back
That's something you need to know ladies and gentlemen
Don't ever come back
What about the time
From hell
Do you really want
Cross that line
Do you want to take a life
What the f*** drunk f*** I think
Every good thing in this case
I like that song
S*** there's a murder lyrics
It's unfortunate but it is reinforcing what he said earlier
Disturbing
You don't need to fear he who can
Remember
If you want some intergalactic
Space junk trash
If you want to be innocent
What like the Millennium Falcon
You can join the Dark Side
But if you want the keys to Eternity
Keys to things that the eye has not seen ears on Earth
You must reject the devil
Champs
How old is pops
Enforcers
Pops
Does it mean
That
Can I feel you are
God will show you who you are
Until you cross those bridges
Until you face those demons
You're never going to have got up on the gates up for you
I want you seen into heaven
You'll never know why people didn't join God
It's extremely painful
I'll tell you you will feel very pathetic and weak
Forgot
He will feel unending power and understanding at
Explosive
Will
But you yourself in God's presence will feel
Incredible God has
Unlimited
Cool school
Once you're in the presence of God like a relation
The Saints take the crowns off
God consciousness
Universe is so big
He was faking crying there or maybe because you didn't have time for a nap
Call me when you can
There was a
I got to find a way to jump how I have been in the presence of God
And a king's throat out
The orchestra's like Merrell we get one more than one Oscar
Speech in a fuk
I mean the part about it where it's very
Clearly
Inspirational part alone is
Like you cannot do stuff like that
Then it's
Do this but
Spirituality that he is
He's present
Where
Spirituality
Ethan service of reinforcing his wish to
Anderson Cooper
He says that God won't open up the gates of Heaven for you
Unless you face his demons
Who redeems you talk about
People like that
He says that God won't give you more weight than you can handle
Keep giving you harder stuff
Well what's f****** harder than killing
Did everything is in service
Without waking
Perceived as the legal consequences
Of have just saying like
F****** take that guy out
Bright
I just had
Interesting
We ever stopped
Considered
That maybe Alex
Still worship
The devil
Because think about
AR Rahman
Almost
Exactly the same way
It describes the devil
Like it is everything like even though even though
Okay little bit
Then he gives you more doesn't that sound more like temp
It's not sounding more like Temptation breaking down or is it also
Sarah Powell
Wait that never ceases to increased punishment
Punishment
Control over demon worshippers and Demon followers do you know who else has control
He said that
He said you have complete power over a
Who is sounds more likely to tell you to kill somebody
Then the devil
So
I'm starting to get a clearer picture that
Siri
You know what that's the other thing that's really interesting is the
Booty and the experiential conversation about the killing of a dog breeds
That you talked about that like it's happened before
Presence of literal God
Too many normal people
The devil Satan right it's been awhile since
We've really heard a nod batshit person
Say that he's been in the Press
God
I don't know I mean like just alone very terrifying
Religious
Overtone
Story saying
Makes me think like
He needs
To get some serious help
And that this
Because it's all applied in service is something that I really think is illegal
I think it was super is
It is inspirational terrorism
Dd-do wish to hide behind your words
While you inspire people to commit terrorist Act
Like it is Onix it's unacceptable on
I very much
Pray I do pray but I really hope
Weeks
It makes me believe that there is a secret ongoing battle between Heaven and Hell
Alex
Has been corrupted
And that we need to start taking Satan really seriously
That's it
Way to look at it
Yeah we should do I don't know
Write a novella
I think it's the best we can do return from war music
Call the feds
But
And nobody listens to us anyway
So pissed off
Is plug-in Fair after heated riled up the audience
Evoke feelings
Some people
And
Commercial for the
8 pack power stack
New product
Memorial Day sale
New sale
The forced sale
The force
You got the 8-pack powerstack
Commercial goes
The f****** rails
Real Fair
Headspace
Commercial breaks
Kenny gets into this
It's the best
These products are the best
Like yours
I got eight things
Here and there
I'm going to get really mad
And it goes so far apart and rails
Physically
Turn off
I'm a God-fearing person listen to him
Creepy
So it's the best or you can
Impala headlights
The gentleman doth protest
Too much
This is the best car you've ever driven or you can blow my head off
Do the letters
I've always wanted an RV
But I really would love to live in an RV
Yeah it's some point in my life
I would love to do that
If I went to an RV dealer
And it was a reasonably priced
In my wheelhouse
Good-looking RV deal
Do you saying that means
First of all it becomes
Because I know at least I can trust them not to blow their own haiwan a Salesman who's almost disinterested
Not somebody I don't want to salesman who is putting their life on the line for a sailor
Scrubs
We need to bring for Saline
So in this next clip its continuation of that ad going off the rails
It's like
That this is
No engagement
Why because I'm some
Metaphysically
Don't even think like that
Screwing over people that count on me
Bonecrusher really scared I got really alone
Sounds like there's a but coming though right
He's not special folks
When you live in a world of crazy people
Should I take a call
Ataxic
We can't screw you over but I
Make a text
It's really hard to tell how much of that is pretty performativity how much of it is like
Him
Representing something he does
Struggle with
It's very hard
It doesn't seem like he's almost describing how you would feel if you knowingly
Get to people like every conscious describe
Is exactly how you would feel you would stay up at night being like
Pink I hope nobody catches me because I'm a f****** fraud this whole thing is
And I'm never
Even though that
Unless your Bone Crusher Never Scared
Do you know what he is
Yeah
If you thought
We heard earlier where Alex was murdered
Was the only time episode
Suggest
Kill somebody that he doesn't like
Cuz he starts talking about the governor of Virginia Ralph Northam
And listen to this
Almost even borek
Should I take a call
That's just a illustrate that this is a continuous thing from that freak out in the last clip
Metaphysically he can't screw on over
I'll take your calls
Should I take it off
Got to go through this
Harmonist Governor Northam
Sounds like there's a but coming
Clean off
It was supposed to promote
Samurai sword
Maybe
House
Underwear the medical injection
Cuz you kept them comfortable
Could you say you going to kill the baby
You have value Northam
Do you think he really
But drop the ball with high-and-mighty person at the end was trying to come up with a better noun
Style font
I think I'm offended on behalf of the Georgia Act
I apologize to everybody with the Georgia Acts
I got to say
Alex
Disagrees
Impression
So it's really bad
I know from listening to hours of the show that doesn't necessarily get represented on the show
I'm telling you about is how much he does that
That's really bad really feel like that
Actually rake braces
It has nothing to do with George
Borderline Song of the South exit
His intention I think he's
I think he's almost just doing like an impression of somebody else's impression of a racist
Voice
Veterans Georgia
It's not
Incredibly Close to Northam
I wouldn't be able to pick it out if I didn't constantly let's do a show at know that
Congratulations Alex
I wonder if someone chopped his head off it would be
No it's not
But at the same time not
What can he said I would be like
Don't don't f****** do something like that
I think that's illegal
I don't I don't know if it's not we need to change the laws because
That is exactly how you get people
Crime
Yeah
He's hiding his hypothetical
Behind the samurai
Like that does all the heavy lifting on that
North
Cuz I'm making a joke about Samurai
Misrepresentation of abortion
Comparative
Advocating for his murder and
Behind battle little bit straight outside
I hope it gets
Murdered
It's still worth pointing out I believe
That
Binnewies exist on the same page
It seems like he's in a murder headspace
For sure
Pier on the 4th
And it's more talkin about North
And
You saying that like North
Well let me tell you nor them you already going to figure it out
You'd be lucky if somebody chopped your head off with Samurai sword brother that ain't answering
You know I live a long life and when you sit there on that Deathbed
They're going to be demon sitting all around you
I'm sitting right in your bed
It's going to be rubbing his hands together and saying
Buddy
Before you know it I'm going to be attached to you forever
Shocking your eyeballs out
Everett
Average
So sweet
See that little friendly fella sitting down there
Alright
Northam on that gesture
He has a lot of inside he does
That means all made up
Another check mark
I walk away from a clip like that is
How much does he think
He's being fun
You know that's a good question
It's tough
To tell
Cuz the excellent kind of implies that he thinks
Funny
Ice I wonder
Right under
Yeah.
He's making points
And there's not a satire aspect
There is it
Political
There is just
Possibly
Humor
Along with his
Is terrible
Politico
Yeah I don't know I don't know I was thinking about that a bit when I was listening
How much should we be criticizing
For his failed
Huber cuz it doesn't really doesn't sound like
He's trying to be funny but I could see him making the argument that I would try all right
It reminds me
Like the the way it sounds and if he is expecting love
It reminds me so much of the same guy at an open-mic
Who is like I am so funny
It's terrible at 9
Like I'm doing comedy
Yes
Being a f****** dick
But it's, and say what I believe in has Silly voice
Right
I wonder about that
Jump off here on the 4th to the 5th
Alex's had a little bit of a jarring experience on the way
Studio
That is easy
I guess you
Here today
Is the last two DHHS pads
Crash
That their cities are collapsing into medieval squalor
And then it's only getting worse in something
Publix
Well just on my way into the office this morning
I dodged
3 *
We know
We've been
On the scene
With men that look like
Zombies
Webstaurant
DC streaming
Almost causing a car wreck
Then I get up
Run into something similar
Close the office
Stumbling out in traffic
Wild-eyed
This is a manifestation of the truly
And the drugs and the alcohol in the opioids
Just the breakdown of society and it's accelerating
It's like Day of the Dead out there
And it's only
Forget
Worse
He says
Intentional
Appliance
Isabella
Exaggerating
Morning Drive
But
To hear somebody talk that way
About homeless people
To be someone like our
Alex Jones is disgust
Because if you see these things
See Witness
People living in that kind of
Condition
And your response to it is what the f****** globalist
As opposed to like some sort of empathy
What can we do
Systemic issues can we address
Help people not live in
The circumstance that I'm seeing in front of me
It's insane
It's heartless
Idea of
What he
Somebody who is
Paintings for
Policies
The number of homeless
Blaming the homeless
And
Vilifying them in calling them disgusting
In service of
Supporting policies that will only create more homeless
It's f******
Nightmare and make the people who are living in those circumstances
Does much more
And they're not even
Like already be starts with zombies
Because that's what he sees them at.
F******
A lot of homeless people in
In Chicago
And
If
If somebody I was
Like if you and I were walking
You walk past somebody and then turn around and go give them a dollar
Go out of your way because you realized you had a
I know that that
Just turning around and saying like
Like if we walk past him and somebody's like
Look at those zombie
I'd be f******
It's absolutely absolutely
I was talking about with the
Prince in his past self
What is present is like
Is punching down
Yeah it's so much just like
I don't know how he would have covered homes
Biking
95 or 97 government
Circumstances
As opposed to
6:30 still does
Much more down were punching them as discussed
Yeah sure the globalist
Are you trying to
Create
Yeah
Exactly their legs
It's falling down
Seth gross
Also
Note
The fact that
Alex covered that clearly fake
Blog post about women having orgasm
I'm going to get divorced
Yeah
You would think it's some point
Maybe while he's on
Next day Alex
Stop talking about that
That was not a real
Article
You take it to hit any kind of journalistic Integrity he would have figured out by then
It was a f****** troll article
On the 5th
He comes in
He starts talking about all the proof
And what do you know
That article is referenced his list
God I hate
Prepares the next move
Forced population
Operation
Which you'll be
By the time
Exist in the context of him talking
King about
Population
It's really an expression of him wishing all these people
Or dad I guess
Expression of like
Let me tell you
My Drive-In
It all really start
Alex Express
You want oh yeah
Problem
Reaction
Horses
In places like Japan
Dance places like Brazil
And places like
United States
The one I get off of the globalist social engineering
The shine post-industrial
Posthuman era
Now you see is Mainline all over TV Oliver radio
Oliver culture humans
We should be.
We should kill babies
So much fun
Sexually
Pleasurable
Bison
Open the gate
What is the clearest at least true
Do all of his arguments are based on just like
Lightly polished up piles of
It's just if you have been
Then doctor
I bet somebody did try and
Call Pancho
Hey this is a completely satirical article in his likes
4 threatened by its written by this guy
Understand
He's like God
To get women to have orgasm
Okay Alex whatever
That's what we call you tomorrow
Schizophrenic
Edward Bernays
And his work always fun is propaganda work
Jerome corsi has claimed that he was trained by Edward Bernays
Maybe that makes
Jerome corsi
Still whatever Alex brings up everybody is like he doesn't
Next clip
He doesn't say like
Instead he just revealed
Just how much
Of
It's difficult
How you would put it but I will put it as like
Eurocentric
Women did not smoke cigarettes
Cigars with lady
Should women wear gloves
The women with smoke in private
That was the style
Tobacco
By The Conquistadors
I digress
Tobacco to the European market
Trade
Envy like 1500
The discovery of tobacco
Introduction of tobacco happen for the Western world
The native peoples of North America
Tobacco ceremony
Portrayed
Possibly as far back as
Is 4000 years prior
Alex's condescending psych but I digress
As if to imply
Getting into some area that has a
Deep knowledge about
But it's Crystal Clear that
He has is it
Is a piece of distorted knowledge
On the subject of central European involved
This is such a clear-cut example of that mentality that Alex has that makes
I'm such an unreliable narrator
About history and culture
He doesn't know what he's talking about
Anniversary music
Population
He doesn't identify with
That's a fair way to put everybody else
Convert them to this b*******
I was being generous with eurocentric packed
I think while I was going over it I was struggling
Define the right word
Thank you nailed it
Why thank you
So
This that clip is unimportant at all but it's just
Example of Alex
The sound like here's a pic
Conspiracy is
And you know it
Exactly like iMovie
Your logical disorder is exploding
Conscious
Until they get him to eat the blood
Portrait children
Okay Eddie Murphy yeah
Eddie Murphy Eddie Murphy movie between Beverly Hills Cop at Beverly Hills Cop 2
About Haile
Remembered
Beside it really is important as an example of
Everything
Not real
Very aggressive
Next clip we get back to
What how come
Football score on the 4th
Whatever
Not talk about it because all you're doing for them
San Francisco
It was if they covered it on Fox News that's why I was aware
Lexington
Here's Alex on route
Restaurant
Coming up
We'll just get some rats.
Don't have type
Just in case something goes real wrong
Papa
The off-chance one of the rats goes Rogue
Is that so
No cost only proper
In this next clip
Alex
Talking about
Abortion
Of the day before
I think maybe she felt bad about all the murder last episode
I like the rat I like that
Like
Make article about women having orgasms
Abortion that's pretty cool
I can do the abortion
Stop cuz it's it's all good coming out of my mouth I really feel like I can do better this time
Kill all humans
I got to redo that one too
So he also is on a real vampire tip
Call Nyssa episodes
So there's a lot of abortion vampire is
Going on
Here is
Answer to start
What's Facebook real heart
Fishing vampire
Charizard
What does Carol mean
Drink the blood of the baby like three
They'll torture The Living Daylights out of your baby
This is the blood libel but also Alex
It's so funny
Fade
The movie they're drinking the baby
The fuk I can't I can't get lost in
Exactly
Fair enough
Greatest living on the cob
Write them
The favourites to a three-year-old cuz I can hear you
Mama
Whale song
You know a lot
Maybe too much
She at works now
Save-A-Lot on episode
Now that wouldn't be how it works
Reality
Like I stopped in the middle of clip Point classical
This is narrative
That is deeply rooted
Semitism
He's just applying it to his enemies
Either because he wants his audience to know I mean the Jews or
He just had some sort of an awareness that this work
Yeah they did a really great job using this against the
So why not use it against everybody
You know how like that's the problem with this horrible thing it was used racist
Now we just need to use it on everybody but why
Your hearing
It's almost old hadn't right for us to bring up cuz I was does it still f****** much but
If you're characterizing your enemies
That they're drinking blood of children
Prefer two to three year olds
Because they're old enough to see
Scream for their mother
What the f***
Wouldn't you do too
Like what the fuc
Is off-limits
To do today
Cuz we if you don't
Who's to say your kid isn't neck
Painted these people
He continues to do so in this
But what he does
Is mixed
Clear
These people who are a member of
Vampire cult
Everybody
And all
Women
Talking about how they have orgasms
Hugo
Abortion
And women show up
I just mess it up
There's a spirit
They're vampires
I took like what you just like what like what
Destroyer you got to let it go
Just gotta gotta
You know tonight if you got to give yourself the Serenity Prayer
Do you have to
I will not fear fear is the mind-killer fear is not a reference
I I mean that
Adjust
Insanity
It's crazy it's really important abortion
Orgasm story
But then starts talking about
First of all
I've seen the videos
So it's weird that you have this situation where it's like both of these things are people f******
It's turned into reality
It's very sad
If it wasn't the situation where we had States
Acid
Fictive laws in
Women are going to die because of it
There's a tent
It's really f******
Scary
If I were looking at this like an anthropologist
Be very interesting
Did you see him as this figure
Who was so stupid
That he made a career thinking people f****** with him was real
There is almost it
I don't disappoint archetypical feel to it like the buffoon
Yeah yeah I see what you're saying
The fool who manages to trick tons of people into
Funding his idiot
Right
It's very it's very interesting devoid of
The consequence
But it's really sad
Ba really in
Time to be
Progress can be made
So
He brought up the rat story for a real
Is because
There is something he wants to couple
With that Braxton
The wrap bar
He's already kind of dumb
You know
Is it because that's what this story is to him
That's where this story live
And that's why you is willing
Going to cover it
Even though it's
A f******
Novelty pop up
Bar
We're going to be there it's a bar
Feel like
I think it's sold out already
Tickets
Here is that clip
Immigrants
Bratz
Those
Interstate we should at least
Rescue Ranch
With you a little rat turds
I think he's thinking of Chip and Dale Rescue Rangers
Yeah
Lady
I only remember monterey jack
Condor
No.5
The second what was secret of nim had also had.
The Rats of nym
Very powerful redwall however
I'm not a dork
So that's the one
Jaja Gabor
So
It's quite a bit
Because he wants to reinforce
Nobody's talking about it
They're bringing disease
Or border agents
She also needs to go
Back to actually talk about the orgasm
Tori
But man
It's exactly a mirror of the last day here too
Trying to present the idea that
Too hard to cut
Somatic
Got it
Traversing
I'll just be honest with you, that's for about an hour during the breaks
I just can't do it
And when you say that you're not
Yeah
Performative
You didn't even really get into anything
All that different than what he got in
Into the day before there's nothing
Pathetic
So
Which would you go
Ouroboros
The prior
How about
Probably that one I like a composition portmanteau though so that one
Is probably
Too late now
So I slept Alex
Because it's too hard you can't get into
It again
Is just not
Hugh
Wants to talk about how everyone out there so much for the info War
Speaking as Alex
Go to learn how to make documentaries
Right
So he's trying to inspire his audience
To get involved and do things
He's advising them to do things that they should absolutely
Now maybe they're not as bad as
The day before
But this is this
Is Darkrai
This first one is you want people to just Honey Trap
Usually go incredibly well
Yeah a lot of people on an amateur level do it
It's usually a crime
Back on very
Fondly whatever the
Alex
Go trick people
If you're a good-looking woman
You can do in any City or any County Democrat
They're going to be pedophiles drug addict
And then lie about them
Sometimes they can't
When you realize that
Every project video is someone saying
Caricatures
46 videos are almost too perfect
Because there
Doing it to be characters
Because it's so irresistible to the right with me
Becomes the gray
Latest cottage industry possible
Yeah he's so closed
Digistream like
Understand
I don't think he does
He's not crazy to the conclusion that
I think that what we've seen like with the the
The troll article and
Of course
Women yelling I love
He's very easily tricked by things he wants to get
Project Veritas videos
Considering
Did you ever notice how they so conveniently fit our narratives almost as if they were doctored and Ed
Edited to look that way
It's almost like they were created service
Dude like 100,000
Federal prison for breaking into a
Congressperson to office under false pretense
Really surprised he's not in prison
That would have been a smart move
He has just basically as honey pot people
Then the next one is a little bit more troubling because of what it is
Implies would be the
End result of doing
Storytime
Private investigation
System thinking
One group you can Target
Isn't
Incredibly sucked up for a number of reasons
I guess stake the place out and find out whose car is who or else you're just going to be
Cars
I mean Alex's assuming the conclusion you're going to
Defined before you actually even start looking into something which is
Not a healthy way to do things
And then ultimately what you would end up doing is
I would assume you probably wouldn't find that many sex offenders
And what you would still want to do with that information is public
Email address
This doesn't come from a place of wanting to
Children
People creating a vigilante Posse
I'm certain there's going to be so many sex offenders in there
As opposed to creating a database of people who you think deserve Target
Here's one group you can Target is not a sentence
Is ever worked out well in the end
Target
Why you why you doing that
That's sneaky
It's back to
Catalog article
He reads it again
Yes god dammit
To do a different kind of creepy
Woman celebrates her abortion
YouTube
There's another woman celebrating
That is a difference later that is another
Who wrote that's a different story
That he uses as support for that
Can we stop pretending
Like abortions don't feel
You talk about it
I come really hard
Linda Blair
Sexy voice
Sexy
That's actually not even a back of the uterus
Chatting
David Outback if you walk
Ben & Jerry's
Impressionism
Pittsfield
Weirdly less sincere than his horny voice
Sincerely
Sincere than is Northam impression
Natural
X10
Yeah yeah that might be what I'm responding to
Feels
You still covering the story
There's a misconception within the story
About to f*** with people like him
Of its
This misconception is
She thinks
Coming
When she gets an abortion
Not true
Search for someone else
Who's coming
Cyanotype
Okay.
Pictures of God
The spiteful
Proud Buster's
Inventors of evil things
Disobedient to parents
Skidim Alex
Drop that scripture
I believe it was Mozart who mastered
The classical demon
Yeah comparatively Alex
Look
Previous day Alex
Maybe not ever
You could do worse eventually
It's going to be worse than that
But this
Is so weird
So
2 videos
Expressing support for abortion
And on the side of beef
Laws are being passed
What's good for her
And
This is Alex's response
To that which
Well not calling for violence
Storzer
Is
Violin
Miley Cyrus
Simulator
Abortion and the sexual
Miley Cyrus
Excruciating
Death
And sooner rather than later
I bet Miley Cyrus
It's going to be very very
Justice must be
I mean we already heard him say do you know if it's God's justice sometimes you're the tool of Justice
So if
Can you predict who's going to be dead in ten years
I don't know how one of his listeners is
Going to give her a painful cancer but
I mean it's f***** up just
Relishing
If she was still Hannah Montana
So
It's always interesting
Serta consider what Alex is intention
To report facts
So you really trying to be a journalist
A little bit of a glimpse
How he sees himself
In the Greater Media sphere
Everything
I know you know that
Focused
Next to you
This is
Set up for a long time
Different ways of expressing
Live like
I'm here to shake you awake throat
Here to get people angry
I mean like what
If the things are making them angry about our lives
What is that
If the things you're making them angry about our
Specifically tailored towards
Protecting White
Why are you making them angry
What is the end result you wish
To see if you're making people angry
Lying about abortion
Lying about
People at drag queen story time
Maybe God wants you to kill Anderson
What are you doing
What the Cure
Making people angry is not waking them up out of there
Media delusion
There's Tacoma with the MSM
What you're doing is
Inspirational terrorism
That's what you're making people angry
You're trying to rile them up to the point where they commit
A crime
That is what you doing
You don't make people angry
Unless you are looking for an action
He's describing I'm here's what I'm doing I'm trying to
But that emotion is
Only
It's only valuable if
Channel it into an actual action
If you're making people angry
About house
Their babies are getting murdered
Then your actual intent
Is for the action that follows
After that
I think
In previous times
The action
Since so much of the rhetoric is punching upward toward
Either group that don't exist
I either globalist
Or the UN
Or the administration
Who are almost abstract
The action you wish for
Subscription to buy magazine
Buy my products
Is tailored towards that
In the present day
Is
The same
Instinct
Drive of shaking people out of the coma
Make it a banger
But the action
Is
Doc's people who are at the
Storytime Honey Trap
Were you manipulative Lee edit video in order to demonize somebody was working for a social good
Kill Anderson Cooper
Yeah
Call Monique
Probably relevance of it before maybe not as over
Is category
Inspiration
Terrorism
For a long time
Mach the crime pivot
Telling people that commit genocide
Crazy as these episodes
Seats two episodes work
This is this is a different level.
Miley Cyrus is going to die painful death would have been in place
But he could see that any day you go to the zoo every day you're going to be like
Right there cuz he's up with the monkeys in The Monkey House
No big deal
You're whatever you go to the zoo penguins
Penguins
You're going to see those
And that's the
Is metaphoric I'm losing it
It doesn't happen everyday
But you don't always say
Yeah
So it is next clip Alex talks about how people whose
Proportion
Sweet dreams
Ebony plays that clip that you reference
Of the video
Of a woman having an orgasm
Wow getting a divorce
Which is using to justify
Covering that article
Show up
You don't want to harm
If so why
My dad calls
Where's your dad
Literature
Scientific reports
And then
Color
Want
Women want to get on TV
But it's all the same spirit
So we goes to a video of a woman getting an abortion
She's holding hands with somebody who's off camera
She has her eyes closed
And that
Noise
Is what Alex is trying to present
Breezing through a medical procedure
That is what's going on
At the end of it
She gets wheeled away feels good
Not good like I came
So this is a woman who
Had made this video because
To create
Or help people understand that not every abortion
Experience
Is traumatic
Couple those ideas
Remove some of the stigma around
People feel
Thing to do I think it's
Probably
Most people would choose not to do for the amount of
Thrown your way
It's something that takes it
And this is what you get
You get Alex Jones saying you're orgasming
And misrepresenting
I don't know if her video had that f****** jonty music
But it's jarring is real it's real weird
I think it Alex might have added it in in order to
Skewer
Xperia
Yeah
Either way it's not
It's not orgasm
Enjoy
It's just completely
Misrepresenting that gas service of this article
And what may that be
Is that article
Had to have read it before
He had to read it years ago
It's been online for five years he had to have read it at some point and it's colored
His perception
Abortion
And it's the real sad
Yeah I agree that seems like the only conclusion
We've got one last clip here
And what it is
Taking Christianity
And repurposing it
N2 fitting
His world
Satan's world
Hear the devil
That is an interesting way to look at it because I mean
But he's twisting scripture you know who can
Scripture for his own purpose Daredevil
Interesting here is
Alex believes in Vampires he believes the globalist are vampires
Because he
And
Because he does
He has created a mythology
G around the ruling Elite
Forever
And so what
Eucharist
Ritual of Christianity
Vampire
Which is crazy is it anti-vampire
No garlic
Right
Flash of Christ
You're misunderstanding what I mean
His son his consciousness
Into The Fray
His children with free conscious will
Weather
Fred is a symbol of My Flesh broken for you
Let's get f***** up
What
Need
Anymore
Take picture.
No
See like I'm not even a little bit
The universe about transubstantiation
So I'm agnostic by Nature I don't really know of
I don't know if any of these
Mystical things are provable in anyway but if they are
Has the potential for a lot of experience
And I'm not one of these hard atheist kind of people
Said
My absence
Like real
Ineffable not
The absence of my
Like strong religious
Just feeling
Being stipulated
I still think that's pretty sensitive to religion
The wave
And taking the Eucharist
Victor Central ritual
Turning it into something that is satisfying
Of huge
Personal Crusade
His world
He's created about the globalist vampires
It's f***** up
Really really deeply f***** up
I don't know John.
Or tail quickly
This use their words
In order to reinforce your worldview
It's a whole f****** another one
To take the Q source
The Gospels
And then repackage them
For your weird
Conspiracy theory world
The Prosperity Gospel from
David Manning from
Not that different
The context of Alex
People are missed
Using scripture
For manipulative
Profit motive
Like people like
Yeah she's the devil
Like that for sure
There's something different
Is the feels like a
I got bigger page 1
Seems worse
Jim Bakker or Paula White Cain in this regard
Disagree religion
Because he's transparently full of s*** that is nowhere near the the Bible
He's he's his Vine
Is ridiculous
It's on its face and he doesn't really use
Also make sure to take the Eucharist because otherwise you'll
Those guys they're just
Close enough
To take something that is meant to be
I suppose helpful
And turn it into something that
Destroys far more people
It does from a financial perspective
Hope
Perspective perhaps
The reason that I think
But I single Alex out more is being worse
Wow he is
Co-op
These ideas from scripture
And turning them into reinforcements of his own
Within a day before this
He was using his f*****-up ideas about religion
Justify
Maybe your
One of God's
Tools of vengeance
And people need to take
Confront
Yeah that's true
Forcing a worldview that's explicitly being used
To justify
Of people that Alex disagrees
Yeah I don't
Jim Bakker doing that as much as
You know I see it is
The Penguins always there
Jim Bakker
So anyway
I'm left with
The bitterest
Taste in my mouth
I hope
My feelings are validated as one of the most f*****-up
Couple days at the show today
Is that
Is crazy
It's understand
Is embarrassing in hilarious over 2 days
No or doesn't
Care that it's totally
Yeah
Second
Through all of this
Is deeply upsetting
And it's one of the only times but I'm willing to directly say I
He should be punished
Like I really think
Cooper I legitimately
I don't know if any of you were a lawyer and you know the law I would like to talk to you
Could probably hide behind heritage
Seriously
Samuraizer
The late-term abortion of like
F***** up speech daddy still think I would
What do you do if you did with Patterson Cooper
I don't think
That is okay
Absolutely
You know
If you can't say fire in a crowded theater Etc
That is
Sing fire
To 1000 people
Or shoot
Yeah I mean
Yeah I don't know
I don't know and I don't
Very uncomfortable with it
I hate to see you
And I just
Worry about what if
Pretends for the
It doesn't get better
Yeah
Deescalate
As Alex has a hook lawsuit
Proceeding
Early July he has his next episode
Like it's not like he's
Pressure is going to
Get off him
Memorial Day sales
Next week
Everybody enjoyed the show soundtrack.
Yep knowledge underscore fight
Go to bed
Olap to plication
Yeah absolutely
The review subscribe
Please do
Until then
I don't know
Alex killed his dog
I don't think his dog ever killed anybody
Dogs have killed
A person
Is Alex Jones
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color