Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
Who is 112 titles
Okay I know I don't know nothing about this for I am nothing
But I know that it's Raza
Everyone out there who doesn't know Jordans
Insane
6161 in the final
Incredible he's got a perfect forehead
That's fair enough
I have the reverse situation
Indeed
Interesting episode we're going back
To the past to 2013
About Alex
The coverage of stuff after
We are
Currently
Interesting
Groundbreaking happens
But
Do I find it very
Big picture Aretha outside of this podcast what happened
It's not a difficult
Variance
To take a little time
I really appreciate it so first of all John
You so much you're now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Next Kyler thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
You're an alcoholic
Finally somebody donated
So I regret
This but
Tina saurus dick
Before and I have I taken
McGrath
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
The show
We would appreciate
We would you know this February 3rd
It was a Sunday
It was
Okay Super Bowl Sunday
To do about stuff that has nothing to do with the real worth
War ritual
There's a lot of bulshit
On that day about how like
I'm not into football
I'm in the arena of the real world
Very much
Does he just do the same
Episode of Every Super Bowl Sunday I feel like I've heard him say that
He's not into football
Every single time
Somebody who's heard a number of them there are
Okay but it's
Very
Similar shows
He uses the Super Bowl existed
Football
Imply that he's more of a man than
Sports
Cool
A Greek youth
He seems a little bit upset about the commercials
Deceived
Upset about
Acquire
Performing
At the halftime show
But he's not really
Upset about it outside of being like
They just want to turn everyone against gun
It's not it's
That offensive
Not really that crazy
That's because they're probably
They were there
To him so why would he
Continue
Taking them from that point of view because he stopped
Yeah
So the show itself is not really all that
Interesting but he does take
Recalls
Second hour
Can you get the call that
Very
This caller
And then flips it on him
Eyedrops a reference
But Alex knows what it
Anybody
Who studies hours
6 knows what it mean
But Mike
Confuse the owner
Who is Mallory Mahoney
Mallory Mahoney is one of our I grab a table or chair at the office
When she formerly was Stratford
Appreciate your call
Here
Intelligence-gathering farming
Get out in Georgia
This is for Prince
So this caller
Is
Lawyer
A criticism on Alex
Around circling the idea
Control
Right
Big about
Chinese conspiracy worlds
Conspiracy Circle
Username
What they're trying to say
Controlled opposition
Maroni
Who are you guys
Getting wrong
Internet strength
After Alex didn't
To write some
Books
Mark Dice
Turn on Alex Jones
It started making videos but however
Bring up Molly
Opposition
Those videos mysteriously all disappeared
Real fast
Somebody say that
That's the example
Paying off large
But it's cool
We started making s*** up and then wants out
He got got back to
Friendship whenever you're
Friendship is based on the transaction anyways
Either way as a non insane human I definitely respect Alex's
The response that caller
He's clearly been frustrated by these accusations but he doesn't seem like he's responding with the kind of blind rage usually
Valid credit
His explanation for why
Used to be an intern at Stratford might end up working
Makes total sense
So in order for someone to make the
I'm going to
A little bit more damage
In order for this like
It's a clear
Proof
Clear
None of this
It's transfer is not ashamed
That's a matter that other outlets for probably cover way more comp
I'm only concerned
Just checking in on the argue
Text Alex to stratfor
That is my
I want to believe
For traces back to a February 12th
2012 article written by
David Chase
Taylor
On his website truth or. Org
Addressing specific
It's worth noting that a related article length
On. This article is quote
Hitler so we know we're dealing with
Source
Call Haddad ship
I would believe less than
I'm Tracer. Org
A website
Important to know what he's up to in the Maurice
Recent days
In 27
Put out a press release saying quote
After months of deliberation and
With great trepidation I announce that I have the so-called Messiah
You know what I appreciate that responsibility
Call the Messiah
Believe that
You should not want
To be king
I do not run out of self-preservation
Calendar
Messiah
He wants to do is barter The Whistleblower
CIA headquarters beneath Lake Geneva
EnV so-called chosen
That's like mailing something to yourself because you can't afford the copyright
So he goes on to quote
Although Jesus Christ exist
The 2,000 plus years ago called the title of Messiah
DMV savior of mankind
The reality is that mankind didn't need a savior back around like they do now
Therefore the story of Jesus depicted in the Holy Bible is the story of the
The future Messiah which is now
Chase Taylor
Aside from all the physical traits
Celebrities the trials and tribulation
And suffered by Jesus over
According to him
I can't vouch for that
The persecution of Legend
Doodly suffered by Jesus
Persecution
Over the last seven years just left the safety
Yeah that's cool dude
Real good source of information guys
Winner
You like
From what I can tell from his website he's mostly posting
Open letters to journalist
Every few days that are basically
In case I get killed in the next few days. Who did it
Just roll over and die
Eddie never gets killed
That I just totally
Zayn Malik high-level paranoid to play
Score
Consider that the source of the
You traced back to an article written by that
Nautical gear the bass
The claims that he
Alex is in Austin and Stratford headquartered in
So there's a geographic
You've already you've already solved that conundrum I believe wholeheartedly
Are we connected
To them
Oh s*** we are no Allstate
Safe Harbor boat base your butt I don't even I don't have private insurance
Let alone is there any connection
To the insurance
Geography is nothing
That means
The second piece
The connect
According to
Alex's career begin
Began his run on kayjay.
Texas Public Access
Free date sites
Also Infowars itself wouldn't actually be founded
Google 1999
So I don't really think there's even a
Like a chronological connection
Just throwing spaghetti
Yeah I like to entertain
Intelligent
Employees to create analysis
But they disseminate
That's okay worthwhile as a connections
They both use
Pizza ovens to make
Pizza at Papa John's
Connected
Exactly
All the 4th Alex Jones is supposedly a conspiracy theorist he's friends with celebrities
Joe Rogan
Is celebrity
That's not this
Alex Jones
Since transfer release
Intelligent
Sodas
It doesn't mean any
This is just selectively using a couple pieces of info
Information to create
False connection that you want
To appear in the world
As if David Chase Taylor took all the time
Information
And made his argument
But Alex's
Working for Stratford
Yeah I think
You probably was up until
And then they
That's what makes
You think the killer was held up
There's one other piece of his argument though and that is that David Taylor says
The tractor is a Zionist
Massage run
And Alex is married to it that that's a big part of speech
Okay I was wondering if
That is what's really behind.
Force transfer narrative that's based on The Incredibles
Inclusive
Secretly working for
It's all about the idea of Alex working
Stratford is annex
Exclamation for why he won't come out and admit what they think
Obvious truth
Set the NWO in all the world
System re-bag
Jewish
I reviewed a ton of
Conspiracies that have spun out of David Chase
Sailors blog post attempting to eat
There is the temperature in expand on the. Make more connections
Between Alex and Stratford
They're old
Super week
They all come back to people who are mad that Alex won't publicly say that the real enemy is
But I've always
Considered
The back of my mind
Is how valuable having anime
Yeah for someone like Alex who's vulnerable
Get out of jail free card
People were way more
Attacking you for not being
Yeah it's it's a really valuable thing
It turned out that
Spectrum
Makes it so difficult
Yeah also if Molly Maroney was some kind of
Deeply embedded intelligent agent
Infowars
They would credit her under
Real name
Her at all vehicle graphic designer
Infowars Maga
What's the
Look
Just because you're a secret operative doesn't mean you don't
Do you do the work you get the credit
The government always gives
She's lifted
In the credits
Is almost indication
It all makes me even less
Seems to have gone on to have a
Career in Visual Arts
Propaganda
In 2013 after she ended her very short time but Infowars
Just called Sprat
Spra
Austin Texas
MJR they do this really cool thing called free art Friday
I'm not sure if they
More artists
Pieces of Art
They created around the city
Define to take home
They post Clues on it
Instagram is where the peace
Lisa's work
The most fun
Super taking something like that but I
Also not so jaded that I think it's
Especially if
Come on
A former Infowars employee goes out and goes
F*** that entire world
We're going to play hide and seek with art
Read Beauty
Oriented
I was waiting for you to take
Dart services
Providers
I've never met her but from everything I can tell Bali Maroney
Really cool
In fact the only thing I can really find about Elizabeth
Infowars
Which totally is understandable
Coming out of college
Explanation for why somebody would take that position
Perfect sense
No his explanation for why somebody would have
Still works
So I don't know I think this is important
Piece of like
AMC Alex Jones
World like a lot of
Critical of him
To the level that you and I are
A lot of them get really sidetracked
That sort of Molly Maroney world
He works he works for
Stratford
Flame
You'll get a better
Albert says something
Teamsters
Imply
That he does believe
There were actors
Which
Is not good
It's clear that at least in the background
Kind of what
Mental illness
I think what he's saying is
Crisis actors
Is this yeah
But it's so muddy
Like what he's expressing
I'm saying that
If this
Professor
Florida
It's a reasonable
Miski ringer
I think I agree with you his meaning was
And that has happy
There have been
He is not necessarily
Confirming
But it's closed
Is real close
There's really not a whole lot going
It's pretty boring
I think he's probably concerned about his his bats
I get into Monday and
Talking Bone to pick
Oh yeah
Which one Barack Obama he had put out
Themself
At Camp David how dare how dare this man with a gun
Can you talk
You got to get them coming you got to get them going
There's nothing you can do this right
Shotgun
Firing shotgun
Firing handgun govern over again
That looks like a fake photo
Furniture the controversy that
No one is allowed to photoshop
This is only for media
So
First things first
Can't Photoshop or use the insta permission
That's a boilerplate disclaimer that literally apply to every picture on the White House that they were
No one ever in
Horses
But it's Universal thing
Is making a big deal out of
Because the Daily Caller
The conservative trash rag run by Tucker
Carlson made a big deal out of that
You can't Photoshop
They pretended that it was
Suspicious detail
True The Daily Caller articles that boosted by drugs
Alex picks up
And now he's got a conspiracy that Alex says
You can't Photoshop app
A picture of him with a gun Dan I will tell you this right now
The Cubs won last
But I can't tell you anything
Singh further without the
Express written consent of Major League Baseball
Right
Then they told me that because something happened
Completely manufactured by Pilot
So
I'll tell you this to
Not much going on not a very exciting
Important
I need to not that Lord moms
Okie dokie.
Okay of course
What's important
Is that Alex gets a call.
The tips him off
That's certain.
Somebody
It's coming to Texas
And Alex
Is not happy
Piers Morgan
Again
Because he's coming into our territory
So Alex is herded a Morgan is going to a gun shop in Katy Texas
And he is going to f******
Finish the show and run
What is this round this is the Thrilla in Manila this is with the rubber mat
Batman
Kind of eggs
The show is
Coming to an end
He's getting towards the end of the show
Diesel
Struggling with
Trip
Katy Texas by Houston
Like I got a
I don't know is it
Piers Morgan actual
Even going to come or not
Yeah
Go away
Exxon
Closing early
Special event
Producers phone numbers
Amazing ladies and gentlemen
I was just trying to get his audience
Succumb to he's trying to turn this into a
So this is exciting
My favorite part
Anytime he hasn't
Surprised like
Oh I got to go here
He always tells
That's what he was going to be
Coronavirus
I was listening
These episodes
Very little
To talk about here very little that interested
The Super Bowl to the power outage
During the Superbowl was 33 minutes long because
Illuminati signaling the globalist
Is the power going out
I just sitting there like
Oh my God
I just listened to
I can't
I cannot
Interest myself in researching
I just cannot
Implied
I really do look into the power outage
What caused it
So
For something I needed I needed
Morgan coming to f****** Texas
Is it
Exactly what I need
It's coming
And he's like oh my God
The last time I got
Already
So popular I talked about it for a week I sold so many pills
It was great
I got to do it again
I have to
So
Here is
Alex Jones
Confronting
Piers Morgan
He shot videos there's a video
Now paid very close to 10
To how
Sad
Alex
If you quote a confrontation
What's your daughter says that's around here
Globalsign
Play the
They want what is a
It's good that I had a fever was actually sick that's why I was sweating
Almost
So
In 30 seconds Alex multiple times ask
To be back on his show
I'm not in a you're afraid of me kind of way
Viral like a lot of people
It is not the Alex
But he likes to
To present himself as
That is an Alex
Where are you
Pull this off
I will get back on 3
My reach will expand even
That is literally like a first-time
Screenwriter walking up
Does Spielberg and being like if you want to take a look at this
Again
To be back on the show
Why don't they promote you that much on it
You can't be first film
He's right there
You have to go
Alex gets kicked out
It's presented like
Sort of stealth footage
And it again it's her being likes
AAA
Now that was very
Sycophantic very
Weasel
Very hate to see a guy brought that love
Would like to see you
And how he would like you to
To see him
How he sounds once he gets outside
He has his rally
In front of him
At all of his fans
Sounds very
We don't agree
What's going on here
You know you lost this round
You sho got a picture for me
Opportunistically
Everybody
Collaborators
He wants to present himself as it goes into the Green Room is
Go back on your shelf. No Alec
The claim of
Like in court
If they want to do like hey this is all an act
After this is all bulshit
Play those two clips back
Back-to-back and everybody black
You know what's Wild to me is that Alex put out the video where he's talking
Piers Morgan yeah I didn't have to put that down that's all
From seeing is just like look at how fake and bulshit this guy is
I can't imagine what would possess a person
To do that
Like guys that present themselves as so
Two faces but whatever
So the Alex has his rally he's yelling into a bullhorn and there's two
Understands the videos him
Getting interviewed by the local news station
Exactly what you wanted
He went down there to cause this
Listeners out in order to create the appearance that there's something actually going on
That'll attract the local media
He gets some sort of
Footage of him with Piers Morgan
Damn and then it doesn't matter cuz
With this van behind the wrestling promo
Shooting on Pierce
Hey man I was
Just trying to
I'll just try to
Be nice to him
I didn't want to offend
The gun store owner
That's who you are
You are the guy begging
To get on CNN
Romantic good idea when we were in Austin we should have gotten a few listeners
And held a rally outside of his Studio try to get the local media on there
Where is Norwalk
I think that would be a 0 for the Press
But the 1990s
And we get shot by the snipers
So he goes out and he does that
And obviously
They comes back
And I have a strong suspicion that you might a party
The night after
Market price
This does not
Stand up live
Usually they're really regular I forgot this morning
Whatever the case
Whatever the reason
He's an unknown sleep
He is on no sleep
And it's not
I think he played some unforced errors on
On the show and if that's a product of not sleeping
That's good
But it's not
Yeah if you just starts off the show
Sport for
Vigilante
America
You cannot support that Alex that is not good
You don't want to be alright
Determining what is and what is not
Sincere vigilantism
The cops are killing unarmed
Black people
Government
That you want them to take
Sitting around hands when those cops are
How to prevent an interesting case study Alex
The mama
I don't know
Dangerous press
Because if you're supporting
Vigilante group
Then
You don't have a lot of lot of firm ground to stand on
Talk about
Going to yell at Piers Morgan
He has he's
Standard
Excuse for why the footage
Just better
This happens every single time he goes and does any
Topsy and Tim was behaving behind the scenes
Are you ready
So funny
So
Settlement
It's always do
Just didn't get it on camera but you know it
Such a fun feature
That dovetails with everything else because you're a conspiracy theorist
Of course you couldn't
The good stuff
They're too smart for
Like being lazy
Plays in the good kids
As opposed to actually putting effort into making something
It's it's good
It's real good stuff
Talks about
Really want to go back on Piers Morgan
Three times in a minute to go back on his show
Why are you talking about
People are sick of it they want
Supposed to get in the face of the gun grabbers
Just sad
You going on why can't I get back on I need another hit
Yeah yeah yeah
I do believe him when he says
Even Ted Nugent is going back on people
MacGyver that was a very direct
I enjoyed that
Let that checks out interviews
The guy who owns
The gun store
This is insane
This guy
Complaints about Piers Morgan
Says that's a adjective the interview to make him look stupid
Sure
Short short short short I don't know how much that is true I don't
Particularly care
I'm slightly Petty
Is
You're paranoid
Ridiculous
Moment of insecurity you have on actually real things
The idea that isn't
Security self-generated
Even even that has to be a couple of people
Forcing him to feel embarrassed sneaky plan of people trying to highlight his belly
Look good on camera
Retro ridiculous
You care about Alex interviewing this gun store owner it's not particularly
There are two horses about that are getting
The only reason that I actually even
I think that it's very worth our time
Is that
This
Text Colette
Is one of the few times
I have ever heard Alex given
Actual apology
I have almost never even when he's had to give
Formal apologies to like James alefantis
Hamdi ulukaya I still think that this is one of the only real
Sincere apology
She's ever given
That's alright thank you brother
Wow only people
Hope Road apology if you remember in the first earlier episode
Gun gun shop
How to give an apology
I'm so sorry that I bought to the b*******
That I thought that you were a gun store that was against the
The second f****** amend
Almost
Like that is almost like he's apologizing to a hype
Like that was very much
Like
Only real God
Is
Is represented by you on this Earth
The trigger
Yeah I just feel that way
It's a limited shows
That like he is afraid of being out of the good graces
Of Gunn weirdos
If you will go out of his way to apologize for that adipose
I just like leaving it be
Means that someone
You can call
In the gun community
Gun Shop
Which great
This guy
Really really
Rusty h
41 school shootings
Several
Confirms fluoride
This is interesting
So here
We have a doctor showing up on Alex
We can just assume
Right off the bat a couple of things what are they
Feel that we are going to be discussing obviously that's the first thing. A doctor
Peter Glidden has a degree in naturopathic which is not
Probably 30 times I seen correct
Get to a product that Alex makes money also
A very quick search of Peter Glenn
Quote member of the scientific Advisory board at youngevity
Does Alex's show at this point
Which I stress is run by a veterinarian
Pretending to be human doctor
Peter Glidden
Give me somebody who espouse
Purely dangerous idea
What is bitcoin
The chemotherapy doesn't work
It's just a scam by doctor
And make more money also
Instead of
Medical doctors
You should use naturopathy and
Clinical oncology Journal
Your selected one line
That he uses
To make a document that says quote
The overall contribution of Curative and adjuvant cytotoxic
Chemotherapy
25-year Survival on a doll
Was estimated to be 2.3% in Australia
2.1 /
USA
Already concluded
The chemotherapy only works
People that use it on
Of course
People about this
The 2% number is 2% of
The total people diagnosed with cancer
Not 2% of the people who get chemo
Just very different
Statistically
A large number of people considered in that
So the 2.1% is in no way related to
The efficacy of chemo is
The Miskin misrepresentation of the
The study is in Port
The name of youngevity
And the real consequences someone believing him is it
I know the chemo isn't 100%
The sure thing
But I would love to
Beyond
Tangerine
Alternate alternative medicine is Olga
It's all good and well
And there's nothing wrong with studying natural cures
Ailment
Main Street Medical
3 months already
Huge problem is when you use your unfounded medicine
Bulshit
Primarily to attack
Street Medical
This isn't trying to advance medical treatment
Concerned that patients are getting the appropriate care
It's a transparent attempt
The trick vulnerable people in
Money on you instead of doctors
That's
Owosso Peter Glidden also host
The show on The Gents
Communication
That work
Is all doctor guys of all people that are making money off
That is awful to have
Where what
Hundred percent
Get as many guns in his men people's hands
Is possible
And at the same time
Remove as many doctors as you can from
We want to get you hurt and go to make sure you
You stay hurt
It's deeply disturbing yeah that's
F***** up
Does fluoride study buddy
Alex has no idea what he's talking
But also part of the reason the Harvard
Became so prevalent is that larger platform
The infiltrator
Bulshit artist
Who use their platform
The Harvard study
Texas
IQ the researchers at Harvard didn't run any neutral
They merely review 27 already
Missing studies
And discussed what they purported to have sound
Most of the studies analyzed were about 10 years old and
From China
The studies were looking at people living
Villages in
China Mongolia and
Natural fluoride levels
Play stressed not added for natural natural fluoride level
Holes in their drinking water was approximately
12 * 11 what is here
Oh I remember this one
I don't think anyone would dispute that even beneficial chemicals being taken in at that high of a rake
Can be dangerous
Information
They point to this meta-analysis of studies and
Flippantly declare Victory and pretend that the Harvard Harvard came out and admitted that they were right all along and that the fluoride
The researchers who did that meta-analysis
The studies were also very clear in their paper
The 27 studies
Furious
Regarding the sign
Method
Some of them would probably not stand up to scrutiny if they were
Estimated to be published
On their own
But they exist Within
In the body of this
Subsequent Studies have found no link
Fluoride
Like you but it doesn't
The misrepresentation of that Harvard study it already taken
Please that wanted to believe the false
Conclusion
So no amount of proof that that conclusion is wrong it's
And one of the biggest reasons
This narrative
Because exact
Luckily with Alex
Pointed out there was a Huffington Post headline
Quotes Harvard study confirms fluoride reduces
Children's IQ
No however it wasn't written by anybody
Play Bang Bang Bang Bang
Yep a contributor blog post was written by Joseph Mercola
Who is an anti vaxxer
Grifter
And has been for a really long time
Multiple times governments had to tell him to see
Making medical claims
Putting forth about products
She sold it in 2016 had to pay back over 5.3 million dollars to customers eat
Defrauded
Reduce their risk of cancer
He's a real pile of s***
Probably worth a whole episode
Some point or shows up on Infowars look forward to that
But for now just know Joseph
Nikola stock
People like him too
Do I have free reign
To attach them
Information
Presumably legitimate name of their platform
Even people like Alex
The mainstream media Outlets
What's have more rigorous editorial standards
He does
That's why he constantly backs up his stories by saying
It's in the main
News
He knows that
Makes his b*******
It sound more believable
Because the Main Street news
Does fact-checking
A contributor platform does not
Expect.
So annoying
Such misinformation
Stupid
Wow
Pretty wild
Fluoride doesn't affect your IQ unless you
To take
It is a
Severe disservice
Science journalism
Not like intentionally
Just it's it's almost like there should be like
In the same way that their tops
Clearance levels
Yeah something like that
Should be under a clearance
F****** abused
Yeah but if you know of course
Breeds its own problems
That just can't be
Allowed into the wrong hands
Viscerally
Gets out of bed
It's so much easier
Propagating
People
It's a more compelling enter
Interesting story
The government is trying to
To poison the water
Triggers your
Your brains desire
And because of the intersect
Action between
Journalism and science journalism
Especially
Nobody wants to read a headline that are like
Incremental benefits might occur based upon
These controlled variables being applied in this specific
Let's also not get into ideas about accusations
Well poisoning Rich tradition
From from history
Triggers that
So dr. Glidden
Why am I calling him
Yeah they do that should be
Mr. glitch
Repeat
Kemah
Because he was calling himself a doctor
That's not
And I love the way
Describes this
Getting in trouble
This is
So off
30-second little clip
What does
You first of all are amazing
Your delusion
Second
Show
Website
Your help
Wow
Cuz I don't know if I've ever heard again
He heard the music come in and listen to Alex the show or maybe he does the same thing on his show
Man that was smooth as silk in the state of Illinois charge me $5,000
What what kind of Oppression are we living in
Free medical
Because I can't just go to school
Free tuition
That's what he was doing I mean
I still a is also calling for
You don't have to do homework
Tuition-free degrees
Yeah that isn't Fortune
Joseph father
I don't actually think that's true like if you're a d
Diy things
You call yourself a doctor
Who's your wife
You're right cuz you're not
I think
That this interview is Loki
Super import
It's one of the few times
That I think
It's totally not into
To anybody outside of our world
But to me this
Text clip
Is one of the biggest
Case studies
For like
What could have happened if that people paid attention
Listen to Alex
How could differ
Currently could life have been
If they actually paid at
Play news crew
ACL
Surgery
Workout exercises
6 months
You better you better
You can't
Would have gotten Alex
Find
A very serious
If anybody was playing
Endorsements and testimonials are really in
Things according to the law
When you're advertising a Prada
One of the more powerful ways
Discuss the ethics
Vouch for it work personally
I know this works because it works for me
There are rules about how those are
Pretty clear about how they can use
And what are the chief guidelines
Is there if you were expressing an endorsement
You have to accurately Express
Their belief
You have to represent them Act
So it's a sin and robbed you don't believe youngevity products were responsible for their knee recovery
Alex just committed
So they would have to under oath say yes absolutely I have a reasonable basis for believing that young
Help me
Get my ACL B
Hold on
Furthermore
Unsubstantiated claim
Testimonial
Cro-Magnon substantial
Claims
If youngevity is marketing by having Alex
Talk about
Instantiated misleading Medical
They are still liable
It's not like Alex said it's fine
Not how it works
Although
Really f***** up
Because quote
An advertisement
Employing a dorsum
Consumers about the performance of an advertised product or service
Will be interpreted as representing the product
The product or service
Effective
Affected in the advertisement
Therefore the advertiser must possess and rely upon
Initiation
Through including when appropriate,
Reliable
Evidence
To support such claims made through a door
Advertiser would be required to be representation
Because he used to testimonial
I adore
This is a medical claim
Denise
Supported by evidence
Inexact
Come out and said
Product cures ACL tear
Because Alex
Used to example
Edit no point did they say something like
These results are not typical
Or something similar
Disclaimer actively committed a crime
Perhaps the most important for breach of a
Luxardo is this
They're from people with material connection
Since to the company they're making claims about
Infowars Nightly News director at youngevity is one of Infowars main sponsor
Resellers of youngevity products
Rob do salary is in part subsidized by youngevity
So his testimonial is
No it is come
Completely ethical when
Goes to one of his own Golf Course
Tweets out a lot of ads about his own Golf Course
Sorry I pays all of our money
To his own Golf Course
Just because
Similarly
Impartial party
Promoting a sponsor
Additional
Peter Glidden show
As well as the show's of multiple other represented
So precious metal Midas resources
His company
Youngevity
He's deeply involved
Depleted
Pretty clear that use of these swords
The testimonials
Are an example of deceptive
Yes 104
Yeah you really didn't add me
A lot of that legal languages
Parsing very specific different
Little tiny change
This is a great table.
Understand
Just like when you hear that if you
You have no familiarity with the American legal system whatsoever yogurt
It's fairly intuitive
In terms of the guidelines are like you can't lie about what people indoors
If you're f****** around if you
Have a financial interest in
The back your endorsement
It makes a lot of fun
I know this is beating a dead horse
Very sure
Alex Jones manifested
Multiple in
Instances of behavior that are directly against
The rules of the f
Is anyone cared about what he was due
Gorp
He could have been shut down
Years ago
For using this kind of deceptive
Possibly over
Is it going to actually exist
Give me flying f***
About what Alex
They could have had him
I meant that he is
Is actually
Controlled opposition
It couldn't just be that he's at this point in time irrelevant pointless and not worth anybody's time
More and more trouble than it's worth to pay attention to him I can vouch for that that's why I adore smite
Do you get one more clip here cuz the rest of the show also isn't there
Cuz I think he wants to go to the
Super Bowl Super Bowl overcompensate for how much he wants to watch the Super Bowl
I don't get sidetracked by
Udder excite
Mexico see Piers Morgan
And there's just not a lot of con
Not much new stuff other than
Like I said the
Power outage
Conspiracy
I'm not interest
Frivolous
Frivolity
Frustrating
But
I told you
What is up to VIP
Youngevity on this episode
Deeply and ethical
Right
Now Peter Glidden
Would like you to know
It's super app
He's cool man
Set up a f*****-up sky
Sure I'm a board member of the youngevity
But I'm
Cool
Disclaimer
There's nothing messed up about what we're doing
Is really cool and if you were cool
Dude f****** stuff he does
By the way Alex
30 doctor
I love that I love that
Yeah I was going to make your buddy spice by bulshit but everyone I know it's cuz they're not f******
They're not f******
Pennsylvania
That is
That's next level like bullying
As a as a Griff
Sick of people saying I only
We do this cuz I profit off of it
My fiance profits off at
We have a joint bank account
I make withdrawals regularly
Her money into my only account
Cool
And you do if you don't answer stupid
It's crazy too
First of all in talking about himself in the third person spot
Makes me very uncomfortable
But then the second thing
If you really were listening
Myself from the revenue stream
What is a Visa legally
Illegally
Myself
I don't know
Yeah time is it
So you know you you get back in
It's easy also these people are liars
That is true
Why would I don't drop it off vitamin
I don't believe you you lied about everything else you tell people not to
To get that because it's the conspiracy
I don't trust you when you say you don't make money off your b*******
What's the difference between you and me
Why the f*** is wrong
I love the client you say that b*******
If you're convinced by him not to get
Chemo
Of course you're going to believe that he's telling the truth
It's on this one
Yeah yeah
So shorter than normal
Risen said there isn't a lot of
You know stuff
Go over it
Loves Park
I wish
Yeah I wish I had more but
Y'all can only I can only do that which Alex allows me to do
Yeah we can't manufacture the footage that Alex
Would have had videotape
I think there's nothing funnier than Alex
To be back on
Salvinos Dad it was really exciting
Beyonce does it
Members of my family
Community if you're not it
Because you're f*****
Stupid it's so weird to me that Flex because
It starts from a place of like
I don't drop it off yet
You don't expect
Mediately
Talk about all of his family profiting off of his life
Indirectly at-bat
Yeah it's so weird
Are you
If you don't
Another episode
Knowledge fight.com
I'm at go to bed
Podcast
Sure.
I don't know I think Peter Glidden
Necessarily
I guess second degree manslaughter
I don't know I don't know how to ethically put that other than
This a bad finger
Piers Morgan before this
Vector
Aboveboard
I'm not at the first caller who was all about Molly yourself
Probably has
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color