Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color
Plexaderm
A little bit about Alex Jones
Paint with watercolors are acrylics
Probably when I was in our classes
In high school
Got those electives
Never had any artist
Stickability draw 4
I can't I have no coordination
I don't know if I could draw Circle for you and right now I could barely do that cool ass fit
Andrew on their folders
I've always looked very self-conscious about my inability
To even do that kind of rudimentary things I never really tried
Because my brother was always really good at cartoon
Yeah I felt like he had the ark
Cystic ability
Had glasses
Jump into his yeah absolutely
That worked out pretty well
Technically probably but never
NeverWet by choice
Started the prison for you I guess I don't know anything about
Effects
Creative
But I do know a lot of
And I don't know about actually
To the podcast
Can't wait let's do it actually first before we do
People who are supporting
You're now a policy
I'm a policy wonk
Sean
Megatron
Brigitte
That might not be
Brigitte Nielsen
I'm pretty sure it's not
Either way we appreciate it very much and apologize
For our ambivalent
Bank of Virginia
Next Exploder button
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Much less
The weather like outside
Somebody
Heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Absolute
So Jordan
Still I was so unsatisfied by the last
Like sodas
So I stuck around
Cuz I felt like every time out
Harlow
Like dead pastors
Nothing growing in them
Generally that means
I usually feel like he recognizes I'm not bringing it
He'll give you something
I'll tell you to give me something
I'm not sure what it was but
Through eight
But before we get into that at like 2
Just give everybody a run
In the present day of Alex Jones
Rainbow snatch
Absolutely
Millie Weaver is going out trolling people
Real exciting
To cover the price
So much laugh
Because it's like
What are you doing
What is the go
Kaitlin Bennett are both going out to like Pride events
The trick people into signing
Capitation
Where are they like
Prove nothing it's just distractionary
It's lame and desperate
Tension
I'm not interested
Makes me feel like I don't want to be involved you guys do what you doing have fun absolutely don't even care
Me to comment on what you're doing it scares me because the comedy is so bad
The intent
True
But it's not even hard to say
Bad that I would slip from
To just outright being mean to it
Because I take it is almost expensive towards powder
Maybe you could be me
Neither a little bit
She deserves a little higher but also aware of Alex lose
That's a lawsuit
No it is not but it's probably about right
Admire it when people Sue Alex and they're not punitive
Appreciate a little bit
Just trying to abusively
Katana Bonnie from
To charity it's not even about
Getting this money from Allen
Sabor principal
The thing
It's okay yeah that's great
His attorney your
Best friend
Please come out and declared Victory even though they had to pay for
Workbar artist
Also just before we started recording update
Rodger stone is back
On the show
Maybe there's some things that are covered
We'll talk more about that
Rodger Stone has made contact with Raptors
Can you talk a little bit more about that
A little weak wrap up on Friday but I have
But I just couldn't muster it and I wanted to
Stick around
Valic
Said me
Something really sucked up
Adult
So we didn't hear we're going to start on the 6th
Alex
Delivers
Almost immediately
Ski is
Weird
A very strange mood
And he has found some science news that
He does not understand
Major scientific
Other matter
Ordered format
96% of DNA
Amanda
Wellington
God
We are
Spirit
Cichlids
Oh s*** s***
We're in trouble
Trouble the world
Chucky
Cuz he read the Bible
Yeah
This
Is a bat house
Early
Maybe after the first break
You still even back in 2013
Have that's the first couple minutes
About the eight-minute mark cuz that's what everyone
It's from like 02
To about like
5 minutes
For 5 minutes
That's just that no man's land that usually station IDs
Gamestop.com
Come back at 8
Yeah it's somewhere around there I believe
It's pretty
He's getting into the
Seattle simulation news
Oh boy
Hey this isn't news
But all the idea that Alex has figured out that some people believe the world is
Simulation
And that he's turned it into proof
Of his version of God 2013
Before
He's bringing it up now cuz
Stop
Article that came out in
On October 11th
Stop
Recent research
The cosmic ray
The researchers studying the particles found that they had a limit
So how much energy
These particles
And that limit appear to be arbitrary
Is possibly representing evidence
The built-in limit
In the physical universe that are part of the
The parameters
Overstimulation Within
However the article isn't written by
So it also points out quote
It could be those that were incorrectly interpreting evidence of certain fundamental laws that we are as yet unfamiliar with
It could even be that this isn't evidence at all for a simulator as a real lattice might work in a different way
As to how we would envision
So it's really
It's really fun to imagine that we live in
Computer simulation
Matrix is real but more measured analysis
Test include the possibility that we just don't know anything
Restraint
To take something back
B suggest
Sing some new findings
Interpretation
Bike supported B
Want to hear Alex talk about this article that's all I really hear
Do you want
To believe the world
Simulation
Three Texas article
Ignoring the part about how it's totally possible
Rule the cosmic particles that we don't
Understand
Paul Joseph Watson in to talk about it he comes
The very boring.
Call Michelle
But yeah
It's B
It's a real religiosity
The thing that
The religious
Understand more and more about
Even they're going to eventually
About
The speed of light squared
I don't know
Why because
That's what it is
Can the universe exist
Without these
Is there universe
Are we in a long string of possible universes
Guess what
Jesus bones not enjoy
The occasional thinking about this stuff
I'm a little bit more about this
Talk about the simulation
Siri but here's
Research firms
Computer
6%
Credible
All sorts of other
Crystalline solid
Doesn't
The true spirituality
Which is the first
So do you understand
This is starting to develop a little bit in 2013
Heard that will couple time
Did this is a primarily Evangelical Quest that he's on
Almost
A way of Trojan horsing
His version of God on piano
Which is
F***** up
Creepiest it's really weird to think about
Maybe there is something
But that's his primary driver
Yeah
Just trying to get through whatever
Yeah that's the that's the idea he feels like his life's work is
Follow through
Computers
Call Dax
Yeah maybe I mean I would say obviously
I believe
One example of him losing the thread
Basically what he said is
Atheist
Watched all those bad preachers in real life
There's probably no God
They just don't know that our DNA is a crystal
Would never happen
Anymore
I'm not entirely sure what you mean
Empire crystalline
At work event
That there's other life forms
Alien DNA
Dangerously close to carry cats
Citibusiness
I think what he's referencing
Is the
I can't remember
Exactly what it is but it's kind of
Certain genetic material.
Get destroyed in viruses
Maybe it was attached
Meteorite
Good DNA cover
Asteroid
But of course if we have alien DNA
Things were here before us
Text leptitox a little bit more about that and I really think
Strong indication
All he's really interested in this
Simulation
Theory narrative
Is using it
A jump-off point
Right version of Christian
Science is increasingly
Created universe
Address for computer
Isn't even
I stopped listening to God
Creators
Which is
Creation
Glad we got pjw three in there
Wave at you
Well precise
You bet Alex
No matter what you say is kind of dismissive
Bubbles fundamental
Pause this podcast
So I can understand what's going on here
Yeah it feels like a college dorm
Like on some real
Spiritual biz
At the beginning of this
Episode
That's one possibility
Another possibility is just like he's out of his week in terms of understanding stories
We're kind of in his wheelhouse
To strip all contacts from
God
What's the problem
He's not going to alienate any of his audience by doing that either but I go home
Oh my God
It doesn't take the whole show
Beginning although he does Touchback
Michelle keeps plate-spinning
God's grace
Butts
Before he moves on to his neck
Better Business
He's got to tell you about how
Successful
Operation
Get
13 + 100
That is
Crazy
Almost
Impossible to believe that number is possibly
Almost no sense that if
Gcn
At least indicate 2:30
Why would Alex only be on once
Sure seems weird
Only on like 200 radio station
So why would those 11:00 other stations not are the most
Popular show on the network if
Them nothing
The oldest Snapchat snapshot you can find on the Wayback machine at the
Gcn
Is from October 14th
And the numbers they're claiming it's a
Stanford is smaller than the one
They alleged to be working with
What's 641 radio
Which Alex is on 100
6 number
Funtrivia Veterinary
Doctor has a radio show
It's only on 12
Peter Glidden that fake doctor that we talked about on the last episode has a show to
I also Webster Tarpley showworld
What what are they run on other station
Do I have 600
Hunter show
Tiny amount of
Small-market
They offer a lot of stuff for his I understand the primary business model is
Resyndication
You make a dress
Resume wassom
Oh my God create podcast
It's not a free like it.
I think I still don't actually misspoke earlier also
Most popular show on
Medications that work
I guess I just kind of always assumed you was the largest profile
That works
He's not the most widely syndicated show on G
No it's
Calling show 160
P5's
Wow
To grow Salix
And all the snapshots that I found more popular
Dcmo go on to cross the mark of being on over 1000 stay
By August
Team
But what's fascinating is that
The network
Expanding
But it doesn't appear that Alex is doing the same
Constantly hovering around 100 to 120
Patience Mark even is gcn it added 400 New Station
It really appears that the growth of the network
Seeing is around other shows not Alex
There's a very
Real possibility that he
Reached his potential already
And networks weren't even interested
Generic is chauffeur
I think there's a decent possibility
Back razor
Could explain
One is Alex's incredibly toxic bran
Yeah of course even back then
Even though he wasn't such a monster and everybody knew it you still might not want
Play show on your network
Seaside
You might know somebody whose work with him and radio be like don't work with that guy just all kinds of possibilities
Yeah
The second possibility is that
Like advertising
Bike cost
Katana moron
So even though a terrorist
For free the syndication
Finding sponsors that would be willing to buy ad time during his show on your network
Might be
Prohibitive
From a cost a
Yeah you still have to have good sales
Yeah it's just Alex
Text taking the
The burden on
Good luck
Or whatever
There's there's a lot of possibilities
He's not the biggest
Wichita
I always really thought so
And I think you probably way back but
Early 2000s
Baby
A little bit more
Noblesse
Let's baggage
But still libertarian
So much bigger Forge
Gcn their cultural footprint
Is ultimately
In some circles
But yeah products
Is plugged into the YouTube culture of
The 2013
Yeah they're not as controversial you can have something
Pretty popular but if
If you don't make waves the people outside of
The audience
May never actually be
Become aware of
I'm willing to bet that possibility
Talk live it's just way outside our radar
Also
Misleading
Third or fourth largest
Best indicator of shows based on Numbers Station
But they're not
That's
For claiming that you're huge cup
Like Premiere networks thing at over 5000 radio.
And have way way higher.
They worked with people like Limbaugh Glenn Beck
Seacrest Inn Coast
Completely different ballgame
Gcn
Putting youngevity fake doctors on a radio station in Barstow California
Also Salem Radio Network had a about 2,000 Affiliates at that time
Westwood one head over eight
8000 station
Even if you accept Alex's
Is 13
Number
Application game
If he ever got called up to
Navigation to Valley
Pretty good about
The business
Feeling pretty full of
Themself
But he starts talking about
Just becoming take it
Molon labe
Wrestling term putting someone over
What's that when you like they're better
Kia
He puts his own shirt over something you would never expect
Is children a big
Color
Glossy magazine
Black baby
He you know you talkin about the magazine in the posters
The image from the shirt become so popular
That's crazy
That's the legendary Patriots stuff
Great shirt
Great so much better than
Gadsden flag and I basically pledge allegiance to
Come and take my gun
Legal and lawful
Cool places all my God
These clips
I don't know why I didn't
He's doing
Bumper sticker giveaways
Bumper stickers but you got to promise not to put them on other people's cars
Bumper sticker without getting a waiver
She do not trust your audio
Hey guys
I heard it was a donut all over again I heard it once in as I
That's weird
You might you might have got you some food or something
The letter
Stretch of the show
They can start to that simulation.
And then for a lot of
Ashoka
He is
Wyoming
She is doing
Goofy b*******
He's doing stuff they clearly is like
Is a joke
Interviews that lady
Is big news story where a woman got arrested for not letting
People, install a smart meter butter house
And
Keeps calling her
Doing the other side
Yeah you can tell he's really having a ball
Because
He explains why
Having fun
Towards
VIP Andrea episode
Sick of these people they are
I hope you're doing
You will be brought to Justice
That's very fake
I will destroy all my enemies
Cleveland
Flag
I'm actually fell on the cats
Yeah I don't I don't like that very false
It's a very performative
In his mind
He has to rationalize have
Just have fun for the sake of
Socks
But it's
Because this isn't
Evangelical
Quest for him
Is really secretly about to accept his version of God
And that's why I
You take this call
And it really really
He had a little inspiration to you II you sound a little down
Forgot forgot to show me the right way and
Friend pointed me in the direction of your show so I think Dad's using you please you can go to total
I know
Yuck
Uno's
Is probably almost one hundred percent
Especially when they're f****** Alex Jones
A hundred percent of a Time Alex is f***** up
Alex takes
The 7th off
He just is gone
Just got
Do some fishing
Course
Is Tolo
Comes back on
Probably
I don't know usually just mentioned be with a friend
How old Rex Widow benefits play
You might
You're never too young.
But every time he's tried to go out with
He's canceled at this time he doesn't call Dan cell
Tell Paul what to do
And that means I turned it off after
Could call
That guy has no chops
And Alex do some
Is it blew my mind
This
I can't understand
Absolutely absolutely
Police officers
California
Veteran and police force
Deserve
Because it sounds exactly
But the system is now
Looking for
Power Trip
How much he loves
But he's going around
Reportedly
Weird
So I
How you find this
Profoundly weird
What is going on
Sue Jordan
Patterns of developed about Alex's personality
The time that we've been watching
Not only is personality but it's style as a broad
You can get a sense for the sort of stories that he prioritizes what sort of angles will take onset story
And what story
He's knows that he's better off just leaving alone staying away from
This story that he's talking about is the story in the news about Christopher Doran
Who's the guy who killed
Some police officers and there was a
That is
Where we in Alex's wheelhouse
As a story he would cover and one you would expect
He would make the biggest
Ballato
We're get to that I don't explain everything everything
Allison Stokke
Who's playing for the globalist
They're about to pull off another huge false-flag to take away is gone
He's a interrupted his own broadcast multiple times
Because there was school shooting
That more
Systematically murdering police
What you would definitely think would be something you could work with
How does Alex respond
This episode of February 8th
That Point Police been searching for doerner for 5 days
And this is literally the first time I've heard him bring that story up
He was on vacation for one of those days but
Yeah it's crazy
Why why there is no reason for this not
Beyond Alex's radar
The first killing was on February 3rd
And by the fourth that Manifesto have been posted online
But listening to Alex's
Future Tagalog about the world being a simulation
The talking all this weird s*** about God joking around with collars cuz he's so angry
What makes this even more insane
Is the what happened after the shooting
Exactly what Alex yells about all the
What time
The LA Police Department was desperate to resolve this
Considering you had extensive military training
Willingness to shoot civilians
In their desperation they made so
Mistakes
On February 7th the morning of February 7th
Actor Alex
Started
Shot at three people
Which is an underhand pitch if I've ever seen one
Alex could knock that out of the park so easily yelling about the police state and how they manufactured the shooting
In order to have an excuse to shoot at civilians people to know that their sheep or something
Cops station perfect perfect
It's a damn layup for Alex
You spent all his energy
Over these last looks
This like
It's not even an issue
He does bring it up
This is the one that he thinks is real
Crazy but I think it's pretty easy to
Acy
One like you pointed out Christopher Dorner is black
Alex's business model is about making
Excuses for white Terror
So I don't feel like
Fields beneath
To get out of his way
Get to
He doesn't
Yeah yeah
The whole story
I mean I kind of do but I think there's more subtlety
It's not captured within that broad
Exclamation
Could fit that into a large
ShopRite
The people that Alex
Consist are not actually
Shooters
Fat in these situations whenever heavy
Are always white right wing
His show
It's one of those groups
Is what he needs
He's believing false Wags is based around the idea that people of those group
Don't commit crime
Ever is the globalist
Cut out or whatever to make it look like
Demonized
When the perpetrators of a crime
Regardless of how closely their actions match up with his beliefs about what the globalist up to
And that should be very f******
Suspicious
Yeah
Daughter is not white
He expresses infusiasm about Hillary winning in 2016
He supports reasonable gun-control measure
Stein for her efforts at getting an assault weapon
And he is definitely not a fan of Infowars
As he explicitly goes out of his way to say Isa
Supports Piers Morgan's Point
Using Alex's
Twisted logic
If you were to say that this shooting in Manhunt worst days
Globalist
Demonize themselves
And if Alex is completely falls apart
Calling the shooting real
Less to do with racism towards
Daughter it more about preserving The Narrative that he'll need in order to minimize and
Excuse white terrorism
Later
This is a protect
Yeah yeah
It's very in
Interesting the way Alex's mindworks
These RV false Flags but I think
If you watch how
Keep you close with
You get a sense that
It's super important
As a defense
Yeah that is it
I think it's clear in this
Next clip
That's kind of the vibe
Shooting
Thinking
F****** stupid
Here's what I got for you I'm going to level it up
Alright I'm in level it up
Movie where you're going to do this
It's still there didn't make the pictures
Put bad because it's going to
Bright
It could be that Obama
Bye
Using one of his own supporters at
The Patsy
In order to make it
Is a right-wing person
It wasn't
What's that
Great sit right
Whatever
It really is Alex
Taking
This is denialism
Deeply f*****-up
Very disrespectful to people who are affected by this tragedy
I think this really happened but also I disagree with all of
Reality so I don't know
I do think there is a race
I think that that's more about that
Preserving
The false flag narrative
Anything else
Might be a little bit
For the eyes are just
Smiling
So I think I am
The pictures
He's talking about
I don't think
Yeah
Know that he was a guy who went and shot a bunch of
People you wouldn't think all my God look at this creepy person
Alex's project
Something that you feel
Probably not good that boiled down to one word
That word is up
That is what he was doing right the f*** there
F***** up
Probably
But
Someone whose opinion matters about anything
This next clip
Blue my mind
Whatever he's talking about here doesn't matter
Not matter cuz that works
Accidentally said something
That I really think you should spend an entire show.
I'm about to cuz I really need to hear more about this
System
What
I think I think that Alex
What does a obtuse
Biomechanical I know they're not mechanical
Please
More about that h
The whole episode about bugs
This is what I'm going to track
Any other time
From now on any times bug some up form
We're going to have to keep picnic this is the new Alex killed his dog
That's wild
Course
It's a day on Alex
The show so there's a new gun
About
Some sort of bail
Going through
Sou gets into that to your
And
Exactly what it sounds
The name of the voice
California
Voice with MS.
Remember it being
October 23rd
California
We said quote I don't believe that this bill automatic rifles
Criminal activity
Enough to Warrant this
Get your guns and the Second Amendment
Where were the Democratic governor vetoed the legislation that could have easily been made law
Ideas that Alex has about this thing that never actually ended up becoming a law
I think that last clip is
Perfect as a reference
Temptation of how Alex
To set him up
To be in a position
To have his cake and eat it too
Free Azrael series framing this gun bill in terms of disarming
Innocence
The government wants you to be the
His real crime
Now let's imagine a scenario where Alex said that
If that were the case Alex gets applied the angles
Does fake and exist to terrorize the public
You take away the guns
Yep it works no matter what the input is the output
It the point behind it is exactly the same
No matter what
It's that it's ridiculous
It also seems beneficial in 2013 that all of his position
So long as Obama is in
Empower almost
From any kind of
Like everything is almost seems to work out because it doesn't really matter which way he's still able to play
Ellen wants 2016 comes around
Now he's
Defending all kinds
So what's your
Defense
The first couple months
This game doesn't work never your
I get really really difficult to play the
Conspiracy
Apiarist
Truth-teller
When your party is in
In control of just about everything and there's no
There's nothing stopping drops
Declassifying whatever you want
There's nothing stopping him from
Technology
He knows about this there's nothing
The counter counter-coup narrative
Asterix
Because even when you're in power urine opposition
That's the way to preserve the business
This model
You get out of
You get out of step with reality
Realized
From this cliff
Just how
You know like you know you can almost take away his
Because there's no bad
I kind of
As long as you cooperate as
Yeah as long as he was like
Wendy was coming up before Trump
He was making good choices in
Successful
Where is reality
Clinton was in office
Before Trump
Hillary or Bill
Culture got much uglier because of people's feelings
Alex
And even with bush
Like it it
It's not
It's not even a
Necessarily
To be there
That's all that really matters as long as the president
Yeah this works
Yeah
No matter how bad he is it still work
As long as he's full of
Arvest
You know on our last episode
As long as his hatred
Conspiracy
And anger
Focus
Outrage
Just directed at the Powerstroke
Really
All that much
That difficult
It's America
Involved
And the problem
To the present
With creating Boogeyman
And of the deep state
It doesn't
The way that Alex
Describing it
So
Nebulous
Anthony
It doesn't work
The same way as
Like bush
Target
Your outrage
Victimized
Recruit
Texas pain comes
The fact that one time
I'm his mom.
I slipped off from a
Did you know that
How close was that
I'm not sure
This story may or may not be true but here's Alex telling a story about a helicopter flying by his mom's house
Dollars
My dad is heaven
12 years ago
Wow
So
For him thinking that is
The real shooting
I mean of course it is
A real shooting his conclusion is
So bizarre
These people came over and flipped my mom off at of a helicopter
Right
Find
And also I don't want to get to
Into doerner
Today except for
To experience the weirdness
Miss of Alex
Two things
Something is real
Because the shooting goes on until the 12th
I'm so tell the 12th so this is probably
I do think so and I'm interested
To see how Alex
Response
The actual story
Maybe he
Is an article
Other than
Bullet points about his Manifesto
He likes Piers Morgan
The real shooting
Yeah and it goes on for the 12
So I am
Hoping for
Serious Whiplash on a
The 9th
Fake shooting
The real shooting again
Anything Could Happen
Him to be consistent
Scorpi gets off the the shooting
Stop
Buju.
Which is weird
Because it was
I remember this very clearly. Of time
The media was all over this
Because it was a very
Scary story
Military training
Who had an axe
The Grind
With the police
Felt
Department
Terminated
And we're willing
To take this route
Clearing their name
Write like
Scary
Circumstance
Yeah yeah yeah because of the movie already talked about
The police figuring out how to
Respond
Buckets
All the f******
Set in
Different country it was set
Down your block
Yeah and he was coming after you
Your brain
Alex the treated is so like
Kind of
It's weird
Talkin about it buddy
You care that much
You don't care a little bit on this episode about that there was news of
Asteroid that was
Comes fairly close to Earth
But everybody is like
World
All right out I like that
Interesting
But these people are liars your might not be okay
27,000 miles of Earth but also
Might be coming for your house
Yeah
Stuff going on in
What happened on this episode that are far more
And here is the first one
I think Alex
Slips up a little bit at the
The beginning of this clip
And then overcompensate
A bit towards the at
Watching all this
Freedomworks
Wyoming
Ghostbusters
George W bush
Whoa
Imma stop right there
Facts
I'd strongly disagree
If this is the result if you take the day off to go shoot a bunch of guns this is not good therapy
Might be very ineffective therapy
I think he started positive things about freedomworks
Well I got it
Why do something
Started
Grabbing it whatever he could come up with
Blossom
Submariner
Effeminate and also
Pretty much just
Scrambling because he get something positive about a group you should be 100%
I really am scared of his
Genuinely
Because that he
Really thought that was funny and I don't
Yeah
Very unpleasant
I think that it's
Towing
Isn't against
Freedomworks
He knows about them
Because
I mean
The fact that he's aware and not again
Memes
Stomper
I doesn't mean that he's taking money
It's a it's a mismatch
Where
He should be
From his own there
Yeah it's another piece of him
You should know that their Koch related yeah
If you knows about Glenn Beck's involvement with
I don't know
Oh and also George Bush didn't call Karl Rove turd blossom
Because you like to talk about
It was reference to a flower that grows out of
Karl Rove made the most
Very stupid
But I was looking up very
And I had forgotten how insane his
Did you know that
Call Maureen Dowd
The cobra
The time now
Silvio Berlusconi
Look up shoes I can play
My favorite though is that used call Vladimir Putin ostrich lay eggs
What's up today or how much of that is PR can I ask
You're buying Hook Line
Idiot
All that lot of acceptance
Match-up yeah
Good humor
I just
Like maybe halfway through you know like you'll see your wrestling or boxing match where someone's cardio doesn't hold up
Yeah
I think Alex is
I just think that he's
He needs to regroup
Good music
I had job
Don't know much about history
Yeah
And
That sucks
What's printings abalone
I don't know I think it's
Another thing
He's obliquely referencing is
Hillary Clinton ad
Recent
Leopold fairly well ability ratings
Most of the bologna
A weird state
He's a real f****** weird place
Crazy
Here and then getting it
I went running today
Stopped
Got to take it again I love running
It's the age-old sign when you say anyways the point is and then get back on
Like you're almost Dismount the weird tangent but then
It's a straight party time
And so he
Begin service
Recovering
The asteroid news
Is a strain
CenturyLink
Something happens
Before
But not very often
The asteroid
Propulsion
Ettore
We see who's calling from an unknown number
What
You can't do that
Plants
Ron Ayers
I was going to Superbowl
Alex is so desperate to get on any other sophono allegedly geraldo's Booker
Who knows
To the radio
Self-love line when I was younger
I do I adjust
To the idea that anyone have a business meeting on Earth
What's going on
Yeah
Pro-ana prostaff
After the Mueller report
You taking calls
Disappointment of Segway
How to display
I think really what's going on
Cover all this stuff
He doesn't
He's decided that the doerner shooting is
Real
Good enough
Rabbit
Positive ratings
Is asteroids stuff
I don't want to talk about it
I'm going to I'm going to accidentally
Globe
This is where I got the sense
But you like he doesn't really even want to be
We doing his show and that's why you keep
F****** Rissa
Thing on stuff
It was all just take phone calls for a couple seconds
I don't want to
I don't do this
I was talking about that asteroid story I don't have anybody
You look take some calls
Starts telling a story
And this is one of these this is one of these
This is where I don't believe this
Great-grandfather was a
I also don't care about this
I do think
This is an indication this is our
Trying to be
I think I think
Definitely coffee
Yes
Unsuccessful
Of course purpose
North Korean dictator
Topside
New York
Chicago
Can you show me where
Around
Because he last out to break
He really thinks that impression is funny
He's really
Yay
Like a bad man but
But also
A guy who's on the quarter inch
Turborower
It's a bit doesn't develop it doesn't there's no
Sargon anywhere I know where problem
If you're doing this one
You go all the way back
22 like
The Irish
You go back to the
The coppers
Chirp the Box
He's talking about
The cops are aloof there bad cops
See see it in their eyes
Reinforces ideas that
It is
The conclusion is
If not
Denial
Denying
So you gets into a metaphor about his dog
Chewing wires
This isn't an example of him
Cuz he's telling the dog knot
Chew on The Wire
I see the look in your eyes suspicious all the time
Don't
Chew on those wires
He's talking about the statue on the wires which
Don't
His
Jumps
Back to the
The shooting
Is incredibly slow
Do you don't want
Oh man
That's unintended
Consequences right there that's that book
Okay of that
What are you doing izbora last
Using the doerner shooting
Hey this is what's going to happen to you
If you try and take our guns
Which is a
Deeply f*****-up way to report on this story
But that one person
Every cop in America
That's not a threat
You know
I know that he does
This way
Had those
You know he had that caller called in talked about unintended
We know that he is at least
Professing to Everett
And he certainly has like Express
Connection with the Louis
Resistance
Is an apologist for Timothy McVeigh
Is a lot of that stuff in there so you know that he feels this way
Like if they trying to take our guns will all revealing that kill about
You know that
Decides
To start covering a targeted
Murder spree of police officers
Police adjacent
People that going story
Assertive in example of
This could be worse for you
Future and take our
That's f***** up I think you meant
As a as a come
At least you
It's just one guy
Target
I don't like your glasses have told approach to this
I just think it's that you know it's the wrong way
It's the wrong way to look at this story
Yes yes I agree with you
Express that it could be
Well yeah
I guess or the reverse
Do you have it could be fake
It really undercuts all of his Meredith
Telegraph
If somebody
Enforcer class
Deserve
With one.
The real world
So
Forever
Has been yelling about how the DHHS
Can pause
Chablis
Go
Bad yeah
That represents
A very severe.
The idea of people who have military
Training
Becoming insurgent
In the Homeland
Is a very real threat Alex
Tubi
People
And now we have a situation where that exactly is happening
And he say
Well
Argument
Screams
Bizarre Bazaar
It's bizarre how predictable
Additional
It's not
Why
This guy
That he loves over
However
That can be used as supporting evidence
Or anyone
Well that's why he fits the profile if it takes until
Basstoven
But all he ever says specifically is like
He wants gun control measures passed
Sports Obama
He likes Piers Morgan
That's about it if that's all that your qualifications are for a deep psychological profile
Of that a real shooter
Did this is woefully
Stupid
Yeah
Simplistic and
But at this point
Jump back to the asteroid party
Because he realizes he hasn't covered
This news
They could be world ending
Deserves to be cover
Your last time you sort of being sarcastic about like
You know
Godzilla
Thankfully this time he decides to approach the issue with class
Aplomb
Sears serious cover
Asteroid Collision Course with Earth
Yeah
Away from the Earth
Right.
You got it
Asteroids
I mean
Happy April first joke day
Not a good joke too long is this cornball Astro
Call zoneaire
Do you have dangerously close to that this isn't this is a weird
. of time
Bizarre
Things to see on his show
I mean I'm actually I'm actually happy that he went to
Space invader
Whatever it was for his
Cuz
Sure
Discogs play Bruce Willis
Also
F*** you man
You can't joke
You did that you're online on Y2K
Like it's almost like
Trolling
I don't know I don't know
Is it like Russia was shooting nuke
Stuff like that on Y2K like
This isn't a parody
Necessarily
This is accurate
15 years prior
But we're back in 20
He is a psychic
That's okay always forget
Yeah
It's on this episode here on February 8th
Alex goes into overdrive
He finishes up his
Normal 3-hour show
And then gets into the daughter shooting
A little bit more in overdrive
Is a little bit more explicit about why you think
This one's real
In overdrive
Contouring your butt
He doesn't really get that much more into
To detail the
It's just
It's a very weird standard of proof to be like this doesn't help with a gun Grabber agenda therefore
It's real by
The guns are the problem
And I don't care who is behind the gun killing people
Heavily implies that Alex
Is it Super 8
Twisted
Either
The defense of
Who's behind
Yeah
That's why they came up with the guns don't kill people people
It's
So weird
Weird
Because if he's saying
This is real
Because it doesn't
Fit the gun Grabber agenda
He has decided what that is
He's created the parameters
Everything
But it also
Implies that all it takes
For something to be fake
To him is with the definitions
That's a low standard of proof
Almost
Not proof at all
He's so close
Too I'm just making this up
Shockingly close
I'm waiting it
I'm paranoid freaks out about someone taking my gun that I enjoyed shooting yesterday
About it
That works for me
But please
Believe that I've read
So it doesn't slip out
Suggest
Another reason
Why you say
Is a real thing
And that is
Has to do
Christopher
Black
He doesn't get to the
I was looking for that key
Feels like it would be right back
Go Fish
Metaphorically
Alucard
So he's StarTalk
To some lady
Who calls in
Who
Is the church lady
But Alex is Matt and family
He's known her for 7
Years according to
It's weird she talks about running into somebody I think
Supermarket
Talks about
Soldier
Suicide
Is it upsetting phone call
Worth listening to
2nd third-hand information
Great
50cc into home Gab
Yeah I just talked to you my phone number
That's what he feels a lot of the time Overdrive
As opposed to
Chucky
The end of the show
He does half hour of overdrive
This is the end of it
All of his claims
That's how you're going to
Literally out to
Empathetic
And put that is
Exactly what he says the media does
Hey hey hey hold on that's when they do exactly
Cries bloody murder about all the time
Guilty By Association
He cannot stop bringing up guys on Obama's border and that means it's a real shooting
This is not good
Shocking glimpse
Turnabout is fair play
But what if you changed it and said I'm going to unfairly only turn about you
False
Call play
Franklin Richards
Situation
I don't like this
I mean I do it once
Hit the way he covers things that matter
Really deeply traumatic event
Yeah there's even when he's
Dealing with it as a real thing
Still f***** up
But I do
Think it's very
Interesting and worthwhile cuz I don't
I don't know the last time
We've seen a major event
The Tappan
Discover today
If it seems like the exception
Not the rule
And what it takes for it to be real
All it is is I don't think it's ever again.
Always an Obama supporter
All it takes for him
Which means
The time that he thinks things
Means nothing
He's not facing
I'm very interested
See how this develops
Over
Time until
Cuz it will
I think the longer that goes on the horses argument
I guess
Cuz there is a sense of it that like
The media will be going crazy about this if it was at
Tea party guide crazy with it
I don't know how this is going to hold up but I think it's
Because it stinks
5 days after this chick started
What is he doing
I have no idea
It's not
So we'll find out
What happens in a later at the
For now
Weider website
It is now
We are also on
The other podcast
Actual application
Where else would
Bugs are real.
What up boy
Let's see
We don't have a lot of winners on this one
I don't know probably did Kill
What does vitamin C do
Steam clean
But I don't think it is
Weird
Cheese fries saving
Lives ended
At the same time be responsible for the deaths
Possibly possibly
Glenn Beck
He probably not killed anybody
Alex Jones
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color