Alex
And talk a little bit about Alex
Have you ever
Glasses
Osborne
Was really young
And I have
Lacrosse
It remains to this day but that my vision was
When I was a boy
Oh yeah
Forgotten a fully straight answer on it
I just know that when I was like very young
I had multiple I search
Define butts
Middle School Junior High
I realized that my vision wasn't
Super Changed by wearing glasses
Let's cross
Okay I realize was kind of just a cosmetic
Okay okay so I talked to MyEyeDr I was like I don't think I want to wear these anymore
I keep breaking
It's no good
They're probably not going to do much
Search for you
Ustadz.
You say that to the doctor when I was younger
Agoura great deal but then my eyes grew
The problem
Fixed
Who were the eye surgeries work
I don't know
Comparison
It's just your way of trying to announce to the audience
It's that you got glasses fishing for compliments
Before the show started
Entire head was
Cleared of everything when I was about to ask you a question I was like
I just looked around for something on your walls and I was like
I got to visit if I had a choice or if it were something that I didn't feel was
Just cosmetic I would probably
Go back
Can get glasses
They look good on a head General
Almost as good as on that ass
Right
Grab
The present is going on
Is Lifan
I get this answer the probably by the time is up
Episode comes out so sorry if
Yeah so today we're going to be going over.
Nomad
What a what a time it was
This episode
When I was getting it ready
I thought it was going in One Direction and it definitely did
Entirely different it's a roller coaster ride
Some of it is unpleasant
Completely absurd
Deeply esoteric
Alright
The grab-bag a mixture of something for everybody
Except
For one very specific person
In this out of context drop from
Today Show
I'll just be honest I love my daughters
Where's my son
Who that's rough
You never like to hear parents say that
Man I guess I also that I'm coming from Alex
That means Rex's not masculine enough
Feels like it might be
Because Alex would be the guy
I need a son
Yeah I don't want to psychoanalyze
Other than to say like
That could do damage
Change to a child
Like hearing their parents National radio
No good
I mean
But you know there's a group of people
I cannot rate
It's all equal amongst them
No not the walk symbol of the technocrats
Share the same positive feelings for me
And that is why we need to take a moment now before we begin this episode
First of all Gabriel thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Deborah real
Next Ed
I'm a policy wonk
That's right
TV show Ed
Thank you so much
Juvenile
I'm a policy wonk
We got
Thank you so much you and I will policy wonk
Watch the last violent
Pleasure
Speaking a little bit with recently about my Santa
Use of living in an RV
So I thank you so much Mickey you are now a technical
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much for making anything like this showed
Going to our website
Jordan an episode of Fantasy Island
Just like okay here's an RV
Lalala
Fantasy Island goes well
It's supposed to be having but it turns out as hell
Open WhatsApp from hell's heart he's you want to be famous no you don't know
Don't
The entire show
And I had to do like
The final
And I kept
Being like
To the final later I got paid I'm literally confused Spanish
Excuse
Not to write term paper
It's right now
I watch the entire season
Where's the turnpike
Finish the term paper
Got it I don't know how I did it
Engaged
What's that what I called improvisational academic
For a large part of my
College career
Classes that I wasn't
Interested
Anytime you're in college
High School
Boston
Text to do
That stuff I found I can Bluff
Really
Today Jordan
Start on June 10th
Hey guess what we have a really familiar guest
Leaving things off
On Alex's show
Lawyers on with the Pepe the Frog
Exclusive on that that has
I love you
Wards.com
As well as the bottom of the hour
They spent 100,000 fighting them
So Alex is declaring victory
Matt Furey
Course of course I mean this is a very predictable turn up
Turning into Alex having
Conference call
Very weird also when they lose
The lawsuit does not mean they have
To pay the legal fees of
Not necessarily
Little bit
Also Alex
Fury had to pay a million dollars in legal fees
I really doubt that
Wonder where he's getting that information
Tantrum I wonder if we're going to find out later
Randazzo are coming up later
Before we do
Alex
Did something on this episode that I thought was really
I don't even know about it if I'd listened
Thousands of hours of his show
Brought back
The the fear that he has
About to be
The Muslim women in the pool supply shop
He brought that back not specifically
Structure of
People of various
Types of
People in places he doesn't want to see them
As adjuster
Application for lot of his
Analyst position
Here it goes again
Office yesterday
That's closed on Sundays
What is that
In
Traditional
Guatemalan
You know what a water bottle looks like you know what it looks like
Parking lot
Why is this place
Do whatever the hell they want
Stories convoluted
Central and South America
I don't know how much that I can take as like
Tru reporting
Not if
Joining the way people are dressed
For our actors
It seems like at Central and South American people are acting address
Also my dad owns a
Piece of a dental practice
Did I get the hookup at
Cracked tooth I saw people who were from Central and South America wearing clothes
So I got to tell you about it cuz they're not
That's f*****
I went to pool supply store I saw Muslim women
Hey I went to the dental office for having fun
This is an interface absolutely
How do you say grow up
There's literally a sentence
About what you're doing
That everyone says when you do this
Don't cover
Always have one immediate visual thing
And then they can
Extrapolate all of that in Central and South America
Different clothes
Here is everything that you f***** up in your
Entire history
Advocating for like he doesn't have any proof that these were there cars
Just buy the car they don't have the
Plate yet
He has no reason to suspect that like
Hahaha
Play I Don't Like
This
So what do you want to do regulate there
Clothes uniforms her
Are you saying I shouldn't be able to
The problem is the behavior that solve it is
But according to Alex South Austin
Is becoming a third world
Which
Great
But it wasn't
I would like to hear this looks like
He'll the sidewalks are all filthy
Trash cans overflowing
The collapse of civilization
We're not helping them for the third world we're becoming third world
Argument essentially boils down to like these immigrants that are coming in at Fern South Austin into 1/3
World country
Dirty diaper trash
Do you think people who litter
Every
Pretty sure it's only snow littering in rural areas no I've never seen any
Littering in rural areas
Again what
The complaint
Okay
You organize a citizen's group with those sticks
But is really sharp
Text so they have the money to repair those f******
Find a solution as opposed to finding someone to blame for it
Sir Leon
Comes along
With Mark Randazzo
In trying to present the
G1
Mad at Paul Joseph Watson
Because his headline
You wrote didn't
Enough
Okay
What you contradicted
Paul does what he wants
What to do
Lot of lot of freedom of expression over there
So I mean
Presentation
Major
Victory
So earlier Alex
Do you have to pay a million
And something dollars
Thousand
You very correctly
Predicted
The vet information
Just bullshitted Robert Barnes
Just guessing about
It would not surprise me at all if they spent over $1000000
It would not surprise
Prize me
That's again
Is Barnes going off of 1/2
That's a regular amount of money
Suspend on the lawyer
Interested in
So what's going on with the lawsuit and what Alex is doing with it and trying to
The claims for
Yeah that's going on it
You see how both sides
Can reasonably claim to have gotten what they want
It seems like a rare instance of a high-profile civil case
Reaching a DC
Conclusion
Thank you everyone
Except
And pretend that they unilaterally walk
In the past month Alex has been screaming about how he's not going to settle that lawsuit
He's going to fight
He's gone on and on about how a Creator Matt furie tried to settle
For a small undisclosed amount but Alex said no on principle
If I know anything about Alex it's that he doesn't do courtroom
Unless he has to
Or unless he's in some kind of position where his businesses specifically off-limits
He has the opportunity to grandstand
Use the cord is a bully pulpit
So I knew that principle stuff was bulshit user putting on a brave face
Because he wasn't sure what he was on the hook for
And what you could be
Liable to end up paying
Siri probably initially offered a really high settled
Alex Presley promised to fight this which helped the Braves money for his legal battle
Became clear that the most Fury was going to win if you want to try was $14,000
Gladly paid the settlement of 15
Thousand
If he thought he possibly could win
And the most
She could lose was
$14,000
It makes no sense for him to settle for a higher amount
Especially given his previous behavior in last something about Discovery could be a problem
That $15,000 is a payoff for him not to have
The disclose is fine
Information in Discovery
Alex guitar lawsuit without being forced to show his internal working
So no matter what
You'd win that's great for him I'm happy for him
And as for Fury
What the lawsuit to get rich
Stop using this work
Promote a message
But he got that in the settlement to
The reason this became a lawsuit because Infowars
Used to order receipt
Request from him
To stop selling their poster with Pepe on it
If they just stopped is there wouldn't
Africa has been a lawsuit
And here in the settlement agreed to put a freeze on sales
Destroy all copies of the poster that they still haven't stopped
That's essentially what Fury wanted all along
Got it
In Fort Worth is no longer using the character
And if they do it again
You could use the settlement against
It's kind of a bummer that Alex can't just be an adult
Yep they made a mistake and ultimately
They reach the conclusion both sides are happy
That's not Alex's game because he is a big old adult baby
Can't Behave that way
He have to claim victory in every instance
Lesti
Lose some sort of appearance of mushy
She's MO
I want directions
Rex wouldn't fight sauce
Here's a thousand bucks just for your travels look good
That's a little thing that's missing from a lot of the coverage
The reason that settlement was higher
Is that you kind of trolling Alex
The 14,000 was the amount that the court deemed that Alex made selling the poster
Images of Fury could look
The settlement
Instead extra thousand bear is a donation
The Frog
Poking fun at the guy who yells all the time but Heather turn the frogs
Kinda prologue
Really seems like that's probably just to f*** with Alex I would
Spilling victory
Temperature
Fight you may have made
He is
Being a real dick
Versabar in general court
The world
Strategic
Infowars
To get 10000 back
And we did this
Intentionally
Create the appearance
If you come against
This is what
You get financially decimated by trying to hurt
And I wants to insult
Theory
Entire legal process
He invalidates a lot of the ways that Alec
What's tries to prison
The first one
It really invalidates all of Alex
Because ideas about being
Upper-middle-class
Living the restraint
This is this is very much like
We're f****** rich
I don't give a f*** about $15,000
So that's
F***** up
Hilarious
That's reviewit to the audience a little bit of the internal workings
Behave
Give It Up
Well I'm trying to push back
Ignite Sao
Invalidates
The same
Sort of we spend money like crazy things and then also isn't
Isn't he supposed to be the good family man
Into all of this like
Zurvanism like I spend 50
Thousand dollars at a strip club
Yeah
I had a little part on Stankonia
Actually artificial member of the dungeon family
Mark run.
I recently suggested Robert Barnes
Just trying to make a name for himself as the lawyer of choice
For the right-wing dumb dumb free speech grifters of the world
The Cassandra Fairbanks
Is the Chuck Johnson
People that you've taken on his clients
There's a clear pattern that applies in
Content
If I was accurate at all
This episode
Here with Mark Randazzo
Robert Barnes together
Kind of a pan
Passing the Baton
And Subway
Mark Randazzo was Alex
Texas lawyer
But the judge rejected his request
Citing concerns about past quotes
Serious misconduct
Run is not lice
Practice in Connecticut
Apply to be an out-of-state
Which is often accepted just a matter of formality
But it wasn't
For him
Because he's shady is
Alex's lawyer Alex needed a replacement
Instepps Robert Barr
In the name of Defending free speech
Took on Android
As well as white nationalist Paul nehlen
White supremacist Euro Jared Taylor Mike cernovich Richard Spencer's booking agent
And gab the website where people
Go to f*****-up
Beyond that is a cup
Wheatley in ethical
Fraud of a lawyer
Used to be the in-house attorney for a foreign company
Recalled Liberty Media
Part of his job was to issue
Takedown notices to streaming to besides
His capacity as Liberties lawyer
He misrepresented himself to
The targets of these lawsuits
Does being outside
Cancel
From them to get them not to pray
Pursue legal action
He told the lawyer for the website
Quote 32b a little gravy for me
It has to be more than the 5,000 you were talking about before I'm looking for the cost of at least a new Carrera in
This weekend
I'm going to want at least used BMW mod
That's not a good way
Who's trying to be like
Some sort of financial
Possibly Pursuit
Even even though he was work
The other people
A hundred percent
Anatole is the worst
He was later working on a settlement with or on a file-sharing company again
Liberty was looking for $550,000 and it runs its whole door on it
Him $75,000
Do you a quote never be able to sue them forever and ever
Eventually Liberty would get wise to March
Atlanta marks
Termination sequence $4000000
State and Liberty
$600,000 in Damages
The Arbiter that case found that market
M60
Association
Kingsborough bribe
Which lawyers are not
After all this it should make a lot more sense
My favorite lawyer of Nazis and white nationalist
Nowhere else to go nowhere else to go original hustle is obviously better and paid more but it blew up
But you know who definitely doesn't want to
People like Alex Jones
Ethical lawyer at all
Alex
You're obviously he's the kind of guy that Alex want represent
Kind of like
Went too far and like oh
Check
Connecticut won't let you be my lawyer I got to get Barn
I don't think he's even Alex's lawyer
Anymore he's on
He doesn't seem to want to be there
It sounds like you really doesn't want to be there
$50,000
Undercutting a lot of the point that Alex tries to make
Victimhood narrative
Whatever
From this experience
Going through this lawsuit
Dollars
That maybe you should
Always
Pursue
Whatever lost
Suits,
I'd be an a****** about
There's a really interesting
Methylone
He's talking about his audience supporting him as long as he doesn't back down
Is the Home Depot account login
Before dishonor
We're going to Raging Bull
Absolutely
Robert Barnes just heard a cash register
A lawyer's advice
Whatever I think to do and never consider the consequences
Billable hours
Supreme
There are no consequences
Wish you would have acted like that
If I was your lawyer back.
Yellow racial slur right if instead of settling
If Alex wound up suing Barnes Barnes
Capacity as your lawyer
If we were in my office
How to charge you
Right
Really does boil down to base
Declaring victory obfuscating at Alex's lawyers acting
Lawyers
How much you love
The free market
Which is great
But he's
Kind of
Maybe
Believe
Which is still a good thing but also like
Like maybe at the fish
Really matter
He ends up saying something
Directly contradict
He said
Bunch of time
Is Robert in love with free market
Different angle
Azusa
Because they were globalism a system
So he says that he's been
Third world countries in communist countries
He gives his Russia
And honestly I don't know what to make
In service of defending himself against
Alex's routine never been to Russia but it's a country
Take to go to someday
I'm not sure if any of this means anything other than ours can't keep a
The story straight
Cuz it really sounds like he's saying he's been to Russia
It's almost it's almost impossible to
Here pronoun reference working
I would bet
He hasn't been to Russia
Argument about how free markets great globalism
That seems like the simplest explanation
However
Has been to Russia
It calls into question all the times he said he's never been there
And why would he say that he's never been
Because he
Me neither Russian
So the only way
I don't know
Interesting to me all day in as much as
An anomaly and it doesn't make sense
Like there isn't a real
To lie
Embellish
Here in imply that you've been to Russia
I think he lies for the fun of it now just to see what
Get away with
I think he's just lying about everything
I don't even know what I'm saying
Barnes is cool
I definitely don't think Barnes is f****** with me
Means I have good
Discernment store
So I thought that was strange
Feeling impatient that he
He's been to Russia when he's
He said that he hasn't
But it would have probably been like
Peoria
Russian
Directions to barely keep their country
The first
In the 20th century
21st century
Why is the dawn of the new millennium
Chris Rock
Example
Midol
Successful
Russia did
We saw all the other victories
We should we can do it better than that
A beautiful
What
What is he saying
I'd like you to try
Parts that busy
Can't make heads or tails
Cuz I don't think
In terms of him being like
Yeah well I'm in bed with Russians
We don't talk to
No
Much imply that
Deify
Idolizes
Some
Things about Russia that aren't
Just realize that
Though they did remove some of the oligarchs
To remain and they have the same amount of power
They just split it between
You were people
Problem
He is right we do it bigger and better as
Star oligarchs
Differently
Yeah he wanted to know what he was talking about Donald Trump
Wonderful wonderful opportunity what is that mean
Does that mean the Heat
It doesn't dizzy kind of implying that Rush
Did help
Specifically it really does seem like
Opportunity
Right
The state of the country that's the most benign explanation
In a large amount of assistance in order to
State of the country is something you would describe as being opportunist
I would see that as being like
Insightful of the time
Opportunistic heavy sneaky
Connotation to it
Ads
I don't I don't know it's implying something real real f*****-up
Beautiful
The problem is
He never asked
Course
Sidetracked
About being an opportunist
God
Hey sweetheart
What
You got a problem
You're upset cuz whatever you're so jealous you got to do with
Okay
I think what if I'm understanding his definition in it and the way that it applies yet
To Trump being an opera
America is like a super hot girl
Hey baby
I am a lot like Alex Jones
In that I am lying to you right now and later on I walk
Yeah it does
Do you like exactly an analogy
He's making
Doesn't look good
It's really it's really
What's showing
His show is
Just wall-to-wall there's so many times
Better broadcaster would have sound
Better
The better for that you're hoping to make their without
Sounding like a real creep
Bizarre
Spirals even further from there which is why he doesn't explain what he means by an opportunist
Yeah cuz you just
Grandpa
This is
Just this is so
Did they destroy me
Because I'm focused on Justice
Americana
It's like a big sexy woman
Want to play
Winners
In one constant connection
Got our ancestors.
God
In the stars and Beyond.
Power
This pivoted
Fast yeah better is a Mini-14 Americana
It's got cuz we're going to commune with God in the Stars
Really really feel like he just did that part on a
You know
Like that reminder that holds like a bounty on him saying you having sex with America
Okay how many times can you reference pulling open americana's
Founder thigh
It does feel that way
Billions are going to get killed in the end
Lord Rothschild
Well that's alright
If you want to see
Shroyer's
All of the Caltrain
Here's my fist ready
Taylor Hart
Loving
You should take this fish from
I want them
Tree Outlet
That's a little upset
You know I'm f****** Americana
The idea of the 1950s
We're going to go to the Stars
Commune with God but we can only do that if I can quickly murder the globalist
Give me a bunch of money so I can have
Jesus Christ power
Yes
I think you some data pretty kind of s***
Even that like even whenever he's like ever have that dream
Somebody
No
No every time you give me an idea of what your dreams are
I'm in a fight
Or like I want to run and I can
Can't run limitation
In dreams
I can't remember the last time I had one
Forget something
Zach crazy
Bananas
Because I guess the f****** Americana just
Slides off my back
Now sure
Maybe it's a piece of
Me and Alex is psychology that's missing
Which is why you guys are connected on
Some kind of superhero super villain
Throughout the day
End
I'm going to play this clip.
We'll discuss it
Really
Really really bad
Studio
Condo Central
For the second
Ebola outbreak
Emma Gretzky
And they're really over 1000 in San Antonio
More phone calls
We are overwhelmed
The 200 people
So Alex has big narrative hear that he's pushing
Congratulations
Right real fun
His ideas are there he has a border
Patrol source
This Ebola narrative is really Alex's main talking point for the day I resisted cutting clips of it earlier in the show
Like it was just a slightly more specific version of The Immigrant
Disease narrative
A big part of his rhetoric
Flog a dead horse
Play every example
This was such a concert
Read being brought up through the show though I felt it was important to address it
Escalation
And the narrative quite a bit
For most of the show Alex is presenting the story is coming from a source that he has a nice
Border patrol
They tried to contact FOX News about it but foxes
Refuse to cover the story
Alex sees this as evidence that he's one of the last truthful and brave news outlets out there
Reality if any of the his backstory for this information is true it's way more likely to Fox realize that this
Insight militias and white nationalist near the border
Just start shooting black people and immigrants might be from the Congo
If any of what Alex is
What is a large source of contact in Foxboro
I see that is evidence that even Fox News might have a Line in the Sand
Whereas Alex.
What are the things that make salad
Incapable of Honor
Understanding how wrong about the story is
Is that
Cease all immigrants as one thing
As opposed to
Two people with individual stories
Experiences
If you'd even spend one second
Considering what these Congolese
Virtually impossible for any
To have Ebola
41 most of them traveled from Africa to
Cuba then to South or Central America
It's not a fast
Strip
Let's their home countries
Months ago
Thank you Basin. For Ebola is 21 days
So if any of them have caught Ebola before they left they would have died on their way
The package has been on their way to the US for months and none of the immigrants who arrived you are symptomatic of
Means they do not have Ebola
And I can say for certain that none of them were symptomatic because Alex is lying about the Immigrant sinapi
Antonio assist
City manager calling Bridge
Call services
I hope there was research
Refuse me and a master's in public health
Is gone on the record
Have all quotes
Been screened by the federal government before being released
Into the United
She also points out that the idea that some that has some unwashed
People is absurd
Many of the people who arrived here as refugees are coming from
Prism higher vaccination rates
The parts of the
Where do earthquakes
To point out that there have been
Is with immigrants that Stephen
True but not the kind
Is worried about
Quote we are seeing what I characterize it's stress-related it'll
We're having some cold some upper respiratory infections
Express they've gone through on their way
But guess what
Fear is addictive
Narrative
Has a real contact
And that clip I just played
About that
In communication
His multiple news team
Teams down there
And what ended up happening
Is that his employees
Owen Shroyer particular
Store Center began yelling at people about Ebola
Swirl around so aggressively that the city of San Antonio
Had to hold a press conference
To explain
People basic science
About how six months is longer than
21 days
These people aren't bringing a bolle to the country
That's stupid
Paranoid
Channel list
Nativist fear
Manifested
If you read some of the stories of these that I reckon
Do Jeezy Get kind of ascent
People that Alex
22c is Immortal threat
To your safety
Jean-Paul a Republican
Opponent of Joseph kabila
Who was known for his oppressive Crackdown
Call I was tortured I have a lot of bad memories of my life
That's what's up
Does Seacrest
PG status
Apologist
Story of
At least 350 immigrant
Two arrived
Tonio from
Africa this way
And unfortunately I can't tell you all their stories
Percent certainty that none of their story is I have Ebola
These are
There are words strong enough for what Alex is doing
There's a danger to his rhetoric
He doesn't realize
Because if he knows what he's doing I can come
To no other conclusion
That he's trying to get these
Alex doesn't have some great stores
Every other source E-40
Time to get info from
Pretending to be a border patrol or something
F****** idiocy one of his interns found on 4chan
And what he's doing
Is
Supremely respond
This is white nationalism of a
Incredibly dangerous variety
If any of these immigrants are attack
Their blood is on Alex
I'd say that without
I've been saying that since
Restarted and one of the reasons
Take that
Is because Alex Goes On
Because our own
He's advocating for men with guns
To protect
Country from
These
Scourge
Gallagher
Warning people about
And this entire episode is
So much
About
Angolan
Immigrants that have come to San Antonio so
You know he's
It's very specific LeConte
You speak again
Men with guns
Protect us from these African
Immigrants that are come again they probably have Ebola
It's insane
Deep deep escalation
Exactly
Immigrants have diseases also attaches to
Ebola
Fragger
It's frustrating
About this
Before but the fact
These assholes will never
Say what they want
You know he's just like
The government people with guns at the border
He won't stay the next part where he wants
What what he wants those
The people who try and get it
If you're going to do something so it becomes defensible to say those things
If you vocalize
The other part
And it just seems like
There's no other outcome that would
Satisfy
Nope there's just nothing
Do not like people who came over in that
I turned themselves in
What they're doing isn't illegal
It specifically
He's trying to
Basically
Create a normalized
He's probably already completely normal.
But the idea of immigrants to come in
Apply for Refugee status should
Yeah babe, into the country
Because it's an illegal encroachment of the country and they probably have diseases
Become airborne
Kangol
Trying to
Do that too
Yeah it sucks up its disgusting it seems like he wants to live in his
He wants Austin to have giant castles built all around
And then he wants Texas to have even bigger
And nobody gets in or gets out there people standing
Therapist
A metaphor of the Alamo
F****** disgusting so Alex
It's a ton of reporters out
I don't know
Is Owen Shroyer at the
I mean
How many of them are really kind of just freelancing
Freeway
We'll get to her in a little bit
The problem that is none of them are bilingual
So they can
I can't understand
Are they of course
Wow
They did bring Google
And I said use a Google Translator
What are your fears
Ebola
He's Worthy
It's not
Ebola
Africans fleeing the Congo
African Ebola
Texas
You don't but so what
Even if it was true even if that
It is
As long as there's like control mechanisms in place
You don't want the disease to spread
We've been aware of the bowl of her long enough
That
People are checked
It's not
It's not as crazy
Suggesting
But the idea of it likes
6 months ago
The Congo or Angola
Because they were afraid
Outbreak
Navigation
They are in any way more likely
Alex right now sees all these African
Folk coming in
They're coming into Texas
And I don't
I was afraid of Ebola
Doesn't mean he's any more likely
These refugees
This is stupid
Also I'm not going to accept
Google Translate
Result
As
Evidence of
Even with help they can translate French
Simple language
I bet they don't know Spanish
Absolutely
America
Yap is language
How's the weather you have bilingual
Another language
The reasons why I think it's so
Important to people
I think it's a really good
Be bilingual
Even if you only white nationalist lunatics disagree
You can do or not do
It really is
Expand
Your mind
Not just because of the vocab all the practice of that
How other people
Express themselves
There's a really impact
Equality
To learning other language
Supported
Arrowverse to it
Does open
Restart to
Who cares I'm not going to get on a soapbox
I'm in the next clip Alex
Is complaining
That no one else will cover this
Stories
Then I suspect
Because no one
Nearly as white nationalist
Richarlison
He'll just waiting
See how the test run on Alex's show go today after that
And so Alex is talking about that and he brings in Mike Adams
Man
Mike
Is so f*****
What he says in his neck
Xclip is like
Hey glad you got kicked off Facebook
Prick
Border patrol
Call me
Azan
From the psychological
Hear something
This Invasion this is an invasion of America
With what
Censorship
Vaccine truth information
This break is being engineered to happen
And then they have to completely control the narrative so that no one
Income online
Absolutely
So
I think there is no
Worst
People who
Seeking Refuge
OG status here
Call them a bio-weapon invasion
Because what do you do
What do you do with an illness you trying to
QuickBook
Look at the country as a body
Write this illness
You have to get antibodies to that
What is that
Man with gun
But this sort of language
This context
Absolutely
I mean they have the right to say I thought
I mean
What they should know
I hope
There's consequences
It's almost like
I want
I want radio listener
To have cookie
Like you know like
What's what how many
Directly traceable cookies can we get back to Alex
Mike Adams
No I mean
It seems like a People's Choice winner Ben Shapiro
The inspiration Spire terrorism
Those people still want to Alex
Yeah I don't know it
It's not it's not fair for us
To fully blame or already
Exist
A universe
Consumption
This is
Zuri radicalizing
It's very scary
Who's calling
All immigrants
Stating
Same
That is the least pass
Yeah
Mike is one of these dudes
2 who like
Pay more attention
Especially recently
The times
He's the one who's pushing Alex
Like what
He came on and talked about
Trump declaring a state of emergency
He was the one who was pushing for like we need to lock up our enemies
Bored with that
But Mike was the one who was making it okay for Alex
Tubi
Yeah who's spearheading it
Luther Royal biochemical but Mike's the one was overtly saying
Yeah
About
Lola
Everybody who
You knows anything
You understand the situation
Basically
Issaquah
In the mainstream media
When they say it's real it's fake
When they say it's fake
It's real that's exactly what we're witnessing now
Wow
That's called thinking poorly yeah you are
Group of people's Pride themselves on
Something like that
Because
Why is not true
So you just do that
Someone says that you just got to walk away
Oppositional Defiant 211
You can't how do you live
I think he's
Gaslighting
Someone
Maybe Jesus
Show years ago
There was some Ebola
Taking care of incredibly soft
Globalist worth
Thwarted once
Again by Alex
Silk and now they're going back
It could be
I know from researching that because we did that episode
The coverage of the 23rd
Outbreaks
That media was covering
I know that people were talking about it
Team
You covered it up
Back then
Which I can say categorically is not true
Here's Alex
George York
And everyone else will cover it up
Not true at all
Were the media to cover it
Mike Adams would assume that it was not
It would have to be
Yeah
Making arguments
Like distrust
They pretend it's a healthy distrust reality
Alexandra
Spliff
This is the last one from
Look deeply irresponsible
Characterizing
Why
With the captured federal government
Alone
Congo
What is the second largest
Outbreak
Baby just a f****** life
Wandering around
It's not 300,000
Thousand last year
Wandering around
If you are someone who believes
And you believe these people might have Ebola and there's thousands of them wandering around
How do you know if someone that
You see wandering around San Antonio is a
Immigrants
The Congo
Their skin
I mean
It does leave
To suspicions of everybody who might
From the Congo
The Congo person wandering around San Antonio is now officially according to Alex
Suspicious
Every single black person walking around
We need to be safe
Every black person
I understand I understand
Fully that that's not what Alex is saying
He's implying
That's what's been
The rhetoric that you putting out
Any height
Much like that
You do you need guns on the border
He's avoiding staying the part that is the real world application
On the Border stopping immigrants
You are wanting them to be shot
If they try and enter the country
These people wandering around San Antonio you want everyone to be suspicious of anyone who looks like they might be a
That's
What you're doing
Especially in the context of today where he's talking about men with guns on the border
There are border militias with
Guns
Kill people
We need we need to monitor every black person in San Antonio
All the f****** time
So we get to the 11th
I studiously avoided trying
Play n
Rainbow snatch
Material belly Weavers
Character that you.
I believe one forgot the adjectives
Brilliant
You don't know Millie Weaver is an employee of Alex Jones
What she believes is some sort of a parody of feminism and the last
Successes of the lgbtq community or something
More more
It's usually pretty dumb
So she went out to Pride
I want you to put your mic down
This is going to make you a little bit like
Screaming possibly
Your what is Herb it is
She goes out the
Viewer discretion
Seems to be highlighting Mike Pence's homophobia
It seems to be
Taking his hatred of gay people as a virtue
It's like oh yeah you want to impeach
Guess what you get then
It's almost a threat
Billy weird for a bit
Normally you probably want to be like
Mike Pence doesn't hate gay people
Traditional Values
But this seems to be making
Millie Weaver at least
Is very conscious of the fact
That should
Be president
Things would be very bad for the lgbtq community
And she's wielding that
Almost as a trump card guy just like
You you think you want Trump impeached
Be careful what you wish for jerk
Yeah
I'm confused
Is she
Parroting
Cuz she's almost more an effective parody
Of what the heart rate
Thanks
They are parrot trust me
Cheesin
Ann Coulter
Brilliant parody
Commentary
Are they can always go
Just don't think it's well-thought-out cuz there is probably
Some kind of
Bet you could do along the lines that might have something
District
Like it really just seemed
Like
Piano
I don't
Trump impeach
If you get weed
You want
Your survival is at risk
Yeah
It's f***** up is there a
That's what the plan was to go to the pride parade
I'm pumped.
You want Trump impeach
And they go yeah and then she says
You love Mike Pence
What you trying to catch them knowing like a like a Snowman on the street
Get people excited about Trump
Down to earth with the
What don't you know that pain to be president then
Which is
Yeah and also there's a fundamental thing that's like
People are drunk atolls
Street festivals and things like that
If you're going out and you're like I'm trying to do is
Serious piece of reporting
People are sucked out they don't want to I want to talk to you
I caught them
Not realizing it a drunk exuberance
Cares what point do you make
Is bringing up Mike Pence's homophobia
Not celebrating
It's very weird that I think we can all agree on
Are Hollow ground
Man on the street interviews during a parade
Just have a great time no political b******* those organizers
Press passes
But it's very hard to
Controlled flow people end up generally being able to skirt those rules
Especially if you're just recording online
Like an iPhone
Nope can't you just love me
The world's greatest
Satirist
Mark Twain of our time
Alex
African immigrants
Nonsense
Escalated
Alex's in a really f***** up mood
Episode
Cuz there's a little bit of video that Alex plays of someone
Like pushing it
Camera away
Doesn't want to be on
Anselm
This
Really
Stitches The Incredibles
Reporters
Congo Ebola
Nothing about any of the information
Sweetheart
Indicate
Please adjust projector
Thing to put on
Information
Now I mean if you had videos I've been like
This is just Alex's
Through
Replacement
Demographic replacement nonsense
Really
Driving train
Bucked up
Cheese
Hypocrisy I hate it but remember when
Publican
Congressman beat the s*** out of a guardian journalist
I do seem to recall Alex B100
Overjoyed was just like hey can you not feel me
To how deep out
To this whole
This whole look like
Me feel unwell
It gave me a little bit of a
Flutter and AFib
I just think he's
There's something really f***** up going on in
On the 11th
Congo Community groups
Thousands are coming get ready for it
Where's my clipboard
I've got that Kongo Klub
60 clubs here
Local Congolese family
Try to make a sound secret-spilling home
So what thousands more come
Millions,
Oh no
No no no
You going to
Dodge
You are done long ago for you
You stupid a******
Couple things that really Disturbed me about that first of all the voice obvious
Then the editorializing
Somebody does within that voiced really f***** up
The idea that African immigrants
Coming in now would ask for reparations
Kind of silly
I think he's trying to distort that
Entirely
And then beyond that
Hear an echo
And it really drove home
He's in a much worse
Yeah you know that the sound quality of the show is diminished
Is an echo when he starts yelling
This is not his professional studio anymore
I doubt there's a there's a
From quality to it
Angrier and angrier
Descend
To worse and worse
Environ
The people who assume that minorities
People so much
Probably only do it
Because they're so awful
That they are hated
It's not like everybody hates white people
Is that you guys are
Yeah if you deserve it
He's group
Why wouldn't they
Where at
Opposition in the
So it was nice web Alex makes it really over it so much of his
Is about this Democrat
Replacement ID
This is all just
It appears that these Africans are going to come in and vote Democrat
Which he talks about all the time but it doesn't bear mentioning
It's so f***** up
But it's become so normal as a piece of Alex's rhetoric that it's almost boring
Yeah yeah yeah
Reminding
By the Millions
What happened
So
Nationalism stuff won't be allowed to run everything and run
Break everything that they want to end
How can we allow that
How do you not know that your
You know you're awake
You eat knows that he's a white man
Why
Nationalist
Yeah yeah with the ideas of what's going
Naive
Stupid
Whatever it is
Willingly
Whatever it is it's a it's a lack of
Caring about getting
Engaged
The actual
What's actually going on
And the f*****-up miss about
More evident in the I mean the shity voice was racist
Put the start of that is just literally
Woman
Tries to help write
The story is a Congolese woman who lives
America knows more people
Country-of-origin are coming
Wants to make them feel welcome
Alternative
Please respond
Congolese immigrants
Made to feel not welcome
Exactly treated like scourge
It's f***** up really like his Congolese woman trees other Congolese immigrants
Or better headline for Alex
People shot at border
So
There's a big thing happens
The 11th
Rodger Stone comes back
What quarter about his case but that doesn't mean
Talk about
You can talk all he wants publicly he just
His case and anything that's related to it
Shut his mouth
About things that involve Mueller the investigation
His own case
Any offshoot of that cave
WikiLeaks
Jerome corsi I assume
Randy credico
Publicly
And that's what you want to be
Yeah yeah for a long time because
Even if we had you on to talk about anything
You would immediately be like
Yeah I know I understand
Cyrillic
That's what you assumed
We find out that there's a psycho drama going on
This interview is
Tents
Bizarre
And I think it leads Alex to start
But we'll get to that when we get
Here is Alex
Welcoming Rodger Stone
Rodger Stone
A person's good to see your face
Breaking your silence now
For this segment
I would choose Gene Autry
Feel so good
Really opening
Excited
Near them and at work on the phone situation
Yourself why is
Rodger even on the show
He can't talk about his personal stuff
He doesn't really
It's weird situation you have a gag order Alex even makes clear that like
We know you can't talk about that business
It's always wondering what are they going to do
I thought one of Alex
Subtle digs
Thank you for contacts
President
Show that no one in the mainstream media will go back in
Infowars today
And set the record straight
About John testified
Yeah we're talking
That's what we're doing we're talking to Nixon
About John
His rundown of the
The candidates
In 2020 of course
It's a pointless interview most hearts
The only thing that were interested is
You going to prison
You can't talk about
Is make a poop show
Malik
Loves it
Their chemistry has not skipped a beat
What is electric
Wolf
Oh man Alex is not good
No
Second
If that joker is really the one that hits the sweet spot for you
We got a long way to go it's also really funny because on our last episode Alex was talking about
Losing his shift for a poop joke
Crazy
Oh boy told you there's a psychodrama
Going on
And I think it really starts to manifest
In this next
What we're Alex
It's kind of like
Hey man
You called me
Flash
Messages
You look freaking
You're looking pretty good
Give him an opportunity to answer
Yeah it does sound like that
Why didn't you talk to me that sounded really
And that's because you answer than Alex was like
To give at least a diplomatic
Space
To break my gag order if we talked more
We have an energy
Between us
You antagonize me I antagonize do we just kind of b*******
Negative influence
Conversation probably is what
But also it's interesting
To know that
Not talk
Alex
Is really hurts it really hurts but also he thinks of Rodger looks great
Pretty good
Looks like it's a little bit spinnerbaits
T-shirt
I'm not sure
Won't stop.
Talking about how good you are
Rodger
Infowars
What a pro
Keeble to get his plug-in so in order to do that plugs
Transition to a compliment into the plug that needs to make to make his own plug
Third stage now so good
Cheese's
So I confronted him about the wire
You texted me
I don't think Alex was satisfied
With the answer that started
Interruption I think that he still wants
Trying
Guilt
Rodger about his
Make it all about himself
So what he does
Is bringing Owen
Shroyer to try and help kill Rodger
Could you please tell Rodger that I am not
Rodger look at our son
You have to talk to me I know you're just saying that I haven't you talked to Arboles
Call room together
This is the level of like
Just Petty
Drama
Shroyer Inn
Rodger call me back
How do I get him back
So come on over here
Let me grab that Mike's Runner need the table there I just decided to do this
Why won't you call him back
Hey buddy is right here you got a weird beard with no mustache now that's what happens when he doesn't have a father figure
Look at beardies Cross months later
Little Owen Shroyer
He really misses you man
Jesus imagine
Feeling
Jilted by Rodger
Emotionally imagine not knowing
The outcome
Did you even bother
Oh by the way at the end of every relationship rogerstone is ever had
He's f***** off and told you to go to hell unless you have blackmail
It was next clip before
To have a little bit of a back-and-forth
Do a little bit
About the house
Biscuits
Literally
Will talk more about this
Danaya tried to explain what the
It's probably cuz you don't care
You're working towards
Predetermined
Conclusion
Goofing around like that makes it
Fully clear to me
There's a pause
Disability
Even though and has Ebola
All bulshit
Display makes it so clear
Ebola
In some cases.
The surviving human testicles for periods of body care
29 survivors of the
The 2016 Ebola outbreak
Had some about a fragmented Ebola in there
With 63% of that 9%
Still showing signs of it
They survived
This is why the World Health Organization
Has specific guidelines
The place for sexual activity for people who survive
How did more research
Be done on the subject
Survivor seamanship
Should be tested every
And until they have
Justin Theroux the comeback
Refrain from intercourse or used condom
This takes care of any concerns about possible transmission
It may calm my or may not even be possible
Ebola and the guys were like hey
Knock it off for about a year
That's a little simplistic but yeah
Survivors of Ebola
Because Ebola deaths
Hideout in the
Testicles
Inspect a person for up to a year that's not
If you have Ebola in your nuts right now you're going to have Ebola in a week
Misrepresented
Information in order to reinforce
Is completely incorrect a surge
That these people in San Antonio
You don't know what you don't see it it's in the balls
Instead of presents
It's that it's not just like hey
That's not even just
No
A virus
I got to do a little bit of homophobic
Goofing around
Yeah yeah
Pretty stoked
Advocating
Murderers at the border
To kill these people
And then
Turn that into a homophobic thing as well
That's really a box right there
Spurt at the pivot
Yeah yeah
So there's something going on
On the show
Amy Rogers
They're having a real
Lost friendship moment
On air
But also
Matt Drudge
Picked up that Rodger stone is on it
Chinese pop
Link
He top LinkedIn
Alex is super excited about the fact
Infowars.com source.com
Newport.com
Website the world not just the biggest news site is
In the world
Shot in the world
There it is live Rodger Stone breaks silence
Keep Springs
I think the interview was supposed to be a bit shorter
But he keeps
Stretching it out because he knows that we're top 10 that much traffic
Bratz
We also staying with garages the top news in the world in the number to website total but
He doesn't say you can look it up
So I just don't
I know
Currently the number one website in the world is Google
Number two
Number three is Facebook
Wikipedia is number 5 Amazon, or bunch of
Chinese website like Baidu and secu.com
Top 50
Drudge's
50 sites if you only consider the United
You can make an argument that YouTube is in Subway's news related but there's also a lot more than just
You don't want to count
The top news site
Send a real tough time figuring out what
Constituted a news site so I can check Alex's
The top news
Alexa allows you to filter their results
And when you do that
You only include new sites
Guess what
Number 22 not number one
He comes in behind Reuters
Bloomberg znbc USA Today Forbes Washington Post Fox News
Yahoo news the guardian New York Times AMC
From Shutterstock
Still considered rudge the number one news source
Right
No he's not
Website
It's number
In the news
Category
Alexa Davis subcategory of news which is
Headlines
Which perfectly describes Drudge
He isn't even number one
Headlines
Check the garage
According to 132nd biggest website in the world
60 second biggest in the United
State which is very impressive
He is nothing to be ashamed of
But it really does disappointing
If you previously thought it was number 1 or 2
Expecting like
He was embellishing B
Lottery Post
No might want to spend it and say that Alexa is a company that's run by Amazon
So fine
I decided to check
Slightly different
Metrics than Alexa and they don't
Include a wide range
So this number is a little bit different
Number 41
How to claim
Also they're not number one news site
BuzzFeed
He'll are all
Far above drugs
Mypoints
Shut up
Because
Drudge is the biggest website
The world
George was founded in 90
T95
Who is launching his career
So the whole time
Has been peddling
Has been right there
How to identify
He's the most important biggest thing in the world
Exaggerating drudges place in the world is one part hero-worship
But one part pathetic narcissism by proxy
Ezekiel's
The two of their careers are like super intertwined it
Maybe there is something to that
There's probably
Probably a piece of it
Yeah I mean it also benefits him
Specifically to
Because the only time we talked about drudgereport really is whatever he
Audit
I just don't I don't play it
The number one or number two
Okay
Conservative Folk
He's what
Turn the fire
Brings up headlines
From Dr gelot he's just covering a story
He brings it up outside of his
Is personal connection
But he also brings out the first I thought it was almost like
Advertise
Alex
When he's on
That's
You know that kind of look at how great I am because of how great this is
And I'm on the number I'm the number one
Result Autumn number one in the world
Yeah I definitely believe that that's fair
Yeah
So Rogers on
Drudge's doing the advertising forum
Everything is great
Some polls
I think this is going to last
Because he believes
But there's a mystery candidate
I need a real people this is not
With Hillary and
Michelle talking about
Alex is an improv guy
Rodgers throws that curveball
Yeah that's
Braunig Lake
Where is that reporting earlier
Like where is it
You never mentioned it before
Needed Rodger to bring it up to ever question
Never ever mentioned
Alex Express
Qanon
Is electric
Psyop
Design
To try and
Fracture the connection
And Donald Trump
Trump doesn't like
Rodger
Coronavirus
And against you
Do you hate Rodger now
You guys are falling out your big enemies now
Chewing on movement
This is
Sending out my
Disgusting
Really I take me to learn to
See-through of that those sorts
Things like you
Like a wild child
I don't think the logic
Conclusion
To come to is this
That's the other kind of bad thinking
You came to the right conclusion people
Is the dumbest possible Road
And you're a s*** advocate
Reach the right conclusion because you found a way
To make it work for you
Your main goal is to only obfuscate the same way just have people come to you you know
For sure
So we learned Twitter
You know I mean
The biggest websites in the world
Love it
But it turns out it's days are numbered
Before you said I'm looking at it
Probably probably
He's a counter-puncher
The idea that Trump has a
Conservative
Twitter ready to go
I don't know what level
Of
Whack
You've got to be
To pick the facts
Going on the president using the powers of
The presidency
Has just been like okay
Weave designs
Conservative Twitter
We're just waiting for the right time
Which I assume is
Very shortly after Mike Adams the health Ranger is kickoff
Sprite you know what then going
It already
Call Jack
Just yeah
He's already over there probably right
It takes a lot to get
Is it is weird
How
Impotent
Trump is showing him
Himself.
Even as he
Exercising
Ridiculously
Powerful pain
Like so much of him
Saying stuff
Is just
He says he's going to do something
The news covers at people get all excited or all angry about it
And then it turns out later that he
Nobody cares because it's 5 days later
It's clearly to preserve this base
It Feels jilted by social media
Companies
Strategic element to
Assertive
Do that
We got that settled I'm sure
So
It does next clip Alex gets back to his personal
Feelings
About Rodger
Did you try just once again
To know why find out
You call me
From Rogers
He does not really care
Did Alex Fields reject
Except maybe twice on the phone while 34 months
Your Calculus
Horse
I don't think Alex got what he needed out of that
Exchange
Really glad he's top links
This sort of breakdown
I mean also insurance
No in full knowledge that he's a prop
Even though it is so obvious and I'm
How stupid these people are
Trump
Why don't you return my calls anymore
Dude
Don't have loyalty
How did you not already know that
I'm like gravel in the
I still feel sad for how stupid you are you don't
You don't feel it
Sympathy for the
The people you feeling empathy for the situation
You know people who don't deserve
That sort of treatment
The care about Alex's her feelings is that the bridge too far
So we get back now to the idea about the CIA
Telling Alex that Michelle Obama Hillary Clinton
To discuss running for president
Hey guess what Rodger Stone
Can you comment on that
Dark Horse
Comes from nowhere
I want to FedEx.
You are going to stay with us
I need you
Cuz you're all you're doing five more minutes
That was
That was a lot every single
I told you before
Do you got in that clip you got Rodger rejecting Alex's
Nonsense
CIA told him something not true sources are shittin
Michelle doesn't suck
What are you talkin about
Alex
Uses the term Dark Horse
It doesn't even sound like a dog whistle in anyway
Usable colloquial term
It's so
Self-conscious or whatever
Brown
It's very shows The Mentalist
Politically correct
So
Yeah yeah it seems like
He's afraid that his listeners are going to call in and be like you should have called her
You know like
Merry Christmas
Visual think he's going out of his way
Responding to imagine
Criticism little gift from like Media Matters
Because Michelle Obama a dark horse
Cuz that would be Luke
But it is not okay that he's still doing
She's a Man
Narrative
Spiraling
Weird
I think Alex has started drinking
By this point interaction with Rodger is not gone
For some sort of emotional recognition on Rogers part that he hit
You wouldn't call me I texted you and you said we didn't have to talk about your case
I thought we were friends
We've been in this Burg
Sears now
If you've been on my show everyday my main source of information
My brand for you
Basically
Threw me aside you needed something and I don't got it and I think
Cuz it starts to get
Real weird
The end of the show is
It's
He's clearly showing signs of
Being f***** up
Yeah
She gets back from break
Can't Stop
Elizabeth short-segment drudgereport.com
Brokensilenze.com
Ebola from Congo
Assault
He's really exaggerating a lot of what footage
He's getting some of that. Keep them over
Human Rodger wrap-up interviewing a fairly boring
Because
Nothing's going to stop what's already happened
Please just tell me
Do you love me
Degree to stay in touch
He'll be back on the show and Rodger plugs his stuff
It's all good
Alex
Ebola bulshit
Groups
Millions are coming
More
What diseases
Commander become creatures with Democrats
You hear the way he's like gasping almost
Is that his
Is
Verbal pattern his shift
Intoxication
Also he's literally
I wouldn't be mad about these people but they're poor uneducated and disease
I think I think
You have no reason to believe that
No evidence of any that you don't know anything about these people
You don't know what economics
Situation any of them know their educational background
You're f****** bigotry
All you're doing
A white National
Yeah
We want we want the best immigrants
Reinforce
My theory is that Alex has started
StarTalk
Conspiracies about these immigrants
Interview with the two of them
F****** in sex
Distance
This is real clunky because one guy is
Clearly been drinking
And the other one has
EXO
Phones kind of trying to keep the ship moving forward
And Alex is just
All of it
Why do we have to take everybody
Got new clothes
After pouring under-educated now there's the Upper Crust
They are both bad because
Is Flo
Why do we have to take everybody
Smartphones
You can play
Humanitarian
Free stuff
Give us your money b****
That's amazing
The apologizing
Michelle I'm sorry Lord Jesus f****** Christ these people are coming over
Bile
Anchor baby scam the place with the
Completely lost
Whatever
It is
It's all of his narratives wrapped in one
It gets worse than this next clip because he takes it
He takes it to another place
But he has no reason to
Support.com
Haberdish and the videos
Not better
30%
Because it's
I don't like how much you saying baby quite frankly
It's up
Goddamn
I don't know what he they're not like us
Hi there Muslim I do not know what he's doing man
Like for this entire episode the attacks on the refugees from the Congo or pretty
Focus the first couple hours
10th episode
Who's the skull
Completely inaccurate based on over white nationalism pretty straight line of
Yeah Mel towards the end of the show
Drink
If I once knew anything about
Population is 90
6% crisp
Only about 1% of the country is Muslim which is
Not too much higher than the u.s. percentage
I really think Alex started drinking during the commercial break
Rodger was on
Because he knew the garage was like to answer was drinking out of a Drudge
Call boy
A camera
And Owen seems pretty annoyed
Like if you're watching the video It Doesn't
He doesn't seem to be enjoying
Idea exchange Altima
Alex's Behavior has completely changed
It's today
He's trying to working all the
Four groups of hate
The build-up is conspiracy in Owensboro
Keep the ball moving forward cuz he's proud of whatever
Disgust
Open picture
It doesn't get better
Would like to know what because he's only on there for 3 hours
I would say
Longer than 3 hours to get to Muslim
Really low
Could be because of his
Lankybox
I don't know if that's
People respond to substance
Differently
He has a point where he
Drinks
Pretty quick
Keep maintain
Sometimes
Some don't do nose
Biology furious at
Anyone
Who says why are we have to be the one
Sure I hate
I hate that so much because
There's a big is a big part of this Americana
You know
That's why we take them in because that's what originally Drew people to this stupid
We were so great
And now they see us for the white nationalist
Dumbasses that we are
And that's what's
Shroyer
He's one of the
He's a brave America
I don't think so
Just me Having the courage of going in there
America right now
Humanitarian Aid
Giving out foreign country and white people are bad
Man he is going through some
About it being a brave America
To his question about why the US is if the u.s. is so bad
So much for it
But I'm not going to provide
More fun
Before Trump Campbell.
The only politician Alex
And Infowars completely supported was Ron Paul
He was a gold standard
Alex's operation was fully behind
For president
A 2008-2012
Alex love Ron Paul so much support it is wet noodle
What is Ron Paul's signature issues with his proposal to literally abolish all foreign aid
Opposition Alex Jones guest Webster Tarpley his amount to willing genocide Intuit
Even Figures were fairly conservative look on Ron Paul's approach to this issue
His Manifesto
Cruel and really f***** up
But this is Alex's favorite politician of all time
And I've never heard him say something like I love Ron Paul but I think he's a little out there on one
Stop sending emergency aid
Two places
Is that when you exist within a propaganda organization
Waterford
Who's dad said on eliminating
You don't get any points
From bringing up how great this country is her providing for it
Manifestly again
Is very slow
Operation exist
As an opportunistic Lee abusive machine
Infowars supported Ron Paul's desire to abolish for it because it would hurt other people
And presumably have more
Provide more money for quote unquote
Now they're perfectly happy to act like they support for 1/8
Said Aid as a weapon to shame immigrants and refugees
Understand
What appears on the surface
To be hypocritical
But if you understand what
What it was about their former position
And their actions
It becomes clear that what motivates both is
A hatred of
People unlike them
Yeah
At a certain point
Do you think they're going to go all the way around and be like hey we're going to start sending more foreign aid so
So you don't come
It'll be an interesting argument for them to try and make I don't ever could because it would probably
Probably involved like
Taxation
Interesting
Attempt on their part to make like a compromised
Between these weird beliefs
I don't know
I think that they value
Cruelty
Seymour
Hangouts I don't I don't think it would do that
Cuz it would be like decreased cruelty and increased tax
What is a non-starter
Tecumseh Inn
Another Kaitlin Bennett
The girl who is most famous for walking around
Kent State with a
Yeah she's great she is
Douche
Got involved
Point USA Charlie Kirk's organization
She's all over the place
I don't really have many feelings about her other than like
This is a f*****-up
On the show
Pikachu
She starts talking about an interaction that she had
Infowars
And what you clearly describing as someone who's willing to talk to her until they realized who she was
See this kind of
My God
Disorder lack of awareness
Probably
Flaky realize
Pirates remember is working now
I don't like her so she he went and got his dad
His dad and himself.
Democrats that are out there
It happens all the time to me if you were minority
Every time I go out
Well the only thing
The same every time he's you
So is the
Used to be happening every time
You go out you got to realize the only variable that is the same
Is what you bring
She doesn't either
I believe all Democrats are programs
2 attack
I think she's is specifically trying to say that
It's all women
As well if she's receiving a bunch of and I'm sure she is receiving a bunch of
Backpacks
From the quote-unquote
In the videos that she put out I don't know why I did
Myself but I did watch a bunch of them and I don't see that being represented
The problem does exist on
And it's wrong I'm totally wrong.
Like you are
Definitely
Poking
I don't know baby I know who she is maybe I don't
I don't want to talk
You anymore
That's not your programming
Realizing the conversation you're in
Is with someone who has bad faith
How is this
How old was the
Mid-twenties
Yeah
Videos here in a second
Because like I said I did watch
Watch a bunch of
They're dogshit
But Alex is really on this thing
I spend a milli
Caitlin out there
All these dudes
I can't believe these people aren't chivalrous
Am I
In the middle of decry
Imma keep doing it
This is right thing
Pinterest
I'm literally
Armed man
Blackwater peopleready
What
We'll have our women defense
That's crazy there's a lot of craziness to go
No it's not
Remember all the times you talked about Blackwater
Curious
But the other thing is he's using
Their perceived victimhood to try and
How many dollars is $2,000
Which is f***** up we can't send women out there their two-week by themselves
What happened to open carry
What happened to your whole life
Michael Moore is a hypocrite cuz he has armed guards whenever one should just carry guns themselves
Why not just give Millie and her Gunn
Fairlady
We can't allow the women to have
Don't think that that's what's motivating Alex
I think it's that he knows that that's bulshit
You need
A show of force
Around them
But he doesn't want them actually have a
Guns
He doesn't walk
These things escalated
He just wants like big muscle
Around
Infowars
Former Blackwater bodyguard killed today in a quote self-defense
I made it just come down
Misogyny
Chivalry
I don't know 100
So I don't know why I did this to myself but because Alex kept going on and on about these assaults
Started OverWatch
Although Kaitlyn's videos that you just put out
What you want down to Pride
Dashi playing the victim super aggressive
Looking for a soul to see
Never watched any long stretches of her working
She is
F******
Is a person
Palmistry
That that style of B
The only value that she has in that field as a as a person on the street reporter
Is that she doesn't
Stop talking
That's basically the only thing keeping the performance review
That would be in the pros
Everything else should be in the neck
Like you are
Don't stop
Looking for
The assault that you suffered is that some girl bumped into her and then pretended the cheat gotten pushed
That's why she
Later
To her because a ton of people
Complained about her behavior
She might get charged with disorderly conduct
Which is just not something that happens
Disrupting
Did you get up that stuff accounts with your behavior
Kaitlyn
Complain
Cop asked if she'd like to file a complaint you was very helpful
The Weeknd
Kaitlyn's and realizes
She has the assault on
So she considers filing
Play
But then she realizes that if she doesn't have to take her
Able to post this video
She so desperately
Immediately she's clear about not wanting to file a report and starts reframing the situation
Is the police wanting to
Skater proper
The cop handles himself quite well
Making it clear to her that he knows what games
She's playing and that if she wants to buy looking
Complained they can do it
But if she keeps bothering people that might be another
Keeps asking
Stop
Explaining to her
Consequences
If you're out in
Public
People keep complaining about your bike
You might be
Wellshire
If you're drunk and yelling at somebody
You could be asked to leave somewhere even if it's a public
What place
You're right they are
Absolutely suppressing the free-speech rights of Alcoholics in bars these days
Alex is going to take this up you might you might run
Drunk Twitter
Doesn't really pathetic display video
There is one woman
Is the f****** coolest
It's okay ones out there pretending to interview people and then just being like that
There's a really drunk girl with blue hair
If you keep saying
You're the gun girl
It's like she just keeps
Cracking herself up
Baby laugh so hard it's ever been on
Infowars Water Bar
It's delightful
That's great
That's so much more
Don't even bother
The lady got hit with a milkshake you are a lady.
Feeds into their victimhood, we are proud of
Imagined accomplished
I took a picture with a gun
Girl with sincerely laughing
About the idea that Kaitlin Bennett exist
Is
So delightful I love you
That is great
There's another clip that she has
You know what she has on
Egregious
What happened before this
Video clearly edited to make it look like it was completely unprompted
Seem like it is
Agonizing
Yelling at her so she can prove her victim
I definitely don't think it accurately portrays their interaction
It's propaganda
And the messages that Caitlin is a victim of leftist violence
That's what
The video is actually about
It's not about Pete buttegeig supporters at all
The message is
Leftist are attacking
This
Steeply white woman
Yeah that's what's going on
The last two-and-a-half years
I've listened to thousands of hours of Alex
But I would do that all over again for iWatch
Another 20 minutes of doing whatever it is
She does
It's just bad faith trolling masquerading as journalism
And more than that it's
Boring
Misinterprets news isn't it
Not interested
And she's not even really
Clever enough to spinner way out of most
Interactions with
She's talking to
Pride rally
Be there in just loves the attention
Do it she respond
And I'm getting it and I'm getting it I love it
Propagandistic better control
2xist
It's really easy just to counter with something like what
Some dumb s*** like that
She doesn't even have the chops to think on her feet on that basic level it's
Disgraceful
But bottom line
That girl shouldn't have bumped into her but honestly I lose my ability to care about her complaint
Directly offered to take a complaint
File it for her
Would slow down the release
Propaganda victimhood beta
Nvidia
So I decided to look into our little bit because of how it's
Stream Alex isn't
Results and stuff but
That's why we talkin about a little bit
I promise I'm not going to talk about
I don't I don't have fiber in
Like I was trying to find a way to capture
Ashura at this is going to make sense
But like what are the things that make
Alex is propaganda
Is it's complicated
You know there's a bunch of things
Pretending to reference
The stories aren't easily like
Nikki if I were sitting down with him talking about stuff most of the time
YouTube
With Caitlin it's so easy
Oh no I understand
The willful misinterpretations
Surface lot
That she's doing and it's just
It's
I hate to say that it sits beneath the class of
Is that you want to look at
Fair enough
Talks about the
Rich oil
Texas
She's related to
Something very
I want to hire security
Texas oil families
Then like all you're doing great Alex people have helicopters
Sounds like I got the money
IPads
Never give a damn.
Stingy
Literally never heard Alex talk about people in Texas who have helicopter pads
Super super
Except when he's
Specifically describing the people who try to
The only other time helicopter pads
In Texas have come up with rich people
He's related to The Satanist to try to lure him
Fear the Reaper secure Ark today
Then I think I accidentally stumbled onto something
Possible and
The other possibility is this imagined
Richmond
Mansion with helicopter pad
The only thing
His brain can really pull up as an image
Of this
High-class opulent wealth
Describe the Satanist Tesla
Like really
Helicopter pad
I think it's either he's a Satanist or he has a childish imagination
Only has a
Few stops along the way
Does actually
Perfect sense that he has a childhood imagination regarding
Wealth because that is how people
Viewers like that
Is a
Very like
You know
View of
Gold Apartments display
Yeah. You know so of course get on his train because look
It's the very
Picture of what ice
Success
That much worse
Exactly
Man
One of the things I love the most
That Alex Jones
10 years ago
Hearing him sing along with the highway
And it turns out Alex
He's drunk
Also like
Talk about The Highwaymen
It's not as fun anymore
How did Daytona
Silver Bullet before and after I was in the Ebola camp
Everywhere is a sign other downfall
Whatever
You like selling silver bullet
Auto professional
I know that moment man I've been there
It's a bad luck
Deluxe
Still there
What is a bad luck
Cuz he starts talking about
Any slips
Penn State
You have been on fire
Elijah
The same fake names you've embraced it
I salute you
Are you I love you I love your fiance
I love my wife I'm not saying I want on your truck
I am envious of you
Why are you envious of her fiance
Why would you why would you
Compliments
Like the idea of being like
You're so great
I'm envious of your husband are your fiance forgetting
To be with you
Necessarily meaning
Idea it's not it's not inappropriate
Grosse Ile real slip
Look what what is Alex know about Caitlin's fiance
He exists
To be with her nose
I'm envious of your fiance
So
You haven't heard
He restarts to give a speech
About gender
That's very very interesting perspective bring it to the table
Every woman is half her father
Every son is half his mother we are unified there is no sex
We are humans humans are unified in total collectivism
Individualism
Cool
Those words all mean things
But when you put them together
I mean I guess he's saying it like there is no clear-cut genders and all that stuff is
Come around
All the time
Alex again
Is expressing a
They're still on this
And Cubans
Discussing about how she believes that
Gender roles
Specific gender roles are what gives Society it's
Strength
Alex respond
Very bizarre
Another there's a lot of people a lot of Democrats and feminist
To simply just be moms
How does gender roles there's nothing wrong
American culture is so strong is because we have gender roles
Down a pedestal
Mama
Quo
That's weird
You know in the same way that
Like empathize with the situation where Alex is going to is get
Tossed aside and
No loyalty from Rodger Stone
In the same way it's like with her and
And Alex
I get you are you
Support right-wing positions and everything
Second-class citizen so
You know I
He's going to be
I'm sorry
But up on each other it's hard to figure out
Anytime
So
What is really important to
Just got here really surface-level misunderstand
If anybody thinks
Wearing pink
Being a mother is somehow again
Feminism or
Is against the principles of the last
I don't think there are many people who actually believe
Surface-level missing
Understanding that she has
Is the idea
You felt
Made to feel like they need
Subscribe to these gender roles is the problem
Traditionally feminine
Is or what you must
Subscribed
Do what you must
Manifest
You need to
Have children or else you're not a full woman
Those sorts of ideas are the things that feminism
Orepros
Well that was one of the central conflict
Second-wave feminism is whether or not
Wit it was
Like the driver was absolutely rejecting
And acting out in
We can no longer just be considered mothers and all of that
Participate in those behaviors haha
And I took the same bulshit that
Social context
Did that exist
What social context do we exist
What's second-wave feminism
Like
Choose
As long as you have
Agency
And complete
They're trying to race
With the understanding
That like
I'm not giving you
Toys
Make your bedroom
Not going to give
Barbie dolls
Like over the top
Puzzles that are age
And that is
Something that is like
Gravitate towards those things
I will stop
Exactly
Expectation
For you I think that's the subtle difference
Caitlin and Alex
Don't
Understand
A pushback on as
If it were
A condemnation
If you want us subscribers
Gender-role because that
What you want
Who gives a s***
There are some people that's not indicative of
The groups that they real on
Yeah I got well I'm in currently
Clean the whole day's pay take care of animals
I am feeling when I cook so I'm feeling what would be
Considered the trip
Additional
Dare you act like that
Have these ideas
On their head
AR
Like really rigid about
Are the people the people who are in these
Traditional
Expectation
Beers
It's people like Lawrence there and have come out and talk about how they don't want
Necessarily
Pasture-raised their fan bases
They got pretty mad about that
They are the ones who are imposing something on other people
As opposed to
Like I don't have it
I don't know
I can't speak for everybody but
Anything about Kaitlin Bennett
But I've ever been offended by it
Dresses
You're not having long hair
The things that she brings up as her
Her feminine
I just wish they'd get a little more
Because it's
Also some of that gender roles
The stuff is
Self Justice
Along the way is
It is
It is comforting to believe if you are in a gender role that you are supposed to be
Watching people
Do stuff that you
Feel like you can't
You then have to be like
Because they're wrong
Otherwise you're going to have to do a lot of self-reflection.
One last pretty long
Because
Like I said
These f*****-up
Chinese like
I'm jealous of your fiance
He's all over the place
So he comes back after Kaitlyn
Leaves and Owens gone
And I've never done this before but I'm going to play an entire segment
Commercial to commercial
Of his last
On the 11th
His last
Commercial break
Paul Joseph Watson
Because it is an absurd
Thing
And I think
You know I don't think people understand like
What does shippo sometimes like
This is an entire
Segment
I want to get this out front for people because I'm not her
Some really bad forces
Kirkland right now which is fine I expected this I wanted to fight Asheville gun
Weird stuff going on and really bad people
Humanity for a future
The lottery like don't you know well
Will do this will do that and I'm like
Yeah I know how that's why I did what I did 25 years ago
But
Really pissed off right now
Who
Conceal
Internet Crossroads
Out of my fellow Americans that make me ashamed in America
American
Proud
Where is minute in and he hasn't said any
Nothing
Great some bad Lottery
Nothing these words mean nothing they're so vague
Bulshit
Natural Paradox here
1 trillion %
Owl shell out one damn piece
Bar agenda
I will settle it out of court to 1%
In fact I'll probably die of a heart attack
Worried that I'm not fighting this artist
Special
I just have so blessed
2019-w
Shake your hands on straight
Associate
Not read your email
Estranged
I just wish I was wiser
Bible says
I wish I was wise
Matthew 11
Because I've been far beyond the Realms of death
Because you're dumb and violent
Senior planner
Currently doing this is so crazy
Good man and good women
We're just trying to live our lives
And because we weren't shaytan
We could never imagine people were
Let me tell you something folks
Evil is real
As the sun coming up in the morning
Thomas Jefferson said 40-something years ago
Flourish
Good man
Do nothing
So this is Batangas Jeff
Is very excited.
What is a like Thomas Jefferson said who actually real quote
Retribution
Cuz very commonly quote is erroneously attributed to Edmund Burke
Even made that mistake in the future delivered back in 19
No record of Edmund Burke
Traces back to the philosopher John Stuart Mill
The original quotes quotes
More to Compass their ends should look on and do nothing
From that point forward it was Game telephone
John Stuart Mill's
I can't even find any real evidence to anyone other than Alex Bigsby
Every single time Alex Jones price quote Thomas Jefferson
Is it completely fake quote or something someone else said
Complete idiot knows literally nothing about the person
Who is this
Yeah that is really funny
Quotes Thomas Jefferson all the time
All the time and yet
Never
Does he know anything
DPS humble or
It's always crazy to me because I'm not
I don't think we've forced
Or anything like that but
Universe Works
Justice
Universe tends towards Justice
I'm at a little secret
So that's not
But it is not a quote of his purse
Number for The Arc of the universe be
After the Montgomery Bus Boycott
The first person to be credited with expression is
Parker
A Unitarian Minister and noted abolitionist
Who did the phrase in it
1053 book
Sermons of religion
This one's more except
Possible for Alex to know the history of make it much more
More popular
I'd like to explain how all Alex really knows our sound
We have no idea of the contest
Talk about it
What was Martin Luther King
Peter Parker
Heated Alec
And everything you say
So
Is b*******
If you don't stand up against
You might be ready
Soap opera
It doesn't matter universe
If you don't
And if you don't take Lex
The truth
God will reject you
Jesus Christ as your lord and savior of support
But if you really take Jesus Christ
Is your lord savior
You're going to stand up against
So I don't think
He said really much event
Play Pacific
It's all vague platitudes
Pics of the universe
Reminds me of somebody
Channeling someone saying
You don't need to do a different voice
If someone who thinks they have something profound to say and
I want to make this clear
We are just pausing it
Cold devil worshiping World God
World government
Marco's Beach
Mustache
Ladies and gentlemen
I'll give you a news flash
God's real
Israel
Jesus Christ is real
Baphomet
All of his millions of servants
Baby daddy
Dusty Rhodes what is he doing
Create a whole new group of people
Free-will like he does
On a planet
Realizing those children
Face free will
And so God I won rule if I'm going to give birth
2 billion Jeffrey Consciousness creatures
I'm going to have to let my failure Lucifer upon
That's the only rule
The devil on
Negotiated Jefferson said you better sick the devil Autumn otherwise it's going to be long
God said
I want company in the universe
I want to see a picture
I'm lonely I have these children
Imma let Satan attack him
Because they deserve to be free will
You don't give somebody free will
Create
Robot
It's the system
Child
Ketchup
For the devil
They're going to die someday
Child is to give death
To have a child
To have a child is to give birth to death
Alex storm here I love the black light posters but I got to get the f*** out of here
Got to go home
I really really love your
Einstein with his tongue out poster I think it's really cool
Chicago
Perfect love it
University.
You have a child
You're turning them loose in the universe like a ship a little sale
Thomas big ocean of consciousness
So that's God's big safe
What is the soul of the world he sent his only begotten son
Should anyone believe upon him
If you think that's stupid that's some preacher
It's free will
Not stupid
Secret
Is the verse in the Bible that literally everyone knows
That's a poorly kept sea
Yeah yeah
Consciousness but you've got to decide
Systems
You want to follow God's program
It's a program
You're like walking Best Buy
Jesus Christ
Problems
DoubleTree Boston with program OK Google
This is real life
But you're going to
Cuz you know you never got a job
I just want to make sure
I feel there's something big
Going on
This is where I mean
Alex says I'm becoming up
You might need to brace
Yourself
Freenote
Alpha Testing
Sure post Noah was debated
Jesus
Full on
Like that's what we're talkin
I don't know enough about software to
But I'll say yes
Working The Kinks out
Majid When you crush that ocean
Big storm
God's consciousness
Imagine before you go up the stairway
Are you come up out of that and you're like oh wow
Cars going to be sitting there
Show machine gun
Hair like
It's okay
It's it's all about to have
Everything's about to happen
God's waiting for you on the other side
But you have to say
Get behind me Satan
But you look at all these leftist week
Fun of them
Laugh
You cry about it but
The people that scare
They're people that point
Who was the fastest
What'd it now
Beta testing
You are Spirit
You are a piece of
Beautiful to hell
Horizons Dimensions to have
Kuro and just do things you can't imagine
I seen the other side
Dementia
It's amazing
What
It's credible but it's also really stressful
Okay hold on hold the f****** phone what are you talkin about
God
Oreo what's your review real stressed
I've been up there Consciousness it is fantastic but deadline
Even in his cosmology
God is going to ask you to fire a machine gun
God is God
You have like a
The heaven that would be Alex's heaven
Interdimensional
Machine gun for Alex
That makes total sense for you Alex
Multiple levels of consciousness
Very stressed
Kevin
Part for me I have walked past the golden
Exhausted
Evangelist
Like to tell you about the coming of the glory of God and how much of a headache
Weird
The shade of believability to it because of the human asp
He's going to wrap this up just got another Mini
So you want to share about
My television
Call Sharon August
Experience the universe unlimited potential
Everybody said.
What
Teacher.
You like a cup couch
You're not helping that means you're not the big
Built the world built the ships built the spaceship
Your couch
That's even more offensive version of what he always be out about Obama
You're just a couch
Nostalgia
But there's going to be a
Spreadable
Pressure
Going up that store
Paul Watson from England
I'm going to talk about
Appreciate this amazing crew
Because without you we are nothing
I salute you all I think Consciousness Free Will and God
I think
That they played money
Plug
You've been preaching for 9 minutes
I think Alex is too overwhelmed to heaven
Probably really misses Rodger I think there is a
Yeah Rodger is his dad
Where is Alex is Troy's dad
So Rodger has become Alex
Dad will think about what
Situation he was in
In terms of being able to
The Rake in tons of Bonnie
Flare-ups when you want to try it
Like really go hard for PR
Mostly under his own control agency over the things that were happening to him
He was getting away with saying
Incredibly horrible things
Either f******
Clown who gives a s***
Rodger shows up in
Becoming the biggest Trump booster in the world
And a lot of
Quality control in terms of
He's home
Control Slipped Away Rogers narratives
So entirely
On the campaign
They lost their way
Astilbe the campaign
To do all of his rallies while he's president no turkey
I know Alex has to
Fights
Because it's a
Keep it as if there's some sort of
About to
Election was all about
Now that he's won
More without a fake villain
So
He has lost everything for Rodger
At least
I was going to say do you think
Even
Let's say he lives
Do you think at any point he
He's really going to wrestle
How much Rodger Stone
It does not go live 75
No that's true
And no no
Because
Is False Image
The masculinity that's wrapped in there
I don't think that there will ever come a point unless I could see situation
Who can you go to like
Deep recovery
Yeah baby go to AAA get involved in the process
Dramatic changes
Yeah and if he did something like that
Not necessarily
To be take that form a sort of like really
Intensive therapy
Like if you were able to
In that process
I think you could
Your version of Alex Jones
Could wrestle
He'll always make it
Excuses always rationalize
Further downward
Like I don't know
This document of this
Time because
You have
I was having a really great
Time demonizing
Really good cuz
I know I know some of those be
Victory lap
I can bring back that one man show couple years ago
So
I think
I think what a
B the Rodger thing
It didn't go the way you wanted it
That's one big
He's getting high on his own
Reply
Metaphor
Because videos
The Kaitlin Bennett
Put out
And the video that Owen Shroyer put out
Are not supposed to affect
They're not
They're supposed to affect the audience
Exam to Alex's
Would he walk
Videos
Was the mark
He's being viscerally affected
The propaganda
The prick everyone else
In the same way with Owens videos with the
People
Alta in San Antonio
Visceral
You can't be the propagandists
Under the sway of your own propaganda
A lot of attention
I feel that's coming
With his
The addition of booze
He's really
Yeah it's pretty bad also after this
After this episode ended
She goes to the Google headquarters in Austin
Because Steven Crowder
Was out doing one of his public spectacle
Beach doesn't exist
Where at
Alex and Owen Shroyer show up
And Owen Shroyer has a pretty
Conversation
Haha
Happy quotes
Not yelling
Conversation
I'm sitting at the table they become station about 8
Bajan
Whatever.
Between two people
They're both dumb
Yeah
Shows up
He's trying to make it all about himself
He's drunk
Trying to turn it into it
And you can tell that Steven Crowder is not super in
Yeah he's humoring him
To Annex
But also like
Trying to
And there's a real tension of like
Alright
I'm doing this
Because I just got demonetized
I'm trying to
The brand movie
I don't have time for you
Coming into making this about yourself
I think it's a Stein the even
The free speech
Bears aren't really a
Interested in what Alex is doing
And they view him
Too far
Sober and engaged in it as like
I am a part of your
But he showed up drunk
And was like
It's a it's a it's a bridge that'll probably never burn
Cuz
You know
Deteriorating
It's not as
Easy to cross any more
It's the same situation
10-4 Rodger
Way back when when he was on regularly when he would plug his
Legal defense fund
Immediately after just like you did on this episode and Alex
You know he didn't like somebody else getting the money that
Thought as his
Qatar doing that are Alex
Crowder makes perfect
Alex is offended when someone tries to piggyback hitch
Perfectly willing to piggyback
If you want to go watch a Crowder video whatever go for it but I didn't want to include any of it cuz it's just
Santa Clemente
A desperate the arse.
Cancel.
Next time they do one of those
Dumb tables we should go there
And you are owned
Where we setup
Timetable on the opposite
Decided
And put our little Banner on there that
Says f*** off
I don't know what I don't know
I like how you thinking but I don't want to do it
Interesting
Assume that by the time it's absurd comes out cuz recording this
Some Thursday during
The day
Real real come out Friday morning
I assume
Embarrassing
Feel like everytime
Where in the present
It's just like
Irrelevant does not look good now
But
You know
Stuff is dangerous
It's worth pointing out
There's that
It's really a bummer to find out that
The heaven my parents
Have told me if
Is going to be
Stressful
That sucks what's the point of having a f******
Can afterlife
I don't know it's a little bit of
Specifically
The devil honest it wasn't just the devil was part of the thing broke away is God is like let's get these people
Hang out with the devil to go get them
Gather
Backup
As I reflect
Tiny bit
I agree
His spirituality as a lot of
But more importantly
I think it's episodes
Is entirely worth it here Alex
3 *
So that is a great display of
Just a guy who's confident
Three Galleria
Yeah just
The guy who knows
What is what
Comfortable in his place
Straight-up relation
Just good
On Monday
Another episode
Do we do it's knowledge
Yes world
We are that knowledge underscore fight non-active correct
Download Artio if you were go to the iTunes
You go to lady other
Astrolabe
All sorts of various places
Redbox
Not only Redbox
Nose
The Frog
I don't know anything about it
But I've seen
From him
Nexium
Okay you kill somebody
We probably have killed somebody
Is out of jail
Alex