Alexandra Thurston color
The
Mellow Waters of Alex Jones I don't know what I'm saying
Control right there I don't know but it's
Times in the world
The middle of the week
Coming down
Having a chat with you this
But
Let me ask you a
What's up
How much do you know about Alex
So much
Okay
I'm going to be honest with you
B Alex Jones levels of honesty
As the front of the show I get to
Shock and offend you with the words of Alex Jones
And auto contact
Campaign tonight
Shocking
Just go up there all these are ready
Lyft call their mom's gay
Yell at them for being offended by it
Before we get going
Go to your demilitarized intellectuals
Jessica
A couple of things
For joining me on the last episode
Super fun to interview him
And this is coming out Wednesday you can still go see him tonight
At Schubas Tavern in Chicago if you're in town
Just wanted to say that again
Super cool
Sorry you couldn't be there Jordan
Weird interview
I still felt weird
Also I'd like to say thank you to all our new friend David
Thanks for donating to the show this one's going out to you
That was just for you
Whenever someone donates their own policy
You're officially a policy wonk David thanks for joining up
And if you guys want to donate there's a link
Knowledge fight
Or just go to patreon.com
They're going to donate please do it
You don't have to
Anyway
Great selfie stick of donations Alex might need some in the
Transition game
Built I want to make this statement clear I said at the beginning of the last episode and I stand by it
I really don't think that we have any business talking about his divorce
I don't like what I'm seeing
I don't like what I'm seeing in terms of
Articles on unnamed website
I don't like
Takes that I'm seeing
I really don't like people dancing in the mud as it were
Weird
Because the machine
Of the internet
Is so
Celery
You get you
Fly off
As little bit as little of your
Neurologist pasa
Denied Sandy Hook
Yeah that's awfully miserable but
Yeah so much more of a monster
It's like if you have a band that you know a lot about Indie like people only know their greatest hits
Song they know Alex Jones
Worst-hit
Words like deep catalog you should really get into some of the
The album cuts
The b-sides
There's not just You're the Inspiration
It's not just Saturdays in the park
Chicago
Lots of 25 or 6 to 4
A great song I didn't know you knew so much about music
Does anybody really know what time it is
Another great Chicago song
Anyway
I really really really want to encourage people to stop paying so much attention to the divorce.
Cuz a lot of it is his business
Yeah a lot of it is not really
Necessarily
Real
In our in our world
Okay I would like to know more
A lot of it is permanent
It's a lot of it is personal
We don't really know the Dynamics that are going on
In his household
We don't know anything about his
Ex-wife
We don't know anything about that world
And we studiously try to avoid
Yeah and it cuz it is November
To delve into that
Another reason that everybody is interested in the reason that things became
Immediately interesting to people about this was
His lawyer said that you playing a character and that was
Defense that they used or we're intending
To use
And the reason that this isn't even interesting really is that he makes my claim
Across-the-board on his own show whenever he wants to dodge responsibility for something as in the case when he
Screamed about beating up Adam Schiff
He said that his
Ramps for performance
For their jokes
He was joking about so many other
Turn things like everybody else
It was doing it so I may
All the time
And if you are talking about his listeners like your
You're not actually engaging with Wyatt is they listen
They do not care
No probably don't care he says he's a performance artist
To them is as much a wink
As it is a mission of
Guilter that he doesn't believe in what he says it's just him being like
Hey guys
I'm a performance artist
To get my kids
Like that kind of
The audience would believe
The globalists are trying to
To torpedo his family
And he's just doing what he's got to do sometimes that means you have to
Give the lie to protect your family and the timing of this
Couldn't be more perfect for Puerto Rico
It's especially if you are ugly
Now is when you strike
That's the tracking know Alex Jones he was nothing
Global is for a long time he was just a thorn in their side now that he has some power
That's when you back his ex-wife I don't know I don't know what's going on
An argument about the globalist being real fell apart
Especially
Look
There's a lot of salacious fun stuff that you could make fun of
We choose not to do that we choose not to engage in that
Because we sincerely believe
The taking Alex
Faith
Entirely on his word
And researching his words
Is a much
Much more scathing attack
And it's something that he can't deflect from
Words actually
Engage with us
Like there would be an argument
There wouldn't be something that they could say
They might actually be like
It depends on how deep cognitive dissonance ghosts
But I mean I'm not saying a lot of
Do you want her to
Save-a-ho over here at that's not where I'm at that's not my business convert his flock
As much as I am trying to
I don't know what are we doing
Alex Jones listeners or is it to the
I guess make a time capsule
I don't know what we're doing multimillion-dollar book deal with
Bingo
Review the 2016 election
Through The Eyes of Alex
Anyway
Either that or just masturbating into the void
That's way more likely
A subject that will be what this episode is this is episode part 2 in a
Series that I would like to call Alex Jones
When you do stuff like
The obsessing about him
Or it wasn't even him it was his lawyer saying that he's playing a character
When you obsess over stuff like that
And you clown on him real hard like Media Matters as and all these websites
The pop culture website
All these people on Twitter
When you obsess about this stuff
It comes out in his divorce
All you're doing is playing into his hands
My evidence for that
Is
The episode we're going to be listening to today
It is from Monday
Sure like
Did all of our Relentless only made him stronger
I'm rubber you're glue
F****** work
Demeanor demeanor defense
This is episode from April 17th
Is a special report
But he put out in the evening
I will say I think it was unadvised
Of him
I think his lawyers probably should have stopped him from recording this
Cuz I think he touches on some stuff that may come up in court
I don't care about like respecting his personal life when he bring stuff
That's the line for me
Surrounded
Weather
A slow but sure biography of him
Of course there is a new entry in this episode
Get excited for that
When you at kill another dog
Nope that monster
Nope
When you
Betty murdered
Jordan step away from murdering all four of your children that's
What do you want to say is because
He doesn't actually say he killed a dog he's just saying
You kind of sometimes have to kill a dog
It's all right how about the time you put a guy in a coma knocked out
When he was younger
Who cares we're not here to plan a prosecution
Maybe that is what
Does episode 23 minute video all I've done is cut out
Like a couple of gaps here and there
A couple plugs
So it's not couple times he says infowars.com
Yeah Joseph
30% off of whatever there's 30% off Easter sale still going on
He's going to get that in there
This is what happens
When you don't actually engage without
On his level what are you talkin about
This is the sort of thing that you can do
To spend his way out
And still keep his cult
Ladies
Here we go here's the
You see that headline
Google says Rogue vendor violated guidelines
Contractors
Business Insider Google responding
Lesson 24 hours after this broke
Choices website
And also on our
Play the gentleman
All we do is break
Cutting Edge inside and tell from our amazing sources Lakers and Patriots
Flip a shows video opens with him holding up his cell phone that shows this
A Business Insider article
Great that he believes
5.
Riveting
Television
Did indeed
Pointing to an article you
Cannot read
Nope with just the headline I'm sure
Totally
This is a continuation of
It got started a little bit before the episode
Of the show with Mike cernovich
Mike cernovich
Was discussed on our last episode
He's stuck around Austin
Great
Each and every f******
Crevice of your shoe
No no no no it's a virgin
He's broken a huge story
That is the Google
Trying to censor Indie list
Infowars
From their search engine
Really
No
But that's a story that's a story that would be an interesting story at at this point it is
Like I could
Kind of
I could kind of believe it
Like based on all the stuff we talked about I'm not saying that that
Could happen or would happen
Open because
You know what
Yeah
I could almost see that being the
Is important to consider
Hey this is just
Google policy
It's company policy
If a site is being delisted
They have to give a formal letter
To that company
So it's legitimately being delisted
He would have
Evidence Reaper
He would have that letter from Google
It's not happening
It's entirely impossible unless he pulls out the letter
Now keep in mind
All he does is break massive stories
That are truthful
By his own words right there
This story is bogus as f***
Right
So
Do you want to know the truth
Should we wait until this develops
Because OK Google has admitted
Or have hired excuse me 10,000 people
To do around the listing stuff on the internet they say is fake news
That's the big story
Infowars
If they can censor you they can sense your me
What should be prominent is what you up vote
She gets the best ratings with people promote
Interstate
Watch the expanse
Takes you count absolutely Google has a right to bacta
So they should be
Maybe
I mean I do have a lot of artificial traffic
Paul Joseph Watson both have
Outrageously High numbers of
Fake Twitter followers
Based on
No Twitter audits that have been done
I don't know I don't know
That argument ism
I'm going to do it for me like his own argument for why something should be censured
That's not enough for me
Gordon's
What are we let him hang himself a little more before we get to the fact that was your plan
Remember though
Ilevel Google
How does he know
Betrayal
What are the sources for at least multiple years
He just works in contacts
Yes I'll probably work he's doing
Regular Susan Rice nozin
Susan Wright news was a bogus story also
Complete bulshit
I also another fun news story that Mike cernovich broke over the weekend
Was he went to one of these the tax protest
We didn't have to be
In Berkeley
He was in Austin at the protesters counter protesting as it were
He put out a video of him with his cell phone
On himself a selfie Periscope video
He's like there's a bunch of people
You can see behind
There's another guy
Who caught another angle of the video
As far away as humanly possible he's like across the street
No it's just like a couple people who are like
Come on they're just sort of moving him out of the way he's walking in front of them while they ask
Scored him out of the protest area
It's so funny it's so it's so funny to see the Long View of him acting like he's
He's in the middle of a huge crowd that's beating him up
It's just a couple people who like
Come on man
I'm not even really pushing him
And you just like
It's you the worst doing he's doing everything possible to try it inside something
Thing that probably wouldn't happen he was doing things too
Rig the appearances to make it look like he was being rude
Christmas
I want to nobody's nobody's arresting him I wanted to have if I were there I wouldn't want him there
Literally every possible situation
Even if he's the one
Wherever
Susan Wright story
According to Alex
Knock you the first world
The context of it is
Completely meaning
She was the National Security advisor so we do have a confirmation
That he did tell the
He said some troops and then lied about the interpretation of them
Which makes it a lot
Yeah or maybe he's just an idiot
Pull up because I could say hey you're wearing a boot like a green blue hoodie
That mean
Bayview
Are coward
I don't know. My brain wasn't doing good with her coming up with ideas
My point is that I did color of your hoodie is true but my interpretation of it is wrong
And therefore it's
Unless I actually am
Still have nothing to do with your hoodie
Okay that's actually how coward signal
Communicate
Handkerchief game where the coward
Israel is what
The point is
They make crnkovich is not telling us
Coerced
Jason Google
Let's finish up this equipment
I would like another drink
How many
The other fake journalist
Last night we posted it like 11 at 9
4 hours of research over all the emails a documents TuneIn whole manuals and a sensor when we published repay
Stages of it
So
Now it's time to get into what's actually going on
3 pages
Went through thousands
And at 11
After a long walk
I just Coleman through
These high-level
Alright
I simply sent them a link
Google given to Mike cernovich
They weren't
Why would you secretly give anything
You could just give them to Mike's
Are public documents
Bouye
They've been delisted from Google I don't know how to Google things they haven't been delisted from goo
Yeah but you don't know that you haven't searched I have what's the first thing that comes up
Kingsbury Ave 300
What is this okay I have the actual number
341,000
Pages
On Infowars listed
On Google
341,000 result
Yeah
You search within the site infowars.com
So you go into Google and you put into the Google
Search bar
Site colon infowars.com
You get 341,000
Results about that did you get some high-level sources who taught you how to Google Google
I don't know
So now this inside information Google works
That is a good question
It's not
Magical robots
Their algorithms work because they have these 10,000
Contractors
Empire
Their job is to do searches all day
Evaluate the results
Do you search for certain terms
And then there is a like 160 page
Guideline
Manual
The teaches you how to evaluate
The results that you get
And one of the things that they are
100 a comb through 160
And they found a couple pages
Kind of
Look bad for them
That's basically what they what was happened
Treating it like some big leak
It's come from a secret source
It's not
It's Google's manual for how they
Do you know
Tryon weed out s***
Cuz if you're searching for something you don't want to get a site that has
Tons of
Pop-up sauna
Redirect you somewhere where you're not supposed to be
Link that takes you somewhere that doesn't have any information
This
Whole thing
This entire manual is essentially
A training manual that goes to explain basically
Their guidelines
Go down to
Basically
It does its person have expertise
Is there a cure
And is this
Is to make sure that you and I never actually go to the second
Can page of Google
Yeah if you go to the second
Their algorithm
Probably didn't
Baby questions Pacifica
Their job is to make you lazy
Facilitate already ingrown leg
Or in his time goes on
Things become less relevant
Like one of the examples examples I saw here was that like
I really got to stop paying for
The URL on
So one of these a lifetime here of something that was considered like a low-quality
By their stickers was an article about Britney Spears filing for divorce
And the reason is because the person searched for Britney Spears
Specifically and that page pops up
No it's because that was that's years and years older he
It can be a jerk
Britney Spears
That is yes but do you understand this isn't relevant nowadays to someone just searching for
What's considered low
Immediately when you search for
Just Brittany
That's not trying to delist
TMZ
As it were it's not it's just considering what are you searching for
You want to make sure that you get to that
Yes it's trying to it's trying to suss out
Your your goals
Yeah
It gets a little bit,
7000 people all working on the same thing might get a little complicated with 160-page guideline with
Which I tried to follow
Okay
Like
Like the one page manual is just like
You know what you're looking for
Pittsburgh
There was a screenshot that was like this posted on crnkovich has website
Infowars reposted that was
Using Infowars as an example of something that would get a low score
Okay
This was not
From Google
Phone
Like main document
It was from one of the businesses
Some of these 10,000 people
Because they subcontract
These things out
How many person was using Infowars as an example of would be low
On the scale
Presentation to essentially
Scott and the reasons that are given
Has been
That their overall
Controversial and often third claims are debunk
Just fair
We've Illustrated this over and over
But it's
There's a quote from
This write-up about the situation
Despite the page
Infowars the lowest possible score
In fact
Explain why this should not happen
It even defended the reason why
That particular page would be useful to some Google searches
Citizens from the
The documents
Simply presenting an unorthodox perspective on the news doesn't exactly qualify even if it may be harmful in the larger more
You could say
That we're being generous with the upper range here but the site may be considered as looking for an alternative
Information
And it redeems that in some way
Okay
Translates to
Just because it's controversial and probably not
Useful and it's coming from a thoroughly debunked
Isn't enough
To delisted or to drop it as low as possible what it what you should do is
Is if you're if you're searching for just like
What happened today Infowars should not be on the top of the list
The New York Times
If a site
Like look a sight that has reference
Navigate
Pop-ups
What you be at the lowest
When you have
Shades of the rest of it
Fifty Shades of Black
Flames
These people were
Told the 10,000
To censor Indie list Infowars
And that is
Absolutely not true
Surgeon
No they were used as an example of something I was low-quality
Witches fire
Snaptube we have the
Recordings of those conversations
So they put up the training montage
Alright
But
Say they turn the recording off I assume I'll training set
Veterans are recorded
Nixon White House
They turn it off
And then the trainer ghost
Listen
This is off the Record
Infowars
Cuz those Fox
Is b*******
The thing
Here's where it gets even more,
Okay
Example that the used
In this sort of guideline that was using Infowars as an example
A low-quality information Source they used to screenshot
Article
Assad
Reporting that
The gas attack was fake
Okay
Later
Because he's like
They're saying we don't have legitimate sources
Ron Paul Ron Paul was on Artis
Putin said
This credible sources
No I'm scared of the former UK Ambassador who has a history of supporting Assad through
Right really murky
These are his sources
And he doesn't
I think he knows but he's not willing to engage with the idea of it like
These are bad sources
What are the only sources Who would know
Because they're the ones
The story is
That aside gases on people
Assad take on it
Like I know every time someone's accused of murder they don't say they did it
Pretty much
Yeah okay find some terrorist organization.
Guilty immediately
Everybody knew
Here's my ears my phone
Here's my fun theory about Assad like
How great would it be
If he
Do it
But he knows nobody would ever believe him like
Like what
Bummer for him
Like the one time he's not the most
Evil son-of-a-b**** brighter
All of the sudden he's like
The boy who cried I didn't do it
Do it
People just just to get over it
I wouldn't be surprised
Example
Even within that example it wasn't saying delist or sent to them at all it was used
Get a loan
The person who's going to turn that into a huge f****** deal
Use another example that's what I would have advised
I was a messed up
Any number of examples
Yeah
I don't know cernovich
Stay away from those guys in your fine they're the ones we're going to get really mad
These work get the extra
What Alex Jones is responding to on this episode that we're listening to
Is the Google put out of state
Explaining
That
They didn't
Make that manual
The second manual
That has Infowars used as an example
Absolutely but they addressed in there like Halo
They didn't they were telling anybody to censor anything
But
They did use them as an example I understand how
This could come off so we've asked
So that's what Google has
No I mean you're making a scrunchy face but I get where they're coming from too so alright let's
Just f******
Squash this
I'm a bit but Alex of course
Who's the co-host of an Alex Jones podcast
Offhand throw away
Because just the fact that they're responding
We're at best
If he's coming after us
Facepunch
Right now
Probably at least for now
Google Google gets to be a giant corporation that you can really real again
Because there's
No way Infowars
Subscribers and listeners
Really think that Google isn't part of the global
I think that Google is so the very fact that Google is responding
To that means like
Do they know where powerful
You know we have something on them
They know they're caught this
Alex is going to get to that but
You you're starting to be able to predict his behavior
Two things one I think the Google probably doesn't understand his listeners as well as we do
Listeners understanding
Maybe night cuz I think they're doing exactly what I would do in there
Which is be like what we didn't make that
Fair enough
Let's try and clean up our mess a little bit
That I don't even apologize
Apologize
Absolutely not another Susan Rice store
It's all
Non facts presented as conspiracy against them
Do highlight victims
To do with the divorce
Not under a gag order
He is the victor
Which is
Which is the only
Real bullet
Conservative movement
Has
Is that they're always the ones under
That's there that's there all that always there argument when it always comes back to it which is why they can
Actually do anything
Like I'd like now that they're in power
They can actually govern in any kind of reasonable
What what do you do
Like you're always the victim now you're the one who's
Victimizing other people
And whenever everybody starts
F****** up
Now the GOP is
Complaining that their the victim
Against the GOP like they just don't have any other Playbook to find the freedom caucus has to become
Campbell wants her being victimized are the mainstream or Bannon being victimized
Later there's going to be whenever everybody has
To claim to be the victim of a man is already happening
Boggles my mind considering the fact that their other argument is that
Everybody else is
Playing the Vic
Now
We're going to move on I think that
Fairly decently address the Google thing I'll post links
Almost links to stuff on the couch, you can find
Some resources on that b explain
Really what's going on is b******* Alex
Goes on
From the main point you going to come back to it
I just remember whenever he does
It's horseshit
But
This clip
And the next couple clips
Hair
Piece of Google
The censoring him in the news articles about Syria being a false flag attack
It was all admit it
Today
What the media attack on us only intensifies from there I mean it is just getting so crazy
To understand that the Infowars has been chosen
As the beta test
Incrementally basically shutdown
And that's why they took things I said out of context
Contacts
And then they pulled him out and
Again targeting low-information readers
So this is
Because
It's not all
That's why you shouldn't be saying that Xavier
No
Not during this trial gag order
He actually did get in trouble in court
On Tuesday because
He made a video like this
I don't know if it's this video specifically
But he's not supposed to be talking about any of this stuff
Technically
She's not
Addressing
Directly but he is basically addressing
Sing the fact that he
He said he was an act
Yeah alright least his lawyer said that he was in
And then claiming that
They're saying that he's
Haha
He's distinction
Is that
He's going to fully flesh this out
What are you going to attempt
Hopefully flesh this out
And his argument that he's going to lay out
Is but there were times
When he plays characters
Like one time he was in con makeup
Character
And I alternative
The guy who wears a lizard bad sometime sometime
He makes the argument
Those times he's doing parody
But all the other times
He's real
So now this is America
Because
He's
To use
Lee performance art
Flame
In the past
Or with him screaming
Which is not what are you talking about now
He specifically in this episode
That everyone who thinks
Playing the role in
He thinks that they're just talking about the times that he puts on a lizard man
Or does a British accent
Or stuff like that
He is so confused about what people are actually saying about
It's
Insane
I could have called almost all of these clips
Alex is illiterate
Because
OK Google
He goes on to say
To say some more stuff about how he is not
An actor
Again
This could have really hurt him in court
Defense
It's really going to work against them I really think of some of this might get played in court
Cuz it's
Overt
Pretty hilarious
He's a man
Self-destruct
Time
Doing satire
Alright well that's
When I tell you what I wear has or mask
Emily's whatever took off
As a joke everybody else does jokes
President's two jobs
I was being an actor there that was satar I believe in
Not selling out everywhere
And there are literally in the last two days over
Google Alerts
12:00 article
With the words Alex Jones admits he's fake
Alex Jones says he's just an actor it doesn't believe it
Yeah you did
No he didn't
His lawyer.
Yeah
And it is an important distinction
I don't know of any lawyers who are like
Here's what I want my client
Goodnight what I said
I don't know a lot of lawyers if you're a lawyer for like
You don't want to be like your honor
We enter a plea of not guilty
Your
Go on TV being like
I didn't kill people
You know what the only way I can sort of wrap my brain around it is like the strategy
Legal strategy of the water
Like make it
Really
So on
The tangle ball
Like just a big not like your headphones are off
All wrapped up you're never going to get those
Discord right here
Yeah that's
So yeah I think that's possible
But
This goes on again this is very ill-advised on a part
Here's the fun thing that I always
Conservative
Don't understand
They're not no no no
So his idea of life
Everybody else does.
I know
But
But you're like
Like what
What's this
She is trying to be funny on Twitter and you're like
Wow
Cut it out
Stick to the base
You know what's really funny
White people are the best
Oh no that's not really a joke
Stuff
Yeah
You're right he doesn't understand if this is the problem
He's not really doing satire
Freeze totally right about people taking them out of context
Admittedly
If he was at like an open mic
And what on stage
Wearing a lizard mask
And just saying Alex Jones
That would be the fun
He was doing like the my mom kicked me off her knee
Does four ways to learn
So long as he
Isn't trying to tell a joke to be fair we seen nothing like our third episode
I never said a word of that list what the media does is clips of me when I really do
Like Stephen Colbert
Nickelback Rockstar
Cuz I know
OK Google
That's me going
Employees
Thrown out of the rent house
Bleachers
Classic
It just so crazy as a real classical liberal
Alex Azar
A class
Cuz he just thought he was that also
Desert lizard
Freedom openness and anti-drug War
That's all the criteria that he gave there
That's a classical liberal
II
You know
I I I don't want to say that I'm
Were there where their movements in Classical liberalism
Liberals that I would not say are very open
Liberalism
Hey your reserve get out of here
I don't know if I've ever called it that before Victorian London
Maybe
Even in his explanation
You're not on the lease
Your roommate is
Which means you should be there
That might be more what's going on
Oh really it might be
The whole the whole you should be on that like it's 5 can sublet your apartment it's against the law
I mean if you don't get your land
Often times our to accidentally tell the truth in the middle of a bulshit sense
You got to get out of here I hate
You're not on the lease
You don't have that it's the 28th in the
Google is trying to delist us
They're not
The story that you posted even the Business Insider story doesn't even say that
Call the lawyer
Of course you too busy with his other lawyers
Maybe he did call already been calling his lawyer
Divorce lawyer about suing the biggest company in the world
They're not quite the baseball field
My man there up there anyway
This is not just full of anecdotal stories about people getting kicked out of their home
It's not just the guy who's going to falsely claiming the classical liberal
He's also going to tell you a story about someone talking to him
Just sit here and watch all these a whole lie about me constantly and then I got the street
Today
Walk up to me and say
I'd really like you I was no time and I
I saw you on the news
It's all fake
I said hundreds of times on my own shows people asking
SMS, is it real
Goddamn hell I don't know and the other question is
Is it for real
Found money or sovereignty
Family
For free open-market free-market systems or not having
Yikes oh you should not be already lost the customer
Done
Notary kids are vaccinated
Tickets for kids
How many times does Seth has on the podcast
Little kids are f****** s*** public
Help
It's not
Science is still out
Vaccines are tainted
Oh man
I don't say this lightly
One of his kitchen
That guy on the street didn't
Iusedtolikeyou I've been yesterday
I saw a report that you're fake
Oh that that ruined all the time but I look
Did he hallucinate
It's possible sounds very
He's very sincere in that story
Like it doesn't sound like he's lying
In the same way that usually does whenever he lies where
Are you put into many details like
Diana Paisley
He does often give too many details but this was like all these narratives to he just flippantly lies and say
Sounds like he believes all the time
Demoralize
This clip is super bizarre
Little I'm excited
Starts with him saying stuff
Obliquely referring to the court case
You shouldn't be saying
Jimmy's Egg
Many speculate as to why people are attacking Infowars
Are you lying
It's all bulshit
Then
He transitions
Into Ally
About callers calling into his show
And then
He tries to explain satire
Deepwater that
That's like the strawman explanation he does not
Way I would stop it up is that tires f****** hard
It's real hard
To be like the pros
Give it a shot Alex
Personal life of the system coming
Imma take the high road
I've done everything I said I do
I'm at left or right I choose issues what are they
Self people
Because that's the New Media Center like Alex is Bonafide he's real people believe him it's spreading
Skipper Bud's always other Freedom Motors
So that who is saying that will that's what he's saying that that's why people attack
Cuz he's almost Vanguard of the New Freedom
But before that he was saying that like my you know all the stuff I'm under attack about my family I'm going to take the high road on it
Merced s***
You should have said
Nothing
Even just saying that
Is going to be a problem
Alex Jones
You should have said nothing
Let's that should be his biography
Mike Birbiglia jokes
What I should have said was nothing
Was all the s*** my lawyer told me that too
That they can track that most of the modern
Next wave of a patriotic libertarian
Heaven
Call Mike drudge helped us launch some
Would watch all around Audrey
Killer
Well Infowars has been a big magnifier
As well for other people and they see that they know we're like an incubation system for other people
Now we take that as an argument we can look at the people who have come out of Infowars and game
National prominence and I can count on
0 hands
The number of people who have come out of Infowars and
Become relevant
0 hands
Sure I read a New York Times profile
Oh no no no dude there was a rainbow snatch
No that was on it for work
All the people that he has on you could make an argument are
Like people who give him more credibility
People like Anthony cumia be hosting
Wants
Two weeks once every two weeks or whatever people like Gavin McGinnis, gone even like cernovich
Yeah but these are guys who have built in
Fan groups already
Don't mean anything
Route 20
Owen Shroyer doing nothing
Paul Joseph Watson has a big fan base
Keep the Infowars is a
Anchor around his leg
For all intensive purposes
He just makes short attention span
Propaganda videos that he puts out on his own channel
They're terrible she is someone who is actually fairly successful
Homegrown
Or whatever
She lives in London
He doesn't he
He's as separate from Alex's he can be while still being involved
David Knight sucks
David Knight
Lee Ann McAdoo hat is great but she doesn't have it
You
F******
It's very beautiful Millie Weaver sucks
Canterbury
Somehow
Evan bring her over here
Ritz
That would be so great
Millie Weaver sucks
Bubba Bubba
Kabob
Ashley Beckford barely ever around
Around aren't around anymore Jakari Jackson
Certainly isn't the notable
Household name
Rambo Joe Biggs
He's not around don't like you
Mark Dice
Not super famous
I really big name unless he's secretly
Andrew Dice Clay
Wearing a mask
I'll be regressed age makeup
Nth Degree
If
Benjamin Button
John bowne
Isn't famous
None of these people are notable do you just have a team of losers
No
Will you
If any of them were doing their own thing they might actually be successful
They might have it in them to do something
No it's possible I don't know
It is past
I've no idea I've never seen universe
Yes in one section of the Multiverse
Paul Joseph Watson
Is the greatest brunch
I sincerely think he probably has way more Talent than
Keys
Expressing through his propaganda video
Yeah probably
That's fair
I'm talking about all the other dingdong like they don't even have a chance to shine in their own
Anything they're just hour to second
Even save the exact same things that he does
They just biggest
The tarantula the strangest thing about his argue
Is that
He is essentially
A cult leader
Anyone
Threatening
His
Consolidation
Mediately torn down
Or at least sent to the side for a little bit
For a little while then just brought back in
Anyway
Truth is my northstars my Polestar
It's what I want it's where I'm going
Nope all the time I get to call you
Getting regular listener
Call
Are you for real
I've listened to every day for the last 4 months
Has anybody said not one
Not what nobody's ever asked about
He does screen his calls
Sure
So
It's entirely possible
That is screener is heard that
But he said that anyone who listens
Relate that information to anyone who listens would know that
This call happens all the time
I live in Dublin
Absolutely
If I dress up like The Joker
50,000 YouTube followers find it.
I was being an actor there illustrating
Evil clowns going take your vaccine schedule a showing articles
Evil clown
You know what
This is acting
No I don't mean take up
And no I'm not really
But I am
Good expression when I believe so I put
People
Show me pictures send it
He's acting 2X
Express Woody really believe
Yeah
Well no I mean what are you saying
Is that he plays this character as the opposite of what he believes in order to make the point
Right in the queso
He is a performer
That he
5% of the time
Is act
And he is only Act
To express Woody actually believe which is the opposite
So bad crystal clear
He's not abstractly talkin about
Other times it might have been performance art when he was screaming at some guy or something like that
About times he's worn costumes
That's important
But also
It's not a good argument against vaccines they have liability for
It's a very bad
Because almost everything
Check the inserts
Yeah well the reason that your your aspirin
Has a f****** little
Cover because of the
You aspirin murderer
Maybe that was not
Videos of the guy could have been the actual Corporation
Section
Almost everything is use at your own risk
We were walking away from this
We don't want liability how come we haven't
A disclaimer at the
What are we doing
I'll stand by my words anyway
Alarm for 1 question
There's so many
I didn't know dress up as a joke
1000followers cuz he dressed up as a
Zucchini
Does he believe
That his listeners
Are so dumb
That were they to see him
He is the Joker
We're going to get into a clip a little bit later down the road where he wrestles with this a little bit further
I think he's disappointed by how dumb his listeners are
He knows that if he calls them dumb
Game over
Yeah so he has to try and
Blame the media and stuff like that
They poisoned everyone's Minds
An act like he's talking about other people about the Dum Dum
His listeners saw him dressed up like The Joker and they were like
Wow you actually believe that that means your listeners are dumb
Also
No one
Who is
Making fun of that clip
Years ago when he did that
No one was like
Look at this guy he likes to dress up like The Joker we don't get this is parity
We don't get this tire
Emerald is like
Look at this crazy assholes
The first time
First
Leave my pictures of it
He really did
Put on like video the makeup and everything
Who told him that
I bet there's just people who can't tell him it's not
That actually sounds far more listen to anybody that's why
Himself or whatever
Going to get
Fuct
Yeah so this next clip coming up
Is Siam
Really further nailing down that he's not
He also explained
He doesn't want to be
That is the least
Truth is his Northstar engine
With others
Totally but also
Really
Shouldn't be making a crystal clear case
I've been in major movies
Reality TV shows
In the world shows with them
I don't want that
I don't want to be a celebrity
I want to be a leader for freedom
For the future
Now
Someone they know
Stanford America
If they can do that
Will you just got really shocked what's up
He just said he was under criminal investigation
He's not
Thinks is happening
They're investigating the bot
Promote
Is content
And stuff like that
The FBI has announced those at McClatchy article
We're discussing that these Russian Bots
Time
There
Promotion
Infowars Breitbart content
To make a very high impact
Never Trump was going when something bad was happening
It seems like all of these anti-hillary
Pro Trump articles
From Infowars
We're being pushed really hard
Identify
Thought that were being used by Russia
Well it's really traceable
But they're using they're not good at
Right that is a good strategy
Syria hoax hashtag
It's really easy to track back to use the first
Everything
Cuz it's the internet
Yeah is it in the same way
Everything what you can pretty easily identify these
These fake accounts
It's pretty simple
Hazel Alex
That because the FBI is investigating Infowars connection
These Bots they are investigating him being a Russian age
And you're not
Or of him making himself into a bigger victim in a bigger March
Back if anybody
Coward
When you're like
If you don't protect me they're coming for you next
What I deserve to become
Like I am a liar and a propaganda
And my own
20-year game is caught up to me now at this point
For buying my weirdo pills and Bones sauce
Vaccine
No viral content whatsoever against fake diseases
Mite bites
For Doctor group would come in with some like weird fake disease
Yeah 25
Anyway this is what cowards do
You have this built up group around you going to turn on me eventually unless I make us a super tumor
And it is going to be super
The cap
I mean Hugh
Things that he should not say it's a cult leader move to
It's always going to be you know
They're coming up to me your leader because they're going to be coming after you the moment
I'm gone I'm the only one protect
Getting you it's an implied threat
Two phones
We all have to kill ourselves or else they're going to get
Samsung
Yeah it's not as it's not as certainly
Related
Jones
Alicia
Has Alex Jones ever been in San Francisco
The people Church
I would almost guarantee
This next clip is weird
This clip
Is Alex
Not really understanding what
Doing an act is
He doesn't really understand it and then he gets a little bit sentimental
He gets lost in that is not true
Cheerleader video on this
Ridiculous
Driver's license
AR-15
The hardship
Small animal vet
Can I pull up the Sonic and act tough for girls
Manchester
I tried that slicker than I probably was was it
No I really wanted to take that girl I really want to take her to the movies
I really wanted to kiss her but my hand on her thigh
I really wanted
And I did
The bad girls as well
Punk rock girls
Walked over like I was tough
It was an act
My heart
What's a hundred percent behind
The beginning definition you want to be
Everything we've done for the
Everything
Product tell Reserve
Big Smoke
Call system
Is being exposed right now
After Victory after victory
Pod leaders
You had the Japan
Because of you
Do have to say that a thousand times
Yeah I would posit also
That
When you're in the middle of an ugly divorce
And
One of your
Arguments
In court is that you're playing a character
Against the wishes of your lawyer clearly you get on air and you shoot a video
For your arguing that you are not an actor
It might not be best
To talk about
Was I acting when I f***** every girl in my school
Punk rock girls
I got the cheerleaders got them out Bad Girls 2
Book if you talkin about
That's my favorite Alex right there
That's a great Alex
I got my license at 15
And that's what I started f******
Everyone
There's there's your clip Media Matters right
Alex Jones a fifteen-year-old sport soccer with his chest out
Finger lady at a drive-in
Is really gross
I wanted a fingerblast a Punk Rock Girl
At least that would be pretty gray
Also
Much like him
Not understanding that what's at issue is not whether or not he was literally the Joker
We're also not concerned with you faking confidence in order to connect with other humans
What's an issue is whether or not you're still angry
I do love how
Incorrectly sites
William Shakespeare
He just came up with that off the top of the stove
Maybe one of the most
Famous
Phrases in the history of the world
I might have thought that Alex Jones thought that one up as dumb as he thinks they are
Into The Bard
He said that
An act can be anything you wanted to be with you like
Silly idiot for thinking that the
Actual definition
Is that word within the context
And that word
Has a f****** Warrior all along it's been an act
Okay
I would I would look
And I'm doing this to get chick because this is not a
Video podcast episode I shouldn't have done that I apologize
You don't OPP dress up like a joker I don't give a s***
Whatever you do in your bedroom which rear end
So this next clip
Things that I did read that I found very
Broadcast
No permit no people misrepresenting that he has a giant Studio that he broadcast
Sometimes he does special reports
From the home
This was recorded in like a study
And sometimes he's in the living room and you know it
Videos
IPhone video stopping home
Did the Giants
Studio
You can get mad at people living in their parents basement you shoot your f****** show out of your home
Second
Sometimes
He will videotape
Himself
Like just about everybody on YouTube
Yeah but not his show show
Broadcast every day I was I was I was really concerned about that be
Because every time I
A picture of a studio
He's got a room
House for that she has a smaller Studio e broadcast out of like on Sundays it's possible that that one would be
Be in a basement
Something like that small enough could be
Just a secondary studio in his Warehouse
Anyway
The next couple clips of just
Again I fucken understand what people are actually talking about with him being
Yes
So
When they didn't say I'm fake
Because his place me as a joker or me
You're supposed to videos on making fun of me
You know where I'm at
It's like some fake Christians
I would argue that his whole show is largely grandstanding
About people being dumb and not realizing their work that walk among us and want to kill us
Have you seen
Who's that
The Joker not a one string
I like you just got it
Got him
1 in
That is so unusual and so out of
Any contact whatsoever
That is creating that false equivalency there in order to make it seem like what they're saying
Which is reasonable
Is a kin to him dressing
Like the Joker
Yeah he basically is using himself as a strawman argument
Kind of explaining what is happening no because if he was actually doing that
Like if he was aware of that boring control he can make the argument
Give me better so confusing memes that he doesn't
Understand
I think from listening to this especially I know where it's going
Like I legitimately think that he
He genuinely believed
That's what
That sort of thing is what people are like
Haha
Victor's really Illy
If it even gets worse
Hannibal Lecter
It gets worse there is one clip that I'm going to play it
There's no
Play towards the end of this
Just literally titled probably going to be used in court
Nevermind
And it's just like they're all taken out of context
Yeah when the feds show up or whatever
He pissed me off
I was angry with my dog just died
But also
The feds showed up
You think so fascinating him for Russian ties
What do you think you would ask him
Can rice be like
Do you have Russian
No do that showed up about video where he said he was going to punch
Cuz I don't think there's a
The chance
I can't imagine them having the time
I imagine most federal agencies
They're busy
I can imagine
I don't know man
There's alot going on in the world
I think they're more interested in some local dick weed
That's what everybody's really good bass.
No cuz based on his Alex's hold
Premise
Oh that's right the Patriot fans are taking over
Probably part of the counter counter counter coup
Who's going on if you guys
F****** programming app get at me get me if you can program
Rap
Your speech like
How dare you meet me in the street
I don't Parker literally I'm not really planning
Holy crap
So then I might know it's performance art
What is it when you say
Yeah that's kind of
Dude
You don't want me to
Molester
Would you have in the past
In the table cut that icon
Probably say I said that so
You did
It isn't about Alex Jones and that's what frustrates me about
Is this treats me to
This part of
It's like okay so it's
The performance are what is it if I say I want to attack
And I'm like really hard you're not going to say
Wow
That is really great for 4
Yeah so that would be at least a hypothetical threat
What would it be if you were a child molester
Booby slander
Performance art either
Yeah ever here so I don't think he understands it all what anyone's talked about
In the moment
A teacher
I think he's not well right now
Wandering around
Understand
Like every
Every single moment
Has been pure
Abject
Confusion over
What is real
Yes
That's probably
I mean you got to assume that like around 6 felt alienated because of his mother
Rejecting anything he doesn't get love anymore she probably started to feel these
These real confused powerless feeling
And that makes the world terrifying
So you start
Thinking you're more grown-up than you are you start reading military history books and not really understanding them
Start to get childish ideas
Mixed in with some curls
Effectual history
So you get this warped view of the world you get narratives that
Don't exist
Filling in
Then around the age of 12 you find this cockamamie bulshit book
None dare call it conspiracy
That's just basically
Nonsense repackaged anti-Semitism about the globalist
The dangers of socialism turning into communism
Japanese baseball
I mean this is so simple
It really is this simple
Next question a lot of rest of the stuff is just window dressing
When he gets drunk
I'm really bummed out now
Did he see pink
Open dancing
No they like it
Tex Avery cartoon
BTU has delirium tremens
Anyway Alex is at this next clip
Oh by the way I think I
Just Express what I would call the unified field theory about
Documented him saying all of these things
Throughout the course of Justice
4 months you get a picture of someone who's
Had a real tough time for the last 35 years
I wish there was an actual
Accessed
To him where we could just
Deism
Well I might imagine
Just want to wake up
Go throughout a day
And
I will wear
Cedar Park Adams
Halloween just like sitting in
See what's going on the problem is you never be granted that access until
Until everything falls apart a vent his life but I would be interested
I'm telling you this
Michael Savage
In the book
You will write all the in
Information
And then I'll have in the foot
Footnote
And that'll be it that'll be my contribution right I feel like I'm doing the right thing
Alex has more thoughts about how he is
Sinon
Court TV
Cowboys
I've seen a lawyer basketball court TV
Articles I read
They'll say how do you know the truth how you do front most recent
How good they look how nice
Off the
Is there an unelected EU
Is there an elected level un
Open
But a hundred dollars taxes every decade
Absolutely
George Soros
Yes
Did he admit he fun of the Arab Spring
No
I have an Empower you
Opposite
Do the anti-second is after listing
Some handed funding
AR groups
But he didn't fund the Arabs
Spring
Create the Arab Spring group global humanitarian
Ukraine
No
How about the Arab Spring
Not all of it so we're those like people
Those people
So they were kind of like mad at the authoritarian
And some of those groups may have gotten some money from George Soros
Because
Like I said he's a global either Global philanthropist George Soros
Call them up
Rockefeller George Soros Hungarian
But all that s*** is wack
All that stuff is b*******
The EU is unelected
August
Secretary of state is unelected then
Hooray
Like if you really want it if it's true if you want to get it never considered that
I think
We should vote for secretary
You know what's crazy
If we did that we would actually have a functioning
Secretary of goddamn
Filled with people who do their goddamn job
If you want to take a step back and not just use the examples that he listed
This litanies of Lies
I mean there's plenty of
We have plenty on our website knowledge lies
30% off
A hundred percent
Website for free spoiler alert it's no longer Easter
So
In this next clip Alex
Is kind of something but he uses the brightness wrong
He explains that the things that the media is doing right now The Joke is on You
The people who are listening
Are you kind of right I always needed
All the old be like out of context
People post about him
It is kind of a psyop again
The people watching
Because they do give the wrong impression
Anabolic
But again as we keep
Keep coming back
It's a better picture
It was a joke as a better pic
Then the reality of
I completely damaged man lashing out at the world through his audience
An inuk
Applicable number of
Damaged people listening
Yeah
And a revelant
Be strong because I never apologized
Long sometimes every month
Something
That's not true he apologized because he got a letter from James Oliphant
Really even apologize about that he still has not addressed the that mosque
Shooter was a white dude in Montreal
He still has been peddling a horrible
Lies about George Soros being a Nazi
Collaborator
Sandy Hook
Dances now
I'm just asking question
There are a lot of questions to ask
20% of our uranium
To the Russians
Not true he owes an apology on that you never correct
I'm selfish
He's
Called a lot of pee
People pedophile
Lot of them
Renfield
He's made a lot of people and he's never really apologize
And then run around and say Jones admits he's fake
IHOP on you
Quite frankly
I become such a logo OR
Icon
Resistance
Their attacks on me
Only making 4
This is a big Essentia the Tampa
I want to see I'm very humble.
You want to wreck your mind
Were you don't believe there's anybody
But you know
You're good
You know you have ho
All the policy all the culture
Everything I promote
Dangerous crap
Fundamentally who I am
That's fundamentally
We're changing the world we're in this together
Of course I believe what I say
That's going to be a problem
Chimeras
I swear to God I bet he could win a governorship
No chimera
That's going to be a problem
Christian Fourier
Cuban animal hybrids with which they turn into a joke
But is all admitted
What are you f******
It's not about it but also like I love that's like the second thing he comes up with after freedom
Freedom
No human-animal hybrid
I don't understand
Those are the two most pressing issues in mind
I've read all the articles about chimeras and they don't say what he says
Fullmetal Alchemist
I didn't okay well
Alchemist
Create chimeras
Okay I just
Human transmutation is bad
Just as a heads up for anybody
Don't transmit
Alex
Russell's even further
With the idea of what it means to play a role
I didn't like I said I didn't cut out everything in between these clips will they seem really disjointed because they are
The entire video is available I think it'll be taken down at some point
It's super disjointed Buc-ee's just
He's not making sense
This is all in chronological order with nothing cutout
This is this is wild
Of course I believe what I say
Unless they go clip
Devil's Advocate
As
Skip
When he goes and does his gifts if you do exactly who you are
Of course he has political you using
Horton and I think some of the public
Google
I like
With contractors sang b-list Us in huge contracts
They just admitted that was true and they just said it was an accident
Cuz I saw my video
Coralite out everything
You're lying
Nope
Perfect example of him being
Completely
Fake news
But then
What is Alec Baldwin
Yes everyone knows that when Alec Baldwin brass balls
We all know
All the world
So perhaps
We are truly all a
Did you consider that
I don't
Is that even your real name
Mr. freeze
So dumb
So pointless under
I don't know
Possible
The difference
Between an
Accident
Sing that
Primarily
Pedophile ring
Underwrap
Well then let's even take that away because he apologized for that
Government works off of pedophile blackmail
Yeah
Play
If you if you are going to
If your
Right
Now
Here is his rule
That he should use
So if you're listening AJ
I got you I got a shopping
According to his own
Words right
He's
Exaggerating
Acting
To show what he's
So if you're going to call him describing everybody in the government
Working off a
Pedophile
Maybe you can say that he's just exaggerating it
The same way that he
Play Devil's Advocate
As the Joker whatever
Make your point
If he's going to do that
Beyond
What is a reasonable concept
In order to demonstrate
What he feels is the true evil beneatha
Like like oh you're you're you're
Okay your comic book villain
Is an amplified version of whatever negative traded is that you wants
That you want to describe
You know you have your
Lex Luthor
Who is just an amp
5 billion
Who just takes things so far away
Is all
Bruce Wayne is
So you have your Amplified version
Describing what it is that you're a
Actually again
Do Hillary Clinton herself
Is a vampire squid
In the same way that Matt describe
Way back when regarding
Golden Goldman
Right
Do you do you see how that
Walnut a good arguments
One that you could skate by
No you don't think so
Not really okay so
No because Alex Jones
Playing the role of the
The villain
Or whatever
Him yelling about the like
The globalist
Views children as
Flake
I retract
Because I just heard yet again you say
The globalist
Use children as Kurt
There's no there's nothing to say
Is Joker think we're alike
He's out there saying everyone should get back to Maiden ordered make the point don't get vaccinated
That's why he thinks it's that tire
Because he dressed up as the Joker
Yeah
And did exactly the opposite of what his point was
So if he's doing that in the instance of the you like pedophile sex rings and stuff like that
He is
No no no I'm saying that if this is the parody is actually trying to make is that
People in the government don't do this stuff
Haha pretty cool perhaps
Maybe he's trying to do a reductio ad absurdum argument
He's not
Nuno
This is a bummer
Wouldn't it be nice
Wouldn't it be nice if that f****** crazy
And you said you weren't good at in promise Who's Line Is It Anyways level Improv
On the way
No one has ever said
Equipped
About how he was right about Syria
The pointless
Who's next
Yes
This is really where
I think
I would like us to
Really absorb this clip because I think it's it's
I think it's Alex wrestling with the fact that his audiences
He doesn't know how to do it
He doesn't know how to say I can't believe you guys
Are this dumb
There's alot going on
Yes
Schmaltz
You feel like you got conned
345 hours a day
Yeah she's being real
Chimeras
But sometimes if I go here
Clearly I'm
In a British accent
Sarcastic
Reading Lord Rothschild quotes on air
I'm not agreeing with Lord Rothschild
I've almost killed all the time
Or not because
Because
People sit there say
Why is he
Wearing a wig saying he's a British professor
Doesn't he know this is fake
People don't know that so I go hey
How you doing
I have a syndicated radio show is a pundit
Regular Alex Jones that's real
I believe
In the news
They're not even stupid
They want to act like
They've been wrong and betrayed their whatever even was hers to begin with
That's very weird very weird
I think he is
Okay
What did he do
Let's try I'm going to bring out a pan
We start with
I love I love your Foley
Right
The New York Times
He's killed that's how do you kill set timer how do you kill set
I think you killed it with that
You killed it with that Darnell
I think he's saying no cuz he's making the argument that like
People attack it so much
They must be threatened
Did he did say that
Okay what do you meant was
He can no longer do that
Because
He has done it
I think that might be
I think that might be what
So
New York Times
Videos
All of it
They don't understand
And they're like hey man why you doing that
You like come on it's that tire don't forget it don't forget it
But I'm not being sad terumi I'm Alex Jones I'm a libertarian
How is he being sorry you can't be
Sarcastic
At the same
This is
Alright this is insane
Here's the last
Alright
He just said the listeners
Actually Alex Jones listeners
Listening
Further MoMA
That they could jump off
Because that was their whole goal in the beginning
Listen
Yeah
Super weird Behavior
Is a surprise a person who doesn't really
Who doesn't really care about the movement
They're uninformed
They're The Uninvited
Thanks. Really what eyeshadow should have been called
This next clip
This next question
I think he doesn't know
Anyone
Because he's crazy
Nobody knows what is exact same kind of schizophrenia
I'm really dumb people think he's smart
But it's actually not mark
Scattered disjointed thinking
It appears kind of Deep
That's not
If you lie is about secret sources that he has why wouldn't dumb people believe him
That is a good
All of the verifiable sources that he's ever sighted have not said what he says they say
Secret sources
Modulo
I did not
Consider his secret
Yeah but you got to be dumb to f****** believe in a****** like him
Great sources
F******
High level
I didn't know he had high-level sources
Google Google
In the vendor company
Who Google subcontract
Yeah
Go to my route
In every Institution
The entire United
Yeah yeah it's complicated web
Tangled web we weave
Shakespeare's
Will Shakespeare said that I don't know if
Willie at I know you said but I just want to make sure that our listeners
Did it was wheel shakes
What's important
Now obviously I know I miss bill
William Shakespeare
I don't know I don't know where I got that next clip is
Alex Jones doing
William Shakespeare level version
Drama
Explaining these effect
Now
I'm at 1.
Batavia band
Advertising
Aurora disinfo
Cooperative
Scum-of-the-earth
Tony Garza real
Absolutely
I can't get into it later allowed amount
I need they are supposed
July
Show
U-Pull-It
Because I touched you
You touch. You are the power
Cam
The videos the Article 13
I can speak to that
Everyone
Now right-thinking people are super against it because
You lie all the f***
Sometimes you're a bigot
Yeah
Cancerous forced to dialogue
Right real
To write all the time misunderstanding your sarcasm
What time I've seen you do something wacky
I get it
And
Hundred percent we even said
But even with that shift clip
He's drunk
He's an a******
But there was no part of us that was like you'd want to actually beat up shift
Legal this isn't like this isn't his Free Speech you just being a dick
But what if we're wrong
No
Sew-in Annie goes through
All of these different
Circumstances
Everybody agreed
This is
Not true
And then it was later proven
All right now
We have that moment with Alex
It's a natural
It is it is
One of the one of the things that I constantly like
Have to stop myself and just go
Yeah I have that moment until like research anything he talks about
Alright
Sometimes
Sometimes there's a part of me that's like
You're the worst
Sometimes I wish you
But the world to be more interesting how much more fun with
And horrific
Miserable
Be so much more simple if we did have some sort of
You know
Arch
Global evil group that we legitimately had to fight again
Because in reality
Everyone could come together much easily
But much more easily than it is we can now
Life would be so much
Try me now it says I believe in the past also said that
The government is likely to get a fake alien attack
In order to
People how's it going to spam how fun would that be
Anyway
In his victim
Self victim status
Flaming
Yes in there you said
You know basically all these lies are going to come out I can't talk about it but
It's all lies and you're all going to see
Which is the beginning
It's against the law for contempt of court
For talking about it
That
Yeah it's bad
Yeah now this next clip
Is way worse
This next clip is like this
If his lawyer isn't screaming at him about this
That's bad luck
And I got the whole system come out
My family is just all about
Take everything away from
I got them
Hit me on every front financially culturally
No matter what happens
And all the other doors are open just like documents on Google
And that's why you got to be so scared they know genuineness
Things my laziness and they don't do enough about that I'm totally real I want you to have a few
I see how pathetic dumb down the public is now sick
Comcast out of this attack
Well I'm just
I want you to win
I want you to win I love you
And I appreciate you
Hundred percent real when I say I want to do
They should take out contacts when I
The Shot Tower joke around so I got to say no.
That was a little performance
Respond before coffee shop
That's almost videos
They take those now
Facial College
He says this and now he says that
There's no contest
He twice in there said that I am 100% genuine
I am sincere he mentions his family twice in that clip
Yep he's talking about his trouble too
Clearly talking about this court case
Again
I am very serious about everything except for these time
But I play characters
That's going to be a real problem
So I could he should really take
Walker Buehler podcast now you're going to be available to testify
That the end of that clip talked about how they teach college courses about like
Fake news using his
His stuff
Good idea
Absolutely
But then
Can you learn more about fake news knowledge.com
I think that's a good place to go so this this is our final quest coming up here
Weaves in
From that last clip
And then it is
I said people who disagree with him
He said some really funny things
And then at the end I think he gets into an existential crisis about whether or not he isn't real
So this whole time
He doesn't believe he's real well this whole time is we going on. I know it's not so much that
You'll see you'll see
They take those now
They show college kids
He says this and I saw that there's no contact
Publix Auburndale
Oh my God the public show brain damage
Like you
Disassociative looking for a mommy looking for Daddy
Like you do
Infowars.com
I don't think all the leaders that helped expose Google censoring instead of
Satellite Google
Temperature Fullerton
Not physically
Okay
You understand
Infowars.com porchlight shows project
Play like just the end of that because it starts with the fill your hand
Fill your hand
Immature full attack
Physically
Okay
You working
Infowars.com
He does not know what he saying
He is all over the map
10 seconds
He sang
Yeah
Metaphors
Beautiful people attack
Are we got to get failure hand.
Jordan
Has been one of the most arduous episodes we've done
I don't know why but I do
Somewhere in the middle I lost
I lost
I know you cut out like
Probably at least 45 Clips didn't I lost my interest in talking about this episode
So
Bored
By this
Again great sales pitch
I'm fascinated by his
Version of what is real
4 years
Like exactly what is the nature of
Just going to constantly
Discuss whether or not Chicago professors
Come in and discuss
That to me is
This idea of
People are attacking me I'm misrepresenting what they're technically about and twisting it into something else
That's fun
The Google narrative
On its own is fairly fun
But the two of them mixed together
When we know
That what's underneath so much of it is this divorce
It's okay for me
Does he actually believe that
What they are attacking
Come on
Is
That
Clip of him dressing
No
Right I think
I think he has a bad lawyer
Maybe
He might not have listened to legal advice then cuz
I think it is Warriors know what's best for him
Use this argument of its
Performance art as a way to
It's not
He's not a performance
If they are going to bring in Infowars into a
Divorce
That's your angle
It's the only way to use the violent outburst
Play
To his insecurities about leaving his body but no for Alex
To his audience it doesn't play
He knows he has to defend himself against
Again I don't think he could have listened to his lawyer's advice but
Play both sides of it
It's a very thin line that he's trying to
Between
Performance artist when I do stuff
You don't like
And I am a serious person when I do
You do like nothing that's what he's saying to the court
Yes but he's saying to his audience
Dressing up as the
Yes
Got time on the rest of the time
I'm Alex Jones good old classical liberal flash libertarian
God
So yeah
More interesting
That's way more interesting to me
Ben even his b*******
Look up bulshit argument is not that's just
But I don't want to poke holes in them
I hope he succeeds
I don't want his kids being taken away from him
No
I don't believe
They're not back
Ruler
My choice to make
You know I think I know I think it's wrong but it's not my choice
Right I don't have any evidence
Said he was abusive
I don't think you should have his kids
But there isn't any evidence of that really
Not that we're aware I don't know that has done doesn't want
Moonlight
Infowars over the summer
I don't know what that's not the
Right when I was 13 14 I would go to my dad's office
And hang out with him at the University
So like I don't
I don't know that his son is any different
It doesn't want to just go hang out at the Infowars office
Look like indoctrination but on the other
Completely innocent
Look at the indoctrination argument
F******
If your parents are Christian they
Yeah there's a long road to go down
Kids be taken away from him and if the argument that needs to be made in order for him to keep his kids as it is a performance artist
Then by all means
Go for it
Cuz realistically that is what he's doing and saying you are kind of saying that it is alright
For him to lie to keep
Because kids
Yes
It is alright to lie
Because it's not really a lie
The area of perception
Wrecked
Real talk
He is a performance art
Inasmuch as he's a propaganda
Okay
He is not really necessarily
All the things that he presents in the argument has to come down to
Intent
And that is our conversation
Ghibli is whether or not
No
So if he is a performance artist
Then he is
Tending
To be this in
Insane
In order to
If he is a propagandist
He isn't ending
To Duke
People with this
He's a believer
What is that
Well I mean there are people who sell junk
Product
In the world
People whose entire existence is about selling a shity Prada
Like I don't think they should have their kids taken away just because they trick people into buying things they don't need
So it's at the end of the day
His Auto
Imagine
Donald Trump
Had had
What
What a better
Mommy maybe maybe the world we live in is an inevitability and some other rich kid would have ended up being president
That is a good point be that as it may
Mozzarella
I don't think
Necessarily
I don't know it's
It's it's so
Confusing but like
Legitimately I believe that he is a real person and at the same time
He is putting on an act
So both arguments are kind of true
In court in order to not have his kids taken away
Makes total sense to me and I'm not against
At the same time him coming on the air
And saying
I am real this is me it is contradictory to what he saying in court
Just on its face
Because he is in his capacity as a performance artist
That's exactly
While you were
Performing
But you would never say that
In your real life
Possibly know untangling that
Performance artist
Just like your gordian knot of a microphone cord
What's more important to me
I think
No.
I don't know what point I want to make here
I really don't
I worry
Not worried
I am
Comforted by the fact
Alex Jones
Is
Inscrutable
Until we can actually
Spend
Months upon months
Talking to Alex
West Jones
In a personal setting
But one day there'll be like we'll do it the jinxed style us.
Turn everything like everybody involved with Alex
Because
Endlessly
He is
He's our version of a true crime
Go back through
You know
Serial killers life and go back to
Through step-by-step
How all of this crap
Primeweld
Where this guy
What kind of and there's always that element
In a Serial Killer's life
You look at their childhood
Can you go
Yeah
There's always that point
Alex Jones
Serial killer
That
Is is expressing his serial-killing in a different
So he's a very fascinating
Figure that is both
Empathetic
And monstrous to a degree where you
You think
How can this happen to a human being
And at the same time
Which human being should not be allowed to
Anywhere near us
Because they're a monster
Push poll of what is wrong with it
Android a part of me that is like maybe the most cynical part of me
Wonders if he drops in those little pieces
Is about his
Tragic life
And doesn't present them as tragic
In order to make people like us
Pick an empathic
Is too cynical for me
That is one here's my problem you know what that would be a great performance
Kafka's the Hunger Artist
I'm not going to
Deny that based on my cell
I'm going to die that based on
The genius level Talent
Would require
To drop in those
At certain intervals for such a short. Of time
And in such a
Genuine when you're struggling
Story of his mom kicking them off Ernie
That's true
Regardless of whether or not
To him
That is a
A formative moment
Maybe the Rosetta Stone like we said it it kind of unlock the whole lot
The
The stuff that's going on with his divorce
Is tragic
For all parties involved especially the kids
We should not
Let's try as a society
To resist the urge to Moc
About this
Stuff
Mock him
For what he deserves to be mocked for
We in this episode have mocked him about his lies
Go to come straight out of his mouth
We've marked him about him not understanding satire
And we've marked him
For saying things that are going to end up in court
Wilshire will space.
Are great they're fun they're fun
Really
Does it also makes
The divorce
Yeah
Manchester
Cheapest kids
His wife has been
Custody multiple times
Suggest there's something else going
No
We can only speculate
We can't know did well right
I meant is that as a as a culture
Like the first thing I
The first thing that I felt whenever I read about his
His cup
Was not
Oh he called himself a performance artist is
Based on all the stuff that we've talked about
And all the stuff
That Weaver
He might be a good dad
I felt
Forum
Maybe
Maybe he is a good dad you know it's getting that we do a podcast about him being a propaganda
And we hate him
But at the same time everybody else heard this news couldn't wait to tee off and make fun of him about stuff
And immediate response
Was
You thinking he's possibly a good dad
Admir I mean obviously my first thought was before kids
Yeah because it drawn out for years
Running I hate children
My immediate thought was
It wasn't
Joy
No it wasn't like I can't wait to make fun of this
It does not make me feel good
I've gotten more messages about this
Anything that ever happened to me
That's not home
There's no real possible winners
Matter who wins this court case it doesn't
Like
Alex Jones still has to be Alex Jones for the rest of his life
He's never going to get help no matter what how
Here's the better speculation
For you and I
Alright
If this is what takes him down
Is that a net positive
Like is it doesn't do well ultimately this is the To The Ends justify the means
Your argument is
Is based on
False presumption
Because it won't Bend
This is nothing
Rippetoe
Take his money away take all of his stuff away take his kids away breaks him as a man
I want
That's not our speculation
I know but
No
I don't think
But I mean I guess what it comes down to is no the end wouldn't justify the
He should be taking down for being a propagandist the monster
Someone who has
Incited violence
Was damaged
Snot
More lies
But he should be taken down for
.
The fact that in his trial
He's trying to defend himself
Nazis who were good parents
At
True
Completely evil people who love their kids
They raise them in systems that led them
Possibly also be nosey
Christian's again
Shirts
I just ate
I hate the idea of
A custody battle being played out publicly first of all events second of all
Hate being used as some sort of punitive thing
Like I would hate the idea of society treating it like
You've done on the air
Here's your punishment you don't get your kids
That is a bummer
That's horrible
I don't think a lot of people feel that way
Anatomy
Like as much as I hate Alex I hate that
Safeway Morris
Cuz that
Here's here's the weirdest thing
Well this is the most
Novelistic
Nobody hates Alex Jones
Sounds more than we do
More
Accurate reason
At the same time right now it feels like
We're the only people who emphasized
Cuz I don't think his listeners are empathizing with that
I think they're saying that it's a conspiracy against
General that's what I've got
Like us
I mean I think on one level we might be the only people who care about him
Under the death penalty
But like yeah I think there's a decent chance that we're the only people who have
A robot
Fair perspective on him
Anyway
Sorry
Sorry we didn't talk about fun a divorce
S*** but you can go find that at every other website
You didn't come to us for the same ship other people
Video will probably be taken down from the internet
At some point
If anyone with anyone smart
I think Alex
Might be off the air for the next few days I would assume that is Laura's be like Joseph Watson
Google is trying to do list knowledge fight.com Mike cernovich
Secret sources
Huge stores
List
Twitter.com knowledge underscore fights
Knowledge
Underscore
Flight
Also the Gmail account adjusted knowledge fight at gmail.com
Our subscribers are going
Because of Apple
They're censoring
True
Subscribe
You can subscribe on iTunes were super fun
Realistically we have actually been getting a lot of new listeners lately and thank you and welcome aboard
You know Jordan
Until next time
Are we a couple of
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work