Alexandra Thurston color
What is the
Best or most
Important
What man
This is crazy right I don't know
Usual Suspects
I was actually thinking of Calvin and Hobbes when he orders for the
Have you ever ordered anything
Cereal boxer
Like four to six
You know what I'm saying positive I have but like my parents growing up were not into that s*** at all
Cereals that had
General rule no sugar cereal
But then also be like
Malt-O-Meal
The Giant
Knockoff brand Baltimore
Go to like Sam's Club like 20 lb bag of Cheerios
Granola and stuff
I don't know I don't have any Vivid memories of that
But that package
You saw that triggered your question
I just recently out the shirt
I was so disappointed when you were like
What a shity question is like
That case I'm sorry
I just got some
Zachary textbooks
A while back
Watch
I didn't realize the flowers that I got this so crazy out-of-control it is a climbing Vining
Really
No flowers yet but it is going crazy
I wish I had it looks like
Vine all over the place
Really cool
But then beyond that
The peppers are coming in fine no fruit as of yet
Butts
Yeah it's tough times going and Selene
Tomatoes
Couple other things
And that we are really going to cook with
Yeah it was excited
Send the
Separated
From the chat
Strong stock
The pepper plant
I'll let you know
Skip my watch
Going to the show I know a lot about Alex Jones
Cracked up so today
We are stuck in the present
You know the world
To go back to our fun
Fun relatively speaking of
Because Friday episode
Really f***** up Olaf happened
Going over June 13th Thursday and Friday of last week
There is a lot of messed-up stuff
That happens on these episodes
Politically messed up so emotionally
So consider this a fair warning
Be pleasant to listen to
You have been warned
You personally and listeners
Abstractly
Wonderful
Episode
Take a moment to say thank you
We appreciate it
So first
Oliver
I'm a policy wonk that's Oliver Darcy
Kicked off the air
More like thank you sir it's wonderful
A Little Orphan boys
Jose thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Appreciate it very much so young
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Freakishly large
Destiny's Child era or Beyonce era
I don't think she called herself babe
Alright alright
Alright I can't see your computer
Do that by going to website
Yes please let's defeat these f****** hands
Start on the 3rd
As you may recall on the 13th
We had a situation where that was Thursday
In the morning there was a ship
They got hit
Ministration
Don't look at me later on please everybody know that it was a Ron it was a Ron
He was around here right
I want to say before I don't know what happened I can't pretend that I have any kind of
Parties on this or any kind of intimate knowledge of the of what happened
It's a good idea to go to
I joked that I don't trust the people
At the helm
Of our let's say
People named John V Department
Has been looking for an excuse
I don't know what happened
I just think the
The calmer heads should prevail
We talked about Alex covering this
Coming from a place of saying it was around or it wasn't I don't know
The facts will bear out as they bear out Ness
We have more information
I'm not ready to condemn Iran and I'm not here to condemn
This is a false flag
No but I will say right now I'm leaning towards trusting around more than the United
Midstate so maybe maybe we're in a
Like a motive perspective it definitely seems
Like it makes more sense
For them
Do not do this
Alex heard about it it's happening
Play Believe
Sure the exact time
It's fresh
As he's on air
And so Alex
Gets into the story
Responsible behind
Another ship
Well if the mullahs are really that crazy
World War 3
So Alex is coming in pretty hot with a
Realsense do you get that he doesn't pick
This is a false flag
Yeah yeah
To be thinking
That this is sincere
And what we're going to witness
Alex's Thursday
Show
Is he talked himself into believing this actually happened
And that it was a rock
That is needs to figure out a way to be like I know I say everything is a f****** false-flag
But this one's got to be real because
What am I going to do
It's a struggle and he knows the destination
Somebody's trying to get to
Trump
Career
All the pretense
I don't like
Coward
I can't stand up to
So defensive
After that clip
That we just heard
Start listing off boat related false Flags
And
Lusitania
This is not a great list and we're going to go through it one by one you're correct on the first one Alex does bring up the Lusitania.
Whispers Club
She is a dumb dumb
Was that crazy
Infowars.com horse.com
Not good
I didn't hear a?
False flag
Sulfide come from
British Naval annals
Pharmacy first seen in journals 500 years ago
B older than that
Beaded hard to prove forget it
Started
With a
And I quasi false flag
Quasi.
Little bit regular
If you're a f****** conspiracy theorist truth-teller and use terms like Define however you
Depending on your mood
You were signaling that you're an idiot and you're just making
Both side gathered
Together
To cause
Naruto double false flag
Another ship
Maybe flying a different flags
In the country or group they represent
Instead there be flying the flag of
The group that they wanted to be blamed for the
In the case of a sinking of the Lusitania a German U-boat
So I'm not even sure where a quasi Falls flight comes in
I guess maybe Alex could be referring to the Lusitania itself
Do you are u.s. flag
In an attempt to appear neutral
Is really irrelevant to what happened
That boat was getting sunk no matter what flag had on it unless it was a German
More importantly Alex's misrepresenting history pretty egregious
Just like here
First of all this start World War
World War 1 started in July 1940
And the Lusitania sunk in May night
What Alex means is that the Lusitania
Recognize
The ship sank
But even that thinking is flawed
The US didn't enter World War
The powers-that-be to false flag attack this boat then wait two years
To follow through with the plan that had false flag allowed them to put in place
That's nonsense
Africa Lusitania was sunk Woodrow Wilson demanded a stop to sinking of merchant boats by the German
U-boat
Germany agreed to cut it out
On January 31st 1970
Germany unrestricted submarine warfare
Wilson responded on February 3rd that the United States
Unless
Germany committed over tax
Against the United
In the following two months
Germany
9 American ships
None of whose name's Alex Jones
Even though
Most historians agree that the sinking of the Lusitania was not the reason the US got involved in the war
But that its members
Asthma cost
Spell eight
And the reason for that is probably classes
The passengers of the night merchant ship sunk in the weeks before the US declared war
Mariners
The passenger focused ocean liner
Which carry people of an elevated social stamp
Here are the nine ships that were sunk by Germany that actually caused Woodrow Wilson degrees on his campaign
Which was
He kept us out of War
There was the the Housatonic which was sunk on February 3rd nineteen
Great named Eli
Ultrasound on February 12th the Algonquin sunk on March 12th
Which was sunk on March 16th
Crew members who were killed
Six of whom were American
The city of Memphis
Suture sunk on March 7th
The Illinois sunk on March 17th again
The Herald
Sunk on May 21st
Killing 21-7 Okumura Bergen
That one is actually attempt entry on this list
Because it was actually suck and it probably or may not have been Germany
Who was at fault but it's still part of the reason why we entered the war
Everybody American's die
So it is definitely part of
Consideration
The Aztec
The song called April 1st
Killing 28110 who were American
The margarita
Sunk on April 4th and the Missouri
Sunk on April 4th as well
Each of these boats as they were some
Debate
It's about whether or not they constituted overactive
The first three involved no casualties
In the case of the Housatonic
It appeared that Lieutenant Collins Rose captain of the u53
Given the crew warning and then told them in lifeboats to a place where they could easily be rescued by a British ship
Continue to
U.s. boats
They're probably would not have been any legal just
Application for
To enter the war
The Housatonic was carrying food stuff
Smite for the German
An under international law they had every right to
To consider that contraband
This sort of thing could be said for the alignment am lost
The crew that ship was Warden advance
The ship was sunk in the passengers reported lifeboats and towed to land
It was a very courteous thinking
If there is such a thing
But here's the thing
Those thinking that happened pretty soon after Germany announced
To resume full scale submarine warfare
In their announcement they made clear that some of their ships had already launched before the announcement was made
As you might expect more lenient
From something from U-boats you might encounter in
The future
Nuvet is one area where they hit a real leg up on all other belligerent parties
But in a central problem if they exerted their full force
The United States would end up getting
Involved in the war
They need to be able to act with him
The ocean and not worry about.
So the best way to achieve
She that was disturb some other s*** that we would have to deal with
On February 24th 90
Woodrow Wilson received the Zimmerman Note
A telegram that was intercepted by British intelligence
Vince from the German foreign minister Arthur Zimmermann
The German ambassador in the United States Johan Von burst off
Zimmerman request that burn stuff
Reach Out
Mister Mexico
To offer an alliance with them on the condition that they attacked the United States from the south
The offer was to involve the promise
To give Mexico back when it was lost
The Mexican-American War
After Wilson received that message Andy U-Boat attack
Mexican
He was a no position to argue with a more fish side that have been arguing that Tampax constituted over
The next attack
Of the Algonquin
And on March 12th did not involve such courteous German
As we've seen with the hondros
They didn't give a warning and they didn't help the stranded crew find rescue
But there was still a problem for the Warhawk
The shipping recently transferred from British to American ownership
Break before
Belligerent flag to a neutral
Thinking didn't qualify as a justification for war
Because there's every reason that Germany could have not known
It was now in American Shepherd
U-Boat straight-up torpedo the vigilance PS4 days later and ended up killing American civilians in the prom
International
That merited declaring war
Reinforced
United States
I was not going to stop
And with the Zimmerman Note it was clear there also trying to promote attacks against
It's for my neighbor's which ended up
Justifying a declaration of war
The public arguments about the jester
Application for declaring war rarely mention the actual ships that were sunk in change Wilson
His cabinets mine
Instead they often revolved around the much sexier story of the British cruise ship that was sunk two years prior
That ship was never the reason
The United States got involved in the war
But because blowhard didn't really care about the loss of working-class wives
They use the Lusitania is a proxy to talk about the other ship
Misunderstanding
Is carried out through history to people who don't look too much into stuff
People like Alex Jones by The Victors 100% accurate
The Lusitania self is really controversial topic even to this day
It definitely does seem like a British government in particular was eager to cover up something
About that boat
The claim that you know what that thing is reflects a little bit of hubris
What are the things that they might have wanted to cover up is that the British knew that the u-20 was nearby and they didn't warn the
This is a hugely consequential decision Sensei put civilians
Is it risk but it happened because
The British have cracked German Naval code
But they couldn't give the commercial ship specifically
Tipping off the German
Some forthcoming about what happened
Effort
Protect room 40 from being a
Exposed
There plenty of lingering Quest
Think about whether or not they were Munitions being transported on this boat full of civilians
If you look at all the
Details
Making your boat full of non-combatants at Target is pretty unacceptable
If anything it was only used as a after-the-fact Justice
Station 4
Because it was their Express purpose to be out at sea
I'm open to the idea that possible negligence led to the sinking of Lusitania book from all the information I have available
They don't seem sufficient evidence to claim any kind of
Conspiracy existed to have the boats sunk in order to get the United States into World War
That wasn't the result
The came from the sea
And the second one is absolutely
Completely in line with what the German U-boat
Campaign was doing at that time
They were at war with Britain
Britain is an island nation
They could be best
Defeated by aggressively isolating
Churchill had expressed a desire to increase neutral shipping traffic
Back to Britain in hopes of causing
The flare-up between
In the same way that he was super stoked that Pearl Harbor Got Back
Bring in more neutral Merchant
Traffic again
Hope something happens. The problem is the Lusitania was not a neutral shipping
It was a British cruise ship that would have absolutely not been seen as neutral to the German
So whatever goal he hope to achieve from a US Merchant
Ship being attacked by Germany
So this one's not
This one doesn't work
Alex believes
Is the Lusitania sink a Glide to the start of World War I
So imprecisely Ortiz silver
I'm not tired
He's got another boat
You know the game started the Spanish-American War
In Spanish.
Alright
Well Kaiser Wilhelm was actually on that way
So that's okay
He's not even in the midst of the USS Maine
Started the Spanish-American war sword
Sort of
Set some of the conditions
In place and was a
Sparks
But use expressly wrong about everyone being off
The ship
The USS Maine had a crew of 355 man and when it blew up
The three of them were killed
With eight more dying later from their injury
There were 16 additional man injured leaving a total of 78 out of the
355 not injured or killed
And the survivors didn't survive because they were off the boat and they staged
Explosion happened at the
The front of the boat
And their quarters happened to be at the back section
Complete lock
On February 1st
Immediately debates flared up about what it caused the explosion with the results
Where
Dick Cheney
No he's cool
He's old but not that old
Others noted Roosevelt
Probably a mine that blew up the USA
In the immediate aftermath really arguing from a place based on evidence to push toward the result
Calmer heads didn't want the
It was trying to escalate and then people like Roosevelt were eager to start a war
Left to their own devices decide probably would have just argued between each other until the formal investigation have been done
And ultimately never have actually even happen
I base that assumption on the fact of President McKinley was
Not interested in declaring war investigations that have happened
So generally confirmed the it was an accident
In the 1890s though
There was a bit of a media Feud New York newspaper Market New York
Randolph Hearst
The New York Journal
Great everybody remember them super no similarities
Propaganda
0 Timberland
Not like each other and wanted to
The market
And how Sensational there news could be
They're competing in a profit-driven zero-sum game where the public were the pond
They found they were able to sell more papers if they were more
Sensational
Inflammatory headlines
Add frame to news stories and more creative ways whether or not those creative tellings of that
Depicted reality or not
They knew that if they built an air it isn't pushed it with enough vigor animotion
It would drive people to buy their product
I would work people up into an emotional fervor then you sell to him
It is not a business model weird all familiar with I believe
The setting of the main United States
Largely owing to evolving ideas about colonialism
Particularly surrounding an ocean of Cuban Independence
First and Pulitzer were both in favor Cuban
Independence
Expressly
Revolutionaries
I mean even if you're in favor of the cause behind their actions
You can still see the
Promotion of is bad
Yeah
They've been playing that game for a while and making a lot of money off it by the time the main
With no more information than the dogs in the government or the hawkish Teddy Roosevelt
Explicitly arguing this
Republic other papers pushed the slogan remember the Maine
I did everything they could to advocate for war with Spain
They did this partially because they were biased in favor of Cuban Independence
But more importantly because it raised their profit margin
Give me to secure and argue that her staff Pulitzer responsible for the outbreak of the Spanish-American War
Sucking a simplistic and.
But it would be equally stupid to not recognize the part they played was a piece of the puzzle that
They were massive propaganda Oregon
Making up stories in sensationalizing
Kernels of free stories
Intent on bending public opinion towards War
Alex didn't get Trump elected
But he did play a goddamn partner
Sure
Hurst
Exactly idea of a military intervention became more and more popular
Heartstrings and embellished
They never would have been able to start the war on their route
They needed influential people like Teddy Roosevelt the drama
Internally within the government
He's kind of a Jon Boat
Is that time
They are similarly no one ever would want John Bolton become president
To somebody younger
Do I remember a story of trump telling him to shave his moustache
Subsequent investigations most notably by Admiral Hyman G rickover
Conclusion
In the main use of a new type of coal
The ship has previously used anthracite coal but it just gets coal
Largely because that type of coal would be able to make ships
Move faster
Unfortunately was also way more Coptic and prone to spontaneous
And this type of coal being present as well as the significant
Significant amounts of pyrite that were found
At least two strong indication that the ship suffered an accidental Kohl's
The absence of any external evidence of like penetration from the ship
Come outside
Who was hit by a projectile or a mine
They'll really just drank
That conclusion
The sinking of the Maine was not a false flag
It was a horrible accident opportunistically by Propaganda
Stop delivering stilted news in an emotionally compelling and dishonest way
I'm not doing the same thing here in the yellow journalism
But I'm single probably reason you'd rather called that a false-flag then examine the actual forces that were at play during the time
So you think he's got another vote
I remember specifically about this
Cuz I read the
Can't remember the drums of war the fog of War by Barbara
I keep thinking about that
The chicken hawk
We need to go to work
F****** hypocritical bulshit that
They're they're scary but the ones like
Teddy Roosevelt who are like
I want blood
Like Andrew Jackson just walking around just drinking f****** all the blood of the enemies that he's
Destroying your leg
Yeah cuz it's like oh it's
Crut talked to the people who are like like those chicken hawks
Describe
The escalation of like
Be careful
I just
You scare me
Of course this is
About
That he's going
And of course there's so many other famous Naval events the u.s.s. Liberty
So the u.s.s. Liberty
Anyone is unfamiliar with that on June 8th
Fired on an American
As it's not in the Mediterranean
It was in the middle of the Six-Day War
The US was a neutral party
And the ship was an international waters so there's really no just
Application for the
Israel said that they mistook the ship for an Egyptian war
Complicated conspiracy theories that I'll get into later in this Epic
Is it there's no possible reality have done what they did in order to try and trick
United States into war with each
It'll be a bad eye
Say that pretty
Is there
And there wasn't any real cover-up or attempts to make it look like a jet
Egyptian craft
Is there anything
There's no way that the us would have had that attack happen in Israel comes over as like sorry about that we met
And they decide alright let's attack
Alex believes that Israel's objective was to kill everyone on the Liberty
So there's no survivors and they could just say that Egypt
This doesn't make any sense
The airships were marked as Israeli
Anyone on board
The ship survived
There's any ship nearby that sell what happen
The whole plan will be bust
If they really were trying to set up Egypt they could have easily park there helicopters with Egyptian markers or just not head
One of the survivors testified that he could see the ships where is Wrigley
From 2000 yards away
Which I give them ample time to radio that Israel was attacking
Given the technology that existed at the time that eats party possess
He would have been in
Impossible for the signals
To be jammed
Coming out of the boat
How to distress call
Ended up being
I'm not going to pretend that the Israeli military hasn't definitely use false flag
Before like in the case the 1954 Lavon affair
This case it doesn't look like Alex's argument makes much sense
If only I knew where you was getting this information from
Well I believe it was maybe he'll bring it up later
Pretty sure the only reason Israel
Had the Six-Day War with two
Inspire app
I'm pretty sure that was why
Define song
I lied there's one more boat situation that Alex brings up with so far I think he's over 3
None of these
Seem like fall swags to me they're just complicated he would rather not deal with the realities of
And of course you've got
Show many other big events
There's the one
Bring it up
Vietnam I'm sure the headline news today Alex Jones says that the
I did not
I said that
Yeah I know it's weird
Be like maybe out Scott at this time
No the headlines would be
Alex Jones bucks tradition
I don't know it was just a dismissive
What happened to the Gulf of Tonkin
That was that on August 2nd
60 for the USS Maddox
Engaged with
Second confrontation
Which was just totally made
Also we lied about not having fired first
In the August 2nd
It was all definitely part of trying to get more directly involved in Vietnam
This is close enough for jazz on this
Right about this kind of makes
Things worse
Here's what I mean
You would sound crazy and paranoid if you just insisted that everything was fake because he had one example from 55 years ago
Alex
Create the appearance of a
Pattern in order to justify thinking that everything could be a false
And that leads him to believe completely under
Lusitania
Call just to get into World War 1
Or that all the men were off the main when it was false
He has to think that those things are false to
Because the reality of the Gulf of Tonkin incident isn't enough
For him to just
Defy his stupid
Way of
And
Don't speak
The war but that's unsatisfying to Alex about the
Books
Tons of books written about it
Ifucking McNamara has gone on record and interviewed about it
Like
You don't get any f****** credit out of that but
Tell you what
Whatever one's off the main
It's just his way of making
Something sexier
And it's lame
That is one of those things
Every part
The real history of every part of the Vietnam War
Is the most
Horrific
Stability
That you can have like
That it was
Started
Set Nixon went by
Find lbj's back in order to
Keep the war going
For an extra couple years so I'll be Jake
Really
Fuct
Absolutely
Possible for anything
Sing like that to ever
Position that were in right now
Is Alex has a bunch of boats
Here's where we get to Alex
He starts to get closer and closer to saying it was real it around it
Large military equation
Roll the dice
Vacations
Still use it to push me into a larger War
Hezbollah Sleeper Cell
Nashville shooting down a couple of Iranian Special Ops
Talking about
Can chlorine in your
Forgot
C Unit Subway
Yeah
Down this road
False flag
What do you mean by that
As a false flag
Convince people to start a war with we might have to disentangle this
I think what he is expressing
Is it definitely did
Right and then now they're saying
To attack them so they can play the victim
So I mean
I don't know
Alex has nothing to base any of this allowed so it doesn't matter
The Trump doesn't like that kind of thing
Nopales
But I'll talk to her in the room
Shrimp
Why does it matter the size of the room
Got out the dirty stuff
Trump told
The CIA
It's not but those items
Interesting kind of
Isn't interested
I'm the new sheriff in these parts
You might have said stop looking into my dirty
Cut up at 12:35
It's all nonsense
But
You know
In a place
Driving doesn't know
He kind of wants to keep his options open here we're only about 10 minutes or so into the actual show
And he's still
You got this ambivalence
But
You got quote
What the boomers are
Unstable
You have a powerful military and they are crazy
You know you got this
You got Alex
What am I going to do
I been
Angie's on air
Light bulb
Flash is over his head
Is on its last leg
It's flickering
But he still considers it a memory and an idea
You remember
Something that
Evidence
Set the mullahs did the
I just remembered though
Ayatollah
Rock and roll over there
L l
Supreme leader
Vows to retaliate
Claire's
Charms
There
Around the world and that
Huge if true
So I looked
I looked all through presstv I looked all through Infowars
The closest I can find
Is Lidl close
Maybe
Impress TV from February 13th 2019 were around valve
Against terrorist groups who attacked their guard troops
Until 27 of their soldiers
Yeah I'll give him
Play me some clothes to the time periodic to talk
Is an article on the Christian Science monitor
Pretty in favor of regime change
How the title at Battlefield 4 internal Wars
It's not that close though
You describing
I'm kind of at a loss
Doesn't pull up an article
The Iranian
Smashing Pumpkins cover band
The world is a Battlefield
No vampires
I mean I couldn't find any
That's just to be expect
At this point
Right after
Hubris
Sturms a little bit
Just pull up Iran's leader threatened to retaliate to us sanctions
A month ago
I wouldn't believe it when it was on the bottom of singing in
I meant to cover that
That's a big deal
Yeah just move the needle
Who is move the needle
So I couldn't I couldn't find Alex's talking about
Really helped you search for these words
Alex's Express
Closest thing I could find to the May 16th 2019
Nautical and MarketWatch
Which I do know Alex excited about the times
The past so it makes sense that he would have read it
The headline is Iran's foreign minister responds to unacceptable sanctions by the United
Foreign minister Mohammed
Threaten retaliation or does he just got soft
Those words only exist coming out of the mouth of Anwar gargash
Who is the Minister of Foreign Affairs
Against
Or does a Reuters article from a 26-20
16th that's reporting on something from presstv
The headline is quote Iran's Khomeini calls for vigilance against
West soft War
Starkel doesn't say a single word about Hezbollah or unleashing terrorists or any of the stuff Alex
The talking about
However
There was an article from May 19th
Android
We're Ayatollah Khomeini
There won't be any War
Biryani a nation of chosen the path of resistance
We don't speak of war and they don't either they know it's not their inter
I still do not know what he's talking about
I'm still
Somewhat at a loss
You know what the thing I learned
About
Mainly
The big takeaway for me with this story
What's up
It's wholly Khomeini Twitter account has a blue check
I don't think he's verify
It's all right I think
Because there were a couple of tweaks
Being like
Do this wasn't us I don't know what happened this is
Everybody was reporting on it like it was his ikaw
Stupid
I'm not saying it's not his
But I would also be totally I believe the world exists is not on Twitter
The guardian has a Twitter account
My brother
They were visiting
So why would he
Hey let's try and get Iran in the US
Stop starting
And then all the sudden a Japanese boat
Perfect time
So
Remembers that I can't find it all
Fairies
Alex
Remember some other details
Really gets him
Stepping close to the line of calling for war
To put pressure on Trump
A month ago to
Damn speech
I'm so used to false flags that
I hate you
Threatened
Everywhere
So he's decided to go
April 22nd 2019
Ron put out
Specifically that they would close the Strait of Hormuz if they were prevented from using it
It's a conditional state
An absurdly high amount of the world's oil traffic runs through hormoz and Arantes
Control a large portion of that
Oman controls of a fair amount of it on the other side of the
Straight but if I were to be prevented
Confirm using it does make some sense if they would shut down
They're part of it
The threat being presented coming out of
Conditional statement about their own Waterway
It doesn't really seem all that out there
Close the Strait of Hormuz
What's going on in the prison
But that wasn't what they threatened to
To shutdown
Block traffic
Every other week
There was always a threat
Shutdown
Sports talk about in terms of threat
Anytime
But they were going to
Shut down the street
Flexiv movie
Ministrations clear strategy
Do with it
But they haven't done that yet
Instance
Of the tanker
Is not
Closings
So whatever Alex
Is not accurate at all this isn't an embarrassed
So absolutely
Alex has convinced himself
This is a rock
Really when I woke up this morning and heard that
In the Gulf
Right off the coast of Iran
I said are they really that crazy
Get started with a false flag where a country to blame
Nation they want to attack Iran
I'll go in the shop already
And then some us officials started
I was sitting here
Earlier
I don't need
Credit for this
4 months ago
Two months ago at about a month ago
I hate you so much
Iran is the
Suspect
And I ran
H2 taken
Options
The sabotage
Ships in the Gulf
That
Look like
Yeah real hard into this position which is
I mean
If it does end up being the case the Rhonda this is a I don't
I don't
It's possible that I have no idea
I mean the Alex is thinking it's still terrible conclusion is correct
This is real bad
Start talking directly to the heads of state of Iran
Crazy narcissistic
Announcement
What did Iran right now
I know what you're up to
Because you shut your mouth song
Price that's crazy
I mean it's bizarre that he actually thinks that like Khomeini
Watching Infowars
Where do you think
John bowne
Bayside
A great thinker
What are you talkin about in terms of the controlling the choices it's like no matter what
The choices you come out looking
Does
Gets into the primary source
Balthazar
Why do I know that because
Presstv
I've been on presstv
About a hundred times
I just got too tired I don't know I'm really young.
Susie's tires
I think you work for the government
I got it right here
They said they're going to do it
Revolutionary guard
Organization that was April 9th
So that's
Stop
An article about an article and presti
Alex would know this
Snapchat
Headline
Rcg warrants reciprocal action against US forces it labeled terrorist
Also the Articles from April 7th not April 9th
That's a little petty but
I read I read the real stuff
Google
Recipes in English
Blog
The website
I read a bunch of stuff on
The article doesn't
Decision to label virc
CG a terrorist organization
But you really have to look at it in the big picture
VG's branch of Iran's Armed Forces recognize terrorist group is really close to
Declaring war
Who be like is France decided to declare the u.s. Navy an enemy of their country
It's an incredibly hostile act from a geopolitical standpoint
For a country to respond by saying if you
Do that you're crossing the line
What's a normal response for a country to have
It's not unfair to look at what the Trump Administration
It is kind of beta
And also that article doesn't say that they're going to sink boats or activate sleeper cells
Oldest rap label them a terrorist organization
It specifically about putting an urgent motion through the government to label the US military personnel is Blacklist
The terrorist
Like the headline says
Reciprocal action
This first article that Alex is bringing up does nothing to prove it
It's all just misrepresented and you know how he is
Press tv article instead of
He's dumb
But he thinks he's cracked
Dakota
He thinks he's God
Yeah
Smart 26 yeah they went on
What's the guard about
Imelda Imelda
With zero evidence of anything
Just weird
Articles he kind of half remembers and never read to begin with
Vague
Conspiracy theories about boats
Yeah
Not too far into Alex's show
Axolotl
At the beginning of this episode
Yeah but it's important to recognize that came out of a gateway
He did over the course of the first hour of his program
Was talked himself into
Getting to the point where he's doing like he's at a wrestling promo at the mullahs in Iran
He's talked himself into that position
Now that is not to say that that's where he's
But
That is something casting
He is
Reinforcing
Defending
And that's who stated line
For now get some serious vacillating back and forth between
Each position
Not so much but we'll get some
Okay
You know
What's going to happen is
Is that if there's a war all these Hezbollah Irani and super cells are going to activate
He's something good Alex's
Right
He brought up for a long time and that's why Google and Facebook and YouTube
Because he talks about the Hezbollah
15 million dollars
Private outside groups
The things was that I was talking about Iranian Sleeper Cell
Because I laughed he's working with
Say that again
Years ago
Beetle with the Democrats
Help launder money
Absolutely
Sure
I don't have much of a response
That because I don't I can't take that seriously but I do want to say that every time
He says I'm going to say it again
I always think
Cisco
It really impedes my ability to listen to
I just get James Brown in my head everytime I wanted to do that I want to do
So bad this is our generation
The three years
Boulder
What are the reasons are not going to respond to that
Rank.
Hip misrepresenting
Some emails
They got released
Prove it anyway
Is nonspecific
Go fuc yourself
Not necessarily not necessary to respond to especially because
Next clip
I'll explain about specifics of how this works
And it's crazy
Obama can give the order
Your house
Congressman
I want everybody about this last year
Asthma
Have your house is listed that's why I told you
Bible study
Who's the real estate
Course
Carjacking
Why not just shoot you in the head
They believe
Surrounded
Embedded assassination
Missouri City
Okay
So we got a we got Trump's embedded assassination team
Are there sleeper.
American Diner
Otherwise because if it wasn't Bedlam already
So is everybody here working for one of the other like
This is a strange way to view the world
Also recently two former state senators have been killed
Conspiracy thing
One of them is from
Qanon folks lectured at to Hillary Clinton
It's nice to see Alex resist that easy pass
Will have
If ever a much more challenging Narrative of
Obama been in office
Alex Jones is audience
Direct path
Alright got a lot of proving that you're making Alex
Soda state senator from Arkansas
Please put gag order on details
Other than to say it was a murder
Which isn't all that suspicious
Considering she's a former state senator
She lost the 2018 primary her death she was just privates
But extend that courtesy to areas up like that I think is appropriate
I don't think there's anything weird about that at all
Last week 48 year-old Rebecca Lynn O'Donnell was arrested for Collins murder
Active volunteer for Collins's campaign appears to have had a friendly relationship
I'll wait until more information comes out on this to make a decision
State Senate Celine type situation
Either that or Hezbollah in MS-13 her employer
Speedway might be the
We'll see who else
Go anywhere
The other States senators from Oklahoma an officer since 2013
Gunshot wound
I don't think they're related
Habitat
He died from gunshot wound they have not been specific and labeling it as murder
Instead
Investigation
It's really sad and I feel bad for everyone involved their families
Community but we don't know anything about what
Nichols could very well have committed suicide for all we know
Do use their death is a
The prop which is exactly what
Because I like
Well that's what I'm going to get a million phone calls
Memories
Prematurely
But unfortunately because
Movie toxic environment we all live in
The absence of information is
A conspiracy Worthy
Bye-bye man I guess it's
Just
Be scared
Do you understand
Lisa didn't get cut off by the break I'll respect his timing on that
Very rare instance of him timing out to commercial for a prelate
Not a registered Democrat now because I don't want to be your
Erroneously
So everybody voted for
Undoubtedly
And that business
This is making much more.
Definitive statement
Is overwhelming
Revolutionary guard
Around the world
Misinterpreted
Keep in mind
Overwhelming
There isn't anything that's different
So
We will block the Strait of Hormuz
Akashi trillions of dollars
You do it you didn't deny it
So you can get the US
Watercraft
Our sailors
Marcille
That doesn't sound right
Yes there's a long history
The false flags and staged events
No one's talking about how the Iranians know where
April
And in the subsequent months that they would do this and now it's happen
He has no doubt
Yeah that's quick note out
We talkin about A-Rod detaining
January 26th
What is implying like it something's happening last Thursday
Is completely dishonest manipulative the only reason someone
There's no other reason to bring this into a modern conversation
About what is unless you are
Trying to
Sway people in tubes
Supporting war in Iraq
In 2016 those US troops that are on detained international waters
Navigation and entered Ronnie and territory
I guess what John Kerry called up his errani and counterpart talked it out with a little bit of diplomacy
And the sailors were released 15 hours later on harm
This was a situation where our troops made a little mistake and it was a faux pas
But because calmer heads were at the helm everyone is able to talk it over and recognized there was no harm
No foul
This will never happen again
I mean
Kind of situation
Easily spiral out of control that people aren't
Able to discuss things that people are treating each other with
Respect and understanding that like
Hey look I'm sorry I know that's your water and we're not we're not allowed to be there they made a mistake
Their Compass was off
Because if you did
What kind of situation
So good on you for the photos on an ounce
Yeah so
Yeah
Search up yelling something stupid
Trump tweeting us into war
Or Alex
Speculate
Towards
Republic
You know what the only thing that I think we have going for us
There's very few people who probably will be square
Rattles and tries to kill people
Riled up towards
Supporting award I don't know how much effect
Um sell for
Anymore
Saving Grace
Butter and
Clear and compass
Of the current Administration
Combined with the fact
Pretty sure most
American dirt
Dude we
We played this song
This is a
The tune I don't need to hear any more Springs
In this rest
Baby constantly will be surprised
Inability to learn
Past mistakes
So a
Sparrow
So in the next Cliff Alex gets pretty extreme
Ecology starts wargaming
What's going to happen
So let's say that Iran
Witchy is that he is enough and overwhelming evidence
No.
So what happens next
Now let's talk about what comes next
A couple more of these ships get blown up
We have cookie
You can bet your bottom dollar
It's going to back a Saudi Arabian attack
On Iranian
Shipping lanes
Iranian military targets
I don't have a bunch of stealth bombers
Thousand feet flyover
2000 lb Bombs all over Iran
That's a war crime
5 minutes later
Sleeper cells every
And Shiite sleeper cells in Iran
And Shiite sleeper cells
And Shiites
Country that Maxwell Trump Dodge
To have
Soft targets yet
Moms
Conditioning supply systems
Iranian specialize in
Machine gun
Vehicle
Houses down
That sounds pretty bad
That doesn't sound good
Yourself
What about it
Is only there cutouts
Professor type
Child molester
Seriously what
Hezbollah
13 hit squad
People's houses
Because the Democrats want
When Iran
Democrats are domestic farming
Election with a foreign domestic
Smooth grooves taking us out to break while Alex informs us that
That over half of the country is
Definitely
You know II
I always want to
Questionnaire
Is every major city
Especially in the context of
What is it
Okay Rapids
Strategic
Multiple metropolitan areas like what about Pennsylvania
Route for the Big 3 or do you go down to like read it
Suburbs all just get along with Amanda
What about the Twin Cities like
What about Minneapolis
Hezbollah hit the Quan
MTV hits
So this is all stupid
To his narrative
Starting to come together a little bit
Are you starting to
Acclimate
To what he wants
The idea
I'm your host Alex Jones out the Iranian mullahs very very
Work
And Mary
On their revolutionary guards it is the government
They are the praetorian guard
They are the mullahs
They are the Shiite aristocracy the royalties
Muhammad
A Shiite group everywhere
Military prepared for major terror attack
Announcements
Remember them closing the Strait of
Clip is the point where Alex's narrative takes a turn towards Genesee
All this stuff about a rattling completely opposed to everything Alex's ever pretended to
Is that for sure
However is that clip what he's presenting is another level of unaccepted
Be as he sees it
No big thing for Trump to take out the mullahs in Tehran in the war
So it would be easy
You'll be the easy thing for Trump to go ahead and win that war but there's a problem
Iran has secret Hezbollah terrorist cells
And literally every Western will respond to attack on
I guess we'd have to do is preemptively lockup all the Irani it's just
To be safe
And just like that Alex has talked himself into the exact
What are the more disgraceful chapters in our history
When we put Japanese people because we were afraid of
What are the reasons it so important to respond like to things like this
Either way that's not my criticize me for being overly cautious
I'm making a leap in logic
I think it's important to understand how easy it is for this rhetoric
To make that jump
If Iran is wantonly attack
And it would be easy for us to win the war if it weren't for the case that Iran and Hezbollah sleeper cells are in all the varsity
It follows that the solution
Alex Wood
Proposed is rounding up all the Ronnie Anthony's West
Sleeper cells
Would be neutralized
Considering we're keeping refugees in internment camps now
Mixed up in
The process about that
And here's where it's worse than it sounds
Because Alex isn't just talkin about a roni and you should be
You scared of
Dumping nerve gas out of the capitol
Hope everybody enjoys
Islam is Shiite
Shiites from
Country
In the world
Steve all purposely immigrated
I know him off the air. That's a crime I know he's not like we need to round up Mosley
Or whatever
It's
So close
Yeah that's f***** up
This is so close to a rationalization for the internment of Muslims
Which is something we already
Kind of know he's in favor of
It's almost like he's using this crisis in order to fit into
That already islamophobic worlds
It's almost like a workaround
He's doing
Patient it's so it's
So f***** up
And what makes it even more f***** up is in this next clip
Prefix concerned that things are going to escalate
Biscuit bearing
Easily escalate
In fact it probably will you got right now
No one is on the news
Threatened to bomb ships
If we put sanctions on them and they just did it
They admit to it
He's responding
Articles
I really really want
Till I get these Muslims out of our country
And I willing
Into completely misrepresented
Why aren't they
Lie that I have
Misremembered or am making up
They never should have got rid of Ales
It's insane to me man
It's really insane
The idea that he's like this is probably going to escalate as if it's like
Lamenting
And then in the same breath being like
Because I Ron has sleeper cells everywhere
We get away from Iran for a bit thankfully
Take a little break
Then I've got
All around the country
MS-13
Really
A video of that coming up with a new
Sure
Guess you heard me right
Albatraoz
Are the United States
Hope you enjoy
Alexandria
Portage Park tennis Wilmington Ashley
Really
Who is
She's a democratic social
Mixed up all the time the hard-right it seems like
She didn't say anything about a violent overthrow or anything about putting people in camps or with organ with Hezbollah
There's a clip of talk about how capitalism is failing
And we need to do something
And believes in his community ownership of land resources labor etcetera
Alex wants to make a cogent argument against that position fine I'll listen
I don't have the energy to respond to that dumb s***
It should be pointed out that The Daily Beast reported last week that Trump is planning on housing 1400 detained immigrant children at 4
Still in Oklahoma
That's pretty shocking inoffensive to beep
People particularly older Japanese-American
Because Fort Sill is one of the camps where they
We're held during World War II
I know that every day brings a new Alex Jones related horror and every day there's something new that directly contradict
One of his long-standing position
This is profound Lee disgusting
All he ever did in his career was yelled by the federal government because they were
The New World Order
Now we have a federal government locking up children these f****** Stylin supports
I remember back when we were covering the 2009 episodes
Huge deal out of the idea that Obama was reopening
Where Japanese-Americans were held during World War II
This was the next step towards
Opening the campus Museum
As a memorial to remind us what this country did when we let fear overwhelm us
Reminder is dead
Trump is doing exactly what Alex lied about Obama doing and Alex doesn't say s***
But all the Democratic Socialist
Capitalism is necessarily exploitative
She's the one who wants to put you in a can
Not Alex's f****** hero
Is literally doing that right
She must have had a really good platform otherwise for her
But also
Healthcare for all
What kind of like overcompensation would you need to do to go around Denver wandering around 4
City council position be like
Not by the way knock knock with MS-13
Elevator pitch
Also community garden
You know what I think that's the part
If it's really offensive
Just a little bit racist
It's all about cauliflower
I just think this is like
Particularly
Disgusting every time we see something or Alex
Flips on one of his old position
Of course you're a hypocrite
But something like this
It is like I would only know that Alex yelled about Obama opening these camps
Alex
Do you have Trump opening up
You know using these places
Where Japanese-Americans were held
To house immigrants that are being
What is the
Why would you yell about Obama doing it and not now
Why we know why
I think we know why Alex
I think what would be a fascinating
If if you were running and if you're going for a historic
I would wonder
How much
Of the right-wing
Character is a
As Obama of Obama
Dictator who is destroying your life actually wind up getting the right wing
Comfortable with
They're actually being what I'm saying like if you spent the last eight years old
If you know the difference yet
You know it's just that now he's working on your side
Yeah that is interesting
Brilliant
Interesting idea
I think it's probably a bit of it
Cool that's a bummer
Alex gets on to
You know
We heard him drunkenly talked about how I eat
Woman RH daughter is 4:30 father
Any song is half his mother and there is no sex
Unfortunately he is
Strongly against the lgbtq
Hands clap
That is fine
You forgot protect
Children
And future Generations in this nation
Throughout history there have been that form inside different
Civilizations
They're obsessed with sex with children
Chats with sacrificing children
In the world
You will find
Having sex with children
And then
Cool
Now the vehicle used today for all of this is
Lgbtq
Q x y z
F*** you
I got is The Bachelorette
Because
Tax on the income and I also
The vehicle for exactly
Is the lgbtq
Community
What are you doing like what are you saying
Aztec facts
To save Aztec civilization from falling
If you knew what to do.
Takeout
Tell me what isn't that kind of implied in there
Be a hero for the western civilization that's going to be destroyed
Did I just pick that mean
Rank bigotry
It's rank bigotry masquerading as historical insight
It's just it's just disgusting
I can't I can't think of any group that
Black what is he missing
I suppose I do too much about like
East Indian
Yeah like people from India
The Japanese
I think he likes them
Yeah I don't
Usually
Just now too so he's probably on their tip
Do you know what else
You know that's a little bit of an argument he had some
Bad words to say about the Australian
Like non-white population
To be pretty okay
His book
Hey we're going to weather this f****** storm
Pretend Trump is a cool dude
Everybody be quiet
Will get past
Sit on the other side
Indian
People
Japanese
Be all that might be
Yeah
It's not a pic of what group
That's probably about
Specific
The lgbtq community is up to
And this one
Is a punk
For the shoes
You get to get out of class and it's encouraged and go to the game
Michigan
Are you sure it wasn't
I was walking across the street to Segovia restaurant
Pride
Broadcast
Glad
Rashes
Is pedophilia
Took whatever
First of all I'm going to guess that I was a story about seeing gay men having sex is embellished
Quite a bit I bet he saw two guys kissing was scarred by it
Chicago
Never seen outright public sex celebration
I believe some people might be f****** an hourly
Wandering around seems like more risk than it's worth
It's not like it's a gay or pricing
People sometimes f****** alleys
It's shocking to carry on
And I was I was like
Hello hello
Super common but I have definitely
We are definitely walk past people f****** and
Just on Halsted
I'm right.
Probably
The article that I was covering as of course
It's using an Austin american-statesman article is a
Complain that the Austin Independent School District
Does using some fun
To quote boost student involvement
Alex is really interest
The school district has its properties
Two churches who hold their service
It's really common thing a lot of parts of the country and honestly I don't think that's even really a big deal
The Comedy Club in Columbia Missouri that I used to perform at rented out their church on Sunday
I think it's the sort of thing that could be really Mutual better
An arrangement in a lot of cases
I do support the separation of comet
In this case however one of the churches who rent it at the Performing Arts Center in Austin was a church called the Celebration Church
Which priest a pretty anti-lgbtq version of
They likened homosexuality to bestiality in as much as their abomination
Cicadas forbidden
Naturally lgbtq activists were not super thrilled at the church renting out School District
Workspace and protest
The Texas Attorney General against the First Amendment for the school district
The government to discriminate against
The church based on their religion
Complicated thing for the district
Stop renting
Space space
Two other people
In an attempt to find a solution everyone can live with
Lgbtq advocate
Suggested that the church was going to remain able to use School District
Then some of that money raised should be redirect
To towards initiatives that's
Supported LGB
Q students and staff
The school board said for sure that's a great solution
Here's why
The school district has raised
180 $2,000 from renting out their spaces
And they're setting aside $10,000 for lgbtq students
172,000.
Do use for
It's really a win-win solution for everyone including the Celebration Church
Everybody wins
Nothing in the story mentions anything about the ages of the students
It's involved in the being busted
Ryder
Austin Independent School District
Includes schools covering Pre-K to high school
Because it's a school that they can't even if it's anybody without parental permission slip
Probably have to come up with them
Fourth graders
Ten-year-olds to Pride on their own without parental permission
Guardian
Impart that $10,000 is
Protection it's like you know
You can't take
Kids
You can take kids to the Saint Patrick's Day parade for school thing without chaperones insecurities
Examples
Play 100%
There's nothing suspicious or weird here this isn't Austin School District realize
They made money off renting outer space
To a group it's offensive to the lgbtq
VQ Community but he's also group they can't kick out without causing a
Huge legal battle
Play disciples make a symbolic gesture of support
To participate in Pride
Is Austin is enough that's probably
The fitting headline Celebration Church
Atq causes
So I don't know if this is a lot of
Alex
Yard work with that what you has
And what Alex does have is a gift for impression
Oh God
I think I might have been a little bit
Capricious earlier saying Alex doesn't do anything
Against
Cuz I pick you might do an Indian operation
Asian is in the mix
I think you might hit Indians
Pan-Asian like I'll just put it on
He's more of a shotgun
When it comes to racist Impressions sniper rifle
But I know it's not good
Yikes
The PC police coming down on people who do clunky hockey racism
Yeah it's it's it's not said because I would not have
Yeah it was no idea what he was trying to do and then he said it was Indiana's like that's just a bad accident
Major races
Defensiveness on his part in the present day
Never leave that aside that was just a little bit of a
I don't look
I mean okay
If I did something offensive
And I was really bad at it
I wouldn't insist on
Continuing to do it just
Because people were offended by
Looking great at it continue to do something
Just the worst at impressions
Terrible
Academy in level skills
He was a mimic
And he was like why won't people
Call Alex Jones
What's ridiculous
Alex is desperate for fun
We don't even the middle of the plug that opposed to being caught off guard by the pivot
Something else
Free Bonneville / 12
You the best deal we've ever offered if you're if you're keeping track
8 pack power stack is 50% off
And you get a bottle of alter
For 12 for free
This is we a need
To move the
I promise I'm only running until
Next Friday
Because we probably shall have her all the 12
Until that point
Show me water bottle for 12
There's other people chances to get it for free
4life.com
Okay
ITube
Pointless conversation on the phone at the audio terrible
Kohl's coupons but also except
The other shirts
Also
I think you might do better if you
Exude
Yeah don't
Say like
So this is 50% off and you get something else with it
3 bottles for the price of one
Don't do that I remember
Tire play in movie about how being desperate and a sad fact does not help you sell things
So here's the last clip from 13
And Alex
About his
The case with a rock
We're getting calls we're getting messages
Where we
Think I shouldn't
Do something
Also by the way
Completely forgot about Ebola
Iran's doing something opal is next week
Leaving aside the fact misrepresent border on
Alex Jones is really just accidentally
Himself into a corner that
If he's not careful
This is going to undo
Most of his career
If you're listening to his justification for why he believes that this was a real attack in not a false flag
It all boils down to the fact that Iran said they were going
How to do X action
FedEx
That's all good and well
If someone threatens to do something and then that thing happens it's generally a good idea to start your investigation by checking on the person who
Who made that threat
But Alex isn't starting his investigation they're ending his investigation
They said they were going to do it therefore it's not a false flag
If you apply that logic to the broader spectrum of the things out a career literally everything falls apart
One of the biggest career-making issues for him was the argument that 9/11 was a false flag
If you use this investigative technique is currently using about a run
You should have immediately come to the conclusion that Bin Laden carried out that attack
Threatening that
Same building in April 2001 Ahmad Shah massoud of the Northern Alliance warned that a large-scale attack
That information
Presidential
What the headline bin Laden
Determined to strike us
Intention
Clear before the attack.
Alex Jones
It was set up at the Oklahoma City bombing was a false flag meant to demonize The Patriot
Put tons of people have testified to the fact
Timothy McVeigh was going around discussing
Threatening letters to the ATF
Before putting his plans into action
By Alex metric
Timothy McVeigh threatened to bomb the Federal Building
That a federal building
Dear God
Purple Swag either
I could go on and on without slippery the way Alex
An attack on a ship
Is his impression that they said that
We're going to do something like this
The new processes
Completely shattered
I know that I can bring this up a lot but I think
Essential to understand
Accusations of false flags are almost
Never sincere
False flag has become a rhetorical weapon
Accusations of false Flags the weapon that could be wielded both offensively and defense
Obviously we know that Alex uses
Type arguments to deny that people like him
Could possibly ever commit a crime
But the alternative this one wasn't
Is used as an offensive weapon against before Alex wants targeted
Anytime a Muslim or immigrant hurt somebody that's definitely not
Because
Those people
So their crimes are all definitely real. Definitely happen
In this case with a Ron
Alex's meal ticket
Trump wants to attack Iran
Occasion
It was a false flag is not a good
It's not something that you can do
Kind of feel out
It's not something that you could do
Terman for water too coincidental detail
That's disrespectful reality and research
Bowflex definitely do exist
But my senses are there
Steven Lee rare
And they are it's not just an explanation
For everything that's pink
Convenient for your worldview
The mythology of the false flag is something that allows certain certain subset of bad thinkers and Bad Axe
The hijack reality
False flags have existed in the history of the world
And extrapolate that out to imply that it means that everything is possible
Once you internalize that idea events are no longer
The pieces of a story that's being told
Everything needs to fit
With that story
You believe
Alex believes the government is evil and militia Patriots are always good
It's imperative
To find a way to make what happened
Set the store you're already telling
This event
To threaten
Sabina pants
Before you know it everything set
You have now made the story
The government looks even in the militia Patriots look even more good
This is all false Wagner
There a crutch
He uses to hobble his broken down there it is along
It's packaged in the
The sexiest of wrapping paper
The wrapping paper that just says what
Over and over and over and over
So what I'm saying is it
Who's my boy
Be skeptical
What's the question
But for your sake and
Publix
Don't start from a position of most things are probably fake
I've been trying to work backwards
Then try and justify your suspension
That is
Psychosis but Alex
Discount Tire
In those Sandy Hook depositions that everyone took
What weed
Kind of trap
So I
Just the longer longer we do this
Amore
Read and understand
The more just becomes clear that this is not a sin
Sphere
Belief system is not
What's your worldview
It's a tax
Circle and I don't know how conscious that is
I think there may be a piece
It is
But I think it might just be
He's done it for so long
Ingrate
Like paying but just like
A certain extent you probably was trained
Along these lines
Predecessor
Where's the people who
We're his intellectual
Probably
Functioned along the same lines
Terribly
These justifications are these bad
So I don't
I don't know I think it's probably just the mindset that he got into
Never grew out of
Event with like 911 seems like a real outlier
Because it doesn't really makes
Yeah in terms of this
The path of
Jism
Demonizing groups he doesn't
You could say that it's demonizing
Bush
Anthony
You can make that are
There's a possibility there
But I think the reason for the outlier is he idolized Bill Cooper
And he was ripping off Bill Cooper
Eddie Duran
Yeah I think that one makes sense
If you look at it as an isolated case Within
You can see how even though it doesn't fit
It's still face
I mean at the same time you could just see it as such a large event
Stats in the immediate after
Nobody
How to process
Tripped
To that one because
Well I would say Vicky predicted 9/11
Because he was ripping off Bill Cooper and of course you're going to run
Okay Behavior after-the-fact make Sprite
He's like I forgot that theoretically pretty
How do you not try and make the most
It is obviously
A ripping off of Bill Cooper
Piece of s***
I don't know I think it I think it's still fit I think the broad picture of using
False flags of the rhetorical weapon
Both authentic pensively
To protect your world narratives
That you wish to tell
I think it makes total sense
9-11 flight outlier but that's why I think it's
So we get done with the 13th
Who takes very clear perspective
Bollocks,
I mean it just seemed like even if I rent
So
Analysis may not be that far off it could be the wrong reasons Wells is always off
You takes
E-juice home I guess
They got a bunch of calls
People who were like
What the f***
Yeah that makes
Perfect because as soon as he gets back on air on the 14th
Is Tunis a little
I want to get into the latest
The push for full for
Largest
Normally
Able to suss out who's behind
Cloudy and really foggy
I got to take a step back
Get over here on this phone
I don't know what's going on
I had evidence
What possibly could shake
Your confidence the next day
Exist on the 14th
Whatever
Such such stupid
Such backtracking.
Pictures of what he does
With the Iran narrative
Its soda mods
Sturtevant house stupid
I will talk about it
Waffle
The little bit
Gets off the wrong picture and
Gets back to just
Define
Zach Boats were false flag
Sinbad
And I told you to get a little bit more to the u.s.s. Liberty
Because he brings it back up here
And we specifically find out where he got some of this
Watching
Doesn't sound like
The dumbass white supremacy
Covering for Israel
I'm reporting history
Just because
LBJ
Israel's okay and
Government
The logic is just incredible I had for the chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff on before he died
2 weeks before he died
He had heart failure his brain was all there
Let it all out on there
I got him on by news
16 years after the fact
Detail City game
More
Really hate to hear something like this
S'more is literally the commander-in-chief of the Pacific
Incident
Incident was a false flag salute
100% commander-in-chief of the
Pacific Fleet during the Gulf of Tonkin
Yeah that seems like he would have at least
Do you know what's up
Or the fact that he was in that position
The fact that he was the chief of Naval operations
For most of the Vietnam War
Villain
Analysis world
Yoki could be used by Alex to reference about how the u.s.s. Liberty was a false flag but mysteriously doesn't
Weird
Thomas More was the former head of the Joint Chiefs of Staff from 1970 to 1970
Before any other resume full of him
Impressive titles on paper
However if I interviewed him right before he died he would have been 91 years old
But even assuming his brain was all there the best-case scenario for someone in failing Health was born in 1912
Is generally not so great
At the time of the u.s.s. Liberty attack more was just beginning his three-year stint as the chief of Naval operations
After having already served 34 years
Send that in the service
It was 3 years
The Gulf of Tonkin
Give me the pilot in World War II need received the Purple Heart as a result of his plane being shot down by a Japanese attack
He survived the crash and was rescued by an Australian ship
Which was that stopped by the Japanese
Have you tried to survive in a Lifeboat
And water
Later in life you testify before Congress
About the need to provide adequate machinery
Since the cause of his crash was that a bullet hits
The unarmored fuel tank
Is playing
Reply to suggestion
Providing Extra Protection with a waste of money
That perspective quote is great
Until you're in the sea and someone is shooting at
You got a different View
Fairborn
Can't really argue
Because there's a piece of Moore's personal life story that matches the story that's told bike
Conspiracy theorist about the sinking of the USS Liberty
That they claim proves that it was a deliberate prolong
They say that the Israeli forces were shooting at the crew as they tried to leave the ship on Lifeboat
Which is matching
Thomas Moore's life
The problem is that the investigations
Testimony of the crew of the survivors of Liberty
That's one thing isn't mentioned
Once
In fact Captain McGonigle testified that he had ordered some crew members who were lowering lifeboats
The water to stop
Not because they would end up getting shot at that because there was no danger that the boat would sink
And who knows if they might need the lifeboats later
Take Five Points away from Griffin
Bronco mechanical
McGonagall
I don't know about a reference
So none of the accusations of shooting a testimony of the survivors or the investigations about the event
The only begin to
The pop up later when some of the crew members begin making media appearances
Start Direct
Contradicting their prior Sports
Who probably be impossible to prove it
But some might say that this change of perspective might be the product of anti-zionist intimate
Becoming much more popular
The United States through the 70s
With me term Zionist occupied for mentors
Being coined by Neo-Nazi Eric
Two years later the term would be featured in William Luther pierce his book The
Diaries
We should go on to
Inspire
Supremacist
The book also inspired the white supremacist Outlaw group
The order who helped bring the term to a much wider audience at 1984 when members of the group murdered prominent Jewish radio host
Kellenberg
In the late seventies early eighties the sentiment that Israel controlled the US government begins
Creeped out of the sewer
Just plain old white supremacist groups
It's a slightly more mainstream conscious
Another group
It's not justification
The attack on the u.s.s. Liberty is a prime example of an event
To fit the mold
Of a US Government bending over backwards
To allow Israel to attack.
Then going out of our way to cover it up for them so no one finds out that the government
Israeli Azog
Subsequent investigations of Liberty event and found that it was a
And a series of miscommunications were responsible for how things played out
Well all investigations except
That was an unsanctioned investigation headed by Thomas More
In 2000 crank years old
His findings have been roundly criticized by people who have reviewed the court records and transcripts
The communications from that day back in 19
7 is being an opposition with the
The fact
Everything I can tell they're not wrong
Investigation
Boris said to Rivermark
I've never seen a president I don't care who he is stand up to
It boggles the mind
They always
The Israelis know what's going on all the time
If you American people understood what a grip these people have on our government they would rise up in arms
Our citizens certainly don't have any idea what goes on
This code is largely circulated on websites that also see the traffic in Holocaust Denial in Russian
I mentioned it to illustrate how more is used by
Particularly anti-semite
Argument that we live in a country with a Zionist occupied govern
This is what he
Izzy's
Place
In culture
Yeah.
He was he was on
Some of that tip for a while before that investigation
Still
Spearheading a lot of this
U.s.s. Liberty ship
Also the next sentence after that was
Zinus operated government their controlling everything also
16 cats are ripe
I don't know what his
Full intentions were in his life or if it's just something where he's been co-opted
Yeah by these
Real buckhead's
But whatever the case
You someone who
Bigger figure
Also more is apparently bit of a race
He wants that the idea of Cuban immigrants coming into Miami
They won't take a bath at least once a week
In one sentence
Thunderstorm in my brain of like who is he
I think it's the black
Still there
He also wrote a memoir
Where he included that
If you're going to be an American you've got to be an American
If you want to be a Greek go to Greece if you want to be a black go to Africa
She is
Conspiracy theories about the u.s.s. Liberty
I don't think I would be surprised
I don't have that evidence and I'm not going to
But I don't
Take that his record is
Great
So a lot of this information about the u.s.s. Liberty
His personal life story is a p
Piece of what's co-opted and put in
To the story of the u.s.s. Liberty
Attack
What's the historical record
Suspicious
I think that you something
Pretty tough
How to get around whatever your evidence
Or way or when you're a Yorkie
Mercy theory about the
It doesn't match up with history
Your life
Right
Weird
Kind of leaving a little bit of a
It's a little bit like William Barber
Nominated
Seems like he had one
Very weird
Little bit of information about what's going on
Studio here on June 14th
This clip really
Got
That's why are they here and somebody else was coming
Wish I was about something else and now they're here on other
God help me
It just never ends
He sounds like someone like on a sitcom whose in-laws are in town
Black God
I think
People that they don't speak
What are you doing hiding in the crawl space
My mother-in-law's
Olay back she's French
So
Did we get this Alex's
Sing a big story about
Flagrant
That's coming up
Extreme
The story is going
It's so flagrant show
So
McCoy
Real bona fide
Call nightmare vision
Tyranny
Give us 8 more adjectives
And it's just openly announced to shareholders
Announce to the world
Like
They're talkin about
Having a couple
How old is a wonderful new ride
We're going to teach your five-year-old how great it is to have their genitals chopped off
Did they don't want him shot.
Oh how wonderful we're going to ship in
Everyday of weapons
Killed most people liberal
When I get
It's a culmination of everything we knew that was coming
Thoroughbred
You got nothing left...
Play Just Do It
How to stop right there as always do and
50 years only first came out
The real sponsorship
Goes on
Deering
The wife
The least amount of money talk show host
Sponsorship
No no.
Security
Kind of yeah
He does
Facebook
Whatever
30 minutes
Defensive
Unplugged
Did I don't listen to a ton of other radio show
Distracted the level of
It's about
To write
If you
It would be much more power
It's it's really really f***** up
The way he does it with the
Getting
Lakeview Thoroughbred tyranny we all knew this was coming
Manipulative
It's a advertising
Techniques
2 a.m.
We have these amazing knives for you
There they will chop anything just so you know the government is going to come and find all of your knife
Take them away from you and Destroy them unless you buy this knife
Right now
There's some similarities
Play Billy Mays and those dudes
Even though I probably would
Do that
Famous congressman
Do actually got the lands of Alaska signed over to people
Senator Inn
Fridays 4th hour
Shut up
I'm at my lawyer
Connecticut
I want you to know the stakes
What the system is willing to do
Protectus operate
Because they know
This is the real deal
So I thought this was the
Yeah I thought this was the unbridled Thoroughbred tyranny news
Right
This is not news
You've got this massive the culmination of all the things that we
Nick begich
She's got to go
Angels go play your harp
I thought that I thought that was the case but it's not the it's two separate
And here's the first one
Which is the actual tyranny do
It's basically a racial slurs
Breach of service or something like that
I don't even believe that
The case but whatever
This is like five hundred times worse than I change
This isn't science fiction
Dystopia
Watching
Listening to you
Real-time
In
Your house
A month-and-a-half ago
Will use
The first
Figure
And then we can use it to as a
To tell all the other people
You better
Watch what you do
Because we not everybody else's devices under our control
We do everybody else's can't receive anybody
It's computers
In your house
Building a politically correct on you
Your job
Twitter YouTube
What he's been saying that for f****** ever
What is website
How small your crew is
If if you have
Proof that Facebook called
I told you
What is about to say
You put that immediately
I don't care
Recording laws
You put this out
You're Alex Jones
Absolute
You know why you know how I know that if he had this he would put it up
He's outed sources on air
You know it has
No
Interest
In protecting any kind of journalist
If he had this information it would be everywhere
What's the Telly zombies
It's good for children
Just
We let you
On Facebook
Weather announcement
Supposed to do
Curious
How much him saying I'm serious twice is an indication that he's joking
I think he's trying to do an Indian voice
Yeah
Oh
If you did say that and you didn't own your own business
You would be fired in your bank account would be ruined
There is a reason that you can't say the
How much of it is what he thinks is being funny
Embellishing of the call
Bright
Just don't believe any of this
I mean I don't I don't believe any of it
Can't tell his how much he's signaling
Being like
He's trying to be funny
People with a really bad stupid sense of humor Tuesday
I can't tell
Honestly at the point where I can't tell
In this next clip really was where I struggled
I can't tell if he's joking or not
This is so
If he's being serious this is one of the funniest things I've ever heard if he's trying to be funny
I tip my hat to it but it's like
There's no indication that he's
I don't feel safe
Classify
Crawfish Bash from
High School to college
You're scared
Accommodate
I can change song
They have a girl
Stuck on You
That works at college
Lamborghini
I can't tell if hilarious or not
Yeah you do you get all your freshman to come in and go to one of these leftist groups
Sucks you didn't
Now admittedly if that doesn't work for everybody
Ayahuasca
I admit that I'm
10 years out of college or so at this point you know
At the same time
When I went to college Alex was 10 years out of
Dropping out of Junior College
Particularly know if he's deeply in touch with what's going on on campus
I'm going to go ahead and gas is not an accurate depiction
Yeah
I mean depends on which college
I heard Arizona State this is what they do
Dispositive
I think this would be at like a Oberlander like
When is real hippie School
It's like an upset
Yeah I don't know I think this is pretty stupid
Here's the struggle that is really funny weather it's based in ignorance
If you trying to be funny I think it's last
Absolute
Assuming that he's actually presented
F****** hilarious
It's too much because
He says things like in this next
Really
Really toeing the line
I think
Old dictionary
Muslim call to prayer
Cuz I just still cute
Mo Problem releasing
Just a little problem
I just don't think Jesus would like to
But you know I think the world's going in that direction show
So f***** up
Is so f***** up
He said we should have a race specific bioweapon the kills all Muslims and Arabs
But I know they wanted to destroy me they want to take me out and now I just picked up killing them all
But I also think
Think that's the way the world's going
I think it's inevitable we're going to have to commit genocide against these people
Yeah yeah yeah
Blase about the idea of an inevitable genocide
No no I do remember that
Kids like you should
Turn the other cheek
Only to release a bioweapon
Specifically targeting Buzz
Right
Really prophetic
Parable
This is an interesting way to
To preemptively
Pretend that you're the victim in
And some sort of an aggression
They could be
You put forth.
TI No matter what any time you had this like
Suck on a dick dog turning into a liberal the college
Call Michael.
We might end up having to kill all Muslims
You know
Unbelievable
That's insane
Impossible
Become on back-to-back
1 hour
Snow
One of them is Matt Bracken
His special forces
Idiot
And here is a clip of Alex introduced
Joel skousen
About to
Eclipse
Important
Because it indicates
It from a very early age
Alex Jones Is Dead
Lived in an environment of rabbit
Rampant
Communists
That's growing up
Was a super John Wayne American World War
Megatropolis
Playing the game
You got to get there and do it
14 years old
And
So
Indicate
Next to me that Alex Jones is Dad was involved
In some groups
Yeah probably
I would love to go buck wild with this if you like unsolved crimes
Yeah I would love to try and do that
Site like meetings
Reading meeting set up
At the home
You do realize
Casino it's presented as something else
Right
Good picture of
At least the way Alex
Experience
His childhood
If you're living in a household like that you're going to end up with some
Lingering beliefs
Unless you go to college
Tex-Mex get your big dog suckin challenge
Those beliefs that you had from a young age
I think I would get
The ayahuasca
Yeah I don't know what's going on
Alex's references are 20 years old
So on the show like I said
Is there to argue that the people who are caught on video
In the boat coming up to the tanker
They were clearly retrieving their Limpet mine
In a row
No two ways about it it is absolutely around
They couldn't have got that mine out of the boat
Unless they knew about the mine ahead of time and knew how to diffuse it otherwise
Bracken it is around Alex Jones
Completely agrees with him
Came on to justify Alex
Texas yesterday
Yes
Who argues that
The Japanese
It was a mine it was a missile
Play contradiction
And Alex
5 minutes
Completely disoriented
And I know that this is Alex's version of what
Looking at both sides
In the end
Credible sources of information
Forsaken
Completely different thing
With complete confidence and pretend Authority
It's one thing for a news program to talk to both
I could see
A credible news program talkative a 1000 back-to-back
You could do that
But you'd have to maintain an objective
Position
It's a totally different thing
Hypothetical newsperson
How to talk to both of them
And how the audience witnessed
Like within the span of
Be convinced
Contradictory
It's jarring
Nadia
And it leaves you with the position of like
I trust Alex I think Alex is a good
Gauge of information
It would be jarring if like you and I you are
Uncomfortable and
Held by cognitive dissonance
Where is if you are
If you
Cognitive dissonance on a
Minute-by-minute
I doubt they would be
Affected by that
Steelix.
Yeah
It's still tough to
Earlier in the July 14th episode
We had Alex say that there was unmedicated thoroughbred
Hernia foot
And then also he said that
Baggage
Got to go we got taken for that workers resume
So they're not the same thing Facebook is going to
And now we get to Alex
Simulating what the second
In part was
The attack on Infowars
Interesting
You might show some cards
Almost in the fourth hour don't want to tell you what they're up to
Because you have scared some employees
Okay
I really haven't told people what's going on
Best Buy
Voice families
Biopsy
I try to have women beautiful women
Get up
Grocery stores at work right now
It's because we're doing something very important
Hours a day
They are so pissed
Ford's the FBI
They say where the victim
I'm not a victim I just want to
Cheap
Finish strong
Play kill me whatever
Money
Yeah
Vaguely discussing
What is this
Attack
Preemptively being set up even before it
Anyone list
Has any information as to what he's talking about
He's trying to use this to get money
For himself from the audience
Which I find suspicious
I find that to be
Everybody ice
Now has already figured out what it is he's about to talk
Alex
The one thing that there
That I have not read any
Raising
Pretty weird
That
So also did Alex saying that he has a problem with
Which is greater
Here I mean I guess there's some sort of insight they're busy at solutely
Boost
Feel a little less
Here is that by the time the third hour is rolling around
He's clearly drunk again
Like I think that he had that jarring
Tabac interviews with
Sweetheart
Who votes that contradicts everything
Galveston was a little bit of a longer interview
It's clearly talkingshit on Trump
I don't think Trump knows anything
Like if you or I were in these meetings
We could tell him about
What Trump doesn't know s***
He is not part of the movement
I'm sure he stupid
The Godfather
Thought
And I
Base that on his behavior
Completely changed
He has Owen on Owen Shroyer
They're talkin about the drag queen story time that's going on in Austin right now
Went down there to go cost
Problems
Yeah
And then they made it really their story is about how antifa
Was going to show up to
Counter whatever anyway is only important
Because you can really see that
Is pretty f*****
This isn't Linda Blair
This isn't
This is
You understand that
Silver ours
These are the skeksis
A drag queen story time
Who started the fake fight
This is a drunk dude
Cuz I mean like the yelling and stuff all kinds of
Completely
And I also probably a little bit uncomfortable about having to make the 4th hours
So I think the following talking about
I think that there is a whole lot of influences probably
And it comes out when you sitting here with Owen like I got a bit
That is exactly what he did to Steven
Crowder when he went out after he drank
Episodes
What do you want out to Steve Crowder's demonstration
The fake fight them too
Started fake fighting because Steven Crowder
Fake fart with
Gavin McInnes
It's just sad
The shows up
Cuz he wanted to talk to
How we need to start using everything
Preservation
Very
Topic
It's so Alex is just
We won't let go
Talk you just keep
Screaming at
Thinks he's doing a bit
You just keeps yelling at him about Satan
And you won't stop
They will face their father Satan
He will pay
I'd like to remind you that Joe Biggs was calling in to talk about data preservation
Jesus is Alive show
I love shape
I want to kill babe
Join
Josh Jones
Jojo Jojo
This is a completely different
Princess purse
Knox
I mean
You do it
Completely drain
Mikey's his manner is completely different
He's acting like all those other times in the past
What he was holding it together before like
Absolutely
Completely
Pretend
To the point where they're trying to deliver his report but haven't gone out to
One of their Marquee
Make propaganda about
He keeps trying to talk
To the point where I think
They had a conversation
And Alex had to leave the studio
A real to get his report
Here I is
Blowing Minds
When he's finally allowed to talk
And then you find out
Church was raining out
An independent school district performing
Performing Arts Center
Now that independent
School district for forming Arts Center
Now when I asked why they were going to be
They said it was a little
There was a little outraged over the fact that this church
Call Dan quired
I was told that there is an lgbtq initiative in Austin
Why is there an lgbtq
Why is there no heterosexual
Finish date with the kids
There wouldn't be any people at all
Play for the Panthers
Congratulations
Theoretically, it doesn't look like
St.Louis
Entirely sure
That's crazy
It's indicative of his thought patterns
This word of childish
Level of justifying
You just got a little taste of the world does Alex let him talk
Stupid
Now
Here
Is
Barging into scream something right at the end of Thor
Infowars
Why not tomorrow
You can also like I see that little cartoon where he liked
Under the desk
That is a show that I would watch
Obsessed it look if Owen Shroyer said dumb s*** for three straight hours but every now and again there's just a
Some weird-ass
I would I would
I'm surprised I still don't
Simultaneously believes that are on did this and I was taught by the bubbler
Clips from the last 2 days
Acme sandwich wanted
I like to guess that's about and it least one of those
He seems to think it's some sort of virtue and they like
You Are Family
Owen Shroyer just said if it weren't for heterosexual people we wouldn't have
Actual people which implies if you have
Days that much what you should really be doing
Is killing straight
Wolfie now that's you using this pathological is
As I would scream
And that is that Alex's other lawyer
Norm pattis
Has been flown in from Connecticut
Superior on the show
I got to say
Norm kind of won me over
First of all
Memes
Stopping
Behavior in that deposition
It was pretty shity
He comes off better than Robert
And this
Display
Introduce
Throughout little bit of a
Also feeds into my
He's drunk
Constitution 1st Amendment
Sprinkler
Wow
Questioning
The daddy of
Talking about this Norm is
Trying to be as good a side
Barely
The Matrix
But then Alex gets off track because he wants
To brag
Why what's wrong with him
The top clips on YouTube
It has over 100 views right now
Jojo
It's barely almost it's a biggest
He's ever done
The average video videos
3 million m
Guess what the lowest video
14 million
At the top
14 mil
YouTube famous for
Tell the little Pimp C
Prosecutor
I do that's a good turn of phrase one of those rare instances
Anger ends up turning
Like a good set
Yeah that's a solid
Are you may put too much for printing
Is always the paper you got to recycle
He is not impressed at all
Those that Alex is a blowhard
I guess it's time to get into it
Infowars
It's 3 minutes long because I wanted Alex to
To be able to present the situation
And then see how quickly he takes it to the
A conclusion that he wants
My family
When your disposal
Obama appointed
Sandy Hook
Which
The judge ordered
Press release
Large number
Gmail
That's Chris
Very interesting individual
The front of Costco coffee
Costco
Ambassador Murphy
Senator Blumenthal
Survive quote I must be taken off the air
Try to set me up with the Russians
Ephrata model
That's alright
And so we learned
Just last few days step
One day one of these hundreds of thousands of emails
No one would know what they were we
No you wouldn't know it was an attachment that you would know what they like to
Donut shop
We're not involved
Attractive
Feel
Haystacks
I get these emails a few weeks ago
And I go right
To the FBI
We've got him a child
Happy I seriously never opened
It send it
They act like older our friends they're not.
Go to hell
I wasn't born yesterday
I was born in the dark
Show
Whatever's going on I'm offering
Hundred-thousand-dollar
Not today
Hundred-thousand-dollar reward
Prosecution
I've had
Hundred and $15,000
Bonuses
Contest
4sho
IPay
Hundred
Thousand
Dollars
We're going to release the metadata
Force.com
The email address that company
Prosper company
Back
Going to find out
If you're going to go to prison
First of all I want to say immediately that I don't believe based on the information that's currently available that Alex
This kind of accusation
Pretty serious stuff
And it does seem entirely plausible to me that someone could
Defiled
If more information comes out I reserve the right to my position
But for now I have no tolerance for people
Guilty
I understand that it's my lot in life to be overly say or to Alex but I don't think that this is an example of
I think it's being that this is one of the few instances where he does make sense that someone would do that to him
And things have played out this way it makes
Remix ability
Play it's Alex's ability to make propaganda out of his own victim
From the way you talkin I can barely track what he saying happened
Someone sent him
Threatening emails about Sandy Hook
They contain attachments that included illegal Toronado
His team didn't see him
Didn't notice them until they were handed over as part of the batch of emails that were deemed relevant to his lawsuit in Connecticut
That seems to be what it's saying as his narrative
Coming from hymns there's a grain of
Assault aspect to it
But honestly it seems
Plausible is a series of events
What happened
Exist
It could be a PR stunt
I'm coming from is very much one where I think
It's wise to exercise caution
Narrative about this
Eclipse is that
Is that the people who are suing him
In Sandy Hook Center
And that's the only way they would have been able to know where to look to find it to take to the FBI
Assumption
Because any kind of data analysis firm would be able to
Run script
On large amounts of data
Specialized
This sort of thing
It would not be something that would be a needle in it
It would be if you were manually searching through emails
Because of algorithms
Programs that people can run
It is the sort of thing where you can look for suspicious thing
First second you would be able to
If you had
The idea of being able to process
Through in like a week
I think that's very doable
Falls apart a little bit
Contest seems like a weird mood
I probably told me something you would do if you didn't think this was a real
Can't afford to make the
I think they got this should cover
You don't need to crowdsourcing investigation with the actual
Gators are investigating
If This Were Real I would really really think the FBI would say don't
Comment on an active investigation
Seems like it would get in the way
Whether or not this is real or not I think what he's doing is super your response
Presumably does really some of this metadata or whatever he has
If one of his listeners could figure out who's IP address it came from the FBI already knows who that is
Assuming any of the stuff Alex releases actually leave
Which it may or may not
All he's doing is increasing the possibility that that person
Is hurt
And this matter is not dealt with lawfully
There's legitimately no reason to do what he's doing right now
I don't think
That's a fair assumption
I don't think he's trying to cover up any
I think it feels more attention-hungry
Then anything else
So I don't know what the reality of this
Situation
The fact that he's making a contest
Strikes me as he's not too worried about whatever it is
It doesn't
All of that
Worried about
The consequences of him doing some
I'm through talks about how people who have threatened him in the past
Have gone to prison
And then things really spiral completely out of
By the way
More than 20 people that have threatened us
At my crib
Prison
People threaten to kill George Bush
What's prison
Those are people who are threatening
Those are your fans
Who are threatening Obama in the comments section of your website
Put on you for
Heading over the IP addresses I guess
I think that's probably you can't
I know where the lines better than this but those are people who threatened
You right
Flights
You're not offensively
$100,000 reward
Monday
Never arrested
You get $10,000
What are convicted
Thousand
Dollars
Now
I wonder who during discovery
Out of Millions
I don't know
I just think people are smart enough
Nowhere
I asked
Thousand
Dollars
Don't know why
$1000000
1 million
I'll sell my house
Million dollars on conviction
$1000000
This doesn't help any
Like offering a million dollars to people who can search
Stop the databases or the dark whatever
It doesn't help in any investigative
Official
FBI could do
Any person getting hurt
Is not a cheap
Buy whatever you're doing
It's
Very f*****-up
Especially when you're
Insinuating
Law Firm
People got you
Megafactories
Because you can see the beginning of the insinuation there
Who Woulda known in the middle of your hook for sure
For sure
Cuz every video I know he's going to go off on the
Wild
This this
These clips
That going on back
And the preemptive sales pitch
I don't want to rely on my feelings or like my ability to
Into it whatever it is out
What's Theodore didn't
But
I've heard him lie 10 billion times
And it doesn't sound like
God this is
This is such a bummer
Cuz this is
I wouldn't be surprised
If he was overjoyed
When the FBI file
Cuz he was like I can
Ride this
Look I'm probably
Intersection of
Joy and anger
Quotes for him
Intertwine so
But he has it's the same thing we talked about back in the 2013 stop when Buzz bissinger
Legitimately
Threatened to shoot him
Hope was Alex when that
Justifiable position
You be like
From everything
Bad actor
Tried to
Yep
Is
Every way
Everywhere
The Gambit doesn't work if someone on his side is guilty of
Yeah like
It doesn't work this
This propaganda doesn't work
If the heat
Anyway
Even if
Second
Bit someone within Infowars or himself was
Responsible for
He would never bring it up on the show
He would never talk about it until the FBI brought it up never make it public
Display out of it
Even in terms of getting ahead of the
The story wouldn't be worthwhile because the facts of the case came out
He will be like also apologize
No because
Who knows
Joint Base on my sense of him for a
Studying his behave
I would bet 95%
Everything I own
And that other 5% would just be
I'll write that off
Yeah
Iiii
It does seem
Tumi
Like
Opportunist
Yeah
Like person doing it is
Stray bat
Somebody
Really ill well or someone
Somebody really f***** up
What do you mean I mean
Really fat
I don't think there's any possibility anybody involved
Like you said there is a little bit of a freak out
Million
Dollars
When you call up or we'll protect you
We found the c*********
I like women with big giant
That's a big ass
I don't like kids like you goddamn rapist
You father going to get it you f****** child molester
I don't want you to leave it radio
I don't care you're trying to set me up a child born I'm going to get your ass
$1000000 $1000000 you little gang member
$1000000
Temperature at on a pike
$1000000 b****
I'm going to
You're not going to ever defeat Texas usaccess yet
So you get ready for that
I'm pissed right now
And this is
Because when Norm
Finally is allowed to talk about
Screaming you makes a really good point
Really text right now
This goddamn ocean anymore
You should have talked to me about the
Reward structured
But this is me, lawyer any food behoove you to listen from time to time
Potential Witness
Thousand Dollar General
So let's talk about what happened here
I was
I didn't say that I just don't want you to create an interest in the outcome of a person who testified
Because they now have it Thursday contingent interest until
Difference in having a contingent officially test
You trying to explain
If you give out money for
You can't have them testify whatever information they find it probably
His lawyers very clearly pointing out even
Dick best
To the bottom of it through this route you probably ruined your face against
Let the professionals deal with this
Norma's is really trying
To set out
Text rape
And angry
Just won't listen to me
Brought
I'm specifically for this and you won't let him talk
Child pronography into your email account
Hoping that you would open it
So that when you opened it there would be direct
Evidence that you would viewed knowingly and tile board
Out of hundreds of thousands of emails they got
What a nice present
House of
Rising
What nice people kissing Maddie
Chris Maddie
Let's zoom in on
So what you did there is he had the the document cam zoom in on a picture on a printed out of paper
This guy Chris
His face
He's making a Target out of
He did
He really did do that
That's
Incitement
I mean his lawyer's right there
Barnes is the one that had infection
Put on me
I'm not in the kid watch your democratic
So get ready
Moorman
Cuz I'm not an idiot
So like
Norm is clearly like no
Like where is Barnes kind of
Insight
A little bit
Norman
Norman's liquor
Guys I'm
You can tell
He is exasperated he's trying to explain to Alex
The correct way to
To deal with something like this
And Alex will not hear it because
He is
So full of Rage
Alex
Praying
About how he would like this
Turn out and I think because of past context clues
This sounds a lot more f***** up to me that it might
To someone else
Fu man asked you to have God
Got anybody God
Never
I do not
So the
You know all that stuff is
It's gross but
Him saying
Not anybody else God's vengeance
Preclude from
All the times lately especially we've heard him talking about how
Yes
Gen X
He says that a lot
So even him saying nobody else is God's vengeance
That doesn't
Mean that he's not hoping but someone hurt
Well I mean he's giving a million-dollar bounty
That right there is not enough
Sara Lee
Stirring a diaper
Doing things on your own
He's pushing really hard
How about the idea
These people who are working against him
Sandy Hook
Are the ones
Norma has been delayed most of it out but I've been fire-breathing today because I pop.
6 million emails you got hundreds of thousands of the Court
These are hidden links that they knew were right what to go to
And Obama is just like God
So shake up their self
Turn off
Satistics that I covered it like
0 point
2%
Who I am
Tyrone
Filthy lie
They find
Grains of sand at the beach
Find a magic child pronography
Obvious
Is that
Problem in this country
Obvious
Your conclusion is
Like if the world machine to sort
Very effectively
Then maybe you could
Find a grain of sand on a beach
It's just a matter of computer
Our then your metaphors Fall Apart
How do you find a needle in a haystack I do run it through a processor
It's real nonsensical the idea that like all that magic
Do you know how this
You know how it works
Yeah I think it's fine
Annex
Because of the way he's behaving
I took Norm
Really tries to politely tell him you should not do this
And Alex does not under
I've spoken to Federal prosecutors they regard you as a victim
The news takeaway nearby
You-know-who
You are not a suspect you are not a Target you are not a person of interest you are a victim and that's the story
Are you showing Chris Maddie's photograph Hunter
Is your adversary in this litigation
Possibility to take
Bear Casey
Heart if I can ask you
Thinks he owns America
A personal attack on Chris Mattie I want to find out who sent the email
That person then I will go to work which Alex Alex Alex
You understand
Lynx
Finding a needle in 5000hd
Contracted out
They contracted out to a sophisticated data mining firm and they spent probably $100,000 to go through your email
Looking for whatever they could find and they did find this you believe that that was placed there and they knew where to look and how to find
I don't have evidence of that yet
I represent listen to me young man listen to me
That sounds dumb right now
Hit the pause button
Whoa
You try it
Credibly frustrated
Because I think
You could have Skype
Escape Army
It's all you're going to do is yell over me
Call me
Well I think
From the
I think that Norm felt
He could win
The Sandy Hook lost
Yeah I think that he felt that he was able
Is going to be able to win that on a free-speech brown
Bright like
And Alex is jeopardizing
A lot of
Because if
I don't know. Sends people to attack the other brother
VI the other Council
In the case
Could be seen as somehow intimidation or
Or something
You could really be hurting his case here
I'm sure that Norm didn't think
This was what he was showing up for
Of course I'm now he's on
But he's doing his best to try
Alex listen
We don't have evidence
Alex
Listening
I think he is a very different lawyer
Ben Barnes
Both both probably on the Steelers
Unscrupulous
But based on
Appearances on Alex's show I would hire.
One on one
Come on over here and Barnes
No no no we're not
Send the kemetic another party so he can defend him for that
$1000000
Great idea
Everyone in the Infowars universe
I just think
I take it there's a level of responsibility that Norm is showing
Appreciate that
In the most
Caustic of Moana
Here because I
Take everything away from it
Flipping out here
Left to his own devices could very easily get into territory that
On its own kind of Legally dicey
Right so I think
You know you have a guy who
It's supposed to do it at least
I'm sublevel be there to protect
Actually showing up and being a little bit
Protect ya neck appreciate that
Even if it's protecting someone who I think sucks the different lawsuits and how they
Taking out with differ
Lawyers I would say normal
Actually trying to win
To get publicity for wasp
The publicity of women
Barnes wants the publicity of just being a controversial
Whatever
Norman
Explain to Alex
It's good to be mad
You have to be mad at the right person at the right time
In the right degree
An hour
When I came down here
I didn't know who you were that I knew who you were I could place you in the political landscape I hadn't watched your show
I've made a study of you in the last 3 or 4 months and you've won me over
Because I think you're an honest
And angry America
But sometimes you're not angry at the right things and sometimes
Chalkboard
Pyramid
Find out
$1000000
Message
And you know you feds they're going to know you did it they're going to get your ass you little dirtbag
1 million bench
Rass
Well if your lawnmower
Okay iru you have
Every reason to be too
1 million is on the street
So I mean
This is a one-track mind
He's a child
Yeah but if it's
It's not like
Like normal trying to address the issue
The real situation but Alex
Which leads me to believe that it probably is a real thing
Yeah you're looking for was just Alex talking about it there would be any Thunder.
You don't know what the f*** the reality is
But the fact is talking about it's in touch with
It does lead me to believe that this would be a much
Larger and weirder publicity stunt
If it was boring
Still
I think it must be a real situation
So above it or whatever
All about this
This bounty
Turn this into
Victimhood.
Excitement of the hunt
If there's so many things you could use
Yeah but
Like the mix
Picture of do you not like I can understand
Like the mixture of
Terror and
Yuri
That could come along with
Obviously
Like this
Square your unfairly
Attract
Disgusting
There is a visceral
Nature to it
Acting like this
Yeah 100 million dollars to find the guy
With your lawyer
Is not
Acceptable
It implies some sort of
Foreman
And that's what I sent more than any
Has nothing to do with
That he's covering up anything I think it's just
The way he works is so based on
Trying to catch
Retention
And this is a really good way to
He thinks that he can spin
Really well to do it
That's the entire vibe that I get
That's why I'm not interested in having dorm talk about the actual situation
Wants to derail
It does seem like normal so does
Doesn't know that I like
What
No this is what it was getting
And he hasn't figured it out
Provide
Good
Yeah he doesn't realize that he's a prophet
Anybody else
The dawn on him
Keeps going
Temperature for sleep
Jerk
Cuz your own buddies are going to turn you in and you're going to go to prison
Stop
I can't handle this one
Will be the real American and the real American
Attacks the right target
Billion
Against you
Time b****
Visual
The shake music
It's crazy
He's sitting there in his is space force t-shirt
Like eyes
Giada around me
Yeah
It's a it's a
Making light
Kind of a very serious thing
The trafficking of illegal pornography
If it wasn't using that
Is kind of a prop for his own
Publicity is life
The person who sent it is obviously
The biggest
Problem
When this whole thing
It is absolutely exploitative still up
The situation
And it's just
It would be incredibly,
Absent
Him
Just going
Just go into town while his lawyer is annoyed
Is a comical picture
There's no way you could have done
The first
Are the first however
How many hours of
This show
Pulled it off so
Like it was just a regular episode of a
And then got junk
Floated
If This Were something that
Spell tour or secretly thought
Somebody a nympho
I don't think so at all
It would be something where you take the day
Take the day and beat with
Norwalk Fair
I considered the possibility to
He can't
Like he needs the money flow come again
You take the day off and has like
That slows things down
For sure
As for the
Desales
They've been pretty clear about the idea
Breakfast
Pushes.
So
I do think there's a possibility that
Afford to take a day off
Come into
2 hours early and meet with Norm
Get squared up
And then do your show and don't do that I need to get any kind of guilty conscience
Monster
Maybe
You need the business to keep going but
I would say
Staying out of jail for
That
Glee was worth
Far more than anything your business
If it's one of his employees that destroys a business
Like that
Very hard for him
Recover from that
And that's a good why you wouldn't preemptively do so
Something like that
You don't that this isn't damage control is anyone's guilty
Yeah
It doesn't fly that way
Yourself
Which makes me think it's exactly what he would say
Yep
Yeah the the consequence
Will be unintended and probably
Nothing nothing is good
To take it personal
Alex
Is feeling to act like
He's not extreme enough
Analysis
You will win the lawsuit in Sandy Hook
Is a matter of law it was protected speech and not tip amatory in it
The plan that some as-yet identified person engaged in we have to identify that person
Haitian hard to prove it
U.s. attorney's appointment
Up
I'm sure
This is a conversation on one end
Just a drunk idiot on the other
So when we wrap this up Alex
F****** Norm
Make sure that
He declares war
Do you have to call his banners
Oh it's called feudal Lords underneath
A good crew
If You Want Blood
Blood on the streets man
I am not going to sit here in my life
And have these dirtbags
And he had nowhere to go
It's ridiculous out obviously
So get ready
And I'm just asking the Pentagon in the Patriots that are left
Summon the meme War I summon
I will never sell out to these people
Mom
Norvasc realized why am I here
So
I understand the
The sort of investigative power
I guess
People in like 14 and 18
On the
Legally dicey sorry for you or I to do it
Cuz we don't
Those sorts
The world
I don't even have a
A VP
Could handle that
Like
The group of
People
Calling
Investigation
Wouldn't cover
But you know what those people do do
Detox people
People
Engaged towards attack
I mean I'm going to leave the Patriots in the Pentagon
Acai
The dod head is like we got to get this done
I think what he's doing is only introducing his
Blood on the streets
Desires
Into a world
Full of people that have
Causing innocent blood
Metaphoric
And it's pretty hard to imagine Metallica's
So I'm torn between
I'm torn between
The idea of
The X
Attention
PR stuff
Because I definitely
And then the other side of me is turned towards
Alex's
Lately been really
He has been using a lot of rhetoric that
It gets very close
To what
You might call like a targeted these people should be f******
Taken care of
And so when I hear stuff like this and he's banging on a picture of Chris Maddie and not listening to his lawyer tell him
We don't know that this is the person
Million dollars Blood on the streets tonight
Yeah
I don't
I find it hard not to hear that and think
Well someone word
Galaxy
It's hard not to hear that
I don't
I don't know what his primary motivation is and I'm not sure he does
Even I don't know if he knows what he's doing any
Just straight
Yeah
Attention desires
And booze
Yeah
The stuff
Cuz I was sent
Really seems like
People not us
Is everybody should just stop and call us before you
Something about
Can chicks with big tits
Of this
Freak out
Play
It is very crucial to the end
My position is that I don't believe Alex is guilty
And I think that
Were he to be
This would be
The ballsiest thing
His pattern
Yeah
At the same time information come out the contradicts what I
Suggestion I believe right now
I'm willing to believe it's possible
The situation is contingent on the information
And it's available right now
That could all change
I don't believe I do not appreciate people say
Suggesting
Face off against
Information that is available now
You have your own opinion
I think it's dumb
I think it plays into
Is victimhood narrative
And his ability to
Make
Money also
So I just think it's on
It's Manny
Jumping up
Bright
Which of the
Pleasure
It's kind of like
I think he knows what he's doing
He's trying to go
Get this guy killed
Because he
Yeah yeah
Take your brothers go to
I'm not totally sure
I've been wrong in the past
I hope we don't I hope we don't see how
Doing all this s***
It's easy to be like he's just screaming is
Just blustery.
He's putting this guy whose picture he's shown on
And obviously he's setting me up
Because they got to take me down
You know you could put
This last clip the last 15
You suckin so who's episode
As the outro music is playing
Alex addresses the idea
The people would think
Keep sending people after
Everyone
Will Texas be defeated he will now the shopping
Full-time Norm is just sitting there like
You wouldn't
Say I want legal and lawful action you said I said people
Everybody
What you were asking
For what
Position
Because you know
A bounty that only get paid when they're arrested
Someone killed
I said I wanted them arrested clear about that until after
Convicted as well
He or she
But
That's
Even when he says Ali I want legal and lawful action I'm not sending anybody after a guy want legal and lawful a
Are you giving out a million-dollar pound
Stop this is a serious crime
You getting Central pornography is not something
Just because everyone hates me
T-Rex sound
And the FBI isn't a very capable position
To figure out what is going on there
Take care of it
Find the evidence preserve the evidence
Who did this to you
The only thing
Very sensible
To do in this situation
Is
Allow the process
Hugo
And if they discover that it was Hillary Clinton and Alex gets to become king of America that's the law
Absolutely
And I understand I do understand how someone
Hood
Take that exact same Colonel of what I
I just said the idea that
It why would you do that
They're going to investigate whatever you hoped
Whatever information
You hope to find
He's going to be found by the investigation if it is
Turtle & Hughes
Defy he knows he's guilty
No cuz why else would you interfere with an investigation
Now that's because the pr angle
You trying to Target this guy and go
As compelling as anything else
As an explanation for why you wouldn't just let the FBI do their job
This is not seem like he's
Doing anything
That will
Positively benefit him
It makes me think of the title of the Flash Forward
First episode was called No More good days
CIA main characters daughter
Has everyone Flash
Fast forward 26 months
Future
Sees what's going on
And she describes it as we have no more good days
Yeah that's how I feel.
I see you no more good day
And I see no more good days
For us
Like a present
Into the future
Tell you how much
This feels like a quickening
Severe and I understand that this is a situation that is put in Alex's laptop
I know that it's artificial on some level to what he would like to
But the way he's covering
It is so
Irresponsible so f***** up
I do I agree with you I think it
Get to sign a very bad
Very bad behavior
You see what's going on with either around
Lost his ability
Even be the
Confident
Confident other position guy
He's that he's waffling all over the place
His longtime
Sources of information or split
All that you know
He's gone so far into the Trump World that Joel skousen doesn't even agree with his bulshit anymore cuz.
The purist
And Alex has gone in pure
He's not he's a man without a base
Anymore
He doesn't have the
Like whatever he enjoyed in the
Late
Hey baby early 2010
Whatever he enjoyed back then
Of having a home
He doesn't have a home anymore
He gave up his home to wander in
I don't know. Ed had
For Trump
And he's just lost he's lost
Now he's running out of gas
He's getting mad
That's what's going on
And
I've lost track of this metaphor
I think you need me to let you go with that alright listen up
Needs to find his way home or else he was
Going to starve
Heat gun
There's always
Did you see that you need help you need help
Pizza Inn
Could be a problem
It gets better
His lawyer is like
So close to Illegal close
You can't have those
Ingredients
Together for very long
The crossing the line
Just a matter of time
That's why we have to keep
Well looking at
Present even though it's
It sucks
Disgusting but like
I think there's a d
We are witnessing
The end of times
At least the show
I absolutely if I was anywhere near
Alex be like
We need to stage
The f****** intervention
You drinking himself to jail
Where is a good operation here where we
F****** Silvia's Camp pills we could stay at
Stasis level
But because of his own
Personal
Ego
Defensiveness
Anger issues
Booze
We're going to end up
Broke
And we're going to be
Unemployable
Like no one's going to be able to know it's going to f****** get it
Took a sabbatical
So he's not on camera Irish it might be able to transition but
The cameraman
Maybe trouble
Whatever
It's clear that for some reason people are
Motivated to do that
I don't know why because Alex is such a
They're scared
Or possibly because
It's still much at baby it's way more lucrative than we even under
Understand
That could be it maybe they think
The Jeopardy to weather with this
Situation
I don't know
On a human level
He needs help
No one is
Maybe once
It falls apart
Thomas Jefferson
The seeds of its own destruction
Donated the domain knowledge
Comcast correct he's on Twitter
The other name of it to my boy
Thomas Jefferson's podcast
Actual Apple
Sheraton all sorts
Oh boy
We got a
We got a Cavalcade of
Douchebags
Murderers
Somebody
We got a bus.
Is Meowth
Spore Joel skousen are both good candidates for non murderers
It doesn't sound like normally I would rather honor him with eonon murderer title for his attempt
Having Alex understand the situation
Just for saying young man
Gonzaga
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color