Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work
Exhausted
Almost almost
How you doing
Longest road
Call Manny
Road trips
Central Missouri
We got to get out you got to go
Grown up man
Her parents and my brother we would go to California every summer
Didn't like to fly
Kampala
Do you like not
Pay for hotels
Cuz all my
Extended family was out somewhere in
California for the most part
Yeah so we would go out there and
Each time we would go to try and take a
Route. So we can have different National Park
There's a little bit of
What National Park
That's really cool
Yeah
The gift
We took a road trip
From Missouri
Down to Boulder
Suffern. James desolation Williams
Doing some work
The Avery Brewery
A promise that we could drink a bunch of
Where the long drive
Elsa guitar
That would have been enough
Toiletries
Too much cross country
You know about the idea of California and going all the way in
Road Dogg lineup
Experienced so many other little places you would never be
Otherwise
There's a there's a
Experience
Different
Moods
Good life
Valuable silly roadside attractions
Never
Anytime we're driving on Wall Drug
Yeah hell yeah
I got tricked by that one time at Ceramic don't even bother
Big old steak nuts
I was Furious
But that's all of them
Vicki assholes
I respect the hustle
Respect
Is this Isabella cast of it's a little write a lot about Alex Jones
But I respect
But you make this your papa
Before we get going with
Say thank you
These people signed up
Michelle
First of all
Next
And I'll probably walk
Alex
Flexicrew
I like to believe that scrape Manning from Degrassi
The beautiful thumb
Thank you so much
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
I like to believe that's the beautiful thing
How to find somebody who don't even a little bit of an elevator
Appreciate that very much
Thank you so much you are now
Heroin
Freakishly large
Which could have also been Bridget
But spelled differently
Either way different people we thank you both very much from the bottom of our hearts
You like sports
Also we are incredibly behind
This episode
Trying to race on people's very exciting
I guess we should have come out
Explain partially one of the reasons
A bit of a
Of
Doing an audiobook
Of Mark Richards book
Who is Carrie cast
Project Camelot
Whistleblower he put out a book called Imperial Miranda volume 1
Our buddy Mike
So kind
To go and
Help us
Secured the text twice
It's not possible
That's what we'd intended to start putting out on
Weird
We tried for the second time
To get through it and it is just
Some of the most
How awful
Nonsense
Really really bad
It's really boring
What is it
The room
It is ultimately
Very very very funny
Credibly boring at the same time
Turn on some of the funny stuff
Wings
Is a human or cat being buried
Nope nope
It's on
Worth it's not worth it to find out though
Cuz we got like 45 minutes has Pages through this
It's very log into putting out
80 Hour audiobook of it
No good
Not going to work
Not that kind of torpedo.
Apologies for this episode and the fact that we just can't
It was
Really really horny
Play keyboard Prison from listening to a dude
It is the perfect intersection of mail message
Up and down repeatedly
No good
So today we are back in the prison
Cuz we got a
Experience The Fallout
Accurately
Interpreted his performance growbiz Friday episode from last week we're in
Yelled a bunch about Chris attorney
Opposed
Council
And
Alex very clearly was
Applying for x
Against the guy appropriate
Filed a motion
Alex got some
Against
Yes pay the attorneys fees for the
Airport
Situation
He can only
Bio-Oil
I'm sorry Arabia now
From Iran
More to the point a lot of people has gone away
And I want
Terrapin
Alex did his whole thing on Friday
Immediately The Daily Beast a number of stories about how Alex
Billion dollars
More information about who had
His email a
All good and well
I think that's fairly fine
100000 Cal and took away the stipulation that
Call back
On Monday
The Connecticut Post
I believe is the publication
Paper out of Connecticut or publication out of Connecticut put out a story where the headlight
Lawyer Alex
Text Jones.
Vocaloid
Pornography
Because of the way it was framed in the headline
It made it appear that Alex had maliciously
Send a batch of things in Discovery
Illegal pornography
So
The problem is
Alex only understand
Answer when you
Have the headline like that
It's going to cause trouble
And prepare things
So we're going to go over there at work experience
Experiences the media coverage of
The situation that
Important lesson
Someday we will learn in the middle of this episode
Some funny stuff
I have tried to make this as not painful as possible nearly as bad as Monday
Okay brochure
Hobart
Soundly funny
But before
We have an out-of-context drop
Is Alex Jones
One of the greatest
If anybody
If anybody have any questions about Alex Jones is loyalties to Russia
We have just thought that
Wait what
That's not fair at all but
The fall of the Soviet Union may or may not
Yeah by understanding the public character is that he wrote
Heights
Through 90
Wednesday of this past
And Alex
Start off by talking about
Tony Rizzo
Jessica
That's pretty short Forest clip
Quick
Short
To sort of set-up he talks about the stacks quite a bit
About the house
Videos covering
Situation
Sailfin
I will find out
Finger at himself
By the FBI
Victim
Someone sitting
Piece of crap
Infected with malware was c*********
Alex Jones
All the articles that talked about malware we're literally quoting Norm pad
Alex's lawyer said it was malware
It was clumsy phrasing on that part
Alex is playing the character thing
Sslikeyesss
Reporting on what your lawyer said defending you and child custody
Shut up with your lawyer.
Completely
Characterized
Really trying to
Get
Fingers around
This trend is going to go through
Rufus episode
Very consist
But his main story
270 is not his own
It is not
Ron
Which I don't
Think he cares all that much about anymore
It's not Ebola forgotten about the Ebola on the southern border
Not really care anymore
0 because you have to move on
Facebook
As mentioned
Is the mark of the beast
And Alex
Facebook or shell
Yes biblical prophecy is
Again
Facebook currency
Attract
One ring
Two Worlds
Nice
One small stacking
He doesn't get to those 27
Believe that
Chipmunk surfboards that is nuts
I read that Libras like
Call for fucksake see you assholes
Yeah it's one of those things where it's like hey this is stupid
Terrible but I think
Some common ground on this one being against
A cryptocurrency
Facebook named Mark Zuckerberg could go bad pretty easily
So good enjoy
Still think you're going to do this poorly but despite that Noble fight
I think we should all team up
Yeah
Another trend
Is it goes throughout
These here episodes
What are described as a moreover gesturing towards
I know that we have no bones about the fact that Alex
Comes from a white supremacist white nationalist
In place
He says
Episode
AR
Profoundly
Disgusting
Talking to the guy who runs Europe Wars
Which is the offshoot that you're up of
Infowars
Delicious
Lemon lime
Alignment
Today lyman's on guess I'm thoughts
About Africa
Can immigrants
I wouldn't say this is a win
Soca
Especially with with a lot of the African migrants
A dominance of of the western
So I mean
Wow
Something like that. Just think like
You're showing your own cards there
Alphalete
Crazy everywhere
Black women is insanely High
Sort of language is the way you described
Yeah it's not
They come here and they breed
You're a rapist
I would say so
Play this about
Cam
Google Express
Emigrate
Fireworks
Good sarcasm
I took Alex this long to
Figure out that there are social media Networks
Gabon the show before and they've talked about how he's on
But like the G word a lot of these other folks have ended up like
Over there
I think it's interesting
Just trying to
Spread
Temporal
I think he's going to pay
Yeah I think the events of the last
Never really
Driven home
To him
Sound devices
He is dead in the water
Google child pronography
Is
What is a horrible crime
He is the victim
Whatever you're fine
Because Alex has such a reaction
Enraged
Spilled monster getting on Aaron started
Screaming about this guy
You created the world
His own devices that
He will behave
Right he's going to completely destroy
What do you got so in order to compensate for that
He knows he needs more right
Plug my Telegram
On the show
Integrate show
It says there's not a whole lot there
Summer videos
Stewardess settings
Received
Can feelings of these desires to
New social media
Video spaces
Dwight's
Supremacy
Trends are important
Cuz they build
Is it probably I got to stop using MedExpress
Left to his own devices
All on its own
I don't think the 17
It's fine for the beginning of this episode
Great about
Is it Alex
Calls prank calls
Arizona
Alex
Or I get to my point
We're overdue for a American
Canelo
I want to call you out as a caller
You are a coward
Not to allow this one
Listener
The come on
And express his opinion
About
The rapture
He deserves to come on the show
Bad guy just call in a bit
He always wants to argue Priam post-trib rapture
That's
I don't know why Alex let him talk so loud
Something pretty Charming
Great great about calling intuition like you're a coward cuz you won't talk to
I'm on the show right now
Unfortunately
It's not also
Because towards the end of this episode you're on the 7th
Alex said something
But his
Violent
This is this is
The scale of like
They shouldn't say
Muscat
Kayak accidents
So basically
The only one of them come back
I mean
No bones about it literally calling for it
Sophia's political
He was specifically talking about is John Bolton
And as much as I hate John
I still don't think
Be able you shouldn't behave like that on a national radio show
Irresponsible
Sure
That seems like a board legal way to go about that
When is real f*****-up headspace
But on Monday
The blowback from his Friday
Feels like all right I did that
Crazy nonsense on Friday
And then I got back with norm and I walked it back to 100,000 I made the
Deal legal overall good
You seen that too
Connecticut Post article on Monday even though it came out on Monday
Or something like that
Yeah yeah
After it got released
Call around social media
That would slow down
Telegram
Probably not
Clearly has
Heard about it
Wow
Where he goes isn't good
Yeah I do think
Starting from
Kind of a fair position
Ladies and gentlemen it's Tuesday June 18th 2019
Europe
DeGraw
Fake news finale obviously
C*********
Hundreds of articles
Both the local papers here in Central Texas
Alex Jones
Shin c*********
Total
Lie
Reported that we were the victims of someone sending
Coded c*********
Email
That had nothing
So the part that is fair here is again this headlines
Assertive
Turtle weed even
Call it insinuation
All the time
This is Hulk
Right it's not it's hard
It's hard to be like but at the same time as
External Observer
Overly
Be fair about this
It is
Do you know that is what the lawyer
Technically in Discovery
He sent those emails over
So it's
It's true and it's false
I would never written that headline
Because it allows Alex
To do that yeah I would never have allowed that headline too if I was I would never have been like
Call it's a
It's kind of a really interesting
Rico's by writing I had probably got way more
Visibility on your on your publication probably got way more traffic
More restrained headline
Way more traffic and
Right where the struggle comes in
Okay I don't I can't pretend
Understand exactly what
The Connecticut Post
Motivation
Ensworth weather in whatever
Rephrase this
In interest of some
Sensationalism
Salacious
Element
Similarly to
It doesn't matter that it's being used against Alex or by Alex
I'm very conflicted about it
The list of things that I
Like
Allocating a lot of energy I think it's more frustrating from
Restroom like a personal
Standpoint of life
God dammit guys we have done everything possible to do
Even though we spent
I want to try to listen to our show
Second bother you
The primary resource
Come on you got to ask
I'm conflicted on the one hand of like understanding what you doing
The other part of my brain that's just like
Stop
Sprite
Lakers
And if
Not play into
I guess what I'm saying is I could do it
If I were running
I could have navigated this minefield
But I'm also glad that I'm not enough
We talked about it after we tried and failed to record that
Audiobook
You can't
Play his
Because he's been playing it for
For twenty years and you're just now
He's got you but you know if you're going to come hackleme
From a crowd you're fighting
Not against me you're fighting against
Every Heckler that I've dealt with over
10 years or whatever likes their strength
If you have an off-day
But it's locked
It's not a good strategy
Sensationalism
Is generally going
Going to be a losing proposition
For you and it's the nature of
Mixing it up with a profit
You don't want to do it
That being said
Alex is in real trouble
Because
What did
Is
Very much
Close to
Threatening
Is opposing counsel
I would say it was that
Question
Right
We'll try and I know he will cuz later clip you'll try to wiggle around
And baby you can get off on a technicality in Earnest and in reality was threatened
Chris Matic
That is what he was doing
Whether or not that will end up bison record against
Whether or not it will come
Up in his
Legal troubles
Things much harder for him
Because
What you guess he's appealing but
Series9
Because of the sex
He has to pay more he has to pay attorney
Not for the entire case but for abortion
So that is an additional expense
You can't
Emotions
To dismiss the case was thrown out
Telecare archons
Consequences
And I think Alex realizes
I got myself in that trouble
Whether he's able
To vocalize
Help people understand
This is my fault
Freak out on air
Screamed about this guy for no reason
And it all
I just hear him being I'm in trouble and I have to do whatever I can to make sure I don't do the
I don't want to let the enemy know there's a war when you
Bora Bora
You're losing you got to call for reinforcements
Got to call Pharrell
Consciously
Shuttered comes out
Call the crew
Default position
So he's had to tell his staff
Turn off
That's all
I cannot control myself I am going to
To sync my own ship
That is exactly what I need help from the button
Is if you are doing your job and you have
To order other people to
Stop
You need help
Bright
You know in the middle of this episode Alex gets
The text from Norm
Who is in Connecticut
Court and it's regarding this motion because of his Friday
Episode I guess what after he gets that text
Broadcast you are
Space f*****
Text yeah I mean it's it's it's weird to have him say like whatever
Automatically go to rebroadcast and then like an hour and a half later today
I heard
Before
Oh no
Needed to deal with it.
Whatever
Earlier on in the episode even on the Monday
Because I speculated on the last episode
Him having this
Bulshit attack on him
Should have made him overjoyed
Cuz this is something where he can really sink
Bluetooth.
His anger took him to a place that is legally ask
Whereas before
Smooth sailing you could have created a fun Contest out of this I've gotten a lot of publicity out of playing the victim
Maybe was overdoing it a little but
Whatever
Yeah I agree I agree I think
His feelings of transformed great right
Over the weekend
Into now like
This is like
Who knows how much like the Borg
That is a
Just could have been so good
Unforced error
Coming into play
Like I said like I don't know how much the legal fees could have been
Substantial amount
Quite frankly I have no idea
What an ass
Yeah
I wonder if
Cuz Norma said on Friday's episode 100000 dollars to go over there
For this portion of the investigation seems like that.
From Norwood
Number
Really
Really Fox
Alex's talking more about this headline
From
Repost
I think he has a
The Cradle of
Being right
And then a whole pound of Beacon Rock
Here's one of the former Federal prosecutor
Democratic
Of course
Material
BFDI
Horses were getting ready for the
Somebody planted it
But not physically
I have no record
Anybody record
Calling for all sorts of charges against
Okay
It's all a lie
And I
So I think that this
Trying to repackage
Do the threat is probably a
Exasperation
Because
If anybody heard what he did on Friday
And just had a normal human understanding of line
He was heavily apply again
That Chris Maddie and
Opposing counsel for the people who are suing him
Sandy Hook
Were the people who play
Like that is not
Up for grabs
Norm pattis his lawyer was on the show
He even with
Alex you're showing Chris
Voyeurism
Picture on the wall of on top of a shooting
Heatedly in been like this
Like when
Show because it is own behavior and because
How Norm responded to him
Exactly what people's accusations are
Alex away from
Going too far with it
Like maybe he got it out of
The territory where it be like
You work tonight
Or whatever but
It's really hard for Alex
Guys with a straight face
Sit here and say
Physically
Bright
So it would not matter what even if he is now trying to make the argument that I wasn't
My email
I still think that there's a
Jobs
$100,000 in legal fees just for that
Then they wanted to meditate
Dover
What was your nose
And then somebody up hardship we can't have this
So you even playing now there's even like a more Broad
Conspiracy about this Gazette
The event
Anybody believe there was a setup
Yeah
People reported on it well and then the globalists are like
Reebok
Crush
I think this is
Insane
Waiting
But every episode
Auto guess what
We get another movie reference there because I guarantee about the maitre
When you talk about metadata all that weird little stuff that you can't read
Yeah cuz I wouldn't describe metadata
Squiggly stuff
You might be right
Broad
The argument
Set up
Yeah
One of the things
Uses
Is to argue that is the idea
The court told him he should be aware of what
He's turning over
Silver for Discovery it's generally
Emprise by Discovery in court
There's a spreadsheet where I have all of my Sandy Hook
Money
Should have known about that ahead of time
The people telling him he should have been aware of that
That they wanted him to open the email
So he would have
P***
Never
Lawyers specifically
Email
I told them all
What's a good God I should Norm
That we don't know about
Parallel Construction
You watch
Winning all of these cases
Add so in order to
Derail the case
Real 100%
Parallel
Construction using fun words
He's so all over the place in terms of like I'm saying I'm saying
I'm not hold on
I kind of am saying that
Turning read any of the ship that I gave to them
See how smart I am for not reading any of the s*** I gave
That's not bad
If I had hired a real lawyer
Nothing stupid for hiring Barnes now
This next clip reinforces my argument that I think Alex is in a really terrible place
We had that clip earlier were you saying that we're in real trouble we need to
Get the the armies coming around
Next clip Alex predict
Trophy
That's a tough out to break
Can you can tell the audio guy was here real soon
Yeah
I mean what would you
What would you do my bosses screaming on air
Book remember me find
Carte blanche
Rebroadcast Alex
Who has the true power now
What I've described as a
Ironic
On the show
Constitutional lawyer
A successful free-speech lawyer represents
Also very confident top lawyers representing mean
Weather Friday
True
It's all for the theater
He's going to have to be brought back to Connecticut
Connecticut to give a deposition on
Understand the last I read he has a deposition
Somebody has to give
On July 5th
So go to Connecticut for that
I believe
The trial itself
The trial is always off
I might be misremembering appetite
I swear I read something
About them setting a date and it's like
November 2020
I might be completely off
Course
Ridiculous spectacle
People who are running this trial org
I don't know if you
You can
Put everyone in isolation
But you need to
Really does seem like this this case should be held in like a on a different Island somewhere
No media no nothing record all of it Siri is 12 Birds
Like there's no human being
Should be involved
Record all of it but don't tell anyone about what happened to tell us over
There's no shenanigans
No one should be able to interfere
I'm here on that June
June 7th 18th
Alex comes in
For break with some
Terrifying noises
CityPlace very often
Never place
25 years
Barking dogs
Panera
He plays are Ritz IRA
So that's
That's good presentation
He talks about
Connecticut
I'm a
You know arguably misleading headline
What's interesting about this one of the criticisms we have about Alex the show
Is Vicki engages with news
Media on
Headlines
He doesn't read
Only knows maybe a sentence
Whatever it is is a fact
Projector
Everybody else
Which I think is a rationalization
Infer why he does what he does
Makes it sound like
There's just so much happening and then meanwhile
The Wall Street Journal
Alex Jones
That's all
It says
VI says the emails were sent to Jones
But
They do it at the bottom knowing full well
Organized fraud
Almost
Both people
25%
Erratic
Article
No faith in your audience
If that's the position
I am I mean like if the article is
Fair
It's actually reporting
Then
I don't
I don't know
I have I have little patience
But it's what Alex is at Iraq
I do find one thing that he said.
Which is
Articles
And the way that their heads
And operate
That does
Because if you're for sure
Alex Jones
And you're talking about it from The New York Times or the post
That is b******* I did not
Consider that whatsoever
Play I can't imagine someone
Seeing that headline not being able to read the article and not hunting down another article they could read
With the same primary reporting
A surprising number of people
Right it's that whole thing
The second step
Most people don't take
Possibly but I also think
Maybe a hundred articles I've never read because they're on the Washington Post
I still know what they say cuz I found
Another article the person
Who's receiving the information it's unfortunate
New York Times and Washington Post business model
Understand what
I don't know if they were the only f****** news outlets that this would be a good Ark
Of course but I don't think it is
I'm just saying that I had not considered that as a side effect
You just scroll through headlines
I agree I agree on that
Name articles
Because there is too much of the
Scroll through effects or whatever you know you see the headline you internalize whatever it says that fact
To getting
Astoria
Guilty of that
I tried to be more aware that now but like yeah absolutely
Susceptible
Just like
Where they share an article after only a couple of paragraphs
Sure
It happens
So in the next
Insult
Flying around about this
Erroneously
Serious publication
It already reported days before
Spell situation
And big influential social media
Unnoticed
For the New York Times
Currently only respected publication
Some local publication to print some headline
Weigel's Halfway Around the World
Whatever
Bums me out that bothers me is that like
Most of the information
Is the sea
Of those stories that came out on Friday
From The Daily Beast
Easton other Publications
Reporting on Alex
And the ones that were recording
On Monday
Just with a different headline
The 8th of the same information
I'm just from a slightly different angle
Alex is I'm the victim of a conspiracy or someone set the illegal pornography it was discovered by
These lawyers in the Epic
Then on Monday
Velour
Discovery
Information that got sent over Alex
Illegal pornography we went over it and there's no indication that he met or anything
Like that
The same information
Is presented slightly different
It's it's
It's annoying
Down one level and then I understand that it's also probably annoying as our show
But it's just
Constantly
Him and Barnes
And Alex
Send Alex repeating that over and over again
But it did that intention
Because I think it isn't
To know
This is what being driven into his body
But it's not as important
The point behind it
Is that out loud
In this next
Everybody's not having to ask a question
Complete fabrication by the most powerfulest
So
Did on ironic
Goodwork Barn
This is what it's all about it's the idea of creating
Plausible
Reasonable Doubt
Or something like that
The idea of
This headline was Miss
Information
It's all fake
How much do you really know about Alex everything probably alive right now
Right now this is the joy that should have
Come on Friday
This is what this is what he would have
F****** dined out on because
What'd
I'm here just trying to lay low for a few days and then I'll bring it back and I'll slam it
I have no Epic
I mean is why you pay Barnes
And it's so manipulative awesome
In terms of
Elation is about deep down
Creating the idea about Alex Jones
Headline
Sticky Lips
She doesn't actually
I don't know I'm trying to come up with absurd examples of like
Blow your mind facts about Alex
It's very
Yeah
A lot of My Cousin Vinny
I just like
I don't think this is going to help
At all
But it's very
Good for retain
The author business
Squaw Valley
Makes an announcement
About another sort of social me
Media things
Reviews on
This led me down a rabbit hole
Cubs.com
Forward slash
Alex Jones.
Subscribestar
Please go there
$15,000 or $20,000
But you're something else
Real money
When you subscribe
You don't need a hotel room
Silly
Successive
Yeah
So this is this is another piece
Another one
Subscribestar
What is
Episode
Recently talking about being a really bad financial
On all three of these episodes
He's doing so many goddamn commercial
Ads are flying around like
Nuts
And he's even started a save Infowars emergency sale where everything is
Everything is free shipping
Aunt double Patriot points
No way wow listen
This is not good
The cash that's not good
Perhaps even worse than all that is this news that he's decided to join a crowdfunding web
That's for people like us
Who don't pretend
4 second
To be successful
And who advertisers have no interest in
It's not for the alleged
King of ratings
The biggest thing in the world like Alex Jones presents
Subscribestar is a patreon for people who are too big of assholes to be on paper
You might find people like Sargon of akkad there that that variety of folk
I'm sure there are some other people who use the site who are
Crazy racist
Buckhead lunatic
But until its most prominent
People's consciousness
Because it's become the home
For people who've been kicked off other crowdfunding websites because they're too big
Witches says all you need to know about
I don't know I actually don't know that I wouldn't be surprised but I don't know enough about it
I would imagine
At least
I understand why people like Sargon would try to rebuild their crowdfunding on a new platform
Because it all he's got
He's someone who's in desperate need of a way to monetize it
And if this is the place that happened
Alex Jones is a million-dollar Studio
He's presumably operation
It's very Unbecoming for him
The crowdfunding website to run his s***
Go go to make a movie
Doesn't feel like
The proper use of
I decided to check in on Alex's subscribestar account
If things don't look great for him over there
Has been active since at least May 15th
As of this Thursday
He is only 129 people
Subscribing to him
Open shared on social media
12 time
This is almost non-existent engaged
Consider how large
Pretences audio
He claims he has millions upon millions of listeners
Right now Alex is all over the cultural zeitgeist
Very very aware that he's in the middle of a legal battle
Video sing without it
Will support his days are numbered
People out of them 129
Have answered the call to action
They're probably already
Auto-ship
You don't know
It's true Garrison has a
Subscribestar
Downers
Owen Shroyer has 50
T3 Jordan Peterson has 65
Mark Dice is coming into the hot 36
Stefan molyneux has 20
Laura lubbers got 29 people on board
S*** subscribestar itself has a subscribestar account
Subscribers
Tehran
They will all work for subscribestar
Perhaps
Given those numbers you might be inclined to say what that website clearly has 130 people on it
Do you know the ones on there
Got 53 people but if that's out of 100
A huge percentage
Cuz there's some people who are doing pretty well on there
Paul Joseph Watson has 1992 subscribers
And Sargon has something around
3000 interesting about that is that there exists
Proves that success is
Possible on that platform and there are more people then are subscribing
Suit
Interesting
Doesn't have a monopoly
Because of their success
They disapprove
The very idea
Of their assumed
They proved that none of these other people who are listed are in anyway
The victims of some sort of a
Tech Monopoly or anything
Like that if they had active engaged
Who's like Sargon
And Paul Joseph Watson
They would probably be able to rise
And they just don't
Yeah that's
Not surprising
It's interesting
The victim
Fellow Travelers
Of Sargon and Paul Joseph Watson
Is he
By their own success
They have really demonstrated
All those arguments are silly
On the other hand
Such a huge
Because
It's really Ali has
So he has to pimp that out quite a bit more where is Alex I noticed
Until
Reasons for pushing.
Right
Heavily
Yeah I were talking
Even now they're still
Least two days later from one that episode aired
I come from a land of
Expecting nothing
You do a comedy show
People show up to a bar if you have millions
Digital 100
Very different
Then 129 people in a bar
People show up
That's great
It's real it's real interesting
To me this this order thing
It leads me to have some
Pretty serious suspicion
It's about the size of
We could be
I'm punching down territory
I don't know it's
It's one of those things
You would expect
Be very different if the reality
I don't know what to do
That looks more concert
6 Clues
But in the snow
Text Cliff Alex
Drive home
The point that Norm
Barn
The Barnes has made about this
Calling into question everything
You think you know you have no idea
Dakota MTV
Is totally false
Is there someone who is the victim
It was completely
Is it raise questions because
Various members of the dissident president pointing out his this is exactly what
Illicit activity being covered up by those
Institutional power
But often do more harm than good
Institutional members of the brat
So I apologize I thought that
Express
But that's why this distinction is really important at the headline is technically correct
Post has lied about Alex
Fair
It's all about the U
Responding to what is it
People's minds
As opposed to what the Connecticut Post actually
That distinction is very important
Yeah I have a newfound respect for
I just
Exactly like a
Evil lawyer
Like he is he is
Hamming up his part
I thought it was just kind of
Bloviating
I know that there are multiple facets
Hours of him
The first time today
Yeah cuz this is mrs. the ANS far as pain goes this is pretty good I do still think it's
To claim victory from the jaws of defeat
Alright
Dave
Beta
Misleading
Potentially misleading headlight about you
How do we
Spins
Into
Everything you've ever said is actually accurate
Little thread
Tapestry of b*******
It's a big swing
So
Text Clint we get off all this stuff Barnes leaves
Alex is going to come back with a coup de gras
Photograph
Recovering the news
Okay
Not too long ago and he said that
Michelle Obama's going to come out of nowhere be the Democratic
Alex is still focused on Joe Biden
Pool
I enjoy Joe
Had a
Little little little
Recently
This is one you can hear
That's Amore
There's nothing you can do
Start a real physical Revolution to do talking about it
Narcissist
Cut off real quick real quick
So
First of all I have zero interest in defending to buy
It's going on and on about the media dishonestly characterizing the situation
Immediately preceding to dishonestly characterized by standing
Send the problem
Edit clip and took it out of I think someone else
He just was like
Fair enough specifically let's start a real physical Revolution as an example of something
It's going to do that was a bad idea
Who's the contact with him
Explaining that there's a whole lot of negotiating that could be done with a GOP
What we do
Specifically while doing the quote within our system cutouts
Let's start
Real physical Revolution is almost
Insult coming out of Biden
That is exactly what he might as well
That's exactly what I read that headline
Yeah he's doing one of the
Strong defense
Compromising
GOP
This is covered by someone like Alex Jones
As if you were triggering a literal communist violent
Yeah
This is the perfect
They will go on for an
Our about how they're the victim of the
The media then without missing a Beat
Just targeting the person that there are
Indigo actor
It's hypocrisy on wardline will put more accurately its profound level of psychological abuse
To subject anyone who trusts
Two completely separate realities are created just by edit exact clip
People who see Biden's.
To see a guy who forbetterorworse
Probably worse isn't dorson copper
Working within the system
The people who see the right-wing
Reverse like the one Alex
Display
Will think the lamest of all candidates of the democratic field
Is an out-and-out radical just waiting to let loose his shocked
This
Separation of folk
Is all Alex's ever really itchy
His life
All the more ironic
Coming from comments of
We need to reach across the aisle and work with these
Across the island work with the guy who literally just cut you saying
That
Incorrect statement
Right
You're not going to reach across the aisle by there's an even more interesting Dynamic to it
Calling for a violent revolution
Sushi mischaracterizing the actual like
Everyone
Every one of his basement characters
Further mischaracterize by Alex
Apply the jokes
Is the violent communist uprising
Yeah it's not it's just the same s*** from the Obama
Matter
How hard
Compromise
It doesn't matter
They are going to call you a violent evil social
The road must
Twisted for some reason
Unpleasant
It's it really only like
Just f****** lean into it man
Say what you think is the right thing to do and don't give up
What they're going to call it
Yeah cuz they're just going to call it something
So b a violent revolution
So now when did
Revolution.com
I mean you got to be worried about the
I think you should
You don't need to
Because the globalist who found a way to paralyze
People fighting Lucian
Because they tried to make it along racial lines so that minorities were the majority of us.
Don't feel like
They could be part of Americana
It's just a
Shut down so very very very very quiet everybody
Everybody
About all of this
We're going into the season of War
And
Fraud
Monster Gear
Broadcast exactly what you wanted that's not crazy if that's
Start a revolution Reddit
What he just did right there should be like blaming the globalist
Characterizing all of this
That's why the minorities don't get it right
Being a
Perfect transaction that is perpetrated on a daily basis
You have an interesting perspective
It's disgusting
That is so
Sort of white
Going to get way worse
Riverside School
Pretend he's going to
Connecticut Post
Which is
Idle threats but Alex makes about lawcraft
Dishwasher
Eh
They're the ones
But pulled out
Information statement
Another judge whether she's
Goes with it as if it came out of the mouth of God
That's not a good idea to insult the judge
Million dollars for the head of this lawyer
The child born
We don't know who it is
That I'm mad at them
Because
The discovery process
Calling
Manipulate
Nigeria
Jen says apology from here
Falls chart
Oh I'm sorry
The family
The lawyer sent that very suspicious
The figure of speech okay
Anybody who got the message the idea that
The families
Misreading of
About that appearance
Because that would be a profoundly f***** up
So if people were accusing them
Above that
The paper was actually saying
I would
Responding very poorly today
Yeah yeah
More information about that idea
Threaten this lawyer
Chris Madden
I think this would be tough
To argue
Not on the radio
The Connecticut
Post
I was talking about this
Yes face with all the table give me a break
Give me a break here that again for Friday's show
Just to show how much is a f****** b*******
The point is somebody directed child pronography into your email account
Hoping that you would open it so that when you opened it there would be direct
Evidence that you would viewed knowingly and his board
Out of hundreds of thousands of emails they got
And I know right where to go what a nice group of Democrats how surprising
What nice people Chris married
Chris Maddie zoom in on
Careers Maddie
What a good boy
You think you'll put on me
Happened to be on the
Free poster that anyone would say
Target
He literally stopped himself from saying I'm going to kill it
Aii wouldn't
I Wouldn't Die on that hill but it does sound more like a probably
This is
The idea that the article just happened to be on camera
I also you are going to Alex
This to me is indicative of how serious you realized
This is this is
Like he really needs
To try and dance
I was implying that the opposing counsel should be
Killed for a million-dollar
I need that
Because otherwise
Unfortunately
Really really
Is bleak
What happened on Friday
On his Friday show
And in this new retelling
He was behind it it was the global life
DJ support our reporters
Mix everything together
Persecuted
You know like like I knew what was going off on email somebody sent me on Spotify.
And because of the
Come out
They're trying to get me charged
About Sandy Hook
Never opened
Scared
Add look at the hundred-thousand-dollar reward
What is approved for the temperature
Dollars extra
So I mean
Like if that
But they never
Listen to that I think
Here's what I figure Rises what's going on
Right now through that
He has had it
Clearly
Explain to him the consequences
For what
But he cannot
Comprehend
What he did to me on Friday
He's had it explained it clearly comprehend
What he did that was wrong
He has to like
This isn't him spinning I don't think I think
That they are
Doing that they planted the
The child Corner whatever
And that's what they're doing with everything else
He still thinks
The people who are trying
Because he thinks that
Running the law firm that suing him
I think he has to
I just don't know if
I don't know what he believes is going on it and one of the difficulties is like
These nuts
Yeah I mean how delusional is
That's a difficult line to figure out exactly
Tuna steak
Spend
Don't know
But if you just go based on the things
He believes
Yeah Hillary Clinton
And the globalist are behind the law firms that are suing
So even if you shifted from I don't believe it's these lawyers butts part of the
Still the people who are suing
Spirit victimization
Fabfitfun that even if he is apologizing
Or trying to deflect blame back to the globalist
He's already called them global
Escape
No just rephrase
There's one party that does get the blame and maybe accurately so and that is
You cut them French
Well you can call on our Monday episode going over his Friday episode
These French people are there
I just thought it was the weirdest non-sequitur Friday's episode.
If you'd let a fridge grew in there that he regretted
How do you
Talked a little bit more about that okay
He was too much French vanilla French people
Play Slayer
They said they were coming here
Projo
What's the volcano goes off
You need help
Really real
Field merchandise
Psychiatric
Or
Yoga
Fix Scott Hall up
You can help Alex
Does miracle
Oh my god let's start this
Be crazy if that
Like really turned him around
That's a big baby.
I know that we have
The wrestling fan but I don't know what time
Does
Got a request
How about
Because it's already pretty earlier
He talks very fatalistically a lot of
The time
Is where I really feel like this is this feels like a real can
Listeners
Oh boy
Amethyst is dark dark days
I can't really feel again but
So I think
In line with your ideas like
He does understand the severity of the situation
But he can't
Yeah you can't show us to admit responsibility
There is a Feeling
Might be about it
About it
Like far off from the actual trial
And he's freaking out like this
About something that he is
About
Like the ideas
Emails being sent to him
What the f*** is he going to do on the stand
What the f*** is
You going to do as the trial date gets
Closer
Now
He's going to
Intensify
Like
I think on some level what year there I have to prepare for not being on the air is
I got to take myself out of the game
Pretty much
I don't know I feel I feel the broadcast
Trust himself on the air
That means there have to be people who are like
Hey
Maybe you shouldn't be on the air
Maybe those people
Rightly pointed the finger at 4 not
Notes topic am I finally been like
We got it
Galaxy
Maybe I don't know
Interesting
That'll be trans
Now
Connecticut
Post article with the misleading headline
Was bad
Productive
It what they didn't do anything wrong
Necessarily but it's that kind of coverage of Alex
That I think is awful
Unfortunate
Later in the day on June 8th
Alex
Exactly what he
And that is someone does
Write a false
No
Experience
Wash
What is a gentleman the top
Story
Is father of Sandy Hook victims lawsuit against Alex Jones
Call nobody.
What is the gentleman that is
Totally insane
No one's won a lawsuit
They got the name wrong
So what's happening here
Can talk about this a little bit more he's arguing put out that article about him
That was written by James Fetzer
And I'm not entirely sure that might have been more family
Against
The writers of that book
The Associated Press article is about that
Is about that case
Right
Now
MarketWatch
Reposted the article
Message
The headline was Rewritten
And then inviso headline
It says ouch
Conspiracy theorist and wrote the book
Completely
F***** up
Totally wrong yet the body
Adjust
Rewrote the headline
Did the worst job possible
And I don't know how this is possible
But
Thursday morning
I checked
That article is still up on MarketWatch
And I think there's a reason why
We'll get to that here in a little bit
But
The globalist
Wrote this story
As a magical
Okay it's lesser Magic
Who's there
Weird Harry Potter magic is only a call
Level get Barnes on owassa taking over right now
Or the judges try to figure out how to put me in jail
Get me Robert Barr
Just on
I can get double billed
City auditor
Over at MarketWatch
MarketWatch
Dubious
Stuff over there by Alex Jones
Various topics
Seat covers
Barely
Regularly
So
I don't know
I think it's just a huge backup on whoever is that a MarketWatch yeah
Unacceptable
Boneheads
You just gave Alex exactly what you need
If I were Alex I would say that they were working with Alex how do you justify you
Victimhood
Get one example of hundreds of Articles have the same headlight
Not just that
I'm guessing that is not
Shooting at Thiessen
Behcet's
MarketWatch
Okay because they
They don't they don't follow the right
Before we get to that we one more clip from the 18th
It's just Alex
And they say oh my God
Will teach you Texans
Big mouth
Good
Is gray Raiders
Manly people
Who wrote a book as an insult
It's just MarketWatch man
I mean it's not that I wouldn't put up with that either but like it's not everybody
The f****** shity headline on MarketWatch
The reasons I wanted play that clip was
I think people could vary
The audience
Or someone in the audience
But we take every time you
Freaks out he's drunk
That was so
Yeah I just want to be clear that there is a very
There's a distinction between like it's drunk
Just has a little freaked out does a little voice
Yeah very different
So intimately familiar with somebody's quirks
Despite having never met
Audio is such a
Medium you can
You really get the sense for people's rhythms
The pattern
I think it's
Alex
He's no different
No I think it's a common
Experience
You think you already know
Yep
So
19th
Evening of 18
Trump had his rally
Orlando
Oh my God
He was
So true
I can't wait for him to defeat Hillary in 2016
It's going to be amazing
You know he had his rally
Just a bunch of clips
Rally
Start stalking
About her Trump
Throwback
Three now
From a very conservative family
Old-fashioned is father and mother
Nothing
It's good to have
Because
What's a corrupt
System cancer from within
Sophie
Part to square that
Trump's dad
Ideas
Eugenics
Lot of those other elements
He's a real throwback to Herbert Hoover
Weasel
Prices Express throwback
To like the good part of America
Does
And the throwbacks
To the good part of America is
The part where Trump said that the Central Park five
Should BX
I think that's what I'm pretty sure
So awesome. There's a lot of talk about whether or not
Camp
Where people are
Weather there
Concentration
I have no
I hate everyone
I think Alex is probably be worse than go on it
NBC and CNN
That
It's a giant concentration camp
Another line
Father the devil
Concentration camp
We got it
Definition
People are trying to emigrate here are go whatever happens so that is exactly
I think I prefer that argument to split hairs over
When you start to look at it a little bit more falls apart
Because I mean like let's start killing
People
While they want to make
Yeah it's stupid stupid
German away that I prefer
Sure I made it still just jumped
Defying
Atrocious
Because
The closest thing to Alex
Expressing
The white supremacy peeing mask
Des
I think
You could make a pretty strong argument that this is even though Alex
This is about Christianity versus Islam
At the same time whatever it is
If
My team is superior
Themselves
If we were doing it to
Thousand years before
Christianity change that
And then due process rule of law changed all that
Fourth hour today I'm going to be hosting
I'm going to get into
The rule of law
Is committing suicide and maybe too far gone but can we can still have
Pockets of the West
Ultra
But if you don't show up
You will be destroyed
Bye
The system that are inferior
Systems that are superior or be destroyed
So f***** up
Also did you just
Always
Jordan
That's white nationalist the s*** he's calling people Savages
Christian
Robin
Is really like to just make up their own head
Lovett they are big fan
Did I really find the most troubling
Is actually the part where he says it's not about
Says
You have to recognize that
Superior systems celebrate
You can hang
But if you don't recognize
That are westerns
System
Is this
Winn-Dixie
Lacquer
Yep you got to understand that there's a hierarchy Dan and they truly believed
It's the that's that's a troubling thing
Here Express
So
Open
Yeah
That's
For him
For him to go.
Prius versus Rollins slurs around like
We got too much to cover
So he gets back to this story here than
So what about
Setzer
So you talk about
Real good
The front story
And
Call nobody.
He's at gentleman
What deception
This is a whole globalist
What is the only thing you can prove you know like you got to make this look so important
Like this is actually true
It's really disappointing
All in all
But
Is implying that there's a
Conspiracy around pushing this one article that has a badass
I don't know that
That certainly was the headline I saw popping up
Love the most
And also like
Reply is
They all of the
These things like the top of
Twitter trends
All controlled by the
Force this MarketWatch headlines
And do you know
It rhymes with
He thinks he's doing it
Possibly
Jesus
Troyer
Shows up to make
Spoiler alert
Subscribestar
Owen Shroyer
P.m. everyday
Is here with us riding shotgun
Clear
Let me be clear
It's been he's on subscribed
Okay
Diversification
Have many legs to a stool
Is critical
Nearest shutdown Infowars
Huge hoax stories that I lost lawsuits
YouTube stories
Adoption in c********* two people just really dangerous.
Supporters
It wouldn't be this Reckless for the things they're currently doing if they weren't about to pull the trigger
Top of
We're talkin 24 hours later
Turn off screen
Quitter
The fake
New story
Father Sandy Hook
So
Either so Syracuse attributing this to the Associated Press
Which is not correct
Absolutely
Which I am
So tired of hearing
Alex's said that
Literally anytime looks a little bad for him
It's an indication the Trump is about to be taken
Fly helicopters
Haven't heard much about that
.
So
If it's nightclub it gets even more
What's going to happen
Because of this one headline
Being evidence
Of
The tide
About
None of it is true ladies and gentlemen
What does that mean
Do stuff like that
That was a lawsuit and they go
We called up to her if they just say staying up
But you know it's not true
Associated Press
When did marketwatch's headline
There's nothing wrong with the Associated Press story from what I looked at it but there was a correction on it
The story was updated like
It's MarketWatch right you don't contact you Associated Press
To get them to
Vix
Article that someone took from the Associated Press
Contact
Outlet and Alex doesn't want to do that because he walked the MarketWatch headlines
If you want
His cake and eat it
No yeah that has to be it otherwise
Otherwise his lawyers are
Really really stupid
Right he wants to do everything in his power to first of all
Not mention that it's a MarketWatch
Make sure no one contact
Do you want to share a contact
Piazza formality
In the victimhood of a poorly-written
Either that or his lawyers are exactly like those dumb dumb Chris
Listen to email Netflix
To try and get Amazon good Omens
So Barnes is back
Here on the 19th is on every day
What is he doing
Is raking it in
So
Alex
Misrepresent
The nature of this
This being an Associated Press headline
Because
Barnes doesn't correct
Pretty sure it's Olive
Forest
I on the other side but first off
Sonos
No doubt No Doubt
About misrepresent MarketWatch
Conversation of what is the
Twitter
I think it's all a charade
Barnes is such a f******
Scale lawyer
I Canna imagine
I cannot imagine a more f******
Uncouth lawyer
Yeah he's so
Yeah these making is his box
Today though
Dislike the idea of allowing Alex
Representatives like my lawyers called
He doesn't
You're implying that I called them and that's what I reported they told me that's f***** up
He's able to
To build that
If this is not true about Alex all things are up for grabs
Like that's good work
And
It's Alex
For the fences
Trying to argue
But he didn't
Mad Houston
That stuff even though he's very
Barry
Heavily implied that it was
Correct yesterday
So even allowing Alex
A big part of it is like
What we keep sort of dancing around
A little bit
Turning it that the idea that I think Alex realizes that like
If allowed to stand
The idea that I did what I did
Is
So f***** up
Consequences of that could be Sosa
And if someone hit her Christmas
Like this like it let's assume someone
Like I don't know if there was a rock through his way
Violet never
Something like that could have happened
Consequences Alex could have face
Would have been
So Siri
Blood knot
Forget about the idea that
Case
Boxing the hook
About people
Harass to these families
PID
Would be
Might Prejudice a quart
About like all
That seems to be what you do defend yourself
People to harass
These families put in defending yourself yourself
People to harass the lawyer who's defending this
That's what happened
Is Baidu
I think he recognizes how f*** to you
If that don't go right
You starting to prepare a little bit
The preparations are sort of 3/4
Publicly
Tip dipping his toe into the I might be dead in a year
Prepare to get off air
I told the staff if I stop freaking out
I've not heard those
I mean some of the fatalistic I'm going to be dead soon
Dispersion
Say like
I've had to get I've had to tell people
Save me from
Giving away any of his authority
Saying it so public
Bananas
First prong of it
Intense
Like ads
And sale
Desperate
The crowdfunding
And all of his reporters getting on trout.
That's not good
Insane
Think that Barnes is
He's going on the show every single time I have a few really feeling like
Just going to be like
Hey man you got to take some time
Best skin defense
I can't you know well be hosting the first three hours for the next week
Alex Diaz
Say getting ready to give Barnes
C u b b right
Might be might be trying to take over the operation
Boris is the most evil person in this entire f****** stores
Publication
So that maybe
I find this very boring
On one level
His response
I think of some flare-ups that are kind of interesting
This
Is
Like a real
Calm before something really bad
These Trends do not go in a good direction
The overt nest of some of this
This white nationalism
Is jarring
Ring and on
Pleasant
Par for the course
Different about it than any other time
First of all very rare for him to
To have a legitimate defense
MarketWatch article and then be possibly misleading
Connecticut Post headline
Inaccurate
Whatever
I meant it's also rare
To really
See what appears
Yeah like that's exactly what I was thinking
Sincere fear he really does
A black cuz he's not pulling the Blustery like
This is like genuinely like
Made
A huge Miss
Had
Something
I never have
I have
Nothing and I have turn nothing into a mountain
F****** gold
And a one-time I am handed a layup
Nail in the coffin
Opposite direction
Yeah
He's going to be reliving that day for the rest of his life
Like that poker hands
100% what happens but I am now
Getting out of the press
On Monday we will be back in the past
Cuz I'm sick of this s***
Bahrain
Going to have to
List of the audience
We will not become a Robert Barnes podcast
I assure you of that
We should do some more donors
Agree with you
First gym
You're not
I'm a policy wonk
Ewok
Next
Not Gorka
And that Robert could be Barnes
Donating to our podcast just in the hopes of these diversifying
In any way
Take him down in anyway
But if it is
Goodworks
Let's switch things up
You are now a technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Text Jamie
I'm a policy wonk
The real world
Never one episode
I've watched a few like
Trailers and that is it
Understand man
Mystery
Prior Lake
We got us
Emoji
You're not wrong
Charlie Richards run
I saw three wheel
Jessica character
Next
I'm a policy wonk
There's always a Tacony
Freakishly large
Close this out
Okay
First someone who bumped up their donation little bit
Appreciate it very much
This is a krill oil
Heroin
Freakishly large
Play guitar last one
This is
In reference to this is an attack on me
Except
I will say thank you
I appreciate their support
But I will not sign off
Express
Okay but
Banana milk is God sent
What's the business
Is freakishly large
I refuse to speak
Dynmk
I like
I like strawberry milk I like chocolate milk
Milk milk
I like soy milk even I like almond milk
Let's see what else I like
What's horchata horchata
Sure
But thank you anyway
For the audience
Sorry if it was but we appreciate everyone's support
I was just thinking about how
That this whole like drops thanking everybody on our patreon
These are all things that we did
Mainly because we thought no one would ever
Steve Ackerson we've already made an implicit
Appreciate everyone
Salata drops
Coronavirus
Acknowledge underscore
Not on
What was subscribestar
Spreadsheet wasn't good but we are on Facebook
Download our podcast
Nope not on
Call Luis
Certainly.
Who got the
Today
I'm in a lot of barns
What's going on got a lot of
I ignore putting School
Probably has
Cuz that guy
Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color