Alex
Remember to Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
But
What's your favorite memory of being fried
I don't know man
Parade a lot of the years that
But I've lived in Chicago
Entirely sure all of
The
Blur together
I mean I don't I don't
My first year here I'll say this was my this was my response
Do at this maybe this is my favorite memory just because I
I came from Columbia Missouri was very liberal town in Missouri
Cute population
This is urban living
Like big cities
Skyscrapers
Nothing like that in Columbia
Crazy
And pride
My response to it
It wasn't as good as I expected
Did you have this perception in your pocket
Describe bubble bars
Kind of expecting nakedness everywhere
That's a false image being penetrated for sure or puncture
I remember growing up with a very similar
False Image like my parents
Incredibly
Homophobic and really awful about that so I always have this
They were always giving me this
Mental picture of just a bunch of dudes with dicks
Throwing around walking down the street
Look it up
We're allowed to do this because Christian destroyed
It was really nice
Annoying
When you do experience it for the first time in your life
Oh yeah this is
This is normal
Why did I ever say
Think anything else would you let other people's Sensational in slightly.
Images into your head without even realizing that they are
That sort of thing
Coming through a little bit of white wearing black pride weekend
No longer that wide-eyed child coming to Chicago voice
Traffic to Pulaski
Yeah it is interesting to see a lot of people dressed up for pride and then other people just walk
Walking around
Very
Very nice
We are going over these scratches
February 10th to 3rd
2013 NRA
With Alex Jones after
Dokkan how is rhetoric
Evolved
Honestly finding out a lot more about other stuff
Quite frankly
But it will get into that I want I want to see the real priority
To keep focusing on this 2013
Sandy Hook start even as the
Someday become so crazy and Alex's Flames out in front of our very eyes
Acceleration
It's still super important because barring any kind of like
Really
Catastrophic still is going to have to do this loss
Coming up
The families are still going to have their day in court
Recording this he has to give his deposition
I'm in that case
And I think there is any
Incredible amount of value for us
To understand the present
Alex
Does present become
Closer to the actual lawsuit
First to understand
Stretch
I'm saying this as much to myself as to you and to the audience that I believe that this is a valuable thing
Even if
8 *
I was just rambling about nothing
Send the next episode
Episodes
Or just
To respond
Well I mean had we have not done those episodes in 2009
We wouldn't know Alex's affinity for the Somali pirate
So it wouldn't have been strained
To the Trump administration's treatment of the children
I'm with the
You know his response
Hey you know we know
You must have known they were giving them at least you tip your hat to that
So there's that value
Go back to the past
February 10th to 13th
There's certainly an evolution of some of the narratives that are are
Really
Orlando
What evolution
Oh
Before we get to today's episode
Very much
So first of all Marissa thank you so much
Text Felicity thank you so much
You're an alcoholic
Eli
Eli I'm not sure Ellie Eli whatever it is we're free
You're now a policy walk
Back alley thank you
Next
Merle Grinch thank you so much and I don't know policy
Camaro Brake
Appreciate that very much
You're now technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Do you like
Please
So Jordan last week
Piers Morgan
F*** it take intermittent outages
Characterized
His coverage of everything
In 2013 he is a
He is a attention-hungry little boy a is
Yeah the guy who selling chocolate
Attention chocolate
Metaphor fell apart
And on our last episode we have the beginning
Of Alex paying attention
Tuesday Christopher dorner's shooting
In California
Where doerner it has shot
A woman who is daughter
Of his defense
When he was
To overturn
Determination from
He killed that guy's daughter and her fiance
Another cop
On the way around terrorizing
Most of southern California for
Alex
Does
You know otherwise episode he wasn't informed
About it
Uninterested
Certainly
Do you get the indications of disinterest from him and are covering it from the jump
True
Bolivar last episode
You think this is bad
If you take our guns you're all day that was kind of one of his
Pieces
Jumping on the 10th
Do the Sunday show
Dior handbag
Basically the same
Motorcycles
20 something
Wow
When did they
And just go out
So you're all dead
Are you trying to take our guns
Implications
1 points
6 million responsible gun owners
Responsible
Where to have their guns taken away
Gray like ninja every cop
Never maybe I'll turn in my gun
Every single
Okay alright
That's Troublesome I.
It is just almost directly a listing of it
This fetishization
Of the idea of like if we are pushed
Too far
We have it within us to
Weak-willed temperature I want
The toxic masculinity
So what what are the things that I'd really troubling about this February 10th episode is it is a really hard show.
It's mostly aimless
Talking about just about nothing
And then I would start taking phone calls from listeners specifically asked to call in
We're people as family members who were enlisted person
Who committed suicide
It's at moments
Like this
The show could be very touchy
It's kind of a thing where callers are able to honor their loved ones memories
And I don't want to make fun of that and I don't even want to really talk about it I don't think it's appropriate
I don't think it's appropriate for his show and I don't think it's
Certainly not appropriate
The thing is at other times
The show is really it feels like Alex is using these colors loved one
And their memories to help push his narrative
And even that is something that I don't feel really right
So I'm leaving
Most of the
The temp outside
Bible Daniel did not posted at all Bible
I regret now that I haven't told the other
Cuz I have heard him
Not if not as much as old man house phone
It's always the same thing
I don't want to argue about the Rapture with you
No he seems incredibly frustrated every single time he calls
Because at this point in time Alex doesn't have
Like a good screening staff
Right
Looking for like military and police collars
He's specifically looking
Four cops called
And he says repeatedly
When you hear someone hang up
Which indicates to me that you might not have multiple phone lines
He might just have a situation where it's like well
If you call it it's busy keep calling
Google
Folsom Prison
Maybe I mean it's it's like a radio station running
It might be I don't know what
Whatever the case
Surprised by someone like Mile Dam
Probably because of the lack of
Infrastructure
So but there's one more clip here I want to play from this February 10th
Episode
Alex
Repeating
Something about Dorn
That is not true
Christopher Dorner
Using a predator drone
Eisenhower warned
So Alex covers the Christopher dorner's Story very little on this Sunday
February 10th show
That is reporting the door has been hit by
He's a victim of a drone
TV is reporting Bureau Al Gore net worth
Two owls
Probably
You out happy
So that it's important to track it Alex's language in that clip because it's
Curious
You sing the outlets are reporting the Christopher dorner's the first US person domestically to be the victim of a drone
But you can test the report it
It's important to clarify however that the party saying isn't
U.s. purse
Some part not the part about the completely made up story about daughter getting hit by a drone
Because daughter is alive at this point he doesn't die for two more days
He does
Right
Because all I do is listen to Alex Jones I know why you
Contesting this part of the story
It's because there's a taylor-white victimhood to be told here and Alex is never a man
To let that go to Waze
The North Dakota story he's talking about his
Broussard was a farmer who owns apparently that included
Which is irrelevant to the story
Interesting details
Haha effect because there's some cows that come up and leave
Did end up at the missile site what I understand
So what day is six cattle from a neighbor's Ranch Land property
When the Rancher came by tried to ask brother to let him properties
To get them back
Which is kind of like passive-aggressive
This on its own is Ali
There's something known as esperame
Which governs how people must
Treat stray valuable animals they fine
Wanders onto your property
Just keep them
If you know the owner you're the legal obligation to in
Inform them and if you don't know who owns the animal you have to contact the authorities to help
Do you sort it out
If you incur expenses and housing the animal until the owner collect you're entitled
Compensation
But what you can't do is
Extort the owner
So the cattle owner called the police because his cows are being held to Ransom
Cuz we all know where this ends
We don't but he pisses you off okay I'm sorry Alex just said that he was going to get hit by a drunk
Well then fuc
Use drones to surveillance house
Utterly disappointing really hoping that it starts with c and ends with a drone strike on his face
Don't be a dick to your no one learns anything from this story
So the County Sheriff Deputy
Inspector from the stockmen's association responded to brother
Accommodating
Mainly they were supposed to free these cows
Broussard said that he deal with it later
The deputy said we need to take care of it now then threatened to kill the deputy
If you step foot on my property Mister you're going to not be walking away
Boy it is it's nice to see somebody move to North Dakota just to commit to it
Can you give me one more stereotype about North dakotans I would like
To live at
Best brother who resisted arrest
That was handcuffed and taken in
Police still needed to resolve
The case those they wanted to investigate the property could find about the cattle situation
But unfortunately the brossart family are truly all related as they refused to police search warrant at.
Randy was released on bail but the family would still not allow anyone to come investigate nor would they even respond to orders
To appear in court
Life with no real options other than a gun battle with a family
Cops decided to employ surveillance drone
Which gathered enough evidence to proper tactical operation where the authorities arrested
On in November 2011
Here's the thing
This story is profoundly stupid
Brother was found not guilty of stealing that guy's house because he really steal
He was later found not guilty of terrorizing the police because of jury decided the same quotes you step foot on my land
Apparently the jury sided persuasive when my car golf
Captain of the Sheriff's Department
Cause for concern
Police officer with literally like
Dakota it's a cause for concern
It's just a cause for
It took until 2015 for all this to play out but literally nothing happens
The family
Took some time
They all got found not guilty
Charges dropped
You can be a dick
If you just really commit to it and you have a lot of guns
Yeah but I mean if you really think about it this all could have not happened at all if it wasn't
Like that comes over to retrieve his cattle
Don't make him pay for them
Will the cops coming
Don't vaguely threatened to kill them
What's a big dick move
All this is his fault that magically there's no charge
No one goes to jail
Go to be white in America
Does seem like that actually in North Dakota
A black person doing exactly that
Find their doorstep
I don't think it would go as well
You get those cows back later
Get to the threat
This is a story that I was once
Talk about
This North Dakota story
Taken out by a drone
She is reporting that the daughter was the victim
Drowning
Here is where we can find a really interesting thing to
Examine
Specific piece of missing for
It's not true that the police were using drones to
Dutrac doerner
And in fact when the police finally release their full 100
Report on the law enforcement
Response
In 2050 the word drone appears
Exactly one
In this
He really had an annoying
Drone on
Federal and local officials also spent considerable time to Bunk in a rumor that a drone was being used to track daughter in the mountains
Ironically the Department of Homeland Security piloted aircraft to help search the forest
Who's capable of locating
You don't know what they're doing the only place in the report is like
Damage at stupid s***
We don't deserve it
The story of Christopher Dorner was the target of drones was first reported on February 10th
Tabloid
Express
Just picked up by all manner of unscrupulous Outlets who took the stories fact
Beginning of domestic Warfare
But the story wasn't
True it was clarified by representatives of the u.s.
Border Protection
And they were consulted because they would be the
People who would be lending the Drone
Really did fall to them
To sort things out
It's unclear where the express
Information from or how the story
I really have no idea what
What's going on here
I'm in a tabloid you know
Pretty crazy thing to make up bro
Princess Diana
Conspiracy
This is
Happening
The sort of thing that has like real lasting damage
Boystory
Offense
Text Abby
Princess Diana conspiracy
And it was a conspiracy
We went over this episode to get back into my feelings about Princess Diana
I've been away from this point
The story got Twisted into reports of the Drone themselves being weaponized
Being killed by one
Although you wouldn't die like I said
All the insinuations go back
To this Express
Story enter the result of a stupid telephone
The new American Road nautical at the headline quote will the LAPD use of drones
Christopher daughter
Jesus witches
Really escalating the rhetoric Outlet
Ask the question that donut
What if
Right
Glenn Greenwald
Tongue-in-cheek piece on the guardian rhetorically asking why would be a bad thing
The kill doerner with a drum
Obviously
If you read it it doesn't
Sea-Monkeys implying
But also if you read it and you didn't have
A pretty decent ability to read
Read
It would be
Easy to miss the subject
NBA2K disguise making a pretty good argument for why would be dangerous or police
Insult Greenwald and his abilities
He should stick
Really screaming as directly as
Angry text
Who were you know launching
Stuff on YouTube about
The New American
Greenwald did
The language like
Drones targeting doerner
Drone
And all of them were based on
Fall story from the
Express
Some people have gone so far as to call a hoax
Yeah
Wow
That's what Alex is reporting on
Disgusting here on the
Like a real
Outlets that ran with it based on
Very little
Irresponsible
Yeah so that's about all we got from the 10
Because like I said most of it is
Stop that I just don't feel
Talking about
It is what it is
So are we getting
And Alex has noticed something
Dispute
Is important
About the doors
Situation
And he believes that there is
In the world
Who are
Courts and are supporting
Here's what
Situation
Syracuse
Extremely
Christopher
Doerner the alleged person
Calling the police
One of the system's killers
Rewire because you got kicked out of a cult
I've never said this on the podcast
Because I remember what happened with the Christopher Dorner Manhunt
Like I wasn't that long ago
I was twenty-nine when it happened or so
But at some point Alex
Going to start claiming the media
I remember the way things
Progressed
Why don't you like listening to Alec
6 years ago or anything like that
But it was the story played out
Steadfastly refuses
Except complex
No one in the media support Christopher Dorner going on a shooting
And terrorizing an entire city
And
Area
There's wall-to-wall
Instigation of his action
I assure you all of the major figures in Media
With his this is what's going to happen to all
If you take our guns bulshit
That's not a very negative
Didn't like his closest criticism is like
Describe
I mean his approach
To it seems to be like less
This is a teachable
Weird
However
Remember
How is information started
Come out about why he was doing what he was doing
And some of the media felt that it was worthwhile use of times
Understand the motivation
Tim's of a high-profile
And very scary spree killer
When you start to get into what motivated doerner
A very complicated picture because
Chance to emerge
Daughter previously been an officer with the LAPD
He was fired in January 2009 after he claimed a fellow officer
Kick the homeless man
Who they were detaining
Daughter was a rookie
So he had to go along with a training
Officer
Teresa Eva
When they arrived on a call they approached Christopher gettler
Who suffered from severe mental
Gettler threw a punch
Unreleased
His father's Custer
Two weeks later daughter reported Evans to his Sarge
In the chest
Space drawing blood
To clear excessive force
Internal investigation
Did not conclude that that kicking it happen
Surprise I was fired for filing a false report again
Set timer
After he was fired
Determination
That prompted hearings at the office
The inspector-general than the LA Superior Court
And eventually the California court of
Appeals
All of them upheld his termination and found no wrongdoing on the part.
However
When you start to get into the details surrounding
Play the case there's a bit of mudding
That a lot of people have their difficult time wrestling
What
The most believable thing in the world is that an LAPD cops use excessive
The first element
You're always going to default to not supporting them
Code of Silence
Lawsuit prior
There's a lot of reasons why you would have a d
Default position of skepticism
I reported the person I was retaliated
As Richard gettler the detain man
His father Richard
The Christopher is
Butane
Richard
Call his son
The kitchen
However Richard also pointed out that his son suffered from
Severe dementia
And was quote prone to contradiction
Edit description of the officer who kicked it was a stretch
XtraMath
Didn't match
He said that she was almost black
Panda shoes
Caucasian Roman
To testify
His father said that he couldn't because quote
He wouldn't
Understand the question
Nor be able to provide
When he did finally come in for question
He was unable to answer
What about his age
What year it was or even what day it was
Ultimately he made a statement that he was struck with a
The club during the Iraq
Which is categorically not
He's someone who
Video
Of him
Being interviewed
Describe
Being kicked
And it's almost certainly based on his
His other Behavior
Interactions
Almost certainly coach
Or it would if not overtly coached at least lead down
Uses of like
Defense
Of dorner's argument
Target
Also I mean the Sun
Come home and made the claim to his father unprompted
Do you know his father Richard his son's Facebook
Was slightly puffy
So do those details
On the other hand there were three eyewitnesses
The interaction
Between Evans and Gatlin
And none of them remember to kick
This doesn't prove that it didn't
But it doesn't help the argument that
Daughters complain about Evans happen
Trivialize
But it also happened a day after she told him that her evaluation of him
Was possibly going to involve recommendations
Areas is performed
Needed Improvement
Which is seen by many as
Being indicative of him being worried
About what was going
Come out
So
You know everybody's motives
Like I said
Fitting way to
You can you can justify it to ascertain
To put steak
In this a Charles gamblers
I recorded
Interview
You can go ahead and do that and then if you want to take
Word of his dad contradictions and
Did literally make contradictory
Huiclaims
Witness
You know you could take that
Kenobi trailer
Jordan was fired he alleged being the target of racist
Switch
Is an area where the LAPD does have some issues
The information that was available around the time of the shooting was
Sprite
Conclusive and naturally it cause some people to question what had happened
But here's where it there's a very critical
Do I have to stink
It's very possible to entertain the possibility that Christopher daughter was the victim of wrongful termination by the LA
PD
Strongly believe that is action after the factor of court
A normal human mind could believe
Might have been wrong
Simultaneously believe that whatever Roxy supper
In no way Justified
How we decide
Respond to it
Alex is rhetoric and propaganda for this level of reflection
Complexity
Possibility
Daughter was wrong
He has to answer
Honda cars
Support for it
And two shootings per day
On February 11th 2013
The date of this episode of the Guardian reported that the LAPD was reopening investigation
And two daughters termination
Including system
From the FBI
But the belly police chief was very clear
I do this not to appease a murderer
I do to reassure the public that their Police Department is
Heritage Fair
Sorry sorry
I'm almost there
That what Alex is responding to is stories covering this developed
The idea that they were going to reopen
The investigation
He's trying to paint the picture that the mediator daughter on which is
And I don't know
I have I have a difficult time
Trusting
Any kind of in
Institutional police
Force
Because of course
But
In this circumstance I think reopening the investigation
It was a Honda
Got the right thing to do
Because if you did f*** this up
You got on it
And if you didn't
Suck this up
You need to
Restored Republic
I think it's absolutely the right thing
To do and I don't I don't know
So on the June 7th
The LAPD release the report covering
If you read this
Report it's very hard to believe the dorner's claims about you
372 true
What are my primary reasons for reaching this
Conclusion is that V
Self-involved for
Evans
Heiser the guy
And prior to that daughter had tackled him into a bush
It's the only PD procedure that anytime any forces used in an arrest
A supervising officer
Has to be notified
And it triggers an automatic forces
That happened in the fence
When that supervisor
Kaiser who specifically required to not be
Involved
Which is to say that they're neither daughter nor Evans
Supervisor
That guy arrived
Interview daughter and everyone involved
And no kick was mention
They examined
And he did have a scratch on his face
But that was consistent with daughter previously
Jack Williams Facebook
Listen to a bush
Navigate it was like a spear tackle
Coming to the crown
It's one where they have a history of
Where whistleblowers have been the targets of retaliation
It's hard to engage with the story without that
Sabine someone
And I will admit is I dug deeper into the story I felt myself contouring
Each new indication that daughter was
Clearly lying
With also
Well maybe
Cute cover up
Feel like I kept having that instinct to be like
Well I mean but
Ultimately if you look at the evidence
To this report there's a mountain of evidence indicating that he made this up
Countless holes in it
Obviously police departments are not entities that you want to side with
You're cool and it's always good to take allegations of excessive force series
From what I can tell
LAPD was absolutely right
Sapphire crystal
It seems like
It's not the resolution that you necessarily want always
Would rather
Come to the right
Conclusion to write accurate conclusion then
Something that I
What I desire to be like
I feel like Alex
Emotional Detroit Detroit
Sheriff Deputy Aloft
Try to fill it up to this
Supreme Court in there like
No
So anyway
I don't believe
First of all I don't believe
The
Basic narrative
Alex
But I also think that there's so much more
Complexity
He's capable or willing
So we'll get a little bit more stupidity from him but
Especially surround
Button
Put Sia closes the book on
Because for my health I cannot get angry
You know who else uses laughter is a
The steam valve
The funny hope
Should I always called him growing up Batman
I would say that that's some
I mean
I know that people often likes
I have to laugh.
From crying but they're not usually
Speaking literally
Kind of a poetic
Way of expressing Outlook
Alex is literally saying
The table
Then he's going to murder everybody
Clip
Complains that everyone is silk
Dumb
And part of the reason why they're still
Because they like monster truck
Pro wrestling
I just love where this
Professional wrestling in monster truck
Monster trucks
Monster truck
Chiron to pro wrestling
Sucking monster trucks
Monster truck rally truck
I love it
There's so little awareness
If he was aware
He would do that sort of thing a lot more legit funny
Expecting a Colbert type character
Complaining that he's dumb dumbs like
Monster trucks events getting into a
30 minutes
I think they're real forgets what monster trucks are real professional wrestling
Match the other day
To do that
Slap each other on the chest all the Mysterio jr. is a great wrestler
Your truck I think you would ask for Rey Mysterio's papers
Probably
Is taking a spot from
Other wrestler
Patriot
Jack Swagger
Tritops onnx quip
Alex
Pretty clear about his position or has been up to this point and
I think a little in the future I visit.
But at least his is
Is Angela
I'm not sure if he's going to say it's a false flag
But at this point Alex is very clear that he believes
Christopher Dorner and this whole situation is
Turns out that his audience
Doesn't like that
This is a stage government event
Justin
Barre class
I don't know
I choose
Engage with that so much I'm really mostly interested in the idea that Alex is kind of
You can feel it like it is
It doesn't come up
Super regularly that you can feel a sense of Alex.
Bummed out of Step
Into a certain extent I can respect that
Because a lesser person would probably hear the audience
Yeah he's sticking to his guns to ascertain
I don't know what that mean
4 time
On the day when the call is first called in today or later today like
Horrible yeah it was a couple weeks
Alex
Is alerted
We know that he is red white papers
Is a lot of books
No he can't do that's not one of the four ways to learn
No that's true but he's read them is that a lot of books
Yazoo
Bhaijaan Beholder in bookshelf
You've got the right
Stuff
Yet
Whenever you talk since
Specifics about
Any of those
Never really points to any specifics about the
Broad
Gesticulations towards a
Talks about other things
A little bit more
Just had an old-fashioned Corruptions
Predatory
Organized economy
Operation
12 Monkeys
By a biologist / biochemist
In their work
It's always a movie
Always
For some science fiction book
You got to go
No Alex
You dumb dumb
Alex talks about the Rothschild
Who are still
Quite Vegas
Interesting
Source
Information
For his beliefs
About the Rothschilds
Before
Russian press
Dollars
100000000000000
So
It's really interesting to hear that Alex's
Media is a sorcerer is playing
The Rothschild family
300 trillion
Dollars
Leverage
300 trillion
Six-year-old now would say is a lot of
Or a villain in like a farce
The first
I have a problem with about this
This is the imprecision of the claim
What are the Rothschild family
Like their traces back to your amp shell Rothschild
Over 200 years ago
Mayor Rothschild had ten children
And even just in one generation to family
Pretty spread thin
Pretty spread out
That the folks who are alive today and by that I mean the ones were born in
There is a sixth or seventh generation of the family traits back from Mayer amschel
Start like
Just a little bit
Not to say that a lot of the members of the family aren't real rich and it
Positions of high status
Society but it's important to point out that
Never really discussed his how many Rothschilds there are
And how it's a real stupid way to look at the world to imagine that they're all working
Together or it's some sort of a bloodline bass global domination conspiracy
And yet none of them has come out and talked about it not a bummer
It's all bulshit
Still running things
And lock it work
In that case it doesn't work in this case there's lots of
Are the Rothschild is the one family member Alex has ever had on his show
You tried really hard to be polite
Sweet a******* to him
For no reason
Consider this
David's great-grandfather was Leopold the Rothschild whose great-grandfather himself his own
His great-grandfather is great-grandfather
Was Mayer amschel Rothschild
Whatever animals Alex has towards David based on lies about what his family did six or seven
Back really only makes sense
When you view it in the context
The Alex believe that there's something evil in their blood
And that all members of the family are intrinsically up to
Generally speaking it's really hard to hear blanket condemnations of quotes of Rothschild
As anything other than poorly disguised antisemita
Part of this is naturally because throughout history a lot of the people who attacked the Rothschilds weren't interested in Vegas
They're real until
Mysterious
A 1909 pamphlet that circulated about the evils of the Rothschild family
Included the proclamation
The Real Enemy!
It's only after
I don't know 1945
The people in most polite Society felt the need to
Aerotek on the Rothschild
We're totally due to the fact that they're rich in
Yeah if we're going to
Still hate Jews
You know I mean yeah
Holocaust happen
Can find a way to CO2 this Electric
The Russia part of it
The Rothschild family ever really,
Complicated history
Dating back to the pogrom of the early 90s
Azhar Hussain
Facilitating
Jewish riot
They were asked
Looking for 300 trillion dollars
Well I don't think the modern state of Russia really hates the Rothschilds
Like that I do believe that there's a lineage
Rothschild
In some parts
Of Russian culture that
It still lingers
And believe that Alex
Be taking its cues
From that point
Part as opposed to
Real History real
That's my guy
And I also don't know if Alex is like
You know
What you're expressing
Semitism
When you make these blankets
Declarations about the Rothschild
But I don't know if that's
What's motivating Alec
I could easily just the European like
This is what conspiracy theorists do
Yeah
I could see it just
BFB in the function of his lazy
More than like over Auntie cell
It's interesting
Is is definitely
Hippie Sabotage
But that doesn't always mean that that's why you're wielding
Variety of benefit of doubt
Yeah it is the same
Been at the heart of most genocide
So everybody kind of knows that if it's if it's effective enough to get you to
Mass murder
People for no reason other than whatever characteristic
To describe is different
Then
It doesn't even matter what you
You hate just the mere fact that you're doing it expresses
Jessamine racism
Bigotry and massage
The whole thing
But I still think there's a decent chance that Alex
Just stupid
One of the reasons
If you know you know a man by the company
Keeps
You hang out with raisins
Alex
Won't stop talking about a very specific thing
That multiple people he knows
Have done
You know what I'm talkin about now
We've heard him talk about this before
I can't believe how
Frequently brings this up
You don't want to admit
You're wrong
Are mad at me
Reminder
Obama
He talks
So much about his friend
Being hit with that Nigerian scam emails
Radio host
Jesus Christ
Either that or Glenn Beck is that we thought asking for a friend
I'm mad at myself for falling for that
He's all the characters in the storage
I just think it's made it also something I'm going to do from now on
Finding every five
Every single time
Winchester missed the first time
Under $5,000
Turns out this pocket
Thrusting
I had a good heart
Most of the show is
Is just
Alex
Musically about the globalist
And their plans
Just sort of Freestyle Wrestling
I'm so now we move on to
So it was next clip but Alex is just trying to make the argument here the rampal
Hypocrite but in the process he does is literally defined
That's a critical hits
Money is philosophically opposed
Taking this money
He is not
Successful in stopping
What are you what are you going to stand up against an oppressive system like some kind of idiot principles
I don't know
I would say that that indicates to me
Is Ron Paul is a big lip service
People like to talk s***
Start telling a story about high school
Things about
His time in high school that like I don't believe
This is one that I asked
Sharon High School
The Breakthrough we got cut off
Before I could really full
Before
School nurse school nurse
Give people
I believe this story
Here's here's why
In most schools the School nurses
Prescribed medication
Even if their educational level and Licensing might legally allow them to
Schoolhouse services are set up
National Association of
School nurses very clear their guidelines
Administer prescription medication that the student is on
Without a quote written medication
Conform
With the name of the student the drug dose approximate time it's to be taken at the diagnosis or the Medicaid
Paperwork and
Administering
Crystal meth
2 p.m. everyday
Why
Cuz it's f****** dope cuz we're moving
We like to party
Pool versus don't have instead of sitting around their offices to give kids
This is just
Way outside the budget for pretty much all but the richest schools imaginable
Seriously think for one second about what Alex's describing
And you just see I call that's
Most School nurses are required to keep epinephrine albuterol diazepam and glucagon
Because those are emergency medication
They could literally be needed to save it
The kid's life
The Beyond
Just aspirin
Gargle with salt water
Like
She kept people
They asked people to
Keep their adderal in there like
Amphetamines it around
Talk about anything with real at all what he's describing is that he saw the school nurse dispensing medication
Primary care physician
I prescribed for them and he's created a nefarious backstory
That into a stupid world
He's witnessing a
Crime that would have made national headlines
Somehow this nurses got access to Tons of Speed and she's just getting kids hooked on it presumably for no reason
That's crazy
I prefer that
Sleep
If I had to guess
What's might
Assertive
Morcellation
Sounds like look at me
As an adult believe that to be a real memory why he experienced that as a child
It's because ADHD was name
Air conditioning
And along with that
Increased understanding of the condition was
Coming in
Consciousness
Because of that treatment over with ritalin became way more prevalent in the early 90s
Alex would have been
High School
We already know that his dad and grandfather were both
Completely insane paranoiac
The kind of makes
Some of that
Insanity
Be funneled in this
Correction
And Alex seized
The school nurse handing out
Prescribed meds
Creative writes a book about it you can totally see him going home and telling his dad about it
Meds and his dad goes off of on this whole life
Hey man I am a
I know what those meds
Absolutely
So also on this February 12th show Alex has an interview
For f****** ever
It's because that's
Alex
Decided that he wants to talk about the universe being a simulation
Do you want Dutch Brothers
You want to get
Real
Lionshead on to talk about
First person you call is
Is David f****** Ike
And you know what
I'm sure some people are going to be listening to this
And they're going to be like
Wait
David Icke was on and you don't any clips of it
They'll probably think that
Somehow it Injustice
It is not
It is a very bad
Very bad
We got pretty boring
It's really boring stuff
David I posted an article on his quote
Hook was released
Contradict
Sure so
Chalk him up on that team
Gotcha
Also on this episode here on the 12th Alex's really bent out of shape about the idea that Chris Kyle
Sniper
He has been killed
Alex
Conspiracy of some sort short but he still hasn't really
He thinks happened
At all
It's very difficult
But now there's another conspiracy
Because they're having
The funeral
Chris Kyle in Austin
And the highway is closed down
Because of precession
Alex
Furious about it
I can't tell you
On somebody
All right that's right now I remember the the whole Jesse Ventura American Sniper off
Yeah
Chris Kyle had claimed the Jesse Ventura was drunk and running his mouth off at a bar
Chris Kyle beat him up and then Victorious
Alex
The word of believe
The globalist
Killed Chris Kyle
They hit him up
To take down Jesse Ventura Chris Kyle
About who had told him to Target tomorrow okay okay
Specific about that that I can't even
I can't
Percent tell you that that's what he's saying
Seems like that's what Alex
It's very it's very nonsensical
What Alex
Seems to be saying is probably more accurate
Then what is actually
But I think more important
Play because of something
Concrete
Alex
Anger
About this funeral procession
Ludacris
Deep and meaningful
Map with other people who should have funeral procession
And each one of them I'm like
Okay
Like all of them
You already said yes I also am certain
Any of these things that I also suggest
All the soldier other soldiers funeral procession
A+ is any of that ever at actually happened Alex would be like
35 shutdown
Pissed off no matter what
As he's complaining about that
This is the last time we have from the 12
I think
Tips
About something
Another one of these Revelations about him that I wish that I'd had
Cuz I think
It explains a lot
The control of reality
Alex
What are the things that motivate
Great
Is
That he wants
To decide
He want
To create reality
Absolutely
He's a reality
Is out of Step
With
The best job all the time stories
And because his stories are so
Stilted they're so factually inaccurate
You're so manipulative in headlines
And Lead
Submarine
Because there's so much manipulation involved no one
The time of day
Any respectable press
People who read
The circles
That I think there was a real chip on your shoulder
I don't know if I necessarily
Fully understood
How much
That really
The primary driver
I know that I've heard him talk about like we control the narrative
You know
I get
I get that I've always have always got that
But that always felt more to me like
I'm going to
The primary Pusher of a news story
As opposed to like
I am going to
Important
I know that that's fine.
I think that another piece of it too is
Alex
Pretending
Right
Ohio
Besides important
He has the
Strength and backing of all the people
People really think is important
A weird sort of delusion
Yeah
I see him
In this
Place of
I don't know how much of what he believes
How much would he says he believes he
No s*** but I know he believes that enough of it
Have to feel disoriented almost
All the time
Because
It's not
Real fright
Situation you can either adjust your
Sense of reality to what is real or
You can
Feel everyday like you're losing your mind
The feeling of being gassy
All the time
So I imagined him
Saying like the media controls the the
The story or the media is
Is the story or whatever
Is it his way of
Kind of like wiggling out through that gas
Eliza Doolittle
Creative
The only other way you can feel gas-lit all day everyday
Succumb
Quit
Yeah
So we move on to the 13th
Crystal Werner has died
In the woods
You know
Wydown
What ended up happening was the police
Shot in
Some
Canisters
Gas canister
Smoke him out
Did not work
Pyrotechnic
Gas can
Canisters
Better called burner
One of them
Set one
Exterior walls on
Bonfire
The place ended up going up
In Flames before
Granny fire
Control
People could get there
Daughter ended up shooting himself
Inside the belt
Alex
I believe
Is
To turn the corner
On Chris Dorner
Because
Of the nature of what hap
Experience
Which you'll see very clearly
Sports Clip
February 3rd
Alex cannot talk about the news without tying it to Waco
Here's another example of
Right now
All he can do is
Burien space through the
The prism of this deeply traumatic events
From his own path
I got it he was at Waco
It's so traumatized
Such a big part of his early
Career
Did everything is seen through the prism of
Man
Criminal in police around
Fire involved
Must be wake up
I think it's often
Died in a Waco
Statue in a similar Waco situation would be like
Will you know more
Chile
He was probably just being
Control there's a bridge
Safari app
Cuz I I don't think
Is a full coming around on him
B
Waco and
Branch Davidian
David koresh
Our ultimate
Victim
They are people just love guns
Good good folk good Christian
Doug McClure
His
Characterization of them
Is Dutch
For government murder
Government oppression
I can't stress enough
There's never a negative word
About crash in the brain
There's never any negative connotation
In Alex's coverage
Only making
Excuses for why the government
Wrong
Well that kind of s***
So
Talks about Waco
Repeat it
In terms of
It's not
Just a situation where he's saying if there was a fire
What he's doing
He is at
His listeners hat
If you've listened to Alex
Look for a long. Of time
Expensive like
Magic Arena really f*** this
Good people over
Kill the guy and it was murdered he was probably
Repeat
Funny Rico
Despicable
Evocative but I want you to remember that I'm also
Attaching to Renee
It's that it's pretty
The responsible thing to do
Especially considering
Comparisons are not
Tear down a wall
In the door situation
Purpose
Alex doesn't know what happened
And he admits as much
Weather was the flower
That's
Is it means those
The pyrotechnic one
Cuz they had
A potential for being able to set fires
If you want to discuss whether or not that was irresponsible absolute
Let's have a conversation
I don't know
I don't have a position on it
Cuz I don't need
If a forced air force
I'll think about it some more
Question of there were recording
Burn It Down
Yeah
To the extent
Was that before there was a fire accidentally
We started
Get out
They're yelling burn it down have any
Actual impact of the fire was started that's another important question
None of that
Reconsider buyout
Triggered
By his memories
And feelings about Waco
It's overriding Isabella.
To think critically
It's overriding his ability to assess
The situation as it is
It's overriding his ability to even make a can
Harken back
Back to Waco talk about that
Just drying
Move Along
I I wish I had
Out of nowhere
It almost sounds like they had to life
Wait wait wait
What what
Monkey
I mean it to be responsible level of conjecture
You could
Look into it call somebody
For combat
Check-in what was meant by burners when he said birders on that tape what does that mean find that colloquial
Slang for these
You know it
Or you could get on Eric
Flamethrowers
Which is a response
TGIF
Flamethrowers
Provided they never use
It's like the epinephrine of the school nurse office nurse monster come
Fire extinguisher is the flamethrower
Just to keep Fire and Ice right there must always be a balance
So Alex starts talking
This point about how Obama
His administration
Mafia
His only real comment about Sandy Hook
Episode
For this stretch of episodes which
Again since we're trying to understand that path is deeply disappointed
Distracted by
Other major world
I'm at 10 also.
It's it's kind of disappointing
But here we go
Mafia
Air Force One helicopter
It's Obama probably did say
One thing that is a through line
We can say absolutely is that Alex does not believe
Adam Lanza
That has been
Consistent from the day of the
The shooting till now here we are in
The second week
February
He has dabbled with
Flirted with the idea that no one died
Also was happy to platform
Professor
Right
It's weird there is
There is
Definite
It's a false flag
And
Push and pull
I lied like pushing
Cool Whip
It was all actor
It was fake
I'm so at this point Alex starts to take a call
And gets one call from the lady
Who was in Iraq
Turn on Facebook
Gerald Celente
Are commenting back and forth
Great-aunt
She said something
F******
You know I think
I'll probably hear in 2013 or black
That's a good point
But now it's no
Stupid
And it last night bunch of us were watching you know
President Gerald Celente
Retreating back and forth with some of us on Facebook and things and all I kept thinking is
Before it lurks could have gotten
Anybody
Information
Probably wouldn't have happened
Obama kids
The internet
Control
We will lose this battle
Very quickly
Hitler never could a roast
The power with circle
Hitler is in his grave
So in this next clip Alex just
Waco indoor nerd
Together even more clothes
This is confirmed
He's turned it into a verb
Throughout the shower
Recent gets confirmed they brought in
These armored vehicles
Thought in the official record at all
It's not confirmed
He cannot
Experience
Any other way
Then add another way
That's f***** up
Cuz it doesn't it doesn't work
So get the call
And this dude wants to spread
Conspiracy about life
Hey they found is I
The building burned
Daughter I thought it strange they now said you know this always weird things every time something like this happens and
Never ends up the Kinect right
They said that they found his driver's license near his body
Personal license survive that Inferno
I don't know why don't you read up on it under his body
So that's how it survived
I didn't burn up because it was under a body
Very easy
For you to not be a super critical or looking into things
Kind of person
He survived a fire
Makes no sense
Simple
There's so many possibilities
You don't know about
In terms of other places
Could have been
Whatever it survived
Possibilities
Which turned out to be
What's in the report
Is that he was on
Top of his ID
So it's shielded it from the fire
Made them able
To find it
And that's what makes
Propaganda so f***
Is because what you would want
To say
Is like
Look it up
You can find that information a lot but do you know what else you can find
Completely contradictory information
That is pushing to your you know like what
Take away the information part of
Contradictory
Contradict
Presentation yeah totally
And also it's a you know
I think it's most unsatisfying February 13th
Instalike
To this caller at that point
I don't know why don't we wait to hear Samantha
Right I don't know why because the report
But the answer is very simple
It comes back to the
Concrete
If you wait until it dries
The idea will not be suspicious
Because everyone will know that it was because it was under his body
If while the concrete is wet you inject the idea that it's
Suspicious that is ID is there it will not be affected by the time that information gets out because by that point
And used it to build the conspiracy up higher
It'll be built upon by that point
And to accept the contradictory piece of information
Or at least
Risk of falling over
So this is why these
It's very important
Boyfriend
Because
Alex
Probably says one of the craziest things I've ever heard
But this one might rank
Up there
Before he does he clarifies that he does still pretty much
This is not a false
And the daughter is still
Afterwards
Is batch
The system almost always wise
Supposedly what
I've not heard him bring that up
Before I think you might be able to contribute
Are there Booth guitars
There are
I mean
That's pretty that's pretty that's a big swing
I like I admire the f***
Yes man if you're going to say anything the Volkswagen
Go all the way back to the beginning killed
Who killed
Veterinarian on the case
I'm glad you brought that up I'm glad you brought up.
You're welcome he's not on the show
Right after all this stuff
African parrot
The daughter situation to go over and over again
Mischaracterizing
The
Dorner's death
A bunch of idiots
Finally stupid thing
Alex then
Has one of his sponsors on
Clearpoint app
It is introduction
He's on the air weather
So he's got to Steve shank the food guy on
Here
Is how
Beef shank
Uses
Christopher Dorner
And this entire situation
Giselle amergint
If everyone had a year's supply of food
And
The only ones
Jeremy
The victims are the problem
You know one of the principles that you and I talked about
Is
Prepared
You can turn a disaster into an adventure
No I'm not saying what
Is a potential
Adventure good
But the mob psychology
Anxiety
Decided to do something
Preparedness
So I'm glad he's not saying this is a potential Adventures
Is he saying that
Killed more people if
No no no
He's saying the day you know you got a crazy on the
It's scary to go out if you got a home
That's insane levels of exploitation and manipulation
Timeline where we never
Oh my God that's the worst
F****** thing exploding people
Well yeah of course
Yeah
3 years ago you would have been like
What
That deserves a
A whole f****** article
Whatever
Food
So Alex is talking about how
Ricky heard
Unlike the police
Radio
What is recording
The police mentioned
Heather talking about
Teriyaki
Flamethrowers
Alex
Thanks for calling
Forecastle
So
They're looking for the explicit purpose
Vernon's house
Gimme a Break
You just can't
Which he would
Unless you wanted to somehow pivot the story
I don't know how much I felt very strongly suspect
Because it's soaked
Consistent throughout this up
But it is
Sew-ins
I know that you still saying it's a real thing
And I don't know how he's going to change
But I know that he is he's indicating to me
That the story is about to check
That this is this is going to be a police state story
Narrative in a way that he
Didn't seem all that interested in doing up until pretty
No recently if it's
It needed he needed to check in a fire and then
Fries
This is something I could work with before
There's a f****** dumb Obama guy
The media loves in bonao this is a so I got I got s*** to say
So we started this episode on the 10th
February
If 1%
Abbas Khan weirdos
Decide to start killing cops
You'll all be deck
And this is how we ended the show
On February 3rd
Very quickly
You do the math
Also be
Deeply
In his
Where he lives
In terms of its
Does he have any friendships
What's that
Based around
Mob like
Extortion
Rapoport
I don't know
Listen
Rapoport
If you hang that
Picture up look
Nobody's better friend
If you hang the end I don't want to see anything bad at
But if you hang that picture up
1.6 million dominoes are going
And that is some
Don't want to see
He happened
I don't understand how Alex imagines that all 1 points
6 million
These gun owners will somehow coordinate
Which cops are going to
Mykel
I would guarantee that anything like this happened they would kill more Avicii
Other 100%
Preoccupation
So deeply f***** up
It's so unhealthy
Some ideas like if
If you put a few.
Towards
This political
Decision that I am against
Will Altos work
F****** country will be killed and it's ludicrous to imagine
Disappear into the forest you'll never know who did it all the sudden the next thing you know
Very quick
Obviously
Close late
And if you take that book to be
Application
The people didn't
Just kill police officers
80s
They also went after Paula tissue
So if
This rhetoric is so wrapped up in that
Mythology
It's hard to hear this is not like people listening
Read that book 2
They know they know what this is triggering
And their brains
Express
Hades god
Politician
Anyone who votes for gun-control measure
6 million
Veiled
It's a variable
But it still veiled enough too much like
That
Rancher
Was only a cause for concern
Concerned
It's not a it's not a direct
Breitbart
Anyone who knows what he's talkin
About
I don't know
Is headspace really f***** up
Weird that you can
It's nice
I think
Long run
In the largest
So you can get on the radio
And threaten to kill one boy
If they do a thing you don't want
Additionally threatened
Ultimately I think
Testament to
Free speech
Being
Yeah
Weird
It seems like that's probably one of those things are alike
I find it.
Over this
Span of time evolution of Alex's
Position on door
Quarter-turn
But he's making
See how it plays out
Because I know that
The factory owner killed himself
Stop people from
Talking about it I know there's a story for a bit
After that
The post
Mortem
The story
Asbestos
Is gone as the
Safeer
People were living
California
Remove
From the equation how does
Move forward with the
The Narrative I think it's going to get
What would I always find fascinating
His position
Somewhat evolved
With no regard for the story at all.
Nothing to do with his
No I'm out of him
Information about
Facts
All you needed to hear
Flip that switch was
Shacking fire
Like I was Bass
Basically yet
You needed a narc
You could resonate with his
Because before that is it really resume
All that much
People are supporting
Triggers
His his audience
Aldi's
These people that we're against
They're fine
Yeah sure
So it's more likely to be a real shooting
False flag
So I don't know if I'm excited too.
Keep it moving along
What happened
Website website
Knowledge underscore go to bed
We're on the iTunes were on the
Actual
There are post office
And mail us
Yeah oh yeah
Manipulative
Food sales
Oh yeah North Dakota
I read
Consumer website where good-looking post
Complaints
People have complained
A lot of people
Have buckets
I can't imagine rancid granola
Allegedly
Yo it's
That's like I don't nobody
Seems like a pretty consistent threat 100% believe it
I don't know if anyone has died from eating those
So I can't prove it I'll still 60 shank hasn't killed anybody
Who technically has probably done that
Is Alex
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work