Alex
Healthy beverages
Alex Jones Jordan
This is embarrass
Question to ask
So great how long is
Probably good five years
Probably closer to 3 or 4
This isn't a quad
What's my birthday
If I ever gone in the entire town has ever called
O'Daniel
What is the first number of years of my life and then
I think somewhere around Middle School I started shorting it shortening
Never dating
Absolutely everything
Nevermind
Puberty you want everyone else to be down into
I remember one time on the
The bus Junior High a friend of mine
His older
Sister they live down the street from me
Take the bus to school together and then I was like
Fourth grade and she was like what
I still remember the damn
Just easier
Looks kind of like a my girl
Situation going on
Stuff on that bus that drink
My favorite
Drop the ball cuz I remember what it actually is
It was that one time I was at
If you are beer
And I was close to the actual parade
And come down the parade line
Walking down the street other than Rahm Emanuel by himself no security whatsoever
I thought it was amazing
On his own
And then also just like thinking that he was going to get a good response again
Memory
Apologies
But I forgot to act in the moment but it deserves telling
Behind
This week talking about health Ranger by Academy
Piece of s*** real piece of trash
First episode will be out by the time we're
I believe that tomorrow the second part will be out
Lot of fun
Some of the people who make this show possible
Help us get along
So
The episode proper
First
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Sent me some awesome audio
I want to actually a wish right now I can place them
Really guilty
Alex Jones bass music
I'm a policy wonk
Permission
Earlier in life
Somebody donated on the elevated level
Douglas you're now a technocrat
Business
Freakishly large
Can't see us which is everybody except me
Practicing practicing silently
Station of being able to sing along with it as it were
About the way you says I declare if the timing is so felonious Munk
It's just perfectly wrong
Our feelings about
And if you would like sports.com
Couldn't support the show the present
We are covering the span of
June 23rd and 20th
You for Sunday and Monday
Before the shows at
Experience for me
One of the reasons
Keystone the other stuff that Alex has been doing it a present day when I say this is unpleasant
You expected something
Disgusting
Studio sexual
That I was having a real good time with it
And then I hit a brick wall
You are not what you expected
The Sunday episode is so fun
And it's almost like we could do Wacky Wednesday episode
It's a waste
In present-day Alex Jones
You do not
Becoming
It is pretty pretty alright
And then you get the Monday and it's just
Everything falls
That was nice.
Now as we record this on Tuesday
Monday is too fresh in my head
Bummed out about it
Pleasant Mount Pleasant
Far too much of a stretch
So here's another context drop
From
Today's episode
Business
They're going to fry you
Family real
Poached egg
Source
What the problem is that is it
What states are trucks by cracking eggs into hot but not boiling water and swirling water around to Ghent
Recreate a pocket of egg white around the yolk
Better option for preparing poached eggs using steam
One way you absolutely cannot do it is by Brian
Ways to cook an egg poaching is one of the very few top to your egg preparations
Specifically doesn't involve Brian
Small point I think it's
Alex pretty regularly managers to have 100 decent Ops
And his stupid brain manages to
Choose the first option that is the only wrong one great
Fry you like a poached egg
Totally scrambled
So are we jumping here on the 23rd
In some ways
Because Alex is
I'm the victim of the globalist the illegal pornography near
He's got a new one cooking
It's the whole show
Almost the entire show is over
No lawyers no no no no okay no guests at all
This narrative is
Ron
It's just it's just all here
Bring up your family
Guess what
There's 40,000 square mile for the u.s. government
40 years ago
By the break
Are the Elite
There's nothing really thought about that thousand square miles
Illegal to use cell phone
He's a real Hitta
About that
He seems to have recently learned that their parts of the country Russ cell phone uses which of course implies
Phone towers
Naturally the conclusion he's come to
Unfortunately
McKay's he's making this argument without knowing literally any details
About what he's talkin to
There's an area of 13000 square miles in West Virginia where cell phone use is against the law
I'm not positive that the elites
Are moving in math
To West Virginia and it wasn't specific about who these Ali
These are some going to leave that part alone
Didn't ban cellphone use
The Jeannette area West Virginia because
The fears about health problems caused by Wireless
It is way more interesting
Population 140
The closer you get to Greenbank the more restrictive the rules are by Wireless you
And that's Greenbank is the home of a gigantic
17 billion
Pound telescope
The largest steerable telescope in the world
It's operated by the national radio astronomy
Observatory
To work at the telescope and smaller Incorporated telescopes of the town
Exploding galaxies at the edge of the universe
A signal that's so faint that it's about a billionth of a billionth of a millionth of a watt
In comparison to cellphone Can-Am it around 3
What's a drastically interfere with these very delicate work these researchers
They're doing
Even though cellphone to didn't
Exist when the telescopes research started
The location was
Typically chosen for exactly that reason
Power lines radar spark plugs
Cars
Can cause interference with their work
So the remoteness of Green Bay
If they were going to be able to make any progress
Work began at the site in 1959 so that's probably what Alex is talking about when he says the rules of them
No place for 40 years
Doolittle off all night
Specific stabbings close enough
Feel like how he at
Misinterprets
A 2015 article about the
CNN provides a really interesting
What a piece of s*** Alex
Part of Alcoa
Can you show talking about how buying up Land series were there
Giant Gold Rush
Growth industry
He's adjusting to his audience that wants five
And if you buy up this land now you're going to be
Be safe and get some
F****** rich
That's the
Year-old resident
Who ran afoul of the authorities in the Greek
It turns out that his doorbell was interfered with the telescope research
Freedom get arrested
Scope anymore
Sounds like such a hassle of a way to live right
Raw
Quote far from complaining about their circumstances
Residence of these parts
Vacation spots will pop-up advertisements
Does refuge from connectivity
They've already seen it in influx of about a dozen Electro sense
People who believe electromagnetic frequencies of the store so their illnesses
The main fear Express by the area's residents is it
Exactly what Alex is working toward bringing about
By appealing to
The same community of Electro sensitive
Of course
He isn't trying to f*** with these people or anything it's just
Great example of how the
His real world
Consequences
Play fuk about
It doesn't care to understand
At all
Everything about the way you telling the story and we'll go on to tell the story is dishonest
The end result is only going to be the people that
If I know anything about the
People that Alex would Inspire to head out there
Telescope
Intentionally interfering with its operations
For being able to help Humanity
Alex's gold
This is a great narrative for Alex this is incredibly stupid
Pretty amazing
It's pretty it's pretty awesome
Expecting
This is this
Fun telescope
Just doesn't
I think there's a big problem now
What it was
Years old
They were like hey guess what make you a doorbell that doesn't interfere with billions of
Miles of galaxy
Man if you see the size of the telescope
Can crazy
It makes sense that they'd have to operate
10 years there's going to be f****** lunatics crawling all over that telescope trying to find out how it killed
And
Alex will have played a role more Extreme as it goes along
I just wanted to make sure it has a lot of information up top without Alex
Usually like to do it but I felt like it was important to let you know like
Deteriorate
Once again telescopes Factor
Heavily into our
Project Camelot a telescope mad at you if you try and
Alex claims that there's 10 places
In the country
That are like this
But does not name any of them
That is specifically responding to an article about Green
There's a place
But not just one
They got these facilities under different cover
I've looked into them
And I discovered at least 10
They're a lot more
There are
Corridors
The Western world
Where no cell phone towers
Allowed
Program worldwide
Bill Gates
Close enough to Bill Gates
I think you could have credit for that
He doesn't prove it method
As far as I can tell it's
The
That's it
National radio astronomy
Is a separate order
From what I can.
I don't have any evidence
Who kept building a bigger and bigger telescope until it was
Big enough
Galaxy maybe I don't know
You can get the sense already that what Alex's narrative about this is like the globalist have set up
This place is there safe haven
And they're going to go there
That's gone bad
Because they are heading
2 West Virginia
Right now
Really
Globalist attack
Breakaway civilization
Is running for the exits
50 million
What's that mean it means they're getting ready to pull the trigger
Bring up the Infowars special please support a straight Pride
Pennywise
Awesome with the beat
Good
So they pull the trigger
Obviously you'd be like I don't know
I don't know if this were
Works out from Alex
How trustworthy of the sources Alex incredibly
Our stand up against it
I'm not scared you wrong yet
I really just wanted to know you just love that f****** talk it's always a delight to hear policy
He's trying to reinforce
This idea
That the globalist are all heading to West Virginia
That is also a comical idea appealing to your own credibility
Knock knock sensor
You steered us wrong
Every
Perhaps
Yeah I would say every turn
I can't think of any specific
Jean on the street
People write but only in service of later steering the Bronx
Everly changing his position arbitrarily
Don't bring dog into
Contacts
We get to get a sense of why Alex is telling his audience about this and it's not because
The benign version of it is by a property in West Virginia
You know anything about Alex
You know that there's also a nefarious
It's part of it he wants to build that's not it
But we come back I'll finally get to all of it
I want to give you the
Want to give you all the
The history of the basics
And
Shut up
I just called
Before I show you where they are
Weather moving to
And what they're doing and how it's all
Hidden
Because I want you
When they released the bioweapon the most your family
Abraham.
I want you
Those are always a sentence of survive
I want you to know where they are
So you know what to do
I want you to know where to go with your
Roving bands of apocalyptic
You understand that the fiction of the coming bioweapon release is not essential to what
What he's telling people to do
Your family why would you get this
This is real f*****-up
I mean I know hiding behind this this like
Hypothetical triggering event of a bean
Maybe but it doesn't work for me
He knows what he's doing he's directing people to go to whistle
Virginia
So Alex explains that
You know he knows about this
Knows what this now please write an article
Which is good he's read an article in the New York Times
I'm still discussing the moment
But
The globalist
This story is not true
So much because I know
Tire off
Ricin
I'm going to blow It Wide Open we come back
The three different Hollywood people the time
The move to West Virginia
What they meant when I got the offer
I was offered
15 years ago
The move to West Virginia where I'd be safe
I really think he's putting people in danger in West Virginia
Such a focus on it
I would believe there's a possibility
What are you f****** move to West Virginia
Mystery Doug
Check out why wasn't that about that
Always knew
Oh you get this other piece of information
This is nonsense
I love this view of the globalist every time there's a new narrative going on he also has a personal connection to
Global early life very very
What's the brain through and spoiling their plans
This is this is just taking his fictionalized backstory and adding new details
Whatever narrative he's pushing it
The present
It's a dumb
Dumb s***
I told you this New York Times story
That came out couple of days ago
A couple days before Sunday
And
I already
Reference an article about this Greenbank area from twenty
It's not like it was a secret
Couple day-old editorial article Alex
Is going to try
West Virginia
This is up
Pagan
Photographer
West Virginia
Parallel reality
50 years ago was an artifact
Believe it's where everybody is above average for lunch
He can't he does not he's not able to
Keeps interrupting
Virginia is already out of the globalist because there's no Wireless their narrative
What was the New York Times on June 21st
The CNN article I read from details
The only article
Yet here is Alex just stumbling across this story is if it's just now come to the surface
The New York Times piece is an editorial and opinion
And it's first-person experience-based article about the author visiting this town and what they learn from it
If I had to stop at we're all connected to the internet in our phone
And by going to place with none of that stuff you're able to fully experience
Just how much you rely on those bits of Technology
Just as a default
Necessity of modern life but there's something deep down the
McCall's out to these places where they don't exist
And there's value in preserving those place
Especially for people who really resume
What isn't in the article is
No mention that people are talking about
The article puts the town's population at 150
It looks like they may have had a net gain in population of 7
Since 2015
The article says nothing
Even close to it Alex
He's talking about
Editorialize is a little bit more
And tries to pretend that
The satellite is somehow
Telescope
Is my area
Wi-Fi
Which also.
Generate electromagnetic
What a bunch of Throwbacks there is a giant
Pinochet
Eclectic
He says that it's a NASA and Esa DARPA command base with literally
He's just making
That off that is that
B******* it's on the article
He has no primary
Source 2
It's just what he thinks and feels
I'm also beat like talking about The Eclectic mix of the
People who live there
They aren't Elite
Or Rich
They're just residents of this town
Like it and not all of them work at the telescope
He's presenting aren't they so weird
It's people who live in a town of 140 people
It's a Small Town living
There is a neglect
Look at the pictures some of them are like
West Virginia
Are you sure
Doorbell
Sit like a little corner store
Nonsense
Delizia Telegraph sneezed
Just making
All of this up
Here goes on to make up another detail
Call Zack
And I did some more research on this last
Massive man
Show your work
Cite your sources on the Underground bands that are being built
Show me a
Okay whatever Underground
Scott's by then I got to go I got to go I can't have this conversation
I mean it's fun
It's not like this is fun comparative
Just like Project Camelot
This is dumb
I know who
There's a charm to it that's been absent from
The charm is it still hasn't aged
Direct people
But a little bit more about the New York Times article
And it's the
All
Admittedly
Manipulation
Neurons
Your bright
This stuff is
Healing Arts
And they're running away from it all over special communities
Urban form
Daniel L almond
So true
The article.
Get into that
The closest tecumseh's on the author brings up a reservation
Central Idaho where artificial light is
It's a place where you can protect people's ability to enjoy the Stars unencumbered by the Light of the city
Somebody loves to Camp I definitely think that
Super cool and a very worthwhile initiative to undertake
There's nothing to do with creating special communities where people are safe from 5G
The business interests would never protect on their own
Like silence Stillness
The ability to see the universe
With the naked eye
Ensure Alex's f******
Stupid
How stupid
So stupid that he just decided to forget about this line in the article he's covering
12 National Science Foundation
Consider the proposal to shut down Greenbank
And ended up slashing
Support by about 40%
That's under Obama's term
But she's a big old globalist why would he allow the funding to be slasher is super secret getaway base in the middle of West Virginia
40%
Does Alex not realize that is soon as that telescope facility runs out of funding and has to shut down
There's no reason for the wireless signals to be banned there
How to puncture the entire premise of the
Conspiracy. The globalist through somehow running
Ludacris
Drives me crazy
His own s*** is in the article he's covered or a strong indication that none of this makes
It happens
So awesome
Or it's evidence
Funding for the program
Has gone from the Science Foundation to the CIA
Obama's promotion
It's got Steph Curry's new show holy moly about how they play milkshake or whatever
Cooking knives
Chocolate Face
So Alex is read this New York Times article clearly hasn't internalized it very well
Conspiracy the West Virginia is
And Alex realizes
I got to make a move
But I said it still slow death
For all of us
Doesn't
How do you spell Terraria
I couldn't believe it if they did that either
Literally
Of the show talk about this
Nonsense
But yelling
About how the global start
To run
Is Robin from everything that deployed against us
The mountains of death of giant third world populations that weaponized
Smartphone 50 bio-weapons the leftist garbage none of them
Other kids iPhone
Go back
Threat
That's a large part of why he's interested in cover
Is there it is kind of like a
I hope someone gets hurt
Which is f***** up
Your editorial
Practices
Some sort of danger
So it's interesting
Talks about but I'm not going to let you
Completely
Misrepresented this New York Times article I protected area has been a secret
Cupboard repeatedly articles
A secret anyway everyone knows this everyone understand
Information would be available
It's Odessa this is a real good punchline
For his June 23rd
We just laid out the
Nobody else has laid out
Weave
Legendary engine
Legendary
Thaddeus
As close as you're going to get to the truth
Azarath
Legendary
Reflect
Killed it awesome
You know you have those moments
Sometimes the past of doing stand-up where someone has a terrible setting to come up north
That was pretty good
Twitter and Facebook is rice from with people who are at who I was at the show with who
Did terribly and then they're like
So we can do the 24th now and I told you it's a brick wall
Like I enjoyed
Threatening to Alex try talk about
Rest Virginia
Just offer
Cliff
25 years
Once in the first five years what I say this is the most important
And then about
10 years ago
Once a year
About five years ago I said about once a month
Broadcast
World
Too bad
So far
Just because you over
Inflate the importance of what you're talking about doesn't mean that the world is
Has no bearing on whether or not this news is important
You have gotten more desperate
Isn't that it's not just a man
Literally saying
Once every year
I used to yell at
People stop listening to me
I think that it's
It's very nice along those lines
Is unconvinced
Is it for sure
And then we get to this
Are where we find out
Why
The 24th
Election meddling
Google Earth
Sounds like a Batman villain
The doodler
Project Veritas
Wide open
But Google is a giant election meddling
Then get them to a little bit of a deconstruction of like
Before the googlr does not like maybe a villain
Ethereal
Serious
Sucks
I was dreading getting back into present-day Alex Jones in the preparation
This episode and to my surprise I found something that was fun on Sunday
In the form of Alex thinking
50 slog Public Super telescope was somehow The Refuge
The globalist to go to to survive the rollout of 5G
Kind of fun
Outside the whole time telling you this so you know where to find them and kill them aspects of that rhetoric
That's kind of the Alex Jones I can
Stomach pretty easily
Got a phone
So
Of course the next day you going to become completely overwhelmed by one of my least favorite
The Alex's bikes
Super hard
It's yet another project veritas
I watched the entire 25-minute Veritas video in WhatsApp
Deceptive editing
About the topic it's covering
Intrepid reporter James O'Keefe talks to an anonymous whistleblower
Google doesn't randomly produce their search results
Robinette's
Needs to be done
I'm not sure but I would imagine
But whatever
The argument hinges on them deprioritized Encanto
That's bulshit
Which is a real big problem for people whose life's work is
So here we are
Honestly there's no smoking gun in this video not no real cogent point
Just ramping
Insinuation of evildoing by Google which is run by sjw who have it out for Trump
Of course
I sincerely
Don't care about the
James O'Keefe is such a long time con man
I really just can't take
Produces too serious
I would think anyone who has
Actual scoop about anything in the real world would know better than to call him
But there's plenty of non-partisan
Investigative reporters ready willing
To take on issues related to Big Ten
Call James O'Keefe when you have a scoop you called when you have an idea for a stunt
That's it
I want to point out a couple things that are hilarious
Most of it is James O'Keefe interviewing this whistleblower whose voice is altered and covered by a physically covered in
Moonshadows
Nightline ABC News
Even though he is covered in your Shadow and
His voice is altered one of the first things this supposed whistleblower said in the video is quote
I believe sunlight is the best disinfectant
Brass balls for an anonymous guy talking to James O'Keefe to spit up
Tie rod end
So
James f
The Whistleblower
Pacific meeting were content filtering was
Discussed at this was one of my big red flag
The Whistleblower says that the meeting was held at a masonic temple
Now why would Google do that
Google is a shitload of office space and are perfectly capable of holding meeting
And they're old
These details were curious to me it kind of feels like someone making too big of a
Swing
You know that that whole culture of the text
We don't have we don't have cubicles everything's open here's some ball games over there
Groupon for quite a while they have the same thing with we got to
Bouncy balls to sit on
Masonic temple
Blower goes on to list
Google
One of his examples is Tim pool
Tempool headed
Response to that on Twitter when he said quote
My channel is absolutely not being suppressed or anyone else but my diffuser up over 30
500% from last year
An hour later he tweeted quote this is not true for my channel
Recommendations are up user up Revenue
What's Insider whistleblower
Feels like he was just choosing cool names in the Free Speech
Grace Community
And one of them didn't realize that now is not the time to be honest
Jump On It
The whistleblowers name
Not playing along with this b*******
So The Whistleblower says two things at the
The end of the video
A little bit discrediting
The first is kind of hilarious
What is describing why he's coming forward he says he doesn't like the people at Google are working in the shadows
Well he's literally talking through it
I also don't like Anonymous sources
Has dangerously close
Jesse Ventura
The others
What do you think
And this alleged whistleblower replies with a long pause
Then says quote
Hopefully I get away with it
Hopefully I get away with it is generally anyway someone Praises not a good action people say hopefully I
Oh I don't know working with a
Perpetual fraudster and a publicity stunt
Phrase it is I hope I get away with it
You know what
I would put it
The other video is secretly recorded footage of an alleged high-level
Name Jen Jen
Who is about
Trump situation
From happening
Videos
Republic that a lot of the other past victims of
Veritas
Explains that they added her comments out of context in the Trump situation
Who's the foreign intervention interference
Trump space
No okay no
What happened to her
In the lead-up to this video that they
Took of her being
Shots
Invitation
The few people who claim to be from
They said they wanted to chat with me about a program for young women of color in Tech
An area I've long been passionate
She goes on to say quote casual chat with someone at a restaurant in Houston imprecise language
Project Veritas got me
Well done
Probably also important to point out that because of the video tonight
In the flood of abuse
Messages
And so she's been.
What message she received the quote your ideology will be shredded
The Pieces Just moments before you get executed for treason
You're leaving you're living a limited time
Enjoy till then
The video includes complete misrepresentation
Tonight is involved
Because the message is more important than the
And if O'Keefe has to comply
Sweetly terrorized Jen tonight in order to
To push that message soap
I already here as they do Keith thinks this video proof is victimhood
When in reality all it does is demonstrate the exact Danger
It exists when you allow people like him to operate freely
Ultimately what it comes down to is furthering two important goals
Sissy
Project Veritas
Right-wing propaganda
Desperately trying to
Present the consequences of their actions as Noble Victor
Repackaging that is a very important goal
This further
Creating a pre-emptive narrative for why Trump really wanted 2020 even if you lose
That's all that's going on
They're definitely problems
The tech industry but ironically
Because people like Alex Anoka
Don't care about the real problem
They care about their Petty battles
In furthering their own propaganda
Medicals
Yeah there
Crafting away for their propaganda
It exists in a post Trump World Blues and whoever the Democrat who wins
Become president everything goes
Create all this everyone cheated
Wrapping stuff million illegals voted in the last election yada yada yada
Fuel nefarious
But less
Insidious I'm dangerous
Version of it
Well we still need to sell
If Trump leaves
Ready for that
This helps
You know I think
And I could be wrong about this
But couldn't that place
Still charged
Federal Building
I don't know I don't give them.
I'm not
I'm not entirely sure
Alex brings up that
In this next clip
This 25-minute video
Isn't edited
Winovich
My God watch this video
So that should be pointed out is there
Veritas
It's getting sued right now more than Alex
Text Jones
One of these few things
Morlock
As far as I can tell they have multiple active
It appears that there is at least
Active cases against okay
Eva Veritas
In the book's right
SK sweets cast
Pretending you the phone repair
Which ended up with him pleading guilty
Dubuque sentenced to three years probation
And 100 hours of
Community service
Then there was one Farrah after is b******* video
Hope you didn't have permission to record a private conversation
So keep trying to argue that the conversation
Private
So can you quickly settled the case paying Vera 100,000
Dollars
I can find no evidence that O'Keefe has won cases in court about the way he manipulative the edit
XVideos
But he hasn't cases
Against him
On the grounds of things like he can record someone in a bar without their consent
Because there's not a reasonable expectation
Enter privacy at a bar
This is why all of his videos are shot
There's no way that what he's doing would be legal if you weren't intentionally trying to secretly record
Private conversations in very public places
That's how we f***** up it Acorn that's why I got $100,000
Cuz that took place in an office
Not in a bar
So you could do whatever you want
Legal anywhere else
But you couldn't if it was in public
That's why
Now that's her post
About it.
Explaining
People will be more
Careful about accepting
Got to recognize that like we live in a time now where do you need to be a little bit
About propaganda people are going to try and f*** with
Especially if you work for a company like Google or Twitter
Weather going to be at Target
Yeah and they clearly research survey
What was more a Honey Trap
Getting women of color in turquoise
They're only smart move
Some smart moves but it's all in
If that
Evil smart
Cunning
Sure
Sekiro
But he has a ranking
Gyros
There's a little bit interested he probably wasn't killed
As we learned
You're right
No there's a hierarchy
He's not at the top okay
Kiro
Michael Jordan
Watch Amazing athlete
Call Jordan.
Michael Jordan
Firefighter
James okay tires with Trump
Of firefighter who dies in a building
That's ridiculous
That is just there so there's some kind of weird
If he started writing listicles
You would think he was a Madman
Top 10 Heroes
So what's next clip Alex talk
About
This actually this was a difficult
For me
Because I
I noticed something
Under lied a lot of
About Apple
What about Tim Cook
And
I feel like this deserves
Disgust
What
On the Undertaker
Number one
She's a horrible person
Albuquerque
I don't care what you do with your ding-a-ling
Major
First of all the
The boiling down to what you do with your Ding-A-Ling which is not great
Alex have a small point in the sexual orientation
Is it true
Yeah but I really thought
Tim Cook to be pretty offense
I want to tell you why
He's being targeted by Tim Cook in part because he won't stop talking about
Tim Cook is gay
Alex says that Tim Cook is
Major Pitt
Spit him about it
And this framing of how Alex is describing his
Problems with cook is where things become really problematic
Also that horrible voice
Is not helping
No that's that was
Skillet
Alex's criticism isn't
The Tim Cook is running suicide Factory
He's running suicide factories in China
Why did Spike Tim Cook's sexuality
This is an important distinction because Alex don't give a s***
About people working in unsafe condition
His favorite politician
The things that eliminated
Many of the terrible parts of the conditions
Spectra-physics
Explicitly enact
Biblia cat
Who's complaints about the plight of workers
Halo
That is a nice port to work
Vagina and nothing I'm about to say you should be interpreted as
Minimize
The difficult and exploitative situation that many of them are in
Specifically about how little Alex Jones knows about China and Apple
Every single time Alex talks about China in apple
He brings up soup
That's it
The story
It's a horrifying image
People killing themselves at their work
It's Bleak it's relatable
It's very resonant with the audience
The people who may not totally love their job
For some context though
History about gnats
Hits from 2011
Analysis specifically leaving out the part of that story where in division 2
Installing bed nets
Foxconn
Responded to a rash of suicides by raising the wages
Employees which is one of the motivation
Described
People who jumped off the roof
Alex has been repeated the story as if it's
Current 48
Years
Meanwhile from 2012 to the present
Four employees have killed themselves
What is the Foxconn Factory that Alex is talking about
Which is 40
But let's try and put this in perspective
The Foxconn Factory is not like most factories that we imagine
It's f****** gigantic
With the staff
10 times the size of the largest
It's factory in the United States
According to Business Insider they employee about
Thousand people
Which is approximately 40,000 more people than live in St Louis
Id2020 1743 people killed themselves
So you look at numbers of
Prairie
In 2016 291 people kill themselves at the workplace
The United States
To do in terms of work
We have our own problems at home that we should be addressing to
And I've never heard Alex bring up us
Workplace suicide
Ever
Similarly I've never heard him talk about France Telecom
Which had more than
60 employees commit suicide
2020-11
That's far more than the number of people who killed them
Themselves
So the rate is
We hire
Not because he's covering it up
Because he doesn't care
Just no reason to attack of French phone
Evocative image from news
From 8 years ago
And he uses it daily as a weapon to attack the people
Perceived as his enemies
Demanded they solve an issue
You keep doesn't caribou
And knows that the only real solution to his
Regulate business
Would you super against
It's a trick
He's playing a trick
What is audience
By appealing to the emotion
Reasonably rightfully should be evoked the idea of a factory putting up
Next to stop people
Killer dubstep
He's using that as a
Trick
Yeah it almost seems like he's mad that
They're killing themselves
Like the factory should be coming here in our worker should be certainly wouldn't be
Exactly
Who cares about the working
Conditions of China
Factory employees
It's just an easy way for him to attack Google
And it's definitely not the reason why he's attacking Google
Tonight is motivation
When you hear make the argument that no one will criticize
Tim Cook for the Chinese factor
Because he's gay
That is an attack on Tim Cook
Specifically because he
He's gay
He's basically saying that his
Elevated status to a heterosexual
And that's complete s***
I'll still be very clear that Foxconn and everybody else needs to do a better job for their workers
You can accept that is 80
True thing
I'm still cold this order bulshit out
And here's why that's important
Cook is literally the first Fortune 500 CEO to be openly gay
Fortune 500 published
Since 19
Tim Cook
CEO in 2011 in
Come out until 20
That's a good 69 here's where representation
Zip for young
Aspiring LG
TQ business
There was no 12.2 instinct
I could be long in that boardroom
And I'm not just assuming that's the case
That's the reason he
He came out in 2014
In an interview with CNN cook describes out there good rumors about a sec
His life private until
Started to receive
Letters
We've been bullied
Because of their orientation
And he realized it would be
Be quote selfish
For him to keep quiet when being public good help those
Despite the problems with apple and there are many to choose from
This is what Alex is attacking about
Tim Cook
In the same way that young lgbtq
You could kids could be moved by their identity reflected in the eeo-1 the biggest companies in the world
Alex he's back to
Threatened by
So ultimately what I'm saying is f*** Alex Jones
He's a small-minded bigot
Completely obsessed with his Petty battle
I should also point out that the Infowars app was never number one
Who's number one in the trending category
The day after he got kicked off all the social media platforms
But it's
Disgusting
See the sort of thing flies under the radar
Of just his eyes out being stupid
But you start to see
This is an attack on somebody
He thinks get special
If that's what he's mad about
The factory
No
If I were in his position as heterosexual CEO ever would be mad at me but never give them the path
That's rank homophobia
Right
When you're used to being the protective glass with the highest
Status
Any other class
Raised up
Makes these people feel like stuff is being
I'm taking away for
Zero Sum game
Approach to
Yeah so she
Social capital
This
White National
Homophobic b*******
Is always going
Dehumanize any achievements
But in the Reconstruction Era
One of these
Operating philosophy
As long as the
Horus
Most worthless white person
Feels like they're better than the richest
Most successful black person
Then we will always
Like that kind of
That kind of
For Alex
As long as
As long as the gayest
Cor the most
Festival games
Rolling hitch
Worse than any straight person
Act with impunity
I suppose there's
There's probably something
Have you operate
Live by
Sort of
That's it
Is what he's responding
Continue
It's okay
What the China 2 years ago
I want to censor everything
But
He's gay
As long as
When I hear stuff like that
I question
Again
Does he think this is funny
What is this
Comedy on his
Who's that I don't know
It's real bad but I
How you get this
Yeah I don't know
It's really hard to tell cuz
Well if you thinks rainbow smash
Who the f*** knows
Exactly
It's sad that
Completely foreign
Sense of humor
Very difficult striped cave
Nonsense of humor as
Hubert bright
Tons of stand-up specials where I'll just watch it at
I don't
Where what is happy
It's possible that he
That's funny
Still doesn't excuse
Apple business
Just real quick
We went to f***
Town on Tim Cook whatever the
Search
Censorship
Leaking it all that s*** every
Justified criticism
The political wire
Shielding of him because he's gay
Yeah I always think it's over
I'm glad you bring that up because it is important but it almost feels like
Taking is red
Listening to it going like
Cannot be pointed out enough
That we went
Absolutely insane on him to the point where it's the project
Very least slow down
Like if it work for us
Alex's imagine that f****** super censorship thing would probably still be going on
Yeah
Spliff Alex
Instead of Tim Cook for a little bit
Anza
Gohan incest Omar
What
Oh my God
Aisha
Let's play some audio
Walnut
Brain
Maryland
I'm not sure
Cheap
Walnut Bryan
So yeah that's that's
A lot of s***
You got over all these dumb
Conspiracies about lawn Omar
Jacob Wohl Laura Loomer
Try to make a documentary
Proving her brother or whatever
No idea
Blew up in their faces
Disaster
The other stuff
Between Alexandria ocasio-cortez in the Holocaust
Museum
Comments as much as they reaffirmed their lungs
Position that the music
These camps where children are being abused
Reported that is some kind of a takedown by the Holocaust Museum
How many ran the headline
Build us Holocaust Museum releases rare statement on concentration camp
But the statement isn't really rare
They put out a press release
December 2018 same exact
Same thing
Dick a little bit into the topic and
You find plenty of Representatives of the museum as well as other Scholars
They're strongly
People making analogies between
The past or present
Compared to what happened
They're living
Like Godwin's law is it that one
That anytime an argument
Get to
Comparison
Hitler is over
Is that guy
Partially that impartially just like it's just
Respectful to the experience
So the people who died to use it as a
To compare something that you don't like to
Absolutely absolutely
That position
I also think that it's not necessarily disrespectful the people who died in the Holocaust to
Notes
Similarity
Disrespectful way to do it but I do appreciate the Holocaust Museum
Like I don't think it's
Home can be through I'm right there with you
Alex brings
The number 9
Hero
James O'Keefe
He's on the show
In this clip I just wanted to illustrate like
How
Cool J
You couldn't get better
Descriptors for the names of the Departments if you want to
Remember that movie re-edits out all the newspaper at Ministry of Truth
He thinks the 1984 is primarily a movie
Eunos Orwell
Haha
I feel like that's the trend with these guys
You think they're not voracious readers did I think they might take
Kid most of their information
From YouTube videos
What do you call it
Depictions of books in movie form
So that's great
They really love
Bill Murray The Razor's Edge
Could not pronounce
This is
This interview is just James O'Keefe
Describing
What happened
And in his 25 minutes
And there's some justice
Applications
Explanation
And realizes the most
Anthony gets a little defensive
What about it
This is a conspiracy theory
If it weren't for the documents
And what are the documents you gave me says I'm going to quote them this is Google
Not you it says
It says quote
Training media are.
People Like Us are programmed
People
Like us
Our program
So
The supposed whistleblower released
The project Veritas about 120 pages of
Internal
Basically it all just boils down to something along the lines of
Didn't realize that our platform was so easily exploitable by people looking
The profit off weaponized
And now that we do we should probably do something about it
Diva be responding to
And the other stuff is but we'll get in
One image
Coup de gras
It shows a flowchart representing a process of how
Conscious bias can affect our decisions
It's what he was just reading what are you just quoted
Is a string of a flowchart
It's not a list of things it's that
People Like Us are program
Which O'Keeffe presented is that being the
Reflective Google's goal
Incontact
This isn't the flowchart that shows Google's brainwashing
It's a slide in a PowerPoint for the
About the interaction between human and put in AI
In terms of algorithm
Creation
Just after this flight
The presentation
And unfortunately we humans have a history of making product design decision
Veteran line with
Default
And not with the needs
Of everyone
The week program thing isn't the result
It's discussing a problem
It arises from
Consciously accepting default ideas that are danger
The presentation goes on to elucidate how the program this problem
Discussant have female drivers
47% more likely to be hurt
Car accident
Because crash dummies were all based on male body types until 2011
Another thing that's important
Slide PowerPoint presentation
Should be accompanied by a speech
This is bullet points that are by definition out of context
Without the full presentation
Intentionally dishonest
Yeah I'm from their own document
Yeah it's like it's like a facial recognition technology doesn't
Would like
Doesn't recognize black people
Cuz they only tested on
There's so many of those like emotion
But I am
Video game systems
Instant film
Spotlight
Baton of stuff like
Algorithmic
Which is going to come up I believe in this
Next
Yeah
So
Here is
James O'Keefe
Because
He's on the show
Why not
Nemours
Still carrying this is incredible
They're their words not their words not yours they say
Is because people are not putting that Line in the Sand
So we're like
Nice sayings
So what
She does talk about that
Manipulative
Captured
Booty talking about is
When you take what she's talking about the Trump situation
Do not be Trump
Running ABV
The interference and manipulation of algorithms in
Gaming system
When she say that like you shouldn't break us up
It would be a bad idea
Companies
That are less able to deal with that
Manipulation
Maybe.
Don't break us up we could stop Trump from winning
He's also discussing that to Jen I said that known as drawing a Line in the Sand
And that's the Google's big companies
He's completely misrepresenting which
Clearly talk about
A lot of this week
Totally clear if you actually read the documents
The project Veritas released along with
A lot of information in there actually debunked
Everything that James okay
Not a surprise
Those documents is more like a movie
You don't need to worry about what's actually
Is this enough for everybody
So that no one's drawing
Is there
Is a lot of AI and machine learning
No searches for quotes
Yo brought up all mail images
Or weather
If you search for wedding it would bring up exclusively White
There's a bias
Come from data
When it's left out
These are bad
Those example
Instances where this phenomenon became
Foundry much more
In 2015
A black man uploaded a photo of
Consultant
And the AI labeled image of gorillas
A 2013 a researcher found that if you searched
Girls the results were disproportionately more likely to be
Pornography
A study in 2015 found that ads for high-salary jobs play study
Times of India website we're being shown
Typically to mail users
These are the sort of
Instances of Honor
Fairness
People like Jen
Tonight we're discussing
And working to resolve
You can find an article on the standard from December of last year where she
Discussing
Particularly in Redford
Words to a study from a harbor
Who found the quote
When you search
Black sounding name arrests related ads
The fair
To all other parts
Google's product
Specifically was working on product project
Related to speech recognition
How could someone with an accent
Get full use of
Speech recognition
Product
How about some
Speech impediment or a stutter
These are the sorts of concerns for her career as it relates to fairness
Can anyone get a cursory amount of research it
This would know that that's what
James O'Keefe
Is trying to misrepresent
If it's clear as day
Yeah but you look into it would you read the documents
You do a little bit of look
Other than the last 24 hours
What imprint does Jen Jen I have on the internet
Find what you was working on before find out what context clues you can have
For this casual conversation that you
Surreptitiously record
What might
Bring to that conversation that you're not allowing
2xist
Your footage
And it disorder
And I think it's an admiral
Google that idea of it
You shouldn't
Have
Algorithm
That would you search for black girls it's all pornography
That is not a pleasant for a good experience for black girls
Well
Specifically
Just
Confronting
The most
Terrifying
Exposing their own
Implicit biases
Is far more than the
Because if you have to actually
Wrestle with the idea with that very idea
Why does the algorithm
Amplify
Implicit bias
Cuz that's really what it's kind of doing
Right there is amplifying that implicit that's Tobias
Stop for 1 second
If you have to add that into your
Calculus
How could you not extrapolate from that so much
Just for you to say for one second
Girl and all I got was p***
How that limits
Automatically without even considering Catalyst for
Yeah and it's
Trade is
Yeah absolutely
Google Documents
They're discussing like that 47% of
Or 4747
A cyborg
Because of
Crash Test Dummies being modeled after
If there's even a slide in there that's like
Now where are those people who designed the Christ
And that's exactly
The same thing is true for so many medications
That aren't like if it's not specifically made for women
At the testing is almost overwhelmingly done on men
So
They're so clearly Liars
And this is too
Clearly a publicity
Once you
Peel back the the top layer of
Okay this is all
Probably just Dubai
Do you start to have to ask yourself like
Now why would you
Do you do that
Very
Self-serving
Secondarily self-serving reason
All there
Right in front of you on Apple
So
Yourself James O'Keefe
Lucky you're not prison for the past
You're not in prison
The world
Oh yeah
Sleeves
And the Alex
Keep saying he's going to play Special Report
I need ends up doing that he does like
Special Report
No I don't I don't know if you get to bound
No bounds joints
I think he's just kind of done
Adidas
I really
Did it yesterday
I was legendary yesterday
Cover this project Veritas videos
Very excited about it
Has h a good enough
People with Wachusett
Espresso reports
He's got to
Dehumanize
Democratic field
A little bit
Infowars.com show
She's doing a two nights
Tacular
About the Democratic
Switch OB
Fuckingawesome
I would like
Cockroaches
With chat
Again has a nice lady at
Swell
Pastor political discourse
Generally
We had a couple clips
Laughed
Wanted 2nd episode on
Episode
Maybe a little bit of a
Upward
What is a better head
Instead we got a couple clips of Alex
Yelling about a lot of r
Know this first one
Is
I pretty much just him calling her ugly
That's better than what I
Fake love
I'm pulling up next Airship I'm planning on whether sex slaves in Somalia
So he plays like maybe
3 seconds of a clip
But he has to interrupt the clipboard even plays the part you want
But she's got a wheel.
I mean
We know from going back to
Flavor of the Somali pirate
Somali pirate imagery to
Demonize her because she's
From Somalia
Which is b*******
Deeply coded
Encoded
Ugly
All this stuff is just like
You are
Really really
Really triggered by this non-white
Tacos
That's all bulshit to but like
Sharia law being thrown off building
South Alex could be more clear
I can't
Stress it enough
How unpleasant it was the jarring
Disconnect between Sunday and Monday
And even both of those episodes are disconnected
Everything else that's been happy
There is no sense
Continuity
Between any of these apis
They could almost all exist
The point
From like years ago
Papago
Breaking Bad X-Files monster the week Dan you don't need
Serialized
I guess stylistic lie I don't really have a problem
It's it's hard to track
A little bit and maybe it would be better served by like we do an episode just about Sunday
There's no development of narratives
There's nothing that's like
Okay I talked about the 5G
West Virginia on Sunday
There's nothing
Just like starting over
Desperate
And really talk
Not the other thing about it though
Is
I'm noticing
I probably pointed this out but it always bears
Alex is almost everyday
Trying to go
Get someone hurt
This wasn't the case
Before
Responsible and Reckless with his language
ABC in 2013
Him being a real stupid dumb prick
But
The consistency and the regularity with which
Seems to be
Specifically
Trying to get people hurt
Whether it's the targeting of Jen Jenai buddies tag team
This is dangerous to her safety
Or the people of this
This is where you can go hunt globalist
Once the ship goes down
Like every single day there is somebody that is being put in danger by Alex
The show
I don't know if it rises to the level of like
Jamming signal
I don't think it does I don't I don't know what that would require
This trend is
Important for people to be aware of
Is that it
It's important to note that pretty much everyday
Something has the potential
To go so wrong
Haha well he's been on air 25 years
Are you only used to try and get somebody hurt every years
And then it was every month or so
The quickening
Jesus what
Man I just don't know how you can
Say all that s*** about Eliana Oma
Without the self-awareness
To know that everything that you said is
Completely and utterly race
Beyond
She probably does
There's just nothing there but him trying to say
I'm trying to insult her in anyway
You possibly can without a coming out in
I'm just saying I don't like a brown woman in
It makes me scared
I think it's important
To not be public
Seeing as aware of
But
You can't be publicly aware of the fact that the documents
You released contradict his claims
Publicly aware of
The fact that is videos.
He says they do
Yeah
Publicly aware of how racist
Otherwise the whole game
Busted
Becomes
Another
Racist
Videos
They're all playing
Game of
Intentional
Possible deniability
Ignorance
In order to
Maintain
Perpetuate the con
It is
Boring
Yeah it is it is
Disappointment anytime you hear that
I'm going to make as many personal
Insults as I can
Can't towards you I'm going to be a
As cruel as possible
Towards you so I don't
To stop and think
Why don't I want
The brown woman in
Yeah or why do I not want to
Learn anything more about Dallas
I am trying argue that
She's a donkey pissing on you
Just a shortcut
Thinking about it I find
Tim Cook stuff
More offensive
Because he
He's hiding it behind
Something that is a
Illegitimate credit
And turning a little criticism
Of a fox
Criticism
Universal
Business Insider article about going to that factory in 20
And they talked to a ton of employees
The watch giraffe
You know it's the other fact
It's just
Drum pad work
I'm not I'm not saying working conditions are all good everywhere
Specific
Complained that he has
Is so much more relevant
The past that he's not been updated
Condition
And the issue with that for me is
He is
Behind
There's nothing
And so it's almost it's almost inoffensive and it's
And how pathetic
Mistake that
Just in
It's just so obvious
It's like oh you just don't like a
A brown woman in charge
Like you've got nothing
You're blinded by your bigotry and islamophobia
Congratulations
If you didn't have the narrative from 7 years ago
How to tell
He built up this suicide net
Narrative years ago
And he just has it in his Hip Pocket to pull out whenever
Tim Cook or a apple comes up
Right
Yeah
This episodes worth it if we are
Because we learn how to post
I just liked I liked
Telescopes
I need to know where they are
Go down to Greenbank that sounds awesome
Pretty fuggin.
Even for me who cannot leave his phone anywhere further than five
From heaven
Hell yeah
Another episode but until we have website
We are on Twitter
We are on Facebook and you can also download our podcast
Overcast
Sure
Through certain
Species of
Tulip specifically for supper so hard to grow
Oh well
So as we come to the end
Probably has
Is Alex Jones
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color