Galaxy color with huge fan I love your work
Little bit about Alex Jones
Left behind
Tom and Jerry
Yeah I think so
It's like Harry Potter but I thought they were trash I was in that
Evangelical
I thought they were a little bit stupid
My dad is a religious studies professor
So
Later
Because I was going through my dad
I wasn't going through their house but I was in their house
The first one he had a copy of The DaVinci Code
Copy of
I left behind
Not the book I think it was a copy of the DVD
Collector's edition
What do you have
Company that made it apparently
For him
Hoping to get like a a blurb or something I think
Without losing
QuickBooks
Send things really hard for my parents
To get rid of
Yeah go to bookstores in only like books otherwise I would be covered
House fire
My house burned down years ago I ate a giant Library bus I told myself I was going to rebuild it
Yeah and then afterwards I do
I just realized like
These are kind of empowerment
Then I would like
Whatever
Pics of a lot of space
Baltimore
Selective of what books
What I just
Find PDFs on Kindle
Kiryu
Do fetishize
Actual books
There's something very funny about that
So beautiful
Tactile
Absolutely
Mouthfeel for a book mouthfeel for a
A lot of books
His bulge
Correct
We're going back to the past
Because I want to tell you this
I wanted to stay in the present
It's an exciting time for Alex Jones right now in 2019
But I realized after our last episode the pretty much the next week
Going to just be him talking about that project Veritas Google video
I think I said about all I need
Need to say about it on our last episode
More time going over him yelling about it
Not a lot of value
In our 2013 investigation
Going over what Alex in the aftermath of
15th of February
If you'll recall on our last installment Alec
Wattpad started to turn a little bit of a corner
Call Christopher Doran
I'm nothing if not a broadcaster
Chris daughter died
He killed himself on
The 12th Alex started
To compare
A situation of his death
The Galaxy
Is very
Super cool
You love
The Branch Davidians
He said the government that killed them
So I'm comparing daughter to Waco is
Is big deal
Like that's something that indicates the position
Bartow
Very interested to
Where things go on
I will find out but first
Supporting the show and make this whole thing possible
Mike so much yarnall policy wonk
Nick
Thank you so much
Next Jamie Lee
You're a no-show policy walk
Relieve menstrual
Curtis
Okay
Spears sisters
Tammy leaves Ruby Lin
I don't know
Anyway you donated on elevated level
Appreciate that very much
Heroin
Freakishly large
I'm finally go to say thank you
Today we have up for sale
We can't express our appreciation
So very much everybody should check out
Twitter
Artist
Novartis
Zella in the hospital
Yeah la artists
Right La artists
Lar
Largest
Nrsv
There's only one way
Express
We have
And that is to declare eular
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites Italy
How to read
Control
I bet you money are few living black people
Abused
Joseph Stalin
Welcome to McDonalds may I help you
Reckon so much lower your incredible today
We are here
We are getting into it
We're down to the
February 4th
Valentine's Day
I don't know
Neither of us are Valentine's days
Supporters
It feels like it's Valentine's Day I don't know
If that's one of those like Thanksgiving is always on a specific number or the Thursday at
After the honestly don't know Valentine's Day
For all the Christie
Oceans of the world
Where are Christians
Disagree
Slough
I would like to direct Alex's
Come to the
Christian
That's a pretty good the debunker
Because what he's doing is try to universalize
You know there's nothing
Necessarily
Terroristic of how Christianity or anything like that but that's a group.
Is the
Described are the things that somebody says
Right before they become a terrorist
You know we're working 17 hours a day
We need to stop this
Federal Building
Like all the people Judy
Pretends were set up
So
Real slow start to the 14th
February 14th
Episode
From the beginning of it's a full Clips out of
Because
Decided to take this opportunity to this clip
So much of the words
Salad
To make his point
Nothing in this
Text clip is saying
Okay but it's the sort of thing to populate
So much of his
Spelling
Response
Normalcy
Cowardly
Such a good indication of just like
I'm swinging from the monkey bars I do not know where my next needs to go next is there a
Learned helplessness Overton Window hours
Jewel Osco dogs are everywhere
Is anybody
The what Alex's do cuz he's hungry
Froot Loops that says 1 + 1 equals 5
I think what it has to do with is like 1 and 1 are Fruit Loops and milk and then 5 is
Like 5 nutrition
Spell fruit
I'll tell you why the globalist trying to dumb down the population it sounds
So at some point
Do some actual issues and he starts talking about Christopher
This point I think
Is there a badger
Yeah especially with his rhetoric
Run SO3
Through the coverage of
Hey man you think this is bad
Yeah see what happens
I feel like that line of rhetoric is not good
Kind of worse
What
So he's giving advice on how to kill more cops
Justifying on air
Anybody who doesn't actually want to commit a math terrorist attack doesn't already
Know that
That doesn't help
He seemed so he thought a lot about killing cops that's what we read a lot of books
About the
What was really interesting about that is Alex is almost taken offense
The idea that people are saying
Trained
Almost as if to say like
Now our guys are trained
Is there some
Is there some reason
Like
You guys haven't
A Praying are crazy
It's almost like
The very fact that you
At him
Means that you wasn't good enough
I think
Disappearance
Yeah it's it's more of a
Threat
I think it's
Brag
But okay
The first one
Is there a guy who is
Alright I guess does he have a tail
He doesn't have telescope that I know of but here's Alex
Available I should add
Infowars.com
What is going on
So he's got this guy
Dr. Cory gold
Spokesperson
There is no other
You seem to have him on the show
Alex is presenting
Are you heard it as someone who lives in Southern California
Millions of people live in California
Easily talk to
He's a syndicated radio host
You look to station
He is not a big time radio host no expertise in the area that Alex's
Talk about
This is just a shoehorn infomercial for youngevity
Which is what the interview ends of deteriorating into because of course
The only reason he's on the show
Stretching
So far to make it relevant like
Oh yeah we got to
Guy without California give us the dirt on what it's like California
Crazy there's there's over
Sew-in ethical
Because it just does he doesn't have much
To say about the daughter situation with
It's not already like
If he's read an article
And he's repeating what's in an article
Which doesn't make him the most
Expert
His Dentistry doesn't seem relevant
I don't know if you're wasn't killed by a giant
So don't know what Dentistry is going to
Come into this
Here is the indication of how things
Do this
This is really
How the interviewer
So it's kind of
Yeah yeah that's not Great Britain that he's dumb b******* about that subsection
Sarcastically
Not plugging
Youngevity
Long stretches where they're like
Presumably
Talking about it in service of the news
Just talk about how great the product
Crazy it's embarrassing
Embarrassed
Yeah to behave like this
Alex
It is
So interesting you bring that up
Because I've still relevant to Alex
Alex
Talk
Probably some connection
But
Here he brings up who his next guy
Evidence goes back to his
Piers Morgan obsession
Can a little bit but
Joseph
So Alex is pretending
Don't talk much about the Piers Morgan stuff
Ludacris we talked about it all the f****** time
But he wants to
Joseph Farah what do you think
I do not
Joseph Perez the founder of WorldNetDaily
One of the absolute worst large-scale news sites online and what about
What is MainSource
Information
History the real interest
Subject
Possibly one that I would love to get into much more deeply on another day
I meant to do a deep dive on his
Stupidity and how he found his way to WorldNetDaily only after running multiple other outlets out of business
How fair is directly responsible for
For Trump's birther claims
And maybe even
Debra chance to look into the trim
They're clearly on display when you look at the books that WorldNetDaily
Chooses to publish
But my research went off track just a little bit
When I ran into a salon article
It dovetails into what you were just saying
About Shane
World
7 and 4 years very similar position in Media
Crazy s*** about them
Conserve depressed
Wouldn't
They floated
Conspiracy theories a traffic jam explicit
Coded bigotry
But now
In 2019 they are falling a
Hey much the same way Alex
Businesses
Both of these organization
Explain but their downfall is being caused by an oppressive company
Because their message
Just too dangerous
But this Salon article written by Amanda Marcotte
Makes a really interesting
Point
No one cares about WorldNetDaily in Infowars anymore
Because Fox News is now doing what they used to do
But with a better budget and more access
The talent
As the article says quote
Conservative audiences want to wallow in fantasy world where women have abortions for fun
Coming to kill you
Globalist to running elaborate secretive conspiracies
Bastille America from white people
No longer have to turn to WorldNetDaily
With its subpar web design and often incomprehensibly written article
The conspiracy theories
His paranoia those audience
Served up in a slick
Professional style at Fox News
In the mouths of supposedly reputable pundits like Tucker Carlson
And Sean Hannity
Supposedly
Whatever the matter of perspective
But that's a really good point
Years Joseph
Crucial role in the
Motorcycle
They drove tons of votes to right-wing candidates but they really only
Useful as long as
People in power never acknowledge them
As soon as politician
Particularly Trump
Began trying to trying to help the public become more
Who's only a matter of time before world that has started
Actual cop
Petition pop-up
It really appears that neither of them were up to the challenge
Ultimately what you have with Joseph Farah is a
Debbie loser who found a really profit
People nice in a market that most people have
Too much dignity to
Then Along Came
Lower the bar of what
Dignified so far
The people who would previously have been ashamed to traffic and Ferris brand of b*******
Found themselves
The position where was no longer career suicide to roll
That shitt
What little thing. It's not about Trump
Confero 2011 when Trump was getting
Obama's birth certificate
Literally call Joseph Farah and then WorldNetDaily employee Jerome corsi
Quote looking for affirmation that he was on the right track
Sarah told the New York Times that he was impressed
But how many hours Trump was willing to put in
To the birth
Knox
It's like
How Alex
Served by
Anti-semite
Out-and-out anti-semites
Saying that he's
Acceptable mainstream
Alex
Probably
Do that
In the same way that Fox News used to ignore that
Now that they didn't have it at
Just fine they like
Cool because now.
Because of that
Because of the phenomenon
It's happening
Where what Alex used to do is being done better
Fox News and other
More heavily funded Outlets
The Overton window shift
So far that's alright guys it's cool now
Baltimore overt white mask
Nationalism
Privacy
White identity ideas
Express things that he probably would have been
Not interested
Years ago now
What is Vine
He would speak in code vac then whereas now there is a
Real
Real f****** trend
And I think I think it's just because he's suffering
Do those
Beneath the surface ugly
Things
Skis just
Lower on the totem
Quarry Gold's not a good gas but Joseph has like a big deal
Conservative media
Like he's he's a he's a guy who runs WorldNetDaily
That's a
Install
Circles
Can we just acknowledge that we're listening to an episode
In 2000
+ 13
Kill 1.6
6 billion tops
Man in the good old days
Hypothetical
What are on here
That are
That's someone who never come on now
Fast-forward to the present
Count dankula
The level of
You talkin to
I guess if I were to describe him
I would like to do more about him and I would have loved to do that today
Another f****** a
The show
Decided we'll get to it later I would say
He is
Alex Jones
With a mustache
Runza media operation
The radio show
Operation
That is
Surfing almost identical inter
They pitch similar story
Alex uses them as a source all
It's basically
It's two guys who are in League with each other
In a pop like a propaganda ping pong
Quote on quote
Telenovela
It doesn't matter which one has the mustache
Yes that would be
That would be fair
Sophie is about to come up on the
Michelle
Alex
Yes come back from
Commercial
About a commercial that you
Play gentleman is our of broadcast is brought to you by The Squatty Potty
Are you sponsoring I'm sorry
This is just trying to reinforce my new thesis but Alex thinks poop
Is hilarious
Years old
What activity
You love's f******
Humor
It's crazy
Almost never here
Sincere or Genuine last man that doesn't involve fecal matter
Crazy
Weird so
Sarah
His interview
The real
Troubling things
Because this is the first thing you hear
From Joseph
Situations
Takeouts
I don't know that's
From him
From now from Farah
That's pretty f***** up like Alex's bringing up this
This situation
Itsfunneh well I mean
Is it correct
Human response
Like a James Bond song
There's a little bit too upsetting
That's a really all that interesting their positions on
The situation it doesn't there's no real development
There's no
Nothing
Fresh
But
His next clip Alex is trying
About Chris Kyle
The American Sniper guy who had just been murdered
Like a week prior
And it turns out I don't think the Joseph Farah nose hoop
How is
Chris Kyle sniper
Why
Well yeah I mean that you know is surrounded
Well I mean
Cinema Stratford
WinCo
Ruby Ridge back in the day
He thinks he's talking about Chris Jordan
He doesn't recognize
Sniper register
But does go on to
It's like Waco which makes me think
I think this might be something as it is
Universal investor Alex Jones world
Propaganda
Especially if they could have had their own pre-production
The night before
Is this a lot like Waco
Who knows if they did or didn't
Probably didn't but it does seem like a
You know at least Joseph Farah has a like
A little
Nothing else really work
Recovering in it
So we're going to jump
I'll get to the point
Where Alex starts
Real
Winners in
In the color category
We have
Oh okay we have of course old man house phone
Starting to recognize
As like real regular folks
And I've heard this dude before but I don't know
Anyting
I don't remember when
But I've heard this f****** guy on the show before
It is soon as I heard his voice
The point is
General Colin Powell
Black people
Alex thinks it's funny that he's got this old racist color
Future responsibilities agitating the black
So
Call Beth
Oh man
Living in a world where is
I'm going to have this dude on my radio
I'm going to let him get away with calling him General Colin Powell
Alright
And then just go
He's agitating the Negroes and nobody's like hitting those
Nobody's doing that
Nobody's bothered by that
It's hilarious it's just a nice little fun jaunt down memory lane
Old white people
There's a little bit of cold water
Colon polyps
Is a different person
Is he referencing someone I am not aware of Noah turns out Colin Powell
School is really interesting is it Alex
And then it's interesting to me how he respond
Because
Next clip you see very clearly
Outwardly agree with this guy
Alex isn't this very well
Weird
Space
You can't
Fight with the guy who sang something really racist
If he agrees that means like yeah he is
The black
Then it becomes
Gotcha
Get dance
What's today
The whites
Mueller
I don't want to check his stool specimen
It's just I've reached a point
Hilarious
Grocery store
In the world
He just shows up on the guy by party some more
Because he realizes
These impact like a no-win situation
He doesn't want to overly agree with the public
Well whenever he makes that little
In your likes
You know what word
That you don't you you stopped you started it and you're like I don't want that to be coming out of my mouth
But not much
I think
Right-thinking people
Like that as erring on the side of the
You on your radio show and you refused
Hey now
That means
You are at least tacitly
Or explicitly supporting the races position
Is expressing
So
I think that's what's going on
Whatever
You know
But what I think is really fast
Is what's revealed by this next caller
Business
Devastating
Alex's presume credibility
Thank you
I just wanted to share
Are you familiar with
Was Gregor Mendel
Gregor Mendel
Now tell me about it
Wow first one who's made his whole career railing against
The eugenicist globalist
And how the hell all these ideas about breeding and natural selection
Gregor Mendel
How embarrassing is that
All the way to Community College freshman biology
Bring up his education
On the 15th
We'll get to that
That is disqualified
I understand if you're like I don't
Know a specific thing about his
Diyexperiment or something like that
Caller calls in
And he's like hey do you know about Gregor Mendel and you like no tell me about it
You don't know shitt
Have all the information at his disposal
But to be caught off-guard by call her bringing-up Mendel is like
You don't know dick
Pac-Man
Nuts
Unacceptable
Particularly unacceptable because his enemies are you done
What makes
That would be like
If someone came up to me and was like
Do you know who John Birch
Tell me about it
Like I am I study Alex Jones who be insane for me to not know
Some of the spiritual precursors
Fights against the global
Do not know where
Like the ideas
Underlie eugenics
Come from
The birth of genetics
Concept
Mendelevium
Bingo
Also I will kick your ass and your family
Conor McGregor Mendes
Thank you very much
Before and after
One of my favorite song that was Helen of Troy Aikman
Strong work
Jeopardy
Who launched a thousand ships
So I thought this caller's voice was
Familiar to
But I couldn't quite place
Until he said
I myself am a Pioneer research scientist Gregor Mendel
The GMOs
Realize
So Isaac near research where we heard that before
He called in on the January 8th from my when you called then when Mike Adams with Coho
Hosting the show
Doctor Winfield I just want to say it's really a pleasure sir
Be talking to you
I myself actually I'm one of America's few remaining Pioneer research scientist
I have no idea what that means I tried to look into it too
Is some sort of a real designation something
It's not it's just a general term
I don't know
I love it I love I love the idea with listening to the show
Cast of peripheral characters keep calling in
Old man house phone
Erase the sky
It really indicates to me that the pool of colors is
Much smaller
Then it appears
There's just a lot of people that you
You kind of forget
For people who aren't they
Distinctive enough
In their nonsense
That you is that guy didn't say I'm a Pioneer sign
Dentist right I wouldn't remember that he called in
A month previous
Because you know what you can't ever forget
Somebody's mouth
Yeah I think it was an avalanche
Frontier psychiatrist
A researcher at Frontier psychiatrist
I don't know I don't know
That's what it means
Fireside get this crazy on the Coco
Maybe
One of the focuses that I'm going to have moving forward is like
Really trying to keep track of these callers
I would love it if
Let's say this podcast
And I end up needing to find a new project
Right I think a great thing to do would be try and find some
Scholars
I would love to talk to the Pioneer scientist
I think old racist man is probably dead
I would like
Corey be tough to get ahold of
Seems like
I did try and find him but it's very difficult to Google Bible damn
If Daniel is a book in the Bible
And Pioneer scientist
The back by itself
2013 in the field of genetics
Is a really good designation
Yeah yeah
He doesn't have much to say about the issue
Doesn't really understand how
We're just kind of moved on
We kind of expanded a little bit past Ike's
He's not interested
He's interested in
Pioneers
So
Dude here's what
Interesting about looking back at this stretch
Showtime
Like if I were just
To tell you earlier
You would have
No idea what happened
Right
The World's End
That's early
Ensure
December
Huge news
Go little bit further through and you know the doerner situation is that was a huge
And here's another one
I forgot happened probably
In February
That is huge
This was
Awakening transmission
Going on
I mean
We don't really know how often
Get the yard
Few hours ago
Prisonplanet.com
Large asteroid
Tear
Because
Waves
Different job
Sound barriers
Broken
Absolutely
Larger question is
Part of a spur
Because watch movie Armageddon
So what's going on
Do you remember this this was the is this one in Russia
Oh this is a difference
Meteor asteroid
Government saying
Uno's
15 million
It was very close
Relatively but it wasn't
What is near Earth object about how much
To his credit
Absol this point
Has been
Pretty on the side of
Nothing to worry about
The government are liars but don't worry about it isn't going to hit
Now on the 15th
Another object
Flew over Russia
Videos of it it's pretty
Pretty amazing
Piece of a meteor
And actually made it through the atmosphere
Kill anybody
But it did end up
Injuring like 1,000
People in town in Russia
And so
Because it happened on the same day
That this other
Near-earth object
Was going to make its closest pass okay Alex has combined
I've been saying
That it's not going to hit us but maybe it is
Can cover or what's it what's his
Prescription for
Not getting murdered
It's really weird because it's been really like Nan
Sensational just like
You're the closest
Something's ever come but it's nothing to be
Be concerned about
And I was like
This is how
Happened
In Russia
What is it
What's it going to be
Is easy going to go Y2K on us
What's the
I wasn't sure
It's interesting to see
See how this develops
Because it's
Irresponsible I would say
Shrikes
Thanks a million years or so
Large asteroid
Extinction
Nope
Large stone blocks
Who this so much
It's a problem there
Other meteor strike
People of uncover
Less common than it is
But it's
You know it happened
Right I've actually
So many little tiny things that fall all over the place
Because no damage no one even notices like
Little miniscule things
Basically
What he's doing is turning black nose
Never happen
Atlantis used to be around
Yeah yeah
That doesn't make any sense
Is that is that
If like 1/100 of it
Fall into Earth
We would all event
The entire Earth would have been
Just
Destroyed completely
Nuclear
Game Change
Right but I mean that's no good for selling
Bible food it's too late if you're already on the same day
But it does help to
Even if
It does help to
Just create that feeling
Yeah
I can do that
I would say that it's kind of erroneous
To say the Play-Doh was a
Historian
Is Pliny the Elder Oliver
Josephus
There's some historians you can
Good bullfrog
Be comfortable calling
Play-Doh
Historian
Sure he's a storical figure
And also I mean we go over this all the time
Something I really enjoy
Play-Doh didn't discuss it as if it was,
If anything is presented in
Dialogues
Prettiest
Emmaus
Secret information grandfather after so long
Went to Egypt
The elders there who told him about it
So if Alex Jones
Bright
This next B2 think is where it starts
Beer from
Insinuation
Towards
Little sensation
A little more than I wanted
Frost the closest to any asteroid
Eastern Standard Time Eastern
Closest to the earth
Recorded
Enter Raleigh for 5 hours
Prisonplanet.com
Absolutely
Drudgereport.com it also has about 015 story
We're reporting on
Down a meteor coming
Thousand plus miles an hour
So what's interesting about that is that Alex is reporting on
Theories floating around that Russia shot it down but that theory is posted on his website
Him saying I don't believe that Russia shot down
Brother f****** story on your website about the theory floating around that it
Paul Joseph Watson has a theory that
No Joseph Watson story was about other people having theories that Russia shot down
But if you believe that's crazy
Don't write about
Everybody wants a good story
Little people
People are reporting all this Rush
I want to say something like what's Fox News where it's like
Oh
Does something dumb and then the next day they're like
People are saying
Specifically
He doesn't believe
No
So that is
That doesn't even
Motivation
You just need a better editorial on your website so you don't have bulshit you disagree
Probably
Whatever
Anyway in the next clip he's not saying it's going to
Ga-14
Caulfield
Bedtime
Asteroid
Countdown
24 Eastern Standard Time or Central
Are we doing this
Around the world
We know that
When the computers remove
Craters
Also
That just gives up
And if you notice
That's during his show
He has to be on air when that happen
So he's pretty excited
Kind of about building that up
There isn't an awareness of like I will be on air when
This
Yeah
He doesn't want to say
But he also doesn't want you to think
It's totally safe
Because then there's no tension
There's no presentation snow performance it's just
The story of like
Hey is Big Thing flying over there
The sky
Keep eyes on the product
So
You know
You got a resort
To insinuation you got to resort to
Irresponsible conjecture
This is where I
It reaches its
Natural
Just a little piece
Imagine something
Mariah
Or Chicago
Or New York or Tokyo or Peking
Or just just
Thousands of people
Confirm
User was an asteroid coming
Don't worry about it
It should begin
So
Presenting some area where it's like I don't think is going to happen
Everything would be happening just like
What is the government until May
I don't know what the rates
To do is
Here's all I know
Whatever Alex is doing
The position of this isn't going to happen
Foot planting
Seed of like a government
If that situation
The meteor was about to hit
Your experience
Just what you're feeling right now
The government
To you and your death warrant is a couple hours away
Asteroid coming close
So you don't know
Asteroid
Is just irresponsible conjecture
Really deeply
You f***** up
His
He has a responsibility as somebody who has an audience
I'm too
Coming with facts
Write the common with a position of
Having an awareness about the
The situation not
Some sort of a paranoid
Combative missed towards
Expert
All you can do with this line of rhetoric is cause people
The freak out that's the only thing it does
He knows he knows
Full
Blisters believe that s*** for sure
It's just causing them to live in a constant
Speed of light
Anxiety feel distrust
Yeah if he believed
Second but a meteor was going to hit the Earth
He would not be on are you be with his family in a bunker or something
If you believe
Anything you're saying
Even close to this like there's a chance cuz the government right
Your behavior would be
Completely.
I think I would have treated like the eclipse
Remember that
Okay
Going to go anyways
Warming is a little different than the eclipse visual
Certain death
Right
Eclipse
Fly
It was next clip Alex
But that doesn't mean that something really bad isn't still going to happen
Narrative
Swag series
The f****** asteroid fall swag great
I just got out of that trailer thought before you started playing the clip I was like
I wonder if he's going to say something like
The government's going to fake it stroyd hitting you and that's why they're doing next
God dammit
If you want to start being able to predict where is Meredith's going
Send it
Okay
So nothing is going to happen but if something does happen
Probably the globalist actual asteroid
I don't know our trying to explain to you that
Asteroid hits happened much more than you
Could happen
F*** you man
The fear and anxiety paranoid
Disjointed
This isn't even like a coherent position
Know what are you saying
Literally anything can happen
But
These are the things you should be afraid of
Happened
Is the government acting in good faith
All other things are entirely possible how ridiculous they are
Turn off a nuke and somehow people would believe it was
A f****** asteroid hitting
Different things that happened but those things
Nope
Get the f*** out of here
So in this next clip Alex
Consulting
Al Gore
Which is fine
This is one of
Two times that he calls Al Gore Fat Bastard
Trump
Austin Powers
Austin Powers references in 2013
Get in my belly
References
Fresh
Certainly everyone knows
Like a Markham markable similarity visually between Al Gore
And fat faster
Looking at that
Hey Al Gore with red hair with a mediately go to
Really actually
Fatboy Vapors
Really pissed off at Alex didn't do a getting my belly really
Good impression
How do you resist
The fat Believers pression
I refuse to acknowledge that accent
Because he
Max microfiber is
It's grandfather and I
I only go with his hair his head is the size of an orange
That's what I do
So Alex
At this point starts taking
Calls
This is great
This is just Alex
Complete dick to a guy
Who didn't realize that Alex had gone to his call
Polish Behavior
That I would love out of anybody who's not out
How are you
Am I on the internet
Is it pointless
Is exactly the kind of behavior I Love don't love line Adam Carolla
I'm stuck taking calls for these people
You do a call-in show there's those hiccups
What's the weather like
This really disrupts the flow of Jairo
But I just don't appreciate it it's
Morrison's yearly angry
Perhaps
After joke around because
Instead of getting angry
I feel a deep Anger from you
No that's what I mean when I say cruel I don't mean the action is cruel is not it's not humor
It is like I'm trying to hurt this
I want them to
To feel pain
Yeah
Subway
I'm through much more like
Crazy
We're doing this overnight radio show and
It seemed more like trying to
Entertain
Selves
Like more of a Mystery Science Theater fuel to a Alex's
While he's taking
Some calls
Went to Piers Morgan
Azan
Afterwards
Alex got
A Morgan show
A bissinger one of Piers Morgan
And then after that
I was confronted Piers Morgan at a gun shop in Texas
And Alex start stalking
Think about this and in the middle of talking about it realizes that he forgot
Which I didn't even realize
That's a big problem
Piers Morgan
Surprising
Texas
Let me surprise
You really should have brought that up
Yeah I agree with you you should have
I think you just kept begging to come back on the show
Are for Alex
Buzz bissinger threatened to kill you
Not even a little bit
Complaints about remember the the brief moment of sympathy
Circumstance
Salad
The thing to point out
Show settings
Trillium
Like really brings home but like that is
Not with Alex cares about you only cares about that
Insomuch as it
Gibson point
Actually had Piers Morgan in front of him
If you the first thing she brought up
And you don't have to be like
A dick
To him to bring it up
I understand that we have a difference
Perspective
Gaston your show said he wanted to
Shoot me and you were fine
Talk about how
Saying that is
You can do that in the polite way you don't have to yell at him to bring that up
This is days weeks later
From when it confronted
A Texas gun shop
Realizing
Well I think he's also thinking that that would have been a
Better strategy
To try and get back on
On the show like if he confronts.
Dislike
Pilloried for saying stuff like that
Have you come on the show to talk about
Maybe that's what Alex is better approach
Yep
So if Alex gets another call
Is like
He's on one
He's talking about how
Somebody
Accused him of threatening to shoot
Shoot up a school
And then he went to LA and had a beauty
George Noory
He got arrested he was in prison and he was
Get people to help him
His story makes
No sense all right
I like
So you want some help from Alex
It's very complicated and I like I'm almost ready to try Microsoft one of your investigators and show him my dog
Help somebody
But
California
Also I don't I don't
Think that he was wrong and
Take on that dude's
K spray 30 lb of
We have pounds of
I got red flags
Obviously probably not polite to be like hey hey buddy
You're crazy
So baby is responses fine but
I think it underlies like a a real like I don't trust
My own audio
I'm not going to help you write about most
I know the government suppressing all of us and I'm going to help in the only way I can
Which is
Yelling
Making you scared of a meteor
That's what I was
I was just
Hearing there is the underlying truth behind those like
The meteors coming or you can't trust the government or anything
Like that
I am going to saddle you with his many fears and problems is
As I can
And I
Can't do anything
Positive
0 positive action
Should I yes nurse started organization could help you positive
No positive Act
Whatsoever
Skip another gas
You have guests here on the 15th
This woman
Remember her name cuz she
She's gone by
Just a single
She's a nurse
No
Had called in previously
Two whistleblower
About the military
Giving
Soldiers mad
Scandalous
Stop
Open interview that's basically all just anti-science
Psych meds
I don't really care about most of things
She think because she says a couple
Things that are
Markedly
Literally disqualified
And here's the first
They have these problems with
PCP angel dust
Legitimate
Amnesia
Good illustrative moment about how unreliable Alex Jones
Supposed whistle
He has this nurse on who blown the whistle about dangerous psych meds
Sincerely and on ironically is arguing
P and ketamine
Are basically the same thing
And now they only came out with ketamine
Watch baggage
But the evil doctors
Still wanted
The f*** people up
The first problem is that while the chemical underlined piece
He was fairly popular likes
70 years ago it's been outlawed for medical uses
19 6
Would be approved for human use 5 years later
Absurd status wasn't response
PCP falling out of favor
Just because Something's Happened around the same time in a chronological
Doesn't mean that the prior thing caused the letter thing
Also
Ketamine are not one molecule offer
From each other they're very different substance
Because very different effects
They both have been used as anesthetics
At some point
History
So it's easy to take
Surface-level approach
Simpler
Uninformed position
The chemical makeup of PCP or phencyclidine is
Conversely ketamine is c-13 H
DLNA
So it's really clear just want a basic very different compound
With ketamine you have nine Less hydrogen's in
That's going to affect
The structure of things pretty considerably
Not even taking into account but now you've added in oxygen and chlorine
These are very different Subs
Disqualifying
Say what you say
It indicates that she's either
Not actually a nurse
Where she is
She doesn't know which
She's talkin about
It just trying to use her
Supposed professional
Credentials
To strengthen her misguided
Science
Which is what you'd expect from Alex Jones whistleblower
Still kind of think
I'm a
Five be wrong about
But what you described are the
The chemical,
For a mullet
Correct
Like so
C9
And whatever it was
Is Amala
So they cannot add or subtract of molecules from the bottom
What you say
URI are equipped
Speak about it
Alter the chemical compound
Slightly
You make Academy
If you look at
To each other to the structure
Completely different
There's no way
It's not
Either of them
Here's the next
She says
Disqualifying
So are you
So Sigmund Freud
The father is
Psychiatry
He's the father of psychoanalysis
The very different
Care about being accurate
Troy Pioneer new ideas but the interplay of the human in
Society underlying processes
Inside the brain
We believe that through analysis
Talking things
Through one could learn about how the
The two interact
Each other
He was specifically and emphatically opposed
Returning the process of analysis
I did not advocate
Use the medication
Dyspraxia
Moreover he was supposed to look at
Psychological issues as illnesses
That needed to be treated
And advances you that's closer
Cinema is going on in our head they could be made less troubling by self-awareness and understanding them
Basically his whole thing was like the
This psychoanalysis allows you to find the ways
You lie to yourself
And damaging ways
Resolve those issues
Do we have no idea which
She's talking about
BP is ketamine
And if Freud is a
Any interview or what just blindly and embarrassingly Def
To justify the point
That meds are evil
Booty Shottas interview
She's presenting herself
To be an expert in
This is like embarrassing
For Alex
Biotics
But he's not
Hold on now
Freud is the father of psychiatry
Who u s
You're telling me that piece
He is ketamine
Instead
Nobody's talking
Initial
Crazy
So
That should make
This
Text clippy a little easier.
Cuz
Alex's
Planing
About how everyone is
Suggestible
I want to suggest
All everyone in the population
They're all just sheep
You could just
Tell them
Tell them something they believe it's a true
Complain
Is interesting
Because what he uses to do
Defend
His assertion
That the human population is
Suggestible
Show weak-minded
Restaurant
You just fell over
Is that your employees are idiots
But you haven't demonstrated in any way that this
Applies to the general population
Are also I be willing to believe that this person was afraid of you
Kind of other
Possible explanation
Employees Behavior
What is Obi-Wan with kind of a petty prick
It's not like trying to generalize
Results
Single trial
I think I should just go out and harass people for no reason
Pretend it's a joke
Well now because he's addicted
He starts by saying
The public is so weak mind you can tell them they fell down and they'll believe you
One time
I did that to a staff member
You can't generalize that too
The population
You have one experience than that
There's so many extraneous variables are you got it
Exclude power relations
Not I will believe anything
Like how
Because inferences are
Like he's either he's applying this one
Instant stew
Everyone
Either that or he only hires people that
You can trick
That's an insult to everybody who works
As well maybe
We can take this
Assume
Wow
Who is
Gullible enough to believe that
CP of cat
Do Serta bulshit things
Maybe it's staph
Yeah maybe they're also suggestible that it becomes a place where everyone believes
All the stupid s*** that said on the show
So it is next clip we get another thing that we always got to keep
First of all colors
Second of all
Alex's fecaliths
Third of all
Does Alex have feelings
That killing dogs
In my yard
I just saw the rabbit
Chihuahua
Got to shoot those new world orders
Damn
Stop talking about killing.
Happens all the time
Every time Alex pretty much the only time I've ever comes
Stopping my life is taking a
Dogs
Sui preoccupation
Jesus
I wonder I wonder what that means
Alex has another guy
The guy who I'd never heard of before
But
Spec
Here is our
I had a little bit of a red flag
Since the last time Alex had a
China expert on it was that guy was pretending
To run a adoption
Pagoda guide
I don't know if I trust
Your ability to suss out who is is not a China at
I don't want you to look into this what kind of awfulness I open the lid
So on the surface Alex's gas to your Steve Moser is
Humane practices
Is the Chinese government
He's trying to lift the veil and make everyone aware the brutality that was
Complicit
And how the one child policy was an actor
And the falsehood that were
Behind the rationalization
Creation
Play squeezo position is
China created a false overpopulation
Idea
Like
To create oppressive
Population
Control measures
Leatherface
But if you look a little deeper into Moser
Different sort of picture
Possibly a guy who is
And uses China as a means of advancing his own agenda
Anti-abortion
So emotional he was the first American answer
Ecology research
Student to be allowed to go to China
Research purposes
After the cultural revolution
Yes is one of the last
He's one of the last his research resulted in him being not allowed back in China
Being expelled from Stanford
Before he completed
His supporters argue that it is all punishment for his intrepid reporting
He released photographs of women having forced abortion
And the Chinese government was mad about
So they kicked him out of country and convince them for to expel
That neatly fits
The antique china
Communist world you so pretty much anyone who cares about who Steven Mosher is
Just accept that as the truth
However
The reality is that he was expelled because he released those photos of
With the subjects faces
Exposed
Which is a really serious ethical breach
If you're doing investigative work
Reporting to Deming
Evil of a government
And a big
Piece of your evidence is
Pictures of spy
Pacific citizens of that governments
Country being the victim of government oppression
You have a Paramount responsibility to
Protect those people's identity
Stanford was shocked
Mosher wood published
These images with no regard for how he's doing so
Could put these women in danger
And after reviewing relevant ethical standards
They kicked him out of the school
This is not something a program
The process of working for their pH
The school has an investment in nursing
It's pretty serious violation
Kicked out of a postgraduate program
It also looks bad for the program
If you're kicking out a bunch of post-grad candidates
It implies that you don't have good admissions
So School 10 to go out of their way to key
Keep students in the program
Incorrect problems where they can be corrected
In the case of Mosher
Actions were beyond what could be except
And so they had to get rid of
That's that should tell you a little bit about this guy
God
Women disappear
It's subjected them to such a high-risk
Retaliation
From that and he had every reason to know that he should have been more careful graduate student
Setting their ethical standards in place specifically
Because
You could put a Target on
That did just that
Because of you
Fallout is much more difficult for research
Stu
It caused a real serious backlash
Weather many good reasons to denounce
Decry the practice
The Chinese government relation to its one-child policy
Hoosier seems to approach his criticism
A very weird angle
His argument is that they started the policy because of fears about overpopulation
But that those fears were fake
And just a cover-up for their real reason
Try that they wanted to control the population
He then takes this implication that the Chinese government was lying about their motive
It applies to all family planning in birth
Control initiatives worldwide
This is really what Moser is all about
He's a devout Catholic who staunchly opposed to all family planning
He runs an organization called the population research
Whose mission is to
Debunk the myth of overpopulation which
Abusive population control program
And quote expose the Relentless promotion of abortion
Abortive
That's it contraception
Sterilization in misleadingly labeled population
And reproductive health
That's really what
Motrin distance
You do not care about
Seriously complex issues of overpopulation
Serious researchers on the topic would agree with him that the issue isn't that there's too many people
It's been our resource allocation is
You f***** up
And then overpopulation is a
The serious issue when the vast majority of the people who exist are living
Poverty
Poverty is the problem
Not just the number of human
It'll be easier to take Motrin seriously if he cared about that
At all
But he does
Because his work is just a trojan horse to attack
Contraception
And all pro-choice
But that's not all
He's also a big demography guy
Great as hero quotes
The practice of abortion artificial birth control sterilization
And a culture of secularism
Materialism
Country
Serious
Only god reigns
We must serve
Because of the above we lack native-born children
And hence need immigration and Catholic families need children to replenish the church
Give us Priestly and religious vocations
Our culture and survival is a prosperous Nation needs Young have more than two children
Glorious
Motherhood
A woman's fertility is our greatest treasure in the boardroom of business
Apologetic
Boy
I like
I like red flag
Sure
But
Let's call it that
There's always
Ghetto it deserves to be brought up there's almost
Always
A little hurdle of white nationalism wrapped up in
Most answer your bored
Incrowd
When you just did a little bit better
Play the surface you're pretty much always find that a lot of their fears arise from Notions like there aren't enough
People like us having kids
And too many people unlike us hanging around
That's kind of been
A ton of it
Which is why they their highest touted argument that they always do is
Nobody should care more about anti-abortion than black people because millions of black babies are aborted all the time
Care most about it
And they do that because
To protect
Themselves on the on the
The flank
People noticing that all you really want is more white
Does
The strategy
Crusade mask
Is some kind of a noble battle against population as evidence
By his experience in China 40 years ago which resulted in
Expelled from stamp
This guy is not on the up-and-up
So you probably are wondering how can you afford to run this kind of very clearly disingenuous operation
Right-wing billionaires
The population Research Institute is heavily funded by the Linden Harry Bradley Foundation
Harry Bradley naturally was the first members of the John Birch Society along with Fred Coe
And the two bad if shared a very similar Legacy
In terms of funneling money to
The Bradley Foundation is contributed millions of dollars
The donors Trust
The coax operated dark money conduit
Which is one of
Buddy connection
Bradley's in the coke allies and their decades-long Crusade against progress
Bradley Foundation is given tons and tons of money
2 population research
Institute and
This
Mosher's
Work
The Bradley Foundation paid charles-marie $1000000 to write his dogshit book the bell curve
Which to this day is one of the main sources White
Supremacist .22 justify their beliefs that black people genetically have lower IQs
The book has been called a part of a
Define racism
Which is no surprise that it
Promoted
By the likes of Stephon
In all the cool kids running around on YouTube
The Bradley Foundation
Funding made that
Possible
Because they're more than happy to use race
To push the agenda that there really are
That's the name of the game
So here we have yet another mouth
Peace for right-wing billionaire funded front groups appearing as a guest on Alex Jones Show
Presented
Benignly
Is an expert on population
How it always goes
Fires
Because
Sure
Speedway all over the place
How does right-wing billionaires
Is it true that you know it's a
Tradition going all the way back for some reason
Ouija
Rich people just
Show up and fukitol
The problem is transparency
Problem
Who's making people show who's there donating money
These these Largent
It needs to be open
Because the influences sew-ins
Sidious
Stefano's so much money
And enables so many
Suspicious
It was a hundred thousand dollars from the people who
Are interested in getting rid of affirmative action
That's why you're promoting the people of genetically dumber than white people
You can make the calls wilken
Between the money and the rhetoric
If it's all open
Butts
It's so often.
It's much harder issue
Years of years of
That ability to funnel money place
Secretly goes on
The damage
That would have been away
To avoid this
At this point just going by
Shame doesn't exist anymore strategy
That I wouldn't be surprised if they
Came out in real life
Donated all the money by Coke
I mean there's still some irony
You know cuz
All of this was exposed to the light of day a lot of these people who have these like ideas about
Yeah you know what's wrong
These billionaires are controlling conversation
I never realized that a ton of things
They support are funded by other
Secretive right-wing billionaire on
They call these people would have to rest with the ideas like
The people on our side who fit the description of the
The demons that we are against are actually the ones funding
The information sources that we have
Huh
Let's go let's go
What else you got to make but it's hard to
2 defense
So they could make that jump
The box that's really difficult to defend
It's possible but I don't know
Like I don't I don't know what the right answer is
Transparency
I agree it'll allow for
A better
Possible future
So one of these interesting
On this episode I heard a intro
Commercial that I've never heard before
On Alex's show and it
F****** hilarious
Don't worry this is documented Alex Jones
Radio Network
What just happened
Worried illegal immigrants
No
I get it
He's saying all the claims are
Okay yes
Don't worry
Consider that as a possibility because I thought it was
Too far beyond the pale for them to even
Take that back
Does anti
Immigrants
Extension 2013 but not to the extent he is
Is that was played in now
Consider what your don't worry
I thought it was
Hey I know this sounds crazy but we know what talking about
Alright
Cy Hackler so raise for all of the racism
It's it's like me like I heard that and I was like
Don't worry
We don't have any mechs
Jesus Christ
I see where you're coming from
I think it's
Much
Much more likely
Freezer chest
So in this point I don't care to address
Specifics of what he's talking about going to play this
Freaky
Comical nature
We hear 04
I don't really care about that all I care about is the idea these like operation
He doesn't realize
Bradley Foundation funded
What's going on here
Himself is some guy he's like how are you so blind
How are you so blind to the eye
The people that you're in League with
Who were taking right-wing Foundation
Or the way that he would try and talk
His way out of that
It always has to because
You such into movies that has to be at
Struggle
It always has been one side's God one side
Coronavirus
Super couldn't get away with
I think he doesn't know s***
Because research
She knows about this
Carnegie Endowment in Rockefeller Foundation
From people like w Cleon skousen
And all of these ants
Communist s******* that came before
He only knows
The stuff that they've pointed out
So his body of information is so one-sided
And he doesn't dig into things
So he doesn't know
Billionaire Foundation
They're funneling
Money to all
These other places
Is that
Suspiciously
Just like
Mosers just
Fuckingawesome dude who cares about
The myth of depopulation through started this Foundation
Thankfully
The Grassroots
I'm in maybe he does believe that cuz he doesn't
Do any
Possible
Just because so many of his
Friends of taking money from
You bet
Places that are
It's like he never
Nobody let him on that it was
Giant
You know like
A Bi-Lo didn't let him know that coat bought two hundred thousand
Facebook or whatever the f*** it is 8
Really hard to believe that he's that naive
Yeah
Different business
I don't believe
Can someone who can't prove anything I can't believe the contrary
I don't know it's complicated
I'm 31 last clip here
I'm in and what day is it
Essentially like 2000 having this nonsensical conversation
About how overpopulation
Birth control stupid
To the sky
Vaca demography
Lies behind
Arguments
Cities making any
He's really just a
Anti-abortion
Contraception
Zealot
He's concerned about variable birthrate switch
Ironically exactly
The same sorts of things that
Are now in the present-day motivating people to murder Muslims
Yeah
Shockingly regularly whenever you hear those sorts of attacks
People
Seem to all have that certain there's too many of them
I'm standing up for the West
So you know when you hear this
You kind of realize
They're making it a little too public
Family friendly
It's crazy
It's where we hear all this stuff in 2019 it's like
He's giving overtures to it in a way that
People don't
We didn't
I don't know I don't want
For everybody but I think a lot of people probably wouldn't
Have that register as like
What he's talking about is intense
I think you just hear that in a much different
In 2013
Goodnight do we do now because
People are acting on it now
Not a radio show that nobody's asked
This further is my point
That this wasn't being discussed on Fox News
In 2013
Probably.
This is what Alex was doing that is now a
Acceptable for Fox News to talk about
I thought he must get more extreme in 2019
This doesn't get to
The audience
Aroused
This is
Pretty messed up
Oh man
Yeah it is exactly
Where we were
The crazy people being where we are now with
You you compare that to the way Fox News cover the migraine
Caravan is
Flood
Pets that are bored
You know that whole thing and you think
This guy was just saying
Boats
Muslims in 20
14in Fox News
Never would have touched
Position
It doesn't
Like it was
Covert
Pretty crazy
Especially because like this
Stretch of time is so bizarrely
Like Alex's
Already kind of letting doerner by the wayside
To be enough for him
And then you get a f******
Meteor coming in
On the 15th
Interview with
Complete racist
Population guide
Crazy
Never
Philip surprise
Lakers 2013
There's so much happening in the world
You got Obama coming in for his second term
So a lot of people are f****** up a tizzy about that
You've got so many newsworthy
Gigantic events happen
So weird
Stinking wallet
While the earlier clips
We're going on
If I
Cuz I always forget
This is ostensibly supposed to be a new show
Yeah it is easy to forget that
If I was just listening to this show
I think I would have no idea what
Going on
Like URI
Say you were informed
Certainly
No clue other than
An asteroid Mike
Because they're doing it
Yeah I think you would not be informed
For sure
But you would get the message that I was watching it again
Unhealthy level of distrust for everybody
Bring us to the end here
On Monday
Twitter
Podcast through
Gravely review on Saturday Ballyhoo also
For having us
Nice
Week for people who can't get enough of us yeah yeah new content every day of the week
Jordan flying around
If you all enjoyed it
And another large Asuza for absolute
Merchsource
Store or shirts
Figure it out
To the store
Thank you are really gorgeous
So
Alex is imaginary chihuahua in his dog murder scenario
Navigate dog was
Did have rabies
The Chihuahua that was
Attacked by the dog
The two hours just you don't know what happened after it got rabies probably
That's because we don't know that for sure we should probably are on the side of believing the Chihuahua
Did not kill anybody
But one guy
Alex