Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages and talk a little bit
About Alex
Jones
Have you ever been in
Corn mazes maybe I feel like I have been Central Missouri we went
Interstate fairs
Yeah I never had any
Experience
I feel like I've been in haunted houses
More
Good houses I always found up unpleasant
There was too much awareness for me that these weren't monsters they were people
Trying to scare me
And that made me was that
Enjoy that
Of course I did one time go to a rave at a haunted
House also
In Columbia
But during that
During October time
Was that
Haunted house
Know when this was but it was
Not during Halloween
A bunch of people who held the RAV4 there
As much as I may be sure I wasn't apart of that
A lot of industrial music maybe not for
But it was surreal to walk around the
Parts of the house
With the light
Yeah
It seemed like all of you
These weird quarters were people would hide
But looking back on it
Or anything I don't know if it was it was just weird
Notable it happened
Play I definitely
Hello.
How many mazes come up
Today is DJ Chicago supposed to last
Celebration
Was trying to walk over here not realizing
Well we live on
We live is the parade route
Some reason
I don't know
Are they going to hold up.
It was only like a block but I had to backtrack and go all the way around it and then
To do this Ziggy zaggy thing to get from
Because Broadway is Miyazaki
Apologize
And I know a lot better
Alex Jones
And I only know what you tell me about both
That's right
But before I say
Episode
I got to take a little time
People who signed up and are supporting the show
We really appreciate it
So first of all thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next Britney thank you so much
Brittany
Thank you so much you are now apology walk
I'm a policy wonk
Next of Barnes Barnes
Paris Enoch in barn
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Laura offices of Barnes Barnes
Patterson acambaro
All I have to say
You donated on a little bit of an elevated level we appreciate it very much
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Is freakishly large
Stripe.com
But instead Sports sure we'd appreciate
First thing I need to say is a little bit of a correction information
Slightly
In
Complete information on her last episode
And that I was incorrect
About
You going away led to
The development
No s*** yeah so cool I was incorrect about that
Now I will say
That I was not correct
About my kids my contention that they are very
There are similarities
Between the two
But I was wrong about that aspect of it
So I guess
It was my sin
Your intention Jordan to do episode today here we talk about Alex Jones
Credit card debate
Is doing live coverage of Both Worlds
Cuz all the time
How far off the rails
End up really f***** up with
Drunk
And yelling about us someone basically irresponsible
Sometimes even cries and tells us about the four ways humans can learn two things does a good thing
I sat down to get us
Source material and it immediately was not going to work
On the first night of the Bates Alex was not drunk
It definitely feels like someone may have given him a Stern talking-to and the show is pretty much just a boring version of his normal
Show but with Owen Shroyer
And Barnes co-hosting
It's a Telethon for sure
And it's really less about the debates and more about Alex's victim status and how everyone's crying
Take him down
Ultimately was a huge disappointment.
4 hours worth of b******* that we don't
I need to go over
So I tuned into the Thursday show figuring Alex
Cuz got to have some next day
Throw out
I can almost taste how hard he's going to go after Beto for talking in Spanish
Has the show started up I could tell that what I was hearing was a pre-recorded message
Message from Alex
It sounds like he's recording it at like 4 a.m. inside a tin can
It's basically just a accusing Elizabeth Warren of being on cocaine
Okay here is a taste of that
Think about
Obviously
For 2 hours
Guarantee
Large amounts of it
So it sounds like it's awful
A couple of minutes
He has Barnes host the rest of the show which is unlistenable but it does feed into your theory that Barnes
Just trying to take over
So I must just be tired
He was up late doing the livestream that I before so we had Barnes cover for him to get energy back
Fortnite 2
A big night
Closeout clown world
So I turned on night to a my reaction was not unlike that of a lovecraftian protagonist
Come face-to-face with some sort of Eldritch Horror
Alex wasn't even on his own debate live stream coverage it was all
Goodnight and barn
Is awful
They didn't they did play a 2-minute recording
Recalls the Democrats losers
But it sounds like it was recorded at about 4:10 a.m. in the same reported the other day
Message
And then Friday shows just that's
Alex is basically announced
Factor in his democratic debate coverage
On Friday it's just Barnes
David Owen Shroyer again
He doesn't even get to make fun of how Marianne Williamson. It was there he was funny
The party
That what's up
Alex is supposed to be deposed in the Sandy Hook lawsuit on July 1st and 2nd
Or Monday and Tuesday of this
Connecticut case where Norm Patterson
Doesn't charge
Given the s*** that's been happening with Alex between these horrible response to the illegal pornography that was discovered in discover
You know his very clear attempts
To threaten opposing counsel
And put a million-dollar bounty on them
I wouldn't be
Surprised if Norman
Alex actually prepare for this deposition
If you work all he does
Kind of wants to win the case
As opposed to Barn to seems far more interested in logging a h on
Iran Infowars
And making a lawsuit
Milka
Milks for all the publicity they can bring
And then settling the case
Because whenever Shake
Get to real
Yeah
Would get more market value out of a better outcome of the case
I don't know why we like totally wrong
I have no idea
Possible make
Said it wasn't a situation where nor made Alex come to Connecticut early
Which would explain his absence
As well as the shity sound quality the recording
Might have been filming it in an airport
Whatever the case is I have no new Alex
To cover the past
Follow how Alex
Two narratives
Sandbox
After Sandy Hook
Today we are going over February 17th
1/18
Some of it's fairly interesting
And some of it is
Profoundly upsetting there will be one portion of this episode
That I'm going to give a contact
Encore in
F***** up stuff
But
It's because I did not watch
Right
Narrative is like
You know I
Me and
Subreddit
The Donald we got
Censored
No one could attack by I'm scrolling through my Twitter feed and it's like all
Or try to avoid
I don't really have a hot tub
Like that so it's better that we stay for a little while
I don't know we'll see what happens
Butts
So
It's interesting cuz the the February 7th
Where we last left off there was that Russian
Getting pretty silly about
Being a little irresponsible that the end was nigh
So we're going to see how that plays out on the neck
Today because that last one we listen to the Friday we're jumping back on
On the 17th
Pictures of Sunday
Before we get to today's episode
For the dogs
What did you say
Where are the dogs and Alex's world coming out of his mouth
So the first year from the 17th
Alex is responding
Some media coverage of his coverage
Of the Russia
Meteor
This is very
Very stupid
Analysis very wrong
About
Support.com
Was it
Ga-14
On Friday
Tear
Alex Jones
So this is a real serious trying to goes on
These two days
Is Alex misrepresenting people talking about
Call Friday explicit point of how Alex need to report a dumb theories that
What are true
Problems
It'll come out of the Alex Jones's
His writers are so bad at writing
Can sometimes be difficult to tell what they're actually trying to
So in this case
I wanted to figure out what was going on what was this Atlantic article what was the Infowars archive is there a cure
Leave this
Temptation going on
I decided anybody
It's probably me
So I checked out this article in Atlantic
Has the headline
Russian meteorite
Conspiracy theories
Here's what the Atlantic article says
As it relates
More wide-eyed theorists have suggested that the object may have been a meteor
May not have been a meteor at all and could have been a satellite that was shot down or some form of
Kinetic bombardment weapon
Russia
The conspiracy loving folks over it
Alright Infowars
So the beginning of that part is
The quote from an Infowars Artica
You know this is the part that makes it clear. Indian forwards articles
They're discussing quote more wide-eyed.
That's pretty much the article goes on vladamir
Azuree
0 Knob ski
The meteor was a u.s. weapon
Target
Better breaks down hoe that's not
But at no point does the article say that Alex's advanced
They take a quote from the article where Alex is
Or the Infowars article is saying that more wide-eyed serious are suggesting
Doesn't matter
Doesn't
Suggest that
They're not advancing those.
Yeah
4 yd
More
Totally fine actually almost responsible
It's totally fair
So the Infowars article itself was written by Steve Watson and it pains me to say this but
Stupid
This is about the best version of it you could write
The Atlantic accurately cover the Infowars article they quoted the part of the story where Steve Watson had written about the WiDi conspiracy
Believing this idea which is a fair representation
Text no harm
No foul
Not just because the Atlantic article accurately discuss Steve Watson
Article
They might have been able to make a much different case
They took into account all of Infowars outfit
16th and Fort Worth Public
Special Report titled quote
Russian meteor shower?
That was published article
Publish an article quote
Suspected meteor explosion reported in central Cuba
They published this article with so little information
It was a real thing
So they had to add this absurd editor's note
Quote there is a lot
Capital letters
Direct Auto
Okay there is a lot of disinformation floating around about this possible occurrence
And I know I wrote it
The word occurrence here
Is misspelled
Good editor's note
Stonework
Satisfied
No videos or images of the supposed surfaced from reputable sources at the time of writing
Fun fact
The articles
Supposed
He's just a copy and pasting of an article in Xena
State-run paper out by the Communist Party
Something you definitely wouldn't think that would be on Alex's Rolodex
Copy and paste articles from
Wait
Okay
These types of bulshit headlines at
The irresponsible reporting
Analysis
Sentences that the media came down in Russia could be related to the larger
Class B. Literally no reason
I think that was the case
It all adds up to Imports doing a really bad job with meteor
Their behavior shows a clear desire
To kick-off some sort of fear and paranoia
But he was very non-committal and I think that's what hurt
They went half speed
Which any football coach will tell you is when injuries happen
You're going to f****** your propaganda game would you go halves
That's when you get here
Real hard
So the situation is that the Atlantic article accurately covered
Alex is projecting onto them
Some sort of lie
And it's really it's really silly
Describe it
So it kind of feels like Alex
Defensive towards
You peace that they that the Atlantic wasn't talkin
No I think it's these defensive about his larger Corpus
I think it's an issue
It's also
I don't think he likes it whenever
Even mentioned at all in an article that has
Debunked
He's being associated with these
Things that are being done
As opposed to him being one of the only
News
Quote news sources
Have a large platform
Even dip their toe into the dumb but this was
Hoodsite
I don't know that's on him
Nobody's coming to Rally behind me or god dammit
You're in the pool
It doesn't exclude will you find out that you know
What is frustrated by the
Discover him
You know if he'd had his
His druthers
Never be getting disorder coverage
Farming again
The people who are at odds with the oil painters are of course
Okay okay
How do you summon
People plus a day
Artist who decided to quit in order to fight a perceived global
War never heard that before
Weird well there's a big difference
Apparently
The internet says that Hitler was there we go
Do you work for PETA
Selling his old oil pay $1,000 on the boardwalk
Remember to Boardwalk
I need to pay
Within the context of me taken
Describing it I believe
He started selling
Cheaper on the street
And then people started to come around later
That they're like
I need get me and Alex I want to say this very clearly
If anybody
Knows how to track
I don't know how I'll pay for it
But I will find a way I don't care I will
Now that being said I'm not sure the exact
And anybody has one
Or knows where I can
Taiwan
I'll probably pay like 200 bucks
Hey by the way Alex
Bye-bye Alex if you listening
You need two hundred bucks
Just make one now
I'm disappointed never
The Pretender right Road
It's in his fantasy backstory
What's.
Throughout
Having a lot of feelings about the Nigerian email
This comes after him
Doing his normal spiel about the Nigerian
What's interesting
Refine
News about what happened in the second
Of the email scam which implies
He's probably
Marion Diehl
But you got to put
So he knows what happens if you fall for the scam how the scam evolve
And also where would he be getting the money to send to the Nigerian prince sales
It all fits also took out a huge insurance policy
Put it all together that's what happened
Show is
Silly
I was listening to it on like this
Is
Not a good show
Worse but in a much different one
And that is
Because Alex
It comes in
And it is Oath Keepers founder Stewart Road coming back in
Gunn weirdo
We love guns
Call Sandra.
But I found particularly interesting
And worth discussing
And here is the first one
Fulton County County
Accounting
They're not going to comply
Tom Lauria Fulton County
Either retire or go to prison
For those guys
You're coming in talking about this is a molon labe count
I have those really interest
January 2013
Roads in The Oath Keepers launched what they called The molon labe Pledge
Where they declared that they will never Reg
Just never
Castration of weapons
And they would violently resist quote the breakers who try and disarm
On their website this Pacific
Quote
This is the Pledge we published in January 2013 in response
Selective calls
Four more in French
To keep and bear arms after the Sandy Hook shooting
That writing is specifically signed by Stewart Road
It is explicitly saying that he was compelled to write this pledge for his group of Gunn weirdos
In response to his feelings
Which is interesting
But I found this even more interesting
We know that
Before January just before January
Launch
Molon labe shirt
Which he announced
On his January 11th
Show the best seller of
Never sold
All that thing she doesn't know how to pronounce Bola de l'abbaye it says quote
Monet label
The expression molon labe popular among right-wing militia types for a while
Adidas shirt who's clearly ripping off something that was cool in the Subterranean world
List
I'm trying to sell it to the main
Cuz he was even unaware of what how to say
Whereof it enough
But he didn't really know
So he was laundering.
That's the feeling I had
A perfect analogy for what does with his rhetoric
But what's more interesting
Tumi is the Stewart Road
Didn't make his molon labe played
Until after Alex released
Shirt and if you
Cellar
Could you have here is an interest
Glimpse at a business
In terms of rhetoric
Alex
Bucked up worlds of
Acceptable
The more mainstream audio
In the process
He bought at Isaac
Shirts
Bumper stickers
All the lights
Take this
Gross world
Ideas
Shines them up and then markets
Then
The representative is f***** up world to Alex's
Platform
Take the product
He's created based off of rhetoric that comes out of their world
And sells it back to
Extremist
I think that there's a cycle gear
It's also the the cycle of
The more you Market this to people the more people see it and
Get associated with it and it normalizes molon labe arises that then
Brings it back
Alex starts
Recycling
And it's a little bit further more money off this if you just
Let's say some weird
Three percenter Shirt Company
Made a molon labe it's much more Market penetration centralization
Of concept
Etcetera
And it's also pretty easy
Alex is enterita Trump s*** having a pretty similar
With him stealing Hillary for prison as a line that he read on a bumper sticker
None of this is David Alex doesn't actually want a war to break out over guns or that he doesn't want Hillary in prison
Look at this
There's a kind of a parasitic marketing relation
Between Alex and
Community
Follow a pattern
I don't know I ate I just find it very interesting
You know that Oath Keepers had been
Around four years
Do a molon labe
Tell Alex released his bowl
There's a
There's something
Wondering
Black chicken and eggs
Situation
The dumb Oath Keepers
Talk to Alex
See that shirt out there
And then are like
Okay cool we can capitalize on
Were they the ones who gave Alex the ID and the
The first place
He put the shirt out there and then they can release their pledge
It's already
I think it's probably closer to the second
Let the world
Where is The Oath Keepers Fester
Yeah
Going back to
Formation
Call Patriot militia
Molon labe with something
Was
It exists
It is a catchphrase
And a cold
In those worlds already
Okay okay
To like the 300
The Spartans
From a historical perspective
You can go back that far
American
It did exist
Since like the early 2000
So I think Alex ripped it off from that
Whether or not it was a field
But I
Function I think
You're describing is a
In the way each serves each other
There's purposes
Capitalize off
The actions of
Yeah I agree
Clip
Trying to start something physical
Virgin
You know plan in Fremont
So
This makes no sense
Stewardess saying that he tells his guys to prepare a 3-month Spurs
So you got to do whatever you can buy April 9th
But this episode is taken
Place on February
17th which you may or may not know is not 3 months before April
So I decided to see
What's 3 months before April 19th roads up to
And on January 19th
Cordially
In Idaho
He's three months nonsense has nothing
To do with the choices
He chose April 19th
Because that's the day when the battles of Lexington and Concord
Started back in 70
1575 Revolutionary War
We are grown up
Really interesting
Because it tells you what these guys are obsessed
They're not really obsessed with the underlying causes of the American Revolution
Because if they were
To memorialize
December 16th
Vanoss and honor of the boss
Party
We could go with November 1st
In memory of the past
Fortiva
Immortalized
Successful conclusion
The six-year uprise in The Regulators
Carolina
There are many many options for a date
Stuart Rosen
When is gun weirdo friends could use
But you chose
April 9th
They chose this day
Because it was the day when their version of Justified Violence
Kicked off
And I fantasize about being able to relieve that
So desperate
Scholars of the Revolutionary War would probably be on white
Play the say that the war started with the battles of Lexington
They would probably be likelier to say that
The Escalade
Listen to a shooting War started
That is why the date resonates so much for these militia picture
Because they want that to happen again
If they didn't then we probably have a more robust
Analysis
The forces that led up
To the eventual shot heard round the world
As opposed to
Just talk about how the British
We're going to see the weapons
And that started the war
It's f****** nuts
For people so obsessed with the revolution who screamed about the
76 it's wild that I have never heard Alex bring up the Intolerable Acts
I've never heard him bring up at Oz
Suffolk resolves Place
The Patriots of Massachusetts
It was state of open Rebellion again
Against the British
I've never heard any of that from
None of this sort of analysis
Your argument is
Stupid and I suspect
It's partially that way because their argument isn't
Sphere
The idea that gun compass
Navigation caused the American Revolution is not
Anybody could
Seriously argue on the merits
But it works really well
If what you really want to do is math
Your underlying desire to
Peculiar political rivals
And you need a justification
That seems to be what's going on
If it weren't
Stuart would have probably chosen
For his imaginary end
Three-month preparation
I think these people belie what they're so interested in
With the way
They present
No ice
Before these guys
Really want to kill somebody
And they know that they can't do it first
Yeah that's what they want they want
Can't do it
Without any control specific
Types of human beings
No sake
I think I don't want to.
I'm kind of old Betsy Ross I think they would be pretty sad
If they killed another militia guy
Pretty safe
The Sunday show so go to Shorter show that
Is much going on
Fences
About his coverage of the
Meteor
Stewart Road
Yelling about guns
Silly fun
And
Alex was very
Trigger
About people talking about his meteor coverage
Another bit of
Criticism
Of his argue
Come out in the media
And Alex is not happy about that
It ran in
The analogy used to murder all pay
Patriots
So
In some respects
Screaming
Alex
Complain about the media covering him unfairly
In this case is related to his
But the federal government is buying a
6 billion rounds of ammunition
It's strange
6 billion people represent 1% of gun owners
The gun control measures
The government
6 billion bullets
This is the sort of thing that I said
Just going to drive any numerologist you might be listen
Completely insane
The average family has 1.6 children all my God
The crypto Fibonacci number
I don't know
Understanding of what the articles
They're saying
They agree with Alex
Government
6 billion bullets
Conclusion was
And that very easily available facts contradict his stories
The details in order to escalate paranoia
All the right-wing sites that cover the ammunition purchase
Constantly frame it is Obama buying all these
These bullets
In reality what happened was that the government of put out requests for people to bid on contracts
The provided very large number of
Presumably around the 1.6 billion number that Alex site
It might be less than that but I'm not really a
Splitting hairs
The reason the people are unwilling to say that Alex is right
Despite him being
Pretty much right about the government
It's because all the stuff he says they're buying
At 4
I need to bury a annoying around this imagine
Purchase
When the truth is that they were buying the ammo for training and shooting range
End of the contract they were looking
Still work for the next
5 years
It's not like they wanted one points
6 billion bullets
To show up ready to go tomorrow
It was over the next
Of course
Half a decade
And their idea was that if they could vote
Contract with a huge purchase
The federal government might be able to get a better price
At first glance 1.6 billion is a joke
A Second Glance
It's still a gigantic
But if you start to consider how many federal law enforcement agencies there are and how many agents
The train at State train
That number is reflecting a five-year
Apply for all those purposes
It doesn't really seem like that crazy
Your number after all
If you want have a conversation but how
It is that our law enforcement practice
This revolves so heavily around weaponry
Maybe we should disarm the police
Conversation
The fact that
And the fact that it gradually becomes
Less
And saying that it's 1.6
6 billion
Seems ridiculously normalizing
2 something
Really really bad.
And it's crazy looking at it
Hi early different perspective than Alex
We can have complaints about the
Complaints be completely incompatible
So the meeting was taking issue with Alex
Consistent with the bullets
For the government's use in a war against
Which is a very especially when a very reasonable explanation is readily available
He was sort of right
Because most generous
They might say he's right about a fact
Did wrong button
Interpretation
If I were running this media Outlets
I probably would not have been so diplomatic
I probably would have said that he was using the
July
Because that's what he's doing
I don't
Complaints fall on deaf ears
A bit over the past
Few years of trump
We need to treat them fairly and we don't save it
We say that
Mismanaged
The point where most news outlets
Trump lied about that
Not enough probably
More than there were
Yeah
Back in 2013
Nobody would say that
Except for Joe Wilson
Wow
I don't think so
Most of the show that Alex is doing is about
Like a lot of the show is taking up with his complaints about the
The media coverage of Heaven Howard's asiop
Russian with this video
Did the government
1.6
Billion bullets
It's just come
This whole thing is just exercising
I think I'm mostly pulled this quick cuz I think it's funny
Alex
Play the clip
From CNN
Reliable sources
Shell which is
Free Brian stelter
Is always
Axe to grind
Metaphor
It's very own brand
Discussion is going on in the clip
He plays is someone I don't know who it is
Unreliable sources
Why is the f*** with Piers Morgan
Even book
Alex Jones
Is Joe
Does anybody know what Alex
Pyrite
I just
I love the idea that he's interrupting the clamp to complain of a organ interrupting
Delicious irony
Sources also
Hooking interrupt
Ironically
Most of the show has been a ham
Complaints
About media articles about
Why are you covering that
Because
Exact
So
You know obviously
The audience is going to be
Having the same thoughts
Alex is just
Cover himself self-aggrandizing
No Alex defending himself
From the
Possible
Interpretation that he's
Just covering any news
That much was sure
Russia
It's just incredible
Not
It's just
It's just sad
Just said
Even even his cameraman after hearing that must have been like little s*** bulshit
Like there's no way that you can say we didn't even cover that.
Complains a little bit more about this at
Acquire
It's interesting
Because
He's accusing them of lying
About them
It's weird they interrupt too much
Face
Bumpkin some bunk
He is gas-lighting hard it's like
This is how he mainstream's illiteracy
Responding to a false
Presentation of these articles
Russian
A response that is
You said that
Because for the most part
He can't
So this is
Sincere misinterpretation on his
When is malicious
Right and then
I'm going to jump ahead towards the end of the episode now because Alex
Call her later
Who Alex
Complained
About how about him
And the car has a really interesting response
Let's do it
I don't expect anything more
This caller is going to be
His version of it and his sworn off any
Never going to go find the articles that Alex was about
Self-contained and inoculated
Facebook
Jesus and that color almost
Perfectly embodies the
The gross aspect
Difficult
It's it's very much
It's exactly like a
Like it's him
Cutting off his family from
Contact cuz they're suppressive person
The other aspect of the authority of the cult leader
Where is called into question
There's some sort of dismissiveness
Punished
Yeah another caller
I have one more question
Million
Bullet Paul Watson
I recorded that the DHS purchase
Yes there's a lot of people online saying that he read the solicitation wrong and exactly like 240
Bowser
Probably robots
Do you have at the cult leader is
Corrected
Infallible is immediately box
People saying that a robot
Long Branch
Screaming about how right he is about everything
I wanted to pull some clips I mean it's not any different than any other
Screaming and it's one of those things that reveals
Every cult leaders deep AB insecurities behind
They never feel comfortable and so they trying
Can create this bubble wear
They always feel
It's a it's a coping f***** up
That it was based on what that color we just heard
Challenge
Cut it discusses like
Yeah that caller East you know
You can always said we're not right and I'm like oh my God this is all
Response to that caller
But this is business
So you get done with the rat and then he says this
And it sounds
Little teeny
Screaming at Authority
Earlier
I'm sorry I went on that unhinged
So I triggered by a collar question whether I got some facts wrong little bit
All the time
Billy starting New World Order 100%
He is a loser little titty
Ridiculous
So I want the beginning of this episode that there was going to be apportioned it was going
We have arrived
So
If you are particularly since
Some f*****-up topic
Now might be a time might want to
Question
Skip ahead 20 minutes
Because at this point on this February
Encountered
And listening to his show
Before
Really want
No
Usher
Probably know who David Clark
If not that he's the sheriff who used to show up on Fox News sometimes
Wear a cowboy hat
I was fake decorative military medals he just giving himself looking like a real dick
He came to Fairmont of attention when he spoke at the Republican National
Convention in 26
We also started
Play pretty heavily that he wasn't consideration for a position
Was Trump's Department of Homeland
Security
That position ever materialized
And we can all consider ourselves lucky that it did
Because David Clark is a f****** Madman
And will probably be in consideration for worst botter and Sheriff Joe Arpaio today
That's great
Before he was the sheriff
David Clarke was a Milwaukee patrol car
Joining the force in 1970
As he rose through the ranks clerk was very careful
To the media
When he was selected to replace live Baldwin
Retired Sheriff
Milwaukee County
In the middle of his term
John Clarke ramped-up is Media presentation even further
Expertly staging photoshoot
Reading stories that made the
The department look good into the media
And always being seen in a full moon
However
Behind that facade with a very
A retired detective who worked with Clarksville Milwaukee magazine
Quote
The people who love him don't know him
The people who know him don't like him at all
When he was in consideration
For sheriff in 2002
He suspiciously wasn't endorsed by the Milwaukee play
Police Association
Even though he was the only Milwaukee Police Officer run
Which I think speaks volumes
Consider how close
Police Union
That guy is not good
There's always been warning signs the Clark might be a really bad dude
The 1994 Clark was accused of using excessive force
15 year old boy
The child's mother filed a complaint after Clark who was off duty
Allegedly chased her son and his friends down
Drew his gun on them
And made them lie on the ground
The boys want to five kids Clarksville throwing rocks at cars
Accounts vary with the mother saying
Your son in the head inside causing bruised ribs
Report claiming he just quote used his foot to turn over one boy
Which Meijer kind of sounds
Politely
Describing Kik
You got it
Whatever the case that is the complaint was dismissed
Estimation ruled there was insufficient evidence
Later career implies
This Mother's complaint
Might have been valid
Traditionally it's been the role of the sheriff's department to quote Patrol the highways overseas
The jails and provides
Security and courts
Reno County
But the city police and was left to local
Even though the
Technically within the county
What are the sheriff Clarke's big things with expanding the role of the Sheriff's Department
Involve itself
SimCity matter
As Milwaukee County Supervisor Gary Broderick
Put It quotes
He's in post
Himself on some other law enforcement agency
Eddie's uninvited
It would be one thing if he was doing a great job with a normal responsibilities of
The Sheriff's Office
Just wanted to share his ex
These other struggling depart
But that was definitely not the
According to Milwaukee magazine
In the first few months of Clarkson
First term quote his deputies got into a scuffle at the airport with police
Keith Jones
A convicted murderer Wrestled a gun from a deputy in a downtown
Did the deputy before being shot by police officer
Prison
Milwaukee prisoners Escape
Van driven by 2:00 step
I'm sure
You could make the argument that it was just stuff that happened at the beginning of his term
It's probably all just stuff it was lingering tub live Baldwin
Previous
Time to sort things out
And you'd be wrong
Because things got way worse
Is Clark Sturman office
Continue
On September 13th 2010 and epileptic man had a seizure while restrained in Sheriff's cust
Officers didn't seem to care over soak
Completely clueless that their actions made
Things worse
Forty-one-year-old James Perry died
On April 24th
Terrell Thomas died Welling
Custody in the Milwaukee County Jail
The medical examiner's office will go on today
Declare the case
A homicide
But when you get into the details it's pretty easy to see
Cy
Thomas died of dehydration
9 days after being arrested and brought to the jail
Thomas have been arrested on suspicion of shooting a man
He was also bipolar
So his behavior in the jail
To place him in solitary confinement
Which one would be enough for me
Me to say f*** David
Clark
The guards would claim that they did what they did because Thomas had previously tried to flood his cell but I don't believe that as an explanation
Super Why
They shut off the water to
Journal Sentinel
Thomas begging for Waterford days
Before he died
And given the fact that he died of dehydration
I think it's a pretty good bet that they give him
This treatment of a person
Completely horrifying regardless of what they may or may not have done
To end up in custody
The idea being incarcerated some
Where put in solitary confinement
Dehydrated to death
Over the span of days
Is a terror that no one should have to live
In the end boys were charged
For Thomas's death Milwaukee County
The million dollars in a settlement
But David Clark was never held response
The travesty
July 26th
Steve Sade squeezer was incarcerated in prison
Her newborn child died
County Jail
In December 2015 Jennifer Johnson's newborn child suffered a similar fate after guards failed
Provide appropriate help
That's a Christian if I bring alcohol and heroin withdrawal
County Jail in Milwaukee
There's a serious pattern of negligence and outright brutality
Exist undersheriff Clark's watch
And it's also
In 27
Milwaukee County Milwaukee County
7 million-dollar settlement
Two women
Aspire Garden David Clarke
Prison multiple
Times while she was in Carson
Fredbear
Incarceration
18 years old
Pregnant
Eventually gave birth in prison the county for the fact that she was made to give birth while Shackled
This wasn't the only person
Who suffered this kind of treatment
It's estimated that at least 40 women who have given birth of David Clarksdale have had to do so while handcuffed
Labor
Sheriff David Clarke is an absolute monster
Any of these people had to suffer what they did
But he didn't
Instead he defended
In labor 40 completely out of line
Organization
He was in charge of
You may notice that a lot of these problems seem to have gotten worse toward the end of his
And probably that's because by then
And Savor becoming a national media
In 2015 he launched a
Called the people share
On Glenn Beck's Blaze Network
Weirdly that's same here Sheriff
6 day trip to Russia
Is part of the NRA delegation
He's paid at least
$6,000 to go on their trip from the group right to bear arms
Which was the group run by Maria butina
Who pled guilty in December 2018 to felony charges of can
Unregistered foreign agent
Of the Russia
And was sentenced to 18 years
18 months in prison
Legitimately no idea what he was doing there or what
But it doesn't
Cool
Parkwood Sheriff of Milwaukee County
Money from 2002 to
One of the likely reasons he was able to stay in office so long was he was registered as a Democrat
Even though he was very obviously a far-right than
A2000
You cheered on the Iraq War going so far as to
At a support our troops rally
Scott Walker and Paul Ryan
Where he expressed his off or George W Bush's quote will encourage
Milwaukee is an insanely democrat-leaning area
The county has only swung Republican
Three presidential elections
12 and 2 of those three times
Eisenhower
Registering as a Democrat it being
The complete opposite
Is it really smart move
Particularly once you're already an offer
You generally win any primaries
General election
Versus a Republican
This is exactly what you see in every
Election cycle for David Clarke
Relatively narrow winds in the primary
A crushing landslides in the General Lee
I'm not
But if you were a manipulative power-hungry piece of s***
Your plans might look at
Exactly like what David Clark did
What do you step, Sheriff Clarke immediately took a position as a
Senior advisor for
The truck backing
Super Super PAC
America First action
In 2017 to 2018 alone right-wing billionaire Sheldon Adelson
10 million dollars
List of that Super PAC
They also received a lot of donation
America First policies
The political action committee we talked to what about a while
Trump campaign official
They received a lot of donations
Probably because they are affiliated
America versus policies is a nonprofit organization
But they're basically
This is a little bit of a non sequitur
But also I know is involved with one of Alex Jones's sponsors
The insane version of the NRA
I was going to dig into that a little bit
Butts
If you search for David Clark in gun owners for America
The first thing
Comes up as a completely batshit article
SuperAmerica website
It features an endorsement from Clark
Spy comes up in the search results
Uncle really isn't about him
Headline is quote
Is gone or do not overthrow America in your will
The article begins
What is one thing you can be sure that the Second Amendment rights are well defended well
The future
Putting gunownersofamerica in your will or trust
Settlements
America's
To defend your gun rights in the Press
Take a lot of balls to be like hey man f*** your children and grandchildren getting inheritance
About guns
Straight up
Movie plot con man
And they're doing it with
The explicit endorsement of sheriff Clarke
Yep he's literally
Fine
Yeah
When someone dies of dehydration in jail after
People who work for you turn off the water to their cell
Do you go to prison
What happens if you
100%
A murderer who is allowed to walk
Because America is a f***
Garbage fire of akka
Yeah after this interview with Alec
Before and somebody's indications
In the time
For there is every reason to have a very serious.
Destructive David
Clark even in 20
A very serious problem
With how he ran
His Sheriff's Department
The encroachment of City
Police
That the rhetoric that you was putting out
It was
Concern Alex buddying up with him
It's not on
Expected but
It's f***** up really really don't like it really loves play
Mussolini
If you see somebody play-acting and wearing metals
It's a good thing to assume they're probably either a really good actor
So I also didn't surprise until
Pop-up based on the fact that Alex is really on to the sheriff right now
Play constitutional sheriffs
Owners of America connect
David Clarke
Makes total sense
He was named like Sheriff of the year
At some point
Also just because
This is a fun fact
And Larry Pratt runs going under through America and
Incahoots
Fun fact Larry Pratt was super against the move to Washington
Three Senators back in night
He was quoted
Quote
The amendment would bring in
Would probably be minority
It would definitely be liberal on Gunn
Control course
Be liberal
The first thought you have
Senior opposition to the plan is that the Senators would like
Weird
The same reason that sheriff Clarke was invited to speak because they want a black man
In order to justify
Hating black people I've been pretending that it's not just cuz it's a pretty strong trend
You see like I was reading this article from
And may quote Scott Walker from before he was governor
City Council
Remember
Some stripe
And one of the comments
There's no way they could get away with saying these things about the black Democratic leaders
And it's because I know Scott Walker is that sounds
Pretty f*****-up Scott Walker
Then
I get what you're saying
Transparent
It is
Like I have transparent it really is how race
Vera Lynn today are
Otherwise
To give themselves Avenue
Pizzava
Probably more pressing
Tuesday
Trojan Horse
Absolutely
Something that shouldn't be
Call Stover
But
Being completely
Out of control with your departure
Or your
Tying down pregnant women
Yourself
Senior prison
Human rights
AR
Yeah but
To me the fact that the militia dudes
On his tip
And the cons
Institutional Sheriff tip movement
Entirely
Is they always
Lyin Eyes
Respect
You are an utter Psych
Like
Purely
Cruel Psych
As almost
An aspiration that
Power
To destroy their own empathy
It has been looking up to
For sure and then the other part of it is like
The Constitutional sheriffs that exist
Constantly talk about how they don't have
I don't report to the police
Yeah yeah yeah
John Wayne type
Right image
Is something that they
Just can't get enough of
That idea putting themselves
Most Authority complete
Control of everything
I could take care of the problem
And they projected onto
Is that
Yeah
Almost without exception
Every single one of these Sheriff
That I come up on
Nowhere near power people are crazy
Some of them
I will not endorse any
Healthy Sheriff
Yeah
I think calling them all serial killers
Unfair to
1 or 20 count
Yeah so I think that probably is about to
The really f***** up
Clark
There's some other stuff by David Clarke
Bears mentioning
I'm sure I meant the first is
Why is he on
Michelle
It's because he just put out a p
Yes
Alex is super into
I am self-funding of course I was setting last clip he was on P
Piers Morgan show
TSA was really f***** up
Sears Alex introducing it
Dpsa
I'm sure of David Clarke and I want to talk to you about something personal
Your safety
No longer a spectator sport I need you in the game
But are you ready
With officers laid-off of furloughed Simply calling 911 and waiting is no longer your best option
You can beg for mercy full of filing criminal hide under the bed or you can fight back
Are you prepared
Consider taking a certified safety course in having a firearm so you can defend yourself until we get there never duty to protect
Yourself and your family we're Partners now
Can I count on you
As We Know
Who paid for it
It's not the only around this 2013.
Much to the Chagrin of the Milwaukee County finance
A 2012 car spent over $22,000 on personalized radio
By June 2013
Thousand dollars
Do taxpayer money
So he could grandstand and promote his own personal brand
Naturally this lied to the finance
Committee voting to do this sort of self-aggrandizing bulshit
Some Dum Dums out there were arguing that they were putting a gag order on Clark
But supervisor Patricia
Who started the motion disagree
I don't have a bandana big enough
Have to gag the sheriff
You see what you saying is that he's a f******
Can blow hard
These PSAs Vicky madarsa
So f***** up
If you really break it down it's a sheriff telling people that police can't help them
And they better get ready to kill someone breaking into their home
Which is something
Glorifies kind of what I thought
Sheriff
Send out a PSA that's like
Cops are going to be there fast enough do you know what to do if you have a passport
Well okay you're in charge of the sheriff's
The other Pope
Police Department yeah supposed to be completely separate you're saying like
These other organizations
Also cat
I responded time
It's really sucks
Deeply
And If You Smell Trouble
Be decisive
Use the element of surprise
Against your attacker and most importantly be ruthless and your response
Always going to f*** with you and make sure
Well if they're in your home
Do you know if it's a home Invader I understand using self-defense
Obviously it would be probably better
Pasta
I'm somehow it supposed to
Specifically talking about
Encouraging
Random vigilante
Just take the random
So the premise of the PSA is it at their layoffs
And the sheriff's department employees are furloughed
It's time for 6
To be cops is around Little House size video
You see the Department's going through
X Financial
I probably unsurprisingly
A close look at why you find it's mostly David Clark's fault
Surprise me interesting directions
Of money that came into the
Department through civil asset forfeiture something Alex is very totally sincerely
Reddit spent 11,000
$400 out of workout equipment
Hundred dollars for a police Harley-Davidson
$77,000
And what's
Yeah I got a horse
$24,900 each
Nations train
What to do the new destination thought that it was possible that it was
Ettore's
Like because if you look for Disney destination
Google
Some parts of Disney
Apparently it's supposed to be about quote Disney
Approach to business
So they're getting training
Standard of Excellence
In order to run their jails better or something
It makes absolutely no sense
Whatever they have to teach you has nothing to do with it with a sheriff's department is doing
It's a waste of
$25,000
Didn't we have a war
Trials where it's like even if you're just following orders
You're probably also like you have a responsibility to it.
Employees
Someone should I
65 new Glock
Outfitted with glow-in-the-dark
565 guns for a department of only 275 officers
County Supervisor John
Junior quote
There was a two-for-one sale there is absolutely no reason to justify
Royce Silver
President of the Milwaukee County deputy sheriff's Association
They believe that this money could have been better spent helping
Reinstate laid off
Throughout his time in office
Constantly try to cut cost
By shooting
Responsibilities from
Sheriff's deputies to lower-paid employees
Correctional Office
Many of the jobs at his milk Milwaukee County like monitoring inmate
Worked all those responsibilities
Ring shifted away
Money all WellSpan
Things are cool like glow-in-the-dark gunsight
Dark Horse
Which also kind of dog tails with
That are happening in his jail
Is it possible that that has something to do with the
Less qualified employees who are now in charge of monitoring employee
I don't know
That's for someone else to study
You know the only person who really
Need like a vigilante to handcuff them and ensure that they don't hurt the rest
Country
Yeah we need a group of people to just like
Hold on to him
Bearhug
Can you be sent to the hateful things you do internally in a country
He should be sent to one of his own prison
I don't know which that even upon
The claim that underlies these PSAs
Every tears that all about
Their physical difficulties of the Sheriff's Department
He played a huge rule
Or at least
Another Factor
Considerate
Ego Live cost
He came out 2016 at the county had paid at least
$10,000
For Clark's lawyer to represent
In addition to that
Account you paid $83,000 more to defend itself
In those suits
That's about $400,000 that wouldn't
If pork with.
Listen to his job
Clark is like all of these supposed Patriots Sheriff's that Alex idolizes
The petty tyrant
Hooters
Degrees terrorized the very people there's more
Check answer
In the strongest
F*** this guy on the horse you rode in on
Would cost Milwaukee County 77,000
I hate him so much is really wanted to work
I knew some of the awful and egregious things that he
Exactly
Like
What are your father's stuff about like
Feuds with city council people
One guy who is
Is budget of Heaven
Yeah
There's so much more like
We could have turned this
CenturyLink
6 hour episode about maybe there might be a behind the bastards
Completely overlap
Ridiculous
There are no
Protections in place
Because
Everybody kind of just
Assumes that
Well we won't elect a psychopath
Where we can all just go like na na na
Redo
It's about David Clarke in the deputy sheriff's Association
They voted like
If something
I don't remember voting
Voted for him
Like this guy give you 77 G
Discretionary
It came out of the
The money that you have gone back into the
The department
Alex
If you knew anything about the
Taking a lot of money
Just take from the citizen
What's up with that
God you are philosophically in line with what I believe is love
Yeah
So many people who wrote our laws and everything
People who
Good live
A better life
They just forget that
Anytime you want a psychopath could show up a
Trick people into
Alex
The show
4 something
He is absolutely not
As long as I get my money
Alex had a
Yeah I mean
But Jenny payment probably had
He was just crazy small town
Because Joe Arpaio David Clarke have particularly flamboyant
That doesn't mean that all of these Sheriff's have gone
Yeah they just don't have the Opera
Maybe they happen to be replaced
Where there is better oversight
Of what they're doing
The circumstances warrant such
That happened
Possibly
Not
Unreal
He's a piece
Off
God
Her interview is just about like it
You bet they are
With him
Clark to say that he would follow the oath
Keeper Mountain
Framing
Trying to get like a
Promise from him
That he will not go along with
Kind of confiscation of guns whatsoever
Andover County
Exactly
In such a way as to be like
Tomorrow I can report
He's on board with our booth
Dwight Clark
Answers this question
In about why he would never get
Involved with gun confiscation
Call firearm
And make some tournament
Ford
Something
That magnitude
You would see the second coming of an American Revolution
Like you to the likes of which
Makeup Revolution
Feel like a parrot that's
His reasoning isn't so much that like hey it's the wrong thing to do
Killed if I did that recognition in his reasoning that like
If I did that
People would kill me
The definition of Terror
Clark's support
Not taking guns are not regulating or anything like that
Assume that he was a sheriff who did believe
That may be some sort of Regulation gun registration would be inappropriate thing
He might have the same position
But if I did
Yeah is that circumstance
His ability to it
Express his political belief is being
You terrorize
By a group of people who has made it very clear that if you do anything like this
We will kill every cop in America
Terrorist
Alex isn't gopb
Yeah
This inspirational terrorism
Oregon climate bill
This ride is
Literal threat of murder has
Perfect yeah
It's been having an effect
4 years
And when you see the sort of thing on Alex's show on 23rd
You realize that like
There's a pretty good indication to
Meet they know what they're doing
It's intentional using fret
Tacit
Implied
Threat
Whatever whatever shape it might take on any given day
As a means of furthering their
Political ideology
And that
My friend
Is the definition
It's a win-win
Because
They can get
More and more
Aggressive in Irvine
Threat
Org
Their free speech being violated
To engage in this verbal terrorism
I don't know how intentional it is but it's a good song
If you if you have no ethics
The fact that you're destroying Society
If you don't care about those sorts of things
Pretty good Hustle
Yeah yeah yeah
It really Banks hard on them
Believing that the world is going to
Before any kind of karma
Before there's any kind of comeuppance
Further action
David Clarke
Is discussing how the last
Serious about
Reduction
The argument it like all their gun control measures all of the
Gun control
It's not about violence
Because if they were serious about violence
Production
They get behind
Him and the initiative
And
Join me Armin Armin calling for longer
Incarceration
For repeat career Criminal
Who has demonstrated over and over again if they get a handgun they're going to get a firearm
The only way to Clark what do you think
Any sense here is if you was doing that what he means is that he wants to reduce crime by law
People up forever
That's the only way you could realistically be advocating for longer sentence
Repeat criminals from re-offending
Expect to get caught
They do not
General Behavior option of
Describe doesn't go well
They're generally an optimistic bunch
In this
The consistent finding is that the severity of a pun
Determinate of value
In terms of it being a dick
But what does
Is this a crime would be very low if we lived in an authoritarian because the odds of getting away with a crime
Will be very slim
But that's not the kind of world any of us want to live in
Alex is already voice
Strong support for Clark
Which should be picked up for
Surprise
Dear Clark expressing another position that is a direct opposition
Longer prison sentences don't do anything to help lower crime but you know what they
They drastically raise the prison population
Dancing project using information from the national research
Cancel half of the rise in prison population that occur between
80 and 2010
Was attributable to the growing Obsession in our country
He was given criminals long
Prison sentences
So politicians could posture like their tough-on-crime
Super-predator
I mean that
That's why we have a much larger prison population
Mandatory minimums
And it was a bipartisan affair
Prison sentences
Single variable calculation
And that variable has to be red
He wants to
To be the one punished
He's trying to trick you into
He's doing it for your benefit
Longer harsher sentence
Do not deter for
First-time criminals because they don't expect to get caught
They don't deter
Repeat criminals for the same reason
Think about it for one f****** sex
If you're in the mindset where you're going to commit a robbery
Do you think there's a single bit of do
Between 20 and 30 years in prison be possible
If you get caught
If you're okay with
20 the other
What time is it going to swing you back to
Your senses
That's complete nonsense
If you just talked about lock
People open till
Or until they're cooked to
Insanely cruel
Gable end up balloon in the cost of incarceration pass
Disappointed Society could probably carry
As people get older the health-related costs
They have go up
And that rises even higher in prison population
The cost of incarcerating people who are reaching the ages where many of them have
Medical
Dumb idea Society
Especially considering all you would be doing is
Buddy that could be better used on initiative
And programs that work to solve the problems that
The crime
The clerk doesn't want
Crime
He wants
More punished
That is an important distinction
In this monster of a he
That's why I what
Norway or Sweden
That has the lowest
Recidivism rates yeah and their prisons are
Well
Who like three times lower
What is the difference between
20 + 30
And you can leave
Intellect
We're learning
From the mistakes that we made as Society
I think we're learning terms of the scholarship
That we have
Weather Society decides to implement
Is a completely different Quest
People like
It doesn't seem like we're going to
And people like Alex Jones
Can spit weaponized illiteracy that
Fights against
People who
Study and research
Just want to make it
Clear all the rest
The stuff that I cut out is just
Guns are cool
We need more like
So after you still riding High interview
I guess I kind of agree with him
I will not be involved
Did Gunn
Consultation at all
Which helps
High-profile
Our Squad
Zoe's Pizza
Someone who looks weird
She's not radical
Everyone's gotten radical
He's not far off from what America was originally
He's a lot farther off from our ideals of what we were base
In terms of actual historical
You know
Existence
I think Alex is always wrong
Thomas Jefferson
If you want about the founding of the country
Very interesting directions
Restrains
Present
Really
So Jordan really he said firearms
Again
I want you to guess
Is this
A real Club
Easiest trivia game Overworld this is not a real quote
George Washington quotes
George Washington was said to have said the following in a dress
The Congress
Completely made up quotes
Important
To the Constitution
Keystone under Independence
The church
The plow the Prairie wagon
Citizens Firearms are indelibly related
From the hour the pilgrims landed to the present day events occurrences attendance
Proof security and happiness
The Rifle and Pistol are equally indispensable
The very atmosphere of firearms everywhere restrained
Evil interference
They deserve a place of honor with all that's good
It's important to remember George Washington was kind of
Machete speaker and a city writer
Very serious tip-off like the pros
Is very unlike the waves boat
Most likely
This is the consent
26 by PewDiePie
My cousin called
But we never tried to pass that off as a quote
Fort Washington
The interpretation
Contempo isn't intentional misreading of his opinion
He's talking about
Washington address
And then that paragraph is
But it's not a quote
.
Is presented as Washington
Words rhyme with mist
From
His editorial article in
Hunter Trader Trapper permit
Time
Confederate Southwest
Is really working hard to Rebrand
I don't know how to do anything about CS
So I don't I don't
I don't know what his intentions
Whatever until it doesn't
Seemed like he was trying to run
Yeah it seems like those are his words he's feeling
Which is why this is interesting because those are not washing
Or Jefferson's words
They RCS wheatley's feelings about the history of God
Which would not have
Nearly as much
Avatar
We're Alex to quote this correct
Give a quote that anybody
You should be able to tell
And that is his intention of prairie wagon
Hooter certainly not something that would have been relevant today
Lifetime
Seeing as the french-owned the Great Plains
And I Washington would be
Be dead before the Louisiana Purchase
Also in Washington's lifetime for uses the word pilgrim
To describe the first
Call mr. K mobile
That terminology
She didn't become popular until the early 80s
Assertive indications
Red Sox
Comply
Over the years this has passed around
Picked up the most traction was being a big
Piece of rhetoric put out by the militia of Mont
DJ balloons book
American extremism history politics of abolition movement
Not only does the militia of Montana's employment
These founding fathers typify the malicious argument
Respect of the second
And the importance of
It also provides another telling illustration
Can of the extent
The militia stick to identify themselves with the tradition of America
History
The militia of Montana's desire to receive the approbation
These founders
Steven Lee overwhelms the demands of historical Act
Madison's words
The Federalist 46
Are compressed
Misquoted slightly
And those attributed to Washington
And Jefferson are simply invented
Malloy goes on to make a really good
There a lot of quotes
Melissa folks
It's from this time. They're real
Some people like Richard Henry Lee or George Mason
Patrick Henry
But what all those dudes have in common
The people like George
Container Thomas Jefferson
Hooter
Absolutely makeup quotes for don't
Do you know what the difference is
Washington and Jeff
Person knew how to read
No
The people who the militia community
Quote accurately
Are pretty much all anti-federalist
Order put simply
They were the people back in the late 7th
Hundred who are opposed to the ratification of
Constitution
Federalist are really who the militia people are most
But they're largely not seen as the founders of
Country by most people have a basic view the route
America
People like James Madison
Alexander Hamilton
Benjamin Franklin George Washington
People associate with the country
And they were all federal
So in order to associate themselves with the rightful lineage of the country's founding
These Patriot militia Folk
Make-up quotes
To Federal
If I had to guess I would say that Alex's
Constant misquoting of Jefferson
To attach himself
Federalist Legacy
Or him being so dumb but he's just been fooled by militia websites and newsletters he read growing up that we're doing
Exactly that
So I think that's probably a pretty good explanation
4y out
Constantly
Yelling fake quotes from Thomas
Literally nobody
The United States more than the people who profess to love the United
I think you could
Didn't want the United States
United States
Federalist 10
Centralized
Government
I believe that president was just a replacement
Yeah
Federalist you probably wouldn't have ended up with the Bill of Rights
Weary
Much more closely
Mirror
The militia movement
People
Right
To be like we are like these people who were against
Constitution
They don't want to beat they don't want
Create a fictitious
With the people who were
Founders Inn
Rata fires of the Constitution that they idolize in Spanish
Itsjerian
And that's why all of Alex's information
Have to go back to go back to him
No absolutely
Cuz otherwise he's completely disconnected from the lineage
Sound
Anyway
Just for fun though here's a real quote for you from walking
In the Revolutionary War Washington
Inside the militias were quote worse than useless
He wrote to Congress and quote they come in
You can't tell where
They consume your Provisions exhaust your stores
At Last At the critical moment
Washington was not until
Thought they sucked and they needed a former Governor former Army
Sew-ins Xscape we get back to
After Clark
It's back to complain about how the meteorologist
I'll just saying that I said all this s*** I didn't say
Didn't say that I said
I'm telling you that they
It's a bad who's on first
Additional irony
Outside the asteroid belt
Empire Strikes Back
Oh my gosh look at
Like my wife
Wow
The one piece
Covering
Meteor that blew up over Russia
He's insisting
Incorrect
He said it was
The secret Lisa
Some sort of an attack on Russia
Very upset
Don't cover how accurately
He actually has about stuff like
Flew over Russia was a spur
Off of da14
Or was related to
But that itself is
Shity reporting that Alex should be
Be criticized
I prefer to call it the 14th of
Da14 was making its closest pass to Earth that day
This meteor exploded 12 miles above ground
Very irresponsible reporter
Conclude the related
It's to space things happening on the same days must be connected let's go to lunch
All credible astronomers the Russian meteor Chelyabinsk
I had completely different orbits
Nothing to do with each other
To quote NASA's jet
Propulsion Laboratory
Not associated with asteroid 2012 da14
I which made a very close flyby of Earth just 16 hours later
This is because the two objects approached
The Earth from completely different direction
Entirely different orbits around the Sun
And their compositions are
The time of their arrival was certainly heads
F****** big universe out there and crazy
And sometimes do happen
Caught everyone off guard
Because it was below the threshold size
Four bodies that are monitored by the International Space Age
That's why I came out of nowhere
Which actor
Start a conversation
We need to start monitoring smaller ship
Near-earth objects could f*** us up pretty quickly smaller even if they're smaller it wasn't at all the criticism
Was being made by
Mainstream media but Alex absolutely deserves
We're at all
Because the claim
The connected isn't just
Service light in Acura CL
Nothing
It's part of the dangerous Broderick
Isn't reality
Coming from Alec
Meteor was a piece of
Is Metro
Can't trust any expert
They told you
But how do you know how about you tell that to
Thousand or so people in Russia
Injured by Chelyabinsk
What appears to be just a simp
Instance of Alex being wrong is actually a functional
Pizza
Which is built on a misunderstanding
Or just an outright lie
What they weren't
It's easy to gloss over this as just like you know he's just
Which is what they did
And I think I
Did the first time but I heard them talking about it
But it's it's
It's more than a fairy
If there's there's so much like
Even the stuff that should be a disadvantage
If you don't have any shame
Turns out to be an advance
You know like you should
You should
Feel embarrassed
If you are dunked on that hard
Shity
Instead of just
Doubling the fuckdown
I'm the best there ever was
Because I also was a true
And so then you take that inability to feel shame or take any responsibility for
And turn that into the media that is
Trying to get you to feel those
Spell
Listen to
The slippery slope there is real
Bucked up
Here and just end things on a sort of
Please God tell me it's a good thing
Not good but it's not bad parsley palate cleanser
This is the literal end of the episode where Alex
Does taking a call from a guy listen
Inside info
About
Barack
Someone in my family is in heat
Received the medal from Obama
He said that Obama refused to look at any of them in the eyes
He would look in the shoulder
Wife of Woodruff contact with them
He had a
Handshake muscle nothing to it you know
The icon
Most
Interested in this clip
Fake laugh
There's the first part of the fake laugh
Hahaha
Focus on that
That's creepy and weird but also like
What do you think he's holding back
Like you see just not formulated his Obama smells like sulfur yet he's just not
Figured out what
To do like what is
Pretending he knows
Uno's
For a fact that I'm his inside sources that Obama
Has been aggressively average dick
Okay I really an insult
Or is the danger Breitbart unimpressive Vols unremarkable.
I mean like this color is like
Really think he's going to get some mileage out of like he's Olympic
Grill grate
Free upgrade
It's pretty pointless
Do you remember when people used to be like I heard of has a limp handshake
Instead of
22 People's Credit
I think it's fine
It's a it is a deterioration
Little better by slide
Did George W bush
When I was in college
Around that time
Sure
That's that's
I am not
Too far away from you
Uh-oh
I
What I'm getting at is I hated that dude
He was the word
But if someone came to me
And was like he has a limp
That wouldn't right
It wouldn't register
Radio show where I talked about how Bush was terrible all the time
I don't call her I was like hey man I know what do to met him he had a limp and Shake
Get the f*** off the line
Have the right to waste my time with even if I'm just about to end the show now I'm extending the show
Use
Stupid a******
Public Disgrace to meet out
Yeah because you don't want it
Encourage that sort of behavior in your collars
All the sudden do you like now
Acceptable
Call Lynn Witt
Bulshit
Exactly
Exactly it's
Really cheap ins
Whatever is going on on your show
Consider you just
F****** interview date
Clark
You just spit it's it's trash
The show is trash
But at least it also promotes celebrate
So you know
Good track
Good work guys interesting leaves
The show full time just so I don't have to deal with it to the present
They lost in space
Look at this
It's a real bad
Couple days on his show
Real wild
The defensiveness Israeli interests
Really escalating
Maybe a couple of stories came out
That mentioned
Any other Google
Responding
I'm so aggressive
I think that might be
Something that
Gross
I think that might be I think I might be a very serious friend
Prestera pay
Shinto
Brought him up in the past
Responded
Couple of days
Constant
Which feels much more modern
The navel-gazing
Self-involvement
Is very
Represent
His present day
Style
That's interesting
I don't know
Yeah it kind of suggested we always knew that
Statistics Drake by
As we see it
Kind of grow into
It's Fab
She loves Trump
Yeah and how much he's trying to
Emulate that behavior of just
Complete narcissistic
Self-aggrandizing
Yeah you know that
You don't have any shame
Ben
There you go you turn into whatever it is they begin
We spent a lot of time
Discussing how
He won't shut the f****** about going to a morgue
Did you know little about it
Narcissistic
Acting out
But it also has
Appearance of like yeah there's a big show for you to go on and people were
Talkin about it
For Better or Worse
Yeah but
Is giving a thumbs up
Or some of that being like hey you just made us all look like you got a crazy ass whole service to euro
Probably because yours is Chill
Whatever it is it still on
Strike me as like
How do you narcissism
As much as this.
Like this Atlantic article him lying about what they're saying
The stuff about like
Fox
AP article
About the 1.6
Those are two things are much
Lowers
Scale
People are not talking
About this
That much
CNN's reliable sources is related to
Reliable sources
It's interesting too
Maybe it's just because of its it's been over this stretch of time
Here's the way I look
The requirement
For that which he will obsess about himself
Seems to be
Wow
For the Piers Morgan
Just like
Duck store
Fear of value list
Just do whatever you can
A PR
Kind of person
That's exactly what you would do
Effective
Tip my hat
Listen
It's stupid it's
Defensive
All
In service of growing
Growing his
Is sort of
Legend
Much
Petty Revenge
Responding to an article that quoted
One of your writers
Correctly
With no
Real Judgment of it
I don't know
It is it's not you that there even talk
I wonder if I guess we'll probably find out sooner than later because if Alex is doing the deposition
Right
There's nothing happening project
Camelot
So I will be back on Wednesday but until then
Beer website
I bet it is
We are on Twitter
Facebook we are also on iTunes
Casual app
Location
Yeah
You can also find
Drip rainwater that will actually sound like our podcast
Listen to it that way
Really struggling
To try and
Screw those babies
It's just a
Overcast
Not enough Sun
But as we get to the end of this
This is going to become president this is really tough this is not a winner though I got one
Okay cuz it's a hypothetical person
Person out there who owns
To sell it to me
I bet you haven't killed anybody anybody
Probably terrible
Adjusted nice
Podcaster out of Chicago
Cover
Is H
Alex