Alex
Everybody
You talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan
What's up
What is your what
Bar games
Hoverboard
Like what we talkin about
9 a.m.
Play cornhole in college to hang out with my boys
It's all I got. An improv guy when it comes to names
No I've never been to
I have a cross eye and I think it affects
My depth perception a little bit darts
Bags are particularly tough
To figure out the right angle on
Madoka be wrong if I start having a few
You know drinking
Steve myself he better
I like shuffleboard more but
Just cuz of that fun
I'm saying that's
Aesthetically I enjoy it
Pretty good at bowling
Only when I'm drunk
Okay
Drunk are an amazing at bowling throwing the ball really hard
One time
E46 must be there's only one person who can confirm this but one time I bowled a
Perfect game okay temper Lanes here in Chicago
Technically
Because it started
The fourth frame of one game and then continued into the
But I got 13
Straight strike
But it was
That you would be the perfect game
But it was carried over to game
Set
I was blowing my own mind
What if I do
The Michael Jordan game going Joe Fernandez
Chug another beer and throw ball really hard
Fernandes Addison Illinois
What what
It was not
Bowled a perfect game
Episode
Particularly about my prediction
Generally
Stray away from
Then I'm making any kind of
Declarative statements about things that may or may not
Desiigner last episode
It had been reported that you were supposed to go give his deposition on July 1st
Hooks trial
I'm Auntie was suspicious in his absence
At the end of last week reasonable conclusion
Didn't know if it was true but I made the leap of predicted you would be gone
Monday evening
Historically speaking the only predict
That are ever true are the ones where we're like
There's no way that we know what's going to
Yeah the only prediction they all the sudden
You got to give it up to the Somali pie
Weather going to be right around the corner
Showed up on Monday in-studio ended his show
And I was
Immigrant
I'm preparing a completely different
Do you know hey
Alex has been gone we haven't done present-day episode in about a week or so
So I figured it is our is our duty
To cover the July 1st
Episode
We started recording
I think this is one of the scariest pass
Messages that I've ever heard.
The show so warning
If you're scared of things
Yeah it's
It's actually just three hours of him singing God Bless America on a loop
I would find that I would take her to be like a little picture
Butter
Would like to take a little
We really appreciate it
So first of all Craig thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
Jackson Journal
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Next bath thank you so much
She going to Apollo
I know you're laughing because it's the name of a kiss song
And they're named Lookout
There might be listening to love God
Pretty hard
Finally
Somebody donated on an elevated level
Preciate it
The Robert
Business
Freakishly large
If you're out there listening anything
These guys do you do that
Kygo Tour website
Wood
So Jordan
1st of July days before the 4th
Such a great day patriotism
Fourth of July
Today on 2nd
So
See if minute when we
So I don't know how it's
You know what I hope it turns out well
Prayers
Women soccer players of these United
So on the 1st that was Monday and over the weekend their headband of course the rally in Portland
Patriot prayer
They're Affiliated groups that had
Better for a bed of a shoe
Zavvi
Counter demonstrators were out in force
You know ships
More of the details about that
The stage for what Alex
About first episode
I sent a lot of things are going to be true all my God so Maddie
There was much more in-depth
Hereafter a few Clips but
It came out of the
The protest
Counter demonstrators
Dum Dums
Is
Osho Tobias
Lefty liberal media
One of the things
Became out of that was
A lot of accusations
That people were putting concrete
Milkshakes at the premise of it initially was
They were turning them into
The bricks but then they could
Broward
That works right
Certainly
Alex
Takes it
Even further
They're making
Bricks
In cups
Case wide open
Exclusive
So many angles to the fact
Today's more than 100
Wards.com
The eyesight
People's faces were burned it with acid
AR
Big League politics
Yeah
Little bit further down the dial-in
Mainstream
MSN
Me and Betty
True
Because Alex
Proof
The videos
We have the audio
The photos
Michelle shared videos
Concrete
People faces
Dot-dot-dot
That's probably a pretty good time to point out that
The right-wing is either manufactured or been
Tricked by fake
Antifa accounts on Twitter and Facebook
Bruises like that
People playing pranks
Going on TV
Pretending to be auntie
Fever like I want to punch a horse
It is something very eager to be tricked by
Go so far as to say they're looking for that information more than they are worrying about
You can make that claim I feel likes for me because I'm trying to stay on
I feel like that's an assumption that would be
You know I don't want to assume
Who knows
New York Times
Chemical attack
Let's not get into that
Real Petty
Newyorktimes.com
Sobec
So Jack.
Get sick
Yeah
I get it
Gone
So the narrative
Concrete milkshakes is going to play a very large part
This episode so she's probably exhausted
Right about now
Surprise
Justin
Small point I might use the term
Antifa
The way that Alex does I do not believe that they are a centralized
Antifa is not
Some sort of
What is the leader of
I don't know of any organization
Nobody's like I'm King Auntie right
To play into the right-wing framing of the
Conversation in and of itself
Try and book back again try convection convention is best
What if I slip up here or there I apologize
Clarity
And not living up to my own
I'll get into specifics here in a couple minutes but for now I want to make a
Get totally clear the knot
It's completely manufactured fascist
Smear being perpetrated by dangerous monsters
Details about this narrative
Wyatt
Sprite
Next we get them to something we've discussed in the past
The milkshake is the perfect weapon
Against people like Nigel farage or Alex Jones
Because it really doesn't
Elicit that much sympathy from them don't ones like you're hurting them
Nothing you can ever do in his life will undo the image in the headline of Nigel farage worth using
Leave his bus
Surrounded by people with milk
These m************ are a joke
Their fevers response
Help highlight
We understand
But unfortunately so do they
They realize the potential of having to put up with a constant barrage of Milkshakes whenever they're out in public is a fate that there no
Not particularly interested in
Because make no mistake about it
What is going to happen or would happen
There'll always be someone willing to REI
Riska Petty assault charge
Particularly distasteful monster
With a milkshakes
So they have to go about the rest of their day
Rally covered in
I will do a lot of hours of community service
Estes Road milkshake
Milkshake on Pol Pot
I think you'll be fine
Panicstream
Comparison I'm trying to stay on diet
Just ask for
Where's there
Power is really only
Supported by being able to come
Control Heather followers prestige
Considerably if they're constantly yelling.
It doesn't work for that
The best way to fight back again
Places to transform the milkshake into a deadly weapon
This is honestly one of those predictable developed
Information
It's a really short
Storm
People throwing milkshake
That makes us
Even more silly and way less manly ineffectual
I got a solution let's just kill us with those milkshake
Great lunch
You can't throw rocks at me
Right
People say with milkshakes
You are making me look silly
Just told people that milkshakes were Rock
It's like a milkshake is almost adapting the behavior
Consideration
The Narrative the concrete milkshake is born out of that mess
Portland Police
Who said the quote that progressed officers learned from some participants that a substance similar to quick-drying Concrete was being a
This is not evidence
But it was enough for the Department to post a tweet on their official
Twitter accounts quotes
Police received information that some of the milkshakes
Today during the demonstration
Quick-drying cement
Anyone hit with substance
Today to report it to
To the police
Now at least that tweets that just received information that this was
The case not that it was actually the key
There was Concrete in the milkshake
But it doesn't matter
That was enough
Immediately the right-wing media sphere of s*** heads
Jack Pacific retweeted a picture shot by Shane Burleigh a people making
They were adding the concrete no evidence at all
Just talkin to
Much like the quick-drying concrete that wasn't milkshakes
Humidified very rapidly
Article started being published with misleading headlines that implied
The Portland Police
As opposed to what
Which is
Possibly even a right-wing s******* themselves
I told them that it was
McKay's
Business Insider published an article with the headline quote
Protesters threw milkshakes
Quick-drying cement
As far left
Far-right groups clashed
Portland recordings
That article includes
This passage
Currently there is no evidence to substantiate the claim of concrete or cement found in any milkshakes
What the heck
Oh so they didn't put the
Narrative
As evidenced by his proof that he was right all along bounce back
And forth very clear to see
This is a right-wing
Mirror from the Court directions
Right into the right-wing media
The goal is to make this Avenue with bacon fashion
Just look stupid and silly
Making it treated like a life threatened
So counter-protesters can't make them look silly
That is the name of the game
There was no concrete being mix
Milkshake
Text because if there was there's literally no way there wouldn't be any physical evidence
How many people would have accidentally
Drank concrete and died
How many easily identifiable puddles of concrete would be strewn around the park
How many people would be able to easily produce articles of clothing with concrete all over them
How many police officers would have their uniforms
Covered in concrete
You'll be a really easy thing to prove if it were true
None of this has been produced as evidence because it doesn't
Exist
The burden of proof is not on me
Or anyone else to prove that there was
Concrete milkshake form
Heads are making this outrageous
Just playing the concrete milkshakes
To be used as weapons in Portland
And does it is on them
To make their case
Improve it
This is being circulated by career
But pretty clear motive
Talk to
Line of s***
Make sense
Sing it louder
That's what they
It's
Because the metaphor is so apt
The Portland Mercury put out an article quote Portland
Police offer no proof that protesters had milkshakes with quick dry cement
But it doesn't matter
By that point the right-wing narrative
Concrete
It was a triple to fax new revelation
The Refuge
It's even more perfect
Because most common form of concrete
Portland OR Portland concrete
You think I was some a conspiracy out of that but I guess I will take Sabrina
To learn about
He's not really into
That sort of thing
In a release put out July 1st
The police in Portland
And why they thought there was conquer
We're Liars said we're on their side
41 an anonymous person said there was
I understand the police department
Anonymous tip if someone is creating a weapon surreptitious
They wouldn't be doing their jobs if they didn't
When someone tells them to people to put in concrete
Responsibility to look into it
Check in with people or a milkshake
You don't make sure there's no credibility to that tip
If you're unable to figure out what's going on you ask people giving out milkshakes to stop or
What you don't do is take the
Twitter to broadcast
Is b******* ruber
It's ultimately at its core right-wing propaganda
That implies that maybe you as a police
Police Department around their side
Email after the fact
Which control
So that
After the fact
They got that anonymous
Email after
Vista the rally here.
Happened after they put out this
An anonymous email was sent to Bureau members with a milkshake
Which is laughable
It's a troll job
If I've ever seen one
How to get a sample of a bowl of blood to put it in
Right otherwise it
Otherwise it doesn't do any good
Alright I get I get the feeling that that's
Instead
That there was concrete
Alright I understand
To do really f***** up
Someone sent a troll email let's use this is
What is a rationalization effect
Support the actions that were taken
It only works
Post factually
It's f****** stupid
For now the last thing I want to say about this is that Alex
To take on the situation is far more
Severe than most of the right-wing should heads on Twitter and fox
Most of them were approaching this
German angle that leftist or trying to break concrete milkshakes in order have bricks to throw
Mechanical idea
But not nearly to the extent Alex
Alex is
Full-on going to argue that antifa was out there making chemical
In this sense Alex is actually smarter than most of the main
Extreme dumb dumb
Because if the argument is if they're trying to make bricks out of milkshake
Set theory
Both salt and sugar have a delaying effect on the solidifying of conch
Concrete workers use sugar or similarly constitute
To the product build-up give them more time to work the concrete before it sets
And it doesn't really take much sugar to cause that effect of very small
Percentage
Composition
Sugar will
Caused very serious delays
You just wouldn't be able to take the ingredients in a milkshake and add concrete to it
It makes all the brick
Yeah
Who has bigger argument isn't there's chemicals in fast-drying concrete that will cause chemical burns
Enter this
Technically correct
Does cause alkaline Burns
When exposed to humans
However all he's done
Is further sensationalize things in no way
It's always really doing when you get down to it is making things worse
Is this narrative were true
They would be even more evidence available
Consider how many people were hit by stray books
How many people had them spill on
There would have been chemical burns all over the place
Evidence will be overwhelming but it's
Not
Call Alex is doing
Is escalating The Narrative to unsustainable
Is it mainstream with a right-wing media is just interested in getting
Stop throwing milkshakes
Alex wants
Do to be able to
Kill anyone using
It's for family scary stuff
Episode
Like I said rank up there with the most upsetting
Things I've heard him Advil
They implied there's nowhere else for his rhetoric and worldview to go
Other than murder
I'm not please
He's looking for a shot heard round
On the world
Because
Exactly if you break it down
What you've got
A built-in just
Certification for preemptive
Attacks on people who have
Could be
I mean
Literally
If anybody who looks
The Kill
Haven't
To resolve those paranoias and those fears
AR
Unbelievably
Barry
Their offensive
They
Leeds
Probably the most dystopian
View of
Of what could happen
Next couple months
I don't know
Alex's idea that they have
On real people
Eyes are all
Mugshots
Shinhwa
Literally attack
It's all about perception
Milkshake attack
Pictures were circulated after the event
Saturday with a picture of a hand chemical burn and another was a woman who had
Her face has some chemical burns on it
You just reverse image search
A standard picture of a chemical burn
Shutterstock
Like stockings remember exactly but it's
It has been for a long time
The picture of the woman with her face was
You reverse image search woman who had her face burn
Buy essential oils
It has nothing to do with it
The concrete burning
People
But the stakes are shocked
Because
We get this next
I want to stress like I've been talking a little bit extremely about the conclusions that Alex could come to
Terms of like
I wasn't talking s***
You literally
Kind of expresses that
Fourth of July event
So it is just like
Justification
You're there going to throw up milkshakes full of acid at your children if you shoot them you're the bad guy
F****** hell man
Are Alex works for the Portland mayor
And I'm not so interested
Because
That idea
Milkshake to swallow
But I promise that will be the last milkshake.
I think it is
Because the relation
Clear between
The right-wing Folk
Police
What are the reasons the people took particular offence at
The Portland Police bureau's official Twitter account being used to publicize and lend credibility to the right-wing
About the concrete
Milkshake
Is it in the
Troubling
Trend of the Portland Police take the side of right-wing protesters
Even when they're doing things that are
Kind of f***** up
In June 2017 there was a rally in Portland that turned a little bit ugly
And OregonLive had article about it has been headline
Portland rallies without major violence
Intervene
Impression that everything turned out pretty alright
However here's the fourth paragraph of that article
Officers deployed explosives and pepper ball to scatter anti-fascist
Crowd gathered at Vail Square just north
Pro Trump
So
Just explosions and pepper balls
If the cops
The rally was taking place a week after Jeremy Christian had murdered two men on a train
Verbally assaulting
Attack
You don't want to tell the police
That rally was organized by Joey Gibson
Explosions in Peppermill
Leader of paper
Incidentally Gibson could also organize the far-right rally in Portland in April 27th
Jeremy Christian wasn't
And was found on video marching around doing nothing to lose
At the June rally gives
Concerted effort
The distance from cell
Christian which I think is a good idea
It's good for business
Stanford history
Australian protesters for about an hour
But a report that came out from the Independent police review division pointed out
That the police never gave illegal reason for their detention
Call tyranny
Pictures and videos came out of Portland Police wrestling a counter-protester to the ground
That might not have been too shocking or cause for serious concern
But the other thing that was in that video certainly was
Kelsey member of the American Freedom Keepers militia is literally helping the police detain the
Kelsey would go on to tell the guardian that the police officer who was arrested the guy
Had asked for his help
Despite there being a ton of other cops around
Literally three of them on top of this damage
Alone
Play get this militia guy and give me a hand
Well I mean he's a militia member there so
The law enforcement
There's a really suspicious theme
Emerging
The police were being on the side of the right-wing folks
Anticipation was
Confirmed on June 27th
When the independent police review released their full report about the police response
At that rally
They said quote what Lieutenant felt the right-wing protesters were much more
Stream from the left
Protest
And the thing that they were
Because the left-wing folks were quote
A group that was diverse in their viewpoints
Syntactic
A police officer
Well they're not all white
Portland Police Department was more or less showing where their priorities
And things got worse from
In October 2018 it was announced that members of patriot prayer were found on the roof parking
Instructure in downtown Portland
A firearm
Before a scheduled protest on August
Earlier
Joshua said to have included
No one was arrested which may be an okay decision if none of the guns were illegal and everyone paperwork was in order and all that
You're not going to risk when might be considered
Location with a k
Chiron
That Revelation should at least inform
How you behave is law enforcement during the upcoming rally
But it did
Police charged counter-protesters without rally with their clubs drawing
After someone told them that they've been hit by a water bottle with quote
Likely came from a counter-protest
Likely came from
Doug Brown photographer who is there on the told the guardian the first missile ice and hurricane
From the Patriot prayer
Across the street
Toward the protest
I don't know who set it off but it went towards the black Bloc
And then the police just warm them
The hospital after being hit by a flashbang
Joey Gibson second-in-command a man named
Was seen at the protest in a shirt that read
Cool
After another route
30th which descended into total chaos
It was declared
There's a clear pattern here it's one where the police department is
Justin doing anything
Control the far-right
The proud boys
That works he stayed violin
Actions under the guise of free speech
2980 Shepherd of the Willamette Week
Joey Gibson
Andy Portland Police
The messages start to make things a little more
Portland
Police Lieutenant Jeff
Leah appears to be providing protest
Gibson
The Portland Police were not monitoring protest hosted by The Liberation
Confront in an attempt
Dissuade Gibbs
Right-wing group from
I'm showing up
Which is to say
You're going to get f***** up
If you do that
Get your back right which is f***** up
No no it's not
The police did long been a tool of the fascist state but
As the Dover State but it's also tough
For me to fully agree
Mansfield
Portland Police lieutenant
No texting all the time with Joey Gibson giving him all of them
All Visa friendly banter and information
Ulta
Texting with
Someone from
Antifascista
Anti-fascist activist
But that situation was a little bit
Whereas me I was providing information
To protect his right-wing group
Nia was using tan as an informant together
Information about
I feel like this is a pretty succinct illustration of the way the Portland
Engage with this unfolding situation
Finding a snail
Add feeding formation to the right-wing provocateurs so they can avoid
It is a trouble
There's far more to the story than I can credibly explain to you here on this episode but it's important to remember that nothing
Stomach vacuum
So when the Portland Police Bureau tweets about something that's.
Concrete milkshakes
It often can't be
Seen as a single isolated event
But rather just one more instance
City gears long pattern
Of the police department
Declared their allegiance
Deciding with a crowd that is intermittent with neo-nazis white supremacist
Istanbul
Giving just the Republic
This is nothing
That's
The Portland Police bureau's current
Is named
Danielle outlaw
Ironic
Outlaw everybody keeps for voter just like wouldn't it be hilarity great
Call composite law
So I mean
This isn't to say that the Portland Police Department is 100 /
Working
Kathy's right
You know it when you look at the information that's available
You look at the stories you look at the trend
There is a clear preference
Differential treatment of the two groups
What is not explained by the behavior of those two
Yeah
Explain by the behavior of the cops
Soccer America
Started
The whole job of the cops
What is 2
Ensure any
Counter protest
It's a f****** to love the status quo
There's there's not been any protest in America
History where the cops have been on the site
On the side of good
Sodas bacon
It's not like a it's not like hanging out with their worth
Oh yeah
Which is
I guess it doesn't really change
Chicago
You don't have to have a universal problem
It does appear that way
From everything I can
So it is next
Just keeps doubling down
Position
Applications
For violence
Killing their political enemies
Fourth of July rallies
Support Trump
Rally's
With chemical attacks
Amethyst
I don't know
I don't think we can
Expanding
I don't really think anyone who is against anti-vax
Is anyone is describing an honor
Kind of means
But what he's doing there is
He's taken
You know
Everything
You go to
Be f****** scared
Every moment
You know what to do
You know what to do probably going to have to kill him
We know it
It's Justified it's defensible they're going to hit
Kid with a f****** chemical weapon
You want your kid to grow blind cuz some some antifascista
Through concrete
Then we'd better bring your barbecue that you're going to
Do you know what I love him with all of my family
None of whom are god-loving people who all carry guns in are afraid me
The exact same way
Is that a lot of people together with guns
And somebody maybe has a janky
Trigger finger
And somebody walks up with the milkshake maybe they fire on accident guns firing real quick
Iowa
Guy throws up
Trigger reaction happen
Alex
To report that there were
Containers
Of chemical
The Portland rally
Should be very obvious
To Alex right now
That what that people drinking and would be dead literally
Doing exactly what the lead-up to the Iraq War was
Who cares
Is Jordan of chemical weapon
Containers
Fox News
It would be open f******
That's what they want
Being like a conversation
Yeah you know like it
What are chemicals
Milkshake
No matter how much
Support social justice
No matter how much you are again
White nationalist
That you are breaking
Your crimes
After 1970
Becomes like
Unjustifiable
Not
That's why they want it to be true
Why it is never going to
So
Anyway it was next clip Alex
Explains that people with milk
Presumably have concrete
Apparently
Moffitt hours
They never will
You never see the
These counter-protesters
Anywhere other than counter protesting super right-wing event
They don't show up to you
Your house
But you know who does have a bit of a history with that
The proud boys
I'm a 2018 video artist Vic Berger formerly of Super Deluxe
Making fun of The Proud boys and their leader Gavin McInnes
Posted in the group chat
Beck singing all caps
Boat let's show them
Then dude showed up at Vick's House
Speaking to HuffPost Vic Berger said quote
When I answered the door you seem nervous
Like he wasn't
Expecting me
It was the middle of the day and my wife was home
He said are you Vic
Your your videos are hurting a lot of people
You're really hurting the proud boys
You need to stop making these videos
Probably because Victor
Chase the guy immediately this incident didn't escalate absolutely
The next level of scary
The proud boys are gang where you literally have
Have to get into a fight or get arrested for the Gang
In order to reach
The fourth degree of initiation
Which is the sort of thing you know
It's the sort of thing that
Did the sort of s******* to gravitate toward the game where you have to name cereals are getting softly punched
In order to join they might
That to me
Act out an assault
Don't like us
It does feel like that might be high
Vic Berger is harf Naomi
The critic of the right-wing who's been docs were threatened by the proud boys
Nathan Bernard also said his address posted
Twitter and others
Members show up at their home
This is a hugely an appropriate level of
Intimidation
Consider
To be a form of violence
And they know exactly what they're doing
You also Tommy Robinson
Who recently showed up at a Critic of his
At the Olympia Bank on his doors and window
This is of course
After keeping out the dude
Got a dress on social
I was doing so course the banging on the walls was accompanied by a flood of threatening messages on the guy's phone
Mike called the police and Tommy left 5 a.m. do it all over again
This is clear intimidation
Stop giving critical coverage
The phobics ball right races
Misogynistic
Somatic islamophobic
But overall s******* actors
Our society
Quote
Isn't doing
They're not showing up at your house
They're showing up when you have a rally
Make it harder for you
In public
Because your views are repulsive
That's what's going on no one's going he's goddamn house
Well anything that they are because
That's the same thing is putting concrete at the milkshakes
Indefensible like it should be for the Pro Bowl
The men Beyond this has gone to
Too far
People we disagree with houses
To his critics
You got to give it to that guy
Anyway
So in the next clip
Sure that's pretty bad
Worried
Okay
The shooter
That's a great plan is that a new route
Beat acid
Acid Beats
Milkshake
Yeah let's say that
This rhetoric
Translate you can really feel that this 35 seconds
Is indicative of why
To do s***
Depleted
Responsible
A very day
Together
Dry balls out
Cam
Wards.com
Bring up for watching right now
Please remember we need your support America is going in
He needs to make it so extreme because that justifies why you need to give him your money
Yep we got a half-off sale on every
Everything free shipping
Antifas making chemical weapons
We need it
Right
He doesn't care that he's putting people in
Very serious
Well it's no because he needs money on a timetable that justifies the timetable that people
You know
Now it looks like
In the next couple days it's the summer of Rage
Just coming up so donate till we can fight but it's like I need $100,000 tomorrow
What is coming to your house
Who's on your kids at the 4th with the July 4th stuff
Reiterate
They're about to make their move,
Wow
Very extreme
Okay
So Paul Joseph Watson
Interesting
Idea
About how we go about
Skin care
Of this year antifa problem
That's not good
. they coming from him
Okay so it's coming to 11
With an object which is
Why is that
Is that can no longer hide their identities
So that's an interesting idea
It's always great to hear noted guy who cries about
All the time Paul Joseph publicly
The government should be the business of regulating
Clothing choices
This s*** is really stupid considering how many right-wing demonstrators wear masks
How the government can
Control the People's Clothing
The f****** insane thing for us
Supposedly libertarian to advocate for
Is the problem is that mask
Make people harder to identify your solution is to
I got bad news.
Paint makeup sunglasses
Facial hair
I guess the states
Also pretty sure a side benefit is that Alex and Paul Joseph Watson would then be able to make sure that Muslims couldn't wear their
Are the Cubs
Sure
And the best part about this Jordan
If you look at the pictures of the people who are making the milkshakes
Set the Portland protest most of them were not wearing
If you sincerely believe that these people were fixing up goddamn chemical weapons
In broad daylight around everybody taking pictures
You would expect they would have been the most heavily masks
People out there and I was not the
Paul Joseph Watson
People not be allowed to wear masks
Because they want to talk to them
It's subject a targeted harass
It's that simple
To step in and make
Easier for them to figure out who these people are steak
Soros
This is one of their favorite weapons of the information Warfare RC
It is simple bandanas
So they're willing to throw away all their limited government evangelism
Freedom b*******
When they're pushed to the wall
When they're when they're back is to the wall and people with bandanas and dessert are wreck
Kinder shop
They cry for the state it really is
Make it illegal for these people to make me look silly
Well I would be a hero I would we were fighting a war
Milkshake at resorts
Strongman I look
Silly girl
Did the government
Social safety net
So Alex
Paul Joseph Watson also due to very seriously like
Mad
About the idea that they've been
Kicked off social media not allowed
On patreon they're not allowed on
All sorts of other
Places where normal people
We know the group behind Alex's Gold Rose City antifa they've literally got a post on Facebook
Right now
People
People need to contact this website
Is being used
Who hosts that website
I want to be clear I'm totally fine with
Because if you do believe that this
You know
Somebody is so you know they're being supported on this platform if you want to make your voice
Your disapproval towards that platform
Express
To platform and his date so choose they can take the person off
Paul Joseph Watson
Should not believe
For the last
They absolutely not be like 8
Apply pressure so these places
Does he think he's
They're going to
Call his bluff
Like what do you mean
Like I was saying that as like a
Well if we get back
Why don't they
That must be a tacit admission that they support
He's just trying to hurt
Yeah
I think it's all just a little
Of the troops towards
Like hey let's flood these places with message
Maybe their crowdfunding to be taken away maybe we can get there
Website
Pizza Hut
Take kicked off its host
Let's start a brigade
Kind of thing
Lame
Certainly doesn't
Match up with
Anything they believe
It seems like it
Is so f****** indicative how is it the opposite
Anytime there's something that goes
It is just not working in your favor
Prince
I'm one set of rules for everybody else
And I want everybody else to
Pretend
So in the sex club
Prettiest
Texas
And
Version
Alex's
Position on
The last terrorist move
Chemical weapon milkshakes
If that's true
If what he is reporting is
Is true if you believe that
Why aren't you killing
You know what I mean is a reality and you accept
That is happening what happened
Is it like
Hey it's
They're throwing chemical weapons at people
Play Clair de Revolution
Clandestinely
Throwing
Chemical weapons at people
And the government doesn't care
How much more severe can the situation that Alex
Is presenting ever beat
I don't see I don't see another like
Ditto
You can always
Add a little design design
Alex
You are saying
People are in
Some sort of a like
No it's gone if you're throwing battery
Honestly
This is only based on
Just knowing Alex
Through this show
But I think there's a part of him that genuinely does not
I think that it would be a war
Unless they
Yeah I like up the police station
How dare they use a guns
I think that you might be right the idea of the shot heard round the world is
That's interesting
Something that I thought
Nope
Crazy Alex Alex has a new product
He's selling in honor of his coverage
But he wasn't almost
Left of the clown World Ultra limited edition
Dot-com
So I wanted to bring this up because I heard Alex called his democratic debate coverage
Clown world I don't really think too much about it
It kind of makes sense that he would call the Democrats clowns
If so
Just made so much about the fact that he literally said
Fortunate
Because you pretty much takes every
Really crossed my mind
Is it somehow weird
However it's come to my attention
From some people who spend more time
Clown world
Analysis clearly signalling
Declare World meme began on the
The publication forward Put It quotes
They were they were describing the illogic of a liberal non-race
Society
When they were poestories Betsy
Seem to fit into the world do they use the code Hawk Hawk
Express that everything was back
From there the terminology and me and took hold in all of the wrong place
If you can't really popular on The Daily Stormer
And on April
22nd of this year
Members of the American identity the white nationalist group formally known as identity evropa
Dressed as clown
And enter the New Orleans Public Library to disrupt a children's story time program being led by local
Welcome to clown World honk honk
Their signs that I'm really afraid because the right is
They're getting really good at it
The world is not for me
I think you've been gone racing
This means our kind of stuff
So I'm probably not the best person to cover this topic and all the nuances of it
But suffice it to say that Alex Jones
And world at this meme that he's naming his Denmark cracked coverage
, sourdough
You know
He knows what he's doing to Disturbed
Pathetic to see how far he's fallen
He's gone for being heavily associated with Ron Paul's campaign in 2012
The drink a quart racist edgelords as fan
Doing interviews with count dankula
Really sad what a couple of really big
Bad decisions
Can do to a person
Career
Like I'm not saying that his career was amazing
Before but comparatively
S*** like just a couple years man
Like it for him
To those big decision
A million small one
Death of a Thousand Cuts
Really made every May
Mistake and then leaned into it
He thought he could mistake his way through to the other
Dukes of Hazzard
Not working
You can't jump Snake River Canyon
And I can mixed metaphor
Here is my references
Directions to the metaphor
You're literally
Paradox
So
Anucort Alex's
Constantly saying
Yeah I f******
Selfie
Bro
I love
He's a good sales but
Oh no my show
Am I at
Are different
They're separate
Now okay
This little clip together is just so amazing
How
How exactly indicative it is of how intertwine
Show and add our content
Marketing
Are completely blind
Think about how
Free speech
Foxes
Most like a poem structure
Content content
It's okay it's not it's it's
It's not
Control it's almost like a DNA double helix
It's the two argue
Inextricably related
Is
My girlfriend
Baby watched
One night
There was this
They they go walking in a park
Somewhere and there's all the sudden
Very very conspicuous
Ice cream guy
Selling Halo top
Or whatever
And they get two big things on the camera Zooms in on
Cut to break
Halo top ice cream as a proud sponsor is like
Too much
Bad product placement
I love
I get up
Co-product
LG batteries
So I saw pack
So
The argument
I mean
Emboldened by
Stories
Antifa
Paul Joseph Watson
And has one
Gender prediction
That they lack of action on the
People forget
Weather Trump Administration
Restaurants
Is made in connection to
Deplorable
We all remember that deplorable
The deplorable
There was that Paul Joseph Watson is referencing a really dishonest
Story about a man named Scott
Who played guilty attack on the deplorable but two discussing one
Attack ready type of attack for that matter
Is that is a fence
So severe though that you just had to do 48 Hours of community service which after which
So
Federal terrorist
Johnny was arrested because
Keep it secretly recorded him discussing the idea of a quote-unquote acid attack
Deplorable
The conversation was about pulling the fire alarms and throwing a stink bomb
By the way
But of course
Or some s*** why is it okay to jail
Replied it down
Another one
Disrupt j-20
Which is a group is all about disrupting events surrounding the inaugural
It's easy to paint them as being solely
Trump as a group because Trump won
The representatives has gone on record that they would have been just as Act
Has Hillary won
This is suspiciously absent
Coverage of the group.
I mean it's obvious
Because why
The person they were talking to was a project veritas
And that might be true it might not be but either way this is not evidence
Anyone playing
Attack
Trying to get that way only serves 14
Exaggerate your side victim
She's really sad
Stuff that makes me real sad
Episode
Journeys like I'm bummed out
Pathetic
Tubi
I think quite literally threatened
End with death
Buy this radio host
And his
You wait for that
Wait wait for those feelings to really develop
And then at the same time feel like they are
So sad and pathetic
It's not worth my time
While at the same time no
They are sad and pathetic
And decided Satin
Pathetic as my only
Make it more dangerous for you
But yeah
So a lot of appearances about have his guide the light of London Bridge
Sure
He is being sent
De-radicalization
Training
And being put on a watch
In the UK who was the guy who
Download the bridge and there's an ice pack going on charge terrorist
Committed an act of heroic
Of how
The hero would be painted as the terrorists
Call Joseph
You got this Royal lawn and who was the hero of the whole thing
Always being poor
So you wasn't even political
You know what a lot of s***
I'm not
Save-A-Lot
Watson's covering the story here about Roy larner the lion of London Bridge
While it is true that easily call a selfless Act of heroic
Heroic
Have to get some sensitivity
Is the terrorist is Muslim
Which is what Paul Joseph Watson
Also small point
In his appearance says that larner charged
The terrorist yelling that he was British
Come on you can't do this
Referencing his paper soccer
He was drunk at a bar
Before they attack
I don't judge anybody
Meteor
A couple weeks before his act
Photographer
A foreign country
Who stinks like s***
Before yelling National front
I'm part of them
Oh no Lovin no political
I wear a lot of Reddit comments like discussing the situation and they're like oh my God
Mike's Milwaukie
You stalker rivalries are brutal
Also after his altercation on the London Bridge
Decided to drop by the
Coins
Piece of s*** all Muslims are the same
Scum
Alright
Court he admitted the first was racially aggravated in the second was religiously
You sentenced to 8 weeks
Largely because of his high-profile is a bit of a hero
He was however banned from dropping by his MP's office for two
I like that
Decorative don't come back
There's a trend
Absolutely it was a member of the national front
Senses of racial and religiously basophils
According to British
In the present-day found to be in communication with
Extremist groups
Radicalization
I guess what the government in crochet
Part of his plea deal in the whole racist islamophobic out
Undergo anger-management Diversity Awareness course
Any sentence wasn't suspended for a year
That doesn't mean it went away
It was suspended for a year
Offense within that year
Spend it
Less than a year later he was busted with half a pound of amphetamines
He was given another suspended
Remanded
Rehab program
Royal order has been given
Equallogic
Do the status as a hero Society
But that being said
What is another chance
The idea of going to
Training
And being like
Is Savin Hill
Him from himself this is not a pun
We are really
Look
This is us being really great
To lock up someone that has a heroic image
Keeping up with the extreme
With the
Tendencies that you've already shown
Oh man that sucks
So like I said giving him a lot of chances
Because he's
I think that's probably healthy
Foresight
Belvedere trying
Going out of their way to save
Soft
Because
God that sucks so hard that you can like
He's just
F****** islamophobic monster
Accidentally attacked
At the right time
Play kids
As almost every Muslim
Study ever saw sooner or later one of
I've actually bad
And then he
What are problems with the right-wing propaganda slick Paul Joseph Watson
World and how they make their money
Complexity
I won't have to be all good or all bad
And that's just not realistic at all
Just generally good people.
Sometimes
It's also the case that sometimes total piece of s*** rise to the levels of heroic when they're metal
Staking everything on this guy being always being in the right because one time he was drunk
Bought the rights
People seems like a bad way to
I would have the wherewithal to
To be able to do I hope
That should I be tested
In such a way I would rise to the occasion
But I don't know
I have no idea
I'm impressed by
Now he's come to
To the point of the episode
Goes wrong
So before we were doing good
Relative
Play Cowboy
So
It's interesting
You don't know the
The past and the present
Combine
When we look at them
I hate you
You know shows up on July 1st for that
Stewart Road
Tmartn2 showed up on July 1st
Reminiscent
To say
Organization
California and Oregon
But also start rounding up illegal aliens
He's in the National Guard Franklin
No no
So f***** up
He's not supposed to believe that that's okay well obviously isn't supposed to be able
Everything he believes
You should be against the idea of executive
President federalizing the National Guard
And taking them into
Two states where the governor.
Want them to be
Used for that purpose
I posted literally everything you believe that Daddy's for it
Stewart Rhodes
First of all I got to say
This drives me f******
Crazy
Change the battery on a smok
It keeps beeping
The background it's driving me nuts
Very small issue
The interview and the problem
It's there it's there that's the issue
Okay sure
Sure the content
Dogs barking
Yeah
Forgot about that
Tigers
So good so good
Stewardess
The president
Beef stew
Declare
Nebulously Define
Group of
People who oppose fascism
To be a terrorist group
Needs to
Federalizing National Guard
Two left-leaning states
In order to militarily suppress
This a anti-fascist
Counter-demonstrations
Wichita
Find out really glad we're going to kick him out of the country
Profoundly f***** up on an object
You still going
Expect a s*** head
But it's f****** crazy here
Delivery is so monotone and
Blase so matter-of-fact
It's very f*****-up
I'm put it as nothing
On what's
Succumb
As next clip
You can't get more f***** up
Portland
Frozen Fox
For 44 years.
Aquarium
Order to seal it in the National Guard
And bring us in the service
So when we were discussing
How's your road.
Largely a lot of his rhetoric
It seemed to be about the idea of finding ways to justify being able to kill your political enemies
Now six years later
What do we do when our very next episode we find roads coming in and arguing to make him
And his buddies the official militia
To go in and with
Support of the state
Go in and suppress the political activity of the people that they're opposed
This is
Next Level f*****-up
Not only
In-house
Button how it's so confirm
I feel like I feel like we just got
Now I'm feeling like we are being dragged Along by
Instead of in control of our own destiny
Patrick Seitz being a certain way
I was telling you earlier like 4 we started the show that I can barely sleep
Part of the reason was
Continues
Cuz it gets
Worse
It's so scary
The seriously are agreeing with it or
Even if it's
2000 people
So that's terrifying
But then also
I'm with Adam Carolla used to call the great magnet
The force
The controls coincidences in the universe
Step back in your life
Wow that's weird
This is so weird
Episode
I was editing a like
Am I being a little am I too
Stream bus Stewart
But I know he's a f****** head
Jumping to conclusions
He's trying to
Create justifications of
Scenario to kill people
Nope
Came together to be like now.
He has to know what that implies for the rest of the
If if
The suspension
That is the end of democracy
Think I care I don't think they care either I think that's
The defeat
That has to be what they're going for otherwise they would never advocate
Stay and your political enemy then
Had precedent that
Fine
To organize and federalized the National Guard
And send them in
Terrorist
Organization
Guess who the f*** they would be coming for an actual terrorist organization
Transfer of power Everett
The fascist groups that have ever been
Caught making a Napalm bomb
I can certainly think about
So it's interesting that you're bringing that up
I think they were they give a s***
Not but I also think
Democracy
Sienna
The the rules
Timing of it
As a necessary challenge
But they need to get around
Disabled
Chabad.org
What roads do this while Trump is still in
Control the military because we are shot
Being built
Charge
We don't they're going to steal the election
Showing all their cards
He's f*****
Believe
We worried about that possibility
And this is the only way that they can get
That the
The train towards
I don't know
Ethnostate
Or is Victor progress
Continue a Justified
Hey we'll get to that.
Millions of illegal in California
Completely insane
Disseminated
All the Judicial Watch found was that there was many is 1.59 billion an active voter
On the California voter rolls
This is nothing to do with illegal votes being cast there's no indication
Judicial Watch
Any of these people voted
These are people who moved away or maybe they died
I never sent it a note
This to take them off of Motorola
Probably because literally no one ever does
California millions or more
Illegal votes cast
Absolutely
These people are liars
And they're lying because they want to kill p
They don't want to miss
Just not fair
Dan
I think
The rest of us
I know
Part of me that is
This is true
The way that my mind is wrapping itself around what's going on
Is like
Immediately following the loss of the Civil War
Like that
The
People in
The Confederates alkyne
Got together with
Do you know what was the problem
We didn't take the military with us when we left
So what if we just had control of it and then tried
Like its
You know that's it but it does have that field of like
This is a group of people feeling like they have their chance to win the Civil War
In this next
Flip Alex
Does what he always does
Which is the
Expressway
Spy saying
But it's
Asphalt
Evolution
What was the last terrorist
July parade
Broken down
Congress won't act as blocking president
Crisis so it's it's
It's the last fall I don't want this violent but I got to do it
So it just makes clip Alex
Into what is
Is going to have
And his conception
Just for a little bit of a heads up
Description of this clip
This is
So f***** up
Floor into a black
A warlord state
How to be really on wow I've never heard Alex sound
And excited then talking about starving a city of people
Quarantine Blues
Like
Be fantasizing
You think it's cocaine I think it's just getting us
About the idea of terrorizing
Millions
Today
Where you keep them in at gunpoint
Did he steal all of this from Charles Manson pretty sure that's what I was saying was going to happen
Cuz it's coming down today
Yeah
Jesus
Helter Skelter
So
I knows it is already
Kind of reference
Best Buy
Play talk about how this is going to happen
Chris trumpism is tournament
We have to do this
When Trump is in charge
Illegal alien
U.s. military
So he's saying that
Federalizing the National Guard
It starts ethnically cleanse
What is what
You know not as many words Maybe
I know one guy
Boardwalk yeah
But like he's saying that if they do that then the last is going to start a civil war so f****** let's do it
Right
So somehow like when you're feeling sick and you just got to throw up
You feel better afterwards
Talk about a f******
Describing it as a self defensive War
Even though literally it is an offense
DeVore
From Trump
What does
Just federalizing the National Guard
Gets really mad about that
Chicken and egg
Alright
Atrocities are bad
Sure
Chicken eggs
So
Top cigarette how to phrase it
So you in the past
Have expressed ideas
That you know a lot of people probably wouldn't
Except him losing in the 2020 election
My position on that is I think that you are being a little extra
Because I lived through Alex's rhetoric and I know that that was what he was saying about the Obama at the end of his second
A bright it's kind of a sensational
Claim the people make that I think of
Kind of unfounded
And looking forward to your hammer
And I do think that's a dangerous
Prediction to make
I think it's unfair
Generally speaking
For the most part
Except when we're talkin about Stewart Road ever go because he's very
Bliss Italy in the sex clip
We're not going to accept the results
Will be in a civil war anyway
Cute analogy
If you have already used this Judicial Watch bulshit to lie to prove it
We're going to steal an election
Then no matter what if Trump loses you're going to say it was stolen
If the election
Stolen base
We're going to start a civil war of trump loses the election
All of this is dirt roads arguing if not now
There's no time like the present
Everybody Open Season
But here's the thing
Preemptive
Because he knows that eventually
He was going to kill somebody
Concrete
Already killed somebody
Did you forget about your
That was
It's mental illness
Is it
It's not right
At the same time
Eventually they're going
Kill somebody already
Come on
Stewart Rhodes quote Tim pool
About something
And makes
War
Preferably sucked up
Yeah but I heard that clip the first time listening through my heart
Sweater
Like I got a real
Sensitive
Holyshit
I can't believe we've reached a point
Where someone who is the head
Of an organization
Of people who has terrorists within their work
Absolutely
The guy who is the head of the Oath Keepers
Feels comfortable, not a program
Talking about how we might as well do it now and then talking about
A blase indifference almost the idea of killing p
People in the streets
Would we kill them
I'm in the streets Belle Delphine
That they were fighting against
Fascist
Do you hear yourself
I don't understand
That doesn't
I get you're saying that that
Sounds like something
I get it
I get why you would think that would you say that they will regret it whenever were murdering them in the streets
For their political beliefs
Now I get but
Have you
Let me give you a quote by Thomas
Thomas Jefferson
I cannot I cannot believe that
Like that
And I can't believe that I haven't heard Mediacom
That's the day after this came out
I have not heard anybody
Casually discussing
Starting a civil war immediately and
Given graphic fantasies about murdering people in the
The street
It is
So crazy
How many people are members of Oak
How many
People
Terrifying
Figure this
Especially when
Part of that
Like what he was really saying
He hid it
Really really close
What are you talkin about how ants
Jeep has mostly Young
And white
Yeah he's
He said hate their own kind
What you meant
With hate their own
There's a piece of that is what he meant all the way
Sad sad eyes
Very young white movement
Old man
Out of here
A little bit and we realized
Alex is still first
Stand for boats
Alex
This is a revolution
It always all roads lead to Rome
As they say
So
It is next clip
I think we just get more
Dirt roads being Ralph locked
Do you even better
We're done
Wendell
Political solution
What's great here
Because
If
Some media is to cover him a little bit
Bun B Alex
Explicitly saying that
Agreeing with him
What's going on
Yeah Alex is All Things Considered acquitting himself fairly okay and not committing any
Strongly disagree explicitly committed
Stewart
It's about the saying it yourself
I understand that there's a difference probably legally
Infatuated
But intention lies behind your words
I agree
Which is the last one we have
Stewart and then we just have one
Palate cleanser after work
They discuss Alex
From Stuart to Scott's house
It's going to get killed
Them streets
Comfort
I don't think it is
Oh okay
Unintended consequence
The ideas like politicians are also going to get it
Something
Something that happens every Civil War
Cosmic Civil War
They're really
Great job
I'm sickened
I am absolutely sickened by this rhetoric
Put out
I don't understand
Anybody in good conscience
Can do a show like this
Like the idea that
You can start with this
Excessively over-the-top propaganda live a chemical weapons and milkshake
To have Stewart Roads on your show
To use what you've built
In the first
Hour-and-a-half of the shower so to come in and
For a Civil War by the way we're going to kill journalist
To ask for cuz they're the ones
When they're really starting the Civil War
It's insanely f***** up if people
Take this seriously
The danger
Oven appearance
The interview like that is impossible to overstate
I pray that nothing happens
Pray that no one
Is Inspire to action by this
But these are two things make me really worried that Alex is trying to manifest
The predictions
He's making about the 4th of July parade
Fourth of July rally
Trying to get
People in a mind-state
Where it is trigger happy
Btime it's already the revolution is a revolution
It better well
Shot heard round the world happening on the 4th of July
Perfect why not it's the stuff of books and movies solutely
It's the stuff of movie
It's dangerous this is so dangerous I don't know if it's illegal
F****** feels like do you know who
Explain best what it is
He's trying to do
Him
Whatever he's
Describe what the left is trying to do
They're trying to start a war but
Jesus Christ
Consistent
Strategy
F****** unfair
Speaking of unfair what happens after this
Alex has an interview with
I don't know if you've heard of her
But she's a racist 40
Senior old do does
Podcast will never
Copperhead
I think it's
Disgrace
To cover it
Frankly and I have no interest in
Critiquing the political views
Of someone who still in
There is something really disgraceful about Alex doing the show that he does
And then having a 1450
Pedro
Who says horrible things
On his show as if
Genexpert
Like in the middle of the interview she
She's complaining about her
It's like
That's not real
I just don't know what to do with that
So we're not going to cover it and it's
It's not some
Saratoga Lake
I don't know how to put but I just can't I don't think I could
Deal with my feelings that I would have
About us spending any time
So
It is what it is
It happened
And
I'm not talk
Can handle it even like just
Physically from of
From a whiplash situation
It's like
Okay if Johnny Carson had gerbils on his neck
It was a dog trainer and the dog
Doolittle flip
I just won't be able to handle
About an hour.
Little better
And I wouldn't even bring it up to
Today but it's not the first time the
Jesus
I didn't talk about it before cuz I felt like it was something
Ignored
But it looks like she's going to be a part of
His stable now so I feel like
I'll bring it up that it happened
But
Document
If if
It being a regular child
Star
Fox up your life
Imagine being a racist forty-year-old YouTube
Aspic part of it to like like I don't
Think
Like as terrible as number the things I've
Over
I don't
Feel like it
Right
For me is a 35 year-old to
Take seriously the political views of
14 year old
Roar
You like
To imagine that they are
Going to remain
The same
Should I be mad at those two girls who are in a deal Nazi band
I don't know they grew up in there not.
Anymore
I don't I don't know what the right thing
Things to do as night I just don't feel good about
Yeah so anyway she's on who cares
Now we won't last
Is Jordan
In much the same way that I have a voice
Your ideas about trumps
Resist the urge
To think that I would
Listen to Archie
However
Alex brings up something
That we've heard him talk
A lot about
In 2013
But not so much in the present
Is there a dead dog but it's something very specific
There is no way
They're on the winning team
He's talking about liberals who go to college and get degrees
By Design
And the system once it catches you in a scam
Thousand dollars is it going to get 100,000
I know you're jealous I'm getting money from
Stopped yet
Break up
People's lives run off their husbands
Hillary
I'm so glad to have you as a listener Alex if you're listening of yourself bye
He's really hoping I mean obviously I don't
This proves that he listen
Where did that come from
We literally talked about
The episode before that like we talked about
A couple of days off
Jethro happens one of our episodes drops Auditorium
I want. Emails but I definitely did the trick about
100% totally desert
You're part of the
Knowledge fight
Restart to INR numbers are going up
To remember pieces of your rhetoric
Forgotten about already you're trying to remember what you said about
Nation of the lawsuits
Is listening to our show just
Turn it off
It's just mind-blowing Chris rollercoaster of a day like this this one episode
Buccaneer response
Ansible nonsense
Leading to the Civil War starting
Let's go people in the
The streets and then
F****** the return to Prince well boobies
Mind-blowing
Alex
I don't know this is a real difficult
Area like I don't
I don't I don't know where you draw the line in terms
Pictures of like
Farm datura
But I think allowed to continue at the
At the rate he's going at the trajectories going east
I don't think there's any way around it
I don't know how much
That fits in with
A robot
Societal useful version free speech
I don't want everything
Do
If things go bad
It's important to remember
But Alex made
That's
A very important
That is very cool
Does episode
At all
It was an emotional
Wreck trying
Trying to get this all prepared
I'm glad
It's over
Release of episodes
I hate the
The s*** I mean I like
I like doing the show
I hate this show in the present day
I want the episodes
He's still going to probably get
People in
In Greenbank
Belltown in West Virginia
About the telescope and how there's no phone
Fine
Episode 3 of Stuart roads in talking about the Civil War has to start before Trump leaves office
Just because he's going to lose the election we can't accept that result then we won't have an opportunity
To appear to be in the right
Restart
People
Stressed out
Socially useless
Corrosive
Dangerous
I think it's probably if not a crime
Should be
Like what he just did should be a
It doesn't belong on the Arrow Toyota
8 scribers
You put
That's the only way I realized
Should be a heartbreaker
That's just the end of the show
So we'll be back on Friday hopefully
The world doesn't band
I don't know we might have to do a real late night recording
We'll see what happens
Twitter also
Yeah
Knowledge underscore fight
Go to bed
You can also download the podcast on ice
Leave a review
Could share the epi
You could go to roh
Usually a lot of people there like to show
So we prefer if you go to a KOA
You can
Just kind of Mingle
That's how that's our new marketing
Sure
I would say that
Milkshake
Probably has
Is Alex Jones
Holding
Alex