Alex
Celebrate America and talk about Alex Jones
Jordan
What's your favorite cookout
Food God
Oh my god do I love a girl I love grilling
I love it
Love
Every Park
Are you go down by the lakefront
Wander around
30 Rock you hit a f****** Grill somewhere
Lovett grills places
Can't Get Enough
I love it because I probably hot dogs
You're not a bracha no
No
I do not appreciate
Map that a lot of people love
Text Shirley
Joy and one of them is
Feeling connected to the
The animal aspect of what I'm eating
Like I really don't like eating meat off a bone
Because it feels like you're biting
Through something involved in an animal
Is it that I just day I don't
I would probably be vegetarian or vegan if I had any
Restraint or control
One of the reasons I don't like
Do not like the recognition of the
Animal
What I'm taking
Chicken breast
You are entirely sure.
That doesn't have as much of a textural sensation is like
Eating a bone
Somebody to buy food issue
Chooser text
Great hammer
Just a good hamburger
Complicity to
220 hot dog
Beyond that I don't know tater salad
No I mean I like having Ron White customer
Those of you who don't know who that is and he is a comedian who goes by tater salad
Hydraulic steering
Collar Comedy Tour
We are going over the pass
I just want to say on our last episode
Silly little girl
Derogatory
Well coming from the mouth of the proud boy
It's
Because I was
Pretending to be a proud boy assumed everyone would hear as being this is what an evil person
Right right
But at the same time it still came out of my mouth
I understand everybody who heard it and felt like
I'm participating in this idea of silly little girl beating
An insult something
Wouldn't want to be
I do not
Want to participate
And that at all
And if
I've got real scared
Free-speech advocates
Oh no
No I think it's terrible to use that
There's nothing blind spots
You can have if you go through life and I think that that's probably why
Accordingly
Well sure you are in a character Where You Are
Personifying
Somebody who is bad saying something bad buddy
Understand that
Does that
Fall Apart
You adjust
Subconsciously believe you still wouldn't be throwing around the n-word
Subconsciously not recognizing how it might be heard to somebody else
Reminder to be more thoughtful
Directed
Set of just letting everything
You know fly out without ever even
For examining myself
Amen
The past
We are covered in February 19th and 20th 2013
Working
Full of tumbleweeds
Floating down the street that's February 20th
Episode
Is that so
July 1st
I'm outside very extreme
It was very scary and then on the 2nd and 3rd of July did not really develop anything
At all
It was
It was very much a holding pattern and it would have made for a very boring very pointless
Episode so from the present-day there's not really much
How's it go over
And then also
A lot of these wacky way
Say folks are
Very
Right now I think they really don't know what's going on with Carrie cast
But she is not coming through with
With content
So
We're back in the pack
Pretty in
I think I think it's today
So maybe underwhelming in import
Based on you know this is our last episode where it hits the roads are calling
I do think it's something
Very
Pens on this episode
And it starts right here
Mistress clip for February
Troublemaker
And is now or character who is
He is
This is this is great
About him
Does a little bit within the context of the timelines variant
Imma try not to get too much into the stuff at me
Me and Marty talked about today
Does not like heavy overlap
To me this is Wendy
Just on the heels of Alex being on Piers Morgan show
Justice
I don't know
The references included
Probably
Hooked
Turbulent time Pro
Now he's got a f****** guy in the WWE pretending to the fan of him
Yeah
Issues
Is that
Some people think wrestling
Is real
Inasmuch as they are fighting you know like
You do still have to put your body through a lot
It is real in that sense
Storytellers that is
Real in that sense but
Everything is predetermined storyline
Some people are incapable of
Understanding
Storytelling
I believe him
Because
Wow
That's one of the examples that he uses himself
Actually happened
I believe that was Alex if I recall that was you
Alex wrestling Israel's like me and my friends back when I was a kid thought it was real
Variable
I meant that was back when kayfabe
Was way more seriously
The business
If you are seen in public with someone you're feuding with
You better start fighting
Having a drink together you have to start fighting
I think it was Cody Rhodes told Dusty Rhodes
Injury around the house
Because it was part of his wrestling storyline like
From something
Sucks compared these wrestlers apparently
Haven't
Seriously
Taking it very seriously because if the illusion is gone
Especially back then that was what a lot of it was sold as Heroes and they were actually fighting each other
If you if you have them buddying up off hours it takes away
We really want to fight each other
XO the out whatever
Alex when he was younger was much
Closer to that era of wrestling
Then
Next clip
We already heard Alex say that he thinks about half
The wrestling audience
Sphinx it's all real
Himself
Here is where that takes
Real
Okay
What are we doing here
Okay what are we doing
Nacho Libre
He's heard
Minorities
Stop certain
I think their fanbase would not appreciate that as much as Alex
Maybe not
Experiment after 2013
So
It's interesting that earlier he said that half of the audience
It's can't tell if it's
It's real or fake the audience
Is it
These ratios are the same
Something interesting happening in Alex's
His discussion of whether or not people think
WWE pro wrestling is real
He accepts that a lot of people get there
Descriptive
He points out
The audience's novice
As if to imply that this cross-section of the audience's in Subway less capable
Understanding the wrestling is a storytelling art form
That alone
Is deeply Pickett
Feather of a position to have
And this is only made worse
When Alex flips up a little bit and says this a little bit later
They're watching
Really
So
Did the first clue
He's at the audience who's incapable of telling the wrestler
Mistake was half the Audience Network
And now just a little bit later you saying that half of the audiences
Illegal immigrants
This is how Alex sees this segment of the population
They're all illegal immigrants to him whether they are or not
Whether they're documented or not
He is using a Mexican Hispanic and illegal immigrant there synonymous
That's f***** up
There's some true, what else is doing
Explain that I need to explain a little bit of what's going on and like I said earlier to Rosa and I covered this in
In a past episode
A pretty 13 Alberto Del Rio was the WWE heavyweight champ
His character was a little bit of a flashy cocky Mexican guy
What is WWE's known for
Very poorly at
Just tastes like
Is that they make some of their storylines mirror things that are happening in the real world
In this case the writers for better or worse
Decided that a good voil for their flashy cocky
Could be an anti-immigration right-wing dude who constantly throws up dog whistle
By constantly saying We the People after saying something vaguely racist and threatened
Which was with Jack Swagger's character for the most part was
The Raiders built this beauty around the idea that Jack Swagger and his manager Zeb Colter would cut promos about how there would America
The really is about
Del Rio didn't belong here it certainly didn't deserve to be champ
The plan obviously has her Swagger to be big s*******
All culminating in a pay-per-view where Del Rio defeats the racist villain
And that's more or less what
It's just basic wrestling
Storyline
All Things Considered
With one very basic and massive
Twist
Namely that the ethnic character was not the default bad guy
Yeah that's good yeah
Whether you're a fan of it or not it's pretty dumb to try and argue against the idea the pro-wrestling has xenophobia
So much of the business has been built on Noble white Gyros defeating scary sometimes
Sometimes not for Indio
Of course there was a very unfortunate case of the group
Kaientai
For a late 90s group of Japanese wrestlers
And so they might or may not have been in Yakuza and also try to cut off Val venis
Alright
I remember velvet I remember that. I remember that being in the 90s
Is end thinking
Episode of the show about how this is demonizing Japanese-American
I really don't think you did
There've been plenty of
Very race
Gimmicks that are kind of embarrassing to look back at
Or the dancing African warrior
Bobby literal Muhammad
What does the cannibal Headhunter Kabbalah
The list goes on and on
The roots are so many
Easy bad guy tropes were created with guys like the Iron Sheik Nikolai volkoff
With a rock during the Gulf War
They often do this very poorly in with
Very little class but ultimately with the WWE is in the business of doing is creating emotional responses to their product
What are the best way to do that is
To create characters that fit pretty easy archetype
And have them get with each other about how their archetypes are in conflict
Each other
Right now for example and the WWE top bad guys is Daniel Bryan
New character is basically just a preacher
Vegan Environmental
Yeah
He's really good at his character
He won the WWE championship and remade the belt with hemp because he refused to wear a belt made of dead cows
He's a guy who's taking a lot
The stereotypes of liberals Chico Crusaders
And then he performs them as a bad guy with amazing skill
I do know what I haven't heard any vegans or environmentalist their liberal screaming about how this is meant to demonize their position
It's because they're not a bunch of big old dumb dumb
They get there certain
Things that are kind of annoying about their position
Anderson good fantasy those things exaggerated
To create a villainous character out of
This is how the Tea Party folks and Alex should have responded
The Jack Swagger
Or if they were adults
They should have realized and recognized that yeah
They do seem to be better at least a couple f*****-up racist among our ranks
And if something they could stand a little bit of exaggeration or parody any interest
Compelling wrestling
Story
Ultimately could have even been an opportunity
Versation about what is and it is what what is not acceptable within their communities
But I can't do any of that
For two reasons
Especially people like that
They took it
Deep down they knew that the things that
Jack Swagger and Zeb Coulter and their characters
The things that they were exaggerating
We're actually things that they themselves believe
And they took the presentation
Flagler is the bad guy
As a personal credit
They're goddamn Kahneman
Look for anything to raise their profile
The fact that Jack Swagger said that he liked Alex Jones is the best f****** thing to ever happen for Alex Jones
Oh yeah getting a mortgage
Sure was big for Alex
Composure
But Alex knows that this has
Potential speech
The rub is that it could only be gigantic if Alex can capitalize on
And laughing it off as a storyline in wrestling
That's not how conman capitalized
Ultimately I think it's super in
Interesting as a glimpse
How desperate all these right way
When folks are free
Allison Glenn Beck both went completely nuts
When a wrestling character mention
Because they do the balloon their rent
It's also
These happen at the time it does
We're seeing that in February 2013 Alex isn't a very defensive
Supposition
About media coverage
There's a weeks-long freaked out about Piers Morgan
Be coming to a close kind of
Ventura last episode
I'm freaking out about CNN indiatlantic accurately covering him
This opportunity to lash out
At the WWE could not have come at a better time
I'm going to guess
That he makes
The biggest deal
That he's actually just mad they think
He would send
A fan letter
No no no no
What are the things that's really interesting about this
And this is
Disgust
Did not care about Allie
WWE
This was far more about Glenn
Okay
Because going back was actually on Main
Where is Alex's
WWE
Attention
WWE recognized
This is also a really good
Corny thing for us
We're getting you a wicked we could all make money off if this is good business for both of us
The people back in Alex Jones started to
Push back on them
They
Dorf
Full on it
Because Glenn Beck started calling wrestling fan
About wrestling fans and how they're all f****** stupid even hearing Alex
Express
So in an unprecedented
Event
I don't know if
I'm sure this may have happened at some other point but I can't think of another time
Jack Swagger and Zeb Colter
Cut a promo
Where they explained what wrestling is
Took one back and here is the beginning of that promo
And I am Jack Swagger
And we are real American
Play believer
Whether people want to hear.
We are here
Great country from eroding into bankruptcy naturally
And Morley
We believe in some very simple principles
We believe that if you live
In this country
You should speak Spanish
Chinese
Arabic
German
You should speak
English
Real Americans are struggling to find jobs because people from other countries are sneaking
Across our borders and are willing to work for next to no money
They're stealing jobs from real American
Country illegally
Then you should leave
If you don't want to leave
We will make you leave
World champion of WWE
Is a perfect example of the problems that plague our country
Which is going to be WrestleMania
When the world title and begin to set things right in this country
Army of support behind
We
The people
Hey Glenn Beck
What you decide
Flea collar promo
It's a scene we record to a listen to positive or negative reaction from our fans
Say
We are entertainers
My name
Is Jake Hager
And I'm laying down
We are performers for WWE
Zeb Colter is the character I play
Jack Swagger is the character Jake place
We are in the political business
All the immigration business
We are in the entertainment
Everything is designed to tell story
Right now the story
Jack Swagger are using the current relevant and topical story of immigration
To Target the WWE World Champion Alberto Del Rio
Also a character played by my friend Jose Rodriguez
In our story we are the antagonist
And Alberto is the ProTech
Just explaining story
It's amazing
In the middle
I know cuz they're interested in Glenn Beck
I'm not in Alex Jones
I wish II
Dream this sequence happened but Glenn Beck is a home alone and he's just start watching this and then the TV start talking
Directly to him
Oh my God it's like a horror movie where the TV
Reven
Even though like the the strictness is that I kayfabe rules
Lazard
Duffy wrestlers we like
This is not my real name, character
These people were really insulting the audience
Rustlers in
Company itself
Probably took a bit of offense to that
At least on some level
EXO
This whole promo is largely like
You're calling already
Stupid
Let us explain why you are stupid
Sir Robert
Specifically at Glenn Beck
Glenn Beck a little bit of an invitation
At the end of the prom
Afford
To continuing to tempura box
Controversial stories with characters of all backgrounds and beliefs
Many of your followers are WWE fans
And they understand the difference between reality
An inner tie
Are you out of touch with your on this Glen
Or are you just a
Stupid
Political
Commentator
We cordially invite you to
This Monday
Or you can deliver
A 5-minute
Unedited rebuttal to our Global TV audience
Anna sold out crowd
Stupid
Wrestling fan
America's like Zeb Colter and Jack Swagger won't stand for
The country our forefathers built
Is part of this problem
And we're going to fix
We
People
Thanks buddy yeah
Pretty f****** Electric
Amazing about this is like
That's such an awesome response
Alex has got to be serious that
Didn't get the
I don't know if you would have
Food I will say I wouldn't have gotten to you did a bad job
Perfect setup
Not the other thing too is that like if you really listen to that promo except for Rolling the r in Dallas
That doesn't sound that different from what Alex says
At all
It's a it's a it's a parody
Only very slightly
Couldn't help but take it
Back and Alex
Both took it
And that pretty much ruined
Golden opportunity for all parties involved
Just keep that conflict machine Rollin Rollin Alex might have been willing to
Engage with it like that
To do work
Enough to do the job for him
Also probably never would have gotten involved with Alex and any real Alex would never allow himself to
Look fat
Yeah the job before somebody
If you're if you're going to get in if you are out
Situation
With
This storyline let's say
And the WWE brings you in
The way they probably bring you in
Is to like
Say whatever you want and then
Get fake attacked
By Alberto Del Rio
Right or the only way if I can yell at people for
How do we prevent that there's no way
No you're not doing
The characterization
It's only that he's back
Because you saying things that are very similar
To their positions and what they believe
But I think his actual positions are exactly what
Like
They're the problem is overlap
The Paradox is
More accurate
If you understand what I'm
Like
That kind of
Then Alex is public
They're exactly is racist
The parody
Whether or not you're right
I think of something to that
Sara is missing a mixing of Hispanics and illegal immigrant
Yeah I think so he's the bad guy
In the past
This would have been a white guy fighting Papa Shango and he would have won
The good guy
No
The big problem is
The owners of the WWE
Vince McMahon and Linda McMahon
To the GOP
That's what's going on here
Here's Alex
Complaining
Really
Because
Establishment Republican life
But before we do Alex's got talk some more s*** about Linda
Power structures
So the argument here is that the GOP hate the Tea Party and so because the mcmahons are such as Fabolous
GOP Folk
They're falling it.
In order to demonize the Tea Party
By way of a
Character
Linda McMahon ran for Senate
Connecticut in 2010
She's mostly remembered for losing both times and spending shitloads of money on each
She spent approximately 100 million dollars on those 2 campaign
According to USA Today 77 million
That was her own money
Even after she lost those races she stayed around in the world of Politics as a major donor for Republican
What you have to understand
The WWE has a whole hell of a lot to lose if they're subjected to regulate
The way they classify the wrestlers as independent contractors a lot of conversation
Recently
Employee with the protections
The complement designation
Their profits would be cut
Spending a hundred million dollars on policy
Is a pretty small loss is more left-leaning ideas about workers rights and more University
We applied the idea of these people who are like growing old
Injuries they sustained for gears in years of wrestling protections it would cost
Hundreds and
So fight back against
Make sense
Give millions of millions of dollars
People who will help
Protect the business
Logical advancements in the world
Worst
In the 26
Campaign donated seven billion dollars to Trump align super
She invents were big supporters of Trumps campaign
The WWE Hall of Fame
In 2013
And he was inducted into the Hall by Vince McMahon
Self
From 1995 to the present day the only
Where Donald Trump
Stone Cold Steve
Also hate
Everything
How do you know if your how do you not give Stone Cold
Induction speech
Such a big part of the Attitude Era
The defining
Donald Trump
Jesus
Christ also a little fun I already the WWE Hall of Fame ceremony
Only takes place on WrestleMania we
It's all part of the day's long celebration
Trump was inducted in 2013 which is the year when Alberto Del Rio Jack Swagger
Russell
B b savior that we're talking about right now
Real one
Also Trump was booed off stage when he gave his except
Your crowd was not super into a guy they were very familiar with who's been a piece of s*** locally for
Couple decades
Yeah pretty much
Bad idea did inducted to the Hall of Fame in New York
So the mcmahons of Trump have had a really interesting
Trip over the years
They began working together in 1988
When Trump was
Instrumental in helping
WWF WrestleMania 4 to Italy
Atlantic City
They hosted the event at the Atlantic City convention hall
Which was called Trump Plaza in advertisement
They would return to the venue for Wrestlemania 5
Making it the only place to host the event into
Consecutive years
In 2004 when WrestleMania was in New York Donald Trump was in attendance
Jesse Ventura interviewed him
And asked if he was at if that Torah where to get back into politics
Could you count on Trump support
Trump said 100%
Twitch Ventura gals to the crowd that it seems like we need a wrestler in the White House in 2008
It's very G to watch in hindsight
Also Jesse Ventura
Very heavily dying his beard at that point
Got very dark beer
Gone completely
He's pretty cool though
He is pretty cool 2007
Appreciation Night on Raw
Appreciated
Call them
Basically made it all about himself
In the middle of his skin
He's interrupted by Trump on the big
Screen who tells them that
Thought you dumped a bunch of money on the fans out of
I hate everything
Trump was even then obviously
To wrestle
Call this help
Spiders to represent them
Compete in a hair vs hair match
The loser would have to shave their head and if you're not a new 4-minute
Absolutely
Vince chose
Who he described as an interview with Imus
As quote
The strongest man I've ever seen
Bobby Lindsay
Did he
Did he just Mandingo us did that just happen
Special rest
So after last
Stone Cold and Trump celebrated at Stone Cold fashion
Which is to say that stone-cold chugs
A event gave Trump's daughter
It's completely bizarre
And very grim
In hindsight
This is all
Tragic
Now what you think about
The timer
This isn't January
Collaboration between trumpet
That's the point when it was heating up
But behind closed doors behind the scenes
Collaborating a bit more as well
Donald Trump been running the Trump sound
Station which New York attorney general Barbara Underwood described as being engaged
Quotes shocking pattern of illegality
In their 2015 IRS filing
Foundation B
To self-dealing
Or transferring assets or income to disqualified individual
Used more than $250,000 of foundation money to settle this
Disputes arising
From his golf courses and hotels
Use $20,000 of foundation money to buy a portrait of himself that no one else wanted to buy
It doesn't
To much of a controversial statement
To say that there's a pattern
OB legal Behavior
Surrounding the Trump Foundation
You could have gotten rid of
Sure but I'm talking specifically about that
Stop putting his own money
The Trump Foundation
In 2000
And his biggest donor in 2007
Was Vince
McMahon
Who gave the Trump Foundation
4 million-dollar
The 2000s
The foundation's total stated fundraising that year was 4.1 million
Go on to give another
If you count it all up you're looking at an amount over 12 million dollars that the mcmahons have given to Trump
Between 2007
Was elected one of his first positions he felt was to make Linda McMahon his head of the small business
She served in that position until Reese
On April 15th
It was announced that she was going to be moving on to become the chair of the pro Trump Super PAC America First Act
The exact same super packed
Sheriff David Clarke became board member of after he left the Sheriff's Office
Former Trump campaign manager Corey Lewandowski is also a senior advisor
For America First action
Fun fact
America First action between 2016
Spent over 400
$60,000 of the money that I brought in
Trump own proper
They paid over $120,000 to two firms directly tied
David Clarke
Clear pattern
Decide for yourself
Don't like
That
All of this
The Happening
First
I think the thing that I hate most about it
Probably
And how nobody doing
Pretty
Super Pacs
Are just places where people
Who get cast off
Baby no stuff
End up getting
Parachute
People who suggested that I don't know if you could prove it but it
Seems like all these weirdos are really slick Trump boosterism and become unaffected
An effective anymore seem to
All funnel into these America
First policies in America
The first action
A lot of stuff
Very volume
Campaign
Maybe they're more juice
Who knows
Could be
My point here is that the McMahon family has been deeply involved with Donald Trump
There's a real irony for Alex
To be calling about is gop's
In bed with a new world order here in 2013
A huge part in Alex's KERO getting elected
Is president
There's another funny piece here too
The mcmahons got paid
When Trump won the election he gave Linda
Job
Even though she was primarily a small business
Right
Even though she was primarily known as a pro wrestling promoter and a person who spent a hundred million dollars losing elections
Still gave her a job
She was an embarrassing aunt
Trump still put her in office
Something that he would never do
For Alex
The mcmahons are Trump collaborators
Alex is a useful
Yep there's a big distinction
It's really funny
To hear it back in the past
Little does he know all the
. man
Because this all sounds like
A f****** joke
Very bizarre
Alex calls for a boycott of the WWE
Cool
Boycott
Grimm
Which
The singer just contrary
Contrarian
Is really f****** dark
Stupid
I would love to try and convince
These folks to Liberty and my position
But it's not even worth it to try and convince them
They are brainwashed by the last door
Understand my position
Therefore
That's very that's very bad
Also
I would love to get it
Supercut together of all the time
Call Joseph Watson
Have like
If someone wants to boycott like
F*** off
A meeting from WWE
It's so stupid
They're all still f******
It's only infuriating
When it comes to
Yeah when they pretend to have some sort of a high ground
If that's
Yeah it makes it
It's so annoying
Because it's so late bear how little
Have they
There are no consequences
In there
Nas it don't matter
Topsail
About Jack Swagger
But it turns out
Across the pond
Over and also pissed off
Why is created a special report about the issue
Set
Received
From
Glenn Beck
And Alex Jones
Or Alex Jones
It's clearly a joke
Like what their operating off of
They're laughing
Comforters are laughing
They're making a joke
They're not even saying he literally got fan mail from any of those people
That humor
Over here
Paper UT position
Paul's report
That anybody who listens to that nobody's going to do while they would if you already frame it if you
Frame it is being real
Really I don't know
Casino like he's coming out like
These people
Said we're got you know and then you play that clip in your leg
The commentators
Are f******
Joking
Yeah
Nonsense
Whatever we make it back to this year in vape we may not who knows but it does next clip
Really aluminum
Okay and
If you pay close attention
Or dogs
You'll see that all he's doing is reading drug
Directions
Ocean trash is Ted Turner
Good point
Don't know where to live
Crazy is open about it like I'm just reading off
Headlines that I haven't read the stories
Drudgereport you're not doing
You're not doing analysis
You are cold reading headlines from Drudge
That's
Half of his career
Crazy
That's irresponsible
Amazing
Next clip
Wants to talk about the
Culture
Causing fire
Video camera
And wrestling
Meds now he's off the wrestler
It's it's
Triumvirate
Video games
Write psych meds course
My response to that is like
Shut up old man
I think it is somebody's mom be more of an old man but
Video game
The prevailing culture in the Youth of the devil love the devil
F*** out of here
They might be rainbow parties lipstick
That nobody ever did
So on this episode Alex
A lot of Long Grass
Thanks
They're probably going to kill
He keeps insisting that he's never going to hurt his family or himself before the bulk of the show I had no idea
He was doing that
Steam very bizarre
And then towards the end of the show he brings up this case
Leading into an inn
Introduction for his neck
Text guest
Investigative reporter not investigative reporter
Airline pilot
Security
Marshalls
So he's got a report
Philip Marshall
This is where Alex is getting his ideas that the government is going to come kill him then
Dodge no kill his family in order to make it look like he killed his family
For this Phillip Marsh
Philip Marshall was a pilot
Who had some connection
The CIA
He was involved with Barry seal
It's some capacity he was mixed up in Iran Contra
Decide
Some soft rice
Sure but with more
Like credible connect
Chance to attend Larry Nichols
In addition to that he was a bit of an author 911
He published a book in 2008 called false-flag 911
And a book that I was just brought up the big publishing February 2012 before
On February 2nd
Marshall and his two children aged seven
19 + 14
Profound
The children were shot as they slept on the couch
Situation is a
Intense track
Situation
Is 8
All the traces back to Alex
Sagacity is about to bring up Wayne bats
It's important to remember that Wayne Mattson often just make s*** up
He's the guy who said that Hillary Clinton's personal chef was murdered
Attached to a method call Larry Nichols
And that's far from the stupidest s*** that way madsen's
Reported
You might notice the Way Madison doesn't come on Alex's show anymore in 2019
And that's because these two dudes now
Heat roster
Matteson is a side of it Alex's working for Israel
Which is on brand for him
Since Matson pretty much thinks Israel's behind everything that happens that he doesn't like
Anders Breivik was secretly working for Mossad
That's something that he report it
He reported
Yeah
After Marshall and his children were found dead
Wayne Madsen went to the town that they lived in
An investigator
Hey what do you know
He found no evidence
The Philippa killed his children
There must be a secret assassination hit meant to punish him for the book you published
A year prior or something
I don't I don't think he was
I think he was
Sneaking around like
Course I didn't let him at the binoculars
A couple weeks after
Close enough like everything was probably processed by that found no evidence of
Assholes
To find out if there was any
I suspect look too hard because
Twist mist
Beginning in at least at least 2008 Phillip Marshall and his wife Shawn Plummer began having severe problems
Their marriage
To be pretty much all his fault
In November 2008 plumber sister told the police
Police that he told plumber that she quote will not see December
Which is one of many over threats
Pre-made to her
Former sister and reported on multiple occasions being afraid for her safety as well as that of Marshall
Children
She reported that Philip quote Philip keeps calling and driving by the residence
Behavior that you might call stocking
On December 5th 2008 Philip got into a physical altercation
Super plumber sister
Would you like to plumber getting an
Protective order against which violate
Throughout this time Philip was clearly involving their children if their domestic problem
When the protective order was issued police reviewed phone message
For his daughter
Michaela this is Daddy
We're going to have lunch
We need to talk right now
If not something is going to have
There's no circumstances under which it
It's acceptable threaten your children like
That is deeply abuse
Flower initiated divorce proceedings then
Back in 2000
Emotion and try to make things work
In 2000
In October 2012 she decided it wasn't going to work and filed for divorce
All the details
Listen to the crime match up perfectly with a double murder-suicide
The bodies were not repositioned nothing of value was stolen from the sea
Seen all the ballistic evidence
Exactly as you'd expect
There was no sign of a struggle and there's no disruption of the blood spatter evidence
Which indicates that there could not have been
Anyone else
A close enough proximity to have done the shooting
Since their bodies would have ended up causing gaps in the blood supply
Phillips fingerprints
We're on the ammunition box and Gun Magazine
The bullets used used matched
Specific type of ammo
But he purchased days before at a Big 5 sporting good store as confirmed by receipt
Security video from the store
Police police searching the house found his safe
Unlocked
In the safe they found his box of ammunition
Which accounted for all the bullets
Everything
I was sitting on top of the
They also found five bags of medical marijuana with a note next to it that said quotes hi Sean
Which is his wife's name
Medical records reviewed after the murders revealed that Philip had been diagnosed with bipolar disorder in 2000
I do his episodes of depression and grounded from flying commercially
In September 2000
They also found it in the more
Recent past Philip have been suffering from
Chronic pain
I've been visiting clinics
Trying to get pain
The bottom line is this
There's a whole mountain of evidence
Philip Marshall is the guy
And that he was struggling with a lot of very difficult
Their long-standing mental health battles as well as
Abuse issues
And beyond that and more importantly he had a
You clearly had a history of domestic
Which is the single factor that you will almost always
History of the people who do things like Philip dick
I feel a certain amount of empathy for what he must have been struggling with in his life
But that just appears
Really quick
When you consider how he treated his wife
Children in the 2008/2009 tray it probably plenty of other times that are less documented by police
Wayne Mattson doesn't know s***
And almost all of this conspiracy nonsense comes directly
You go to websites that are reporting on the conspiracy and have
Questions
Quotes about it almost all of it directly
Goes right back to Wayne Madsen
In quotes
Reporting
Is not
Bring up gun control
Talk mainly about the
NeverEnding
That is another one of those things
Most gun deaths are suicides
This kind of Scituate like
One reason that I
Would love company
Control is just because
I don't
Thinking I should be allowed to have a gun
My personal level of
I can't have a gun because
That to me just the mere fact
Owning it is
Owning
You know clicking off but
One of the things that
Is shown over
Study after study when talking about psychology
Profiles
The people who commit
Suicide is a little bit more time the moment
Bright
Hope you and I can talk
Pizza that from experience
That's a shity argument
I forgot control
It's not an argument for gun control it's something that I
Think is involved with
We should have got cuz it's bad for you to have a gun
To have a gun
Per se
I don't mean that no one
Figure make that argument
It's a good
Reason
They're to be more consideration
So you're buying a gun
More factors to go into
Absolutely
So
The reality of the situation
Without Marshall is very sad
A very
I need another way to put it
Incredibly sad
The horrible turn
And the way Alex
Editorial
And just make stuff up
About how he imagines
The whole thing
Is just
Next Level monster
Drones
If if that isn't true what he's doing is
So f******
Engrossed
It's not true
Based on the evidence available he's just making up a story line about a Cuban tragic
Can you imagine what his ex-wife is going through like it's still only a couple weeks after here Alex is on air
Talking about her children like
It's f****** awful
Because
WeedMaps
Is this next clip
We get
Starting to just report the Roni has information
About the situation
Unfortunately
All right what are you basing
Nothing
Hear this next clip
This is just Wayne Mattson make
Shut up
Marshalls wedding ring on a box
Like what do you mean what do you mean where did it come from
Oh good
Videos and buying ammo
Before
Bulshit
He presents himself as a f****** investigative journalist
The facts
Contradict
Everything he's saying
He doesn't know about the domestic history that police were investigating and and
Had police reports about
Glitter
Contradict
The amicable
End of the marriage
The fact that the police were aware of the security footage
Big 5 Sporting Goods or if he does
Please reply
Just completely lying about this
Fall back on is I talked to a neighbor who seems like a nice guy
Which is what people say about people
Every single f******
Hi
It happens right
UK me I wouldn't even say that if it was true
If I if I if I had a very quiet
Polite neighbor who I was interviewed by
Local
I wouldn't say
I will probably not say anything
But I also think a lot of the time
When people say like goes always a nice guy it's not defending them
Expression of shock
Seems like a nice guy
It's just boring response now
Clipper
Showmars
Some years ago
That's not true
Mental health issues that he had
You just
Years prior
That was grounded as a pilot because of that
And they continued
Play kits
. this is not
Okay
This reporting is not okay
Can you just straight-up lie like that I guess you can
Really what is
Do Weymouth
He's huge in the circle
I don't know if I don't think it's true but he presented self
What Project Camelot guy no big big heroic backstory
He pretends he's got a lot of scoops
And then just
Treated
I don't I don't know how
Actually make
Yeah right
Probably Google ads at the job that he purports
Pretty bad
Especially
These are been on
True thing
These have been things
Fact
Now
When he has to give a reason
For why he thinks the Trilla Marshall couldn't have killed her
Does children
Adam cell
This is what he's got
People who
Real bad
Thinking
That's like
Wow he loves the Saints
The Super Bowl was being held in New Orleans
And so he couldn't have possibly committed suicide
Prior to that
Cuz he would put it off until after the Superbowl
I don't think that this is a good understanding of how people in
Crisis actor
Like when you're in a mental health crisis
Other things do not cut
They're not as important
Things that you used to find great enjoyment and you no longer relief
Fuel vacmop
You know Hobbies Fall Away
Pastime
Groups that you're involved in you just drop out of
Like it's something that is very
Common
People who are in
Major depressive episode
So the idea that like we would he would have loved the Superbowl
That is
Not good thinking
This is bad investigative journalism
This is only okay to bring up
As like
You know he love the Super Bowl
It's a it's a shame
Primerica
Just kids
Yeah that's the only
Go to it
It's so
Alibi
Hi for a car
Miss the Superbowl
God dammit
The government
Super Bowl
Three days later then
For sure
It's two days before the Super Bowl 2013 Super Bowl like
Wasn't Orleans but it was the Ravens and 49ers like if he's a big stye
Just because it's at the stadium
We're not even engaging with that
Do you know how is even worse than that
I don't even want to allow it to
So here is Alex
What waves doing I think is
Inhuman
Like it's really disgraceful to the memory of the
You people the children
They're that they're lost
The family
What are you doing
Under the guise of like I just want the truth
Yeah he's doing is such a
Massive
To them
It
Can't be overstated how
I don't know how you can sleep when you act like this
It is
This is
One of the
Examples
That I will use
From now on when I say that
Because it goes for real
WeedMaps
He's getting haunted
Maybe his own apartment
Covington
So what are you doing terrible but what Alex is doing is pretty bad
Reporting on Wayne's stuff as it's fat
I mean like
It's the same thing
Same impulse as
The Jack Swagger's house it's only important because I'm worried that it makes my team look bad or
Whatever
This guy
Because there is one trait
It's similar
We're both conspiracy theorists
I must deny that he's capable
Of doing
Herend
Just not okay
It's not okay
To deny the ability of someone to do terrible things
Because you think it looks bad
Right
That is
Pathetic
It is
It's a bad thing to do
Defend anybody
Cuz they're on team
Regardless
Just got there on your team regardless
Directions
It's good that it doesn't
Work
It's good that it's an ineffective strategy
You know it's great
Kavanaugh
All of those
Nevermind
Perfectly
It works it so well
That sucks
So
This makes clip we're done with Wayne Madsen
I just really
Was a shocking display of
Evil being
Yeah I want to be done with Wayne Madsen
Forever
I was shocked
Like Madison was coming up to the beginning of the show sometimes
Boring
You guys are terrible I started to look into
The case and that I found these
Articles
Police reports in them
Contradiction
But from Wayne Mattson
You're leaving a lot out of this story
It's not the story you want to tell
You want to tell the story that
Depends
You
If you're not a factor
This is about
Okay here's what we
I got to pitch
We do a regular Ghost Hunt
Okay buddy
Instead of doing the like let's go
Alcatraz
Feeling out goes there
We just go to places where s******* like Wayne Madsen
And Alex Jones and all of those people
Have
F***** over people
And explain
I can't feel any ghosts around here right now
Well the problem with that is that physically it's a lot of
Some places
Like Wayne is in Washington DC and Alex's in Austin as they're having this conversation
Okay I mean
Alright I'll picture
But then we have to go to like California to
The crime scene
Fitzgerald Madsen crafted his interview
Then Austin
This is this again
Overcoming
They suck
This exposes just kind of funny
Tacos Alex
Alex
Casino
Casino gulag
So funny that you just described
Well I'm probably just some piece of it
Completely obsessed with Death Race
It's just really funny to me that
He's talking about it
Casino game show gulag
When in 2019
He is
Completely
Like most public.
Disgraceful bootlicker for a guy who ran casinos
Came to prominence as a game show host
And his running gulags
Police state
Casino game show gulags now let me
Really Grease the wheels so this casino running game show host guy can
Run gulags that I justify him running
Enraged
Angry at us being dragged Along by faith
Do everything made perfect
That's not okay that he accidentally got that right
Bulshit
Goes to show
I'm angry
For a large part of the end of the
Episode
Alex
Is
He's really mad at
LA mayor
Villa Ragusa
Sure why not
It turns out that someone
Has been putting up stickers
And posters of Alex's
Illegally
In Los
Oh no bill for the removal of those
Happy about it
He goes on to
To say like
What if someone hits
Spray painted like
Some McDonald's thing somewhere
Maybe
Depends on if the property owner
Complained I assume the reason that you're
The reason that you're getting a bell for this is that it was on
Maybe city property
Four on subway
Cuz I'm sure that the city wouldn't even remove it unless people complain
Just let it be
Irremovable difficult to remove
Posters
I bet
Complained
Take care of it
Alex
Complaints about it
201 2000
To enlist his audience to harass like
Clerks in La about a f****** invoice for probably like
$1,000
It's the time to try and send
Who cares
What absorbs
I'm fine with that
Oh man
No cuz you remember
He has to say all the time
Put them up in legal and lawful places
I guess he gets bills
Infowars sticker removal
I like I like the imaginary rules
System that these guys work on there like Alex is like
In a sarcastic way but if it was the sheriff
He'll be fine with it
Notification down again
Who said to Bill somewhere else he be like
Exactly right Sheriff can do all of that like it was a sheriff coming down on some liberal person hit me like
Good Noble law
Imagines that feel ragosta is coming around again
Yeah
Ridiculous
So Alex is nephew.
With Antonio
I look forward to that being continue to do this for a week
Max Keiser comes on
Is Alex gay
Max Keiser
Talk about how that you know how
It's 2 billion Bond
Bullets
Commodity
We're right there aren't very expensive
Almost think
He's advocating people buy them as an investment I'm not
But
I only pulled this clip out because
Listen carefully
Something very weird
So the bullets are always the weak spot
What
He's
Sing the bullets are cute
Eminem
He has to say that to himself
I think I accidentally
I feel that way
Yeah
Think so
Sincerity
He's expressing that is
But he thinks bullets are cute
Weird
So it is next clip
Yeah what Max
Kaiser
Procedure to do
Then you'll see
That we could happen any day
A massive kind of
They don't really have great now
This is what's going to happen to Southern California the place for economic
Analogo show
Almost
Without exception
Everyone that comes on
Has to either directly say or imply
Did any day now gold is going to go through the roof
Because Alex works for a gold company
This is ridiculous
Go to break
They're listening to
Commercials during the break
Apparently
Comes back from break
Laughing
Squatty Potty
He's been wrong about it
Pretty much everything
He's also wrong that The Squatty Potty is hilarious
Commercial
I don't know how hilarious it is
A little slight elevation in their legs is helpful
Coronavirus
But it turns out I'm probably wrong
It's for window mount
Really
Free Squatty Potty jokes in 17 seconds
Is impressive
Funny no
Hilarious
It's not funny
It's hilarious
Getting into the pro wrestling narrative which I always
Excited for
Disgraceful
Reporting about Philip Marshall
Max Keiser have joking about
The f****** right there
Nuts
The 20th is a show that I would
Describe is mostly
Full of
Poop
No
No it wouldn't there are episode
That I run into
To from time to time
They are just
This is Alex
Phoning it in
Yeah but it's
F****** impressive
The skills that he has
The ability to say nothing
Passionately
For long stretches
Yeah that's
Today there are episodes you'll just be like an hour you haven't said anything
But you're yelling
That that's
Right
Stock
Little bit
Industrialized
You want to
Brutal crash the dollar
It is all that all that strong in a row like they're eugenicist
Nothing
Just did General thing
The generalship thrown all over the place
And that's what most of the 20th is it was a hard listen
So nothing
Okay
You think
That he
He thinks about his show after he's done
You don't think
How could you do that unless when you went home you didn't even ask
Yourself like
Was today a good show
Not a chance
Whatever is a virus
I can read
About
Fuel
A great about it
Quite a bit I think it's the difference the difference between caring and not
I think he understands
Woody's talkingshit
Who cares
As long as
As long as you keep in the money coming in
That's really what this is about
So you don't have to worry about them killing him
You don't have to worry about actually winning the battle at the globalist yeah cuz it's all bulshit
So
He's not like man I did a really bad job you're always like hurting people who can't hurt you
Exactly
He's never going to be in a place where they can get to
Sure he lives in a townhouse
So I think there's something
But today I think you just
Suit of loser
Sense of caring
When they're already
Steaks are Imagine
So on the 20th
I wanted to play this but instead
Describe it for you
Because it's too long
Yeah a caller calls in and he's like
Hey
We need to be upfront about this
I'm saying that's not you
So you don't have to get criticized for this
It's the Jews
Of course they did
Alex's likes will thank you for letting me off the hook for this one
Because Alex was pushing back a little bit
But not much
It was
It was a very strange
When you get a caller like that
You know what they're saying
You don't need to be like yes there are Jewish Mafia is an Italian mafia is a
You don't need to do that
Probably be like
I got to go I got to go
I thought it was really interesting because he does keep him on the line for like
They have a long call
All the time
Not on the show
It's weird like it's
It's the resistance but it doesn't
Aggressive
Lovely
Yeah oh yeah
It's wishy-washy
I felt it would be a disservice
Do not like playing the hole
Yeah it was
But we do have a few clips
I've other things
I wanted them is Alex
This is just a
I think a precursor of the world of Cruelty
He would go on to become the mouthpiece
Because
MC little shades
Of
Adelaide
I just can't help it
Got another
We already know that does that fake laughing when he's really a
Which makes the comment even weirder
I just don't I don't I don't appreciate her enjoy
People
Expressing that Delight in others down
Even if you disagree with the other
Especially because
Kind of discussing
Yeah you know it's not just like
You know you
You don't get your way
Or something like that it's
It death
That does seem to be
Huge component of their non-zero-sum game or their zero-sum game
Kind of Outlook
If my
Progressive causes our champion
Put into place
I'm going to laugh
Because it makes my enemies fall
Honestly
It's just that I want to put in place
Makes even my enemies lives better
You're right you know I don't want universal healthcare for the winners
No no
For some reason there
World doesn't exist
Like that
This is what you
Christian like election night
Alex and Rodger is laughing
It's that it's that
Glass carries over
23 years after the
That night
Yep
And I mean if anybody needs
It's clear
What they were laughing at is people crying
Exactly what's happened
The children being in camps
People dying
The bills in Alabama and restriction
On abortion
Those are the things that
People mocking people for
Being afraid we're going
Want to come
So
Put that into sharp Focus
His cruelty is always been
And
Is very bizarre belief
About spiritual
I've also always been there
Cousin this next Cliff he expresses
A very strange
Belief
About why Society
So
Civilization rise
In order to make it easier to
To sacrifice human
Being
To Gaia the earth guy who's actually was
To explain what
So you need to kill a lot of people in order to make Gaia / Lucifer happy
No.
Is for Gaia gods
Yeah I don't know he doesn't complicated cosmologists really great the break
Happened right there Nora comes back from commercial and
Jack Swagger
Zeb Colter
WWE characters
To hate the Mexican champion
Alberto Del Rio
Love it
Alex has only legitimate complaint
But he doesn't
A lot about the Raza
This episode on February 20th
Misunderstanding of what lorazepam
That's
If he believes it to be a specifically only
Hispanic nationalist
Group that seeks to destroy all non-hispanic
Which is
But in complaining of
He says something
That again
Is very bizarre for the present
Our kind of horses Spanish
Your portion
Alex
2013 is warning
About
Which is kind of his entire show in 29
I just don't like
How complete the dismantling has to be
Daddy
It's vile
Only because he doesn't believe this stuff
Dismantling gets a facade Falling Away
How thorough it is
You know like getting a new episode
It's like there's at least one thing where you can drive Direct
Parallel
2 today and
He's doing the
Nationalism
The race-conscious
Business
And now at the same time in the
Benno couple years later
Going to be hanging out with a lot of people who are pretty
Super into
Race Consciousness and nationalism
It's fine because they're
Race-conscious
Right
Become super
Clear the all of this doesn't
Matter all this doesn't
It doesn't mean any
It only has two
To do with feeling like white people will be targeted by XYZ
Yep that's it
That's the only thing
Underlies
Position
Everything else is built on top of that
And a primary the primary building block
Is
White
Right
Fear arises
Almost certainly
Because
They assume
That
Well because that's what they wanted
Basically
That's because what they do want when they get power is
Able to do all that stuff
So they assumed
If they were to gain power
They would want to do the same
Maybe to them that you could not
Maybe not take away all rights like that might be
Too much to put on Alex
From everything I've
But certainly make second
You know what I mean like I don't know if
Looking at Alex
In 2013
I would be at all comfortable
Assuming
Really
If I would say that
If you got
Everything go his way
He would completely make all non-white
Not have Civil Right
Protections
But he would like he would pave the way for somebody who would
Probably weather
Justly or not probably
More interested is upholding a system wherein
People who were up like him
Were considered secondary or
Different or weird
As opposed to him and all the traits that are like Kim which are normal and anybody like him
Completely incapable
Kind of
Right she wants to uphold
Which is functionally very similar
Quite frankly
Ed's
If it isn't immediately
That that very thought process
That everything that everything that
Yes sure
You didn't want to outright Holocaust but all these little things start popping up
And then all the sudden you have to
Add this
Directions
You have to put down this thing over here and then finally somebody's like Welsh it
Let's just get rid of them
It's how it goes
It's a road
Yep
So in the last clip we have here
I just think
Crazy clips
And Alex
We know that
Relate everything
From movies to
To reality
Really tell the difference
Xtrema 2
Movies
You don't talk about as much but
Without a doubt is one of the most foundational movies
I have long believed that he believes himself to be Howard
He believed him to be a self to be this guy who's mad as hell and
It works against
It did not surprise me
February twenty
Ashok
Play the clip from Network
And start stalking back
To it as if he were Howard you this
Is bizarre
Call Gord
That's crazy
Razor
You know what one of the things that makes it even more crazy to me is that it's not very performative
No like he's just talkin back to it as if you would not like
His normal screaming certified
Do you think they're getting
No you're not getting through to me
Like he's responding as if it's
Actually a conversation which is outside of his
Performance style General
Here's what it felt like to me
Private
It felt like that's something
In private and we weren't
Supposed to be
Yeah I feel like I was
Standing closet door like looking out
Saying that to movie like that was
Yeah
Feel
I would assume so
Feels like you can do a better job than
Hoosiers
Yes
What you have here is you know an interesting couple days
A little bit
I think that you're seeing
Weird developed
How
Attention
Starved Alex's
In 2030
Like willing
Engaged
In
Not very optimized
Publicity stunt
Be going
Two Piers Bart like going on Piers Morgan show good
Well done you did exactly what you need
Showing up at the gun shop in Texas
You did a good job after
To the fact but how you
Confronted peers
Was very not Optima
Go back on his show repeatedly
Looking kind of sad and weak
Does not work very well for you
But you wanted to go back on his show because the first one was so good
Should I understand why
How to behave like that but that's not very good
The way you trying to turn
You know any
Media coverage of him into a scandal
Not good
The WWE stuff
He's not doing this right
There is a way he could have gotten
So much press out of this
And all it involves is a little bit of humility and a little bit of a sense of humor
If you had done that he could have played this so well
Glenn Beck's not showing up
He would show up for that
But Alex
Is desperate enough to show up
Just play ball
He could have done it
But instead he's an optimized version of this Feud with the WWE
He comes out looking
F****** silly
Because they want back
Responding to them
Talking about Glenn Beck
And casually mentioning him
In a joke
Did the comment
This is this is a sad
Who really wants
He got a taste of that attention
Glenn Beck
He wants to feel
A w
If you do that again
He wants another hit
Alex doesn't even know that
The Squatty Potty
He is
I don't know it's interesting to me
Me because this Ron is
We're supposed to be you know figuring out his
Rhetoric after
Cooking
Stretches of time
Like it's not something that he's
Primarily interested
And we saw it
Flare up
When
V-Star how
Popular
These conspiracy theories
We saw his attention
When he found that YouTube video that a 10 billion views
Amy had the professor on
To be interviewed
About his
Crazy.
I think that these trends that we see
With his
Desperate
Attention
Got things with Piers Morgan with
Criticism
Really responding aggressive
Play to them
The WWE stock
I think that trend
Is going to
Him
Down his dark
But that's just my sense
That's what I have right now
I think it's related
But on a secondary
Level development
Sandy Hook narrative
I think we're seeing
The essential pieces of the stage
If it needs to be
Be set for him to go
Down
Really dumb bad path
And we're already seeing dump bed
Marshall story is
Is unacceptable and on defense
Like did the short jump
From that
Two saying directors at Sandy Hook
To be less
Dignified in order to
To that point
But I think he will be he will need
Be motivated
Dim sum
So
Yats
It's pretty bizarre
Long string of things
It should have some
But apparently
I think misery is it
Is a consequence
So there's that it's cold comfort
At least there's some
Obedience training
The consequence has to come very close to the event otherwise you don't learn.
Yeah
The consequence for all this
Broken everything
Yeah I think about that a lot like one of the things that I reflect on
Like a lot of this
Work comes down
Listening to his shadow research
Also reflect
Pokemon
What what is going on
Thought that I can't ever get away from his how many times
We had a chance
A situation where at
Yeah like how many times
People had an opportunity
D2 like whether it's the people who have sued him and then let him go with a
Like giving an apology
Or the people who do things
That could have warned everyone
People who had inside information and maybe they signed not.
Disclosure green
But they could have been brave
Stood up been like no
This is dangerous
I know something
Betty's is helpful
There could be helpful to me
The past
Like we could have not gone down
Alex could have been
You know brought low earlier
Didn't happen
Yeah it is interesting
The idea that
Proximity
Punishment
The act the proximity
Because it is
No matter what happens
Now it'll never be able to
Alex won't experience that as the consequence of action
Exactly
Maybe that's
Just a human thing and it's not his fault
Process
But it is unfortunate
Because
His inability to process it will probably be
Text Meredith
How's the speed is victimhood and its feelings of I've been wronged by everybody even more
New episode the weekend
Goes wonderfully for you guys have some
Cookouts where you can have I don't know if you want abroad have abroad
Be the guy
Not letting you eat meat off the bone enjoy your lives out there
On Monday and
Knowledge
Yeah that's it
We are also on
Twitter
You can go to
Download episode.
Do that you could hear the new one
But you could share that up
To like
Your favorite social media platform your own
Pick all the platforms Alex's band from
Baby great
Alright
Probably not cuz I would say Jack Swagger
WWE
Former WWE
Now boxer
Mixed martial arts
No anything but also kind of a s******* he recently tweeted the where we go one we go all
Jack Swagger might be a bit of a dumb dumb
Is Alex Jones
Alex