Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple to stay around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones Jordan
How do you feel about internet
Do you root for the United
You know like in the Olympics
Thrilled when United
As well especially
Camaraderie
Crushing other countries
Actually feel what it does
Don't feel like War but I remember when I was younger
I guess
I don't know what years it would have been but it was around like tarryall and
I'd like the French World Cup team
I don't know why my brother was
The French
Took a little bit by osmosis
Then I studied French
I always had
Little little connection
Francophile
I could cheer for them even if they were again
Could see myself
Endorsing another
I'm not
Is USA or bust guys but I also appreciate
I know you're bringing this up because the woman's congratulations
Congratulation
Oh yeah
I remember I don't watch
Football at all
Okay
Like it was
Intense
Ever since that I watch
S*** out of women
I would say
This is a little bit
Sucked up to
Probably the sport I watch most
Does pro wrestling
None of her wrestling anymore or regularly but
The little amount of other sports I watch the eclipse by
I don't know if there's a ton of international competition
Pro wrestling
Iran vs. Saudi Arabia thing was
Well played poorly done the Guthrie
There's a lot about today
International competition
Not so much
Jordans
Sting episode to go over we are going to be talking about July
5th 2019
Very clearly
I've gotten a lot of feedback
From listeners
Expressing
A sentiment that
This is too much Alex Jones in a row
We need a Wacky Wednesday break I empathize I understand
Absolutely I understand that and I feel
I absolutely do
One of the consideration
So is that going on now
World right now
What are the other issues is
Pizza X.
Like if I check in on some
Something is
Wednesday thing
Come to like 2 hours
Somebody talked
2 hours lost
A bunch
It's very difficult to
That stuff in
Today is a modern-day Alex episode
But it'll be also a hybrid
Wacky Wednesday
I think that will be satisfying for some people
Jordan
Michelle
I really appreciate it and I completely forgot
To give any shadowfell the last night so we're behind
Thank you so much
Next Spencer thank you so much
Text
Zach
Exactly
Somebody donated on an elevated
Appreciate it very much
Drew
Heroin
Is freakishly large
If you're out there listening
Is button supposed to show weird
July 29th
Alex and predict
Did that antifa was going to commit chemical warfare against
All manner of
Conservative hammer out there with your kids they're going to Blind
Magical milkshake
We're recording this on Sunday and there was a whole weekend of nonsensical bullshits or something pops off tonight
Don't blame us for not knowing about it
At all
Surprising
So he's got a kind of pick a different
Kind of ignores that that was a
Legitimate prediction and
And so instead of focusing on how wrong
He was
Decide
I am going to
To go f****** hard
About how great
Which was
On the 4th
The theme that's going to develop throughout this Epic
2019 I'm your host Alex Jones
Trump speech live
It was
The confirmation
I'm just how far we're going is a culture
America
Demoralize us
Very Americana Pure Western Renaissance moment
I'm so honored
Free
Turtle Trader
Be able to do
Picking off next Wednesday
Call Sweetie
Proof
Okay so I guess there is still a little bit
It certainly D escalated
Have you heard this
It was an exorcism
Yeah it's kind of a vibe that Alex is going to be putting out as B
Trump was
Presiding over a suit
I'm sort of a
Pseudo pagan
Christian ritual in order to exercise the anti-American forces
Really f***** up
If you consider like
If you just take a step back if you forget about the fact
Alex
Had the career he's had
Presumably someone who's red thing up here saying Trump is doing magic
Strip away all the other stuff.
Alright man
In that regard
Really does agree with
Getzen trumpet
He's up there to imagine
I think the truck will probably not believe it is literally is Alex's birthday
I don't know man
Who knows
Sew-ins next Club Alex
Believes
Melania
That this was a magical ritual
Conducting
Super emotional
Oh boy
That's
What's the weather
Show cameras
Kosher up on Melania Trump's face
Anita's
Trump almost broke down crying
On
Fire
She did get lit on
And
Americana and Country
Christian America
Crocheting
Globalist
Like I watch some of the videos that Alex was wanting to or is that there is about to cry
Looks confused
What does the Rorschach
He almost crying
I can see some down in
It's all kind of similar visually
Angelic
Beauty and
In love
America
I think of a woman who wore a jacket
Said I don't
On the back of it
Right that's what I think
Nothing is more Godly but not giving a s*** about the death of the poor
Might think that is
America's Best
Sure that he might not be internally
I can find no evidence
I'm crying
There might have been some it appeared
Tears without
Might have been the wrong
Yeah
Yorkie before the clip start you said this is
I agree
Narrative
Is all religion
Just ritual
Sit into his audience
Not a power trip
Someone
I saw Trump
President
With his wife
First to
Perform
This is crazy on a couple
Reporting an exorcism
It's crazy is that it's now being reported at 6
So not only is it a magical ritual
Especially on the 5th it up pretty good way
You could deposit it to be reported
And now everybody globalist
Show me one
In person
I don't know if she's a global
I mean
Why do I protest
Alex
It's talking about
Being View
Horses that need exercise
This is probably the only point of the episode
That I think is like
This isn't what I want to cover
The rest is going to be really fun
But he's got to yell about like drag queen story time at Pride Parade a little bit
Because of a
Specific things
He's saying
About them
Push back on a little bit
Otherwise it would just be like
Scores of articles with them
Children are mounted on top
The man
What
Videos and photos of this
Children
Just making this up
Sponsored
Other than I don't really defense
Bright real
Formal structure to it at all your might actually be somebody
That might actually exist
They don't have a CFO I'll tell you that right now or not
So
Group kids at
True
I'm at was wondering where you was getting a
Videos and photos of this
In Europe they have sex with the children in public
Openly having sex with Rebellion
Really don't think
You don't I really don't think that's true
Side mirrors f***
Can kids outside
Completely made up Hangouts
Did you community
It's become incredibly
Common occurrence on this show to hear Alex a street like this but just completely not true
Refreshing
Pensive nonetheless because
Scale
Houses for people talking points
From the far right to your campaign.
Coming out of Europe
Which diesel
The director against the lgbtq community
This traces back to backlash
The pride parade held in Warsaw
And as we discussed in the episode where recovered Stefan molyneux gone to Poland
Warsaw in Poland is not the chillest place in the world right now for non-heterosexual white dude
Jaroslawkuzniar the head of the law and Justice party and the power behind the Polish president
The moment has labeled the lgbtq
Q Rights Movement a foreign import into threat
Wright's just before the pride parade of far-right journalist
From Poland called
People to
On lgbtq
Atq active
That's not good but he was quick to point out that he didn't mean it literally and then he compare Pride Parade organizers organizers
According to the independent quotes
Town Council
I'm staying at their municipality is LGB
Free in recent
There is a real
Negative friend
From a political perspective right now
Some articles that I've read and information I found
The population is
Towards greater except
And support for LGBT
Horse backlash from the far-right ruling party
Part of that backlash has been attacking Warsaw mayor Russell
For participating in the Warsaw
A saying quote
Not everyone has to go to equality parade
Respect minority rights
It's really important
For me that works I'll be open
Warsaw be tolerant
That is a sentiment that isn't direct opposition
Far-right agenda
And so to attack the rising
Tide of public acceptance of LGBT
AcuRite they've launched a public campaign
Portrayed quality
Is actually being an attack on families
An attempt
Actualize children
So weird
Across the world from Warsaw to Austin
Coming up with you today
Mirza narrative
Almost working out of the exact same Playbook
Please or were they not
Secretly the whole
I want to write a blog about it
March for Life and the family was held
830 Townsend Paula
The March has been held in previous years to protest abortion but this year was co-opted by the
Ddlg
EQ momentum
And it made it
Quote protect
Children for premature sexualisation
All of this is absolutely with Alex's lying about and embellishing what he says
The mayor of Europe was having sex
Two children in the sky
That is how it snowing in his audience is full of jump
Who will accept his version
The story when in reality
The mayor of Warsaw Justice
Expressed support for the pride parade
That is what he's embellishing and lying about
And this is why I never accept those arguments the people make that it's like
I was just an over-the-top.
Truth
You wakes you up out of your Slumber by being hyperbolic
Sex with children
In Europe what he is embellishing is a mayor expressing
Support for a pride parade
That is not leading you to the truth that is lead
You towards accepting
Far-right
Fascists mirrors
Coming out of Europe in service
Dehumanizing
Legitimizing and oppressing
Lgbtq individuals who are just trying to
Except
Not a trivial issue
No sew
For Alex's sodas
No no
Mexico
Alex gets back to talking about how true
Trump's 4th of July speech
Mcgonigle's office
The ritual
What
He knows
What rituals
Bucket was
Solutely
That they're attacking it
It just really shows
Crystal clear
Fourth of July special
The last few days
Is hyperbolic in order to wake people up
Complete bulshit
Hyperbolic about exaggerating
Which is
They want to f*** your kids then turns around and uses as an
Introduction
For his sales pitch about why
Existing to fight back against this imaginary.
Exaggerated
To make you scared
To figure out
If you would just pay attention
Into the structure of his show
Now
What are the things about Alex Knows Alot About You
Call history so
He knows a lot about real
I'm trying to find a better way to phrase
Going to have to let it slide
Hear the lovely imagination I would like to imagine is the last getting mad about
Unfortunately
He doesn't understand
What the thing
But he thinks
It's pretty clearly damaged
How much they love
The demoralisation of the people
Call him
It's really funny that Alex thinks at The Battle Hymn of the Republic
Is somehow going to trigger Libs
Or that it's a distorted version of Christianity or even American history
The song itself is just a new set of lyrics
61 etcetera
Preexisting tune from the song John Brown's Body
Which itself is based on a folk song these precise origins or a matter of.
Dispute Scholars have argued that it has its roots
African-American community
Pre-civil War South
Do you mean like most music
Brown body and Battle Hymn of the Republic are strongly abolitionist
Songs
John Brown's Body was dumped exclusively by Union soldier
And it was decidedly
Confederacy
Is evidenced by the lyrics
They will hang us our apple tree
Now three rousing cheers for the Union
Free over
We're not still singing the song it's like working
Battle Hymn of the Republic was written by Julia Ward
Someone who
Would absolutely have called dub if you was around in the
She was decidedly a dedicated abolition
Specifically to give a more cleaned-up version of John Brown's Body
Rally the Union Army
To defeat the Confederacy
After the Civil War how dedicated herself to
The battle for women
Suffrage putting her squarely on the right side of a
History on two important issues
Suppertime
Though her version was a little bit less overt
I didn't include part about
Confederate President Jefferson Davis
It was still pretty clearly antique
Confederate
One person particular stands out
Quote in the beauty of the lilies Christ was born across the sea
With a glory in his bosom the transfigures you and me
As he died to make men holy let us die to make men free
Well God is marching
The only people who should be triggered by the playing of The Battle Hymn of the Republic are people like Alex
Confederacy
This song is literally about killing his family members
Who took up arms
To defend slavery
I don't think the people who don't know about the song histories with
That triggered by a deer
I feel like most people who don't really think about it all that much just kind of accepted as a patriotic classic
Tickets brought out every time we have in America fetishizing holiday
Every
I think most people kind of it rolls off them like
Anybody who knows
These are
Specifically
Abolitionist
I don't know kill the slave owner
Let's fuk up Alex's great-grandfather
Alex legitimately believe that he is his answer
He has that idea that like your ancestors live on
Confederate ancestors
Is legitimately still trying to kill him
Through it anybody
Yeah
Absolutely that's the only
And because he
The wounds
It still be fresh absolutely
He's still bitter about that
So I don't know I think
He's just talking s*** about the Battle Hymn of the Republic
That is par for the course
The next clip
Alex gets really we
Eclipse are really enjoyed
This is
Adding a new layer
To his past
Make salmon
Into just a pickle
I've never really I don't think I've heard him bring this up before
I think he might have brought this up
I think this is just a wreck
Would be
Bugger
Crazy wild
You are
And they never even
Tony hillerman
And then later it happens
Oprah Winfrey
Providence
Bloodline
What wars
God put forward
Future
If you saying that cause and effect exist
I guess I agree with
But the part that's really strange
To me is that what you expressing
Is this from
The age of Ariana
Right
Which I don't believe at all
I don't believe that at all would not be so full of
Complete
Ninety-degree turns down bizarre Road
I didn't tell you what the passes looked like that I guess so
Which again
Makes no sense
It doesn't
No sense because of God is already
Preordained
It doesn't matter what
You don't have any
Control
But stupid
Alex talked more about how the trumps were
During the speech
And again I just have to stress
No evidence
I do not
Right
Alex
Trembling
Spirit
This is just turning like
Trumpet
This is almost like an attempt
Deify
For a long time
It's so over its
Vainly
Make it this attempt to do
Inexorably thai-american Providence
What it means to be patriotic
This
Singular executive
Right
To be against metallic
Attempts to Saint
And for
But who knows
The 2nd
His
Americana
If I know anything
So
On this episode one of his big
Narrative
Very convoluted and I don't really care about is
Is that he was
Looking at responses
2 Trump speech
He saw the
Media come out with a bunch
Huh. Trump stupid
But
Pieces were immediately
Down because the media realize they were going to come out with us
No one liked it so they doubled back I don't I don't know that this is
I have no way
Confirm or deny this
I think what Alex is talking about is other people posted
Like
Stream
Or rebroadcast
Like CNN
MSNBC
Copyright
That's what I'm guessing
He's talking about
Sure
He's not
Specific enough that there's any
Threads I can
Can pull
And I don't care
Completely made
Right but
Part and parcel of this narrative is it the reason that they ended up
Taking all these
Because the back
From the Patriots
And the good American
Strong
If you're wondering how Alex
Not very good
Attacks with headlines
Publix
Comment
Comment on the one that quickly
If you are gay
Public sentiment
Good
That's that's that's the Acropolis of our time
Suggest
That if you had better information
You wouldn't use you
You comments for Smitty's garage
I don't know
Not very serious people
Cherry pick YouTube comments in order to
Is a dam
Valic
Does process
And what he considers relevant in
Information
If you think so that YouTube comments or somehow worth of being apart of it
Discussion
I think
I don't know it's just embarrassing
If he wasn't playing
Games
He didn't have an audio
If we did that we would be pilloried
Not if you cited as one of your sources, everyone would
Beautiful
Specific everybody hates
Trump and here's why I believe that
S***
Suggest when he says that he watched
Dozens and dozens of YouTube videos
And look at the comments
It's more like he
Went to dozens of videos
Without watching
I don't even know what
It does not matter to me
YouTube
Yeah
But you know is that he was watching it may or may not have been taken
They were expressing
A real hatred
Now it wasn't just
They're also article
Besides the cover
Fox reporter
Us would have been better off
That's
Don't celebrate Fourth of July by Cindy American Revolution was a mistake
Every reporter
BuzzFeed
Looks like this
He's got a face that's more
Full screen
Sir
Good analysis
So far
Right photos
Of other writer on July 4th
How much America stock
Alex is going really hard after Fox reporter Dylan math
Complete
This is pretty weak stuff
Yeah yeah
The article that Alex is responding to someone that Dylan wrote
The article was updated this year
Apparently
Alex just
Enough justification to report on a four-year-old article that was written and published
As if it's somehow a recent thing
World Cups
We're all good together
Dillon's argument comes down to three points
Just why staying with the British Empire outcome
The first is that slavery would have been abolished
At this is not a debatable point
England abolished slavery before the American Revolution except
Before with India following along
The Emancipation Proclamation didn't formally abolished slavery in the United
I'm sure Alex would probably say who cares about
22 years of
Non slavery but I think that's a pretty dumb argument
Dylan's first point is absolutely correct
If we were still in the British Empire slavery would have been outlawed sooner and possibly even without a civil war being needed
The second argument
Cuz there's conflict
Violence between the colonists
And Native American
It would have been far less horrible
Buy the part of the
The British Empire
Dylan's not paint inversion
Of what wood
Possibly
Pointing out that the ethnic cleansing that took place in our early history
Was the direct result of an inch
Satiable hunger for Western
Which the British set limits on what their proclamation of 7
B3
It's hard to know exactly how
Things would have played out but if you look back at what are independent country
The native peoples
It does make you feel
A little bit
It's possible it's possible
Play some point you're arguing a counterfactual that's always very difficult imagine possible worlds
We're thinking
About there
In terms of
The Dominos
You cannot make
That's why they're still fighting people still would have been violent towards each other
Possibly the Trail of Tears
Possibly reservations wouldn't
Uno's
Texas
System of government
Is more stable than what we have,
Parliamentary systems he says are less likely to collapse into dictatorships
Since they lack of focus on a singular Authority
Which characterizes
Presidential
He further points out the Parliamentary
Systems generally experience less gridlock
And legislation
I can be generally
Much easier that's her
Nervous system as opposed to our conflict based
System
Often ends up
Situation where one side want something one side wants
The opposite of something
And no one can make
Any Headway
Complete gridlock
Agree or disagree with Dylan Matthews point it's not fair to say that
America from the text
This article
It's one thing to dispute his premises
It's entirely another to accuse him of being
Because you don't want
Engage with his ideas
Then do a little segment on your show where you call an ugly and apply to the danger to children
Childish
But it's no surprise
Absolute
Dillon's article was originally published on July 2nd twenty
And on July 7th 2015
Books published a response article with the headline quote
No the American Revolution was not a mistake
In this article Jeff Stein does exactly what Alex Jones
Incapable of doing
Taking Dillon's points
Considering them
And express
Counterpoint
But he feels makeup better
Surprisingly not once
Call Dylan ugly
Doesn't respond to this ugly do so little
Do the American Revolution was a good idea get a load of this guy
Fox publish both of these articles because
They both bring up interesting perspective on his
They both use primary source
Does the defender different views on how things would have been different if the United States
Hadn't declared
Vox published both
These articles not because they hate America but because their media Outlets that are interested
The publishing
Incontact
In contrast to that Infowars is a media Outlet interested in publishing content based on
Personal insults
Making s*** up and lying about headline
The difference
Could not be
It's really it's really interests
Especially within the context of these
Dum Dums
That's all I do like
Dangerous
Ideas you guys can
Existed
In the marketplace of ideas and debate our ideas
I want to talk about a four-year-old Vox article
They themselves published
A response
To from another author Wendell was a debate
Between the two like these articles are not just
Articles that exist for like a guy made this point in
Completely unrelated another guy made
Different
Just Times article is it Direct
Fonts to Dylan Matthews article
There is an interplay that's happening.
Within a meteor
Thought source
Thinkbox is allowing
These ideas to be
Be discussed
Interact with each other
For public consumption
That is a Marketplace of ideas American Revolution
It was good
And in fact I just agree with some of your points
Here's why I disagree with this point
That is
What Alex and his
Dickhole friend
Pretend they want to do
In reality
To do is save these people are bunch of globalist fux
They called him ugly and then applied at they want to hurt your kids
And that make money
Off of doing
That's what is it called
Free-speech advocates
Get on the right all they really want
Is to be wrong
Loudly
And never have
They don't want any
They don't want any kind of
Learning
Possibility they don't want any
They want to be able to stay
Say what they want to say
Hwoarang
How racist are you stupid
Without ever having
Exactly
Jordan
Open text
You since yesterday
Telling you that
I found
Grounding
Completely
Game Change
The game will be
This is also
Going into where we reach the point of the episode where things
Take a little bit of a fever
Wednesday
Okay
It's coming
Studios
This is a guy who's Italian
He pretends about the Vatican
Hanging out with Leo zagami
And so
Decorative boxes right over there on that day
Well just affected Trump
Or the left
Good time to celebrate so I don't normally have
More
It keeps being like
I should have a third
That I rarely see
Could have their glass
Rude
Asian rude
The book called A confessions of an Illuminati
Was
Maybe ghost written by Lego the blurb on Amazon
Because it's glorify Leo
Replaced
Penis with
Super important Illuminati inside
I've listen to Leo zagami show up on Alex's show in the past
I've heard him even when he made an appearance I'll Project Camelot cuz he did
I have listened to him
And a lot of stuff that I was able to
Define
You're my research today
East Knox
Stop that has ever come up
It is not stuff that Alex has
Everett
Soffit to be like
Hey now I should tell you this about Leos
I cannot wait to tell you this is one of my favorite stories that I will ever tell on this podcast
And no matter how much I do this
I cannot
Over self
Alright you got a lot
So here's Leo just to talk
What would you call this historical timeline
We wear in Eatery distressed organization
Friends
I strongly believe that that is part of his
Citi Trends
Confesses to a crime
We are
Jimmy Chino Airport
That's it
Illegally trafficked
If I understand correctly celebrating
Customs and Border Protection
Expensive
Dumbass I don't really care about that
B b of the Mind
Know why that the
Heavily controlled what I'm saying is I'm not calling
It's just hilarious
So you remember earlier when you were
Talking about how
At least
Well Alex makes
Interesting
Comment.
See it's funny because of all the stuff he said about Obama because she's married to a guy who
That was a birther
Alex doesn't really care about Aldi
Itsfunneh
What is
Trump to be telling her what to do
So
Alex
Talking about how
Leo's
It's weird
And kind of uncomfortable and Italy
End the end
We talked about Leo zagami a little bit in the past
You popped up in our 2015 investigation as a complete weirdo
Except smartsound
Because he thinks anyone with an axe
Anyone who missed those episode
Leo zagami is whole thing is that he used to be in the Illuminati but now he's become a whistle-blower warning the world about there in the
Nefarious satanic play
He also apparently is a Vatican Insider which I guess just comes with the territory
If you're in with the Illuminati you probably get invited to some Vatican mixers a little cocktail hour at the Vatican
Yeah I assume you go to every place of power you know like
Basin
For sure for sure
She's running one of the simplest scams imagine
You can just make up whatever she wants and trick idiots has inside information about
On the flipside the Catholic Church
Insanely corrupt organization
And people who protect
So there
Pretty easy also to make sure talk about
Incredible
If you just put
A bunch of priests are going to be out of his abuser
Even if you're making
Get up your prediction may come through
Safe game you play
Information about
Lupo's part no one really cares about him outside of
Coverage
Comes from that
Perspective
Super
Critical and
Pretty dicey
However
There is an amazing story
Tippy Toe
And in order to
Conspiracy sites
You today is as close as I can get
To the actual true story
Sagami got to where he is today
And how we clearly demonstrate
How little research Alexandra
Do on somebody
Before they allow them to be presented as a credible guest
On their show
There isn't too much concrete
Information
Should know about Leo zagami pre-2000
Really important
If you're going to make bulshit up about the Illuminati website
Record producer under the name Leo young until 2000
At which point you decided to start exposing the Illuminati
His father was a professor of psychology named Elio zagami and his mother was Jessica Lange Young
Julio Legends is quote a member of the Queen Mother of England's family
Her middle name is literally like
That's who's the
That's apparently his father's
His maternal
He doesn't specify how he's related to the Queen Mother and predicting around
Inasmuch as I can
Relationship
The only reference is I can find to Jessica lion young be related to the Royal Family come from various websites that have re-posted
Leo self-written bio
Given the other things I know about him I strongly
The fact he's making up his
Leo's life story
Up to going public Illuminati go something like
He was born into a Scottish Sicilian Illuminati
Cretic bloodline
And that sucks she's been apart of the Illuminati since
As a lifelong member he was groomed as a prince of the Illuminati recently ranked 33rd degree of masonic
Notorious Italian
D2 LOD
Okay okay
Before you decided to expose the speaker
Replace the previous King of the Illuminati that Leo was disgusted by the Satanism you was around
And chose the path of light
Full line
Okay this is an essential piece of his hero's journey
He stood to inherit every
Power in the world all the riches
About the world
He rejected at all
To fact-check his story I should point out that the large you claim to be a part of
But it also closed when Leo was 6 years old
Likely
The only direct evidence he's ever provided of his membership in any Masonic Lodge
Is a picture of his membership badge
From Kirby Lodge
Twenty88
It's important to understand about the Masons though is that they keep exhaustive Wrecker
Their entire organization basically revolves around ritual
A record-keeping is a part of the
Including the record-keeping of course our reports
Where they kick people out
Leo zagami was kicked out of Kirby Lodge
For Behavioral problem
Including but not limited to excessive use of profanity
After that point you started
Just joining a bunch of fake Lodge
I just don't even involved with the Masons
To create the illusion that they are
If you ever reach any high level of initiation anywhere
It's in
Fake Masonic lodges
Which seems on brand
Are they are they are they
More like
Apostate Masonic lodges or they like a bunch of weekend dudes
I think it varies
Is either of those groups and I think there's even a third
Cross-section that is like
I want to be weirder than that
Whatever I
Feel like
Is Masonic isn't actually summer create my own Lodge
Version of
Them
So in 2008 Leo found himself living in Norway
In March 2000
Search from a Norwegian politician
What a dire warning
The Norwegian government is building more and more underground bases
Isn't bunkers
Planet X
The people that are going to be left on the surface will die along with the others
Get no help whatsoever
The planets are going
And the rest will die
All the governments in the world are aware of this is going to happen
I assure you a hundred percent that things will happen
There are four years to prepare for the end game
Get weapons
And make survival
A place where you can be
Be safe with food for a tie
Okay so he was on
Well this is from an alleged Norwegian politician
The point out that at the time Leo zagami
Lived in Norway
The politician offered to answer any question
Jim Carrey might correspond
It is messages
He makes a number of predictions that do not come
Come true
She said that Steve Jansen would be elected prime minister of Norway
Which didn't
Oh okay
Interesting Lee
In February 2000
So he was in place to be a valuable source
To check in with about this letter from Norwegian
Politician
And that's exactly what happened
What's a bit more into this
As it goes a lot there's something very suspicious going on
Call Leo to interview in Valparaiso
Politician whistleblower
Leo's
Profile in
Conspiracy world was raised dramatically in the span of a couple months
Thanks to the project
Project Camelot
If you'll recall when we covered Jessica Shaw
She specifically said that after she went on Project Camelot
Came famous overnight
Well it may seem like an irrelevant joke now project
Pretty large platform
Decade ago
Will undoubtedly got a whole lot of tracks
Future.
On the show mixed up in the story of this alleged Norwegian politician
A cynical mind might suggest
Kind of already have
About pretty much everything
It's likely that the letter was a bit of a stunt
It may be the only person who stood to gain anything
From that kind of stock was
I have no idea though I can't prove it either way
It could be an amazing coincidence that right after he got interviewed in Oslo for Project Camelot
Is whistleblowing message from a Norwegian politic
Because it was sent
From El zagami at gmail.com
Who else could send that
After his appearance on Project Camelot Leo's wife
I took their son
It's very hard
Determine what actually happened
I'm here but I can tell you that I don't believe the version of the story
Repeated ad nauseam
Conspiracy Cirque
Hold on I'll just read to you from
Papers
Which is written by someone who claims to be a
Personal friend of Leo's
Keep that in mind for later
Controversy papers
Hold on to that.
The Illuminati
Has accused him of spousal
I don't I don't know if the accusation of domestic violence is even I don't know if it's true
Wherever actually
But I do know that I don't believe that his wife left because he was secretly
The Illuminati
David Icke pulled this exact
When he divorced his second wife
Pamela lyrics
Who he
He decided they needed to split up after 11
Years of marriage because he
Became suspicious that she was a shapeshifter
When intimacy deteriorates
These people
Always end up being secretly involved with their
Imagined enemies
You can even see this with Alex Jones blurs the lines between the actions of the globalist
And his ex-wife globalist want to take my kids away
They used to be we just called witches and
Is a simpler time for these
What's interesting
Is it Leo's
First wife
Was Muslim
In fact
He repeatedly insist
The Cheez-It Direct
Descendant of Muhammad
Do you know what else
At that time
Leo was Muslim as well
In a message board post
What
Leah wrote that his wife quotes that I should stop immediately my Illuminati confessions on the net and convert
Restricted more fundamentalist view of Islam
Otherwise she will leave me
That was obviously a brainwashing in position
For me and I couldn't accept such a
Proposal
Okay
Alright
Riveted first off
Different play
We will go onto later claimed that he converted to Islam infiltrate the religion
He became a Muslim quote during an Illuminati ritual he made in Egypt under the Great Pyramid of Giza
Illuminati religion
Add a Muslim
Khalid saifullah Khan
If there's one thing that you learned about Leo zagami when you look into it
It said he is a dude who has used a lot of different names in his career
Generally
Don't like to have a good time
That's why they don't do it
So after his wife left
He miraculously realized that the version of Islam
And represented assist
Afraid of Leo's
Right but wasn't he inducted
Staying religion
Through the Illuminati
Don't worry about trying to make this next to be out loud
Similar problems with us
So because
His wife was involved
Leo was punished
By having his marriage broken up
His child taken from her
Awful
What I know about Leo
What we can learn about him and what we will learn about him
Today
I think he's a maniacal
Who if not directly you might want a divorce from if you find yourself
Accidentally married
From his account of what happened
In any case to weeks of not seeing my son Isaac
I tried to put pressure on the religious movement of my wife in order to show me my son again
But instead at 9:30 p.m. on the 4th of March
Two policemen
Police woman came to my house and arrest me so I spent
12 hours in a cold prison
Translate Leo was harassing his wife's and she called the police and they responded appropriately
What year was in prison for that difficult 12 hours he had a breakthrough
When he met with a priest
He found the strength to tell the priest about his quote forced conversion into Islam to please my wife's family and the way
Play they sold me after the authorities
As the only a true Judas could do
Yes my wife told me to my worst enemy the Norwegian free maze
So the conversion to Islam was both
Who is by his wife religion
I got it okay whatever
Greatest enemy is the Norwegian the Freemasons the total
Serious
That's fun
Yep
Conveniently
When he was arrested for that 12 hours
The Norwegian police confiscated
Which is all the proof about all the stories he tells about that
In the CIA
This is another essential
A piece of this hero's journey that
This tragedy
That makes them unable to unequivocally
Calabasas
If his wife hadn't been brainwashed into filing false charges against them he never would have had his computers
He would still have all the proof
Global
But now he just has to be totally right about everything and everyone looks at him like he's a Madman
Spoiler alert
He is a Madman
You have no idea without doing
Leo's Message Board post continues
Quote from the 5th of March 2008 I'm officially a Christian again as my sufferance has made me realize
He is our only Savior and Muhammad is a false prophet is descendants are involved in Satanism in the New World Order
Soleo left Islam and Christianity
But guess what Jordan settings
Rejoin
According to his also rejoined the Illuminati
And that's just somebody higher up in the Illuminati
No teak access to the sky
I will say that it does work
Chris wave when your make
True
That's true that is helpful
Soleo claimed 2008
Personally controls major parts of the Illuminati
For good
As you've already pointed out this
He claimed he was protected by a 12000 manstrong paramilitary group called the green lion security
Interesting Lee lion being his maternal last name
There is no evidence
Is that this group exists
Apparently rejoining the Illuminati
Protect Leo from legal
Whole Foods
According to his own book
Confessions of an Illuminati volume
He was arrested in July 2008 when he arrives at a courthouse work
Child custody
Apparently recently appeared on an internet can
Conspiracy show and quotes
In a typical Italian actor bravado threatened
To kill the Norwegian prime minister Jens stoltenberg
Bloomfield threatened to bring down the buildings of government and Parliament in doorway
But he says quote
I'm serious about the death right
It is the Italian way of expressing
Strong emotion through strong words
Alright alright okay alright
I did I thought I was Italian up a time
Excuse for George prime minister
Leah was lucky to walk away without facing
Charges or jail time
Time for that probably do much
To help his already in Norman
Complex
And tendencies towards grandiosity
He continued unabated pretending he was in charge of a large portion
Of the Illuminati
Not want to let this craziness cool down to room temperature
Leo zagami made another interesting religious conversion in 2009
As he should
No
New religion for 2012 Matrix ism
Yes Matrix ism is the official religion of mayordomo Illumina Touareg universalis
Nothing else will be tolerated about true illuminated beings
Cuz of light working for the science of God and the kingdom of God in 29
I've only got one thing to say
There's a pretty consistent thread through his work.
The kingdom of God is going to
We started at 2019
Which makes it particularly
As they celebrate 4th of July
Matrix isn't was a religion created by Anonymous individuals online
Leo would later go on to imply that he was involved in the creation of the religion
Which might be true
Since the founders were Anonymous I can't really confirm or deny it
What I can confirm is that creating a religion based on a movie
Squarely in category of things
I would believe Leo zagami could have done it makes me
Very sad people who got really depressed after Avatar because they could never lie
Live in Pandora
You know
You could just feel things
When are we going to get judges
Is to understand who's
Who is it
To the point where we can
Tube8
James O'Keefe
Massively James
Somebody who does
Steal something
Goddamn 7-Eleven
Not dangerous
Leo zagami
Ruining thousands upon thousands of Lies
City of influence
Yeah
In there man
And how he has eluded first of all
Just outright
Exposure
His life
In 2009 when he was announce that Matrix ism is the official religion of his world
Leo was fully back on his b*******
You got a big fraction of the Illuminati use now in Georgia
Conspiracy world
Previously promoted him profile
What kind of forced to go along with his new
Or risk having to admit the bathing pool by a narcissistic weirdo
Just because he had Natalia next
He has them trapped because they
Illuminati Insider
And his base
Cons of their beliefs on
So we'll continue to pedal is Illuminati.
Giving speeches here and there
But honestly
His Trail runs a little bit cold for a while
Between 2009 and 2011 I'm not really sure what he was up to
But
In December 2011 he was arrested
I have literally no idea what he was arrested for
But I have to assume it has something to do with being a dick in public
When he was in a processing room
He gave a cameraman a little interview
The illustrates the mindset that he was in at the time
And we are now going to listen
In this first clip
Leo
Talk about how he was arrested
I meant talk about what's going to happen on December
21st
Because Leo zagami
Was very until 2012
Do my English literature understand bad that I was arrested last night
Olivia
Call Amber
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
Emperor of the war
On December 21st 2012 Leo zagami will become the emperor of the new Holy Roman Empire which is
We know that in 2019 he is opening a bottle of champagne with Alex
We do know that
What's the difference
Certainly
There's a little bit
I think it's some people could say hey this could be a guy doing a silly Italian accent
Like on drugs
Ready
He's frustrated
Smoking a cigarette
I will give him
This possibility
Should he
ESO
Want to take this out
Entirely possible
He is having a full-on
Manic episode
Completely delusional
About that problem is illusions
Fit in with his life's work
It just seems like a more overt
Location of the things that I want of those things
Literally Jesus
Call the obelisk in St Peters
Terraria
Empire
Great opportunity of having a lawyer
Look when you're the Messiah what are you got to do
Bring up this over there
Do you want a baby
Make a clarification for our audience so bad like I didn't mean to write or
Right now that would be difficult
Alex
Tube
Which was surprising
It would be surprising
It would be
Fbb Netanyahu is like
I look shocked as you check this guy out though
I don't want anymore
What are we going to do what are you doing
The next clubfoot Smackdown for because if you thought that the Revelation that he is
Is shocking
This next clip
Is
So much more shot
Doby's Mill
Between Tower
That is what I would
I would never have guessed that I am Jesus would be followed up with
I'm working with Osama bin Laden
That's tougher Alex George Bush off the hook
Thanks for 911
Yeah that's strange I want to point out is that I've listened to a ton of Leo zagami interview
And the way you speaking
Is
Not
Out of order out of the norm
Things that I know I've noticed with you when do as the
More manic time
Your manner of speaking is a little bit
Like there's more pressure behind the
The speech there's more
You speak quicker
People whenever they're in those episodes
Windows
This is very
Normal
This is normal speech patterns
Northern Italy
I don't know I don't think this is necessarily indicative of
Some sort of a break with reality as much as it is like
I got arrested
Idol 4 I shouldn't be arrested I am
It's it's
Exasperation more than
Like a break
That's it that this sounds almost like
Robert Evans
He's from the kid stays in the
Was just a little bit less is just a little bit more drunk when he was given those interviews he be like
Yeah that does sound like you
Robert Evans
You probably think you were G
While you're producing Rosemary's Baby
He did 9/11
He's Jesus
He's working with Osama bin Laden
And the Jews accepted that he was
And they're not the only one
Democracy
Begone
And that Christianity will be outlawed
Roman Empire
So here's the 2011 will be the only religion that allowed
Plies very strongly the Christian
Who's the guy who's lived
In favor of a novelty religion he is a legend
Created
And not just that the best possible but really I'm Leo
Sew-in Leo's
Conception we allowed you to have democracy
We are Aristocrats we're in charge
Staunchly against
So he's conception Leo's
Is that
In 2012 he will Ascend to the role of emperor of the new Holy Roman Empire
As Jesus
I've somehow I guess 911 was part of that setting the stage for it
You'll see in 2012 were past it now and I don't
Julio we didn't
Your logic your strategy
Man when we're wrong we can admit it
What extic
So Abby
That's going to happen in
Between 2012 and 2019 thoroughly
The. Of tribulation
It'll result in 2019 Harley clear about what that resolution
Implies
But there's one thing that is
That is true
And he does
Say
And that is you don't follow him
You will die
Covid-19
What time do
Haha
Right right
Part of the Catholic Church
Yeah like it this is the padlock
Down there that has a really complicated code that only the real Jesus could unlock
So now we've got the Jews and the Vatican
Well
They're fine that
The savior is working with Osama Bin Laden I guess
Right right
This is a test
Pill to swallow
This is what we call a big Swig Leo insist that
If you betray him
Life human
I never made any money
Don't betray me
Threatening
I remember a lot of the times
In the Bible when G
Flexon hell
So it's a little bit inside
The nature of God
It turns out that God is an alien
Kingdom of God thank you very much for the people of the world
There's one last year where you just sums it up that he is working with the New World Order
Remember 7
What's the news
So he's got
Lions
All of that
Happened
Before Alex ever started having Leo on as it supposed to guest in the Illuminati
And as an Insider and Vatican
All of the things that I told you about
Including
An interview that is publicly available
You think that I would want to ask him but how
This responsibility as recognized
A new world order
Once the New World Order which he himself was took power in December 2012
Weirdly none of that ever comes up on info
Despite Leo making
Bunch of appearances as well as being
A noted Gaston David night and Owen Shroyer shows as well
I think
Clearly shows that Leo zagami is Lassen expert in anything
It's very useful
For someone like Alex
A person like Leo's used to love the force of escalation
Any mainstream news Outlook until you about the corruption
The Vatican and how there's a systemic problem within the Catholic Church
Where abuses have been covered up and abusers protect
And that should make you feel bad
Call
But Leo zagami by pretending to be an Insider
Could tell Alex
The preacher actually abusing children because it serves
The purposes of demon
Which of the country to the Earth using black
Magic
And you can see how these two situations in Plaistow
Lately different solution
That's the sort of role that Leo zagami can play
Towards radicalization escalation of rhetoric
Rat is very Danger
Yeah it's
Essentially acting as a
Vatican
Because if you can
Since enough people that the real issue is
Cops
Since they look at this
Perhaps unintentionally
I made it hard to nail down exactly
You know what is
Conscious
What is
Right kind of a byproduct of
Stupidity is probably making it more difficult
The treat the actual problems Alex start talking about
Child
Serious issues
Jordan
You might remember how I told you that Leo zagami you
Used to go by the name Leo Young
And until 2006 or so
The funny story about that
He's a good DJ music live.org still has a profile up for Leo Young
T.i. I don't know
According to his music biography
DJing on it
Where you was a fixture at a bar called Legends
Which according to his bio is a quote
Celeb hot
By 19
He claims he reached the national finals
Prestigious
DMC
Jacob
This very well may be true
I can't find a list
That Year's finalists for the Italian
Can say with certainty that he didn't win
Experience that contest whoever encouraged him to
To get more involved with the Raves
Respect the neck
Decade
He claims he is quote recognized as the man responsible for organizing Italy's
Firstrade
In Rome in 1989
Well I'm not positive that history Bears out that Leo zagami organized the first Raven
In Italy he's not making up that he was
Involved
I found a mention of him in an essay posted on the Red Bull Music
Academy's website title quotes
The rise and fall of Roman techno night
1888 290
Well there isn't much about him in the article this is what is
Quote for all the excitement amongst these young DJ
And those who history is forgotten such as the notorious
Willie wild Leo Young
Around
Techno in the soon to emerge hardcore
The vast majority of Roman club Owners and party promoters were less enthusiastic
This is an article about the rapes
Which centered more less around drugs
At Leo zagami is described as quote and notorious
The Mind reels
Stupid up to
In order to get that reputation
Giorgio it's 10
F******
On Family House. Net
About that notoriously wild reputation
Quotes
Leo's generally considered to be as mad as an upside down clown
Renowned for a reckless penchant for Ludacris coiffeur
Questionable new Mystikal
Threatening verbal Behavior delivered illusion
To a bloodline
Of eccentric Castle dwelling a
Aristocrat
It seems like that was always kind of part of his personality
Are you just ramble about nonce
Make no mistake about it
Leo zagami then known as Leo young was an active member of the House music
The late 80s early 90s
He held a three-day Rave called
L'impero.
In 1989 Senpai 1991 he was running a weekly club night called
In Rome
He did a 12-hour DJ set by the Berlin venue called tracer
I used to be a fixture there
Between 95 and 9
He claims he was the first
DJ ever to play at the Bolshoi theater
In Moscow which I'm not sure
He claims
Prodigy their first gig outside the UK
Probably isn't true but might be
That's crazy
It's absolutely crazy
Leo zagami with a f****** raped
Is bio a lot of the claims that he makes about his
Now
41 consider this line talking about how much he admires his grandma
Quotes
Not only did she get Leo his first international DJ Reza
But she also financed
Learn more about recording by becoming
The famous London production duo Double Trouble
If you was Illuminati royalty and all that
It doesn't
Like you'd make a specific
Point of his grandmother pay for him
Study with some London
That seems kind of ink
That's the first thing that every Illuminati child is
Say it's our grandmother
The next line is even weirder
Talking about how when things were going well for him in London quote
Unfortunately he had to go back to Italy where at the time you had to do an obligatory year of bollocks in the military
Before getting your passport back
If he was a member of the ruling Elite bloodline
Prince Illuminati
You'd think they'd be able to get him out of something that trivial interfered so drastically with his life
See you as a bone spur for
For fucksake
Curious
Distance from this long-winded
And very clearly self-written bio
Degree Mason
Secret societies at all
Turn of the Illuminati
None of that is under
The only time the battle
I can even comes up is when he says the quote
We're happy with him hosting a rave in an old church
If I'm being honest with you I don't know what to make
My mind goes back and forth between thinking that his luck had run out with the clubs
And it wasn't paying the bills anymore so we decided
Then I also
It's possible the baby he did way too many drugs
He started to believe his own bulshit
With the information available there's no way
All I can say is that Leo zagami is Loki one of the most interesting people who's ever been on an episode of Infowars
Interesting
And Leo zagami life
You've totally wanted to hang out with him and listen to everything he had to say absolutely
Let us all enjoy someone's Leo zagami music
Leo Young's music this song is this a little sample is from a I cannot stop
It's called DJ pimp and the Scarlet woman
Add layers after every break
It goes on like that for
I don't know but it's okay is a while back
Look
Honestly
Beethoven's music
Pickles are Kerry Cassidy
He has some skill
First tracks
Just a few months back
New interplanetary Belvedere
Italian record label artists spotlight
Elio Young
I've listened to the whole thing and it
Pretty service
I'm not sure any of it reaches the level of being a hit
But none of it is stuff that if you heard in the club
Particularly like in the early 90s
You be yelling for them tutor
Turn off
Leo zagami is still an active DJ
Are you talking about now
Like video of
Four months ago promoting the gig in Russia
Greeley
Really
Like what I was looking into
His history
All the stuff about like
Wait a second
Claim that you
Secretly
Infiltrated Islam
I like this is a fascinating story
Am I cute
Hours into this rabbit hole
He claims he's a DJ there any music available
Oh he's not
Make that up
It was just the craziest roller coaster ride
Had to go down
Nana's
He is a
Interesting figure whenever he's talking about his real life
What I'm talking about
I'm not positive but I've ever talked about this tail light
Alex
Dalio on
Infowars in present day
Communist
Scam
That's kind of
The place he serves
I mean that we are in a situation with
Trash communist can
This is
IDK used to say a song Back in the Days by
Text Beverly Hills Cop
Also I am
Anymore but
The show
And also
Alex
It's clearly defensive
About criticism
Robert Barnes is on the show
All the f****** time are there
It is yet another inch
Responding to criticism
Cuz he's a little
Council
His body
Just doesn't know who his friends are
I've gotten that you got in with the wrong
Krowd
Now we got bars
Barnes
He wants to become an American
Who is Miss America
What about
Bolsonaro like you keep talking about
The globalist globalist Allies around the world what the f*** are you talking
Where the f*** does
Is this fit into your Holy Roman Empire
What you want to become an American cuz Trump is president when you clearly have designs of world domination
If you realize the Trump doesn't
Stay present
Forever
Like there's going to be a different press
I think they think
Yeah I think they do
Also
I don't think that naturalization
Would be like well you know we
Get why you did it it was 11 years but we got it
I think you'd have more difficult
Text clip
I was just gets back to his trumpet
Exorcism
And
Loves it
We have become exceptionally in some respects
I guess what great power comes
Responsibility
Over the soul of America
Watch
Where to
You catch that
Yeah
Bordelon from
Responsibility
I think Alex realized in the middle of the quote that it was Spider-Man
Power Acworth
I wonder how he felt about far for
From home I imagine he saw that recently
I bet he was.
Did you know that so he was a British politician he was super into the Confederacy during the American Civil War
But don't worry
Slavery.
Union quotes
The slave-owner as an enemy
Slave as an instrument for his destruction
Also
He literally said quote political rights proceed directly for religious duties
And I hold this to be the basis for liberalism
Leo Leo zagami
Probably
What I'm getting at is Lord Acton's.
Because
Look stupid in front of
Which on its own is in
Incredibly
Yeah that is
Jesus and your 911
Giving a Spider-Man quotes
Smartest man
Yeah
So do you ask
The Christian exorcism ritual thing
No.
Absolutely I mean
Thinking the same thing
Fultz form
Be powerful
Absolutely
This is Philly
This is
Sweetly f****** silly
Quite frankly
They're talking about Trump conducting a
Yes
Liking this is what they're about now
This is a guy who claims that he has all the white version
Magic Ritual
It's not like you
No
Shout out to Robert Evans
Love's egregore
Vented by the French poet Victor
Hugo and his book The Legend
It's a faulty transliteration of the Greek word egregore
Which Loosely translates to water
It's close to a Greek word though.
Mistaken it was a fake word created by Vic
Central Recreation
Weirdos
Including collectibles
BMV
Society
It's been adopted into all their mythology
It's the same thing with Lovecraft created the fictional book the Necronomicon
Well then a bunch of ton of real world
The number of definitions out there for what counts as an egregore
But the general rule is
The thought-form this brought by the thoughts of a group
People
So for instance if you want to take a note of benign and very basic level
Klaus is an egregore
For the most part the new age in a cult world's take on it is basically just dress up versions of Base
Self-help ideas
Basically just artistic
Expressions used to warn people not to let negative thoughts
Consume them
Leslie manifestos negative thoughts
Like the god of guilt at
Sure
You have like
Popo's that are created individually and then egregores are created as a
Different kinds of clocks
Edward Elementals
So don't do it
What you might call the mainline version of new Ag and occult nonsense
But that's not how everyone
1st and egregore
I found an interesting post about egregores friendly explicitly
Red Ice Radio
Where the author discusses how a listener named George
I told him about a conversation I had with a quote
Heiress of a ridged
Jewish
King Family who was a Rothschild family
Like how close today
Leah was one
To my classmate
Accept the Geneva University
She was an attractive blue-eyed blond lady
And she was wearing the Star of David I asked if she was a believer
She answered yes or no and then added she believed
A god of the Jews who was
The Jews rather than survival
I immediately asked whether she was speaking of an egregore
The response was yes
And she broke that conversation
Never again did we mention
The subject
The article goes on to suggest
Jews of the past
Create
Which explains their world domination
The article says quote is this egregore is Lucifer
And Elite Jews have made him
The master meme of the New World Order
The elite Jews are the Communist capitalist internet
My friend you change a couple of words and that's that
You got yourself and Alex Jones quote
Got a genie
To do their bit
Jin's come out of a different cultures
You know I was doing the Americanized
Like whatever you have to
You can't
He can't deviate off the path
Passed because
To say I strongly disagree with everything in that article but I do admit that it is swinging
Sing for the fence
Listen to this amazing rationalization for being a bigot
It doesn't take a genius to recognize this egregore is the cause of anti-semitism
L using them to manipulate Jews who were taught that they are reviled for no reason
You see Jordan
Don't hate Jews for no reason
It's just
Stink truly consent
The egregore which is what they're really again
Progressive rationalization
Wow
It does not take a genius
In fact
It explicitly excludes
Believing
So you know what's weird about this blog post
Other than the content
I found it identical post out now
Auntie
A closer look revealed that this article wasn't actually written by someone who works for red eyes
It was a reposting of an article that was originally posted on the website of a guy named
Henry Mack
With a byline on it
Literature
So it's definitely good Prudential for him to win publishing
Glimpsing around mackhouse a pretty good sense of what he's all about
His most recent post was quote Jews immigration to divide and conquer
A quick look through his archives shows the following headlines from
Identify with whites
Event proved Protocols of Zion
Prime
You might be a redneck
Shut out of Twitter for a week I wonder why
Rimac outruns eclipse
Asymmetric website where he wrote an article in 2007
Otoscopy created to destroy non-jews
Which was then widely circulated on very high-profile aunt
Systematic websites and media Outlets like red eyes
David Dukes
Where do I bring all this
It can't just be good because I love saying egregore even though I do
Yeah
In 2008 when Leo zagami wife left
We are reached out to carry to prove it he knew about that allege Norwegian politician who would contacted warning about
Our planet
He was clearly looking
A rebooking on the show
This Norwegian politician
Consent to friends
Where do the politician
One of those two people
Was Henry Makow
I'll reach you now from his letter from March
13th
Which I remind you is after Maca wrote his article
Accusing the Jewish religion of being based on a communist Lucifer
Leo begins with letter quote
Dear Henry thank you for your kids
Continuous support
Forgive me if I could not reply earlier
The weather is mostly about I was wife was secretly working for the Illuminati and that's why she left him
And then awkwardly shoehorned into it or a couple references
Is this Norwegian politician
The content of the message
Important
Clear friendly tone of it
He refers to Henry is my friend
Dear Henry multiple times
Eddie and the letter fraternally yours
Leo zagami is listed as a source or reference in no less than 15 article
On Henry's website
Dating back to 2000
I have a long-standing relationship
And let me put it simply
Egregore is not a commonly used word
And Henry seems to use it 81
Here are the headlines
Is it come up when you search Henry Mack has website for the word egregore
Purim celebrate the slaughter of their opponents
Jews the unloved
People
And then here's another one
Leo zagami
December 12th 2012 start seven years of tribulation
Points of a Skype conversation that Henry had with Leo
It includes this pasta
Quote Leo mentioned
Cabalist
Then it says in parentheses
Macau
The guy that Victor is that
With a hyperlink
About how they created
All this
Is enough to be
Really f******
Sad little license
I should tell you the Project Camelot was not the first high-profile interview that Leo zagami did in his antiloop
Luminati career
In December 2006
He appeared as a guest
Best on Red Ice Radio
The white supremacist
Defies antisem
This Jordan
Is what you called way too many
Red flags
Oh and about Leo's wife leaving him that I mentioned earlier and told you to remember the one that was written by
A personal friend of his
That one was called Kent reversing papers
The blog was written by a guy named
Kent Daniel bentkowski
Cat passed away in August 2000
Edit block is way too difficult to navigate
So I don't really know too much about what he's all about
But if you search for his name
The first thing that comes up in a Google search
Is it eulogy Poe
Before him
On the website of you guessed it
Red Ice Radio
Gaston their show at least
10 *
Which tells me
All you need to know about what he stops for anybody
Comes up
You're a really unfair Shake
Demonizing
Here's a little clip
They want you
Straight white guy
Suffering and death
Dead
They want your daughters
Brainwash to disown you and your son's groveling at
You know
You know who they is
She doesn't explain.
To be like at you know who we're talking about
Yeah you do
So I think Leo even on top of all the interesting aspect
Step is life
Clearly involved with a lot of people who have
Deeply
Anti-Semitic
Worldview perpetuates a dear friend of Henry Makow Israel
From way back
I don't I don't think there's any conclusion UK
Can draw other than
Some of that stuff
Is
Probably
In his is Raichu
On
Alex's show
Clearly
Exist in the
Context of
Gore accusation
Of the Jewish god
Being creation out of the Mind
Of
Sweet dreams of the
The past in order to
Navigate the world
You know it makes
So much so
Ini dad be fine with it if they weren't
F******
Directly
Contribute
And
Of course these people get
Conned non-stop you have to be really really stupid
To believe any of this
Nigerian scams
The promise
Akhand and then making more people
F******
Right
What
The same way burning coal
Releases
Better destruct
Burning
This sort of coal
This sort of
Con
The by-product it pollutes
Is that other
People become
Much more stupidly
Yeah
Yeah it that is probably a big part of what makes it so abject
I mean
As long as I wasn't
That's why V like a the confidence-man
Is such an archetype
In American history
Kind of enjoyable about watching someone pull off like a really good spam
Especially when it's against the rich person or somebody like that
They totally have a coming I don't want them to have their fun is a hero for a reason
There's nothing
Intrinsically wrong with
When you're directing it in the right place
The part that's the problem
So NSX clip
This is Barney
Stupid s***
What a shock
So there was all this effort to sort of
American history
American Freedom American Liberty
Celebrating our military
Celebrating the spirit
Heroes and Patriots
Overtime
And not only here in America but around the world because it's America that led the world every other Democratic country
American Revolution
F****** stupid you're not even close to
Realized it like really loudly in between every dead so Alex
I think that he's listened to enough about ya listen to bunch
Of his appearance
Never
And it's either a function of
Subservience
Like Alex knows
That Barn
He's got something
So Alex doesn't have a spot to
Zombie way router
Barnes wasn't my butt
And second
Nice bed
How
Much
Like Barn
But if my lawyer
With sitting in between two people
That Trump just
Exercise
Literally
Using Magic
And I didn't say anything
I'm a bad lawyer yeah and if you join in on
Yeah exactly
Concelebrating military prowess
Cuz he was like
I'm not going to out
Sign off
But that's also because I think he doesn't want to be a lawyer any
I think that there's probably
Express
He wants to be the go-to lawyer for
Dumb s*** head settling lawsuit
It also probably rather transition into this
Paw Patrol
Work for a living
He can rattle off
Stop
The rest of it
He's serviceable and propaganda role he could he can hang
With the Owen Shroyer's and David nights of the world easily
Leo zagami talks about how
Priority are your problem
You're going to Walmart in a mad about what
Tabloid covers
What are you doing
What is the point
What do you have princess on the cover
Wwjd
What would Jesus
Just be doing
At Walmart
Obvious
Next clip
Good this is bad
Is targeted for the same reason that
All these American activities
People Like Us.
Infowars
Infowars is independence day is July 4th
Because it reflects
Americana
So
You know
Julian Castro Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Milan Omar
Don't love this country and actually working against
Alex Jones
Kaitlin Bennett America
Really about
Another one
Protecting the real America
Both groups are that are different from
I didn't bet
You know if there were something really easily distinguishable to tell between the two groups
So
Let me get let me ask you a question
Infowars
America
They are the 4th of July
Is authoritarian propaganda 101
With the entire the only right version
Patriotism
Good job
It does seem
Like you should be
Disqualified
Calling your cell phone
Noah Mara
Cradle
Plumbing
It is a problem
It's definitely we are the Fourth of July we are America
You don't know what those
You're making them up
Just taking
Xenophobia racism
Hierarchical structures that are create a red suit
Superficial characteristics
Something's it there's been a trend
Away from
It doesn't seem like it fits within our ID
Deals
At least the idea
Set forth
Brilliant
1812 9th
When they wrote
The Declaration
You know Leo zagami
Does he think
He is a reincarnate
Four of the bloodline
If it's not it's not clear but he literally said he is
Videos of Messiah news also from the bloodline
Right
So
Like I said I think he's
Typically breathing in order to make it to Alex candid erupted
Which is a smart move on his
Much more time
A button this
I think he shows
Is card
In terms of like
Really wanting to
Just a comment on the show
Listen
Is Prozac
Farts does it home
President Trump's America forever
Forever
Because the audience continue to support it because the audience
Next level
My eyes
Start singing battle
The reverse of what it called does when they open up Galaxy
Taking your products
That was
Smoothies
Consignment Barnes
Unapologetically
Knocking it out of the park
I mean he's had a day
Here he's drinking champagne
He's hung out with
Jesus who did 9/11
Also Club DJ
A lot of people
If I were him I'd need a drink
So here's how he ends up finishing up the
The Sun
We're going to fight to ensure that
Alright
24-hours on-air whatever
What's the difference
Between this episode another present day episode
I think
Well first of all
That story and I've been like this episode was a
The thing is like
I think in the present day
I recognize the stakes
So the things he's saying
And they become so serious that I allow Alex
To really
Guide
What I need to cover
Where is I approached this episode centipede
Trump is doing an exorcism in his fourth of July
Is so goddamn stupid myself to be like what's interesting to me here
How much do I know about Leo zagami and it led me down these roads that are far left
I mean they're disturbing
They're less
Awful
I think I think I need to take care of that with me
In the future I think it's a lesson learned
Of you know
Don't shy away from the important stuff
When Alex
Is being a dick about it
But also trucks
Better story to be told somewhere else right where Alex is
Another episode on
Complete Nutter bigot
Start another civil war
Also I think they're still
I think there is some value to
Keeping an eye on
Presidents
I think it's far more important to
Trust my
To nowhere
Interesting
Could be
Not least because you did not begin this episode with
With your usual exhortation
Parts of it that I hate
But man
Live account
Crazy
Hades.
What a life
You know if he wasn't mixed up with
People trying to rationalize antisemitism didn't have the complete
Real dicey
Dubious history
Personal life
I want to talk to that guy
At the right point
Anna's life
Definitely
He already was quote a notoriously Wild
Yeah baby
On Wednesday with another episode but until then we have website
The threats were also on Twitter also
Contact you if they want more details is all this month
For the next year
Yeah yeah the month of July formation
Showtime
Nearest
Mariano's
They often
Speakers
I know it's a lot more people are going to the bar at Mariano's now
Other than that
What's a
I forgot about that part of it
Uncle Ben
That's not good
Uncle from Spider-Man
Is Alex Jones
Alex