Alexandra Thurston color
A little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
What was the last Wild
Last wild animal wild bird
Farah
No no I mean like in the forest
Like I was in a forest
One night I was at a comedy
Michelle
Fullerton
I don't know the cross street
I was smoking a cigarette pretty drunk
After the show
Walking down the street but a
Swear to God
Walking down the street
Casually
Just walking out like
Isn't
Super uncommon
Wilson coyotes
You'll see
Summer things also confirmed it was it was
Is a wolf walking down Fullerton
I just am already defensive my wolf sighting
Poinciana wolf in Chicago
Who's crazy
Longer goes on as a kid
Like a camping
I saw a moose
It's almost forever one freak the f*** out
For this moose
Yeah we had to run and get in our liked minivans because my parents were scared of what the most could do
Names of moose were like
Was threat
Think it f*** you up
In the van
To see it from a closed
In the relative safety of a car
Pretty cool
Yeah yeah yeah
Also I've been thinking lately about getting
Exotic pets
Either that or just quitting the podcast becoming a park ranger wanted to
Just walking around with one of the Iguana and how much I like
Plants and animals
As I get older in life I kind of am realizing like I really like animals
I really like playing
Maybe I should just be around them more
Did you just really hate this place I think so
Yeah it's probably something we should bring up
Keep my personal life
Kind of personal
Complaining on the show
About Alex or people were lying for a living
Listen to the shonos I had to move
In April and moved into a new apartment
And almost immediately
For the last 3 months
I have had
Credibly
Disturbed
Because of this place
The neighbors have
It's been incredibly loud the guy upstairs
Just like my
Play Shake
When he walks around
It's very it's very difficult
And the sower
That's the long and short of it
I am going to have to move again I hope there won't be any disruption
Interrupt
The podcast
I think it might go a little smoother than
Time possibly
Things could go very wrong
And we will see
But
In the next couple weeks
Thirlby
Some interruptions
Possibly hopefully not but possibly just to give you a little warning in
It's crucial
Cuz I have to get out of here
Some days
Almost nothing
We keep doing this year
I'm running on fumes
Today's weather
It's just it's incredibly insane
Various
Noise pollution aspect
But hopefully
Soak sorry if we missing episodes coming up
But
I also not sorry
Hey I at the end
Yeah you got to get the
Is it like
Difficult because
Well off
And so
Expenses
It's a challenge
I really
Stress enough how much I appreciate
The sport of people who
The show
And donate
Damn Jackie
Able to
Play swear I won't go crazy with it
And so in honor of that let us take a moment
Doctor supporting the show
Very much the first of all Nick thank you so much
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
In our partnership is growing
Whataburger number one November
Text Caroline thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
No
Sorry
Next Chris thank you so much
Next hurdle blurred thank you so much
You're now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Someone who I donated on a little elevated level appreciate it very much so
Much you are now a technocrat
Business
Heroin
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
You donated for elevated Levelland
Really nice conversation
And I really
Gatorsports
And being cool so sweet thank you so much you are now a raptor prints
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites
I don't want
How to read
I am out of control
I bet you money are few living black people
Abused by white people
Joseph Stalin
Scott
I'm cutting off the part where does the Bernie Sanders impressionist
So much Sam really appreciate it and
That's what I feel
Website
Support the show
We would
Sojourn what we're doing today is we've got at July 7th
+ 8
20 nights
All right what are the check-in of the present-day and I felt
The audience would not let us all
Off the hook if we didn't
Because of big breaking news in the world
Particularly the arrest
Jeffrey Epstein
Particularly interest
Covering up because I
Leave their media Outlets
They can do that much
More
Precisely
Better than I can
I'm also not particularly interested in covering
Alex's version of it
One of the main reason
Is because all he does is talk about how Trump never hung out with him
And Jeffrey Epstein
Just friends
The Clinton
I don't care
To respond to that
Because then it becomes this
Game of Life
Is this
I honestly think this is good
Researches
Weak sometimes
I think the
I took him like this
Is a little bit beyond my paygrade
And I don't trust
That we could
Cover it
With the
Respect
Also not covering it meme
Smile quote
Is going to be way lower potion
Quotient
I dipped in here on Sunday
And I expected
It's be wall-to-wall
Clinton
Going down really
I did cuz it's such a big piece
Is worldview right there it is
I thought for sure it would just be
Nothing but apps
Can you talk
I was shocked to find
There's not much
He doesn't talk
Too much about that situation
He declares Victory and
Claims the trumps not involved
Declare victory
So Alex is mostly
Here's how I would describe
Alex is definitely affected by this
Operating
Off of it
But it's not a primary Story 4
He is onto other things
A lot of it has to do with like
You know Trump
Is great
We're so great
Gonzaga
And I think it leads him
To make a little bit of you know you know that moment
And a Bond movie where the villain says something a little bit too much
Are we are we doing the speech
Are we giving the the monologue whenever bond is on the on the chopping block
Old game
I think that this might have shades of that to it
This here's our first clip from July
I'll say this
This is
We have successfully radicalized the president
President
Especially
Is the CIA
Define
Michelle's
So I mean whenever you have protestations
From Alex about like we aren't some sort of radicalizing force it's difficult to hear stuff like that
You kind of already know it
You literally know what you're doing
Yeah you think it's
Good
You know what you're doing people make accusations you were doing this
You could really do
Disputed that you don't
Agree that it's bad
You can't
Disagree that your radicalizing the present
You just f****** said it yeah
Whether or not that's true
Weather
Braggadocio
People usually put
After radical
Is
Terrorist
Usually that's how people
Will do that
He's kind of
Turn the president into a terror
America America
Alex has a justification for
Terrorism is good she has a rationale
I guess basically
You know sort of radicalization version of like
A rubber and glue
Chicken and egg something but here you go
Islamic
All of it
So you justify radicalizing the president of the Pentagon and the CIA your attire
Your imaginary enemies being super radical
To be the worst f****** thing in the world therefore
If I'm the second worst thing in the world
That's better than
This doesn't work this is really bad
Incredibly terrible
If you accept this line of thinking
Like it rationalizes pretty much anything you could possibly think of doing
Especially
Your justification
Entirely imaginary
Right you know what like there's no unless unless your imagination is completely Limited
That basically means you have carte blanche to do whatever you want
Anytime
As long as you can come up with some
Lindsay rationalization
Confirm
This
Because of is somehow worse
Bombshell
The people were doing this to stop our terrible
Absolutely
We of course
We have
To commit the Holocaust
Because
The Jews were going to kill 6 million and one of us
I mean he does believe that the globalist
Orchestrated both sides of World War II
Do a World War
It wouldn't be as bad as the global world
People first
Sew-ins
If we get to Alex
Clearly indicating that he still believes
FIFA
Is out there throwing concrete milkshake
Otherwise people will forget that you're supposed to shoot anyone with
Milkshake on
Write a good portion
His coverage
He's trying to because the enemy is so radical we radicalized
Straight why these people that their cancer superrradical
You talked about Aunt
So terrible out there there on concrete milkshakes
So many people have died at those rallies right like a
So
But it's interesting because do you know Aunt
Think about it
And Alex knows why
The target
Go out
Happen
Because the police are being
Blackmail
What were the police being blackmailed
All of them
How to share but last year
We got 30 plus pages of secret documents
Members brother
For a while
Soros
And one level is your
Chop't
New stamps are going to attack
Because they're conservative
Dallas makes perfect sense so far contracts he found online that he's using his justification for
I don't understand what the
To deny that these are real
Getting
This b******* and the police know that and so that's why I was blackmailing
With the information that they can't
Comment on well I hadn't considered that
Talking stupid
So
Stanley dumb like
Just the idea that there would be contract
Is stupid
Criminal Enterprise like this supposed to trigger riot
Like that is what these fake documents
R4
Did Alex's
Narrative
The idea
Luge
Corporation
Alexander Soros
Wood rot f****** contract
That would somehow be by
Is so stupid
It's so stupid you have to be
Like so detached from reality
You have to be so far gone
To imagine
You would just do it without a contract
Jesus
You know what people like
Mules and like drug runners
Goes wrong
Or regulation unemployment
Contract when you're a rioter you're acting writer who knocks over conservative
Court of course
Stupid
You think about how efficient that system is
You're in you're already in Port for the criminal trial right for you doing all the time
You just go across the hallway to the Civil Court just doing for the
It's
To directions to because if you're Alexander Soros and you hire some people
Go to start a riot they don't start a riot
People break their kneecaps like a contract for it to be enforceable
They did not deliver all the work that you
But you got to hire somebody to do the end the contract
As if you just really convince those people to commit the right in the first place all grows out of like anti-communist bullshits
Unearth narrative Alex needs to make about how we get the contract because there's Union
Please or something like that
I have to assume that's coming at some point
Stupid I hate this s***
Whenever Peter this stuff I just like
A person listening
Denying those documents is a must be real like
I can't imagine how hopeless
You must be
How far gone you are from reality
Eliza somebody would make you
President of the
Crazy
So that you know
Cool
He's also got another complaint about Auntie so that I actually think it's pretty funny
Squarely under that heading of
Can't use a bullhorn well
This is another complaint
Light
Aflac
And then get it going that way
Fluid
What is in the burning American flags as we just we're just think in front of a lion
That masculine thing where you have to help someone light a grill
Credit where credit's due again so Alex follows this up by being like they have every right to burn a flag
You wouldn't expect that position
Explicitly
We saying
Wrong with that burning
Disgusting
Repulsive I disagree with it but they have every right to do it
You do sort of imply that they're just trying to trigger people in
The fighting right now
You know the flag on fire is trying to bait
Someone into a fight
You could make that argument
Implying intention
Shinzon somebody that maybe they don't have
But it's certainly much better than
It should be illegal
Okay I'll give him a little credit for that
Burning Flags cuz it really sounds like he knew he knew he knows exactly what he's
Bullhorn
Flag burning
Alex Alex is your guy for those
To know exactly what things
Really
Because
The news
Not good drinking whiskey
Tito's from time
Okay
Flag-burning full hornung
What else
Not like spending time with the kids
So you got it that
Not checking into who he's talking to right
Real good at that
Direct
Play as we get to the 8th
Because
Being a little bit here and there it's in his standard deflection are away for the most part
To talk about how everyone
Start demonic pedophiles
To the actual
Feel no compunction about us
Not really talking about it
Alex is mostly interested in someone else
Van Nuys
July 8th episode
As a British guy
Please help
Just stop by
Islam assistive
Trump bleach on his face in the prison
Marked for Death
For up to a year
Trains
That's a big store
Yeah with me
That would be
Everywhere
Yeah
It was
So this is an amazing display of sloppiness on Alex's Park almost impressive how bad a job is doing good
The story he's talking about is that a Charlene down
Who was a fourteen-year-old in the UK
The police began operating on the assumption that she was most likely
Dad started investigating the case has never been
Investigators believe the Charlene was known to engage in sex acts
In an alley behind a row of business
In the township
She's from the owner
Zayid
Was arrested for her murder
With salacious accusation
Can flying around that there's nobody
Because they put her into the Kebab meat they sold their fast foods
We'll see
Muhammad Ali was also arrested on charges of helping
Dispose of the body
In 2007 both men were acquitted because there was no evidence that any of this was true
Call Charlene
So took that as
Does absolute conclusion read was a place where she was no.
Frequent gossiping tabloid level
Thousand and Muhammad were both awarded $250,000
Compensation for the damage
That the botched investigation because of rumors like this this young girl and put her in
Kebab meat
Yeah I imagine that his restaurant
Flourish
Probably had a little bit of
Difficulty
There's more to this case that is publicly known even right now
Is it the story of Charles
Being killed is not true
Every reason
Hey 2019 Channel 5 made a documentary called the murder of Charlene Downes
Really troubling
Details about the
That were not known preview
For instance the documentary reveals that about a week into the police investigation to Charlene's disappearance
They decided that if they did so they would not return her to her parents
But instead Placer in child protect
Custody
Reasons was out for that was that on the day Charlene went missing
Her parents invited a pedophile into their home
The maker of the documentary uncovered a social service report regarding an incident between Charlene
Did you stay with them
On the day she went missing
But there aren't a ton of details about the nature of that in
I'm not entirely sure
Exactly
What why what happened
This wasn't the first instance of the parents allowing abusers
Into their home
Has reported in 2013 that a four-year-old family friend
Admitted to authorities that it hurt
And at least six
Man with criminal conviction
Sims 4 rape assault or violence
Heaven visitors in their home
There were tons of warning signs that she was living
In a very unsafe house
Obviously I don't know the details of the case and they're probably few living people who do know
Exactly what happened
What I can say is that just a very small amount of research would have demonstrated to Alex that these she was murdered and put into
Kabobs
Is bogus
Irresponsible was refuted in a court of law and is still only still repeated B
Islam agitators
Who don't care about the
They don't care about what really happened to Victor
They only care about using the appearances of these in
To demonize their scapegoat population
And that's what Tommy Robbins
Has been doing
Gears
One of the main groups that is kept the Kabob narrative alive
Any self-respecting person would have accepted
You know that it was bulshit
Was bedl
Vigorous defense
Wichita me Robinson
Confounded
They are.
Deeply responsible for this.
Kick to the Dustbin of history as just
The issue is that they're not making it up out of whole cloth
Right part of it was based on
The guy's name but it was based on a guy who's like a contractor whose
That he overheard
Aida Mohamed talking about it like we killed her and put her in the
Kabob
Whatever investigation
I found that he is a unreliable source of information
Information
There's nothing
Confirms this or it anyway
Lends credibility
And they uncovered some
Disgruntled business relation
And the guys who ran this fast food restaurants
There were some indications that he would have a reason
To create salacious
Just rumors about them based on
Prior working
Relations edl takes that
Insist that it must be true as opposed
To Be Wild
There's nothing really to back this up that is
There's
A lot of other information that looks pretty f*****-up about the
This case maybe we shouldn't use this
As a banner
Seems like all we're doing is being
Racist to s*** like all they were doing was being racist
Sister ship
That's kind of because that is what they would do
Okay so what they were doing was being racist
The s*** and that's why
Looked like what they were doing
Is a real f****** tragedy
Because
The reality of this situation
Tubi
Oh really
You know terrifying
Encased
Child neglect
Did abuse
And instead of dealing with it on
Demerits
Turn off the information
You know you just
Move the guilt over to
To the party that you want to blame
It's disrespectful to evict
It's disrespect
People who
Yeah
Tommy Robinson in don't care
They do not care
The co-opting victim
Will use energy
Application
Play wolf
Under the under the radar under the surf
Like the cruelty
Torrid
People
Muslim
That's very overt
And very visible
But just underneath that is a cruel to eat
People who are survivors
Because the coop
Using
They're actually in order to demonize absolutely larger Muslim population
Because if you spent
Any of the
Time
Effort
And resources that you put towards
Demonizing Muslims
Towards
Helping victims of abuse like
Maybe
People wouldn't you know
Maybe you keep a few people from
Actively
Hurting people along with diverting
Any attention
To what really could be fixed
Right
Xenophobic in ethnic
Bass
Demagoguery is not the solution
The problems of crimes
Against children
Right nothing solution
To anything other than a Jeopardy question for what Trump is doing
Be all Tommy Robinson
It does
So f*** him
So
I guess there's one clip of stuff about Epstein that all play and it's just because
This is
This is insane
Like the idea
I don't I don't particularly care to be like
Categorically that's not true let's look at the other end
Alex is just repeating
That is not good that is not a good source of
He's not your
Spiraling out of control talking about how
The last
Are vampires
Are we
Apparel
Okay
Children
That's just the blood libel
Yeah
Interesting
They say that we put them in cages and we're Nazis now let me
Mirror pieces
Nazi propaganda
Hey dude
Calm down
I do I just did
I hate I hate some of this stuff is important like it
Really insane
The level is
Stupidity Vuitton display here
Like responsible
Detestable
It leads people into
Same
Stupidity
The dumb f****** beliefs
They are
But it's also boring
To be an opportunity for us to do a deconstruction of
Historical roots of the blood libel
How
Far it's gotten
Cuz
We're listening to this
And we're like
Literally saying that people are drinking f****** blood
Somebody eating a f****** child
And all of this
Naked over it
Going out in public to a large audience
And we're over it
Things that by degrees I think we've become so descent
The ties to stop headaches
I think most right-thinking people could hear all
Of the clips that we play if you like
Fukkit this dude is crazy
It makes sense if you understand why
Elizabeth
I'll just make a twist excessive talking about here's the roots
Here's why you saying what do you say it doesn't make it
Make sense or good
Existed
Yeah
But it also is
Is just
Play recently
They're like
So you guys don't allow Alex
Speakers.
Do you cut him out of contacts and that
Kind of stuff sure do
You need to
Okay
We can't even begin to describe how much
Context we have given this matter
I can't even breathe
Jim to describe
Who's one of the principals when I started I was bummed out by
In context cuz context makes him worse
So not only
Do liberals
Drink
Liberal
Beautiful things
Destroyed
Sure
Ridgeland
Institutionalized
Almost like he's talking about Integracore
It's almost like he watched something about Munchausen by proxy
Just in cases
More s*** talk
Liberal
And
The flight unpacking
As much as
You know life just come
From cursed bloodlines
Yep it seems like so much of his
Distinction of who is an
Leftist
Comes down
Issues of
Race
There's so much of the
JW stuff is being
And Alex's world it's difficult to hear him
Did whatever you talk about blood
He just
You go fart
You close to
Stuff that look if you if you come from curse bloodline
You're not
.
Done
It's like a Sci-Fi novel
Another reality
You got this.
If you say that
I really think whatever you talk about Bloodlines at all
Your
You're in trouble
You're already past the point where it's like
Are you going to say some
Something good cuz you're not
I've ever heard bloodline
Discuss
Like here's a contact for a benign bloodline
Thanks
Oh yeah and my family's history our bloodline has shown very patrician nose
Is a
Common
Yeah I don't know if you can do this
Oh boy
There is no way to say bloodline without
I feel like it
Territory I'm not positive anyone can really never
Marathon
So in this next clip Alex
You know
You got a lot of a lot of things
Things working again
You know you got the world
World government
You got the leftist
Antifa out there you got Elvis
Eating human kabobs
Right
No
Another enemy of all World churches
Devils
So
I mean
I don't I don't know how to look at this other than
Just like a direct
Extension of all of his
Like destroying
An impudent
Any kind of
Agreed upon reality
You know like anything's gives
50 Cent
Community that isn't
Connected to his crazy worldview
Must be attacked
In some way
Any kind of popular culture that we all share like we talked about
Clarett or whatever that program
I guess we won't talk about that I like to go to my church where all my friends cookout
Do you know that
Where am I going to get involved in local politics
Has been great for me
There is nothing that doesn't every single thing
About his rhetoric in his world
You to isolate from everything
Things that are tacitly or explicitly approved by Alex
Which are almost
Exclusively
Bigotry related
Militia
I think you like the movie Independence
Daiso
His book right
Welcome To Earth
Come on
I would say probably
Thinks he's a globalized
Probably
Maybe
Galaxy problems
Empire of some sort
Is he a Scientologist
I don't know I remembered all the rumors but it never interest
Stood me all that much
I never really looked at
Next Corp
You know like they're f******
Devil
Running of the world's churches
Yeah
Ism is everywhere
As evidence
Next
So how his voice lilt
Okay so f****** condescend okay this is amazing
On your face
New York
What's 666
This is a safe
Saudia 606
Six pieces of glasses where that real sucking condescending tone came out not true
Look at him
He didn't do and I'm just
Hallelujah
Remember if you suspect
Donut conspiracy
Recite that aren't true
Building isn't dedicated
What room is the building includes a sculpture that is provided by funding from the aleutians trust
Grew out of a company called the Lucifer publishing cup
Okay for a couple years and I was like 20 years before the UN
Confounded
The people behind the Lucius trustworthy Asif
Back in the early Knights
And as such they had approached
The name Lucifer publishing company was likely chosen
Because we like bringing connotation of lucid
For within this circle
The time
And the name Lucius trust was chosen as a replacement because it contains the Latin root word meaning
Lights it doesn't evoke images of the devil in
People
The keep the enlightening meaning of their name
Avoid people thinking they worship the literal Chris
They were doing such a good job at first they were like
Lucifer
People are really
Yeah unfortunately they were wrong about changing their name
People still like literally
Kristen Bell
This is just made up to a completely inaccurate
The Justified
All this just serves that exact
Text same
Function
It's just it's just
Justification of radicalization
That's all this is
Destruction
Just like
It's believed
Go to the Loo yeah I go to the movies just got to be sucking walking into things
It's beautiful
He loves the Renaissance right
The devil real
About how Trump is the good guy
The Border
Naoc suck
I think Carrie has a little bit of a racist voice
You decide
Media
Cheaper
I mean what are you going to do about it
They're like the people who are against Trump are killing kids every 5 minutes and torturing them in order to gain
Spiritual demonic power in order to overthrow the United States
Like he's so close to
To Steven Kelly the guy who wants to store with a Getty Museum
Cuz Big Daddy
Alien base underneath it
Save the theme s***
Well that's because
Alex Jones has entered the territory of Z creepiest
Darius
Dude I've ever seen on Project Camelot
Like really f****** close to a guy who I've watched a bunch of his videos and I like we can cover this
It's not funny rise creepy as hell
Jesus
Guys
Just leaving
You want to eat children at the border
Disincentivize
People that come
Just
Say it
We don't bother with all this
Demons
You you're the bad guys
You think you're doing it in service of a larger good I guess but
Just admit that you're
Bad this is an objectively bad thing but I will
That
I don't know everything about the
And should
Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Go down to the Border
Then
Sprouts
I'm willing to amend my position
I agree
Now you're right
Keep you updated on whether or not
Alexandria ocasio-cortez becomes a demon
Still no couple hours
Racist or not racist don't know
I couldn't hear
To whom it was being racist felt like it drifted a little in
To Tuscany
Cookies very good
Football
Twisted Tiffany
Is there 28
It was a very racist
It was
Clunky
That should be your family crest
So he gets into the second hour
Is
He decides he's going to hand over the show to Tommy Robinson
No because Tommy
Something big
Going on you will be soon
Robinson is going to have the floor
Rush Hour
Request the president
I'll just let him
Gyros
Disappear
Probably got five minutes
Just watch this
Political emergency
So Tommy Robinson gets an hour on Alex's program too big
The president of the United States for Asylum
Which is funny
Tommy
Assertive
Begin
His case
Is Tommy Robinson
It's not it's Stephen yaxley-lennon
Ministration
Republican Party
United States of America
Go fuc yourself
Tommy Robinson
Because you can f*** right off
And I've exactly zero interest in even engaging
With his particular brand of b*******
He's made a career of xenophobia native nativist agitate
Lying about very serious issue
And there's nothing in his pattern behavior any of his actions are carried out good faith
Ever
For some level of con
Last July on a radio show called conversation
Even Nigel farage tried to explain to
Steve Bannon
Who expressed support for everybody
And even Nigel farage said Tommy did break the law
There's something
Incredibly hilarious
Plan that he's launching gear though
Four years Tommy's bait
Tons of money by demonizing people who fled mortal danger in their home country
Seek Refuge
Status of the EU
Or the United States
And now that he's facing a little bit of jail time.
Clearly legal action
He's begging the president of the United States intervened in Britain have the very same refugee
She said it was marked as being sincere in the case of Muslims and non-white peoples in the United
Man you know what that reminds
Remind people
People who are alive
First Amendment rights no regulation and then
Those happen to them and they're like President regulating
F*** off
That that is the
Wolverine irregularly
To prison he deserves it
My field notes
54 mm
The Queen's Court determined the quote to condone the live broadcast of these
Defended being aggressively confronted as they arrive for court
In conjunction with prejudicial commentary exhortation
Engage entrapment
It would pose a risk to The Wider interests of the justice
Which makes sense
Encouraging harassment
The court was on pretty solid footing
Pull-A-Part in the livestream where Tommy says quote
Him find him go knock on his door follow him
See what he's doing
That
But like my first check was going to be like
Harass those people because
Yeah that's a very obvious
What it is
No
Over the top
Incorrect don't believe the Tommy brings up this part of his commentary
Stupid
It was a legitimate Brie to the justice system call to vigilante
Even beyond that his actions worked against
To stated goal
He pretended he was there to cover Muslim story grooming gang somehow imagined that his livestream would help the prophet
I guess
Without his help the man on trial and sentence
To 12 years in prison
But because of Tommy's interference
Batman was almost able to
Appeal his conviction on the grounds that Tommy's livestream
And the ensuing protests
What Tommy is doing is illegitimate
Answer your threat not only to the larger Muslim Community in the United Kingdom but also to prosecutors are trying to deal with
Are you Tommy
Professors are
Like legitimately
He endangered the prosecution of that case
He brought a camera into the quarter which is it
Explicitly not allowed
Primarily because you can use the footage you captured and purposes
You know that encourage the harassment of people like judges arteries
Or council member
There's a very good reason to not allow cameras
In court broke that law
Because of his overwhelming me
Pretension
What is pathological hatred of Muslims
You received it
Suspended sentence
So if you reoffended while still under that's
Andre offend did
He was given every chance not to
To be in the situation he's in now
The UK courts tried to save him from himself
As we saw with the lion of London Bridge
Yeah well
Yep
I definitely wrote sympathy for him being held response
No and he's
This is the situation
You know when you're when you're talking about Frozen
Reform is it about Rehabilitation
Yeah
Punishment
What is what is the purpose behind the prison
I feel like
Prison is the wrong place for him what he needs is exile
I pick him out of the Deport him I revoke his UK citizenship status
I don't know how that would help Sterling would probably leave him
Using that as of course
But like yeah
As I was
Listening to this
So the thinking about it I was reflecting on it
I don't love incarceration
Generally
I don't I don't know what the right answer is for punished
Sing like this
I don't know how you deal with
Someone like him
Especially someone who
Has a
Decade
Decade-and-a-half
Lifelong career is it
Big Brawl
Based
Political activity
The
The career of xenophobia and agitation
I do not think that you would be receptive
Kind of rehabilitative
Intervention
How does that
Square with my feelings that I don't think
People
Generally
Should
Be in prison
Only real
Punishment for these guys would be removing their ability to
But like their platform
Should be completely
You know like
Like with Jim Bakker
Jim Bakker
Spent his entire career scamming people out of money
And then when he got out he reformed himself and started
Bright
With the Lessons Learned of where the line is
But it's like a
The quote from blow or whatever I want in
To jail with a and then I went out with
A problem for most people
Fraud
It's the part where you actually committed a like out-and-out fraud
The present
It's not even respond
Like he's not going to go in for whatever
Come out with like
Push it even farther whenever he gets out
No deal brexit maybe he will have
You just do whatever you want
I don't have any
Real feeling
In about the other
I would love to see a overhaul of the incarceration
Can State I would love to see that
Needs to do that their sovereign country they have their laws because
That operate however they operate the first
Aha is long
As long as the prison
Is where people
Are sentenced to
For what
He did
I'm not I'm not going to go to bed for
As long as he's not being held in like solitary confinement
Or being targeted
Specifically for violent attacks
I don't really I'm not going to cry to your
I want him to be safe and warm and it's far away from
Damage
As far away from the possibility for him to do.
Today like
As long as
He's not
Being like harmed
As long as he's not in solitary confinement
If you have to spend two years in
In prison and that's the only
Consequence for all the damage
Richie's done in his career
Getting off
Really he's really
And it just goes to show like
This is a natural
What's 4
Chickens come home to roost
What do you do
You
Beg
Trump
And if there's one if anybody listens
Take away one
Do not ever give these guys
Even this
Slightest benefit of the doubt
If you're going to sue
I'd go all the way and asked for a goddamn
Destroy these guys
I really hate this
I hate this s*** and I hate the show
It's legit most of the show
Rambling on and misrepresenting his case completely different
Much less patience
At least Alex is the target of my enter
Talkingshit for an hour it is boring
It might be something in there that's like
That's an interesting
Thought gives me a greater context
What Alex
Snopes
There's nothing that he could say in the course of this hour that will interest
Whatever you would like
So Alex has a plan
Getaround
Here's what it is
Paternalism
Inside
Prior convictions works for journalism
The cop
Girlfriend
Had some cocaine
If you got in trouble for having a fake
Passport
And mortgage fraud
He's a career f****** criminal creative nonfiction
He's got the rest
Super Broly
Use a
Yeah really is
Uniform
Uniformly if you any right-thinking person
Would know that he's a piece of
And it's not right
Is whether or not
That's pretty good
Sort of
A good just general personality test
Step if you like Tom Robinson
You believe that ship
So
I do
Care at all
I don't care
Tommy Robinson deserves go to prison
If I sound like way the police decide to give him another shot or whatever the courts
Society
Alright we're going to give you another suspended sentence
I also don't care about that
Go to prison
Like I would love for him to stop being a s*******
I don't think prisons going to solve that problem
I don't think I'm not going by problem
He's going to be probably no matter what
It doesn't matter
2zz propagandist with bad faith
He just is a
Have us all on the road to Tarsus
Moment where you realize it
Oh God this whole career was brought into the world
Right but he never will
No I don't care
When Alex
Probably Carol little bit if
Asylum
I don't think that's going to happen development I think it starts
To get a little bit more interested in this
Just
I don't give a
That would be why
That would be
Do you know how ridiculous international version of pardoning Arpaio
Really
It's an internet National
Waiting to happen even f****** farraj doesn't like tummy Robin
That's why I that's why I could start getting more involved with youth camp once for
Raj started the authority
Just wild to think
The UK bigger community
Multitude
But even people who don't like
Like each other
15 different accents in London
So I don't care
I don't care
Okay
No
I don't
Give us
But it's interesting to me that I would scare so much
Yeah that is
It's not really
I only doing this to set up
Clip
Alex care so much to take over his chauffeur an hour
But he doesn't care that much
Cuz he's got another guy
Yes coming up
He's cutting
Carpe donktum
Who makes memes I don't know
If there's a the Latin phrase
Ramen
Use the dog
I don't know
Listen
Cease badonk
Piercings in my life where I'm like
Yeah
Let me stay up till 3 in the morning researching
Leo zagami
How about car
Kerouac
Ticking Toby Robinson
Because he's got carp
Here's what I know about Carpe donktum
He makes memes
He apparently wanted in forward meme competition
And Trump retweeted that me
What is pretty much royalty world
I don't know how much veracity there is today
Because the world is so
Yeah
I believe anything
Speech
Internet
The people who you invited
Of course meeting of the minds
True or not because the bigger issue is
It makes so much sense
It could be true
Yeah that's the world that we are living
Yeah yeah
This is the dumbest I sound like a broken record but I don't
What's he got to say
Not a lot
Does he have a new
Does he have a meme
Is this like a new album to talk about now
He also is apparently
Thinking about starting a website
I heard that
Why don't you have a f****** website already
Handsome
The president
Do you have your f******
Scams that you're running
Patreon 2
Nobody donators
Always surprised
When I see you
People who are in this
Scam world
Who aren't doing a good job monetizing their scam
Stand is there people who think that there's sincerity involved at like
I don't know I don't know
I think it probably
Maybe comes down to ambivalence
Not knowing exactly the steps
You're supposed to take
But
Looking to the right places maybe like
A lot of that money is coming
And somewhere else
Describe star account that has a ton more donors and I just looked at the patreon
I don't know
Who gives a s***
F****** care but a
Meme guy
Coming on
Alex's show
Hey we didn't get invited to the social-media thing and look where I'm at about it
What about about it
We got f****** Carpe donktum he's going to be there
There's kind of a passive-aggressive thing going on yeah
It's not super
Stream
It sometimes is about to die it's not
It's not as overt
No but it's
You can see
Feel it still
Trying to
Make right
The fact that they didn't
It's
Whatever it is f****** lame and I
I don't
I sound like a f****** broken record but I don't care I don't care
I know.
I don't even like you saying those were
What is real name
Don't give a s***
So he's talking to
My bad Docs
And
In the middle that conversation Alex brings back up Tommy Robbins
Play in order to make this
Situation seems so much more severe than
Brother
He has created a false
Version of what time you getting in trouble for to present to the audience
To make it appear that
Just because
Bear point out those lumps are committing crimes
Titleist does
Sure Carpe donktum
That it's insane
Next year when you find out that
In the late 80s
DJ Envy
I don't think he's old enough
I don't think Carpe donktum is old enough
Look at that mold
I just
I'll be more disappointed when
Pence drops out
Trump
Donktum
Tony Plumbing
And I'll look the fool
Far-left believable
I wish that that were so out there I could
Could never ever under
Understand it but I swear to God if
Just chooses
Meme
Not even not even Carpe donktum
Prairie supposed to work
He's just going to hold up a meme next to him while he's given
That that
Would make as much sense as any f******
Nasher
Alex
It is the last clip
She just talked to Carpe
More
This just
Set up this clip but it just really can
Smart Cookie
What that mean
Is that true
Preparing
So he's having these people come to the White House
As if it's some sort of Willy Wonka
Let's find the snitch game
Breakaway
Correctly
I think what he saying to start with is that Trump is inviting these people
In order to create Ministry of propaganda
So that's why these people are coming
In the middle of that
This is also a test of loyalty
Slugworth will show up globalist
And I suppose if you make the wrong meme that's like fizzy lift
A bunch of little mini Stephen Miller's will show up in a song that would be
Somehow more racist than the already
Depiction
Cannot handle
The present day we live in the dumbest timeline
Yeah
You ever try and wrap your head around it I dice I've stopped
I've just decided I can't wrap my head around the world
With that we live in when the going
Turn pro
Hunter S Thompson
Like you just kind of got to lean into it I guess
Semblance of Sanity while also like
I mean where are we
How how
How far away from home
Are we
Without even realizing
The steps we took away
Like it's crazy every time I walk outside I hear that
F******
Everyday everyday I walk outside
Clownworld Daniel
We are suggesting we talked about it on the ship
S*** now it's not everything is it isn't anti-semitic mean
I mean that's what you know fascist authoritarians do General Hitler co-opted
VRBO
It's part of
How do you fix
Infect
Areas of life
I can walk them towards their side the okay sign
Another
Example of
The strategy of
Mild psychological warfare
So I mean we come to the end of this and I mean I think
I wouldn't I would assume that people list
Probably felt this but
Completely run out of
I run out of Interest
Not Alex but like this
Like
But this present
Is much more like the present then maybe how much fun it was to
Look into Leo's
This is indicative of the experience this like you going
You kind of expect it's going to be awful
Do you know because with Epstein getting arrested
You kind of think that there's going to be an awful nice to it
He kind of think you know what
The version of awfulness
It's going to be is
I need you
You stood up
You prepare
Alright
I'm not I don't want to do this
But here we go
And what you find it
That is largely
Alex just read
Shredding territory that we've covered a hundred times
On the show
You're covered the blood libel
.
His dumbass
Nonsense
Tommy Robinson and his history
Not
There isn't there isn't a whole lot that
It's like climbing a rock
You just find like
There's nothing to grab here
Oh well
Yeah we we got to the top
The mountain
So we just go back down
Is there something up
Was there
Just just the satisfaction of having done
Boo
Ultimately
Not all you were me
Although this does seem to be something of a pattern for him is when there is something where you're like
You got to have
He's got to have some awful take
A little bit
I'm barely going to talk about this
This is awful I think I actually everybody already knows what I'm going to say about the
Nail-it lockherup let's call it a day ago about aplenty in the past
Break
Ryan's
As a jump-off point for something else
Which is
Demonizing your opponent
Justifying the radicalization again
Them
And then parlaying that somehow into
We got to save Tommy Robinson for from
Consequences of his own actions
Like I think that if you look at it it really
It feels like Alex's
More interested in using
Whatever
Current events
Type coverage he has in order to
Yeah I think he is more interested
Funneling that towards Tommy
Tommy is more interested that then
DJ dubs
Technically is leaving
Maybe or has already left
Who knows
But when he does go
Alex is looking for a Tommy Rob's
To take over
No cuz he's already got damn really he already has that off
I don't think Alex
Could afford time
I don't know how desperate Tommy Robinson is but it means you had
He works for a rebel media
He probably would
Need more than Alex
If Tommy doesn't
Leave the UK
He's going to get arrested again
I don't think that's an Alex's best intro
To have him
Tell me what time
Definitely be asking
Sing for help
Do the states
Right that's the whole idea
Oh you don't mean someone in England to someone who is British
I think you could find someone else because I will tell you this right now I guarantee
He is like I am losing a British person who talks like that I need to replace it with another
I mean
Shirt
I guarantee I think
Think that there are less baggage
Having people
Who having a
But Alex good
Lock to that rule
Sure
What what it what is that would be
Appears
I know
Broken record
I just don't care
I care about the Mist
Information in misrepresentation
Stop I absolutely do I care about the
Corrosive influence
But this is very interesting Alex's phoning it in
Quite a bit
Yep
Hello
It's I resent it a little ways to my time
Much better use of my time then
The last couple days of his shower
So
Oh man
Until next time
It is what it is
Another episode
Right so we also go to bed Jordan
We are and if you wanted to download our podcast
A switch you should do
You can probably tell some
But you can go to
Yeah
Go to a direct libsyn
You can
Corner Bodega
That will
Charge you a $5
To get it but they will give it to you under the table I promise
That
So you can do that there
Naturehike
Those are fun
So
AOC
Probably has
Is Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color