Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Do you like to sit around and drink
Apple wine
Boone's Farm strawberry daiquiri apple wine
Alex Jones
It did not occur to me I just now read that
It can't be apple flavored like strawberry daiquiri
Strawberry
Squeeze strawberries
Anyway
The fat man roll around in a barrel and then whatever falls out is good
Cartoons
Moscato wine review podcast
As we have Alex Jones related
It depends on how the trial really
Just switch to
Red white beard
We are number one
Podcast but instead we just
Outlaw Wine Festival
Just another interview
Ugly not too white dude sitting around
Regular Show
Discuss what he's up to
The come out of his mouth but there's a twist
What's address
Twisters that I know a ton about Alex Jones
How about me how much do I know about zilch
Show off with a little bit
First of all
Speeches I love her
Today is my birthday
I wanted to take a moment to reflect
On the fact
It's not exactly what I anticipated
Is no part of me that would have predicted
That I would be
A co-host
Hey Alex Jones debunking podcast
I've actually my goal since I was about eight years old
Over the years when I was younger I thought I was going to be a professor
They're like my dad
When I grew up a little bit I wanted
To be like
Archaeologist
Or maybe a Greek
Teacher on a date
I love the language
Knotted study didn't
Extensively in college
Really
Speak Greek not really but I can translate it and mostly homeric
Oklahoma
Greek
Slightly
Fluent
My point is
Just trying to derail this week
Those were things man I got a little bit further down the track
I thought you know I'm going to be a stand-up comedian
Expectation of my life for a really long time
And now we're here
It's not a disappointment
Today I could not be happier that this is how I spend my time
It's great and I can't thank you all enough listen
See
Mastiff
Download
A thrill
It's great I can't
I can't thank you enough
Listeners
At least
In some ways validating
. of my life
Centerview speak Greek
We are now it's fight at gmail.com
We now know that we got a we got a whole new audience
Yeah but thank you to all the all the people with us in the beginning and for sure
Do you guys have been amazing
And then I knew people probably
Pieces of my speech
Yeah but if you want to give me a birthday present
Feel free to
Nothing that would be the best
The most awesome birthday present
Is continuing
Do share the show with friends
That would be awesome
Receive Word of Mouth
It makes such a big difference leave a review on the iTunes
Unsubscribe
If you feel so inclined to give me a physical gift
I'm not going to turn you down we got a patreon
Go ahead and do that
In this 33rd year in my life
I want this to
Expand I want
Further
Go after right-wing propaganda
Cuz I hate it
So much
It is
The scourge of every conversation
Absolutely
Is that I'm going to introduce this as the anthem
For my 33rd year
On the planet
This is what it's all about this is what it's all about I have no idea what that
Japanese pro wrestler theme song
Advanced I take no joy or pleasure this
I am so sorry
Make sure this is your last 33rd birthday
Anyway
I'm not sure but that's that's the anthem that's going to be going through my head entire year
I'm mildly hungover but I just want
Sasha Banks theme song
I really should have probably written my points out
And let's let's keep it
Let's keep going
Forget into today
I want to I want to thank
The show early April we forgot to give a shout out
And this one's for you man
I'm a policy wonk
Welcome to the team policy walk
I will go through
Give everyone one of these everyone who has donated in the past.
Longtime supporters
Appreciate it
Something going on in Fort Worth
To defeat the Huns
Alex isn't Court
So you can't do is show
He's in court during the hours that the show is going on
So two days out of a week David
And I could not lift
No the other day
Paul Joseph Watson who's visiting Austin
At this point
Great
Hit by truck narratives that he's been spinning are completely bogus
I just want to take a second without playing his voice
Explain what he's been talk
About
The first thing is Malcolm Nance
He's a pundit and former
Extensive experience in the
World
He is an expert on Al-Qaeda
Is Terrorism
Specialist
Antique
Trump Hotel Istanbul
To be the first Target
Terrorism against
Prop prop
Nominated meaning
Is the most likely thing or nominated meaning he was like
That is
Version of what you're saying is what
Gotcha you saying is predict that will be the first because of course
Of course the World Trade Center
Predicted that would be the target
Because it had already been the target one time but
I nominate this to be the next you're not saying hey terrorist
Get at it
You know this is the most likely
Oscar thing all over again maybe they hit it but they
They got the wrong place we watching
Yeah we're going tomorrow I'll go
8120 language
What's the term nominate
I think probably because
It was
Matthew language
Yes it wasn't
This guy
Rhetorically in bed with the Muslims
The second thing is there was a shooter in
Who went on Facebook live
Send shot that old man
Yeah yeah it up a couple days later killing himself after he was on the Run
Boulders apartment tweeted out a picture
Headline news type thing
Haha
There was a cropped picture and it just showed Cleveland shooter at large considered armed and dangerous
And there was a silhouette
Picture like a like a random Place holder
Avatar image
Let me get this
Please
CNN
Doesn't have
To publish to let everybody know that it
The black man
You nailed it
Let me ask you one further question
Was this a
Totally accurate
And factual thing that
He tweeted out
No because the pictures it was photo
The picture was photoshopped
With the silhouette Avatar
Picture
And then
To the right of it
Is a picture of
He's old he is posting
Just completely inaccurate things in order to race Bay
Someone point
You didn't apologize
And when he was hosting the Alex Jones Show
Brought it up
Why won't see you then play that this guy is black
Possibly
So he has to know
Yeah
He knows
Absolutely
And then he still goes and f******
Says it in in a public sphere
People can hear him
Are already on edge
Hoping that
Somebody like that
Like
Kind of
And according to quadcast
The statistics are that almost
Old white men
And
I got some weird statista
Took the breakdown later so that I found
On this planet
It's going with this is kind of been up to
Huseman
Just watch
Be honest without the quick editing that he does
In his videos
He's not ready for Primetime baby
He is not good at that desk
Okay he's not there yet
Does he
Realize
So much on quick edit
That just having him
For 10 minutes
No personality
No
Give know it
Which is
F******
By the the he was on air with
What if Alex Jones
Yeah I still think Paul Joseph Watson
I think that's
I still think it's the end of info
Alex Jones
Is the cult leader
And when you take the cult leader down
The end of the
If you're not good
If you're not good about how you
You take down that colt
You have
Charismatic
Figure rise through the ranks
And take over
The leader dies
Yeah one else comes
Yeah but it's not generations of the Branch Davidians
That's out of Alex's at UVA
And then David koresh
Right leader comes
Please go off the rails
Suicide
So I think that
Alex does end up going down
And you end up with
A new leader ascending
You'll just you'll see it fell apart much quicker
But I still think
Google
Alex Jones has done a really good job of building up
Individual that fits their own demographic
Do you have Owen Shroyer
Kind of like a frat boy
Who's kind of like
Cool bro
Like he's 27 years old
He's kind of smarmy
Like a man
Play basketball
Then you got
Alright
When you get robbed
You got robbed 2
Coos
Huge nerds can identify with Rob do
And I'll kind of guy
Got that
You got
The f****** smoke shop of a lady
Superhot Lee Ann McAdoo
Fox News
She's not blonde
She's going to dirty brunette
Okay well there was strawberry brought blocked at least more diverse
Fox News
Slightly so then
You got Millie Weaver was kind of like a young sorority girls
Discovered that sort of demography
Sometimes clouds and rainbows match
Then you got
F****** you got
I don't know why you got Jon rappoport but you got them
David Knight for the old folks
People who are a little bit more night
You got
Jerome corsi for the race
You got Anthony cumia for the people who loves Opie and Anthony
You know
I'm against peace
How many people actually work
Missing people
It was just them everybody who has
Beard on screen
Also does double duty as like the boom operators out on the road
I've seen video of him holding up iPhone
Beautiful
He's basically made
Segments of
The youth population that are covered by
Each of his
Trying to hit all four quad right
Unfortunately all of his quadrants are old
So I'm confused as to why he thinks that
It's a good idea if he were to go down there is
Conceivable like all of them for like Voltron
Incapable
Unit
Cuz they all have their own little segments
Like
What's
Mark Wahlberg
Most
At the very beginning
Sutherland izan
And then Mark Wahlberg
No Donald
About
I don't know
My point is
The pjw
So we're not going to be talking about covering
W any further than we already have
Possibly
Against as lawyers wishes
Has been
Dispatching
From the road
As it were
I think he's shooting videos in the courthouse
Daybreak
God
Because there are
There are videos
That he's shooting in front of like what appears to be an in
Firewall of legal books
I would I would describe it
Good all these books
Match Lee looks like 1,000
Part encyclopedia
Like it's just going to all all the books are like
That's what it looks like
You cannot pull them out
I can't imagine that Ruby
You've been recording
North Korea is coming at all this
Talk about that
This week
Those like fighter
Buy boats
Future
Because of course not a national security
He's lying about things
Right
They should have seen that coming that's on them
You can't with with tropical don't even get fool me once quote the band
If you've already gotten
Dislike
It's all stupid
WeatherTech
Video that came out on Friday
What will be discussing
Aired on the Alex Jones Show up Paul Joseph Watson
This video came out on Thursday
And keep in mind
And on Thursday
Alex had put out
A statement
Please respect my privacy and my family's privacy I'm not going to be
The press that was on Thursday this videos on Friday
He is now talking
If you consider Infowars and pjw
So this video is
This video is ostensibly
About Bill O'Reilly
It really feels like he's working through some stuff
And he's using Bill O'Reilly as an
Excuse
Okay here's the introduction of the premise
Here we go
I haven't commented yet on Bill O'Reilly being let go from Fox
Stanford
I've been on the air
O'Reilly
Real really know which direction this is going to go
Cuz it sounds
Could be about
I love the mystery of it like
I'm legitimately
When I was listening to it I was like
Dammit I'm stymied
I don't know which way I should have
O'Reilly's
Shows like that
He's a complicated you're also I'd like to find out the Bill O'Reilly according to
IMDb never appeared on extra until 2015
So
I think what he meant was Inside Edition
Junk magazine shows
There
TV nonsense
At some point
Extra
Proto
Yes those are is too late for us today and we will leave
He's playing the recorder
Conveniently
Include the part where you start
Screaming obscenities
What is that mean it's clear that Bill O'Reilly isn't he doesn't understand
A sentence with
You understand
Okay
He was on TV in the 80s.
Proto Infowars
If it weren't for well
It was nice to Bill O'Reilly
But we all know that Alex
No matter what
To eat sold out
Like that
Still not sure without where the ball is going to break
I'm not
Although I will say that in this neck
The Alex doesn't reduce
It is a little bit on
So all deals
Oh no we're being unfair to the gyro cycle at 30 years old
For having a security team
New York actually
I mean there are plenty of instances you can find of Alex yelling at callers to
Text one
To Noah
Is this is this going to turn into Alex Jones criticizing Bill O'Reilly
Everything Alex Jones
I think he's working for me
He's looking at
His own future
Maybe if any continue if he has a future
Eventually we'll catch
Good. We don't meet
We should be covering stuff like
Like this coming out in
The court
Case
That if true
A real bad
Use it you think he laid a hand on your land
I don't know
There it is
This is why I wear this is why we're truly
Anyway
He's up there saying Bill O'Reilly
Security
Why two colors
Not true
No but I sounds like it's a very plausible
I didn't do that
Bucking stock
I don't know about that but probably I believe it
So why not why wouldn't he send a security detail to a random colors house
Media Matters they have
The audio of what Alex is talking about Bill O'Reilly show
Which I will play now
Hey Bill I appreciate you taking a call during the day I think Keith Overman shuvit
Diego Mike is
He's a guy on guy
We have your phone
So if you listening Mike we have your
And we're going to turn it over to Fox
And You Begin
Maybe Mike is from
Because we're not going to play around when you call Ashley's Gentleman Just so you know
We do have your phone
And if you say anything untoward obbs
Or anything like that
Fox Acura
Then we'll contact
Authorities
And
You will be
There
F*** are you talking about
Noticed that it just caught and let me know
What are you doing live radio
He said some
Yeah and they have that there because the SEC will find them
Swears on air
The Janet Jackson
Right it's always been
Have
Chops
Take them off the air and the square would never make it
Unless tons of people
And they would eat up to seven
As is
The problem with you or something like that
We don't know that
Right
The idea that
He's saying
I don't agree with your position I'm going to send security
To you
Is not fair we don't have enough information
He's having fun
Security call the local authorities
For somebody
Swearing at him
But that's that might not be the situation the guy might have said I'm going
Peculiar
That out
I don't know
Compelling
I don't know I don't know
Howard Stern been threatened
With death on air
I don't know I didn't really look
Discern
Broadcast radio Schofield
Exciting popular made a lot more money and had a lot more listeners
Cousin Alex Johnson
Isaac the radio Factor has been on for
Decade
Yeah
Also did we actually do a rundown of
Makes the most money
From radio and wasn't O'Reilly
Up there
A nose
He had a huge audience whenever he was on but yeah now it's
The two will get into the specifics
Six when he brings up another lie later but
It's interesting cuz at this point it is still he's painting this picture of like Wally the complex guy
Also just refuses to address the fact that he's getting fired
For sexually harassing
Tons of women
Oh yeah you wouldn't want to
You wouldn't
Look
Alex wouldn't want to put out there
That he's against
Dangerous
Position to take a nap
Yeah I think so
Clubwear
He's gets mad at Bill Riley can you say p**** on the radio
Like
Like if you
Called Alex
On the radio
He would probably
Hang up on you
What do you leave it in there
I don't know
He keeps them so much that he shouldn't so I don't know why only thing
That's the only thing I
I know
Donate to our patreon for my birthday present
Be able to get Alex Jones has karaoke anyway clips
Escape from the factory
Sexual problem
He says this
No
But it's not like get in
The fact that Bill O'Reilly says
Is great
Sure is it a research yourself conservative
Wind-up car
With a red Galore
Who does regular
Misused term
Yeah basically
Here is the
So Alec suspended narrative
Before
O'Reilly's
Used
Image of
I had his picture up there and then subtract
Could be availed
I like hey check this out
That's pretty funny
A timing thing
Because it didn't happen
Alex Alex plays
What he's talking about
What you just said
He plays the clip from The O'Reilly Factor
Sexual harassment
Sex crimes or pedophilia at all
Here listen
But Alex just
Just made that up in real time
Seargeoh
Psycho Killer
Well
Wait
Nothing
Things to do with
The fraud tax scam
Tea Party
Facebook censoring South
I had nothing to do the thing that Alex claims
You so mad about
Cuz I never looked into
I don't want to go
Dig through
F****** O'Reilly we should have known
He was like whatever you take antibiotics says Eli
Although that does sound
That does sound like some chips
O'Reilly
But it turns out it's just completely in Alex's head
It's just
You could make an argument
O'Reilly in that is a very complex
But very unlike O'Reilly
Like O'Reilly in
That they're both fun
Yep
Fortunate
Aunt
It is unfortunate
Is that like
We have a joke
That we're up against
But he is an idiot
Like if Joker was just really dumb and yelled a lot that's basically
In the Dark Knight all of those complicated plans are just like
Robin
What situation for a ride.
Cell rap
Crystal.
Up
Also he
Unfortunately
His report was doctored
Our listeners we like we don't have any of those
Tweeters
Things people do
Just hang the picture
I'm changing my birthday wish
Everyone Jon rappoport is Twitter handle is at John
Jon rappoport
Just ask him about the picture
Picture is
Where did the
In the middle
Cuz it's not what you would do with the picture you love
Complex
His second wife
Picture that she ever
As far as I can tell he's been married
For years and years
My friend
He goes on Skype
To see his other children
DeForest auto detailing
He tries to heal the babies
To get vaccines brainwashing
Not necessarily wrong on that one
Not necessarily right so this next trip we finally get into the fact that
Bill O'Reilly the sexual
Taking a little while but we're there
About me
And Rodger Ailes
So
I love that I love that
Rollaway bed
Course they
Of course
If I done that
The symbol of masculinity
Are you are you a cheerleader
As long as long as the girls have a
Spring in their step
Thank you Alex
August 5th
Clip of the episode finally getting into the fact that Bill O'Reilly is a sexual harasser
And that is
Episode
Alex then going on to muddy the waters
And claiming
That first of all
There's other people who are worse
You got it
Globalist
REM play
Global instalike
For Global
Yep this is
Before he gets to that
Install
Narrative
How to get to like
Really big like
Bill's bad but
What about these other play
The people play that is like
Biggest example is what about those emails
Obama
We can have that conversation
Not really going
You know like
Just saying
Absolutely
Is Bunker delivery tail lights
You better stop bombing those people cuz that's
Now
Did you know that when you was at the George soros-funded command bunker
If you make it
Two terms as president
I think and pick when and where you want to use
I think that's a good system
I think I think that's a nice reward that's a golden parachute
You know methadone
You got a weave someone off
You can't just have them come down
Just go from Bob and to not exactly you need to wind down
Anyway this is
What about it
Government
Roblox
So you shouldn't have said you agreed
Because first of all that's a clunky analogy
The Snowden scandal
Difference between the letter in the spirit of Elijah
Before
You know like
UK
Spirit
The letter of the law is a literal interpretation
Things like
Kids deals
The gum from the store you lock him up
The spirit of the laws
Figuring out what the laws are made for
What kind of behaviors they are there too
Create in the population
The things you do not like
To see if I'm not applying your legal strategy
To enforce those things
When you realize that locking up a kid
For stealing a piece of gum
Create more issues and the spirit of the law would say
No go with a warning
Well because that's not why
Your $0.45 piece
Is that how much gum cost
America gum game
Isabel
To the
To the corner store to get a piece of gum
Cup of coffee
Preferred nickel
You got to say
Play Genesis perilli go down there
Play some Missouri
Who cares
There's a place called arrowrock
It was like a fake old timey community that they take student
Do on field trips and stuff like that
General Store
Niger by like really old
Candy not like not like
Old fashioned types of candy
Yeah I really enjoyed it but
My point is
I like
I mean there are there is a problem with abusive children Hollywood clearly a there are stories that keep coming
Those doors
Others lives that have been ruined
Example
Over and over again
Conversation
We would very much like them to be prosecuted as well
But just because they're not
Computer does not mean that Bill O'Reilly then
Because we're apparently going from
From the bottom up
Is menopause
Finally got Bill O'Reilly out of there
I just wish you would f****** go to jail
Cuz this is
To do this thing where he's like
If every problem is installed why we solving one
Sort of a really
You can't get anything done
Actionable goal
We have to set plans that you can actually build tour
If you just
You're just going to
Be overwhelmed by the task in front of you
Smallest thing.
Get Bill O'Reilly f******
Fired from Fox News
So you can't hurt more people
It's really frustrating
I mean on the one level he's dumb
But on the other is actually advocating things that are
Just bad
Beyond
Not that they're not good ways to live
It just on wise
Goals and work towards them
Little Steps
That's the way to go anyway here's the clip where he starts to get into
Conspiracy
And it's
Good morning
Arthur episode
That's a dumb non word
Hear me out on this
This goes back to our third episode
The Secret of 2017
We what is it
We still don't know
The Secret of 27
19 is a lot of people are going to lose their
Alex crying about wanting to live in a farmhouse and all this s*** Megyn Kelly is awful
That was the secret 2017
Possibly have known how the first four months of this year we're going to shake out
I saw someone I remember it maybe was
I think I might have been like w kamau Bell
A list of people who gear is not going
Absolutely
Cheapest
And he missed the secret of 27 for someone who has so many high-level
Fake sources and what-have-you if they were real you would think he would see
Any of these blows coming before they
He is not
I think it's appropriate now for us to revisit equip that we played
In the secret of 27
19 episode
Relevant
About
Before we do
He was saying there the Megyn Kelly is a part of this
Patriot values
Like that
And it's worth noting that Megyn Kelly did do an interview this week
What you talked about Bill O'Reilly was part of the reason the
But you left Fox News
Damso was Rodger Ailes there was a taco
The conveyor
So you can't work in
If your woman
How much
Keep him off
Sandpoint
What is this
Like how the f*** did he
For millions of dollars over and over and over again
For the rest of his
I think that at this point is becoming a thing where he's like
Something years old I don't either
George W
One of them
I'd like a monster
If we're being
Real with it
Obama and Bill Clinton
Should too
Absolutely pretty much all of our presidents
Has been done. Okay
Killed
Revived
And then hung
Picture of the White House
Ended
Memory of the fact that he's talking
We celebrate Merkel had Hitler's put your up in the air
It's absolutely unacceptable
I don't know
We're all going crazy
Make America gems
So close to America if everybody donates
Patreon
And I I don't know if I said it on the show
We will record at least
One audio commentary
For one of Alex Jones movie
We will do that
I'm willing to do it
We're going to do what we're going to do a full mst3k
Alex Jones and a new series of mst3k
Chicago public
TV show
Where is faith
We could afford that
Content
I feel like I'm saying that too much
Contacts
Yeah because now I'm saying we'll make me
F*** off to you
But mostly I was thinking to myself anyway
In honor of this
Bringing back up Megyn Kelly
I want to replay this because
It's horrible
It's fun now in the context that we know the part of
The reason that she left
Sexual harassment environment
And people are going down for it
And this
Is how Alex Jones back
Beginning of 2017
It is video 2017
Spoke about
Can Kelly
Houston
You look at
She's a woman
Megyn Kelly
Cheerleader
Who looked okay
Which I forgot about
Fall he is
She's wanted to go jump remember that way
Ship
Because she feels weird
After bite
Sly
This is just her thinking oh my God I'm hated Fox
NBC
Cuz those failures
Swindle into joining
And now that we know that his
Code is vampire mates pedophile
Pedophile
She left because of a
Horrible chauvinistic environment
Responses
Critique her attractive
Insist
He's told friend
But you think she's ugly
This is horrible
That's the only reason women do things right
Usable level
Ugly mammal
Ugly mailman
So disgusting
Yeah
All men should just be we have we have genetic research
We can clone
We cannot let you know
Feel bunch of sperm and then get rid of it
I got plenty
Just f****** tear them down if there's one thing I know about man it's that they're not
So thrilled to hold onto those you get rid of
Rubbing one out
Straight into the
Absolutely
Okay
I'm not saying
This is a great
I'm just blue skies
How do you want to kill
Everybody has their own preference
Sure
Cool app
Kind of indicative of how at this point
It's not really clear what he thinks
About the Bill O'Reilly situation
He has acknowledged
Then he's a sexual harassing person Hollywood
All of Hollywood
Whatever
I meant actually what's going on is it wasn't so much about the
Sexually harass people
He was a patriot
There's a purge going on
Who is so unclear what is a year at Fox News
For 12 hours
Get rid of old white
They just run around all day
Hit the Patriots
And that includes the football
They may be there they may not be there
Yep
I would also assume that
Here's a clip
I want to see
Two things that I haven't pointed out
This is straight through
The eclipse are jumped segment
Just chop his entire thing
Everything out
Recording
As he drives
The court
This is in his car
This is what he thinks about on the way to
Yeah absolutely go to send my right to have my kids
I got a
Can talk about Bill O'Reilly
For 15 minutes to make sure that everybody knows Bill O'Reilly is not that bad
I don't know
No I don't know
I mean
We even actually said that
What Bill O'Reilly did
Somewhere in like
Media mattress
I think that
He thinks
All he did was
Trying you this position
To get women to have sex
As opposed to
Right
Turn off on its own Alex's dealing with the fact that some women probably
Corner
Broke
I would I think that those are things that
Most likely happen
He used demeaning language
Sexualized
Professional
It's called that one lady hot chocolate
A black lady
The Worksource
Oh boy
He's minimize
Icing for sure
But I think the
Still implying that his behavior was
Yeah
But anyway this is just like
York
They paid out like 25 million
20 million in
Sexual harass
25 million
Rodger Ailes got some huge
The number to like
They paid Rodger Ailes and
Is Bill O'Reilly mortal
They paid the women
It's in their contract like there's there's not much
That they can do about it
Contract why do you have
Here's your money comes back to them being really marketable Stars
Good executive
In terms of getting the
Getting high rating
And Bill O'Reilly
With Bill O'Reilly and fox
I want
1 claws
Bill O'Reilly in the
Desiree
I'll take I'll take
2 million
As long as I get to put a toe
Right through his balls
Do you get a running start stationary
Okay
This clip is Alex not really knowing what side he
It's it's
It's bizarre
Real Steel
Resent
Red
Via killie's heel
Sexually aroused
Right right
Invisible to all their racism and their f***
King liar sir
Shoot that arrow in
To their sexual harassment
They have to fight against feminists
PC culture
Is because
You know all those people would go away
Then that Achilles heel would never be at
I love
It's f****** argh
If they can take down those guys
Then hate Vicky
Which is basically saying like
Harass
There's a world
Gets that suppress
Can't sexually harass people
Ouroboros solid
Exist until like 30
Mercury in this clip
You nailed some of them
Really really dumb
To tie himself
Like because
The issue
The issue is the Bill O'Reilly and Rodger Ailes
Intimately and literally committed crime
But he think
And it's the globalist
And I know you got more to saying you're going to kick ass and putting my hand I love you
Philly rant
Crime
Yeah buddy
Timer
The globalist
O'Reilly's got in trouble in the past before
Audio came out of him like talking about a lady in a falafel
But
Nothing happened
Two people in the past what it happened was sponsors weren't willing to pull
It got to a point where they could no longer
We can be a
Get tied in with
Real-time sponsors
Kept falling off
Any ended up ending his show like
15 minutes early one day because it had no content to fill it and no ads
Shepard Smith
Live in the other serious
Yeah it's crazy
Which is
Paper
Tying in his fate
Because what's going on is a crime is being punished
It's not free speech being
And if he ties himself
And with this
Unfortunately
The metaphor in the analogy is that what
He is on trial for his a crime
And it's not
Is the custody
And
The more he releases videos like this
Spending sexual harassment
Almost seems like you subconsciously want
Toulouse cost
Oh man
How big can of worms
Also sort of by proxy arguing that you're saying
The timing
Of this Bill O'Reilly
Yes
Intentional and the people are trying to
Destroy him
Yeah
Don't
Destroy them too I don't know this is very murky territory
The Secret of 2017
Is
Who turned in the trailer
Uno
Common real
Is it going to be is that again
Christie novel everyone did it everyone is
Alex
Juicy islamophobia
Take note 6
I bow down to Alex
In this clip
O'Reilly down
What happened
Weather in England
Doesn't
It is
Is the feminist slogan like
Let's bring those call hijabs back to Pennsylvania that we were talking about what's going on here
Party
Love is
It comes out almost like a Dennis Miller
Like
Alright man
I know that there are
Terrorist event
There are things that he is correct
It is not a
But government and CIA and all of those Buckhead
Have back
Manny
Terrorist organizations they
They've done all of this s*** like
Rim thing is us
Rehab
Let's take a step back
What's the address
Where the LIE is Alex's truth
Because these things are true
But the light comes
From the fact
Implying
Fayetteville
Parts of the government
George W bush would be included
Anybody who's
Implication
Is that they're backing these terror group
For their terrorism
They're selling children into slavery
When in reality often time
It's proxy wars that don't go well
And you need somebody
To fight as opposed to us because if we fought there it would trigger
So you have
No but it's not what Alex's describe
Also and then again
He does that say
Before
Where he staying in
They care about women
It is that
Lifetime to get
I'm out of here
Which has that same ring of
Well
Because they don't all women traffic
Then it doesn't
Then
They don't care about the the certain problem
Just because you don't solve everything doesn't mean
You can't solve 1
What
You know I'm not a
Foreign policy and War historian or anything like that
At least two stomachs
Groups
Turn back in the future
Did helping
Present
Like there were strategic goals that we were trying to achieve
Them with the help of
Say Al-Qaeda back
They were
They turned out terribly
Fighting
Help
I'm so it is
Sword of Justice
The rest
Yeah
That doesn't make it right
Is far more complicated than Alex
Texas pitching in order
American Gothic
So bizarre.
Bill O'Reilly
Did sexually harassed
And then
Atlee
What
This
Is very weird
Blankets
Such a tangential thought
It's it's
It's mental illness
Demonstrative
It's an inability to track slot A to B to C
Basically
There
Internal
Get back
On the subject
So-so nenen this is
Another one of those things that we talked about
Is waste
Later time he gets into an area where
He doesn't know quite
What's his
What is a narrative
Yes Alex Jones asked
Themselves that you think you sort of lost track of his persona
Those like little spots
Given that recharge
O'Reilly
Because
Clip ended with him saying
Bill O'Reilly
That's kind of up and down on those
About that
That his listeners if he
If he really just said
Hey
We don't like Bill O'Reilly
Because you sexually harasses
Phoenix
He's going to get angry
Sure sure
Bill O'Reilly
Should be allowed to sexually harass people
Is just a free-speech issue
That's what it was really bored
We can make our position very clear
Hate Bill O'Reilly
For his behavior
It's not like some
Capitalism
So
Is how he can talk about that
Which allows him to address
Supposed to address
And then in order to
Kind of avoid action
Position right
He switches back into islamophobia
So I mean if you are taking him
I'm assuming.
They think
He agrees with whatever it is
On Bill O'Reilly
Nation of it
You know either it is
If either it's mental illness
It coming
Combination of both
Or it's just a coincidence that he's a lunatic in people believe
I think he's been playing the role of a cornered animal for like 20 years
That's true
On the defense
Yeah
Damn
Now he's back in
Familiar territory
So this next clip he explained
What Bill O'Reilly's biggest mistake was and let me say this
It's not what you think
It's not sexual harassment never got it
He could at least
It's not it's not
Bill O'Reilly is biggest mistakes
Completely
Republican Party
Absolutely Independent Media
Time for us to address this a little bit
We have a
Agreement with Alex
The most
Of the mainstream media's bulshit
You know like
It's fine
Believe that and not agree
You're not like I don't think necessarily the tienen does a good job I don't think Fox News does a great job
They actually have better
Journalistic standards
So they have a better job blog
Or Infowars
But they aren't like
They're not holy
There's no reason there's no reason to implicitly Trust
Something just because it came out on Sienna and it was with the level of betrayal ved's
They have like
One of the things that I I refuse to
2 ever
Forgive them for is
Adjusting themselves
To make every
Sing a horse race
So many billions of dollars
So much time
Tearing Hillary
In order to make
Get them rated
Everybody's is closer than you think
Who knows who's ahead in the polls this day
By giving him so much
Attention because
He's a he's a great
Then
F****** they were apps
Absolutely complicit in his win total
F****** cheered for the Iraq War
They did more to get Trump elected
Main reason
Alaska
Even out.
The other the other problem is that a lot of the mainstream media in Alex
Are we engaged
In the game of war profit
More money off of
Tricking people into thinking
I mean we do think that the world is about to end
But they also
Make money off of that
We just privately are afraid that that's the case
We fear for life not enough for bottom
So this next clip
Shooting what his lawyers
Maybe arguing
Performance artist
Character
Probably shouldn't be saying publicly
He wants to make the point
That he is
Super f****** real
And he juxtaposes that to a list
Which is delightful
Goddamn
He gets in
A Scanner Darkly
Play a little bit
Because he was
He was in that movie
You don't give a shout out to my husband
Intense thoughts about it they will get to come back
Mendelson author wi British
First of all rehab
Bizarre slave
Reprogramming Center
Not certainly not
Helping people overcome
Genetic
Addiction
But
I like everyday
In trial the
Could just show the clip that he made that much
Yeah
Remember trawood
Washington
Not
Another day
The other thing I want to talk about Philip
First of all I love
Become a big fan of his in the last
Few years
Read a lot of his books
It's important to recognize
For the speed attic
He basically wrote these books and almost
The Fugue state
He would just binge on speed
Because
He was married
He needed to
Support his family and he got paid by the word
So a lot of the stuff you wrote was utter garbage
Stuff it's really great
I think there's a parallel
Alex
Okay but it's probably the super male vitality
Or brainforce
These things
Hood Beats
Maybe
Good thing that I want to take issue with
Is the government drugging people
These drugs
Pacifier or whatever
Sportage
Destroy the
A Scanner Darkly isn't the vet
Infants that he could
Could go with it really shows
He is a good book and
The drug aspect of it is really into
Interesting
I would have gone with the three Stigmata of Palmer Eldritch
Which isn't much better book of his
Of course it has
Better book that has to do with
Drugs
Basically there are there's a drug
Choosy
That is
Will people ever want the entire world is on
Thomas drug
It's because
Everyone's lives are terrible
And that you're able to escape into a Fanta
SeaWorld drug
And tries to take over the
The game
Okay
But
Alex please read the three Stigmata of Palmer Eldritch also have gone with that's a salad addiction
Frank Herbert
How do that means better than lkj
Say it again
Throughout silkie dicks work that he sort of trying to
To deal with his
Through his narrative
Like there are a lot of
Drugs
That's why throughout his story isn't
Alex is dumb
That's my boy that's when there's someone that I really like and someone who I really
Is misrepresenting them coming
Advise on the phone
Yeah right
A liquidator
Hello
I like your style
Expressions
Gianni's career took off I advised that I'm in 440 seconds
Alright
No way
Advisor on the movie
He knows plenty
Roar
I know that it sounds like a real
Stewart Title but it's one of his biggest book
I just never heard of
You're not a PK.
I'm doubtful you know me
Anyway
This next Club
We're done with felt
I know I know
The sadness
Listen your voice I've never lost interest in the rest of the show up there for a minute
Now I'm just waiting for the brink of love
Actually I forgot
Outer space
Betty White
This next clip
Is just more about Bill O'Reilly being a sell-out
Never sell
Ever ever
Ever
Lady starts quoting Mark Twain
Orioles bird
Halfway Around the World
Hawaii
Closer than
Dlisted
Revel when we talked about originally
Off the Google search engine
The fact that he saying now that they
Closer
To what it really
It was in a day or two he's already changed the narrative on what we're seeing in real time
These
Just become one of his waypoints
Is opposed to the main story
On the last
Episode
.
Contractors
To download anything
Only Google itself
Can do that
Is fill out report
Of what they found on their searches
Information is used by Google
All this stuff
Downvote
It can't be true
Can't do that
It's very bizarre but also
I have another Mark Twain quote
Alex Jones that was from the outage
What is
Get your facts first
And then you can distort them as much as you please
Similar
Skip the first part about getting it the first one
The world before the truth can get it
That's how you have a job
Yeah the only reason you have a job is because Ally is so easy to transfer
Richard
Within that same couple of sentences he gets into the Google stuff
The same thing you're saying now with Louise Mensch
And that's that horrible
Yeah
F****** which
But she's going on
Too much
The whole other thing
Misusing these quotes
Is just so Alex
It's so Alex at the light
Bizarre
Anyway
Any fact that most of those up
Reply to him
Direct
Sitting here like Athena
Whispering
Thanks
Excellent
Alex Jones
Winston Churchill
Bill O'Reilly
Sometime it doesn't go far enough
It's very bizarre so here we go
Never Surrender
Those goals are pretty good but also I think it was more of them
Michael Caine impression
Wasn't
If all Alex was about was defending art
In literature and defending
Repression of religion
I'm pretty sure that's what he does I would I would not have a problem with it earlier in the episode
Skull covered in
Million dollars
The more you want that I just want to
Gross
Just want to touch it one
Okay
Demon covered diamonds
Letsjerk
Based on your goals
I'm not going to not touch it if somebody brings the disease.
Progressive near me
Okay so in the neck
Calendar year I'm going
To strive to live
Embodying Sasha Banks theme song
Are you going to find a diamond encrusted
Try and touch the sculpture
We have very different colors
He's going to get into Bel Air
He's getting back
Call Billy
Thug
Seems to be what this is more about
He doesn't give a f*** actually was harming women
He was creating a threatening and hostile work environment for these women's based
Denver women that he wanted
Dafuq
Bill O'Reilly
He played that clip
Anything to do
Celia or online Predators or anything like that
What a
Well admittedly Bella Riley
Isabel
He is a thug sure I don't know what that means in this context
I don't know but you know it's Rachel.
Actually believe
Bill O'Reilly
In the term of like
Hired Hand
Organized crime
Then
Racketeering
What is Utah
Alex's
About Rush Limbaugh and Bill O'Reilly
Great we get to we get to the
Trifecta of monstrous right-wing propaganda
Talking about Rush
But
Snopes
Horrifying monster Rush Limbaugh
Parents against
Rush Limbaugh
The man who finally made me
Acknowledge that
My parents
Easily influenced by the scaremongering old ugly
Yeah I do mean ugly
I bought it
As the sole
Of Rush Limbaugh
Will take some solace in knowing that in this Cliff Alex
Going to talk him out pretty good
Lincoln Lawyer bunch about the
Audience
Kenmore Liquors in Hueytown
Who's the biggest
No you're under attack in the media because you're engaged in a very ugly custody battle that it proven YouTube
But
Rush Limbaugh
Has 30
18.5 million weekly
To his show
And that is not the number one show on terrestrial radio
NPR Morning Edition
Considered both have over 14 million listeners
Every week
The right after that
Is Sean Hannity
5 million a week
He brought up George Noory that's Coast to Coast
That's only 2.75 million a week
Numbers are f****** stupid and way off
Savage Nation is down there at 5.2
25 million
That's beat by Glenn Beck he didn't want to bring that up
Egypt different numbers
Do you think the people who cares why here's my guess
That's a great question
Is
There are underlings
And they just
Like they just give him a
Spreadsheet
With A-1 and then a lot of zeros after it
Say this is how many
Listening
Congratulations
Possibly
I found out
Statistics amor
Cuz I wanted to know more
Pacific's
Some things that I'm not thrilled
Oh no
One of the things I learned
Is that
Percentage-wise of his audience
Chicago is the biggest
Best city in the world 1.22% of his audience
Chicago
Into you
Only person
I'm listening
That might be what these cats are
I might be skewered
It's you and then you have
Registration
So it's those two
It might be at
An interesting Issaquah cast has a
Affinity
Explanation
This is a comparison of the audience composition of this property in this case property means infowars.com
Or audience segments
Composition of Infowars
5 to the internet
Population
At Large
The higher the Affinity number is
The more concentrated
Are particular geographic area
Multiplier of time
For San Francisco that means that given visitor is 10 times more likely to be from
Francisco has any internet user chosen at random
Okay
An affinity of 5 *
So I looked at the statistics
I want something
Cousin
State
The Affinity ranking is 1.98
Twice as likely as a random internet user to Via United
That makes
You know it doesn't
Make sense America is not the top
Who is the top one
Number two
The Cayman Islands
3 *
Affinity rate
I
Don't
Understand
I don't either I don't know where the Cayman Island
Car payment
The not very big
Right area
What's important I think
Then
It's a tax shelter
So maybe
No
Ears
Number one
Syria
No s***
Syria has an eight
.5 time
I'm guessing.
Probably more recent
It's just
The current
I'm not sure what time frame is covered
Syria is then
Like
Reading those counter-narrative
That's what's going on with that
Because he
I'm guessing they read all of the
Syria wasn't really
Responsible
For all of this
More likely to watch
Another
I'm not going to say that Syria is just all Rubble everywhere
To Reliable internet
And or maybe reading
News
On the internet are not necessarily
Do random civilians
Those are the people who are
That could just be a sod
Just like I am Chicago that could all be him
Cayman Islands
But if you look at the numbers
People
We were listening
In Syria it's not very high
Considerate
Compared to other
Yet their Affinity rate
Being used for this
Because that seems to imply that
People like it
Yeah but that's it you're much more likely then.
Sitting that website
To my life pretty consistently that I don't like
The hatred
Funny
Fair enough
Super Bazaar also I checked
Ratings
Traffic news website
In the last week has gone up at all
So the even disc
Stuff isn't really doing
We're just reading other people's tweets
Yeah well and I would assume that really at
It kind of feels like he is reach
His saturation
Like he's got everybody here
He's going to get
That's what his audience is
The people that
The people that are going to be there for
And he's not going to gain or lose
He's just right
Point where everybody
Would be listening to Alex Jones
Is listening to Alex
Also I just checked our Twitter we got a hot tip for our next episode check out that thing
Thanks for the
Thanks for the heads up we'll see if it's we're going to do James
Yeah just constantly
Cuidados live because maybe were record
We were going to get to work
And for the rest of this week
He's recording from his car
And what have you
Still a f***
Looking businessman
Driving
Need a drink
Okay
Picture of Alec
On screen
Wow you
This audio play it
Man dude
Yeah
Easter sale still on
Still on
Easter sale for Lent
Tomorrow it won't be tomorrow
It's this thing called fear of loss of game
We're going to put that these are selling
Fastly
Wouldn't
Handle
They're just selling to
Do fast we've got to put a
Set a timer on the hour
The 2nd
Artificial scarcity
Yes that is we're going to run out of this thing and you're not going to be able to get it
That motivate
Some people who are afraid
They're not going to get the sea
Is what people have
That's like all the sale is going to stop
Atmore
I am
You know you come to realize that's sale never ends
It's always
But if you pretend you're going to end it
People don't call you on it
Wee-Man
I mean
Kohl's the store with a bar here in Chicago
Why are they
Probably I would hope so
No it's let you go and you go into a
Clothing stores like hey these are 50
Percent off
Constantly going out of business
The mattress store that's over by the Target here in Chicago has been going out of business
6 years
Yeah
Stamps
The scam
Alex
In the first clip
He's doing his plug
I would describe this is Victor
Victim
Infowars.com
OK Google
Royale
Cut off.
But there's also like
Because O'Reilly got his
Advertisers pulled because they had a crisis of conscience
Support someone who is a sexual harasser in a stereo
Prompto the crisis of conscience
Play some Ciara.
Being like they're pulling our sponsors
Is like
Are you saying you committed a crime
It's happening
You're Alex you got it
You got a drool taken away
Because you violated their terms
The service
That's not a crime what he's
This is happening
Because
A lot of s***
Has gone specs
Tacular libads
Totally
It is
Florida that's connected to him being a propagandist liar
Well I don't think I don't think
I don't think as much of that bad stuff is
It's all connected to
Mistakes he's made
For twenty years
It's the chickens Roost
Has word come home
It is connected
To his custom
The hearing which isn't connected to
Google
Accurately recognizing
Constantly debunked
And so.
Currently recognizing
Debunked
Which is connected to the globalist
Exactly
If you want to say you have journalistic integrity
Fire Jerome corsi
That guy is the worst
I don't that's Rapaport
Tell Rappaport to hang up a Transit
You know the guy
Also I actually want to do
If there was
Skype interview
Where Alex is just like
Hey this is a professional operation
You look like shity song
II
I want to do
An episode sometime in the future about how
It's become very
Clear to me
That John Rapaport when he does his reports is
Is using sort of a hypnotic suggestion
Techniques
He's using the way he speaks is very
Intentionally bike
Hypnotic
I've noticed a couple things that he does
That are like
Is not a mistake you're doing this on purpose
Are people aren't paying attention
It would be very easy
Need to get lulled into like a
Oh yeah
Becoming
I also want to do a special report about how
I realized
The Alex Jones's career
Very closely mirrors that of the rap
A group of Jedi Mind
I've got these in the world
And if you'd like
Come to fruition
We're in the middle of his login
I don't know
Your your birthday
One day a year
Pennywise
Just like The Purge over it
Once again all visits to our website
I would also like to say
Easter sale that he was promoting like his commercial was like
I am going to
The global it by having a Christian holiday
Sale were celebrating a Christian holiday
Yeah nothing
Nothing says celebrating the Christian holiday
Blatant capital
Yeah but I think he was a
Expecting people to get mad
Or something like that
Starbucks
Expected for War on Christmas coming out of it
Hairdos so pathetic
How's your f******
Do your f****** thing sell your bone saw
Here
To be a little more accurate
Put in water
Make your bone saw
Wow
Chocolate and Millie Weaver
Intuit
Zeigler
That
What
Millie Weaver likes
Chicken taste like chocolate
To the squeamish either and
And she's like I don't think I would have wanted
To eat bone broth
Chocolate
What's the weather in
Basic also I learned
That Rob do and Owen Shroyer
Together
I'm starting to bark
The play basketball so
He take some of that bone broth
Things cool
Why are you sure
Because again
What every time we do the show I live in a worse world
You're destroying my views
I think a bigger issue drink phones
Because sometimes my knee
Thank you
Bones are also what kind of competition
You're getting out of Rob do out there on the court
Please
Alex Jones
Real thin ice
With this plug
Because he is
Reference
Sing somebody
That
You just don't talk about
Dude
Chill
Chill out
Alright Is It Michael Jackson
So here we go
Please deportes.com
Knockout formula
All superstars together
And then everything else
Absolutely
Don't know if your lawyer
His lawyer
Loves his
F****** cauldron With Every Witch Way
Worm root
All of these different
Boiled in there
Bishop
Is amazing
My impression of his lawyer how I think it went
Trying to just avoid the question I imagine
Don't do it
It would have been awesome to
To find out that his lawyer was in the car with him the whole time
Knockouts
Anyways we got to get to the court or the flip side
The ingredients
And knockout
No difference
Troubles
Explored a lot of product
F****** Walgreens have you tried
I haven't cuz I'll never give him any money
It has no different ingredients really than most
Over-the-counter
Herbal
Remedies
And
They're not 50.
What are they
They're about
Maybe time
About the same
Is $30
Nothing is actually Morris
Source
These himself
He had the brilliant idea
What if
Threw a bunch of s***
Is it a pill
Okay
So what if
My bone broth what if I grind up a bunch of bone broth
And put it into a pill
Sure
Now I got to work with people too
Find all of these ingredients
Right
Spells
Put different you know he's already talked to the fact that his super Bluetooth
Just Tom's of Maine toothpaste with a couple of greedy
Stuff so I wouldn't I wouldn't be surprised if
Some
You know Nature's Best
Eric brand
Like
NyQuil
It just doesn't have the
The same
Yeah exactly Dawson has like some of these
Slavery
It is insane.
Placebo effect
The point where you
Work better
Happens to me every time in the store
Every single time like I'm not getting
This is obvious
Human brain
Mentally stupid
That's what we're learning
Altro
And it gets well
He's turned off
I don't know why he had to make sure that this video
Are elected audio-video as long as his Drive
I don't know why that's okay
The long drive
Yeah so you know his Drive is over
He's gotten to court
And
Dismount
Is clunky
Very.
Call
Thunder
Nachos
Great job
So that's the end of it
If you go by the end of Revelation
He technically just blasphemy
The final commandment at the end of Revelation 2
You can't add anything or take away anything
Sing from the Bible
Committed a great heresy
Which is
Cool I mean that's what you'd want to do if you were building a system
Nothing else
So
5 paraphrasing
The Bible like that
Sort of
He's exploiting it in order to build up his own persecution
He's just added
Context to the Bible
That's it like that.
Absolutely
Yeah
We have the Bible is problematic
Roast
Define versus
The stuff in it
At the end
I love you all I look
Forgot
Yeah I remember that for my church days
I definitely remember people saying that
Metaphorical
A metaphor
Like a rock face of the cliff
It's a good face
Dammit I still haven't seen the fasting
Furious
Let's go now now
And I want to take a moment to reflect a tiny bit I really don't think that we got a concise
Assessment
I really don't think that he made any point other than to muddy the waters and save it what this really is about is the
The globalists trying to take him down
Yeah but he
He got the opportunity to
Puffs his chest out at Bill O'Reilly
Talk to my
And there's also a little bit of
Patty like a Bill O'Reilly baby
Stickin around
Do you know what you're famous for
One Clip where you said
The f word. Bill O'Reilly
Don't disagree with Alex entirely on that
Gets to throw in some islamophobia witch
Stock and trade
Especially now that
We're seeing all of these tensions arise
With people who aren't Islamic
He has to get that narrative
Distract away from
And then what you said some full-on bulshit there
Megyn Kelly
Kelly
Superman Kelly leave Megyn Kelly alone
Leave her alone do a Chris Crocker Style video crying
It right there she created knockout absolutely
Get to die
It was my idea
My dear was throw bunch of s*** together whataboutism with liberals
Pedophiles
Conversation we are always under
But
Throughout it all
Most
Is he has a full-on understanding Phillips
But he is a f******
Policy wonk
He's really getting down to the
Like the substance
Of what's going on here
Like he's really in the Weeds about this Bill O'Reilly
He's got a
He has which one
Bill O'Reilly the Frog
There you go
Fine Nails 15 minutes
Coulda said that
Sucks anyways
Pjw instead in the studio
You Alex good luck in court this week Alex
I know it's a
It's going to be all week
I'm not looking forward to seeing hot take
Nobody reminded me
F****** tweeting at me all these updates
No I'm watching I see all of it
Like I said
It is this fine line we walk
I sincerely hope that
Well
The way
Any custody battle with whatever's best for the f***
Kids which apparently nobody
Lettuce
Thought the knowledge fight with a couple of new pieces up there
A new entry in the Life I'll be in the Alex Jones biography
Biography
Wearing clothes
We're almost done
Well six-year-old kicked off his mom's me
That is a full picture we've already
Please
Refining us however
Find us on Twitter with just crossed the 100 Twitter followers
Barrier in the big leagues now
Yeah he's not going to give it to Julian Assange
You should give it to us give us his blue check mark
You said that already
What else
What else I think
What else is you
Let me ask you a question
If you are a type
What type would you
Bone broth walk
No I'm apology log
Your
Holding
Alexandra first in color