Alexandra First Time coloring
Flex fit round
Alex Jones
I think everybody's clamoring for plant
Play watch
July 11th
12 stands
Whatever day it is today
Beautiful holding
Right now little bit of a holding pattern of peppers are coming in well
But Notre fruit and yet there's a
You know we got the
Serrano's
They've come
You can see them there by their over a foot tall
Fruiting
We'll see what happens there
I don't know I think probably by now this is my first rodeo with having a bunch
The plants I'm not entirely sure
Ground pepper
Trinidad scorpion
Chocolate bhutlah
I thought that I messed everything up
But so they're coming in nice they're still there still probably in the
6 in height range
Maybe just don't
Rub your eyes
Right right right
That's the same thing with like jalapeno
Gnu rubberized
It's going to hurt but I mean
It's a scale of how much is
Glove to plant
Yes.
I didn't mess up
Finley planting stages
I think I was the Scorpio
Really
I didn't want from touching
It was from touching the package the seat came in
Someone had handled the thieves as in Trussville
So good
All red I touch this and it hurts so bad I need to find a way
I got this scorpion this scorpion hot sauce like 4 days ago
You can see Jordan holy quarters gone
Yeah it's great
Like putting hot.
I like
Oh God there's a lot of
Certainly a sort of
I don't know anything about
The year of the
2013 investigation of how
Uncovered
Fallout
Everything else around that they were going over
1st and 22nd
I'll tell you what
February 22nd
Is a bit of
It's going to take guns away from
Veteran
Pretty much the entire show
It is
Not worth it
I just tons
Tons of stuff
Things we've already gone over it so just be
Rote repetition of this isn't true
This is nonsense
We said that before we have
But first there's a bit more meat on their bones
And so we shall go over it but first
I'm taking moment to say thank you to people who supported the show
We really appreciate it
So first of all
You are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk drama
Tyler
Next
Boxcar Willie Nelson
Journal policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much you are now about to walk
I'm a policy wonk I'm almost certain I mispronounce that and I apologize
It also makes me think of the great Blood Sweat
Beer song Luke
That's probably much closer pronunciation
But I will say that Lucretia Mac evil is a great song
Boo-boo boo-boo boo-boo boo-boo
Dog portraits
Donated an elevated level we appreciate it very much
You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Capital of Saskatchewan
Drive from like weed
Right
Do you do that
Sports sure we would appreciate it please do
I started listening
To this episode
Me to no end
Now
Very exciting it is hot out
Yes it was finally hit summer in Chicago and it is ice cream weather
That is not what he
Looking back at digging into past episodes of Alex
What's the show
Exactly what you wanted
He doesn't follow through
But it's the sort of thing you really get excited to hear
That's really sad
That is so exciting
Because he is
In this late February stretch of time like he is kind of in a holding pattern
He's
Kind of got about all he can out of the Piers Morgan
He's got this double
W e Meredith
Swagger going but it doesn't
You can almost get a sense that he doesn't even feel like this is
Like really going to do that much for him
From listening to this episode
I could get a sense
But he realizes they're more interested in Glen back also
I think that he does feel like
I got to do something
We're going to write I got to mix it up
Yeah yeah I like that I like that
He's been the same boring unrequited love
Can I get there to go back to his old
Really rekindle the flame there like maybe try a little bondage
Little light Blythe
A baby I think
Wacky sidekick would do it okay well there's a lot of options
Read
I don't think it would help
Sound effect board
Kazoo noises
That would be great because we was Layla drop
Air horn
I would love it
Doesn't really follow
At least not in the 21st and 22nd that I've Listen to I see no evidence
I'm shaking anything up
It is
Very similar
Broadcast
An extension of him
What kind of in a rut
A good amount of self-awareness
Usually pretty abs
But he makes a couple of really valid complaints about himself
In this next clip
Frustration
To try to transmit to you
In the first hour is generally the best hour
And so I must
Absolutely
Swear I'm in control
I don't believe him about reading 100 articles in preparation for the show or anything like that
Those criticisms of himself are quite valid the first hour
Saying nothing in Treading Water by the third hour
I never go to Carl's when I say I'm going to go to college
I say I'm going to cover something later and then I just start rambling about it never really cover it
Is a Hallmark of your show
Feature not a bug
That's how you get away with not covering things
This is a very weird to
This is where I brought him in for a performance review
HR backgrounds
Maybe that's why his
You told Allie take more calls
You don't know what it is
The moment of introspection here that I may find very uncharacteristic of him
Scaled-down
Sometimes
But this this level of opening the show
We need to mix it up I'm
Ready not good after an hour
A lot of the time
So I overcompensate by having gas
I never cover news and I don't take calls
We are in a 13 Going on 30
He and Rex swap telling the truth through Alex's
And then
For some reason they probably stepped on the
The same Lucky Penny but
Okay
Is b******* it's possible
Siri
I have other theories
Better much less Pacific
He's not feeling great realize it's a bad job he's doing that
Seems more like a psychology
Restart
He says a couple of really
F****** weird things on this episode of
When he's being more critical and more self-aware
These sorts of ideas come to
To the surface
Now we've already heard him say that you got to give it up to the
The Somali pirate
Which was groundbreaking
Somali pirates
There's another group
You've got to hand it to the globalist
That's weird
He's not done he has more thoughts to expound on here but
It's always
Last breath
Was important experience at death
Life is very fragile
To quote Shakespeare
Said this before I'll say it again
It would
And the stupid
But you are targeting
Beautiful
That is just beyond
Beyond
Okay
But you got to give it up
It does a pretty good job to how epic it is
I mean it's hard to
Taken outside of any
Contacts
I don't know how terrible that is
Because you know you
He's expressing like okay so a parasitic
System
That kills its host
It would think that it was
Purses from the house
To survive
But in doing so it leads to its own
Describe colonialism
I don't know how far off he is
In terms of just
Sayings
But you can
Take that outside the context
Text
When so much of his fear in so much of his rhetoric is about there being like
A plant
To destroy White
Or a plant
To get rid of the middle class
What you very clearly
Expresses
Mostly White
They're all this is an attack on
The gun Community the Patriots
You can't hear him say stuff like
You are attacking the beautiful and the intelligent
Without thinking
You're speaking in code a little bit year
If you were just dealing with the people I don't like
You are dealing with the people who are similar to me
And a Target exam with your eugenics
Nougat
I do feel like that
Part of what
Expressing their
Taken in the context of his work
Noah
Because he is being
Perspective
Self reflect
At the same time
Globalist
AR apps
Absolutely
Yeah
Screws is my head because it's like
Do you really believe all this b*******
You can't you can't ever took your hand
Has gone if you
Indicate that like you have any doubt of your worlds
He doesn't have
Well I think
I don't know I don't know I'm not as troubled by but I see what you're saying
I think there's a
Self-critical in
Introspective Alex
Is also
Expressed
By virtue of his interaction
With collar
This guy calls in
Want to talk chemtrails
Prove
All the arguments Back Down trailer
This guy is
Is pretty amazed
Buck
I wanted to mention to your the modified atmosphere several months ago I
I want to encourage others to do it if they've already done it great and they Elders should
Need to do this is we'll get ahold of a microscope get some rain samples look at your rain
Under a microscope on you
Mind-boggling I have water samples
In my refrigerator and it's amazing what happens over
Long-term video
Glass containers I have the water in when I first collected it
And now over the course of several months
Today's disgusting fibers and God knows what the 10 there has all
And
Unscientific
Surprising thrown off
Any other day he might have jumped on that.
Pivot into
Something you didn't want to come
It's really interesting also like whenever you you wouldn't have poo poo.
Said I'm not poop
Yeah you looked at stuff and hold that that's a great way to look at stuff
To start
You know but
Don't fret
Leave me alone
It's it's great
That you want
To go down this Avenue
You haven't proven anything
You are spending your time
Go to spend
Yeah like
Seeing those
Moments are always kind of shocking
You could respond to everyone like that
There's no there's no collar that has something that
So we couldn't use that response
You are capable capable of critical thinking or at least word in 2013
To an extent that like
Incredulousness all of the like
Easily fool the bowl
Elements
It's dammit
Really operate like an adult
It's worse
It says
And that's very unscientific is one that he recorded a long time ago
This is just a little
May I could babe
Vacations weird
Misses the come-up but
In the same way you have that got to give it to
The globalist
Cancer
They're also
More indication
Of like
Him expressing
Weird ideas
Turtle weird ideas
Kind of always
You'll like he believes
But
Doesn't really overtly say
Next one is about how Evans
I'm going to be replaced by robots
And I think underneath it is something
That maybe we
Haven't done a good job of
But I think as a firm belief
You working in the military
Problem
The algorithms are all out of control
That's insane
Call her
The thing that I think is interesting with underneath
The globalist
At least
To believe
In Alex's
Misconception
That the only value of human life
Is based on work
Alex believes that
I think he agrees with that
Do you know did is that okay robot
Take over all the job
Wow
Kill Them All
Alex believe
The date his enemies believe
That but at the same time
He doesn't
Seem to offer any
Kind of
Real world
Solution to this
Or any kind of real
Humans have value outside of work really disagree with that
And keep people working
Yeah
Thieving of our imagining
A society where your value isn't based off your work
Figure able to put in at a factory
Or or whatever
Conception because you projecting
He's
On the same Spectrum
Which
The only value of a
Is taking his red B
Solution is to get robots Kill Everybody
Keep people working so they still have it
I think the fact that you know if
His enemies
Are sucks
That
You know we're going to replace humans with robots and it because they're not working they're Expendable and
If he believes
Contingent
Upon him
Create such a Groundswell
Popular
Support
Excitement
Around the idea
There is there is an entire
Beautiful world we could create if we were
To job
The tides
I think that being the end-all-be-all of Arts
Right leg the amazing
Community thing
We could do the amazing
Cleaning up of
Nature we could do
There's so much
That sounds like something we should get a robot
Yeah probably
People exploring Hobbies
Creative Renaissance
You could go through allowed to follow their path
And had the freedom
To be able to do it
That
From him and put it in terms of like that be in the solution to
The problem
Don't shut down coal plants
And keep I keep
People working
Car factories in America
Isn't
Great solution
To his perceived problem and it leads me to believe that he believes the same thing
And are only valuable as
Right
I mean
I suppose the things
Would add to that
Is there is something
Beer with n
Outcome
Like
I do absolutely think that major corporation
They're doing everything
Possible at all times to Autumn
As much of the neighbors
Absolutely
Unreasonable to think they really care what happens
Two people app
What is a rationale
The irrational fear is the part where they're all going
To kill us
You know
Like so that's another part of his worldview that
Is
Just assumed
If they are doing one
Sing
I'm not going to think about what my
Next I'm only going to take that it
Right right
If any part of the status quo changes even the slightest bit
Bright
Apocalypse
So if Alex talks about his love
Of the John Birch Society
Is that mean we already know that he loves it on a site doesn't talk about it all that often
But find it important to point out
When he does
Talks about like people taking the John Birch Society was crazy
It's cuz they were
Just like
Some kind of
Skype type of people
Really really really sucked up
If you look at the materials that they distributed
Especially in the early times
It gives you a
A good example of
What up with
They were really about
One of the first books
Put out
WhatsApp to Alder
This book called The Jon Frankel
1 letters
Insane
Violence
In in certify
Same conversation as the Turner Diaries
Or
The
Desserts that sort of malicious
A violent revolt
Yeah against the government that is gotten to
Collectivist
Or whatever
Piece of their DNA
It was one of the first
Books that they ever put out
Distributed
And so what
Talks about
Is dad being
To the John Birch Society
Being a part of the
His childhood
Was something that Alex
May have had access
He was a wee boy
Which is f***** up
That book is
Is a real serious
During heat
Football in all of this
Sublimate the mail.
Desire to
Because
Basically what he's
He's doing is living out
Murder fantasy
Through the
He's he's that he's angry at those because
Cuz he doesn't want
Fight a war
He wants to get his murder
Yeah
There is something
Into that probably
So I mean also the the John Franklin letters
Just to give some
Sensitive
Like what it what it's all about
It was written
Probably is anonymously written
But it was most likely written by
Review Loki Oliver
Who was one of the founders founding members of
The John Birch Society
Get out of the group because he was too openly
Systemic
Had too much of a bigot
And he would go on to
Join William Luther
Pierce
I just warmed
William Luther Pierce was the guy who wrote the Turner Diaries
Which inspired
Timothy McVeigh
To do the Murrah building bombing
That's a good dude
That I was able to find
Pierce
Discusses like his inspiration for writing the Turner Diaries was reveal Oliver
Copy of the John Frank
Letters
Which helps him
Start a figure out how he wanted
To write his book and
DD
They're all just writing
Fanfiction of
About
It does feel that way
Justin Bieber
Did
Anti-communist
Organization that
Just felt like
We don't like,
Is absurd
From the beginning
Was a deeply f***** up
Propaganda
Strategy
Yeah and also probably had more to do with suppressing worker
Chris Wright's
Vatican its actual opposition to copy
Strange
People get together
There's always a thing that they say they're doing but manager
Sure helps that they
Their businesses
So I don't
Towards the China issue
Allergy
Speaking in space
Pacific terms I can't really know exactly what classified
CIA
Approved at the CIA
Was that one of his self-criticism was allergic to providing
Pacific no real alternative
Ciac classified information
Years Around 1949 involves China and spoiler alert none of them
On July 22nd 1948
The CIA put out a report titled
Current situation in China
Is a report the situation is described as being
Not very good
The support for nationalist Chiang Kai-shek
Quote is that because we aren't successful prosecution of the war under his leadership
And his apparent unwillingness and inability to occur
Compass positive reform
Airport
Describes increase
Stability in the Nationalist side of
The Chinese Civil War which was unlikely to be something that we could result no matter what we did
The report is not pro-communist or promo in anyway
It says quote the prospect for the foreseeable future and Chyna is it fast and indefinite
Inclusive prolongation
Civil War
With the authority of the national government area in the Central and South China
And isolated major cities in North and Northeast
Is China
The worst Prospect is complete collapse of the national government
And its replacement by a Chinese Communist control regime under Soviet influence
If not under Soviet
Control and uncooperative towards United
If not openly hostile
So strange that they would describe the Communist coming
Power is the worst case scenario in classified
If that's exactly what they were work
According to the reports assessment the US was in a really precarious
Do you ask
Pastor Bill providing Aid to Shanghai shek but his government was increasingly ineffective and facing opposition
But also from within
Anti us sentiment has been growing not only from the communist
Do you ask
Was taking the side in a civil matter
In the hopes of turning China into a giant
Calling
Where the US to increase the aid offer to Shanghai shek would almost certainly have grown and along with it
Check resistance
At the same
Time to question the USSR loomed large
Increase
84 the Nationalist could very easily result in the USSR
Formally and materially supporting the Chinese communist
To get out of hand
Really really easy
Considering a lot of these variables the report points out that quote
Many Chinese view the USA program is prolonging the agony of rather than resolving the Civil War
That was a sentiment that we couldn't fight
Was doing a terrible job of running
Inspiring to side with the Positive vision of what comes after the war
The CIA assessment reports
This time rate full acknowledgement of the uphill battle that would be involved
He tried to somehow help him win the Civil War
And how even if the US was able to lead them to Victory
It would likely not be a good
Since his government was
Completely unstable in all likelihood
You wouldn't be able to effectively govern the country
If we were to get involved it would likely involve
Full military commitment
As well as a pretty high level of us forcing
Reforms on his nationalist government
Which would be
This sort of thing would obviously trigger a backlash from the Soviet Union whoever strategic interest in their neighbor not being us puppy
The issue of the US position in the rise of Communist party in China is it
Complex 1
But I can find no evidence
Equipment
The best argument
The US didn't
Determine that it was in their best interest
To enter a full-scale war
In order to support Chiang Kai-shek in
The Nationalist
If that's the ultimate Alex wants to make the by all means
You should make it
I suspect he doesn't present the situation honestly
Because if he did
You be advocating
For a foreign war specifically in the interest of nation-building and imprinted US foreign policy on another country
Witchy presumably is
Supposed to be a guest
The idea that the CIA installed now the power at this week's lusive domain of insane anti-communist propaganda
At the time strident
Tommy just wanted the US to get militarily involved
Because it would create a problem for stalling on it
Is eastern border
When the US didn't pursue that strategy
Because it's obvious
Horrible
It would have brought
The interpreted that as he was not wanting to apply that Eastern pressure on spelling
Which is then translated into being active support for the communist
USSR in
That's all that's going on here
Revisionist history
Oversimplify
Application in order to create a way in which
This support
Communist
And it's run by
The John Bolton's of their day
Going for
I want I want to kill these people
And I don't care
It's probably worse
John Bolton is bad at
She is like I don't think
Take over China well
Vicky would be able to be as effective 50
The years from now is the John Birch Society was
No but really sick
You know like yeah his influences
Is Insidious and
It's awful and will probably cause
Untold pain
In a lot of people's lives
But I don't know if he'll start a school
A school of thought that says
The even when forced to go underground
Because of the the people who looked at it is like.
Stupid s***
Influential
Anyway John Birch Society sucks
You're the worst
Sir
So Alex discusses how there's going to be a civil war
It's interesting that like he's always saying
You know with the intensity and like pressure that he sang it 2019
Finally come to this
Think about 20-30
Your broken record
You say that all
When the Civil War happens during the
It's important to remember
It's a toad on what
Target
Super smart
It's going on now how long is a sheriff now
There's a reason
Earlier what are you talkin about
You're going after the good beautiful people there's a little bit of code
You're trying to Target the white right-wingers
Set the consideration
If it weren't like this
How he sees things
This is going to be the minorities in the Socialist
Hey buddy
Clearly you're saying
Your you're
They're manufacturing an enemy
Except your
Creating the structures within which they
Manufactured
Like because his enemy is Imagine
He is imagining what his enemy would think of him
Ryan actually just telling us what he's
Yeah yeah there's there's something to that
So there's going to be a Civil War and the right-wing side is going to be manufactured
Create this whole war and that it all of it is just a
To demonize his side
Is it really gravy
Was that mean
I mean
Like
How are they going
How is
How's it going to do the whole thing
I wish I knew
Yeah I mean I guess probably cuz I had to guess who I don't think he really lazy
Without specifically it would be by like
Tricking
Some people on Alex's died
The paradigm
And getting involved in the war so they will be duped into it
Or just like
I guess agent
Provocateur
Starting up militias
Ready
Thanks but all people who are in the clan or fed them
Say that would be how it works
And you have to then
Create an entire side of
Loosely knit
Barely even Associated people
And put them under one Banner
You know call them all one thing and then like you said
The goal there is to
Take it you know
Shoot anybody with a John Deere hat
Picture you characterize
An entire side as
You only need to see one thing
Like I like if they had a milkshake
You know that it would be worth shooting
Manufacturer
I mean 8 p.m.
Because it is interesting
Sing houses
His mind works
And another one of these like moments
Introspection but I think
Go awry
And Zack
I've ever heard on Alex's
The show
Now that's not true in distress
I do think that if you understood how his brain work it would be
Easy to defeat these goblins because they're imaginary
His brain works and how he over
Simplifies things
How he doesn't
Look for
And any
He doesn't look for the reality
Or whatever you know if you understood
This imagined enemy because you like yeah that's just your brain
Right this is your brain man
Yeah that's a big heaping piles confirmation
If you understood how my brain works
We could
And this
If all of your audience understood are you could all be done with this a long time ago
Congratulations.
Spoken true facts about life
If you understood the code
I understand much like Leo zagami having a code
If you understood that code
The globalist
And bring in
But we just know
Or argue with them
Do you understand
Thinking could go very poorly
You have a guy who's the Arbiter of
A completely on explainable
Plan these evil globalist are doing
If you don't debate these sorts of things
Filter automatically against whatever therefore understand
If only you understood
Easy only you could
See all that I see
The globalist believe X
Sex
It might just be a really good way to get people to believe something foolishly and unquestioningly
Yeah it doesn't
Question
Intellectual Arguments for all the things that I believe but just be Oppositional defiant
Just beat the Lakers
Reactionary opposed to anything I tell you our enemies are for
That's f****** stupid
It is
It is a recipe for
Self-destruction
More than anything else
Yeah
Like okay fine
So you get rid of all the people who disagree with you all of the globalist
And now all you're left with there's a right-wing Patriots
That you love to hang out
John Deere is doing big business
Hold on
You're only
Distance is against what somebody else does
So in your little group
We should do this will guess who that guy is
He's a f****** globalist
Neo global
Smaller group
I imagine probably does happen in the last
Nearly as much at 10
As I do Alex and
A stupid world
But the way they all turn on each other
Shapiro
Kessler the guy who organized the Charlottesville unite the right rally on
I've tried to accuse him of being a fat
Did this that sort of behavior
So well in a world of paranoia
Everyone is the target of that paranoia
Anime
Why shows up
It's
It is inevitable for his
Globalist
Like
He talks about whenever they end up
Killing off most of the population
You think they are going to turn on each other
Like he understand
It doesn't feel like it applies to
To his group
At all
Introspective
Episodes
Because it feels like
Trying to figure out his
Trying to figure out himself
But publicly telling you he's trying to figure out him
I'm self probably probably
Thanks for going therapy is weak
In the next Wipeout talks about
Things that Obama is doing
Though is identical to something you celebrate
Did Trump doing
Idiot
Statistics instead
Alex was very excited about the idea of trump
Is soliciting
Stories of Violence by immigrants
Not too long ago Alex is very excited about that
Thought it was very important stories need to be
Hypocrisy is pointless
It is
So explicit
So
Want
Little measure
Remove so you have
To think for a sec
And then you're like
The critical you don't want it to just be us
Ifucking mirror
It's Ross
A little bit
Is probably one of the
The most overt
Problems
That I have with
Undercutting
Pretty much
I know I know that I've said that before in the past
Like whenever there's
Really.
Deeply
In conflict with
His primary brand
Nobody tries to prison
But
Something he says and
In this clip makes me
Think like
Boo
I don't believe that someone like Alex
To present himself.
With the police
He has
Should ever be
Indicating that he believes that some people deserve to be slightly slaves
Arbiter of
It's not even that he personally will not be
I don't I don't cut into that I don't I don't believe that for a second
And I don't believe
I don't believe it just
Because you don't agree with whatever I believe
You deserve to be the victim of the consequences
Universal Health Care
Easter
Repast
Just because they were against it doesn't mean
They shouldn't
Have the positive
Benefit
I don't think that it is right
Did anyway
For Alex
To take like
Alright
You're not on my team
You deserve to be enslaved
I will I will be fine with you being a
You're about human Liberty
Your whole thing is liver
You should be opposed to it in every con
That's how it work
If you don't choose to join Alex and be free then you lose your freedom
And that makes
Send
Or at least
We're fine with it
That is not okay
Absolutely not okay
Indicate
Interested
Less than interest
And truly think people being free
And more
Pinterest
Yeah that's really all I can
Test of
Partisan leaving early
Plans or anyting
Will only benefit the people who
Agree with me or what
This benefit
And it seems like
The only thing Alex's intro
Sit-in is benefiting
. giving a s*** about the
People who died
Right
You're a little bit of work being
The only thing that
Do these things
Right there is a sense of
Using the globalists to express that
Possession
But there is still a willingness
Engage with that idea
Define
Value
What is weird
It's all sounds a little bit
Tumi
Like when I get really
Secure end
Man I don't know how to wipe my TV
I'm not any good at
Terrible
It's just like
Directed towards me and he seems
To direct it toward the global
Making him
You know us back to that don't make me feel bad
Going to do it
Tea party that's the only hope
For America
Socialism
America
And others
So I mean
If you think Karl Rove
What is a socialist
Wells Fargo
Make me a Karl Rove at the Socialist
I mean it's just the way to
It's just nonsense
Making
I'm sure that everyone falls under your negative headache
I guess just probably anybody who believes in any kind of
Social safety net of any sort is probably social
According to Alex
What is he talking about 40
98 part 2
I'm not sure
Cuz
Figure out if I do anything
Number that was Columbus
Some stuff in like South America
Leonardo DaVinci
He finished his painting of The Last Supper in 1498
No
Yammy like he's obsessed with a Renaissance
Started
The only thing
Really huge
From 1498
History is left
Vasco de Gama
Arrived in India
Circumnavigated
South
Forgot
Creating
The spice trade in 1498
I don't understand how that's related to what he's talkin
There must be something that happened
I don't know cuz I feel like
Earlier we heard Alex talk about Cher
Clark being great
And that's
We see is an indication that Alex having him on was
Very much a strategy in order to be able to report on having him on yet
Because he's a sheriff
Popular
And so Alex being able to attach
Because no one gives a f*** if you'd like
Sheriff larger-than-life
Monster
Happy
Fair enough
You still using coded words for for black sheriff
Well spoken like dude you know what that means
Right you guys not a lot
He does that a lot of things that I just choose
Not point out because if it did it would ever
Alex talks more about that the idea of covering
His own coverage
I'm Sheriff Clarke
And I think at the end of this we really get
Education
It's not wise
It's kind of ironic song
Everything is someone who
But I think it's on
Eagles Cowboys game
Because of exactly what he expresses
Choose clock
Love love
The idea that someone covering him
Right
More importantly is that point that he makes about like
You hate that were talking about this and you got at the conversation
Doing something f***** up we're saying f***** up being and now we're hijacking your cycle
The strategy that has been
Really
Really effective
I think that is
A large part of what makes
It's the media 3 or so on
Hannibal absolutely
Descending
To the mud with these people who are bad
We're just trying
Either create their own brand or unpopularity
Rise there stars
Sensational irresponsible horrible Flame
The venue cover
Literally what happened in 2000
That got us
To where we are right now
The Bursar
Nobody would even have question
Nobody would
Ever thought about that unless the mediator
Is bulshit Bad actors
President
Seriously and then repeated their claims
Nobody with nobody
You were just being racist
Yeah and that's how we
Yeah I think there's something to that
I said before about like me pointing this out as we are a Alex Jones podcast
I think there's a large difference
Between
Especially when we started
Didn't expect anybody would like
There's a difference between
Critical analysis
Reporting
Don't b*******
There's a difference
I mean
Simply simply put
The easiest
Way too different
Invicta
Type of coverage is we don't have that
250 rule
Well if we have somebody on our show was going to say that obviously the birthmark
Conspiracy
This is bulshit brighter we have to have somebody else
To argue I
Yeah that might be a part of it
I'm not entirely sure but I do have a pretty firm
Send that
The queerness
The strategy of
Trying to make people cover his stuff
Is
Very effective and he's very into
Yeah absolutely
Kind of self-aware episode on The Chew
I have a couple clips
From the
Just because I don't want to do it on our next episode
Let's just get it out of the way
A large portion of the episode he has been refused back
Got on the show who's the pharmacist who works for youngevity
I assume that
Definitely pointed out that
He works for you
Aboveboard about the fact that like
He works he's a spokesperson
For their sponsor are still giving out like
Pretty irresponsible advice
In many
Census
Sample of the Ebola blood otherwise the supplement
Going to work
That irresponsible
Still like get off your bed
The only other thing that happens I think it's hilarious is the Alex
Is Onnit big Narrative of
The military
For the government
Is that a veteran
A lot of
Mail
Like a bulk mailing to all the veterans
That turn in their guns
Alex takes calls from veteran
And none of them ever receive this message
Like it keeps
But they're all they're all talking like they have
Or like Alex does not
The fact that not received a letter
Problem because they're out
Excuses like I haven't checked the mail
Yeah yeah I don't know
That's right I heard from one of my guys
It's the
It's a sad display of it
Very good
But this one clip where Alex
Explain
So even if you're in the f******
CIA
You don't know what Alec
Nose
Is the CIA
Compartmentalize
Do you know what your world is doing but then there's other people compartmentalize.
This person
You know X
This person over here
This other person thano W you know the alphabet
Compartmentalize
And what he's doing
Compartmentalizing all the information
So if you know X
Now you know why all right
No option
But
You then explain
Poconos the entire game
Power structure
At least two of those books about the Vatican were written by Leo zagami cell
Mission of like what books
He might be reading
Hazel eyes
Getting on the Nazis from those book
I would say is like my dad is
And I grew up in
Close proximity
It's Scholars we will dedicate their lives
Studying various topics
Helping
People about those topics
I know is a Hallmark
Of every good academic
Is rattling off how many books about a certain subject that threat
It's in Supernaut infuriating in conversation
Instead of
You know engagement with somebody's argument you say
I've read more books about
When you more than people who are in the CIA and it's too complicated for me
Express to you now let me tell you how many books I've read
Gray
That clip is
Is definite like regardless of whether he believes it or is
Acting or not
You need to
PSI Chi
It's disrespectful to like
Knowing things very idea of knowledge
I don't know
That's what happened
Imagine
Somebody
Who actually cares about subject
Being like
Acting
Now that's the first time we've heard Alex radloff how many goddamn hope he's right.
It's it's sort of
Tio2
Something that's irrelevant
Yes you could have read 10 books about a certain subject and know nothing about
You could beg
You could have read horrible books
For your ability to
Internalize information could be
Below-average
Thank you could have not synthesize the information from those books
You may have
Technically red
You can come away with it with
No expanded knowledge base
What are you saying it's just
Appeal to like
If you don't know that this doesn't mean anything you like he's right about the book
Don't understand
But he doesn't know anything
Frustrating
The literal
Interpretation
That is
One who speaks
It's does not know
Right exactly
Sprouts has not internalized the information from
If you if you are mistaken
Quantity of books with quality of information
Yeah
One last is talking about the talking to the youngevity
Pharmacist
Fuchsia
Right
Some people might
Accused us of being somehow body-shaping
And I don't mean to be at all
It's just I'm interested in the relative size of Alex's next
Throughout his career
Banana split
The
Next version of plant
It's not that his fascination with
Are not good or bad unappealing or appealing about a smaller or larger
Her neck and I'm not trying to make Alex feel bad
At all
He talks about his neck a lot
His neck was shrinking
Cam
Bread that has gluten
Cut the Wheat Belly I've not heard it before
It's not heard that formulation of
Gluten intolerance but
I don't I don't I don't know if this is still something
I has
I'm not sure the first time I've ever heard
It's it's
Also relevant in terms of like not and not just making fun of his his neck or anything
Because it's within the context of
Almost a testimonial for his supplement yeah
Like I've been I've been taking the I haven't taken them all but it would take
Back on the the Infowars life
Products
All my arms shrinking
Me getting smaller
That's no he's indicated that he's losing weight
So sometime in between 2013
The present
Perhaps when he stops taking
Youngevity products
His neck I got freakishly large
As he has
His aunt description
Freakishly large
I think
It's almost a refresh
Testimonial like I would prefer that
To any
Actually
You'll be able to
He's more religiously
Look I'm lazy like you I'm trying
Maybe you should buy it why are you making me feel bad
It's grounded more than a lot of other one
If you was trying to
Completely craft
You wouldn't bring up his
Belly
Although I don't know if it would be wise of him
To say
That
Their products could
Gluten
A Dodge I don't know
You would expect you be going over the top though
Even though he's telling you I honestly I don't actually think that is just his way around like
Arguments it's like well why are you unhealthy
If you take all of your help supplement is never on Olive
That is something I've always heard
Even when doctor
Group comes along
Is likely
Aisle and I mean to take how I just got to forget sometime
And that way
Can't be living proof that it doesn't work
Consider that that is a
Mercer
Compared to the present day
You see a bit less of like a really over-the-top sales
I think probably part of that might be him not getting
A huge cut
You might not have as big an interest
Are not moving the product
Then
Then he doesn't
Omnipresent
I'm here and I think
This is a bit of a
Alex is right when he started the first
Episode on the 21st
He is in a bit of a right there is a little bit of
Stillness
To his show in 2013
Still not really talking
About Sandy Hook
You're at this point
And I wonder if those two things
Are going to join together
The Dish Network
Is it possible that maybe
Being really f****** irresponsible in his reporting
About dumbass conspiracy theories that he's already
Throne
And put dip
Tutto into a little bit
Is that going to be
Who knows
Feels real bad about
Shut
You know what maybe I should be less
I'm going to
I don't know I don't know
Interested
If only because
Like to take a
Zup
It makes me think that maybe
At least
Something
Excited
Very excited to see what happens and especially because I'm not super-excited about
Present day
I don't really care about Alex
Feelings about that
Trump
Media Summit
I don't particularly care
How about China that so
Cooking up a little bit here in the past
A much-needed
Yeah I prefer that
We do have website its knowledge fight.
You bet it is
Ross on Twitter
Do you know where you could download Artio if you would like
Go to I-20
You could go to local co-op
How many people get together
Skateboard shop
You get an episode of our podcast
Skateboard
But not if you just get trucks
Episode of ours if you're only getting trucks
No
I have no evidence
That the caller who put rainwater in his fridge killed anybody
I don't know but I do I have no evidence
You put a drop of water in the fridge it's only a couple years before you got it
You know what your
I can't prove you wrong
Reroute no evidence that
Probably have killed somebody
Who's Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color