I love your work
Sit around
Beverages
Little bit
About
Alex Jones
Drawing
Intro out and I don't want
I don't want
Steamrolled me with a bunch of ummagawd Federer so great
What's up
Have you ever told somebody to go back to where they
I mean I know I know why you're at
Asking me that question
Certainly relevant here on this record
I don't know I don't
It was a s*** head stupid kids
I pray that it wasn't
Usually your ethnically
Go back to their home
Portland
I imagined I had it at some point
Sticks out to me
I don't think I remember witnessing it
Almost non-stop bases
Small town
Illinois
And I don't think I've ever actually I think
Mayhem
No I don't think I've ever said it
Sure
Completely different kind
Caught up in love
America get out now my family see that was the whole thing
My family was all into that
My Act of rebellion
Unfortunately
Regeneration
To get out
But
Stretch episodes
To go over
The password is going on
Deer in this late February stretch
Going on to movies except
I don't think he was still late 90s
Comeback
Inflight seen a couple times around
Kicking around
Marquis guide 2013
You starring in The Scorpion King
F*** I wish I remembered exactly what I think
Espina and the rockets fight at Wrestlemania
Where
That's fight between
Alberto Del Rio
Did not manifest
Third to last message
Yeah they don't really care about their belts whatever their star power
What are we doing this I do believe sincerely
Something is really big
Going on
I think
You get a sense
Grommet from Alex
Feelings of
The show up
Tennessee on this show that I
Thank God were
We're getting it.
Before we get to
Today's episode
Take a moment to say thank you
When we talked about how I was going to move
I need to move
Supportive messages
Drake generously
Little donations I really appreciate it very much
Ain't that means a lot
Particularly the people who are saying you're like I went through
A similar situation
You gotta keep your head up
Things will be better on the other side
Thank you very much
And also
Northport
Jordan
You're now a policy wonk
Karen
Next
Poor blurble on your now
I'm a policy wonk
First alien
Poor
Board board one word and then blower motor
Rbl orbulon word
That's Tuff
Next Ian
White ship from horrible horrible on
Next
Conrad's
Fire bones
Who donated on elevated
Appreciate it very much so
Jos
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
We would appreciate
So Jordan
Today what we're doing what we are going over February
3/4
Alright
This is a very exciting.
I'm Alex
Is really
F******
All over the place in terms of how desperately he wants more people to pay
Hugo's on some other people
He has some big gas
All very clearly
Expresses an interest of like
I really get the word out
But here before we
Context drop
Sucker
Brian
Good religion
Is religion
His religion includes calling you a
Dumpy branch
You are a piece
4th February
It's not really relevant to a ton
Stop but it is
Expression of Alex
His beliefs about how
System is already
Black people
So we don't need
It's implied that he
You sort of minimizing
To defend
Minorities right
I think this
You get a sense
Alex
Uses White
And Western culture kind of energy
Which is an important as he
Tried to pretend all the time
Systems going
Enchiladas
So you have
Kodak blacks and others
Yeah
The other which is
Western Towing
Which is presented in direct opposition to the Black Panthers
Pharaoh's people down
Clear what's going on
So I found that to be in
Tristan butt
Kind of secondary
To what what else
What's going on
Towards the beginning of the episode
Makes it amazing a noun
That I stink
That means we are getting close
Toupee
5% chance
Story
Alex has a
Game-changing story
And I'll tell you
I have no idea
I have a theory I think it's
Hidden camera
You couldn't be embellished
Or it could just be fishing
Like literally
Yeah
I'm not entirely sure
I haven't listened
Too far enough
Should know what his
News stories
Text
Kind of lead me
Maybe
He's got a little bit of a bird with
Brings up
Wanting to take people's guns
Have you know
Jordan
I love a quote
Autoflower strains
It's supposed to be from the US
Arms
UN website
So
Made up quote
Which doesn't appear at all in either the arms nor from the report from the July 20th
One un report that was titled
Small Arms
Those two things or something and Alex doesn't know the difference
Or intentionally consist
Plate most likely on purpose
To make it harder for his listeners to
The arms trade treaty from
And you have the July 2001 illicit trade
Small Arms report
Which is
Use the date from that
Is it to the treaty
Completely different things
This quote is definitely not from either of those um publication
When I looked into it more many websites trace the call back to it
2004 debate
It was held at King's College in London
Between Executive Vice President of the NRA Wayne LaPierre
And Rebecca Peters
Beheaded
The international Acts
Action Network on Small Arms
Well I am
It was active in big
Parkview at the Fishel body within the US
William up here himself has lobbied the UN on behalf of the NRA
You can make the argument that the two of them are on
Being representative
None of the kids
Christian right-wing websites can get their citation right on this quote
Ronpaulforums
Got message boards frequently side is being said by a representative
College
You don't seem to agree on the
Some say that it's July 2001 most likely because they've mix
It's been up with the illicit trade in Small Arms
Father's Day the debate was held in 1993
Most likely to associated with the passage of the Brady handgun violence prevention Act of that
What website I found called Liberty
1993 while simultaneously linking of the debate
From 2000
F******
Five stars
It's so sloppy but it also really feels like they're trying to confuse people about the Genesis of this quote
No one gets
Citation right because they want the argument to be that the un's
Get rid of guns because it threatens the full control of
The quote is a whole mess
Useful
If it were appropriately cited as being said by a lobbyist
Senate debate
That's not nearly as nefarious or scary
Of course which is why you got to lie
There's another problem.
There's this debate the great un gun debate it's 90 minutes long and I watched it twice
And preparations
Episode
Never heard Rebecca Peter say anything about civilian gun ownership
The power Monopoly of the state
That sentiment is out of step with Rebecca's
However it's very in line with the accusations that we
Pierre makes about what Rebecca
Disposition
Secretly are
But it doesn't match up with what she's actually saying okay so we're dealing with
Quotes
Is being a
Attributed to the US
Actually
Supposed to be from a debate
But actually wasn't said by the person that it's a
Attributed to the other person was lying about that other person
It appears that way
Okay arriving into this is a real quote from the even from Rebecca Peters in Urdu
This in my best estimation is it was fabricated out of whole cloth after the 2004 debate
To preemptively attack the common Small Arms
Treaty and the UN created rules about the illicit Small Arms
I'm straight
Primero circulated in right-wing militia type internet communities
Hey given elevation credibility by being Amplified by people like Alex Jones
And attached
Two figures like Ron Paul
It's all a lie
As far as I can
Is not fun
No also interesting note in that debate
Wayne LaPierre
Cannot stop accusing Rebecca Peters
And her organization to being funded by internationalist like George Soros
Great great
In 2000
4 weight is way ahead of the curve on the Soros
At least for non-european fascist to you yeah we talked about
Wow
Alex talking about Soros for
11 years
No and I mean like was a 2011 I believe Glenn Beck
Hot water for
Segment
What an idiot
I think it was
Real big notable one was Bill O'Reilly
Should about Soros but that was three years after this
Oreos are regularly
Mostly European one
Pretty as the curve for
For Americans
So he's got a big
Big thing going on
I mentioned our last episode that story about how
All the veterans are getting letters
Need to turn in
Veterans call in
Alex tells a story about going to this
The academy
I believe is the name of it okay
He overheard some guy
The fat
I heard an old guys related to Ron Paul's
F*** that.
You you can't even do that the better part of the story though is when he's at the same motor shop
Man
Everyone treats him like a
So like
This is why there's value in Alex
She's like just automatically be defensive about everything just
Fight it doesn't matter
Because he recognizes that there's good arguments
Measures
Control but
They're not going to use it appropriately so
No gun controls whatsoever doing this for a reason
Other than what they're saying
Dangerous level of
Pretended your psychic
Yeah
Because I mean what I hear that all I really hear is I recognize that there's a really good arguments against my position
And I know I'm going to lose them
Yell at people
Just recognized
There are good arguments
African regulations for safe
F***
Him
I do like that I do like the balls on them
Just like
Oh yeah I know I don't know
There are good arguments but it is 100% +
Impossible for the other side to make any argument in good faith
They are always lying
Happier with zero gun laws
Then I am with anyone even being like
We should do a background
Lame
Not good
It's pretty disappointing
I would say
Not quite as disappointing
As a narrative
Takes over the show actor
Department of Justice memo
NRA
As I recalled
Did the Tylenol
That this f****** memo is literal proof
That they are ready and about
To ban all guns
Let's see this
Oh my God
Getting ready plan to confiscate all guns
Truth
The loaded Bowl
Question is called select firearm violence
Prevention strategies
I know where the document doesn't call for complicating
This is a descriptive report not a prescriptive one
It's not arguing for any particular strategy rather it's looking at
Various strategies that have been employed or could be employed
Engagement how they worked
What the strong points were and what the limitation
In the part of the report about gun buyback
It specifically points at the gun buybacks aren't really effective
Unless they're quote
Masses and coupled with a ban
That doesn't mean
That's what should be done
It's just descriptive lie saying that went BuyBacks have been done
Historically haven't really brought in minigun and the guns that are brought back are the ones that are at a high risk
Stop being used
Violent crime
Describe something
Sowell
As a
Hey
I get the people are saying
Text but there's no point
Unless we go all the way
More lessor or at least supplement
Huge
Do paintballs market value of people
Incentive
It's it's
Ridiculous
You can already see where this is going
From this
The paranoia
Going to possess Patriot world
AMA and his Department of Justice were preparing massive gun buybacks
And complete gun ban
This is such transparently dishonest presentation
What is exactly what you'd expect
Group of people desperate to
Create the appearance of their guns are about to be
They don't really have much of a reason to
Exist as an organization
NRA that is
Aura force in public discourse is that fear isn't constantly reinforced
So any excuse to ramp it up
For them is a good
Interesting
Highly suspect
This is going to play
It's Alex's feeling
Songs about Sandy Hook
And I think the introduction
This report
Is further evidence that he is about to get
Going on that report is coming in
That's whenever he
He's going to be like
And here's the soft launcher
Sandy Hook
Which possibly did involve a real victims according to him
He believes that is that they did that in order to push a gun controller
On January
The 4th 2013
So I can easily see Alex using this
Narrative that has now introduced
I using
Timing of it to build up his narrative.
The shooting was a false flag
I get the sense
This is possibly
Like app
Piece of ground being lazy
Yeah
And maybe I'm just putting pieces
Together the dark really there
But it feels kind of like
That's the kind of
Every
These pieces of evidence
Line up to a perfect conclusion what we're going to do today we're going to talk about
Squirrels
And how they're bothering my neighbor has v like I need to mix it up
You've got your I've got a giant piece of news involves the media
It's going to be game-breaking if I have the ability to release it
The timing of this report being a couple weeks
Weeks after
Just coming to the surface now here in February and February
There's a lot of there's a lot of stars aligning
It won't happen while driving
Most frustrating thing you know the destination
My Waze app
So if Alex talks about the little bit more
Cuz it's three pages long it's nine pages
What are the things that I find really interesting is that like
We have a show where we can
Can take as long or as short as
We want to do these episodes of
Being able to
And so does Alex
It's just a matter of whether or the on the radio
You know what you could broadcast
Infowars Studio says whether or not
Some
Station in Cocoa Beach
Is going to be up
So what I hear Alex
Say something like he doesn't
Text clip
All I can hear is him making it
Excuses
For not doing the
What do you think I think is the guiding principle of his show
Which is if I prove things
You we'd run out of time
Repeat myself over and over and over again
Being demons
How many gal for long stretches of time about nothing I'm going to
Do a f****** long
Critical breakdown of the Watchmen movie lawyer for a while
It'll take too long
Who just believe me
That is a dangerous mentality while you're listening to the show in your car
I want you to pull out your phone
Google make sure
Everything that I'm saying Google
It's not good
Not a good way to approach
A truth based
Show
Yeah
Seems like it's
Dealing with a
So in this next
Clip you know whatever you do broadcast
Show that the call-in show is run the risk
Prank callers
Pretending that there's somebody that they're not
Pretends to be
Celebrity
And they call in your show
That's not what happened to your
But Alex is worried that it might
Politely
Reset my pilot screw
Radius from the self-evident truth
Chanel
A morganatic communicate more often
Oh man Ted Nugent just out of nowhere calls in the show
Playing
Nugent appearance f*** is
What is Ted Nugent he's driving around actually loses signal at one point to another call
I don't care too much about what Ted says
It's all just like I love God
But there's one clip that I think is important
Play Ted Nugent
Because it revealed
Alex does
And taking too many girls of the military that have their legs in their arms their eyeballs
In their skin
Second Amendment because the Second Amendment
Now
What's important there is the teeth and Frida
The Liberty
The only place that traces back to is the fake George Washington quote that we talked about that Alex.
Ted Nugent
Allegedly from an address to Congress recalls gun
The teeth of Liberty
That is a haunted person
What he's doing and he was trying to say
Outside right now
Looks like the teeth of Freedom Liberty
Is a very specific
Expression
In one place in one place only
Smoke has mythologize this fake quote
They don't realize they're just quoting some guy with a column
For Farmer tractor trailer magazine or whatever
Trapper Trader
Whatever it was
They dictate the recording George
They're not
But it's interesting because you got understand how these things were early memes
MacDade we write this in the same way you have these
You know Pepe kind of things around the internet now
These ideas were
Circulating Message Board newsletter
So when you trace back
Liberty Liberty
Alex has been
Do you know that there
Swimming in similar pond
So f***** up bad information
Militia it's
Information
I really don't want to
I don't want
The the
Country
Descendant to Fascism and
And I get killed
Because
The song Imaginary bulshit that these guys believe it's a quotes
It's really annoying that they
What they believe
Isn't real but they still get to kill people in real life like
You only be able to hurt imaginary people
Just got on 2nd
Play the savior
Ghost
It will be because
I believe so
Alex Goes to other calls
This caller
I don't recognize the voice so we can't put him down as like Bible day and or old man house phone
Frontier
Psychiatrist
Frontier psychiatrist who believes
Numerology
I believe the 2013
Is unlucky
The occult
Numerology of course you probably already know that man covered that at some point some time
I don't know if you've actually figured out a recharged is
The school and Bones picture with bush look at the clock in the back
I think something really bad going to happen in 2013 because of course you're part of the 11th Hour which would be 11
12 colonies
13 original states
Great response
Migrate
So you got a picture of George W bush bones
12 + 112
Is 2013 going to be super unlucky because I have a bunch of plan
Analysis response
Hey buddy
I appreciate that you like the show but I think talk to somebody because you're drawing
Hindi was f****** connection
Responses
13 is a lucky number because of 13 colonies
Man I bake my luck
Because I love God
Don't I don't remember the Bible verse where God was like
If you love me
Is you're going to have to make your own
Like I don't
So should the letter be
To me an indication
Lack of care for the people that he's into
So you know like
Obviously
This guy probably will
Would be looking for
Weird nonsense
With or without aloe
The reality is with the reality is Malik
Clearly part of
In this next clip I think we get another indication
How little he really cares
Is it gets another call from a guy who's been listening
For 15 years
Elizabeth is dismissive bulshit
What's today
Temperature in years
A lot of your videos
Community
What the f*** kind of responses that even listen to the question
I doubt he did but if he had let's make let's just assume that he did listen and that was it
His response
I don't understand someone like Alex Jones
Skin like
Working in
Who cares kind of way
This guy is calling it
He clearly believes the sheet you're saying
A+
You know I got all your books
What can I do to wake up my community
The color is asking me
How can I help
People with the information
You put out to the world
I do to make the world better
According to our agreed-upon
Ception of it
You know what there's no real use the people aren't on our team already they're probably not going to
Why haven't information War at that point
What is the point is there anything you could
Send me to help wake up Micah
Community
Azure like posters
Perfect place for Alex to jump into plug
For sure right
I'll help you and do that at all he was just like
Shut the fuk up
People aren't on board already tonight
Which again
Already said this
After stress
Why do the Alex Jones Show
If people who are going to wake up at already woken up does that not imply that all you're doing is preaching to the choir
I guess so
Fair enough
Being afraid of everything
So in this 24th
Especially looking back
Real gross van
May have killed a lot of dough
If possible
Sew-in in this clip we here
Kind of a transition
And Alex's
Telling of his
Childhood violence
From being
The
Result of him being bullied
To him and Tyga
Right
And I don't think he understands as he
He's telling the story
The very serious difference
Between the pipes
It was really fun
So
Wow what he's describing is him initiating violence on people which
Is very different than the idea of self-defense
Like I still don't like violence and
Is the answer but someone is being picked on
You know someone tries to start a fight with him
I don't think there's really that
Much bad
You are wrong
Especially in adolescence
About fighting back
Better Avenues to go down but in the world we live in
I'm not going today
I'm not going to blame Alex
For fighting back
Going
To blame him
Forgo
Who he has determined are bullies
And then stopping their heads
Yeah very very different
Yeah that's that's really stuck
That's really not good
He seems to think that it's all the same and all very like
Appetite back
He's not
At a certain point you're not
You even says I went a little overboard that's f***** up
So we can
Paul Joseph Watson
The news story
But he is putting out here on
25th
Not facing reality
Is actually
I'll tell you what
Drones
Oh man
It should be pointed out that this
Is not the
News that Alex
Isn't that story visit
Is another story
It's another completely overblown exaggerated
Manipulative Libra
Presented story
Victim
Have an oppressive government
The actual story is at the Department of Homeland Security released
Promotional video about us
Infowars angle on this story
Surprisingly
Isn't providing surveillance
Promotional video includes footage
Which they're offended
To quote the first paragraph from Paul Joseph Watson article
Quotes
The promotional video for a surveillance drone
Being purchased by law enforcement bodies across the country
Just fun
Spying on a private guns
Hopefully depict
The scenario is criminal activity
I don't care about the stupid story
The desperate attempts to make their gun obsessed
Community look like dogs doesn't
I literally have only even covering this
Because Alex
If you have a problem with it
Is exact same depiction of a private sale be his sponsor where to hide your guns.
Included dramatized
I wonder what's the difference between these two
Situation
Oh I know it's the fact it in the Hydra guns commercial the person who's purchasing the gun is a shirtless black man with over
Oversized dollar sign chain around his neck
If this is being presented as a criminal act in that video.
It was part of a compilation of reenactments including a guy using a crowbar to break
So
I was perfectly fine accepting money from people who present private gun sales to black people as a criminal act
Off the books
A white person might be illegal
Proof of tyranny
Is upon us
Is woefully transparent
This is nonsense
Private gun
But I understand if it's too much to unpack
No
I don't know where the line isn't it I don't I don't know what my full feelings on it are
But I do know that if Alex wants to get right with God soda
Could be consist
He's never accepted money from Hydra guns.com
You should have made a huge deal about the fact that in there video there depicting
Private gun sale to
Cartoonish characters
I every time you tell her that
Giants.
Buys a gun from a guy and then texted into his pants and every time I'm like
That cannot be
This is
That's just not possible
He doesn't care about that depicts
More important
It'll bickering about private gun sales
I think it's more important that sort of
Undercuts
White people haven't got
So in this next clip Alex gets
Religious on
Your dumbass
Man
We've heard him say some weird religious stuff
The past
Sometimes
I understand
This makes no sense
Just amazing
What is about
Buried
Average
Silicone
Turn the other cheek
The really big deal
Right
If you if you wanted anyone may follow after me
So long as their plan.
Legitimately like next-level f***** up but Alex thinks
Like Jesus didn't turn the other cheek
Yeah it's Bible because
You are
Because you was beefing
How do you spell receives any wasn't ready to die yet
Putting it off but then a few years later I am going to
Stop
Appears
Which part of The Sermon on the Mount
He was still in the early stages of his preaching though he recently gone out to the desert and resisted the temptation.
Who's coming off some momentum broken into the main
Stream Felix for stand-ups it's kind of like
If you didn't do faces of Jeff out you don't have any late-night credit
On the desert but you're not mean
Not there yet
The sermon is basically the Jesus laying out with means
Christianity is all about
You got the Beatitudes at the beginning that be like blessed are the meek
For they will inherit the earth
You got some points Jesus makes about what behaviors appropriate
And then you get to the
Turning Park
Explicitly explained
In opposition to the mentality of an eye for an eye
References back to the Old Law of Leviticus
It's a revolutionary ideas pacifism the Jews of physics
Expressing and it's clear what do you mean
But I tell you to not resist an evil person
If anyone slaps you on the right cheek
Turn to them the other cheek also
And if anyone wants to sue you and take
Your shirt hand over your coat as well
If anyone forces you to go one mile go with them
2 miles
There is a
You're an idiot that doesn't know how to read the Bible
That's fair
I don't know I'm not I'm not the biggest biblical scholar and I don't know what other info
Who's Alex could be talking about
Cuz there is a point where Jesus
Hit
Already
I don't I don't
What was the Apocrypha
It could be that
There's no reason that you would think
That
That boggles my
I don't know enough about like weird scriptures but I don't know enough
To know is that exist
Somewhere in
Non-canonical book
Maybe it's in the one where Jesus
Spot dragon
Turn the other cheek
Specifically about math
Q5 like that is part of The Sermon on the Mount
Also seriously The Sermon on the Mount
Is pretty much that one
F******
Oh this is why
Kind of thing
Sure
Is like
Oh this is the whole reason that were not is Beatitudes
I thought it was but then you said it and I didn't want
Correction
I researched real service speaker
I'm not going to pronunciation
You know what I am good at though
Warning you
They were about to
Get a guest appearance
From my cat
I recently on behind the bastards
Had the pleasure of Robert Evans telling us all about terribleness
Mike Adams
I wasn't even aware of was that Mike out of
So
The Mike Adams Porsche
Variance
I'm surprised
Is the pump
Second prime
Situation
It turns out Mike Adams might have made a lot of parody videos last time
Now I did search for this
I was hoping to be able to
But
Mike Adams YouTube channel
God damn I have no one else has seen fit to repost his We Didn't Start the Fire parody
Blake from the
Blog post about natural news
It didn't sound like they made new
Music
Put video over
Or like pictures over
So was he one of the founding members of The Lonely Island and then they then they were like
SNL writer
Hilarious
So Mike Adams in the next clips
Obama
Test
Is a good activate
Listen to make
And then Alex
Talk about something
Absolutely.
Not true absolutely
Does not happen on
The show ever
There is no
Master of neuralink
You're horrible
Hundreds of hours
Probably more than
Alex's show
I've never heard any caller
But even is closed
What is describe a person
I've never heard any callers it's like
He couldn't polish into that
It's bananas
Make the idea these present
Was somebody trying to reason with a like
Alex
Obama colors
People who support Obama
And the people who call in
Are like
I don't actually support Obama
It's not as bad as you say
Crying on the line
Mike Adams got this parody song
Throws put out
I didn't
Realized
I think Mike Adams
Might want to be
Venus funny
I didn't realize
You know that we talked about where he's like this gun can't fire itself
I think he really thought that was probably super funny and we're shooting for funny
Because the vaccine zombie that's clearly an attempt
Fire parody song
The pattern
And then it comes in
With this
Like you got a bit
He's coming into Alta show where they delivered
TUEBL
And it's got all sorts of trace minerals in it that you can see here
He's got a prop
He's got a talking
This is this is amazing
Realize you could be
So unfunny I didn't even know you were
Trying to
New level of bread
Crazy
He's doing the late night
Chose
Easy listening for what
Crazy
Jordan
We don't think you
He's funny
I think you could have strong evidence
The Alex doesn't think he's funny either
Because Mike start listing off the mineral name
Letter in the bottle
ABC
In the room Ono
Vista house
And it's got all sorts of trace minerals in it that you can see here
Magnesium in
So you forget American history
Better
Wolf you could have speegleville box
Alex didn't respond to the Obama Museum
His own bed and then move onto the squeezy
Andover explaining it
You have no help in that room
Too many open mics with that was with that but I felt
Yeah I felt that open mic bombing
So much longer conversation about
Unimportant
Health news
Are we getting to the 26
Naruto
Big news
And that is
But he was on another show that morning
But this isn't the big news that he was teasing in the earlier
I promise that I'm not holding out on you I do not know what that is
Howard Stern for hour-and-a-half this morning
Howard Stern
Serious
And Robin
Okay
Started fluoride
Maybe they were f****** I didn't realize it
Especially considering
State of Affairs between him and Howard
In 2019
You get the sub
I'm not entirely sure
But it is
Alex's
Really excited about this greater exposure
The show is getting
He now has like
Reached
Howard
The king of all media
And it's a real to be on that
Absolutely
So you
You get a sense that like
This is Howard
He's putting the piece
Together
To like we really got to push
What shows in a rut got to mix it up for how do you do that
Well
You are who you know
You got to change up a little bit
The content
And then also simultaneously
You got to change up your
You got to figure out how to get new blood in
That's amazing
That nobody had any idea like we all
Thought that Alex
I'd like
Hilarious conspiracy
There is for they were a listener visit for y'all
I like Howard Stern would have them on
When is platform like
Piers Morgan
And then we had no idea of it
All that would really
That lead to an incredibly
Yeah that's true
That's true so another thing that I would
Is the other do gas
The show
We're going to talk much about
Does but I have some thoughts
So in about an hour
Studio
He has some other
Riffs on Mike Adams
Mineral
Has more we came up with more mineral names
Nissan on his show because I think that this is child
Sweetheart
Editorial editorial position
To make clear because of the circle
This point Alex won't say his
Son's name public
Which I think is probably good
But he's letting him Beyond
His Radio Show
His son is
10 years old
And all he does when he comes on is these little bit
Better just like recreating
Some of the jokes that Mike Adams bombed with
And then also repeating tunnel
Clearly has heard Alexei and then passes them off
As his own beliefs
As a ten-year-old
I really wrestled with this
Because on the one hand I feel like playing clips of this 4th grader doing an impression of his dad
Talking about global offshore
Clearly demonstrates how evil Alex
Adult
He knows what his son doesn't
Understand any of the things you talk about
He's just repeating
In his own words
Is it temp
To gain his approval
He has a responsibility to treat his son as a ninja
Individual not as in
Extension of himself
Exactly what Alex
Is doing here
That said I decided to go
Because this
Your old is someone who's not express
The only way to practice empathy towards this child
Is to refuse to accept that it's okay to make fun of him
Because he's connected
Alex
That's treating him as an extension of Alex as opposed to treating them as an individual
A child
Somebody
Since you know Alex is the one who does look really bad in this
Situation
But I don't care
If you think that is
Is the case
Appreciate your perspective but I did
Disagree with you
And I would rather deal with I would have about myself
Indirectly or directly making
I would really prefer not
Criticize
10 year olds
Mineral jokes
Better than
Unfortunate
For Mike but because I kind of knew that ten-year-old as a victim of child
F****** unobtainium but Obama
Is it better like
I don't I don't
Take that approach to it at all it would just be playing a 10 year old
Repeating Alex's
I've got a great
It's just
Bring this up
Unexplained
To give you all you need
10 year olds
Ojai schools are fight clubs
High School
It was
The coolest couches
Everything's fine
Just broke the rules of Fight Club
Yeah
He's talking about Fight Club
So I would say
Not cool
For coaches
It's not called
Police after a kid gets a head
Cracked open
I don't think it's cool for these
These coaches to not be
Snitches
They would let us kill each other
And they would never do anything
Think about it they were so cool
That is indicative of
If you believe if you believe that that's the appropriate place
School
YooHoo voice
Also the fact that
There's so many things there's so many had dramas
Soul Man
It's hard it's hard
I'm surprised
Yeah
Alex comes out against
Yeah well it's about time
Is a religion
The creation
What
So apparently the only real science of the world is that which confirms the existence of God
Science
He's only good in so much as it is in line with religion which
Memes
Oh okay so then
So then
Would never have created gun
What do you mean that confirms God
Don't you get rid of the Bible passages about guns
Do not confirm or
Is the existence or non-existence
Turn the other cheek is actually like a mistranslation
From the original
Drop another round
The span of time
This from the 23rd
Alex has been
Really really excited
He's got coming up
On here on the
He is someone who he is talked
A lot of s*** about
It is a major
Your figure
And right-wing
He's somebody who has a
SEC radio show
Has not been
Cool about
He's really f***** up s*** about him
Is it really Glenn Beck
This February 26th
2013 is
The first time
Being a guest on Alex's show
And I believe
It signifies the moment when
Person
Goes from
F*** this guy to he's one of the greatest Patriots ever
Michael said okay
The either
Savage
He has Michael Savage on the show
25th
Alex got a call from
Some what's Naruto's like
Hey you know he's fine with like Obama using drones
You need to ask him these hard-hitting question
Sure about this
They are really big differences in your world and Alex's like
I'm not going to Beta guy in here and then ask him all these confrontational question
Am I headed
What about the timing of David Rothschild
Go f*** yourself Alex okay
The reason that he's not going to do that
Because he's so excited
He recognizes that
Savages
Canticle
Any idea of
Heaven
Some sort of
Between them
I'm some sort of the
The coming together
Mutual respect
Building
Super valuable
Alex might be able to go on the Michael Savage
He might be able to
To bring some
Savages audience to him
Many interviews of people
I'm smarter than that
He knows what's going to happen if you goes into hostile territory
Well he does know quite a bit
As a person that if he goes into
Any environment where
Like let's auri were
We could so easily bait him insignia
Alright easiest f****** thing in the world
I don't put myself in that situation I'm a f****** billionaire
I broadcast out of a
Enclosed space yeah and then I live my life
Liberals
Or anything
I think it's because he's afraid of being proven wrong
He is full of
Gotcha
Okay
Alright
And I have a reason for things
Making that a little bit
I don't know he has
He's been eligible
More verbal
Physical attack
Here's a couple fun trivia
In the 19th
He was friendly with Allen Ginsberg
What
What there's a picture of him
What are we doing
Stop it out of here he also works for Timothy Leary
He was a gatekeeper
Facility Michael Savage is a f****** weird history
Timothy Leary
The Story Goes because Michael Savage
I was in no way interested
Psychedelics
And taking
For the place where they were
He
Is crazy
But he hasn't history through the Bohemian Circle
Through the 60s
70s
How many turns
Fleetway the other direction
And a lot of people who knew him back then
Who speculated that he felt a lot of rejection
From those people apart of
Is turning on the
Weird betrayal
This doesn't seem like a my don't know what
It's weird another person you used to know I'm
I also said that
Wanted to be
And that
He bombed performing
He's wanted to be like as Lenny Bruce type
Workout forum
I thought
Political
Goddamn
He is a guy who
Before he got super political was writing books
About like
Herbal
Healing
Alternative medicine stuff
Because he is educated
I feel
Maybe nose
Some valuable information
There
Transition
To what he's become
Awful
Do you know what I sometimes
Think about
So many of these right-wing
I am the wrong amount
I'm not funny enough to be famous
I'm too funny
To have
Probably be a right-wing hack
If you do stand up and you're not
I have to have a little bit of humility to transition out of it
Because otherwise you
Could take it as like a real Injustice
To you that you never made it
You have to you have to
Check your ego tiny bit recognize like
I didn't deserve
How to be famous
Nothing about you
Super talented that doesn't make me
Entitled to some kind of
Alright record dealer victoire
You don't make something happen baby
Along the way or took them
Tracy didn't make along the way is what led to
You not being
Successful and I think a lot of these people
You know the people like her Gavin McInnes
Or
Michael Savage
The reports of him being a comedian or trying to be comedian
I don't they're just based on people who used to know I don't know how much that's actually
Like what drove
How does generalization
I think a lot of those people Felton
Entitled to some sort of
To success
Stand-up and when they didn't get it
You externalized
I blame it supposed to be my
I just didn't have it
Or maybe with timing or maybe with luck who knows you don't have to feel bad about it
But they've already I mean that's
That victim
Mentality
What makes
So powerful
At the end when they
Turn it out
Fire
So also Michael Savage
He got into radio in the nineties
And part of it was because he's written a book
About immigrants causing disease
People didn't want
So you got the radio
Pretty success
Pretty quick
His books have been pretty successful Savage
Borders language
You wrote a book about
Politics is a
A bunch
People in politics
It's very weird
Surprise
Money on that but also another Revenue
And that is his son
Is the founder of Rockstar Energy Drink
What
What are we doing his wife
The CFO of Rockstar Energy
Bread
He's a super weird dude Michael Savage
Really when you look at it
There is there's a ton going on there's a lot of psychodrama
In Subway new Allen Ginsberg
Timothy Leary
Executive son started Rockstar
That's so crazy
Very weird
Michael Savage
Attempt to create
They're not going to talk about
Electric Kool-Aid
You can wish they would
Michael Savage
Just start screaming about how they're all like diaper Doper baby
Largely
Michael Savage
About how great his show is
Whatever
I finally got on in New York City
9 at night now what happened
Michael Savage
I exploded with younger listeners
And talk radio in general I have eight listeners
I think you might have answered your own question as to why emotional
Yeah I think
Would you put yourself in Superfly situations like this we engage in that kind of casual misogyny
Maybe you are going to attract cicadas female listeners
I mean the only
Women don't really listen to talk radio also all women are stupid and we should never have given him the right to vote and I don't understand
They don't listen
Caesar salad
Michael Savage radio
Casually misogynistic
I don't
Women don't lie
Your
Talk radio
In this neck
Michael Savage
Dude it if anybody
What I kept thinking is like
I used to listen to Savage
When I was in my like
Late teens or early 20s
Cuz there's a radio station eagle
Columbia Missouri
It was on
Angel
There's something kind of thinking about it
Grievous is politics
Dynamic where like you'd scream at collars
And talk politics
It was kind of like
He's an a******
Story about getting like some really great pasta
And like The Passion of the story
This little Italian Eatery
End
See the lighting in
Play
Nurses like
Asmrs quality this voice telling you that story about this
Grape meatball
I was drawn to it somehow
Anyway I have this perception of Michael Savage
Trump
From years past
And I think a lot of people have
Positive associations with him
Some people probably think that
I don't think he's as much of an idiot
Alex you
Yeah but like
I kept thinking in this interview like
Jesus Christ this guy stupid
Like listen to this
Smite down for this week
Think about what he's actually said
By saying I saw a kung fu movie when I was out on vacation last week I was watching a lot of television
And it was a picture of a Kung Fu Academy in China
Chinese
Kung Fu teacher
Annie sez
In Chinese
No mercy
We have a government
And educational establishments
I'm weak
I'm in pain.
Alex
Okay so who wins this battle is it the use of America or characters in a cup
Movie
You understand that this is Tommy he's making a movie is a
Send accurate depiction of
Absolute
You can absolutely I would recommend
That was Bruce Lee's original
Amazing you can do that
Right
This is stupid
I saw this
Movie
And I thought
AR used
Compete with those hardened
Kung-Fu acolytes
Uniboob
Understand what is width
Ding-dongs
Differentiating between reality and movies
It's so crazy
B b b b
Like accidentally
Realizing that a lot of people just have
Sort of inability to
NCA reality
I don't know
The same way that marijuana is in Reefer Madness
You are everywhere they were coming to get you
You might
Jack be able to trace some of those
Lingering scent
Ability to differentiate reality from that as president movie
I don't know
But I should tell you that whatever the source
Savage
F****** really bad idea
You better put that
If
So
If you just
Pretend
But your enemy wants to do X
You you get to do X2 them preamp
That's bad
Where does savages
Except
Should be putting those
Like he's advocating
Anybody he thinks is an enemies
Absolutely
That's one of his big guy
Don't want to go to Kung Fu Academy
Right I would put them in a cat
Barack Obama
Here's why
Is that dude
Can't Get Enough
Dwight
What
How do I know what they really want
I'm more divisive presidency in my life I've never seen
Relishes
Angry
Deprez they will do something crazy
To justify a reaction
Clear
He's trying to provoke a war in this country
Weather
He's only a matter of whether someone goes off or not
A little 20
I express my racism
Yeah let's go ahead and do it
Tires
Cheese's
Well if you're going to do it
Also by his own logic
Already be starting
Yeah probably
This is exact same sort of rhetoric that will be going around during the Civil
Alright Sarah of like the Rock the Boat
You want you want to be able to
Is restaurant
Agonize old white man
Whatever whatever you take
Towards
Respect
Be respected as
Human
You're in town
Two old white men
As opposed to old white man making them angry
Barack is making old white man Angry
He's doing it on purpose
He knows what will make old white men x-ray existence
Existence
He real
Images of pretty real
God dammit
That's f***** up certainly has on many other occasions
Savages
We talked about amanat last episode
Alex
The 2050
Team.
And Alex was like trying to get him off the hook it was like
Don't speak
Remember that one
Rockstar Jeffy gets kicked off radio
Dependably so f****** Marina
That's the dynamic
He's been living for
Quite a while
So Alex talked to him
He did on Piers Morgan
How great Alex did
Savage said something
The fact is Alex you did a great job
And you should keep doing it
So like I said he knows better than to go play
2003 Michael Savage had a show on MSN
Yeah just mix it up in my bed
ABC is a clip of what got him fired
Let's go to a call if you have an airline Horror Story give me a ring right here on the Savage Nation
Did you have a worse case than this one
Hey Michael Savage prejudiced people dating app
There's two undercover security guard
Yeah
Somebody was smoking in the bathroom
Someone was smoking in the bathroom
What happened
I need a suggest
That Johnny might take your
How's that
Watch STD consumer Utah
Trichinosis
Okay let me know the knights call he was busy
Get me another I put it on the side of my tan
No more calls I don't care let's go to the next thing I don't care about these bums they mean nothing to me
They're all sausages
Next scene
Spectator I got him fired
Television
Advice
Record
Broadcasting World on MSNBC
And you could hear that producers
You just watching like
We shouldn't have given
Rave
Yeah they'll angst
I don't know I don't I don't know how long it show was but
Might have been a little longer than that but I have no idea
The kind of person that is
He's allowed to get away with it on radio because
Radio news
Anybody who can draw
And if you're in
For whatever Michael Savage's bring to the table you're not going to be
Turned off by him yelling s*** like that
Sucks
He's a real piece of s*** and I think
I was like when you go into other places
You don't fully control his own radio show areas
You might
F******
Yell at somebody if they're sodomite and they should die
And then all of a sudden it's a big news story that you got fired that doesn't look good for the brand
And it's not fun
You know like now I'm a billionaire and it doesn't matter to me really
Is like a really bad I slept poorly
For a couple days
How to spell slept
Wow compare
Waterbed
It was like a kind of creepy
Everybody else has a waterbed
It's probably Michael Cedric
So
Earlier clip you think it'll Bama's antagonizing old white man
Is that you
Pretty strong
Indication that he might be
And his next clip.
They're very clever don't ever underestimate your enemy hours
Very angry
Alex
That's exactly
You have someone who's as overtly
Does Michael Savage
Crackers guns
Right
Alex
Agrees with him
Always tries to play that
Begun
Everglades bear
Because he doesn't give a s*** about them taking gun from white guy
Yep
And that's really really
For Alex's
The sleight-of-hand that he likes
Play
Race
Love you Alex
Defensive of whiteness
I really don't want to die
It makes me
Sofa
Because nobody is trying to
Take the white
No one no one
Trying to do it
0 people are trying
And the end that ends
Do I know part of it
I don't know
It is a bummer
Michael Savage prescription
For what
To be done
Right
Allowed
Antagonize
All right he has another
There should be drug testing in Congress
There should be drug testing in Congress Alex
My final word
You can recognize
She's on power
I guarantee you 60%
Yeah
Little bit different it does give him the
Sort of expert
Is that you might want for like
Plant-based medicine
Books
It's nothing to be judged
Too much
And like homeopathy
Adjacent
To that sort of world
He was in his earlier career
Herbalism
But whatever is being presented as like he's a doctor
Yeah it is
Understood by
Cristal
Shell gas
What time does appearance
I know I just
Bummer
I really don't like Michael Savage
No he is at
Giant bees I the only in the only interaction
Ever had
Only a couple
I had no idea
This much
You can find somebody videos
Screaming at people
Michael Savage's like
The the final stage
Of most of these propaganda
If they had their druthers
They wouldn't suffer anybody who dis
Clear on this episode
Like there are good Arguments for gun control that just gather people
What do fuckyourself
A pure distillation of what it is they actually
Which is
Go fuc yourself
You're not me
Do you f****** Michael Savage
Expresses outright hostility
To everyone who
Is non-white
Non-straight
Women
Muslims in particular get a Hard Punch
It's not
Any other reason
He hates them
Yeah it is
Hateful angry dude it's so weird to me that you can be
Somebody that it even exists
Well the only people on the
The planet I identify with our other white males who look almost identical to
Because I mean
It seems like a psychopathy
Where it's like
I just cannot understand
And will not engage
Anybody who is not
Clinical lab
Express
Michael Savage
Cruelty and body
And has been for a long time on the radio
And that is why it makes total sense
How to use another one of these dudes
Who became big
Truck guy
Whenever absolutely
It makes total sense
Their brand is cruelty the brand is
Funny largely
Status quo
Coronavirus
Easiest
F*** that you
Structure we get to the 26
We still don't have
The big dude
The Gate of report whatever that might be
I feel a little self-conscious
Because
Of
My guess
I might be
Completely out of line on
I might be way off base
I don't know
To the next episode
And I still don't.
But it does feel to me from the
Just the context
Clues that I
Descent
It feels like it's drifting in
In that direction towards
It being a revelation
About Sandy Hook
Together video of
Like when did the Nancy Pelosi like make
When did that video where
Nancy Pelosi misspeaks for a second
Shut up about
What was that
Write 30
We caught Nancy Pelosi gone
Instead of
And that's it
You something about that like f****** Department of Education
I don't know but
Time
Especially with the fact that he
Everywhere apparel
Next episode we find out what it is
We'll see again
IMDb soul
I'm going to guess we're not going
Modify.
Tyui wood
But because the tension
This is going to kill me
The next episode
Is more interesting to me then
What the f*** in-depth do you have going on
Talking to you got your
Google find out
Maybe Wednesday
Website
You bet
Go to bed Jordan
Facebook
What is it that we have a direct Lipson haha
Confined are Twitter accounts
Sometimes we'll post up there
If you are looking for
Apartment
Dan
Just tried out a cup
Couple of different
They all offered with the pack
Episode of knowledge
Is wild
So that's the best place
That
Is
You can also find us
3 *
If you pick one letter out of
Sign eventually it will spell knowledge fight and will give you an epi
So I went on Howard Stern
And them onto the New World Order and what-have-you I don't think they have
Flint
Surly
In a co-host
Robin
Probably
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work