Alex
Around big novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
What's the longest set
You've ever seen
That's the first time you said that
200 episode
Rudolph
I don't know I mean
You ever seen
Flowers
I've seen Comics 2 hours
Patton Oswalt live
I saw the veil Crawford back in Columbia Missouri do an hour of not stop laughing
We actually were at the comedy club
In Columbia
We were sure
By the security guard
Are you younger
I think it was before I actually did,
I think it was it was previous to buy getting into
Territory for me
Once I started doing stand-up
I resent it
What does negative
Enjoyed it
Friends do
40 minute hour
Half hours.
Not not that cigars
Does the Pakistan a lot about Lavell Crawford and Alex
Correct as we are going over some present-day business
We're going over July 16th and 17th
20 nights
Which is Tuesday and Wednesday of this
Have I found some b*******
Going on in the world 16th and 17th
Down
Alex
Most
Sounds impressive
Here
I don't like a good bit of this stuff
That we're going to go over
Forget today's episode
Michelle
First of all
I'm a policy wonk
Text Elliot
Text John
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Human mangle Heimer Schmidt is that
Mima t.i. cool spelling
Cyclops
Normal spelling
The boring normal swelling
Somebody donated on an elevated level
Mercer Roberts thank you so much you are now
Business heroin
Freakishly large
Sports shirt we would appreciate it
So I was going over this and preparing it on
Anyone who pays attention
The news or social media may be aware his rally where his audience started chanting
A representative ottobar
By I'm sick of this b*******
Tone
It might come out a little bit in this
A lot of the time I like to
Play around
Blunt
In something
This episode than normal.
Well
I don't want to comment Miss
Literally about the government
But I will call I will comment on propaganda techniques
Start the show on July
This is an interesting thing Alex makes
Horrible Freudian slip in the introduction to the episode
Alive Tuesday level of transmission what
What does a globalist
Satanism perhaps
Globalism
It's possible it and everybody is capable of Miss p
To me a reason I'm
Drawing Focus today
Is because Alex is really good at the end
Like when he comes in he almost
Never makes
So rapid that gets its Global transmission
He says he'll be back Lord willing tomorrow every single day
The repetition has
Become script
So when he says this is a globalist that's a pretty big dude from the strip
And it probably would just be like haha that's funny you're stupid
But on the 17th
He says this
July 19th
18th on Wednesday on Wednesday
Trolls
Heat
Yeah cuz I I mean I don't want to
Make a mountain out of a molehill
I do not hear him
Screw up the intro very often and in 2 days twice
Stancil departures from the norm
Those are
The fuk up
I don't think it means anything I just think maybe is phoning it in a little bit even his subconscious doesn't give a s*** anymore
He starts off on a narrative about before but I felt the way he was talking about it
Deserved
A little bit of a
Classified the foundation of the CIA and others by the 50s
Hollywood
Destroy the attention span
Because you better get rid of it by the last lie
Goldfish
The Ford Foundation
They're they're terrible
Sesame Street
Coronavirus
Very idea of berseria
Create television
In order to destroy the attention
Population
That's exactly the sort of unhinged stupid
Come out of the mouth
This f****** idiot
He's relying on fake studies information meeting with terms and it completely made up
Live
In their home
It's going to destroy their attention
You'll be easily treatable
Globalist
That's really the point
Alex constantly talks about how our attention
Shorter than a gold
She heard him say it right there
Because it's a great mental image
Goldfish before they don't seem to be all that
Interbreeding
Goldfish actually have
Significant
Favorite they finish the Dostoevsky more than you can say
Either
Unfortunately I was just repeating something years ago it's been thoroughly described
This piece of salacious in Spokane
From a 2015 study the consumer insights
Team of Microsoft Canada
The study of sounds of problems
The first was that the stuff about attention span was just something that was cited in the Microsoft report
But didn't have to do with their actual research
It was allegedly from a source called statistic brain
We're taking the information from the quote
National Center for biotechnology information at the US National Library of Medicine
And the associated
Simon Maybin at the BBC reached out to all these entities and none of them could find any research
Backed up the claims that were made on Stitcher
Which was included in the Microsoft Canada report and then repeated tirelessly by dumbfucks like Alex
You want to convince everyone that the modern world is built on a satanic
Of course it also was repeated exhaustively by well-meaning but maybe not all that thorough media Outlets
Who are huntingford
Easy human interest story to report and before you know it the idea had the appearance
Credibility
We're at when in reality it might as well just been made up out of thin air
The only problem with this notion
The bigger issue is that attention span when you talk about it like this is a meaningless term
What does it mean with me
How long you can pay attention to something
How is it
Intention calculated into the measure
I mean obviously if you were trying to pay attention
Intuit longer than if you were
Or if you're interested in the things you're paying attention to you stuck
Could be able to pay attention
Do longer than 9 seconds
Is this alleged attention span sad had any real-world meeting could watch a movie or TV show without being
Wheatley overwhelmed in-laws
It doesn't mean any
People who study attention would never think about attention in the way Alex
What is presenting the ID
Humans pay attention to things differently depending on how much it appears the situation there in requires them
It's like effort
In that way
You kind of able to discern how much effort
Task is going to require
And then you subconsciously decide whether or not you're in
Interested and exerting that amount of effort in the service of completing that
300,000 people just turned
It's not working
Subconscious conscious decision that you're making and I respect you for it
The very idea of what Alex
2 talkin about is to
What is it about
Is it the physical TV screen
Because if that's the case
Exactly
Could be caused by watching Alex
Cuz she
Is it the constant
Changing of topic
Because if it's that Alex jumps
From subject to subject of the f-far quicker and more disoriented
Racine
Distraction game of vaguely referencing
Been jumping to another subject without ever getting into what he was talkin
He's talkingshit
There's no reality to the idea that your actual attention
Spanish being shortened
And the only possible approach
Is possibly
Society modernized
Our ability to convey information forces
With the Advent of the internet the ability to disseminate that information in little chunks
Has allowed people to
Taking information without exerting a great deal of attention
Which is possibly train people to expect not
Have to pay attention
The things were very long while still expecting
Some
Information
Expressed
If that's
Conspiracy
Lady wants
Listening
I probably also bring up that you know if that's the
He's an active participant
Especially these days
Completely obsessed with memes
He's run meme contest he calls himself the meme machine
The other weirdos like Carpe donktum on his show whose only relevant in the world of this point is that they make
Memes are probably the method of conveying information that requires the least attention imaginable
Totally fine people information
Exerting is zero
A name in his
In any way
You can still
Require memes
Any vacuum
Now but you can also still resent that you have
Have to do so
You know like
Of course he does
S*** on me and very well
Position
I'm not I'm not
Do you know deriding the entirety of memes and
Culture
Means of communication through me and I'm just saying but like
If you're concerned
Train to have a shorter attention span
You should dick suspect
What is memes right now
Opposed
Or I don't know cartoon
Political cartoons
If you got it it takes a while to get all the drivers figured out and then you have to figure out what the f*** it is he's trying to say in the first
Apex that is better
To be a
Recurring theme
I can find no evidence of the globalist
Therefore soundation publishing a plan to ruin the public attention
The media so they be able to
People wouldn't be able to remember what was
Being talked about previously
Can't find any Declassified documents
Festivus
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
Huey's from protocol number 13
Agents taking on to our press from among the goyim will at our orders discuss anything which is inconvenient
For us to issue directly an official document
While quietly amid the din of the discussion
We shall carry through such measures as
We wish and that offer them to
The publication as accomplished fact
The abrogation of a matter once settled
And immediately
The Press will distract
The current of thought
Grandparents
Have we not train people always something new
In the discussions of these new questions will throw themselves those of the brainless dispensers of Fortune
Who are not able even now to understand that they have not the remotest conception
About the matters
Which they undertake
You know it.
Is absolutely an example of
The difference in communication
Because what that really just said there was like
Forever
It's very similar to the ideas expressed by Alex
It's one of countless passages in the protocols about the need to distract the volume so they won't get in the way of the elders evil plan
Interesting
Medium
Every Super Bowl Sunday
He believes that matter sublimating their Warrior instincts through fake Warfare
But his bigger issue I promise you this
Is that the whole thing
Sports are a distraction
He asserts that you could know everything about the New World Order and their evil plan
But instead you know all this
Quarterback
And it's a waste of your time and attention
We further distracted with amusements game pastimes passions people palaces
Soon we shall begin through the press to propose competitions and art
Sport of all kinds
These interest will finally distract their minds from questions and which we should find ourselves
Compelled to oppose them
Growing bored or just accustomed to reflect
And form any opinions of Their Own
People will begin to talk in the same tone as we because we alone shall be offering them new directions for thought
Okay so they're just going to Django
I bet you'd look a lot of globalist blocks
Fraud
Specifically used in all sorts of
Nazi propaganda
Seems like a lot
You know it is
Kind of an understandable impulse
Do you know what I mean like it seems odd
Hundreds and hundreds of millions of people would just
On their own
Choose
Fascinated by this
Like it's something that is a part of our culture
Except they're so the idea has to be
Well there's a reason for it
Instead of just
I want people like it
And it just kept growing
Our brains
Narrative
Someone doing
Something
All of us
Together
Independently
Conspiracy to
Need to organize things
In a way that fits fits in with that.
The tendency of
Your brain
The protocols of the Elders of Zion are so Insidious
Is that it has that
Roots real
And then at the same time
Swatson so many
This is weird
It's a mess it's almost like an overlay you put on top of the world
So on the 16th
I was struck by
You forget about menu
You constantly relearn
If you're paying
Become
Extremist religious preaching extremist right-wing talk
Shrek it's so crazy
That you just
If you listen to his show a bunch of probably just
For granted the fact
Supposed to be a political commentator
And he's on the air screaming about God in the literal devil all the time
But it's very strange
If you just allow it to exist on question
Like I was listening to this on my
What the f*** is that how is this
How are people not
How do you not just see this be like
I could get the f*** out of here I signed up for libertarianism
I told I like I don't know what you're doing
You're talking about the f******
Shoot devil
I can't I can't hang out anymore
Situation
Incredible
We develop in the art box
We can destroy universes
Angel
Be there just service
That's why the Fallen one pizza
Fallen ones
Consciously understanding full spectrum
Spiritual deception
Meant to make us give up
So
Like I said I can't stress enough how f****** weird it is just as
Extremist
Religious
Fundamentalism
Paired with
Right-wing
Extremist
Tendencies
I can't be clear about this
It is not going well
No I usually end up with like
Not good
Yeah
Expresses his belief that the enemy
Are unrelentingly lion
Documents at Alex's reference
In the past I have a pretty good going to be found in any Declassified Ford Foundation
Soros documents
Similar ideas to show up
Crazy protocols but how
Is playing
Universal protocol number two
Where's the scotch
In the hands of the states of today there is a great force that creates people
Depressed the park
Play by the Press is to
Requirements
Be indispensable
Give voice to the complaints of the people and express into create discontent
It isn't the media that the Triumph of freedom
Finds Its incarnation
But the goyim States
Not knowing how to make use of this Force
It is falling into our hands
There's an entire section protocol 12
I also prefer called number 3
But they will be compelled to offer us international power of a nature that Viet position
Gradually to absorb all the
State forces of the world
Informa super government
What you see here is a discussion of a plan to use the media that they've taken over
To lie and deceive and manipulate
An order that they shall be able to wear people down
To the point where they just give up
And allow them to create a world government without any need for Bloodshed exactly
Alex is talking about
I'm starting to work on a little bit of a theory
And I promise the rest of this episode isn't just being like haha Alex is a PT protocols
Although that would be fun
I thought about it I realized I realize how to be matically that would get really exhausted for the listener
But I do want to point out
Are just a couple of insta
From the first fifty
Keep minutes of one of his episodes
And they very clearly traced back to The Prado
And I'm starting to work on this. It whenever Alex
Doesn't offer a source on something
30 claims
Classified or admitted he's just referencing the protocols of the Elders of Zion
But he knows that he can't openly start preaching about this
Debunked 80
Cosmetics
Without losing all but the most
People in his face
Which probably isn't
Enough to keep
The bills paid
So
He pretends
That there's some sort of
It's in the Congressional Record or whatever and then never site it
Because he's really just repeating
Protocols
That's a theory I have I don't know is that true
He brings up something in the future
Classified
Is it midday admitted back in the black
You're back at this era or whatever that I don't have a citation for and he's not specific about
I'm going to see if it Tracy
Is back to the protocols
And I guarantee
I guarantee
Victor will at least
Be some overlap 60%
I think that's probably fair but
At this point
Still iPod
Not even fair to call it a theory
I hypothesize
And I will apply the scientific method
This July 16th is Tuesday
On Wednesday Trump has his rally where
Things took a turn for the authoritarian
Fascistic
But on Tuesday Alex is way ahead of the Curve
Ant-Man
He is
Just screaming about Ela Nail Bar
Real heart
It's pretty gross
A lot of the time it's
This whole
Stringy
Justin being like
She comes from
The high-class Somali bloodlines
And they're slavers
And so he starts
Trying to
Scream about how Somalia was involved
In the slave trade and Muslims are all
The blame for slavery
Sure
I'm not going to I'm not going to get into a ton of that but that's just sort of context
For some of these clips
Is first one here Alex
Is screaming about
We're told our bad to remember that children was the opposite everyone tried to get in here because we treat women and children better
To everybody else and that's the truth on Omar has a chip on her shoulder because she comes from us
Orange hellhole
It's all about Conquest conqueror their own lusts for power so the somalis
Toilet paper to wipe
Their asses
They can't produce electricity
Tell you every Somali Ivermectin
They're God's chosen and they're going to take the world over and I'm going to learn from them
You're about your inbred
But he just say all somalis are a bunch of inbred crazy people
Stuff like that
You can't say things like that but then pretend that you have a nuanced political point
Note outright
Racism
That's just outright white supremacy white nationalism whatever
Whatever label you want
To put on it
It depending on what's the time
Yeah that's Stark I mean there's really nothing to even like if you hear somebody say that you just go okay
You're done
I can't even imagine like a
Straight newsperson complaining about
People of a certain ethnicity yelling at them on the
Now that's part of it you all are a bunch of inbred crazy people
Complaining about like
Itself
Crazy-house far gone
Alex's
We just
You know
That criticism doesn't even land
Other complaints
Representative Omar
And here is
I'm going to get into
For Isis
We let
Scorpion
Brown recluse a black widow rattlesnake bites you
Doing that over that song
Decorative trumpet already sent out
Alex is doing
Hi babe
They're just trying to
I mean
I don't I don't understand how I could okay
Like
Can you do that
I don't think you can
But it seems like this is a crime
Incitement to violence
Like he's admitted to Crime you know now on Thursday
Did that so he's bought I know
Charged with a crime I imagine myself in like one of those bodyswap comedies
We're like I end up like
Record scratches I end up in
Did Trump's body welder
How do you stop it
Cuz you definitely still feeding it and making it worse
I think about that even a person with the best intentions
Dropped into the circumstance like
These people that you have
You have fed and lied down
Like they are not going to stop
It's very scary
No I remember specifically this
Team from
Speaker for the Dead
Sequel
It may have been that whenever it may have been the one
One of the main
Starts
Inciting all of these people
Turning them into a mob and he's
He's describing it so well this feeling of
Part of
And almost like
You just letting your will be become part of the mob will and how that feels really good
And then
He was use the one leading it and then it
Just got out of control cuz
Once the mob is there it doesn't matter what an individual says or does
And so out of it you just realized
What have I done
It's almost like you're you're
Dissociate
Are you from
There's that feeling of like
Becoming absorbed into the hole
Is used
So naked
Two Play-Doh dangerous
Positive feelings you have a being absorbed
Intergroup
People
Because it feels so good and it's so powerful
Can we do
Real f*****-up things you can only Direct
You can't control it
So that isn't even that is.
You know you can
What kind of wood Alex's also do exact
And qanon
And it hopefully
I don't know just
Did not Lobby prices
She's not a terrorist
Alex Jones is an over white nationalist who can't handle criticism
Renata white person
It'll take any opportunity
Scream bulshit
Send it positions without making them
In November 2016
I meant were on trial in Minneapolis for passports
Presumably to train with ISIS
These were young man and they were facing
30 to 40 years in prison
For their crimes
As a newly elected Congress person in Minnesota ilhan Omar wrote to the judge not in an attempt to lobby for
Approaching the situation from the perspective of restorative justice
As opposed to wanted punitive
She was one of Thirteen individuals or organizations that wrote To The Judge expressing this
In the letter she points out that incorporating these been for what amounts to
To basically their whole lives
In effect
Helps terrorist recruit
Society was no expectations of the to be 50 or 60 year old released prisoner
It will do that with distrust and revulsion
Such punitive measures do not only lack ecstasy
They inevitably create an environment in which extremism can flourish
Aligning with the presuppositions of terrorist recruitment
That is Americans do not accept you in
Continue to AAA trivialize your value
Instead of being a nobody be a martyr
She doesn't tell the judge
What they should do
Rather she offers a perspective that this sort of fanaticism
Forward
Do uses the word fanaticism to describe these
Can be fought most effectively with compassion
The fanaticism grows out of feelings of systematic
Which is why are we should all be working
She doesn't save these men should not be held responsible
For their actions
Just if there's a better way to deal with it these situation
Then by locking somebody up for deca
I think the important point to really highlight here is that these men didn't commit any violent act they had.
Intention of joining a terrorist organization
And that could mean that they're not
The point of possible Rehabilitation
Right you're welcome to have whatever feelings about that
That you want
That you can probably have
It's a good idea to lock them up or it's a bad idea
Eric
I think you'd probably have a reasonable argument
You're not too far gone if you encourage
Locking up people who make overtures to join a terrorist
I don't think that's beyond
The payoff I disagree with that but I don't think you're a monster for thing
It's entirely off base
Use this story is proof that Elon Omar or support
The Twist the story like this is to take a person's
Compassion
And use it as a weapon against
Which is something that Alex would never be doing if
Omar was
Alex constantly has Vox day on his show as a guest
Who legitimately celebrate
Terrorist Anders Breivik
Is a freedom fighter
Fredericton
Plan something awful
He killed tons
If Alex had any intellectual consistency
He could never endorse or give a platform to someone like Vox day
It's simultaneously pretend that Omar's letter to a judge
Is proof that she's a terror
He can do both
Because he's a white supremacist
Who is totally fine with white terrorism that's directed against the
What is multiculturalism
And he believes that
Appeals to restorative justice where marginalized people are welcomed into the body of society
Is an appeal to Terror
It's just that simple
You can make all this make sense
Yeah it does make sense all you have to do is consider through the prism of
Yeah
He's fine with white terrorism
Done by people who are afraid of multiculturalism
East
That appeals to multiculturalism are in themselves terrorism
I don't know because he's a f******
Super white identity dude
Yeah that's what it is
I mean if you if you think that any encroachment
Soupremacy
A terrorist Act
Yes I suppose in his
How this makes exact
Yeah
Because his behavior
Strongly implies
Yeah I've always been I've always been confused as to why people do
Understand why you would
Very obvious
Like okay
Good decision America I was
I was 12 years old and America
Bomb device
F****** home
And my mom died and now I'm 17 I don't have any job I don't have anything
And I know that America Center bombed
Large group of people who are chanting
Xenophobic
President
Stop them
Exactly
Reasonable
It's not
It's not a good thing
I'm going to stop just short of calling you can understand
Not it's
You're able to
Extend your brain
But yes
So Alex
Wants to yell a bunch about how the Muslims started the slave trade
In
Somalia
You get really mad
That
You can't get a map
The come up on his
His
Overhead cam
Can start screaming while pointing
At the backdrop he's got a map there
Google Maps
Africa
Right there
Pacific Ocean
What's the temperature outside
Muhammad was a slaver
History
Shut up
Well
You just don't get that from MSNBC level of professionalism
One of the reasons that they show ID I still appreciate
Remind yourself
Just imagine Wolf Blitzer yelling about like walking away from his desk
Make me feel.
OverWatch to get to buy white man country
It's insane to imagine the sort of behavior being done by literally anybody to him
Type of relationship but not in the same way Tucker knows better
He got get a trial by fire when
You tried to do the bow tie
4 years
You realize like
Don't f*** around it's not worth it
Alex
But that also was a testament to it like how much Alex's brand is
Right like there's never a the he doesn't come in the next day like
What the exception
Of maybe whenever
May or may not have threatened that
Lawyer
Required
So if is Mexico if Alex talks more about these
Slaves
The world
How much
America sucks
Right over here
Because of slave ships
Alex would you like to open up a conversation about missionaries
Fair enough
No no no
Open up a conversation about you know tons of
The colonization efforts that were masquerading as planned
Really just
Brutal exploitation in
Resources
Nobody is nobody is
The history of no one needs to feel
Guilty
To move forward live together
That's what we need to do
Obsessing about the idea of feeling guilt
About the long
Distance
Past
Is only a way to not deal with these
Right
That will keep these
The problem and that's what Alex wants
There's a star
There's a stark difference now as
Says it's kind of
As the question is becoming more and more
Clear
It's becoming more and more
One group
Like alien Omar
And
Notice America
His failures
And use that information
Into Improvement
That's the idea
And then the other choice
They are trying to improve America
Sing everybody
Yeah that's it
There's a visions of the future and wanted
Hopeful
Unwanted
Darkened
Emma's next CLEP Alex fits more stuff about Omar
I mean I know it's not
Why do I say
I know the title
Flavors
Out of Somalia
What does he talk about boobies
Pirates
Is it about the idea that people think you talk about titties
Talk about that video
Spell consist
He loves using the word boobies
But also knows there's like
I got to make sure they know that I'm not a blue-footed booby
Get your mind out of the gutter
It's not you could just
And they have a right to rule
Ml
Enel kidnapped
Are you a racist
So I mean all you could see here is just a building up of
The Narrative against her
Yep
Will you see this on the Tuesday and then Wednesday
See Trump's rally it's not to the other it's
They were living in a
Appointed
Acceleration
Surroundings
Yep and the targeting of this woman
Is so severe
Yeah so scary
So in his next life Alex
Let's talk more about her letter
But you sent to this judge
And I want to point out that there are just factual lies
How do you say
Flashlight
Etax.com
Flashback Bradford
Judge
To show Mercy to Isis terrorist
The story
Attention
That
These individuals were
Freedom Fighters
Feeble
Shantae their freedom fighters
Today is a freedom fighter
Literally
So I
She doesn't she didn't say that you called them
Is fanaticism
Call the extremism
So this is just factually inaccurate
You would make that kind of factual yet accurate
Is if you were more interested in the perception that you painting
As opposed to the reality
Which is very key
Alex just talked about how
From Somali royalty
And that her family it was involved enslaving
I don't speak to anything
Other than
Her skin color
And he says literally that she doesn't look like other African
Right
So he said he uses that as sort of his defense for why he thinks that
When she comes from higher class Somali stock
Which is not good
Is he actually just trying to say that she's of fair-skinned which is why
No evidence
To defend these claim
British
200 years ago and I know somalis have all those big castles and it's life shift
Serums
You know you're from the upper ruling are the class everything is going to be going to show Oswego
I am Somalia Royals today
My American red white blue petunias
That a big old Selassie
Bacon burger for yourself
Seeing Lee
Offense
The amount it's the size of a peanut beer
Impression that he's doing
The fact that his brain immediately ghost
To have a big old bacon burger
This is hateful
We get sort of
Ostial on Omar business
Because Alex
Coming back from break
He's a real weird mood
Terrifying profit
Of what's to come
I was thinking this morning when I saw that flesh eating bacteria is spreading all over the US from illegal aliens
Barbosa going to release a bio-weapon more than blowing up
Amish witches
Do it
EXO
Intelligence agencies right now smell by attack
Giant right wing attack on some groups with a whole bunch of right-wing patches that he was false flag
They don't want us there when they have witnesses
What happened
Showing his cards a little bit worried that they receive in the present
Or probably I mean you know you see that
These caches of weapons that are found
You see these groups
Recognizes on some level they probably going
To be a rash of right-wing violence
There's a decent
And no
Probably have that is
The park
Is just in case
Such
Man that cheating
You know
F****** T800 career
I feel I feel helpless in the face of somebody who is
Actively
Inspiring and
Inciting violence
Narrative
Saying that when that violin
Has carried out it has nothing
To do with
And we'll all be just passed
It's terrible
Here we signed Alex once again spread
He talking point about immigrants being the carriers of disease
Unfortunately his dumbass
Complete flop
The flesh eating bacteria
Flesh-eating bacteria is a condition that's very scary
Centivax very rapidly spreading
Decaying of your flesh
It's visually really f*****
Visceral
In the same way
Perfect condition to attach to the population
According to the CDC since 2010 between 712
Condition occur annually in the United
And here's the thing to everyone who knows anything about flesh eating bacteria nose
Most of the reports of it happened during the summer
Why
Because almost everyone catches flesh eating bacteria from swimming or falling into warm water
When Alex
The summer
What is the arbitrarily decide to blame it on
Immigrant
Because even over white nationalist would blame immigrants or anything he felt he could get away with
A quick look through the stories about flesh eating bacteria from recent days show a clear trend
Nashville been contracted flesh eating bacteria while kayaking
Virginia woman recovering from flesh eating bacteria
She said she's recovering after she went swimming in Norfolk
Milton woman contracted flesh-eating bacteria after scalloping in Port st.joe
You're the tough one
From CBS
Quote Florida man contracts
Eating bacteria without you
Even touching the water
However if you read the article in the fourth paragraph you got a clue of what might be up
Tyler King
I've got a small theory on it how that guy
No
God dammit
Anyone who isn't
Demonize immigrants would never blame an uptick in reports of
Flesh eating bacteria in the summer on immigrants
They would know that this is a very well understood phenomenon
It happens every year
Alex f****** care about the truth
Disgraceful
Embarrassing
Disseminating there is no two ways about it
I just to make this very blunt
The CDC is very clear
Quote it's very rare for someone with necrotizing fasciitis
Spread the infection to other
It's not considered a condition that has a risk of being highly transmittable person-to-person
They don't even routinely prescribed antibiotics for people who are in close proximity to people
Because it just doesn't
Spread that way
It spreads from people who are at risk
Swimming in warm water
When you talk about it risk certain conditions
Like you know having cirrhosis
To the liver
Diabetes make you at higher risk
Of getting the bacteria but then
Time if you have an open wound
Or if you fall in
You get cut by something you have a higher risk
Right
Serious researchers are concerned that we're seeing an uptick in cases
Is a bacteria but it's not because of immigrants
It's because of climate
As water temperatures rise the amount of time the ocean water is at a temperature where the bacteria can live and reproduce
Increases
Which in turn increases the chances of someone catching it
Even so it's not something that most people should worry about all that much
Cases of people who don't have open wounds a preexisting
Think addition to put them at risk catching flesh eating bacteria
RX
Eating lire
Against
It's very clear A2B
There's no two ways
Yeah it's
F***** up that's the
Entire
Republican policies
Make the world worse
And then
The people who are running interference
The propaganda for it
Blame all that s*** not on the Republic
Policy platform
But on immigrants
And Sprite
Making the world at workplace
And then making the world a worse place allows them to
To blame
Immigrants from
Making the world
Play Perpetual vacation
Machine
So Jordan at this point on the 16th
Pier
Alex have a gun
Almost
Gas
When I heard who it was
Who cares Kaitlin Bennett I want to say very clearly
That like that I generally prefer these episodes is
I will listen to Alex and when he says something really
Substantial episode
Digging to the things that he's saying and then move on
So are you already written
Researched all the stuff about
Alana Omar in her letter to the judge
Sunvox day f****** shows up yeah
I can't believe that he's the best examples that refutes Alex's position about what he was saying earlier
Episode
8 very bizarre it's almost like he's
F****** with you you are making this happen
Episode 9 we do a modern-day episode mate
Can perfectly
Okay are we living in a simulation where you're actually the main character
I hope not it's terrible job
Appreciating the circumstances for myself to begin
This isn't what I would choose a lot of people have a little bit of self-flagellation in
Yeah baby
Vox day one of the things he wants
He wants to spend a good amount of time complaining about Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Rashida tlaib
Call Bart.
People that are real
F******
Scared
Eddie says a couple things that I
Cinco just like
Being born in the United States doesn't make anyone an American anymore than being born in a manger
Jeremy Jesus Christ account
And the idea that the is Magic
The idea that geography
Determines genetics and nationality
It is a
Literally every major thinker
Dating back to the Chinese sages would have laughed at
You're on real dangerous territory here when you are like yes we're all citizens but some of us are more citizens
Yeah especially when you're specifically talking about for congress people of
Color
Really f******
Dangerous
Bad idea
Good once you introduce that it's possible that there's levels of citizenship
Course they're all citizens but they're not American
Comparable a level
But apart
What I'm saying is we want to be apart from each other but also equally separate but equal
Adolphe beef
Thrilled
About Trump in his camp
Because what comes next
If he doesn't do this
Will be way worse
Which is
Kind of f***** up but then the way Alex responds to it I think is even
More f***** up and indicates
He knows what's going on
You f****** Intuit
For those who are concerned that
Trump is an extremist in putting people in concentration camps
They had better
Embrace and accept
Endorse and support
His
Boomer Civic nationalism
Because
They're really going to like what comes after that a lot less whether it's from the left
Or from the right
Because
The history of
Human migration has always been accompanied by large-scale Warren balkanization
Recognizes this and he's attempting to get in the way of it
Everybody
Describe that versus a fastest model which will probably go towards
So he's basically saying is probably coming but it's also the left
Fault we're the ones
Causing right-wing fashion
Play it's a good way to be like people on the left have been warning that looks like your head
Hey you know you call people racist long enough they're going to f****** start throwing the n-word around
You're going to make them races ya calling them racist
Cuz of that you've made me a fascist
What am I supposed to do you called me at enough like f*** you yeah I am alright
What we should have done what we should have done is nothing
And then allowed them to create it on their own
I met wait no
We still get to right-wing fast
Kind of literally is going to be
You're right
It's a trap
Who admires a brevik
Not a small detail
About this s*** head
He has this to say about
Congress
Reiterating
The fact that he's willing to take on these issues publicly the fact that he's willing to take the media's Overton window and smashed
Completely with regards to
The fact that these
Women are not Americans and do not belong there
Again they're US citizens
But they're not Americans by any definition of family
So there an enemy with it within
F***
Right
Will I be presented all he wants is like they hate the
What I'm actually talking about it's not something else
So nebulous
Impossible to
Define
Like the idea
Any sort of criticism of the country
Is makes you not an American citizen
Goodnight America
I would say
Trump got elected
Alex
Is then condemning himself
Well yeah but
Real American
Occupied government
Is there a was there fog today were making him be on American Dad
Trying to get that sense that everything is someone else's
Longer conversations
F****** stupid and Alex trying to sell voxspace comic book
And to that end
We we get now into
The 17th
And Alex
First hour of his show on something
I find
One of the more disturbing
Things it's Loki
Incredibly disturbing
It may not appear to be immediate
I think I can
Explain why
It has to do with the
Detention centers
For immigrants
And the Border Patrol
Alex
Nuremberg
I assume we'll see
Alex's found a video
Candace Owens
Put out
A is him introducing
Where she singing with the two of the most anybody has ever done
USA
So you can hear Alex things that she came out with this video she's not with turning points
USA anymore she's filming this on her own
He's presenting this like a current video
What up
Video is from
It was posted on her Facebook on September 7th 2018 I assumed was streamed live because she does mention that
So this is in no way current news
Also she went to a nice facility in Broward County Florida
Announces using it to somehow refute the argument that AOC
The detention centers on our border
The only thing Florida borders is the water
That's where they get all that flesh eating
Arkansas video proves literally nothing
And neither do the Clips Alex shows to try and build help build her case
For reasons I'll explain later
Her videos almost a year old
From halfway across the country
Where the problem
Disgust
Classic propaganda
Because I would know that he
Can't really address the actual complaints it's very serious issues
You said they're being brought up about ice border patrol about you
Trumped overtly supporting
Utilities
He moved the goalposts
People are talking about detainee abuse in Camp
So he provides footage of a discussion of camp
What two pretended Deb is just overblown virtues
Signal being out of their minds
I try to be sensitive about this and I try to avoid
Comparing things to the Holocaust
But Alex is literally mimicking Nazi propaganda strategies
So I really don't know what else I can do in the circle
Many people forget the during World War II the Nazis were knocked
Completely open about what they were doing in their camp
People
Have this image in their head the
It wasn't
Secretive
Try to cover that up
Right
They tried to create a public perception that
Does bad as everyone
Stories
Is that were saying that they were really awful
We're almost certainly
From the US Holocaust Memorial Museum
Positive stories were fabricated
It is part of you plan to step
One booklet printed in 1941 glowingly report the in occupied Poland
German authorities had put Jews to work
Buildclean Hospital
Set up soup kitchens
And provided them with newspaper
Vocational training
What are the essential pieces of the Grandeur deception was teresian
Again from the US Holocaust
Memorial Museum
German
Did the East perform labor
To be implausible in reference
Two elderly Jews disabled War veterans and prominent musicians are artists
The Nazi regime
Publicized existence of creation
As a residential
Where elderly or disabled German and Austrian Jews could retire
And live out their lives
Obviously this was bulshit
It served as little more than a stop along the way before the victims were sent to their ultimate that's
Summation and as a place where Nazis could use the place to
To help mold public
Perception about their activities
In 1940 for the Red Cross wanted to tour
But the Nazis knew they couldn't allow that
No outright to the Red Cross facility
They decided to allow the Red Cross to torture Asian
Quote as an elaborate hoax
The SS authorities accelerated deportation
From the ghetto shortly before the visit
An order the remaining prisoners to beautify
How to plant garden
Houses and renovate Barrett
DSS Authority
Social and cultural event
For visiting
I'm not necessarily trying to say that our government is currently produced
Eurasian staad Style
I'm saying Alex
The strategy of neglecting accusations of abuse of people in custody at one place by pointing to the Optics of a
Completely different place is directly out of the Nazi propaganda
The Playbook
The Nazis did such a good job with their propaganda films about duration gstaad
The reaction many people had was to wonder quote
Waikato residents appeared to be
To live it better more luxurious life than many Germans and wartime
You may have noticed that Alex
Similar comments
They're nicer than
Camp he dropped his daughter off
I'm infuriated for the children of America who nobody gives a s*** about on the left
Well they have their fake paid protesters they're pretending the people
Inside you're going through anything
And it's nicer than any public school system that I've ever
Seen in my life
That's the true
The policies that I support from the Republican party that have left these children in this horrible
Situation are what the left is not taken
Seriously and ignoring whenever they talk about our
Concentration camps which are also the policies
Of the party that I f******
Support
Now the obvious difference here is that the ice people probably didn't create
Completely manufactured reality
Experience
It might just
Very well have been as nice and well-run as she says it
I need the stress in this case it's
What's about the government creating a false perception that the media
Why would they bother when people like Alex and Candice are willing to do all that work for them
And it seems like people don't really care
Something that made her video at least seven immigrant children have died in US
I make no mistake about this this isn't
The problem this is a nice prob
Any predates
Obama is definitely to share some blame in the current situation
But it would be delusional say that the Trump Administration is
Things much worse
And allowing conditions
To worsen
I want I want
Just make this clear
Me to misconstrue the point that I make
I'm not in any way saying
The camp
We are running or on par with
The camps that were run by the
I'm not I'm not making any kind of direct
Comparison Thayer
I'm talking
Specifically about this strategy
Used
In order to shift public
Perception
Of the reality
Right
When you have ice
Border patrol
Facilities
That are the subject
Conversation
People in Congress
People who are concerned parties
Daisy OU
People who are human rights
Would you have people having those conversations
About this
Specific
For Alex
Talk about
Something else
Entirely in order to
Deflect from
The original issue
That is
Specifically
Monopoly strategy
Employed
To trick
The world's Community into
Being pacified and not taking the issue seriously
Which interesting Lee enough
Sounds very similar to something that was ascribed
An anti-Semitic
Propaganda
Really drive home that he thinks
He thinks but she just put this video out
I was coming up today
Credible
Powerful
Procedure for third fourth
Detention Center
He's presenting this is a current thing that he doesn't even more
Someone comes out she's really pissed
Rabbits facility
These are like Informer nice hotels and stuff
We going
She wants you to go viral
A few hours
Hand shooting a
Well guess what
I saw the left this morning at 5 a.m.
Screw you
She wants to go viral we're going to help
Because it's put it up a couple hours ago
F****** b*******
Alex
Is very unclear about this
Still talking about
Candace Owens and I thought he was talking about her
Specifically
He's talking about some other local Fox affiliate reporter
Who has a social media account
This thing
Platform
It's a sort of relief
Candace Owens
We need a little palate cleanser and there's something kind of fun
Award winner
A car with a parlor account
But you just a conservative or open
Facebook alternative
You're not supposed to
So
This is just another one of these social media upstarts where people have been kicked off Facebook and Twitter have tried to create their own homes
Open telegram
Parlay
Pronounce like the French verb to speak
I just started calling a parlor
So the official pronunciation of the Parlor
But it's spelled parley that's how it.
Parler is how you spell the French
Yeah it wasn't it wasn't spelled
I guess people are just quitting
Official pronunciation
Back against the French pronunciation
Reply poem that's supposed to be about free speech and free expression
It seems like a profoundly Rocky start for the creator of the site 290 be allowed to call the
Due to crushing anti-french bias
On the part of the mob
Yeah why didn't you just call it
Freedom page exact
Since launching a parlor has gotten into a bit of a feud with gab has gotten into a beef
And most people think that the site kind of sucks
It's not scaled
To the amount of users
So there's often like
Slow down glitching
It's our thing it's right.
Experience
A June 15th and daily. Point out the Candace Owens herself is only made 13
Total post on the site
And hadn't posted anything
January
Because why would she
She's still on Twitter
Your Griff doesn't really run on diminished levels of attention
It's good to signal to these alternatives
Twitter be like yeah we can use the real thing that you're going
Going to refuse to pronounce the name correctly cuz your name
Yeah they are
Swing social media
Alex makes an announcement
About video
So he took the video of Candace Owen
From a year ago
Into the video
Okay
Pretending the camps are all cool kids
And look at look what he says about social media
Powerful migration Detention Center
You need to get to shout I guess those bands are really working
Alex's pool Twitter
Publicly
No I guess they still have some sort of
I guess
That's not good this is why I
Concerned whatever the social media fan started
I know that there
Should had their Bad actors they'll find a way around it
But they still have
You just
You cancer
There's no real level of
Control that you can exert that will actually
Keep people like Alec
Out
He'll get in the pool somehow he's going to take a s*** while he's in
It's just it it's just too much data
There's no way that you
So a.m. is next clip
Make the correction about his coverage of Kansas
And when I heard this I was certain he's like how I found out that it was from last September
Correction
Crashing cuz I videos the morning and I was watching this Candace Owens video like 5 in the morning
Monkey shooting this video
Shino the video inside these centers
Michelle it's super nice
Did I miss the 2 second Forge is like this is coming out to film crew
Why does she showing all this
We all should be angry
You certainly are
I can't believe that he thought to make a correction and it wasn't that this is almost a year old video
Like how it's amazing to me
No he said that you didn't have a film crew she was doing it by herself
But you did he didn't see the whole part correct
Because in the video she mentions her film crew
September 2018
About that because it's
Obviously I'm wrong
Brings up those out
Pieces that he added
To her story
In order to add proof
That these places
Will notice
Texas and California and Arizona
Which watching footage
Released yesterday
Showing exactly
She said she found in Florida
The same
They're all the same
Play selected
Clips from the sap video that was released free
But he's being
Dishonored
This video is about a camp in Carrizo Springs Texas
Human Services
Alex play some clips you know where the kids are playing sports
Reading textbook
No idea how he
From the DHHS spokesman Mark Wahlberg the reason for Carrizo Springs
Sup is not children to stay in border patrol stations any longer than they need
You probably don't trust me so here he is saying that
The reason for Carrizo Springs and the reason why we spend this up again not to allow
Children to stay in Border Patrol Station any longer than they need to
Oh so let me know
This AP video is explicitly about a DHHS Center that has been set up
Because of how on Save ice and Border Patrol
Factors are
That's not my interpretation of the video
Here's another part of this two-and-a-half minutes
And make this point
Then various branches of federal
Patrol
Across the Rio Grande Valley the Department of Homeland Security's Inspector General
Had no access to showers
This video is
Two-and-a-half
Minutes long
You just select
Actively taking out the
The parts help him build his
False mirror
If you need this to be any BoRics
Please listen to how this report ends
Who runs the company that took the contract to run the center
Explicitly under the condition that the government allow the children quote
Unfettered access to human rights lawyers lawmakers and the media
And every response that we've done for Orr
It's been to keep
Kids out of CBP jail
So let me be clear I'm not saying that this DHHS facility is a good thing and I still think
Constituted an appropriate attention
But it's a completely different
And in fact in that clip
It's very clear that the people who are running it specifically
Of the very unsafe things that are the things that they do
See you talkin about it complaining about
So if you're keeping score
Alex Jones has made an emergency video that has to go viral
Biking
Vining an almost
Dear old ring
From Candace Owens is Crypt we Florida detention
Concentra
Keep children out of ice and border patrol centers
Were they often don't have access to shower
Alex is presenting
These two things
It's some kind of a debunked
Atrocities that are being reported out of my
Wichita you all you need to know
He doesn't give a f*** about what's real
He doesn't give a f*** about those kids
He doesn't give a f*** about the truth
A f*** about doing a good job
If you're trying to do a good job as a journalist
He's failed miserably
But it's important to remember
He's not trying to be a journalist or even a pundit
Consider this
If you were trying to do a good job of creating the image of a modern duration
Can start for his followers to accept the reality
Understand how people like him
Like
So these guys now are all running
Just so they can
Allow children to
And people to be kept
Did the Border
In order to try and discourage other people from
And also just
To be cruel because they
And so they're creating
Because they know
That a lot of the
People who support them a lot of people who are necessary for the gp2 remaining
Empower
Wouldn't
Fans of murder
So they're lying to them
Their own
Their own people would suggest
They know how
Evil it is what they're doing
You know and it's a lie
I just don't
I mean they know they don't just know they're lying they know they're lying in service of
Cruelty and murder
So that's what I want
I know I'm nice I'm constantly struggling
With that experience it fresh
Whenever you
Care
It's tough I don't know I mean whatever you lying
Finally you're doing it for a reason
You're aware of that
They don't I don't see anyway Alex to do this just
Coincidence
No this is specific and Direct in on purpose Alex
Or whoever who works for him
Took the time to watch this
Is Two and a Half Men at 8
Pipi's
To take the clips of it that they do
They would have had to see the other things that directly contradict
The ways in which sport
The only reason you would do that
Is an order to create a false
Appearance
About what
December's really are
And the only reason
Would do that
It's because you're aware that they're really bad
And if the appearance of them being really bad is allowed to
Stand up
Republic
It's going a road
Whatever
State of the market you have whatever political power you have now with Trump
Send it
It's very clear like it unravels very quickly and
When you take
Will you take it
The second 2
Understand
This is a strategy
This isn't okay
Exist on the same program where Within
A day of this
You have a guy who admires
Anders Breivik coming on the show
To save it some American or some citizens aren't American
Work it like this is here
Is
They're not f****** around
Whenever I worried that Alex would take
The
The band
Social media
Dream about it
What is things that I was
Looking at was like
You might just start end up saying the n-word and
Like really good old fart with it
You know what guys I've been around for a long time
Or something like that
It Was Naive of me possibly to expect
That kind of
Is
This is exactly that but slightly different version of it
Then I expected
To find this show is inexcusable
And its presence
Anybody who works there should be
Deeply f******
Themselves
They have to be aware of what they're doing
To get this out this out of our mouths
Stout
Alex's new shirt
I swear to God
I swear to God a bird of this place outfits
Okay
Recently Alex put out a Betsy Ross
Just caught these colors don't run
I'm kind of
They owned so hard we just got still burn a little bit
Shirt
There we go
In this clip
Alex is simultaneously saying that he stole this shirt
From somebody
But he came up with it himself
What
I said work just fell out of the
Betsy Ross
American flag shirt
I said I want to be an American flag
Classic American
With katzenstein superimposed
America's back infowars.com
Infowars.com
Chris Pratt
Criticized for t-shirt choice
Which
Don't tread on me
Under the black
We'd already come
By the way
Iraq flag
American flag
Inspired by the triggering of leftists
The shirt worn by
Chris Pratt
Is it inspired by the left getting mad Chris Pratt's shirt or did you come up with it mysteriously before
It happens to be the exact same shirt
Which is it because Alex
From your own words you have a habit of stealing things
From people
You stole Hillary for Prison from a bumper sticker you saw
You have a habit of stealing people's intellectual property
Whatever I hear you say like
Oh yeah I read this article about how crisp
Everyone's mad at his shirt with the snake on it with the American flag
I know I've already come up with that yeah we're going to sell this inspired by the left getting there
I hear that and I think
You stole this shirt
Did you create the fake backstory
Anyone already exist
You can't just then make the same shirt
Still not okay
There's still you yeah
Ibuprofen is really long novel about about this whale
And then the other day I was just reading these books and I saw that somebody wrote a review of Moby Dick
That is a really good idea and so I'm selling my new novel Moby Dick
If you would like it
Inspired
4000 of those
Has Chris Pratt
Please feel free to send them this clip and Sue Alex
On the fence
In property law
So
Not too far back we heard a clip of Alex
Alleging that the Nazis at Charlotte
The white nationalist
We're all gay
Who had been employed
Find
Narrative went by the wayside
Alex is back on his phone
This includes
About Richards
Did you know that in Charlottesville
The Democratic party and other groups put out ads
What is Colton Washington
Nazis
Khaki pants white button-up shirt
Tiki torches
Democratic Party
Within two years of the becoming
Nazi
And most of them were simply art Department degrees
I mainly game in
And then I had there
America
Richard Spencer
Is a total fake
The Nazi leader
Where's outfits biking from 1938 Germany
A giant
Cedar
I have the ads
Recruited Charlottesville activist for $25 an hour
If you were like someone who admire the knots
Germany 19
Seems like that
So we've heard Alex go down this road before making a bunch of bulshit up but have a good night the right rally in Charlottesville is full of actors
It's one of his many attempts
Make sure is
Doesn't think there were real white supremacist real white nationalist
For some mysterious reason
Incredibly threatening
The same thing with the
But you can't allow the image of reality to penetrate because if you do
Run the risk of your audience being like yeah I don't like coming is a m but they're f****** Nazis out there
We still don't like Nazis
Azerbaijan
Also like
He knows enough to know that there is it
Considerable faction
Did were they to think that they were
In League with
Supporting
Legitimate white supremacist right they would not be on board with
It would be a much tougher sell for him
Giselle Vasquez
Austin flag shirt to people who were aware that he's holding water for
Defending
Like Lizzy
Jet racing
Right I think I wouldn't be surprised
Treating this like white
Supremacist p***
You know like
They're getting off on this but they would not actually want a white
Supremacist
I don't know
There are a number of people who have
To think
Isn't
Supporting
I know racism
Supremacy
Aspiring.
And were they to realize that
It would threaten
Their contribution
Into his Marketplace
I think he knows that
He knows better
To allow that perception
Which is pretty accurate that's almost
So in order to
To get around
Like he had Jason counselor the rally organizer on his show and directly accused
Fake documents contract
Which put into writing their plans to start race riots
Which connects
And of course
He has the argument that the Nazis really just Casey tour students
How come you just dismiss this is stupid bullshitted
The Democrats used to recruit these ha so I thought
I wouldn't be doing my job if I didn't at least review his evidence
And man am I glad I did
2nd August 2017
Began reporting on the ACT
Has been used in Charlottesville
Specific CEUs is here
On his July 7th
Episode down to the $25 an hour figure
His reported was based on a post on zerohedge
Problems
The jump out of me
The first of this is based on a Craigslist ad
Just about anything on Craigslist
My job to an apartment
Knows that it's easy for people to make fake ads on there
How would you do that I first moved to the city and was looking for work I sent out hundreds of emails Craig
Posting
And looking back I'm not sure any of them were real
If you're going to
Make the Nazis are a
Actors argument stronger
Obviously when he saw this ad he
We traced it back to
Did the Democratic Party
Skills
Now the bigger problem could be founded Vista
What is riposte
Is on Infowars
Website they copied
From
Zerohedge
This detail
I have no idea how to slip past both
The crack editorial Department
Zerohedge
But some Highway
The ad was posted by a company called crowds on demand an offer $25 per hour
To participate in events in the Charlotte North Carolina area
I'll be the first to admit that Charlottesville is in the Charlotte area in terms of name similarity
Geography
They are not close
Do not
Miles apart
That's a four-and-a-half hour drive
The release for ACT articles about this conspiracy on Infowars website
Most of them are just embedded videos that are gone now since their YouTube channel is gone
Try to guess that they are correct
Headlines like
Breathtaking actors prior to Charlottesville rally
No one caught that Charlotte in Charlottesville are not the same city because they don't care
They know they're lying to begin with
So it doesn't matter if they're being accurate about their life
The job is to create a narrative
To create an excuse for the Nazis violence that is deeply traumatized
It's easy to look at it
Buck up like this
And laugh and save these guys are
But it's not being dumb
What do you see something like this
Defies credulity to imagine multiple people looked at it and didn't say
Hold on that's a city in a different
That's a fingerprinted
List of credible reason
Sounds like someone might behave
This way is a pretty f******
It's not even
Creating this horrified
False narrative
Are there any kind of even if just anything could have made their own
Scribbled out the date
It is lazy on on that front I see what it is
Is a finger
The fact that someone would accept this level of leak b*******
In order to perpetuate their idea that these Nazis were
It means that you were defending Nazis
Absolutely
The Republican party is defective
Cuz you like nuts
Physics web Alex gets another guest on the show
Episode
Gentleman's chest
Would you believe that there is news that Alex haven't gotten to yet an hour on this f****** dumbass
Candace Owens video from almost a year ago
Somehow didn't manage
Cover news
I'm confused
He still doing is he still
I'm fixing to eat
You video that he's lying about his recent
Lying about it
All right kind of news
Ben Garrison and have a conversation about Trump
And how about those that work
That's fine
Still got to go do whatever these two.
Just imported attention-grabbing
There's an article that I scrolled passed on Infowars
I was like God dude is hilarious
You know what I didn't know that I needed that
In my life by
Restaurant
Think it might be fake B whatever push
It's one of the great things about not caring
About
Be specific tentacles of Alex's world is
Jersey
I don't give a f*** about Ben Garrison
I don't really care about his
Perspective on
Stop
I'll really
But in this
Interview he says a couple things
That I think are really
Interest
Evan this first one
I think he accidentally makes a case for a
Washington d.c. it was too late to cancel the tickets I said heck with it I'll go and
And one of the invitees so I was kind enough to invite me to the
After party at the Trump International Hotel where I stayed and it was a
The really nice experience and let me tell you Alex about I mean I saw
I thought you were going to Harrison Smith there
So they have some at the social media Summit he's people were staying at Trump's hotel when they
Came in and they had their official after-party at Trump's hotel
This is a pretty clear-cut case
Emoluments Clause action
What
How are those lawsuits
No he's break break
And yet all of these lawsuits
I don't know I don't I haven't kept
I haven't kept track of a lot of those.
Details but like people coming on Alex's show an indicator
Trump is prophet
From the president
And I just don't understand how like it can be soaked
Casual and
Not they don't
Care I just I don't
I do
I don't understand how come no court has yet has been like
Because they don't
They were found not to have to go through
Because it.
Real it's so f****** unreal
How is it that what is even the goddamn
Tution
Love it so goddamn much ignore the entirety of it
Tell me it's crazy in between that and like all this other all this other s***
I guess impeachment never
Was meant to be a thing
Why would anybody
Republican
Seriously the threat
To say anything other than
The Democrat Party
Is
Week on this sort of thing
Empty
Smell blood and attack
I don't know
They get into the 28th
Democratic
Upgrade analysis
Man
Bernie's a poop head
Elizabeth Warren
I've had a certain feeling
For a long time about what's going
As the primary
Heats up but I kind of felt like it would be
The little bit speculative of me to say
Chick-fil-A
Alex
Open that box for me
Is malfunctioning
Choose crew like why am I here why am I doing this
Because he's going
Bringing her back and
You know the guilty pleasure of hoping she does because I love her so
It'll be really fun to have a Hillary too and I had to go through that beat out cuz I like the curvature her and
I think she epitomizes that
So long time I've had a nagging
Suspicion that these
Like they really want Hillary to call
So many of them made their careers off the 20s
Election season
They know
They need names
For themselves the creative cottage industries
And now it's
Petering out a little bit
Desperately wish
Hillary was there because I like
Galvanized
Really turned things
It made them
And I don't think they have faith
They're going to be like let's say Biden or Bernie run
Elizabeth Warren
See you later
He'll be able to
How's the same boost
To their Market
Right
Gasparilla
People on the left
Think a lot of
People on the left are like
You know would be great
More sympathetic approach but I don't
Do we need to get her back again to run Hillary wants to run
Emotions around around Hillary
We were so high that they got they got to ride that
All those people
You're not going to find
The same vehemence
Lock her up
Chance
Bernie Sanders
No and it's just not going to be there
He doesn't have the same 40 Years of Hillary Clinton socialist
Alex has
Attacking Hillary
Made so many
Ambivalent to positive comments about Bernie Sanders
Buc-ee's
Birdie ideal primary stolen from in like
In the past has worked with the rampal's of the world
Alex's complimented him
Guest War
Exert isn't the same
History that Alex has with the Clinton exactly
Throw on
He's worried about it cuz always got a dumbass
An election season is kind of different to go up against a guy with pretty much a 40-year track record
Saying
Having any kind of ideological consist
We are running to bit of trouble
F****** want Hillary
Neither punch
They loved it
In the same way that they pretended America's attention
In Spanish been shortened
Understand that Trump has made this
Easy for that
And a real challenge
Trump
Going to be
No
They're going to have to work on whether or not Charlottesville is Charlotte
If they have to
Ocasio-cortez
Like the best because God is a year old video of Candace Owens
And then lying about it
Video combiner
Not putting in a lot of work
Right much better
Use accustomed
To a pretty simple
Deflection errything
Did the world
This coming election season I don't think is going to be
Especially with his diminished
To the
It's going to be much tougher for him
To command
Detention
Deflect
Think you just want
His his
Yeah I breathe
They were all of it
God can you imagine
Loud the screen from the left would be
If Hillary showed up was like I'm running
For president
You could hear it from across the
The country that
What's super interesting about this when Rodger Stone
Amazon
Because these people want to replace the hit
They want they don't want an unfamiliar new cycle to be what 2020
Is about
They don't want to
Have to build up a new villain
Cuz that's hard that's a lot of work
You got to convince people to hate people
We have to create
Some sort of a larger
Conspiracy about Folk
Probably the only reason
Hopes
Busy, so she for everybody
Joe Biden Iraq
Or at least these propaganda
Is Michelle Obama or Hillary Clinton
Because they've got that already
They have the
They have the muscle memory they have the stories already built
@simple
I really want Hillary back
But
Behave yourselves
And I think I got I think I recognized
Tough road ahead
So in his neck
Clip
Mika Brzezinski
Scarborough
The uncovered footage
Of
Jeffry Epps
Trump
Mar-A-Lago club
To push back
So what he does is what he's done since
Epstein a comeback in
And so with this club
People to who Club
And I can assure
30 years ago no big deal
Whatever
I don't really care
Any Galaxy Shooters week
On this subject
Really
Won't even dignify
Messiah
But
Alex starts talking about Joe Scarborough
The intern was found dead in his office
Oh yeah yeah it's f***** up
He's embellishing that story quite a bit and I don't I don't want to get into that either
Albert
Quick warning
This next court date is
Disturbing
A very serious level
Speculating
About Mika and Joe cell
In the middle of trying to
To deflect
From the Epstein clip that they aired
And this is so f***** up
She likes her daddy
Her daddy was a killer
I wonder what they talked about
Probably got like a tourniquet around your neck
Daddy material
What Daddy did to me
She's married
And now he's been a good servant
How old
I can't imagine
What level of f***** up you have to be to think that's an appropriate thing
Put speculate about on your show
I understand that he
You know sees Mika and Joe is Target
And they're f****** with drop with this
Speaking footage so I've got to defend them
But like
Speculating about their sex life
Way and then also speculating that
Mika was molested by her father
Is so inappropriate
It's
If anybody cared
This will get you f******
Fired
I can't Alex can only exist in this territory where no one can stop him from doing stuff
Cuz you do stuff like this on the regular
That is
Truly disgusting
That
In private
I would be
Did you find out
Somebody
Was thinking
And decided to tell me
Let alone
To go on a
Syndicated
Radio
It's still just like it's so rough
Posit
Disordered Behavior
And it's what you see this is how he
Interact
With anybody who
Thanks
Is a threat
But he allows whatever wild speculation
Borders on
I'll be because he's couching it in that stupid like I wonder if
This is this is
Have to put up with this
This sort of abuse
It's wildly inappropriate
Alex Alex
Play like all jokes
I'm out there
Your character sucks
That's that's
Your character hurts
That's
Anyway
I was about to after that I was about to turn off the episode
But I didn't
I kept on listening and Norm pattis
Just comes on
Nope weird
But Norm comes on
And it's just like
Defending Alex about it
I don't really care
Seems like more of a s*** head than he did last time
Because last time it was sitting next to Alex
Drunkenly losing it right
So he looked very saying and comparison
Situation
Hey white whatever hookah
It is appearance.
75% off 12
Fourth of July sale
Course Fourth of July sale
4th of July sale
Celebrate
For what
We going on for 3 weeks
Insane
Still at about to start
There's always a war on it
Like I just
It's one of those things is always very difficult about the present-day stuff
As we go along at the board
The ship gets
Real f*****-up the more you have to recognize
Then what we're looking at isn't the fun show
It's not like
Alex misrepresenting the news
Leeds Utah
To figure out some
Something about
He's anti-communist sources are like
It's not really interesting an intellectual level you were seeing is
Outright Sasha
Just propaganda show
Yep like this is
The transition tap
I'm every couple days or so maybe there's something
The anomaly
Now that is interesting like his
Everyone
Go to West Virginia
Opposed to what the show Mostly it
Mostly this
It's mostly
Nativist
White nationalist agitation
It's mostly misrepresenting news stories
Specific
Luckily the further that goal
Seriously
I want to apologize if anybody
Felt a comparison with durations.
Is inappropriate
I understand why someone may
I want to call myself out is being like
I recognize and I don't want to minimize
Anybody's experiences in the Holocaust at all
But specifically looking at
The technique
Little-used terms
The propaganda
Are important
And they have historical parallel
What's right
Not paying
Tension
To the real Danger
It's presented by people like Alex
Do you think these two
Techniques
If we didn't call it out
The entire point
Comparison
Is
Keep things
Like that
So if you see something like that happen
And the
Connection is not
It is
There
The parallel is there
So that is why it is
So
Important to limit
Comparison
While at the same time 2
Pointed out
Whenever it is Jermaine
Whenever it is there because
Comparison is
Thing that we should all
Very aware of
User
Use those techniques
Let's play
They're doing it for a reason
Like
Talks about
Immigrants bringing disease
Is reminisce
Sent off.
Propaganda
That is
One of the ways
They demonized
The populations that they stopped
To demonize
They did it for a reason
And Alex is doing it for a reason
And I refuse to take
Which is why
Walmart
This this sort of rhetoric
Being
And then simultaneously
Play we see
The guy that Alex
Idolizing
Hosting rallies
Is that go the way they do
Ijump
Think
You got to you got to be worried
So anyway
We will I hope on Monday
I think I'm moving on Monday
That is that is now been
Schedule
Monday I'm going to boo
But there's still a chance
We'll have time to
Recording episode
Before that
Yeah but if we edible take off Monday apologize
We will be back as soon as we can
Appreciate everyone
Support considerate thoughts
It means a lot to me and how is helpful
Getting through this
So thank you
But
Website
We also have a Twitter it's at knowledge underscore fight
And I'm at go to bed Jordan
ITunes
Square on
I think we've still got some old clips
On YouTube
Yep I we might
Have those there
Eventually baby make some more of them have you ever seen the fairy rings the mushrooms that grow in the circle we have a
You can get our episodes there if you're still listen
I have I had no idea
Something I want to do
Maybe I'll put the call out
I would like anybody who has
Specific
Question
Not about like trivial matter
What about Alex Jones
This world
If you have specific Direct
Questions
You would like answered
Please send them
Please send them to our email.
Cuz I would be curious to know if there is
Some question
That
I am able to answer that people don't feel is
I am very difficult time and knowing is that is
And if so I would like to be able to provide that answer
So if you have
Questions gmail.com
Please feel free to
So
I would say
And I'm no expert
Canary Theatre students
Who are hired
Didn't kill anybody because they are imaginary
Fictitious
However
Is Alex Jones
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work